It's adapted from the online April Day's novel, Network 19, 9. The male lead wants to kill me.
I used to watch lanterns with Mr. Wen.
Aren't you used to Wen Ruyu having a princess?
It's an honor to have you by my side this year.
Maybe I can meet them again.
Let's go. The Crown Prince is over there.
Let's go over there.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Calm down.
Hurry up.
It's not the time.
Let go of me.
Hold me tight.
This is the riddle stall I told you about.
What are you doing?
Young Master.
This...
Looks like they are lovers.
Today's lantern riddle...
Let's go.
Forget it.
Go away.
What are you doing?
Be careful.
Laya!
It's dangerous!
Run!
Laya!
Doctor.
How is he?
Doctor, how is it?
I've checked
I’ve checked it carefully.
but I'm not sure which poison it is.
If we delay it for a while,
I'm afraid...
if I look at someone before I die,
I'll go back to the first time I saw him.
Then...
Doctor.
Wait for me.
Okay.
Rest early.
Doctor,
If someone tries the poison in person,
can you confirm the poison on the arrow?
Of course.
But life is at stake.
Who would like to give it a try?
Mr. Wen, what are you doing?
Please cure me.
Mr. Wen.
The detoxification needs to be punctured into the vital acupoints in your body one by one.
You are...
You'll die for sure.
Do as I say.
Mr. Wen, I see.
It's the meteor powder.
Write it to me.
Thank you.
Doctor.
What happened?
My wife was poisoned by the meteor powder.
Please treat her.
Okay.
Yu'er.
What's wrong?
You look pale.
Mother.
I'm fine.
Young Master.
General Yuchi is here to see you.
Okay.
This is the corner of the sky. It's nutritious.
Take it to the princess.
Thank you, Yuchi.
How about
keep it for yourself.
The princess is poisoned.
Are you alright?
The princess was assassinated in public.
His Majesty was furious.
She's looking into it.
The princess...
Tell me if you need my protection.
Oh, right.
I've got news
Is there any news?
Yuchi, tell me.
I asked my friends in the army.
Back then, when the North arrived at Vegeta City,
there was a joke.
Our army
bribed a North General.
But I chose him because
he was injured on the battlefield.
It's said that he can't do human deeds anymore.
and no offspring.
And those who don't need to think about their children
is easier to get paid.
Wen Ruyu.
Wen Ruyu!
Run, Wen Ruyu!
Run!
Laya!
Wen Ruyu.
You're calling me so closely.
Godfather.
Let me have a look.
How can the medicine from the South
can't stop the North's blood.
Godfather.
What did I do wrong?
Please tell me.
How dare you ask me
How dare you ask me?
I think you've grown up.
You really want to be the wife of the Wen family.
Godfather.
Isn't Wen Ruyu my spy in the Southern Kingdom?
Bastard!
Who told you it was him?
Nam-kook is so cunning.
How much does he know
How much does he know?
Tell me.
He should...
only knew that I wanted to assassinate the Crown Prince.
I didn't know Godfather's existence.
He didn't arrest you
to lure me out, right?
I don't think so.
He's just worried that I'll implicate his mother.
I'm sorry, Godfather.
I will make up for my mistake.
I only give you three days.
to find out his purpose
and kill him.
Remember.
Do it properly.
Don't let anyone suspect you.
Understand?
Laya.
Don't blame me for being angry.
I've met the South agent.
He will create an opportunity for you.
If you can't kill the Crown Prince,
you will never be able to atone for your parents.
No.
Eunuch.