adapted from online April's novel, Network 19+9 novel "The Almost-through Male Wants to Kill Me".
Mr. Wen,
Why did you steal the letter?
Do you remember?
This medicine
can make people unconscious.
I think Mr. Wen
you will tell me everything.
I'll say it once.
Get lost.
You want to kill yourself?
I'll kill you!
Let's see who dares to touch him.
Who are you?
How dare you torture my husband?
I'll kill you today.
Princess Hai.
Long time no see.
you still have such a temper.
Please accept it.
Let me take my husband back.
There's still room for this.
The princess doesn't seem to understand.
Mr. Wen stole confidential documents from the Shadow Sect. The evidence is solid.
This is a serious crime in the South.
As a princess,
I can't afford it.
If I die in the Shadow Sect,
in the Shadow Sect?
Princess, don't be impulsive.
This is related to the laws of the Southern Kingdom.
Please give me some time to think about it.
Okay.
I'll give you one joss stick.
Now,
All of you, get out!
Calm down, Your Highness.
I'll go out now.
Wen Ruyu!
Wen Ruyu, wake up!
Eunuch.
News from the palace
that Madam Wen went to the palace to plead.
and asked His Majesty to come to the Shadow Sect.
Eunuch.
Did Helan really give an incense stick to stall His Majesty?
Tell everyone to leave the Shadow Sect.
Yes.
Wait.
Pick some useless ones.
Yes.
You're awake. How are you?
Can you hold on?
What are you doing here?
Don't worry.
Her Highness has entered the palace to beg for mercy.
His Majesty will be here soon.
I will let you out
I'll let you out.
Idiot.
How do you explain that letter?
Aren't you afraid that the Crown Prince
according to the clues?
I don't care anymore.
You've done so much for me.
I only care about your life now.
Wait.
Where did the smoke come from?
Help!
There's someone here.
Someone!
Hurry!
Follow me.
Here's the water.
Eunuch.
If they were burned to death inside,
will His Majesty blame us?
The Shadow Sect caught fire in an accident.
We couldn't save him.
His Majesty
will understand.
What are you doing?
I can't leave.
Leave now.
I can't take you out.
Hurry up.
Why should I go out alone?
Laya.
Listen to me.
I got that secret letter.
But I can't recognize the signature of it.
When they dragged me here,
I hid the letter behind the flower pot in the corridor.
You'll find it when you get out.
You want to prove that your parents are not traitors.
Go now.
It'll be too late if you're late.
I'm not leaving.
I'm not going.
I don't care.
Laya.
Wen Ruyu.
Don't try to kick me out.
In this world,
no one cares about me as much as you do.
Only you.
Only you love me.
You asked me that day
if I wanted to stay with you.
I'm willing to stay with you.
Laya, don't be afraid.
I'll take you home.