Which way are you even going?
Huh?
You're the one in my way.
Hey, didn't you just use the bathroom?
You need to lock the door.
Didn't I teach you that when you were little?
You're the one who barged in!
Don't you know manners?
What are you doing?
Don't move. You'll cut yourself.
You can't even shave properly.
What a mess.
If the hair's tough, rub it a bit more.
It's best to shave in the morning.
Hey, Bro.
Mm?
Are you familiar with the route back and forth?
It's been several days. I know it inside out.
Who's here so early?
Should be my classmate. I'm off!
Hey—
You have classmates?
Morning, Cheng Jiang!
Morning.
Huh?
Who's this?
Ah, this is my brother.
Wow! Your brother's so handsome!
Um... You are?
Hi, I'm Coco.
Nice to meet you!
Ah, she's a classmate from our old high school back home.
She's also studying at the language school.
Alright, we're gonna be late.
We're heading out!
Bye!
Bye.
Hey!
You—
Get out.
Let me soak for a bit.
I don't wanna talk to you.
You actually came back, huh?
Whoa, what's with you?
Where's this random anger coming from?
I'm not angry.
You're even stealing Mom's wine?
Hahaha.
Mind your own business!
If you keep acting like this,
I'm squeezing in there with you!
This is so small.
There's no room for two people.
Go steam in the sauna for a bit.
Hey!
Ahh, so comfy.
Why do you keep getting angry over nothing?
Life's too short not to enjoy it!
Don't let a golden cup
sit empty under the moon!
Hey, how much longer? Hurry up!
Alright, alright, just a sec!
Come on, have a drink with your brother.
Alright, stop being mad.
Let's have a drink.
I already got it for you, right?
Mom won't even know.
Come on, that's better.
You know, this Japanese house—
it's got a bathtub
and a sauna room.
This...
we never had it this good back in China.
Well, now you've moved to Japan.
You can soak every day, steam every day.
Just don't get all swollen up.
Pour me another.
No.
Then I'll get it myself.
What's going on?
Ahhh!
Ugh, this feels amazing!
Why's your little guy getting hard?
Huh?
Hahaha!
Shut up!
Did you get hard?
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Okay, okay, I won't say it anymore.
Fine.
Ha!
I really can't hold it in!
Ugh.
Alright, fine.
Okay, okay.
I won't say it, I won't say it.
An electronic pet
for 10 years.
That's crazy.
Move over.
Ugh.
Paper books are still the best.
Can you go read in your own room?
Why do you have to be here?
These are all in Japanese.
Hey, find me one I can actually read.
How is it?
I raised my little chick pretty well, right?
Oh yeah.
I forgot to tell you something when we were in the bath.
Stop. Can you not mention the bath thing?
Okay, okay, I won't mention it.
Coco said you're really cute.
She said girls must really like you.
Hey, she wants to introduce you to her sister.
She told me to ask you
if you have a girlfriend.
Have you even memorized the hiragana yet?
All you ever talk about is girls, girls, girls.
Isn't that annoying?
Hey.
What's this?
Give it back!
So you like reading this kind of manga?
Hahaha!
Why are you embarrassed?
Ah?
It's just a manga.
Did you learn this from the book?
If there's anything else you don't know,
just ask me directly.
Sleep.