♪The photos I look at before I sleep♪
♪Become the faces I see in my dream♪
♪With a constant yearning to see you again♪
♪I blundered through time in a daze♪
♪Let's reminisce about our past♪
♪Come back to me♪
♪Let's go back in time. A long, long time ago♪
♪I only wish my wildest dream comes true♪
♪Let's go back to the beginning of everything♪
♪We can't replace all those yesterdays
that we've lost♪
♪It's more like an adventure♪
♪We look forward to staying the same for eternity♪
♪Let's reminisce about our past♪
♪Come back to me♪
♪Try to fill our hearts to the brim♪
♪Till all that is left is a word of farewell♪
♪Time moves like my train of thought♪
♪It wafts into the distance
along the rays of light♪
♪With your gifts♪
♪Traveling back in time♪
♪Our encounter is fated♪
♪I see you again when I turn back time♪
♪I wish to always stay by your side♪
♪If I can go back in time♪
♪And see you again♪
♪I'll smile as I say to you♪
♪It has been a while♪
♪I wonder if you're calling out to me internally♪
♪Or if you believe that love♪
♪Can transcend everything♪
[Parallel Love]
[Episode 21]
Jiao Yang.
Where are we now?
What's wrong?
I couldn't see clearly just now.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Maybe I was just blindfolded for too long.
Is this a gallery?
What did you bring me to the gallery for?
Come.
This design exhibition
was designed by my mother.
I came here often when I was young.
I don't simply bring anyone to here.
However, you're different.
That's why I brought you here to see it.
How's it?
This painting...
My mum drew it.
Who is it in the painting?
The right one is my dad,
while the left one is my mum.
My mum
had a lot of fantastic ideas.
Meanwhile, my dad
always helped her realize her ideas.
He realized them
by turning them into real buildings.
I didn't know that Chairman and his wife
were so romantic.
I think that the message of
of our chairman's wife is
not to let go of your lover's hand
no matter what.
How romantic.
Lin Miao.
You told me that I'd complete your home.
Actually, you feel lonely sometimes.
You'll miss
your future home too, right?
I don't want to let you go.
I don't know
how the world will be like after ten years.
Jiao Yang.
I've spent effort in making this surprise for you.
You must appreciate it.
So, Miss Lin,
are you willing to spend your life with me?
Thank you for everything.
I got no choice,
being in loving with a hard-hearted woman,
By the time she acts,
I guess
it would be the end of the world,
where flowers would die
and the sea would be dried.
Then...
No. No.
You spent so much effort
in making surprises for me.
So give me a chance
to make one for you too.
No need. Being simple is the best.
It's better to keep things simple.
No. No.
It's better to make it grand.
It'll be sincerer.
Let's go.
Didn't we agree to walk together
toward the future world?
We've done exploring the future.
We shall return to the real world and fight.
Let's go.
What fight?
I don't know it either.
Fight.
Does it have the one you want?
Come on.
You still think that lipstick will work?
Look at Ding Ding!
Something has happened.
Yes. Something must happen.
What has happened to him these days?
Keep smiling at the computer.
Impossible, right?
The truth is in front of us.
On my count!
Three, two, one. Go!
What are you doing?
Tell us!
When did you realize the
relationship between
President Jiao and Assistant Lin?
No idea.
Tell us.
I really don't know.
Hey, Assistant Lin.
I've informed the hotel.
The rooftop and dining hall of Leisure Hotel
have been reserved
to ensure the inauguration of President Jiao
will be perfect.
Alright, I'll go back after sending the documents.
I am wondering how she's doing
alone there.
You're right.
It's more comfortable
to wear flat shoes sometimes.
Dropping our ego and stubbornness
will give us better scenery.
Don't be sad, little kid.
Let me help you.
The castle can be easily rebuilt.
Please, Chairman Zhao.
Su. You aren't here
for a cup of tea, right?
You're well known for
your steadiness, Chairman Zhao.
I want to know
why you looked so surprised
when you saw me at Zhong Lun.
Su,
Although you aren't a member of Jiao's family,
you and the chairman are somehow more alike
than Jiao Yang.
If the chairman's wife was here,
she wouldn't like to see
the current situation
between you and the Jiao family.
She really missed you.
Missed me?
Yes.
Before she passed away,
she kept mumbling about your compensation.
Compensation?
Just sent me to Hong Yu
and put me in an awkward position,
asked me to serve Jiao Yang
forever, right?
How could you describe your mum like that?
Her compensation
wasn't this.
Then, what was it?
It's a good cup of tea.
However, we hold different opinions.
That's what I could say.
Good luck.
Cheng Jun.
Can you
call me mum?
Cheng Jun.
Cheng Jun. I'll compensate you.
Sorry. Sorry.
[Zhong Lun Law Firm]
[Cai Jia Rui]
Zhong Lun Law Firm.
Ding Ding.
You edited the photos?
It's just my hobby. Just a hobby.
I didn't know that you have such a hobby.
Keep the secret, Jiang Rou.
Don't ever tell anyone.
No way.
I'm short of cash this month, sister.
-Don't blackmail me.
-Hello.
Hey, President Jiao!
I have something to tell you!
No, no, no!
I'll treat you lunch for a week.
Deal.
President Jiao. You've been
holding my hand for some time.
People will know it.
Who cares?
I don't mind announcing it.
Assistant Lin. The glass
is not clean.
Get someone to clean it.
Sure, no problem.
Almost get caught.
Luckily. Luckily.
They almost knew that we caught them.
-Luckily, we are smart.
Let's go.
What about we go separately?
Why?
Look at your hand.
It's like being glued.
Let's go separately.
Sure.
I go first.
Help me, Assistant Lin.
What's this?
Jiao Yang's birthday?
Yes. It's not today
but the day after tomorrow.
These presents were given
by the other companies.
Better early than late, right?
The day after tomorrow. That...
That means one day
before the president's inauguration?
Yes.
Have you prepared anything, Assistant Lin?
Just a birthday.
What should I prepare?
Birthday is celebrated every year.
Just buy a cake.
What do you mean by birthday only?
We have not more than 100 birthdays in our life.
The number of birthdays reduces from year to year.
What day do you want,
if it is not an important day?
Be careful.
[Little silly]
I've told you,
don't call me when I'm working.
I'm going to hang up.
Alright. Anything?
I have something to ask you.
Ask me? Seriously?
Don't feel too good.
I ask you.
What present shall I give to a man
on an important day?
Such as he gets a promotion
or increment in salary,
or...
Your boyfriend's birthday?
How did you know that?
Seriously?
You don't know what present to give?
Teach me, please.
Let me think.
Jiao Yang was raised in a rich family.
He lacks nothing.
You can think
of something
he wants very much.
Something he wants?
Thank you for everything.
I got no choice,
being in love with a hard-hearted woman.
By the time she acts,
I guess
it would be the end of the world,
where flowers would die
and the sea would be dried.
I got it.
Thank you, Jun.
You help me all the time.
Ice cream for one month, okay?
No problem.
Great.
I'm going to hang up.
How's it, Assistant Lin?
Have you got it?
I got it.
You know what birthday
present to give to President Jiao?
I meant the president's inauguration.
I'll delegate the tasks now.
Jiang Rou, you'll be in charge of the decoration.
Ding Ding, you'll contact the media.
Okay.
Ying Jun, you'll be in charge of the security.
In short,
the president's inauguration in three days
must be perfectly done.
It'll be perfect!
The mission will surely be completed.
What about you, Assistant Lin?
I... I...
I have something more important to do.
[Zhong Lun Law Firm]
Lawyer Gu.
Why are you here, Director Su?
I don't think that we have an appointment today.
You're right.
I'm here for my personal matter today.
May I know
if your firm has a lawyer named Cai Jia Rui?
Why do you want to know about Lawyer Cai?
A few years ago, my mother appointed Lawyer Cai
to handle something.
Your mother is...
Liang Yu Jun.
Sorry, Director Su,
Lawyer Cai Jia Rui
was in Zhong Lun before.
He was my mentor.
However, my mentor had
passed away a few years ago.
You might be disappointed today, Director Su.
Passed away?
I'm sorry.
I'm flying in one and a half hours.
I'm quite busy today.
If you have any doubt,
we can discuss it after I come back.
Okay.
I'll print it if everything's okay.
Alright.
Jun.
What are you doing here?
I've signed a
long-term collaboration contract
with Zhong Lun on behalf of the company.
I didn't know that you're doing an internship here.
I purposely
asked your boss to allow you
to follow up the project of Zhong Qing.
You will pass your internship.
We've broken up, Su Cheng Jun.
Please stay away from my life
and my work, okay?
I don't care about the project of Zhong Qing.
I'm not going to follow up with it.
I don't mind if I fail the internship.
Jun, we've been together for four years.
There were a lot of misunderstandings,
but we broke up peacefully.
I just wish to take care of you,
and your life to be better.
Stop it.
I tell you.
I won't be involved in the project of Zhong Qing.
If you've let me go,
you wouldn't be so afraid
to work with me.
I think that you haven't changed.
You're still the same.
I can clearly separate
my professional and private life.
I'll meet you
to discuss the work tomorrow.
This is the more important thing?
The pool needs to be decorated
for the president's inauguration?
Need candles and balloons?
It needs to be so mysterious?
It must be something.
I didn't know that
Assistant Lin didn't say what she meant.
This is obviously
a birthday surprise for President Jiao.
How dare she hide it from us!
Seriously.
She did it because it's a surprise, right?
Why don't we give Assistant Lin a surprise too?
Good idea.
Assistant Lin decorated the rooftop wedding
so well.
Why can't she do the same
here?
It's too ugly!
I agree.
Do they know about love?
It's not romantic at all.
That's why
we're here.
Why don't we help them?
Let's do it.
Why are you still awake?
Are you doing something without my consent?
I'm preparing for the inauguration tomorrow.
Please rest early.
I'm going to sleep.
Wait.
You haven't given me an answer.
What's that?
Your lifetime employment contract.
Sign it.
I don't want to.
Why?
It should be made based on a mutual agreement.
Boss Jiao.
We've become like this.
What else can you choose?
What's that?
What have we become?
Explain it.
It's...
like that.
This is you. This is me.
We knew each other.
Then, like this, like this, like this.
Isn't it obvious?
So, did you purposely do it?
Don't fall into the trap.
Give it to me.
I got the contract.
I feel your sincerity too.
However, regarding the time to sign it,
I'll consider it again.
Good night.
Is it a sign
of the end of three months?
Why are you so late?
I was busy in the morning.
I'm available at night only.
Come in.
This one.
These are all
Zhong Qing's projects we handled.
Everything's here. What do you want?
Award.
Bring me paper and a pen, Jun.
I want to record something.
How can I?
I
can't leave you alone in the room.
I can't afford it
if there's anything missing here.
The room is equipped with a CCTV, right?
I couldn't escape
if I did anything.
Jun.
If you can't even
give your client a piece of paper,
I think I should reconsider it.
Okay, okay, okay. I'll take them now.
[Power of Attorney]
[Appointer: Liang Yu Jun]
The will is invalid
if the person has not passed away.
Paper and pen.
I don't need them anymore.
It's late now.
I'll come again next time.
Are you fooling me?
It's for your own good, Jun.
It's not good
if your colleague saw you
being with a man in a room at night.
I...
Crazy man.
Thank you, Jun.
From the report,
there's no explanation for your condition.
However, it's strange.
Your organs
are aging.
In our body,
the bones and cells regenerate.
When we get older,
the regeneration rate will slow down.
Aging is inevitable.
But your organs
are aging at an accelerated rate.
Welcome to the year 2010.
You'll be given three months
to assist Jiao Yang
to be the president of Hong Yu Group,
so that you can return to the year 2020.
Or else, you'll disappear forever.
[Leisure Hotel]
Lin Miao.
Are you willing to be with me
in protecting Hong Yu?
I told you that I'm going to give you a house.
I've talked to President Liu.
Unit 001 of Infinite Home won't be sold to anyone.
It belongs to Miss Lin Miao only.
It's the surprise I prepared for you.
Don't be picky.
So, Miss Lin,
are you willing to spend your life with me?
The venue has been decorated, Assistant Lin.
We're waiting for your final check.
Alright, got it.
I'm going now.
Jiao Yang. I won't be absent
from your important moment.
[Leisure Hotel]
Assistant Lin.
Do you need to check it again?
It's the inauguration of President Jiao.
It must be perfect.
The venue has no problem.
You go back first.
What about you?
I'm finalizing everything again.
There's something very important,
but you haven't checked it yet.
Is there any other venue?
Why don't I know?
Follow me.
Hurry up. Hurry up.
You'll know it later.
Did you get it wrong? No, right?
Lin Miao.
Is that you, Lin Miao?
Give me a response.
Jiao Yang.
No. What are you doing?
I asked you all to organize a feast.
You all blindfolded me.
What's so mysterious?
A feast?
♪Reluctant to miss the moment
when we passed by each other♪
♪I stand at the corner of the street♪
♪Looking at your back, I think quietly♪
♪You asked me to stay♪
♪As rain falls, I can't hear you anymore♪
♪I only remember you said it♪
♪After the rain, let's fall in love♪
What's this?
What's going on?
I...
It's our present for the
golden couple in the president's office.
Wish you two an unforgettable night.
Assistant Lin. I don't know
what you're afraid of.
Since you've prepared a surprise,
don't forget to give it to him.
Don't disappoint yourself
and us.
Yes, it's been decorated for a long time.
Why should it be wasted?
Lin Miao.
This is the feast you organized for me?
It was organized by everyone.
However, it's not a feast.
It's your birthday celebration.
Happy birthday to you.
Jiao Yang.
Happy birthday.
Congratulations.
You're one year older now.
Thank you.
It's really
the best birthday present.
It's not a present.
What's this?
[Hong Yu Group.
Lifetime Employment Contract, Lin Miao.]
Mr. Jiao Yang.
Congratulations for
passing your probation period.
[Agreement]
I've decided
to accept your lifetime employment offer
♪The breeze hasn't seemed to go far♪
and be your personal assistant forever.
♪The same old place never changed♪
Nice to meet you.
♪For whom the pupils are open♪
I entrust the rest of my life to you.
♪Scenes of the past that I want to get back♪
♪You said hugs are hard to forget♪
♪The leaves slowly drifting away♪
Thank you for the surprise.
♪But how could I turn back to pick it up♪
The road ahead is long.
♪Wishes shining in the sky♪
♪The fragments of Eternity♪
I want to be with you all the time.
♪I'm sure I'll smile and stop you♪
♪From saying goodbye with tears♪
♪Let this beginning of the encounter♪
♪Every scene of you and me♪
♪Time counting down, from broken to whole♪
♪Let this beginning of the encounter♪
Jiao Yang, I just want to
spend my remaining time with you
no matter what.
♪The future is in sight♪
President Jiao.
Everything's ready, President Jiao.
Please pick a nice necktie now.
This is fine.
It's your big day, President Jiao.
Isn't it too simple?
Why don't you pick this?
Jiang Rou.
President Jiao is the
president of Hong Yu Group now.
It's better to be low profile.
It matches his title.
Take this one.
Help me put it on.
I hope that you won't
ruin everything today, Assistant Lin.
I hope that you can act
based on the situation as you did last time.
Cope with it.
What are they talking about?
I don't understand it at all.
Me neither.
It's enough as long as they understand it.
I know everything.
Everyone.
How do I look today?
Handsome!
Great!
After the inauguration,
let's celebrate at the dining hall of Leisure Hotel.
Thank you, President Jiao!
Let's go!
[Case Cover]
I'm here to visit you again.
To appreciate you,
to be exact.
[Liang Yu Jun's grave]
Do you remember this?
I didn't know what you said in the hospital
was real.
Cheng Jun. I'll compensate you.
Thank you
for treating me as your son.
Thank you for everything.
Do you think that I'll say that?
Compensation?
Do you think
it's enough to compensate me for the abandon
and the bully of
Jiao Jun Hong in the past?
That fellow got a huge gambling debt.
What were you doing
when I went to ask for help from you?
You only cared about your designs
and Jiao Yang!
Did you care about me?
Do you know about
my life
after I returned from Yue Rong Villa?
I'd have been beaten up
if my neighbor didn't call the police.
I wouldn't have a chance standing here
to appreciate your compensation.
I don't know why
you would leave something for me.
Anyway, thank you
for hurting me
before your life came to an end.
I'll show you
how I'm going
to destroy the things
you appreciated the most.
Within three months,
he has got promoted from a vice president
to the president of Hong Yu Group officially.
Stay focused.
There might be breaking news today.
Welcome, Chairman Cao.
If I didn't come,
people would think that
I was looking down on President Jiao.
Glad to see you.
It's the big day of Hong Yu.
We are a family no matter what.
Hong Yu will better
if we work hard together.
You're so careful, Chairman Zhao.
What should I say about you?
Alright, please be seated.
Dear colleagues and news media,
welcome to the
president's inauguration of Mr. Jiao Yang.
Let's give a big round of applause for
the president of Hong Yu Group,
Mr. Jiao Yang!
Thank you for coming, everyone.
Wait.
What's wrong?
No idea.
What are you doing, Su?
Excuse me, Chairman Zhao.
I'm here for Jiao Yang.
You should
give a face to your brother
no matter what.
Yes, Jiao Yang.
You're my brother.
How can a brother
be absent
from such a precious moment?
Something interesting has happened finally.
Why is he here?
Manager Su.
If you're dissatisfied with me,
we can discuss it personally.
Please behave yourself
to avoid troubles
on this occasion.
Are you threatening me?
As your brother, I feel upset.
I'm here to congratulate you
for your success.
Really?
Please do it
after my speech.
Get a seat.
Although you weren't invited,
we would still treat you as our guest.
Here, please, Manager Su.
Don't go
too far, Su Cheng Jun.
You and the Jiao family
are the one who go too far, Jiao Yang.
You all took my mum away from me.
You all even took away
the only care she left for me.
You'll disappoint her if you keep doing this.
Please leave.
Don't make a fool of yourself.
Send him off, Xin.
Security! Security!
Please, Manager Su.
I'm here
to take back what I deserve today.
This is the will
of my mother, Madam Liang Yu Jun
as the wife of the chairman of Hong Yu Group.
It's clearly written that
I'd get five per cent of
the shares of Hong Yu Group from her.
I request Hong Yu Group
to halt the president's inauguration
and give me an official response.
How can it be?
Yes.
Seriously?
How can it be?
President Jiao must be clear
with the words written on the will.
The signature belonged to our mum,
Madam Liang Yu Jun.
[Liang Yu Jun]
[Witness: Cai Jia Rui]
You can get the best handwriting expert witness
to verify it.
Trust me.
You'll be disappointed.
♪The breeze hasn't seemed to go far♪
♪The roof where I accompany you
to hide from the rain♪
♪The same old place never changed♪
♪Which page of the story
does the petal mark♪
♪For whom the pupils are open♪
♪Scenes of the past
that I want to get back♪
♪You said hugs are hard to forget♪
♪The leaves slowly drifting away♪
♪But how could I turn back
to pick it up♪
♪Wishes shining in the sky♪
♪The fragments of Eternity♪
♪I'm sure I'll smile and stop you♪
♪From saying goodbye with tears♪
♪Let this beginning of the encounter♪
♪Every scene of you and me♪
♪Time counting down,
from broken to whole♪
♪Let this beginning of the encounter♪
♪Cherish our moments of happiness♪
♪With everything I have,
telling you that♪
♪The future is in sight♪
♪Let this beginning of the encounter♪
♪Every scene of you and me♪
♪Time counting down,
from broken to whole♪
♪Let this beginning of the encounter♪
♪Cherish our moments of happiness♪
♪With everything I have,
telling you that♪
♪The future is in sight♪