♪The photos I look at before I sleep♪
♪Become the faces I see in my dream♪
♪With a constant yearning to see you again♪
♪I blundered through time in a daze♪
♪Let's reminisce about our past♪
♪Come back to me♪
♪Let's go back in time. A long, long time ago♪
♪I only wish my wildest dream comes true♪
♪Let's go back
to the beginning of everything♪
♪We can't replace all those yesterdays
that we've lost♪
♪It's more like an adventure♪
♪We look forward to staying the same for eternity♪
♪Let's reminisce about our past♪
♪Come back to me♪
♪Try to fill our hearts to the brim♪
♪Till all that is left is a word of farewell♪
♪Time moves like my train of thought♪
♪It wafts into the distance
along the rays of light♪
♪With your gifts♪
♪Traveling back in time♪
♪Our encounter is fated♪
♪I see you again when I turn back time♪
♪I wish to always stay by your side♪
♪If I can go back in time♪
♪And see you again♪
♪I'll smile as I say to you♪
♪It has been a while♪
♪I wonder if you're calling out to me internally♪
♪Or if you believe that love♪
♪Can transcend everything♪
[Parallel Love]
[Episode 11]
For the demolition of Yue Rong Villa,
the vice president of Hong Yu Group,
Jiao Yang, used force.
Bullying women, and threatening old employees.
Hong Yu Group's gangsters'development logic.
Yan, Yan, Yan.
Stop it! Stop it!
Help me out!
Lin Miao.
No, this...
What is this?
It's obviously video manipulation!
That's not the truth, right?
I knew it was fake!
It's making a buzz on the Internet right now.
This morning,
after the news of althaea
being found around Yue Rong Villa
has been exposed,
the animal and plant conservation association
and many conservation volunteers
have surrounded the company,
saying that Hong Yu is an unscrupulous developer
that uses plants and animals for profits,
and requesting the government
to stop the development of Yue Rong Villa.
That's weird.
Something's not right
about the last incident of cat hair.
How could there be a sudden spam attack?
It's the same this time.
Why is it that every time Jiao Yang
achieved something,
something goes wrong?
Could it be that someone is sabotaging?
Actually, in response to this incident,
the first thing we have to do
is to reassure the volunteers,
control the media,
stop the news from spreading,
and avoid it from getting worse.
In this way,
we can at least buy some time.
Someone's definitely playing tricks.
How could the villa's security footage
even be leaked?
Unless...
There's a mole!
There's a mole?
Could it be that people from the villa
betrayed President Jiao?
I don't think it's the people from the villa.
Think about it. If the people from the villa
are trying to harm President Jiao,
they could just disagree with the development
at the beginning.
Why even bother going through all these?
If
it's not the people from the villa...
Then the mole...
could be...
It's not me.
I know it's not you! You don't even
consider whether you can handle it!
It's Su Cheng Jun.
Manager Su!?
I remembered now.
Xin, think about it.
When we were locked up in Yue Rong's data room
when we went looking for althaea,
and
when we served the inspection team,
Manager Su never showed up.
But it was President Jiao
who asked Manager Su to remain in the villa
to organize the application form
for the protection village
and the information of althaea.
You are saying that it's Jiao Yang
who ordered him to do these?
Director Zhao,
I think before we
have any concrete evidence,
it's better not to doubt Manager Su.
Shut up.
Secretary Yan,
do you really not know,
or are you playing dumb, or have you forgotten?
Su Cheng Jun is President Jiao's half-brother.
It's only natural if he wants to usurp authority.
Jiao Yang and Su Cheng Jun? How is that possible?
How come I've never heard him mention it before?
Precisely.
Listen to what Jiang Rou said, so well-founded.
I remember when I was little,
Jiao Yang and I were at Yue Rong.
Back then, he went to see Aunt Jiao.
Things weren't very pleasant at that time.
No,
I have to tell Jiao Yang.
Diretor Zhao, calm down.
Miss Jiang Rou,
Manager Su is President Jiao's brother,
why didn't I know that?
You have only been here for a short time.
Let me tell you.
You go, you go, you go.
What's up?
Is President Jiao inside?
Assistant Lin, you are finally back.
President Jiao just came back, and looked awful.
Oh, no!
Just now, Huang from
the finance department said that
Ya from the marketing department said that
Xiao Xiao from the outreach department said that
the Board of Directors proposed that,
if President Jiao doesn't handle this issue well,
he will be suspended.
Suspended?
Why do you all gather here?
President Jiao, are you alright?
Me?
What can happen to me?
It's just suspension,
and it's not the first or second time.
This kind of thing won't put me down, right?
So do you have any plan?
Assistant Lin as a top assistant,
any bright ideas?
President Jiao,
how do you feel about a one-time donation?
[Proposal of Opinion]
In the name of Hong Yu,
make a charitable donation
to the animal and plant conservation association
and the official organization
of environmental conservation.
By doing this,
not only will it save Hong Yu's reputation,
but also show those protesters that
Hong Yu is highly passionate and determined
towards environmental protection.
You did all these?
Yes.
Alright.
Just do it as you said.
Just do it as who said?
Jiao Yang, where have you been?
I have been looking all over for you. I am worried.
Assistant Lin just made
a very good suggestion.
From now on,
everyone has to listen to
Assistant Lin's instructions.
I'm going to show those who are up to no good
what our president office is capable of.
Listen to Assistant Lin's instructions?
Then what are you doing, Jiao Yang?
I...
obviously have other things to do.
Jiang Rou, your intel is more reliable.
You and Ding Ding
will be in charge of monitoring
public opinions on the Internet.
Ying Jun, Xin,
you two will be in charge of contacting the villa,
and getting the real security footage,
so that it can be used
as evidence for future clarification.
Director Zhao,
you have a wider connection.
So the name list for the donation,
I'll leave it to you.
Manager Su, you are more experienced.
You will take charge of communicating
with the donation platform.
Alright.
As for me, before we get off work,
I will have the donation proposal
ready for everyone.
If there's no problem,
we should get a move on.
Wait.
I have some questions.
Something as big as the donation platform，
how can we leave it to an outsider?
I'm worried.
Director Zhao is right.
The platform is very vital,
I certainly can't handle it by myself.
Assistant Lin,
how about this,
Director Zhao will be in charge of the platform.
As for me, I will assist
Director Zhao.
Then let me reassign it.
So Director Zhao, you will be in charge of
communicating with the donation platform?
Manager Su,
you can help with the name list for the donation.
Alright.
This matter
is extremely important
for both President Jiao and Hong Yu.
I hope everyone can pay much attention to it.
When this is over,
I'll treat you all to a nice meal, alright?
Alright!
Keep it up!
So does she like me or not?
If she likes me,
why did she reject me?
If she doesn't,
but she's so upset about my problems.
If she likes me,
but this woman kissed me,
and still said that it was just business.
If she doesn't,
why did she look for me in the mountain with tears?
She likes me. She doesn't like me,
She likes me. She doesn't like me...
she doesn't like me.
she likes me...
Come in.
It's still 'she doesn't like me'...
President Jiao,
So this is
the other important thing you said?
Is it trendy to count leaves these days?
As the saying goes, to see a world in a wild flower
and a bodhi in a leaf.
It may seem like I'm counting leaves,
but I'm actually reading into
the philosophies of life in this big world.
Forget it. You don't know Buddhism,
you wouldn't get it.
Why don't you just tell me what's the matter?
The board of directors responded,
saying that they will not
fund our donation campaign.
Also, within such a short time,
to raise such a huge amount of money
is a bit difficult.
So...
That's it?
I thought it was a bigger deal.
Don't worry.
Money is never a problem.
I'll take care of it.
Cheng Jun,
you've been in Hong Yu for a long time.
You are indeed a very talented man.
Compared with your peers,
you are more down-to-earth
and you have more of a sense of calmness.
You have the potential to become a leader.
Thank you.
But having potential
doesn't mean that you can become
a true leader.
What kind of person you are,
I see it very clearly.
When Jiao Yang and Lin Miao
were planning the rooftop wedding,
you knew there was a clash of venues,
Instead of informing Jiao Yang in advance,
you went behind his back
and contacted another hotel.
You were trying to take advantage
of the situation, weren't you?
Making Jiao Yang take the initiative to request me
to allow you to go to the villa,
was also what you had planned for a long time.
And this time,
Lin Miao came to me
with the rebuilding plan for the villa.
Although I was pressured by the board to agree,
I never would have guessed that
Yue Rong Villa was your mother's legacy,
but you're the one who proposed
to tear it down and rebuild it.
Can you live up to your mother's hard work?
I didn't do anything unjust to my mother.
Alright.
Since we are mentioning your mother,
for her sake,
I can drop the whole thing,
but you have to leave Hong Yu!
If not,
I'll get to the bottom of all these.
I heard that President Jiao and the others
wanted to restore Hong Yu's reputation
by donating to charity.
What if,
it was like the last time,
they can resolve the issue...
So what if they do?
Jiao Yang is too naive.
He only knows how to rob Peter to pay Paul.
filling in one hole after another.
He thought that by calming the public's opinion,
the board would spare him.
Childish!
Beloved.
From now on, you have to maintain it properly.
Don't ever scratch it,
bump it or dent it.
Maybe I'll be able to reconnect with it someday.
Don't worry. I'll take good care of my car.
I've been discussing it with you for so long,
and you don't even let me touch it.
Why are you willing to let go this time?
That's none of your business!
Hurry up and pay before I regret it.
Alright.
But with the car sold,
how will you get to or off work?
Why are you being such a nuisance?
How much is that?
You're home.
Why are you dressed like that?
Mo...You rode a motorcycle?
It's quite nice riding a motorcycle!
Not boring, not stuck in traffic,
cooler and more stylish.
You didn't sell your car, did you?
How did you know?
You really sold your car?
It's just a car. It doesn't matter if I sold it.
Besides, this is the first time Assistant Lin
has asked me for help because of work.
how can I just stand there and do nothing?
But that was
your 24-year-old birthday present.
How could you...
Out with the old, in with the new!
Besides, I'm tired of driving that crappy car.
Look at me now,
dressing this outfit,
and riding a motorcycle.
I think it's quite nice.
Have you fallen under my spell again?
At this point,
you still have the mood for jokes?
Aren't you fully in charge of the donation?
But that's indeed not enough.
That is not enough?
So what's to be done?
The organization of public welfare is,
at best, a way to allay
the public's environmental concerns.
But then the focus
is on how to give the board an answer.
You know what?
The value of althaea is actually worth much more.
As far as I can verify,
there are already
research teams working on
the industrialization of artificial
cultivation of althaea.
If we can get ahead of the curve,
we can carve out a large
portion of the market in the future.
Exactly.
With this,
not only will it solve
the earnings problem of Yue Rong,
but also stop the board's blabbering mouth.
Once we realize artificial cultivation,
the world will be amazed by the beauty of althaea.
Daddy,
does althaea really exist?
Jun,
althaea is the most beautiful flower in the world.
One day, daddy will find it
and let the world be awed by its beauty.
Althaea is not only an ornamental plant,
but its usage is also actually very versatile.
Jiao Yang, do you know
the usage of althaea is very versatile?
Now the hard-to-find althaea
can not only be artificially cultivated,
but in the future, it can also be worth up to
tens of thousands of yuan per shoot.
Tens of thousands of yuan per shoot?
I believe the future of althaea in the early stage
is very promising,
but isn't that price a bit much?
I'm telling you, not at all!
Althaea is not only of high ornamental value,
but it is also highly utilized
in the medical and aesthetic fields.
If we can
form it into a complete industrial chain,
the prospect of it is very promising.
How do you know so much about althaea?
Through reading!
There is a book dedicated to predicting
what the next decade holds for althaea.
Is there such a book?
Yes! Of course, there is!
President Jiao,
you should read less Chicken Soup for the Soul
and more useful books.
It's late.
I should take a shower and go to bed.
You should get some rest, too.
Tell me,
why did you reject me?
Because I'm from the future.
I'm telling you,
in our place, it's already 2020.
And I am already thirty-three years old.
Lin Miao,
are you really from the future?
How do you know so much about althaea?
There is a book dedicated to predicting
what the next decade holds for althaea.
Do you still remember
the people who attacked you online?
Those are called spammers.
It's a popular tactic in our place.
You wouldn't get it.
President Jiao.
President Jiao!
What is it?
The board approved of
our proposal for the charity donation
and said if things work out,
we're allowed to
proceed with the project of Yue Rong Villa.
But if it doesn't work out...
I'll take the blame and resign.
You don't have to worry too much.
Since the board has conceded,
that means there is still
a chance for things to turn around.
And when I came up here just now,
Assistant Lin asked me to tell you...
What did she say?
She said,
We'll be working overtime tonight
to get through this with you.
President Jiao, what's wrong with you today?
Why are you so restless this whole time?
Come,
Xin,
do you think if there is a possibility
that someone around you
is not from this world?
Then from which world?
You can go back to work.
Wait!
I have my own arrangements for donations,
you check on someone for me first.
Right now?
But later I...
Now! Go!
Assistant Lin, what brings you here?
I came to see
President Jiao's work progress.
Well,
President Jiao assigned
another work task for me,
so I'm not quite sure.
Another work task?
What task is that?
Is it about the althaea project?
He's about to be suspended,
but he still has time to work on other stuff,
What is he thinking?
President Jiao,
this is the donation proposal
perfected by Assistant Lin.
Alright.
I will go through it now.
Also, the thing that
you instructed me to investigate,
by tonight,
I will compile all the information gathered
and give it to you.
Thanks for the hard work.
President Jiao,
Assistant Lin also asked me to tell you that
you shouldn't stay up too late.
Only three days left,
I have no idea what he has been up to.
Cheapskate!
I'm drinking it anyway.
[Jiao Yang]
[Jun calling]
[List of alternative donation platforms]
[Chairman Li]
Don't worry, it's all taken care of.
Thanks for your hard work.
President Jiao, you're still here?
I was just about to leave
and I saw your light was still on.
Thanks for your hard work.
[Headquarter Base of Hong Yu Group, Dong Hai City]
Jun Jun!
Jun, what brings you here?
I called you so many times
and you didn't pick up,
so I wanted to look for you at the office,
but you did say that
you didn't like me going there,
so I've been here waiting for you.
I've been waiting since afternoon,
but I never thought it would rain
while I was waiting,
so I went to buy an umbrella for you.
Good thing I waited for you,
otherwise, you'd have to go home in the rain,
right?
I'm fine.
By the way,
I made a lot of your favorite food.
Spare ribs, potatoes,
braised baby back ribs,
salt and pepper baby back ribs,
goji berry spare ribs soup,
-butter baked potatoes...
-All right, all right!
Do you want to come over
to my place for dinner together?
Okay.
But Jun,
You'd better not come to the office to see me.
Is there something
you've been hiding from me lately?
Why would I?
I've just been busy lately.
Then you have to promise me that
you won't reject my calls,
my texts,
or my QQ messages in the future.
Alright, got it.
Let's go.
Is that your colleague?
Should I buy an umbrella for him?
No need, his assistant is picking him up.
It seems that today is destined
to continue working overtime.
A girlfriend is way more reliable.
A female assistant or what
should get a pay cut.
Is that so, President Jiao?
What are you doing here?
I was just afraid you'd cut my salary,
so I rushed over to suck up to you.
Fine,
let's go.
-Let's go!
-Go!
Lin Miao!
have you noticed a pattern?
What's that?
Two people with two umbrellas
is a very wasteful thing to do.
I think it's only a waste
if two people have two umbrellas
but they only use one.
I'll hold it for you.
Then President Jiao will have to
hold the umbrella for a good while
before his little assistant,
me, can get home.
Hold the umbrella for a good lifetime?
Are your ears deaf?
You managed to hear a good while
into a good lifetime.
A lifetime?
President Jiao,
I'm your assistant.
It's my duty to bring you an umbrella.
Please stop saying these obscure statements.
By the way,
Xin said you even assigned him a task.
There are only two days and two hours left
until the deadline set by the board.
At this hour,
how can there be time for other arrangements?
It's only because there are some obscure people
who love to talk about some obscure principles
and waste the clear intentions of others.
Now,
you're saying some obscure statements.
No matter how obscure I am,
I'm not as obscure as you are!
Do you want to share an umbrella with me?
No, I don't. Haven't I brought an umbrella for you?
Alright.
I'm telling you, Lin Miao,
from now on, unless I say so,
you're not allowed to court me.
President Jiao,
your suit is haute couture and it can't get wet.
You're to blame if it's ruined!
I...
Is there such a thing as a life?
[Please respect yourself!]
Cheapskate!
[Lin Miao]
Cheng Jun,
I made a sandwich.
Want to have a bite?
I'm not eating.
There's something important
at the company today.
I...
Why don't I pack one for you?
You can have it at the office.
It's okay, I'm running late, I'm heading out now.
No, you can bring it with you and...
eat it after work.
Report, President Jiao!
The controversy on the Internet
is all under control!
Report, President Jiao!
The unedited video has arrived!
The donors that Director Zhao
contacted the past two days
are also willing to help!
Well done.
Now we just need to screen the donation platform
and we're considered
ahead of schedule in finishing our work.
President Jiao, on the choice of platform,
I think I need help from Assistant Lin.
You need Lin Miao?
Didn't you say yesterday that
the screening of the platform
was almost complete?
It's that Director Zhao
is not satisfied with
the detail of the information
I've provided so far.
She said to have Assistant Lin and me
collaborate to get this done.
Fine, then I'll give you...
two hours.
Within two hours,
make sure all the tasks are completed.
Alright, President Jiao. Thank you.
If there's nothing else, you can go ahead.
Alright, President Jiao.
[Lin Wei Jun's data]
President Jiao,
here's the information on
the person you asked me to investigate.
Lin Wei Jun, twenty-three years old,
an orphan.
She grew up in a welfare house
after the death of her parents.
Close with a granny named Chen Rui Fang there.
She's so miserable.
Her biography, education,
place of origin, and other information
are all compiled here.
Because of the short time,
so...
there are only these two photos from the orphanage.
That's the last copy of the investigation.
Xin,
tell me,
for you,
what do you think about
this parallel time and time traveling?
I know the question is quite tripping.
I mean what if.
What if
someone around you
might not be from this world,
how do you feel about that?
After sampling a large number of
movies and TV shows,
time traveling usually intends
to spark an earth-shattering romance.
You see, President Jiao,
in the year 2003,
the TV drams Love Across Time,
told the story of a heroine
who traveled to the Ming Dynasty
which resulted in an amazing love affair
with Zhu Yun Wen, the eldest grandson of
the emperor at that time.
Right, right, right!
And in the year 2001, TVB's
A Step into the Past was again the story of
Xiang Shao Long, played by Koo Tin Lok,
who had an emotional entanglement
with Kwok Sin Nei.
So to sum up,
a female protagonist
has one in ten million probability
to travel to another time and space,
but the probability to have a love story
with a male at that time,
is a hundred percent.
Is President Jiao in some kind of shock?
Where's Lin Miao?
President Jiao,
didn't you assign her
to Manager Su this morning?
That's fine too.
After the donation campaign is over,
I'll show you
what a hundred percent love is.
What are you talking about, President Jiao?
Nothing.
[List of Donation platforms]
[Su Cheng Jun]
The statistical analysis
done by these five platforms
has nothing wrong.
Which part of is Director Zhao not satisfied with?
She's probably just not satisfied with me.
Actually, the incident at the villa,
was just an accident.
You don't need to take it too personally.
You don't have to comfort me.
Being careful like I'm walking on eggshells.
I've already used to it.
You can just think of it as
a double-check for Director Zhao.
Having gone through you,
I'm sure she'll be more at ease.
Sure, I'll give it to her as soon as I can.
This way, she could
make the decision before work ends.
Then we will be able to
complete all the tasks ahead of schedule
by tomorrow morning.
By then, the company's misconceptions about you
will be cleared up naturally.
[Signs of boyfriend cheating on you]
[A few signs of your boyfriend cheating on you?]
Cheng Jun never likes me
to go to the company to find him.
I'm going anyway.
I've just heard an astounding piece of gossip,
it's about Manager Su.
Dad, where did you get this scanned copy?
Yue Rong Villa belongs to Hong Yu after all,
it's not difficult if I want to
check a piece of document.
Su Cheng Jun colluded with
other people behind your back,
and you, as the leader,
were wrong with your judgment of people,
and still you want to shield him now.
Dad,
I believe Manager Su.
He must have been framed.
You believe him?
Why would you believe him?
Because he's trying everything he can to help me!
Absolutely foolish!
Say whatever you want,
but you just can't fire him anyhow.
I'm telling you, Su Cheng Jun must be fired!
Manager Su signed the agreement
to demolish and rebuild the villa
with Yue Rong Villa behind the company's back?
Keep your voice down.
The worst part is that
the chairman already found out.
He was just given a lecture,
probably he would get fired.
He's going behind the company's back
and making a personal deal!
Dismissal is just a minor one!
It was said that Manager Su
came out from the chairman's office
and went to the rooftop.
He's not trying to kill himself, is he?
If he is, it's his own fault!
It's me.
The water's already murky,
it's time for me to go ashore.
Manager Su.
Assistant Lin.
I...
heard things.
Are you okay?
Maybe, there are times when
people should just accept their fate.
When President Jiao
invited me to join his team,
I was grateful.
So I did my best
just to help President Jiao
with this resort project,
but I didn't expect it to be a total botch.
With my identity,
people would inevitably suspect
that I had ulterior motives.
Manager Su,
your capabilities are apparent to everyone.
I think it just a misunderstanding this time.
When it's over,
the chairman will change his mind about you.
Really?
Really.
Assistant Lin, thank you.
Manager Su, what are you doing?
Please let go!
Just now when I was standing alone on the rooftop,
looking down below,
a lot of horrible thoughts came into my mind,
but then you showed up.
Manager Su,
things are actually not that serious.
Let go of your hands first.
Assistant Lin,
thank you for saying this to me
at this very moment.
Thank you for being willing to stay with me.
It's nothing.
President Jiao,
Assistant Lin is not with you?
Director Zhao reminded me that
I have to go back to the office tomorrow
to look at the screened list of donation platforms,
but Assistant Lin is nowhere to be seen right now.
How would I know?
Am I her assistant?
By the way, President Jiao,
this is the follow-up material
on the girl you instructed me to investigate.
I've sorted it out for you and left it on your desk.
[Lin Wei Jun's data]
Lin Wei Jun, who exactly are you?
Lin Miao,
what's your relationship with Su Cheng Jun?
Assistant Lin?
You two know each other?
Not at all.
She never said that
she knew Su Cheng Jun.
This cannot be!
Lin Miao, you have to make it clear to me today.
♪The breeze hasn't seemed to go far♪
♪The roof where I accompany you
to hide from the rain♪
♪The same old place never changed♪
♪Which page of the story
does the petal mark♪
♪For whom the pupils are open♪
♪Scenes of the past
that I want to get back♪
♪You said hugs are hard to forget♪
♪The leaves slowly drifting away♪
♪But how could I turn back
to pick it up♪
♪Wishes shining in the sky♪
♪The fragments of Eternity♪
♪I'm sure I'll smile and stop you♪
♪From saying goodbye with tears♪
♪Let this beginning of the encounter♪
♪Every scene of you and me♪
♪Time counting down,
from broken to whole♪
♪Let this beginning of the encounter♪
♪Cherish our moments of happiness♪
♪With everything I have,
telling you that♪
♪The future is in sight♪
♪Let this beginning of the encounter♪
♪Every scene of you and me♪
♪Time counting down,
from broken to whole♪
♪Let this beginning of the encounter♪
♪Cherish our moments of happiness♪
♪With everything I have,
telling you that♪
♪The future is in sight♪