[Episode 16]
Why did my father call me here in such a hurry?
Is it a recurring condition?
The chairman's condition is stable.
You're here about
the X Hotel billboard proposal, I assume.
Come in.
Secretary Chen, give us a moment.
Yes, sir.
Dad.
How long have you known X Holdings' top brass?
Not long.
When I was your age,
I was always cornered by different Omegas
on my way home from work.
Among those who chased after you
was Shao Qing's mother.
Conquest is in every Alpha's nature.
I don't think you speak for all Alphas.
After all, not everyone
enjoys cheating on their spouse.
I admit, emotionally, I failed your mother.
But I gave her a life of status and comfort.
She might've had a good life
marrying someone else.
Maybe even better.
Of course.
That man might have cheated, too.
It's just...
If she hadn't loved him like she loved you,
it wouldn't have hurt so much.
I know all the awful things Shao Qing did.
I've heard everything
I've spoken to his mother, too.
I gave her a piece of my mind.
"A piece of your mind"?
In what sense?
Teaching her step by step?
Like hiring the top criminal lawyer
in Jiang Hu?
So, her precious son could get bail quickly?
That kind of reprimand?
As for the legal fees,
I'm not paying a cent.
But you'll still cover
her living expenses, right?
Dad.
There's no need
for any of us to fool ourselves.
Even if Sheng Shao Qing wants me dead,
he's still your baby son.
He carries half your blood, after all.
So, you...
You're my child, too.
The one I value most.
My one and only heir.
The future of Sheng Fang.
You could have let Sheng Shao Qing,
Sheng Shao Qi, or Sheng Shao Lin take over.
Oh.
And also Sheng Shao Qian,
Sheng Shao Yue, and Sheng Shao Wan.
They could all take your place
if they were capable.
Being your "most valued" child is a lousy spot.
I get all the responsibility.
And they get all the affection.
Selective breeding, top-down screening.
Dad.
You're such a brilliant educator.
There is also a set of advanced concepts
even when treating your own children.
You have a style of your own.
I asked you here today
not to talk about that.
Shao You.
What are you going to do
about your relationship with Hua?
What?
That young guy from X Holdings.
He's no saint.
I don't know what you did
to attract his attention,
but since he's playing nice now,
that puts us in a better position.
I know you're really into Hua.
I'm not saying you have to break up now.
But you need to keep your head clear.
Since you've accepted
the proposal from X Holdings' heir,
you'd better keep things low-profile
with Hua for now.
When did I say yes?
So, you're going to turn him down?
That heir from X Holdings or Hua...
Shao You, don't tell me
you don't know which one to pick.
Honestly, there's no need to pick.
Sometimes,
you can have your cake and eat it, too.
So, you want me to be like you?
Be greedy and take both?
What's wrong with that?
What's so wrong about it?
What's wrong with it?
You should ask my mother.
She knows better than anyone
what it's like to live with a greedy husband.
We're talking about you now.
Stop talking about anything else.
Plus, the guy from X Holdings
is not your mom.
No, he's not.
He's not like my mom.
He didn't fall for a scumbag as a teenager,
get married, and have kids.
My mother had neither power nor background,
so she had to put up with your cheating.
What happens between Hua Yong and me
is none of your business
I'm leaving. Take care of yourself.
You...
Shao You, heard you're marrying
into a rich family as a live-in son-in-law.
So, how about handing Hua over to me?
You out of your mind? Looking to get yelled at?
All right.
Just kidding.
Tomorrow, I'm going to meet up with Yu Shan.
We're celebrating you winning UKW's heart
from X Holdings.
It's been a long time
since we've hung out together.
You better be there.
Got it.
You're going out drinking
with friends tomorrow night?
- Yeah.
- I'm coming, too.
Why?
Trying to flirt?
I'm going to make sure you don't drink.
Didn't you say your genes were super strong?
The little one's not even afraid of cyanide.
So, what's a little alcohol, right?
I'm sure you wouldn't want
for baby Peanut to start life as a boozehound.
Hello? Who is it?
Hello.
Nice to meet you, sir.
My name is Shen.
A colleague of Gao Tu.
You work with Gao Tu... Shen...
You're his boss, right?
He's mentioned you before.
So, what's this about?
Here's the thing.
I'd like to talk to Gao Tu in person
about something.
But he quit and changed his number.
I can't get in touch with him.
So, I figured I'd reach out to his family.
Do you have a way to get in touch with him?
Of course.
I was just on the phone with him.
Mr. Shen, what business
do you have with Gao Tu?
I...
There's just been a misunderstanding.
I'd like to clear the air.
Got it.
And...
When you ask him out,
could you not say it's me who asked?
I'm afraid he won't dare come over.
Okay, okay.
I'll let you know once I set it up.
All right.
Thank you.
Gao Tu is an Omega.
There's this sudden pregnancy
then he vanishes just like that?
And that boss of his, Shen, the rich Alpha?
He's suddenly acting all worried about Gao Tu?
I bet Gao Tu's carrying his baby.
Talk about the stars aligning,
just what I needed.
Even the heavens are on my side.
Things are much better now.
You'll be discharged from the hospital soon.
Thank you.
Brother.
I have a check-up later.
- Just wait here.
- Okay.
Here you are.
Go on. Call for me if you need anything.
Okay.
[Gao Ming - Don't Answer]
Qing, I need to talk
to you and your brother, it's urgent.
Don't worry, it's not about money.
Call me back as soon as you see this.
Hello?
Gao Tu?
Hey, what's going on with you?
Why's your number out of service?
Are you okay?
What's the matter?
No, nothing serious. Here's the thing.
That money you gave me
a couple of months ago...
I don't need it anymore.
So, I was in a rush to return it to you.
But I couldn't get through.
So, I figured I'd try my luck
and come find Qing.
You want to...
give the money back?
There's no need.
If you've got extra cash,
just keep it for yourself.
Just...
don't gamble again.
Don't worry.
Listen, I've got a real job now.
From now on, money's not gonna be a problem.
And I swear I'm done gambling.
Okay.
That's good.
Dad.
Things have been a bit rough at work lately.
I might not be able
to send you money regularly anymore.
It's okay.
From now on, I won't
have to worry about money anymore.
Oh, where are you right now?
Qing and I are at the hospital for a check-up.
I see. Let's grab a meal sometime then.
How about tomorrow?
At the place we used to go to.
Sound good?
Maybe not.
Hey, Tu.
I swear, I'm not calling
to ask for money this time.
It's been over a year
since we saw each other, hasn't it?
Son, a family should at least
act like one, right?
Tu...
Was Dad really that bad before?
No.
It's all in the past.
Then it's settled.
See you tomorrow.
Okay.
All right then.
See you tomorrow.
What's going on?
Mr. Hua., the Chairman would like to see you
tomorrow at 8:30 A.M.
Please come to He Ci Hospital alone.
He wants to talk to you
about you and Mr. Sheng.
It's nothing.
Shao You.
Why is your glass empty?
Let me pour you something.
Mr. Sheng can't drink alcohol.
Why can't he drink?
Yeah, why not?
Why can't I drink?
Because of me.
Excuse me, waiter.
Can we get a pitcher of orange juice
and two glasses of warm water?
Sure, just a moment.
Wait.
Shao You.
You came all the way here
just for orange juice?
Do you want me to order you
two bottles of kids' milk too?
Yong.
Shao You just got
a public proposal from someone else.
And you're still here fussing over him?
Careful, he might just get annoyed...
and marry someone else instead.
Bo Qiao. Cut the crap.
Here's your orange juice and warm water.
Enjoy.
Boss, there's a commotion outside.
Hey, Yu Shan. Where are you going?
Someone's making trouble out front.
I'm going to check it out.
Someone dares cause trouble here?
Heard it's a shareholder
from Country P's X Holdings.
I'll take a look.
X Holdings, huh?
Then Shao You has to see this, too.
Yu Shan, I'll go with you.
Let's go.
Hey.
You're the owner here, right?
And you are?
My boss likes this place.
He wants you to clear out.
Buddy...
Your boss is welcome as a guest.
Guests should act like guests.
You're interfering with my business.
That's not okay, is it?
And what's so bad about that?
Do you even know who my boss is?
Nope.
He's a major shareholder of X Holdings.
Be smart about this. Clear this place. Now.
We'll pay you double.
Is everyone from X Holdings this arrogant?
Are you done yet?
Is clearing a place out that hard?
- Boss.
- Boss, we're just talking.
Boss, that's the guy in charge here.
So, you're the boss?
All these years...
I've never met anyone
who dared to say no to me.
It's happening to you now, isn't it?
What did you say?
Wanna keep your left hand or your right?
Hua...
Hua Yong.
Mr. Major Shareholder.
What happened to your hand?
It doesn't look symmetrical.
Need a hand with that?
No.
No, no. I'm good.
Let's go.
Mr. Sheng, finish your breakfast.
I'm heading out and won't be long.
Where are you going this early?
To take care of the last obstacle in my life.
So, I won't have to worry about it anymore.
Psycho.
Come in, please.
Uncle.
Don't stand there.
Sit down.
Okay.
You wanted to see me.
Is there something you want to tell me alone?
The last time you told me
you were from Country P.
Your country has an X Holdings.
You should know that.
Yeah, I know.
So, is your family in business or politics?
I was born into a big family.
Some went into business, some into politics.
But on my father's side,
they were mostly entrepreneurs.
So, how would you say
your father's business
compares to X Holdings today?
X Holdings grew from Bei Chao Holdings
and it's undergone massive reforms.
What my father built doesn't even come close.
You're right.
I think there isn't a company in Country P now
that can go toe-to-toe with X Holdings.
X Holdings is okay.
Yeah, it's okay.
X Holdings from your country
basically holds all the cards, doesn't it?
A while back,
the real power of X Holdings
already proposed to Shao You.
It's big news.
It's something you should know about.
Yeah, I know.
I'm hoping for Shao You
to be able to say yes to his proposal.
Really?
Shao You should be with
the right person for his marriage.
Besides, a marriage with X Holdings
can also provide greater stability
to Sheng Fang Biotech.
Hua Yong, I think...
you should probably be able to understand that.
I completely understand.
In that case, I'll change my form of address.
Thank you, Dad.
Dad.
Who the hell are you?
Hua Yong.
The real power behind X Holdings.
Our father...
Why did you hang up? Answer it.
What's this?
You just met this morning...
And you're already taking his side?
Well, he agreed to let me be with you.
Of course I'm going to back him.
It's called mutual support...
A healthy cycle, you know?
- Hello, Dad?
- Shao You.
About you and Hua...
I won't oppose it anymore.
Wait, what?
I'm saying I approve.
I'm okay with you two getting married.
But if Hua ever treats you badly...
you have to tell me, okay?
The Sheng family won't let him off easy.
Dad...
You tired of playing emperor...
And thinking of becoming a judge now?
Just focus on your health.
Don't go worrying about everything else.
By the way, when are you going to get married?
No idea.
But Yong said...
Yong?
How come you two got all chummy
after just one morning meeting?
What did you talk about?
You should have told me earlier
Yong's the owner of X Holdings.
That way I won't snub him.
If you're polite to everyone,
you wouldn't have snubbed Yong at all.
You...
Enough.
I've got to go. I'm hanging up now.
Our father...
Mr. Sheng.
I have something I want to say.
Will you marry me?
Why aren't you the one marrying me?
Then I will.
As long as you're willing, Mr. Sheng.
I don't care who's marrying who.
So...
Will you marry me?
You'll be Mrs. Sheng from now on.
- Dad.
- Good evening!
I don't think it's the place we always come to.
Mr. Shen.
I'm sorry, this kid was busy.
Mr. Shen, I've got him here.
Let's lay everything out today.
Oh, by the way, Mr. Shen...
There's one more thing I need to inform you.
Gao Tu... He's pregnant.
And the baby is yours.
What?
Gao Tu.
Is that true?
No.
I'm a Beta.
Mr. Shen.
Here.
This is the hospital report I pulled.
Take a look.
If you still don't believe it,
go to the hospital
and run a DNA test on the amniotic fluid.
Mr. Shen, you're such a promising young man...
I'm sure you don't want some child
with questionable origins.
Ten million.
To have us get rid of the baby.
Not a penny less.
Gao Tu...
You used my trust.
You planned all this just to get pregnant.
So, you could demand ten million
when it came time to abort the child.
Gao Tu...
It's been ten years.
You've been by my side for ten years.
And this is what it was all for?
Excuse me.
I need the bathroom.
You...
Mr. Shen,
Let him go.
We are talking about aborting
an Omega's child right in front of him.
It's a bit cruel.
Why don't we settle the terms
before he returns?
Come on, sit.
Let's talk this through. Come on, sit down.
Take a seat.
Mr. Shen.
Hey, Brother.
What's going on?
Hey, Qing.
Pack your luggage now.
We have to leave Jiang Hu immediately.
Gao Tu, I know you're avoiding me on purpose.
We've never had an open and honest conversation
about many things.
So, there's been a lot of misunderstanding.
I hope that after seeing this video,
you'll contact me as soon as possible.
I'm not what you think I am.
Please come back.
Give me a chance to explain in person.
Where's Wen Lang?
Not answering the phone for days.
Also absent from the group meeting.
Is he playing the same game as Mr. Gao?
We've made contact.
He...
is in hospital.
He can't go home until tomorrow.
What happened?
The doctor said it's from stress and anxiety.
It triggered an early rut.
Looks like he won't be able to
work properly for a while.
He brought it on himself.
The chance was right in front of him,
and he still let it slip away.
He didn't clear up the last misunderstanding,
and then made an even bigger mess.
Now Secretary Gao's avoiding him
like a mouse hiding from a cat.
Even if he posted a missing person ad
on Mars right now
they'd still run even farther.
Hey.
Gao Tu.
What did you think of the movie?
Not bad, I don't watch a lot of comedies.
Well...
Are you blind?
Stay back. Can't you smell him?
It's an S-class Alpha in his rut.
It'll be a problem if we get targeted.
What are you doing?
This is a common area.
It's unethical for you
to disperse your pheromones.
We have underage Omega at home.
Put away your pheromones.
Or I'll call the police.
Gao Tu.
Come out.
Who the hell is that?
Stop knocking.
- Gao Tu.
- Reel in your pheromones
I don't know any Gao Tu.
Please stop knocking
I'm begging you.
- Gao Tu
- I really don't know him.
Gao Tu!
I really don't know who's that.
Come out.
Help! Help!
[Uncle Ying Yi]
What's going on?
Nothing.
Spam call.
Go back to sleep.
Uncle Ying Yi.
Yong, I'm sorry for disturbing you
in the middle of the night.
It's okay.
How can I help you?
I'm in a prickly situation.
I've had very little contact with old friends.
But I know Wen Lang's done well
in Jiang Hu all these years thanks to you.
You're too kind, Uncle Ying.
You used to be the one
who took care of me the most in Country P.
I've never even mentioned you to Wen Lang.
If there's anything I can do for you,
just say the word.
Wen Lang's in a bit of trouble right now.
But it's not convenient for me to step in.
Could you go on my behalf?
Gao Tu.
Come out.
Gao Tu!
I miss you. Come on out.
Oh my God.
That's scary.
The target is an S-Class Alpha
who's having mating disorder.
He will indiscriminately attack anyone
who prevents him from seeing his mate.
Standby.
Yes, sir.
- Sir!
- Gao Tu.
You're suspected of unlawful entry.
Stop this dangerous behavior immediately.
- Gao Tu.
- Or the police will take further action.
- We're here to ensure public safety.
- Gao Tu.
- Sir!
Sir!
Gao Tu.
- What's going on?
- Get out of there.
We're out of options.
The target's got a bad case of mating disorder.
There's no way
to communicate rationally anymore.
Get the tranquilizer gun.
The rest of you move.
- Gao Tu.
- First team, this way.
- Second team, over there.
- That's really scary.
Gao Tu.
- Get out of there.
- Fuck, the target is moving too far.
- It's hard to shoot.
- Request for reinforcements.
- Get out of there.
Gao Tu.
I'm sorry for the scare.
At the request of Mr. Shen's family,
I'm here to help resolve the situation.
Sorry for the trouble.
Everything's under control now.
Let's all move along.
Mr. Sheng, we exceeded our expectations,
completing multiple projects
and reaching objectives this year.
Various medical enterprises at home and abroad
are all in tight cooperation with us.
The market response has been great,
so our goal for next quarter
is to keep expanding the market share
of our new products overseas...
Mr. Sheng? Are you okay?
Blood...
What happened? Mr. Sheng?
Get the entire medical team in here!
Chen Pin Ming, get the car
to the hospital! Now!
Hurry! Get in here!
[Emergency Room]
- Mr. Hua
- Dr. Wang.
How is Mr. Sheng?
Mr. Sheng is an Alpha.
The gestational sac formed
after he was permanently marked.
The sac wall is quite thin.
And the fetus is unusually active.
The sac has ruptured.
He's lost a lot of blood.
It's very serious.
You need to be ready for the worst.
Chang Yu.
Go get Wen Lang.
Yes.
Where's Sheng Shao You?
Hey.
Are you okay?
Wen Lang.
If anything happens to Mr. Sheng,
I'm counting on you
to look after Little Peanut.
I'll name you as the legal guardian
until they come of age.
Why don't you raise your own kids?
I'll go wherever Mr. Sheng goes.
Don't be silly.
The child is so young.
That's your child with Sheng Shao You.
Hua Yong.
Can't you at least think of the baby?
If something happens to Mr. Sheng,
we're all done for.
It'd be me and them who killed Mr. Sheng.
If they didn't have
half of Mr. Sheng's blood in them,
do you really think I'd let them live?
Don't you love your child at all?
I do.
If I didn't...
Mr. Sheng would be heartbroken.
Daddy Wen Lang, take me to the theme hotel.
We'll take you there
when they come back from Europe.
No, Daddy Wen Lang take me.
Let's wait for them.
Let Sheng Shao You take you there.
Dad's busy. He needs to rest.
Father doesn't agree.
And the event is almost over.
Please, Daddy Wen Lang.
Just take him there.
Peanut is so well-behaved.
He won't be too much trouble, right?
He won't be trouble?
Why didn't you take him to Europe?
Your family honeymooned with the kids?
Sorry.
I forgot.
You don't have a wife.
Who doesn't have a wife?
No, I'll correct it.
It's not that.
Your wife ran away.
Daddy, where's Father?
Honey.
Daddy Wen Lang took me out.
There were mice and big dinosaurs.
It's not a mice.
It's Mickey Mouse.
It's a mouse.
Black ears.
Sharp mouth.
The mouse in the strappy pants.
Honey.
It's Mickey Mouse
Mickey Mouse.
Yeah, Mickey Mouse.
Peanut.
Whether the ears are black or white,
a rat or cat with a pointed
or protruding mouth,
can you tell me when you're sure?
Your father's tired now
and need rest.
We have a time difference here.
It's still dark.
Daddy's taking a break.
Only with proper rest
can we have the strength to go home.
Do you understand?
Okay.
How could a kid understand
the kind of filth running through
your pervy brain?
Go do whatever you were doing.
I'll take Peanut
and get to the bottom of that rat.
Okay. Bye, Daddy.
Bye-bye.
- Hurry up.
- Wait.
Daddy Wen Lang.
I'm going on my own.
Yeah, okay.
Go on.
Watch out!
Peanut.
- Sir.
- Young master.
Are you all right?
Is the young master hurt?
- Is he injured?
- Daddy, don't worry.
I just took a little fall.
It doesn't hurt.
Gao Tu.
Hua Yong, Hua Yong.
Don't be so disrespectful.
Come on, put your socks on, Peanut.
The kindergarten teacher said
a name is a symbol for all.
We should learn to listen.
Learn to subpoena.
It's called calling each other.
Only when the police, prosecutors,
or court summon a suspect,
that's what they call a subpoena.
Dad, what's the police, prosecutors, and court?
It's short for the police,
the prosecutor's office, and the court.
So, what's a suspect?
It's someone who's done
something seriously wrong.
Just like Daddy Lang.
Is Daddy Wen Lang that kind of person?
You could think of it that way.
Daddy Wen Lang is basically on death row
with reprieve now.
What's a death sentence with reprieve?
It's just a little better than being executed.
Reprieve from death penalty.
Really? Is Daddy Wen Lang going to die?
He won't.
But it's worse than death.
It's all about faith.
It's all thanks to
Uncle Gao's magical breath keeping him alive.
Stop teaching nonsense.
Quit pinching Peanut's cheeks.
He'll drool in his sleep.
Look, his cheeks are all red now.
He won't!
Peanut loves it
when I pinch his face, don't you?
No, no I don't!
Go away, Hua Yong.
Don't pinch my face
I'll be drooling at night.
Look at your son.
One day, you're gonna end up
climbing all over my head.
You were already climbing on Daddy yesterday.
That's not allowed, show some respect!
Father, I was just joking.
You'd better be.
What's going on?
It's nothing.
You're not having another baby, are you?
Don't say anything with the kid around.
Even after his death,
Pangu continued to hold up the earth.
The sun and moon hung in the sky,
keeping it from collapsing.
So, the heavens would never fall.
Mountains and seas
weighed down the land from below,
so the earth would never rise.
From that moment on,
the world became vibrant and full of life.
Daddy.
Father says you might have another baby.
What does that mean?
Peanut.
Would you like to have a brother or sister?
Yes.
If I have a younger sibling,
I'm the big brother.
Do you want to be a brother so badly?
Yes.
Being an older brother
means I can protect my younger siblings.
Daddy, I'll protect you, too.
Who are you to protect my Alpha?
Get in line.
You're so annoying. Get out.
What did you say?
You're bullying a kid. Shame on you.
You can't talk to your father like that
I'm sorry, I was wrong.
Go to bed early.
You have to go to kindergarten tomorrow.
The little thing is so mean to me.
You were the one who was being rude.
Don't steal attention from the kid.
He's 36 months old.
How old are you?
I'm only 300 months old, too.
Okay, stop it.
Peanut said...
he wants a brother or a sister.
No.
Goodness...
It was just a stomach bug today.
But I was scared out of my mind.
Please don't ever scare me like that again.
Once was more than enough.
Okay.
It was a casual mention.
Mr. Sheng.
I'm a coward.
Don't ever say that again.
If you dare to say that again,
I'll go get sterilized.
You little maniac.