SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Subbers: Archanfel, Toki, Joe
Double Life
Episode 18
Burglar.
Isn't he that guy?
So weak.
You're wounded.
Is there an assassin?
No. I just fell
Good night, Lord.
Wu Ziqi.
Where are you going at night
instead of sleeping?
To practice to grow stronger.
23 did well in her mission.
Here's her reward.
What is that?
I have no idea.
It's Soul-replacing.
Once another eats it,
your Portent will be transferred to him.
Take it, Yun Shang.
If you do well,
you'll all be rewarded.
Yun Luo.
Sister.
I didn't ask you yesterday.
What exactly between you and that dead meat...
What dead meat?
My mission target.
Since he'll die anyway,
isn't he dead meat?
He has a name,
Wu Ruan.
Fine. Wu Ruan.
What exactly is your relationship with him?
You want him to be your husband?
He is a dying man.
Yun Luo.
That's why I called you here.
You just left the Pavilion
and don't know how vicious the world is.
I don't want you
to be a killing tool of the Pavilion.
I know how
to expel your Portent.
You know it?
Yes.
If there is a way,
why don't you expel yours first?
You need it better than me.
I can't
do it alone
because it needs two people.
So, let me
take care of yours
and I can deal with mine later.
Really?
All right.
What do you need me to do?
No matter what happens
or what you'll see later,
do not panic.
When I eat this,
hold my hand tightly
and don't let go.
Yun Luo.
Do you get me?
Yes.
Sister.
What's wrong, sister?
Yun Shang.
What have you done to her?
She's your sister.
I don't know.
I did nothing.
She said she could cure me.
I didn't expect she'd...
She won't die
and she will wake up.
Let me prescribe to condition her body.
Thank you. This way, Doc. Wang.
Her condition...
Do you...
Do your villagers
know how to cure her?
I don't know what she ate.
I never
saw it before.
Is there no way at all?
YoYo English Channel    YouTube