[May your heart be like mine]
[Episode 14]
Tianxing?
Boss,
this chick is quite a looker.
Yeah.
It'd be a shame to kill her.
[Lu's Mansion]
Wan'er?
I've brought the stuff back.
Young Master?
Young Master.
What's wrong?
Why have you come back?
Can't I come back?
No, it's not that.
Someone just came to the mansion with news
that you were in danger in the woods at the city's outskirts.
Young Madam was very worried when she heard this.
So she rushed there immediately.
What?
Oh no.
Qing?
Qing!
How did she manage to escape again?
[Maple Inn]
Brother Xie,
are you alright?
Miss Yunyun.
Why are you here?
Did you do this to save Mrs. Lu?
Yes.
Once she wakes up,
I will...
Let me help you inside first.
Master,
how is he?
His pulse is irregular,
and heat is emanating from his internal organs.
He must have been poisoned with an extremely hot poison.
Chiyan Powder?
To save me,
he transferred the poison in me to himself.
No wonder...
I hope this silver lock
can protect you and keep you safe.
Tianxing?
Tianxing.
The Nine Nights of Hell.
You're saying he's been poisoned with Nine Nights of Hell?
It's Yu Xiaolin.
A red line
will appear on
the poisoned person's left arm.
The line will grow a bit each day,
their blood will turn purple-black,
and then they will...
You've followed Yu Xiaolin for many years.
You must know how to make the poisons he often uses.
Please, tell me.
I beg you.
Please.
Master,
what should we do now?
Though everyone fears the Nine Nights of Hell poison,
in fact, it's not difficult to concoct,
nor is it hard to cure.
It's just that its antidote is also a poison,
with an overpowering potency.
We need a specific herb to protect the heart meridian.
What herb?
Marsdenia longipes.
This herb grows in deep mountains shrouded in clouds and mist.
White Cloud Mountain...
Some might be growing there.
Wait!
You have many other matters to attend to. You can't take risks.
Master,
he got poisoned with Chiyan Powder
because of saving me.
I can't just leave him like this.
Please.
I beg you.
I'll go with you.
Let's search more carefully.
The herb must be nearby.
I'll go take a look over there.
Mrs. Lu!
Come quickly and see this.
Is this the Marsdenia longipes?
Where?
Here.
Yes.
I'll go pick it.