I've taught you for so long
to make you steal things,
not to help others.
You show kindness to others,
but will they treat you the same?
If you come to terms with it, come back to find me.
Don't waste your talent.
Get lost, you stinking beggar!
No?
Move aside!
Get out of my way!
You little brat.
Next time I see you, I'll kill you!
From now on,
I'd rather betray the world
than let the world betray me!
I have some extra food.
If you don't mind, you can have it.
Xiaojing, it's time to go.
Coming.
Take this umbrella too.
If you encounter any difficulties,
come to Tianshu State and find me.
My name is Cui Xiaojing.
Master,
you were wrong.
Someone will show kindness to me.
[May your heart be like mine]
[Episode 3]
Father, please have some tea.
Wan'er,
our Chen is careless.
If he ever mistreats you,
you must tell me.
I will certainly stand up for you.
Thank you, Father.
Chen, now that we have some free time,
let's go to the count room together.
Now that you're married,
from now on, all the household affairs
will be managed by Wan'er.
Managed by...
her?
If you don't let her manage,
are you planning to let Miss Rong manage instead?
I'm not.
Alright then, let's go.
Lead the way.
Young Master.
The keys.
Why are there so many keys?
Chen.
Open the door.
Did you forget which key it is?
I didn't.
I'm Commoner Swordsman.
I never use keys to open doors.
It's open.
So many books?
How do I know which one is the account book?
Honey, are you reluctant?
Hurry up and give it to her.
Xiaobao.
What are you waiting for?
Get the account book.
Do you want me, your young master, to get it myself?
Honey, here.
Honey, don't worry.
I will definitely manage the accounts thoroughly.
The records for these years are all here.
If this continues, it will be exposed sooner or later.
I must find it as soon as possible.
There aren't many places in the Lu residence to hide things.
Why can't I find it?
Where on earth did Lu Chen hide the booklet?
You bumped into me!
I bumped into you?
What's your attitude?
I know you are the Young Madam of the Lu family.
But I'm pregnant
with the Lu family's eldest grandson.
What? Are you scared now?
Let me tell you the truth.
Mr. Lu married you
only because of your childhood engagement.
He had no choice.
He doesn't love you.
And among all the women he has,
I'm the only one who's pregnant.
It's enough to show that I'm his true love.
Why are you laughing?
I'm laughing at your naivety.
If you were his true love,
he wouldn't have married someone else,
and there wouldn't be any other women.
So, since there are,
how sincere can this love be?
This Qiao Wan'er is surprisingly insightful.
It's really a shame that she married Lu Chen.
Everyone in Qinghe Town knows
that the Qiao family has fallen from grace.
You shamelessly married into the family.
Let me tell you,
if it weren't for you,
I would be Mrs. Lu.
Don't go!
Mr. Lu!
Honey?
Doctor,
how is Chen?
Master Lu,
the young master's pulse is very steady.
He should be fine.
It's just...
Doctor,
since you said the young master is fine,
-why is it that when I pinch him so hard,
-It hurts!
he doesn't react at all?
Well...
Your grip is really strong.
Mr. Lu.
Master, he's awake.
Chen,
are you alright?
Honey,
Mr. Lu, I didn't do it on purpose just now.
Who are you?
Take care, doctor.
If Lu Chen really has amnesia,
no one will know where the booklet is.
The doctor said that
once the blood stasis clears, he will regain his memory.
How long will it take, Father?
A few days at best,
or a year or more at worst.
A year or more?
No. I...
Wan'er, I know you're worried about Chen.
Actually, I heard of a secret recipe before
that can open the meridians, directly targeting the brain,
with the hope of bringing him back to his senses.
But...
Tell me, Father.
What's this recipe?
No matter what the cost,
I must cure my husband.
Does Qiao Wan'er really like Lu Chen that much?
How come I didn't realize it before?
I must praise myself
for coming up with this idea of pretending to have amnesia.
Oh, right, Xiaobao.
I have something to ask you.
What can I do for you, Young Master?
Now that I have amnesia,
I have no memory of my past habits.
Can you tell me what kind of person I am?
Young Master, you are delicate and precious,
and extremely picky.
The water you normally use for bathing
is mountain spring water that the servants fetch early in the morning.
Also,
your clothes are all custom-made at Jinxiu Pavilion,
and even the fabric is...
Extravagant
and indulgent.
Young Master,
I didn't mean it.
It's alright.
I'm not angry.
Don't just talk about these material things.
Tell me about my family.
Young Master, you are... very filial
and value family.
Every year on your father's birthday,
you hold a grand celebration.
By the way, recently, you even repaired the ancestral hall
and had a custom-made urn for your younger brother.
Young Master...
Did I say something wrong again?
No,
I shouldn't have placed my hopes on you.
Never mind, I'll go and take a bath first.
Young Master!
Why does this water taste a bit sweet?
Honey?