[May your heart be like mine]
[Episode 23]
Thank you for your trouble, Master Xie.
It's my duty.
No need to thank me.
If there's nothing else,
I'll take my leave.
What's going on?
Others,
protect the lord.
Come, come, over here, over here.
Go check over there.
I'd like to ask you, Master Xie,
for a favor.
I've found the location of the booklet,
but unfortunately,
my brother
has installed an intricate mechanism.
As soon as the box hiding the booklet
changes in weight,
the entire Lord's mansion
will sound an alarm.
Only Master Xie's Lingxiu Point
can perform such a sleight of hand.
The Lord's mansion is heavily guarded.
Even with my superior martial arts skills,
it's impossible for me alone
to steal something without anyone noticing.
Don't you enjoy creating diversions?
I've brought you what you wanted.
Why haven't you released Xiaojing yet?
If I release her,
will you go back on your word?
What else do you want?
The two booklets in my possession
can basically confirm the approximate location of the treasure.
While what you and this lady have
is the exact location of the treasure.
So,
I kindly request that you, Master Xie,
accompany us on this journey.
Young Lord,
the treasure should be right here.
Start digging.
How is this possible?
My treasure.
Where's the treasure?
Where's my treasure?
Young Lord.
Brother.
Lord,
I have a request.
Master Xie,
what's the meaning of this?
Please get up.
Stand up first, then we'll talk.
Lord,
I'd like to borrow this booklet
to save someone important.
The person you want to save,
is it Miss Cui from Shenyin Sect?
How did you know?
Just as Xiaolin planted spies in my mansion,
I have done the same.
He
must have a plan, right?
You should follow his plan.
Aren't you afraid...
The lives of the people in the world are important.
So is that of a single person.
Moreover,
I'm well prepared.
I won't let him succeed.
Thank you, Lord.
The show must go on.
Otherwise, my brother
won't release her.
I understand.
You still came.
You planned all of this.
You've been meticulously plotting against me!
Xiaolin,
the one who set this trap wasn't me.
It was Father.
Father has always valued you highly.
He saw you as his pride.
But he also felt your ambition was too great.
You can start a business,
but you're not the talent to maintain it.
So he set up this trap with the treasure.
If you were content being the Young Lord,
you'd live a life of wealth and honor.
We brothers would govern Tianshu State together.
But if you harbored rebellious thoughts
and touched the treasure...
Brother,
please stop.
You think I'm not prepared?
Si Xuan!
Why did you...
Brother Xie,
do you really regret saving me?
What I said that day was out of anger.
This is the antidote for the Heart-Piercing Powder.
Consider it repaying the life of Xiaojing's master.
Please don't hate me, okay?
Miss Yunyun.
How could I?
Miss Yunyun
Miss Yunyun!
Protect the Lord!
Tianxing,
what's going on here?
I'll explain to you later.
Keep him alive.