Music
But that doesn't mean that they automatically belong to you.
By your logic, does it mean that you can claim ownership of any item in our auction related to China?
Blue and white Rui earways, which is dated back to the Qianlong period of the Qin dynasty.
The shape, decorative patterns and inscriptions showcase the exquisite craftsmanship
and its cultural heritage of porcelain production in the Qin dynasty.
Hello, is this the Jin Yue Hotel in Beijing?
I would like to ask if Professor Zan Maochang from the University of Qinbei has been admitted?
Okay, thank you.
No.
If we keep causing trouble, we will be in a state of emergency.
Will the emergency be delayed for the first year?
Do you have other experts at your archaeological site?
No, it's like this.
Isn't there a recent Qin Han Archaeological Research Conference in Beijing?
Almost all the experts we can go to have been there.
Wang Jun, if you want me to call the city and ask if there are any people who can still be found?
Actually, we can answer these three questions.
Do you know how big this is?
Can you do your job in the city now?
I don't care about friends in the city.
Do you know that if you answer the wrong question,
those six black peaches will not come back?
This is a tough question to ask.
Anyway, you have 20 minutes.
The decision is yours.
Hello?
Professor Zan.
Sir, I believe it is necessary to remind you
that there is only half an hour left before the auction of those six black pottery figurines.
Wang Jun, Mr. You, the three of them are excellent.
You can trust them with this matter.
We won't wait for anyone.
Hurry up.
Feng Kun, I'll be waiting for you by the phone.
There must be no mistake in this matter.
Turn on the computer.
Okay.
Luo Qing, check the information about the excavation of the Yangling external pit and the burial tomb.
There are many ways to use the Yangling
external pit.
Please take a closer look.
As you can see, the female and male forms are very obvious.
As well as the facial expressions, they are really realistic.
This is a high-class artistic object and is considered to be a burial object as well.
These cultural relics are royal, spiritual, and burial objects.
These loquets should have been used by the Zhuo Yi clan.
The price for lot number 32 is starting at $800.
Please raise your pedals for bidding.
$800.
$850 here.
$900.
The price for lot number 32 is starting at $800.
Please raise your pedals for bidding.
$800.
$850 here.
$900.
The first one was discovered in the Yangling area of the Hanjing area.
The largest number, the most complete type, and the male and female forms are all there.
Different characters are also found.
The second one was discovered in the 80s in the Xuan area of the Western Han.
The number is not as large as the Yangling area.
The third one was discovered in the 80s and later in the Maoling area of the Hanwu area.
The fourth one was discovered in the 90s in the southwest of the Changlin area of the Han High Group.
But there are only male and female forms.
The fifth one was discovered in the Ba Cunpu area of the northwest of the Han Chang'an city.
The inspection room discovered the loquets, taoyong, and silk.
Later, archaeologists discovered the production of loquets in the Ba Cunpu area.
And also some unsold loquets.
How many times have you done it?
The fifth time.
The fifth time?
How can I remember there were six times?
Where is the sixth time?
The sixth time is...
Ladies and gentlemen, are there any higher bid for the lot number 32?
$1500.
The King of Liang, the Queen of Liang.
The King of Liang's information.
This is the only information.
It's in Mangshan, Henan.
The King of Liang, Mangshan.
Okay.
I got it.
Mr. Manager, may I use your computer for a little while?
Just a moment.
Sir, please take a look.
If you have any question, I would like to explain it for you.
$1600.
Are there any higher bids?
And it goes $1600.
Once, $1600.
Twice.
Wait.
Dear ladies and gentlemen, I'm very sorry to inform you that the bid is over.
Dear ladies and gentlemen, I'm very sorry to inform you that the auction for lot 32 is temporarily suspended.
Mr. Hong, come here.
What's up?
Let's go.
Mr. Hong, come here.
Mr. Hong, I'm here to buy flowers for you.
Okay.
Let me have a look.
I'll do it.
Where did you get this?
You can keep it for us.
Keep it in the shop.
Is it a problem?
Come on, Mr. Hong.
I'll buy you a lot.
Here.
Keep a look at the flowers.
Okay.
Go ahead.
How is it?
It's good.
It's a little bit red.
It's a little bit light.
It's a good work.
This is a piece of work that's been passed down from the Yuan Dynasty.
Do you know how to read the Luo Shen Wen Tongjing?
If you want to make a mistake, you have to make a mistake.
Either you are a modern person or you are a person.
This Tongjing is a wine made by the Qing Dynasty to put in the Yuan Dynasty.
It's made of the essence of the tea.
You're so good at it.
You're so bad at it.
I don't know if you understand it or not.
If I make a mistake, you can come to me anytime.
My
Thank you.
I'll eat later.
Okay.
What do you say?
Give money.
People say that the dead make money.
I'm a bad person.
Don't believe it.
Who wants to say that Lao Mu is not trustworthy?
Why is this man trustworthy?
Lao Mu read a lot.
You put something here today.
Is it rare or is it easy to understand?
He read it all for you.
Come and take a look.
What?
Brother Song, I've been with you for years.
I've done the Pei Xingqi thing.
If it's really that I can't do it, why do I have to go back?
I'll report it to you when I get back.
I'll report it to you.
I'll just run away with the stuff.
That's right.
You have to say that you want to be a self-reliant.
I'm drunk.
I'm out there.
I really don't have the heart to go out.
I'm going to go.
Who do you think is the murderer?
I don't know.
Do you know our rules?
I know.
The dead have to be killed.
The body is buried in the ground.
I don't know.
You don't give up?
Then what do I do?
Or I'll do it as a dead man.
One by one.
That's right.
Then sit here.
All right?
Come on, let's go.
You get the bottom.
You go first.
Brother Sheng, you go that way.
Hurry up.
Brother Sheng, I'm wronged.
Hu Wen, you're angry.
Brother Sheng.
Brother Shu.
You haven't finished yet.
You're not lucky enough to rob the farmer's gang.
I'll get our fortune.
Brother Sheng.
Yes, yes, yes.
This is right.
The New Year can't be a bad thing.
We can't be unlucky.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
But it's been 23 years.
Let's eat first.
Eat, eat, Brother Sheng.
Eat, eat, eat.
I can't let him go.
I'm talking about you.
I can't afford to be angry.
If I die,
this meal should be a celebration.
The place on the source
was bought by Shusheng for 150,000.
Once it's done,
we'll have a meal.
Brother Shou will have to spend a year.
What's the use of Shou?
No, no.
I'm not going to eat.
Shusheng is a country.
There's something I can't say.
But everyone eats in the same pot.
It's our own brother.
I'm the chief today.
I prepared a meal.
Old Mu.
What do you mean?
We are the local people.
We can't break the rules.
Shusheng is a mountain.
Don't let everyone spy.
You have to remember this.
Qin Chuan and Sichang
keep secrets.
The internal cabinet will be made later.
What are you waiting for?
Eat.
I'm going to the office.
Report the price.
Don't lose the price.
Don't lose?
The business with you,
Qin Chuan's big fruit, big growth.
I'm a nobody in this industry.
You must have never heard of it.
But I've always known you.
I know a lot of people.
But there are only a few people who can find me.
How did you get him?
Uncle Liu.
You did business with him.
It has nothing to do with Lu Shusheng.
It doesn't matter what relationship I have with him.
I came to do this business with you.
This is for the royal family.
It's the black one.
You don't have to touch my wound.
I'm sorry.
I was beaten in front of the government.
You have seen it.
You must know the weight of this thing.
How much?
Two times more.
One thousand.
Six hundred.
Six hundred is six hundred.
The show is great.
I came with a shirt.
I know you, King of South China.
But I can only ask for one hundred.
One hundred?
Yes.
It doesn't matter if you don't agree.
You can find someone else.
My mother.
It doesn't matter if the thing is good or not.
One hundred.
She went to Sichang to sleep.
She made it.
There is still next time.
If it doesn't work, I owe you a favor.
I'll wait for you to be careful.
Even if someone else wants it, I won't sell it.
Okay.
I think that old man is deliberately messing with us.
Making up the room, organizing the room.
Is this what the department should do?
Why waste time on our students?
How can this be a waste of time?
Education in this department is the basic training.
Professional skills must be learned in further development.
I don't remember.
I'm going to work in the field.
Do you have a skill in drawing these things?
If you can accept that you can't draw better than a skill in the field,
you are like this.
It's this.
Let me learn what kind of talent our high-class students are.
Okay.
You have a high-class skill.
Communicate.
Come on, put the horse here.
I don't dare to be.
Okay.
It looks like you.
But is it okay if the drawing is like this?
I think you came here for a short time.
Let me give you a simple copy of what our teacher Zan usually tells us.
Listen carefully.
Look, look at your eyes.
Look at Mr. Zhang's drawing of Jiang Zai.
It's a very standard drawing of the archaeology.
It's primitive.
It's life-changing and fun.
Look at this drawing.
What's wrong?
It's cold and like winter.
You said Mr. Zhang is the best in archaeology in China.
Can I compare with him?
What are you standing up for?
What are you standing up for in class?
Sit down.
If you don't draw like you, you'll learn.
Can't you draw for two months if you don't draw well for a month?
If you can't draw well for two months, you can draw for a year.
You can only draw until you're good.
Teacher Zan.
I have something to say.
Luo Qing, Shilin.
You guys clean up and give me a task.
Teacher Zan, what task?
Not far from the Yangling, we found a tomb of a thief.
The Cultural and Cultural Affairs Bureau asked us to do a rescue discovery as soon as possible.
Okay, let's clean up and go.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
This drawing is not only artistic,
but also the most basic scientific.
Okay, you stay and continue drawing.
If you can't draw well for a month, you can draw for two months.
If you can't draw well for two months, you can draw for a year.
You can only draw until you're good.
Luo Qing has only been here for half a month.
Why can't he go and I can't go?
He's better than you.
I've been drawing well.
Look at my hands.
These scissors are all evidence of hard work.
The effort that didn't take much effort is useless.
Teacher Zan, do you have any objections to me?
I have objections to you.
Look at it yourself.
You've been drawing for eight months and you've drawn like this.
What are you thinking about all morning?
I'm a good person.
Xing Zhi.
Why are you here?
Come, come, come, come with me.
What are you talking about?
You're so stubborn.
You've hit me with your attention.
What's wrong with you?
You mean the pain?
You're a man who studies love.
Your hands are so deep that they're touching the ground.
Xing Zhi.
How can Tang Mu say that it has nothing to do with me?
Think about his position.
How close is it to our Yanglin?
His research information
has helped us to study the historical location of Yanglin.
Zan Maochang.
These words are good for outsiders.
I know your uncle.
Your Yanglin research is short of funds.
Take Tang Mu's work of rescue discovery.
There's no problem with the money.
Right?
I can't hide anything from you.
Xing Zhi, this is it.
Just do me a favor this time.
You see, this time you found out that
you are the leader of the provincial council.
How good is it?
Then let me and these kids
give you a good start.
Master, you sit there.
I'll help you with the little things.
I'll help you.
How about it?
You're back.
Yes, I'm back.
Come on.
I'm back.
You're back.
You should eat first.
The food is on the stove.
No hurry.
I've already made the moon.
I'll make you a bowl of porridge first.
I'm back.
I'm sick.
I'm so tired.
Next year,
we'll move into a big house.
We'll build a sunroom
and sunbathe every day.
Is there money for the house?
No, no.
Even others can get a house.
We can do it too.
Where did you go today?
Can I go there again?
I'm selling goods.
You're crazy.
I'm a man.
You don't know.
You're crazy.
I'm crazy.
I should have sold you a pillow.
Look.
You and You Si.
I'll call you directly.
Where did you get the money?
I left it there.
Do me a favor.
There's something in the bed.
Take it out.
What is it?
I found a little money.
I'm going to give it to the kids.
I got it from the countryside.
You're lying.
I'm not lying.
I've already
suffered a lot.
I don't have money to buy goods.
I don't have money to buy vegetables.
I have some money.
I can't do it.
I'll pay you back sooner or later.
I can't get used to it.
I'm sorry.
But I can't watch you go to me.
Shulan.
Look.
Why are you crying?
Think about it.
Three people.
One minute and one minute.
I'm making money.
My sister.
She can let me work.
Besides, my sister can't jump.
My hands can't lift.
I can't do it.
I've been a little dizzy lately.
Think about my brother.
I'd like to give me the goods.
Let me make some money.
I lied to you.
I'm so scared.
Don't be afraid.
Open the box.
Open it.
Look.
New package.
Come on.
Wu Du. Mingwen.
Cook the shrimp stock.
Do it.
Eat.
I've decided.
I won't do anything else.
I'll do it with you.
What do you say?
Don't worry.
We'll have a good day.
When you sing,
I know
you can die.
You must be a character.
In your opinion,
what kind of person is it?
It must be
the Emperor's
Emperor's son.
OK.
The king will use it in the future.
What do you like?
Come on.
I'll give you a toast.
OK.
Thank you, Captain Qi.
You've made a lot of money
in the south.
I'm sorry.
We only found 34 black-spawns.
The rest are lost.
You've tried your best.
I know everyone is concerned
about the six black-spawns
that were shot by the Wen Suopu auction house.
We just got news from the embassy.
The customs officer
detained these cultural relics.
The reason is the evidence we provided.
It's too simple.
They raised more questions.
For example,
can you clarify
how many
peach trees are planted in the tomb?
Besides,
what else is in the tomb?
We don't even know
where the hole is.
How did you know?
The bottom line is
we need to find
the hole of the black-spawns.
And we need to prove
that the black-spawns are from that hole.
Zhaoyun,
can you find the six black-spawns?
It depends on
whether we can get this case
after we get through the police.
Where is Qi Xian?
He's not here.
Da Cang.
Yes.
What did you find
about the black-spawns
in Suizhou?
Sir,
we only know
that the six black-spawns
and the 34 black-spawns
were from a foreign country
called Hualunwang eight months ago.
They were imported from Qinchuan
and sold to Hong Kong
and then to other countries.
They were sold to foreign retailers
in eight months.
It's clear that the underground
trade chain is very mature.
So,
as long as we can find Hualunwang,
we can find the black-spawns
behind Hualunwang.
Captain Yang,
have you heard
about Hualunwang?
Yes, but he's very cunning.
He's in contact with the country
and knows that his nickname
is Hualunwang.
It's an ancient Chinese name.
It's been a month.
Time is heavy.
We can't
just leave it at that.
Zhang Suo,
can you be sure
which country
is the black-spawns from?
From this...
From this pattern,
we can only see that
it's probably from the Western Han period.
It might have come from the ground.
But
there are 11 ground-spawns in the Western Han.
And there are many
black-spawns, black-spawns,
and all kinds of ground-spawns.
It's too broad.
As for
which wood,
it's even harder to say.
The Wen Suopu Pai Mai Hang
usually has a mark
on the source of the cultural relics.
Do they provide information?
Yes.
They mark
the six black-spawns
from the Sanmiao Village
in the west corner of our Qingchuan.
The cultural relics are very good.
In the next month,
we'll have to
send them to the Zansu tribe.
When you go to the Sanmiao Village,
I'll call you if I need anything.
Go to sleep.
Go.
Captain.
What?
I'll go with you.
We'll go together.
We have five cases.
He's my master, you're his master.
Let's go.
Thanks.
Did you hear?
The police
have brought back a batch of black-spawns.
How many?
34.
Let's see what you and Xingcheng
will do with my money.
34?
Only six?
Are my six in the Wen Suopu Pai Mai Hang?
I heard that these 34 are similar to mine.
They're probably the same size.
How are they similar?
Are they the same?
They're all black-spawns.
Who told you that?
My brother and sister-in-law
are working in the civil service.
Who is he?
His ex-girlfriend.
You don't believe it?
Of course I do.
The police called him by his name.
He's a man of great talent.
He can't leave any secrets behind.
I won't tell him anything.
The police
are good at making people happy.
I want to see how black-spawns work.
I'm from the Public Security Bureau.
I can't be a black-spawn.
Why don't you ask if there's anyone
who can take you to the surveillance center?
Surveillance center?
I came back from the office.
I thought I'd go to the surveillance center.
Do you know anyone there?
No.
The man in the last painting
in the front two years
graduated from Peking University.
Luo,
you're a little tired of the food.
Here,
we'll take you to the city tomorrow.
We'll improve the food.
Really?
I'm a customer.
I heard that a group of black-spawns
were caught by the police.
Is there a part of them in the surveillance center?
Now that's the situation.
The police are asking us to report
if we can get back the six pieces of the painting.
If we can get back the six pieces of the painting.
We're really worried.
What do you mean?
Last time, you answered
a few of their questions.
This time, they asked some tricky questions.
The painting is still in the painting.
It's still in the painting.