♪By the riverside♪
♪I sow a seed of karma♪
♪Forlorn fates intertwine♪
♪Written in the stars♪
♪Should your passion smolder out♪
♪Will you give up on your ideal world?♪
♪Our past can only be entrusted to memories♪
♪I'm mooning over you♪
♪Amidst loneliness♪
♪Berthed in sleepless nights♪
♪You're my desire♪
♪That teems underneath♪
♪I'm drowned in your beautiful eyes♪
♪I'm mooning over you♪
♪Next to the Three-life Stone♪
♪I cross the Bridge of Forgetfulness♪
♪Gazing at moonlit nights♪
♪The moon appears brighter because of you♪
♪Leaning against the tower, it returns my gaze♪
♪Gazing at moonlit nights♪
♪The moon appears brighter because of you♪
♪Leaning against the tower, it returns my gaze♪
[The Legend of Anle]
[Adapted from a novel by Xing Ling]
[Episode 27]
[Crown Prince's Residence]
How is Anle doing
lately?
Did the Crown Prince send you to check in on her?
No one would dare mention her name
with His Highness around.
It's me who wants to know.
After all, she has been nice to me.
After what happened,
everything has changed tremendously.
I am worried about her.
She is doing well.
She asks about you.
I'm glad to hear that.
However,
seeing how distant they are from each other now,
it makes me feel sad.
A lot has happened.
Things can never be the same again.
The weather is cold.
I hope you take care, Your Highness.
Thank you for the concern, Official Di.
Even now,
you still speak so politely to me.
I am glad.
From our first meeting in Jingnan
to our reunion in the capital,
you were plotting whenever you approached me.
I knew you had ulterior motives,
but because I trust you,
I never pried.
I'm grateful for your recognition
and caring.
At this point,
if you think I've been
a capable pawn in your bidding,
could you be honest with me for once?
Is there anything
that you must do regardless of the price?
I'm waiting for an apology.
Unless he gives up his pride
as the ruler of the nation,
the truth about the wrongful execution
of the Di family
will never be known to the world.
The 80,000 restless souls
will never find peace.
Ziyuan.
Sorry.
This apology
is ten years overdue.
Your Highness.
I will get the apology I seek
from His Majesty.
My father didn't know about
my grandmother's actions.
If it weren't his intention,
why wouldn't he give the Di family a chance
to clear their name?
My father, Marquis Jing'an,
couldn't save the family even if he took his life!
For ten years,
not a single official in the court
ever spoke up for my father.
Your Highness saved me,
so I am grateful for that.
But by doing so,
you incited His Majesty's anger.
You know very well
what the cause of it is.
I am the sole survivor
of the Di family.
Perhaps you now know
the pain that I felt back then.
Ziyuan.
You're not alone.
You've always gotten along with Wen Shuo.
He likes you too.
You can think of him as your own brother.
With him as your companion,
you could be happier.
♪Alas, my yearning has come to naught♪
♪Love has died as raging waves did us part♪
♪The ocean is embracing the sky,
but it was merely a dream♪
♪The broken strings reverberate♪
♪Unable to feel each other in our hearts♪
♪Lamenting how hasty love and hate is♪
♪Alas, my yearning has come to naught♪
♪Love has died as raging waves did us part♪
I might not be able
to come here as often from now on.
His Highness is in a bad mood.
I must keep him company.
Besides,
I owed him for saving me.
It pains me to see him in pain.
But according to the legend,
it was you who saved His Highness.
Young Lady!
Actually...
[Crown Prince's Residence]
Young Lady.
Young Lady, why the long face?
Did the Crown Princess mistreat you?
We've said what we came to say.
Let's not see him again.
Ten years' worth of grudge.
It can't be resolved with only a few words.
But His Highness is a reasonable person.
Young Lady.
Once he's calmed down,
he will understand your frustration.
What saddens me the most
is that we must stand against each other.
We can never move forward as one again.
Anle.
It's been a long time.
How are you lately?
Even the silly brat
has become so mushy?
Anle.
Since you're already here,
why not stay a little longer?
I've learned how to cook.
I can show you a thing or two.
You can work at the Ren's Residence
as our cook.
For real?
Can I bring His Highness with me?
You may be
Di Ziyuan now,
and your relationship with His Highness
has changed,
but you will always be my sister.
That will never change.
If Jinyan were alive,
he'd be as old as you.
You are my brother too.
Come by when you have time.
If any of the girls catch your eye,
let me know.
I'll give you a hand.
Sure.
This manor is too cold.
Keep the hearth burning.
His Highness can't stand the cold weather.
Understood.
What is this?
The cloud cake from the corner shop.
I was waiting there
to get the freshest batch.
My mansion is tranquil and peaceful,
but you found a way to stroll outside.
My apologies.
Aside from sending snacks,
I don't know a better way
to cheer you up.
The cake doesn't disappoint.
It's time to get it together.
General.
Is there any news
coming from the Northwestern borders?
Nothing major.
It's just that Northern Qin
has been pillaging strongholds
at the borders.
Indeed.
Winter is colder than usual this year.
Northern Qin is covered with frost.
Nothing grows there.
Even the cattle died of starvation.
To survive, the people of Northern Qin
must rob the southern strongholds.
These cases have brought fear
to the people of Jing.
Our defense at the Northwestern border
has loosened.
I fear the Northern Qin's military
might seize the chance to stir up trouble.
Are you reinforcing the security?
Correct.
The border garrisons
are meant to defend the borders.
There are openings and flaws
in the Northwestern border defense.
It's hard to keep the two strongholds,
Qingnan and Junxian, safe from enemies.
I'm going inside to write up a letter.
Send it to the Northwest afterward.
Yes.
What will you do against their plan to approach
the Di family's old servants in the Northwest?
Di Ziyuan was supposed to be
the acquiescent Di Cheng'en.
But now, she's the unyielding Ren Anle.
Things are much more complicated now.
The Empress Dowager passed away.
Her death shook the court.
Now is the time to act.
Once the garrisons in Northwest are reinforced,
all of our plans will go down the drain.
If you get in the way of my plan,
not even death can absolve your mistake.
Your Highness.
As I said, always be patient.
The right timing has yet to come.
Han Zhongyuan
has been sitting on the throne for ten years.
The Di family's tragedy won't be enough
to dethrone him.
We must let the flame
burn even brighter.
Your top priority
is to help me take control of the Northwest,
not to stir up trouble in the court.
In that case,
why not mobilize the troops?
Take Anning hostage to control the troops.
Then, you can finish her off.
The Northwest will be devoid of a leader.
It will be ours to take.
If she is unwilling,
this is too big a risk!
Since we can't kill Anning
or approach the Di family's former servants,
bringing chaos to the imperial court of Jing
is our top priority.
We can spare Anning.
But there is someone that must die.
You want to kill Ren Anle?
She is the sole survivor of the Di family.
She is cunning.
If we can't make her work for us,
we must get rid of her before it's too late.
We'll use Han Zhongyuan
to eliminate her.
That should incite people's dissatisfaction
and cut off a loose end for us.
She gave Han Zhongyuan a slap in the face
in front of every official in the imperial court
and caused the Empress Dowager's death.
Even though the case
from ten years ago was overturned,
it doesn't change the fact that the person
on Dai Mountain
wasn't Ren Anle.
That alone constitutes
the crime of deceiving the Emperor.
[Lingxiang Pleasure House]
Fabrics! Have a look at the fabrics!
Homemade chairs!
Miss Di was born in a rural area,
but she doesn't bow down to evil
and stands righteously.
As for the Han family,
the Crown Prince has a great reputation outside,
but that doesn't hide
the imperial family's dirty secrets.
Despite her young age, Miss Di is already
known by everyone.
The way I see it, she is just as capable
as the legendary Di Shengtian.
The Jing State will soon have
a second Di Shengtian.
Yet another legend.
His Majesty is filial to the Empress Dowager.
Had she not taken her own life,
who knows how this situation can be resolved.
After committing such a heinous crime,
she can't even give a sound explanation.
As you wish,
Miss Di has earned the hearts of the people.
What else are you worried about?
When did these radical scholars
start gathering here?
I've never seen these people before.
They showed up
the day after the Empress Dowager's
passing.
Cursed Di Ziyuan.
Curse the second legend!
Sorry, Your Majesty.
It's only a bunch
of baseless gossip from the people.
Do not take them seriously.
Your Majesty.
You have nothing to worry about.
The Crown Prince has taken over
the morning court session.
Everything has been settled accordingly.
Accordingly?
I miscalculated.
For the past ten years,
I've so wishfully thought
there wouldn't be any threat.
Your Majesty.
For the past ten years,
the Jing State has had peace and prosperity
under your rule.
It's only a few baseless rumors.
Nothing in this land can threaten your place
as the Emperor.
Wrong.
There is someone capable of that.
For the past decade,
she's had me ensnared.
I couldn't act unless she did it first.
You mean her?
Even when the Di family was wiped out,
she had never been to the capital.
Perhaps
she is already dead.
She won't die so easily!
She won't show up,
but her grandniece
keeps stirring up trouble for me.
Her audacity is outrageous!
At this rate,
her words might come to pass.
She might become the second Di Shengtian.
No one
in this world
should reach for this throne of mine.
Sir.
His Majesty summons you.
Is this about Miss Di?
I thought it was already over.
The Di family's case was overturned
and their name was cleared.
But exposing the truth to the people
humiliated Han Zhongyuan.
He will not tolerate this.
He could contain his fury
during the birthday banquet.
But with the Empress Dowager gone,
someone will have to
face his fury.
That means you could get yourself killed.
I must keep Ziyuan safe.
Only I can take on this burden for her.
Sir.
-But...
-Linlang.
Don't try to persuade me.
I've made up my mind.
I know you understand me better than anyone else.
Understood.
So,
if I don't return,
you know what to do.
Once you've left,
I'll shut down Lingxiang Pleasure House
for a while.
If you never come back,
all the resources of the Qianyue Pavilion
will be handed over to Miss Di.
Good.
Sir!
[Ren's Residence]
Young Lady.
Your moves make your intention too obvious.
I'm not an old woman.
I can't be as ascetic as an abbot
in a temple.
A mere mortal can never break free from desires.
If you still have feelings for His Highness,
that is understandable.
He and I...
As long as he is the Crown Prince of Jing,
he will be standing
on the dead corpses of 80,000 soldiers.
I'm no longer the Crown Princess
appointed by the Founding Emperor
but the villain who cornered his grandmother
into taking her own life.
There is more hate than love between us.
Young Lady.
You've been obsessed with revenge
for the past ten years.
How will you move on?
It hasn't reached that point.
Let's go to Luo Mingxi.
It's time to plot our next move.
Very well.
Why is Lingxiang Pleasure House
closed in the daytime?
Yeah.
I asked about the song list for today.
[Lingxiang Pleasure House]
Do you hear some tunes?
[Wanshou Hall]
Luo Mingxi.
You feigned your surrender.
You did it so it'd be easier to operate
and help her overturn the case. Am I right?
What happened back then?
How did you swap Di Ziyuan out
with Di Cheng'en?
Your Majesty.
My family was close with the Di family.
I grew up with Di Ziyuan.
Marquis Jing'an ordered me
to take good care of her.
When that incident took place,
I took it upon myself to swap the two.
I did so
to preserve the continuity
of the Di family's bloodline.
Your loyalty to the Di family
is truly admirable.
But you were only a teenager.
Come clean.
Who is your accomplice?
There is none.
Come on.
Listen to this song.
I think it's...
It's the Song of Pure Melodies.
This is Miss Linlang's
most famous song back then.
I've heard this song in the past.
It wasn't as melancholic as it is now.
There is even
a tint of sadness from a farewell.
This is remarkable!
Luo Mingxi is in trouble.
Luo Mingxi! What are you hiding from me?
I am not hiding anything!
I...
shall accept my punishment.
Your Majesty.
I acted alone ten years ago.
I accept your punishment.
♪I know my heart will be uneasy♪
Very well.
Guards!
Lock Luo Mingxi in prison!
He is stripped of his title
as the Minister of Justice.
Find out who he was working with!
-Yes!
♪I can't dream to own you♪
♪But I'm willing to forsake my life for you♪
♪I'd go the distance for you.
May the light stay with you♪
♪Romance aside,
I fight for your destiny alongside you♪
♪You're my dream from the bygone youth.
Arriving at the end of my life♪
♪I bear no regrets. But when we reunite
in our next life? Will you still remember me?♪
(Official Luo)
(is cold and cruel on the outside,)
(but he cares a lot)
(about our dear Linlang.)
♪Please don't leave me in oblivion
when we part ways♪
♪I'd go the distance for you.
May the light stay with you♪
(Unless you get my permission,)
(do not act on your own.)
It doesn't matter if Di Cheng'en is dead.
But it's not worth it to trade your life for hers.
♪You're my dream from the bygone youth.
Arriving at the end of my life♪
♪I bear no regrets. But when we reunite
in our next life? Will you still remember me?♪
(Linlang.)
(Make sure)
everyone likes you.
(Only I can take on)
(this burden for her.)
(Linlang.)
(Don't bother persuading me.)
(I've made up my mind.)
(The Flower of Longing grows in Jingnan.
It can't withstand cold.)
(I've tried cultivating it,)
(but it never germinated.)
(Sir.)
(The seed germinated.)
Linlang.
You're always so resourceful.
♪You're my dream from the bygone youth.
Arriving at the end of my life♪
♪I bear no regrets. But when we reunite
in our next life? Will you still remember me?♪
[Crown Prince's Residence]
Your Highness.
Enough with the lonesome weiqi game.
Try this out.
I made some plum blossom jelly.
I learned a new recipe.
Why can't you put the same time and effort
into reading books?
Your Highness.
His Majesty
ordered to have Official Luo sent to prison.
Why?
Luo Mingxi used to swap Ziyuan out
with a mere beggar.
No matter how cautious he is,
when the case is overturned,
Ziyuan's identity will be unveiled.
The secret will be out eventually.
This is indeed a crime of deceiving the Emperor.
To save Ziyuan,
he'd go this far.
Your Highness,
the people have some objections
against this decision.
Someone is using this ruling to stir up trouble
in the imperial court.
Something is off, Your Highness.
Now that the Di family's name is cleared,
it means the allegation of their treason
was a setup.
Anle isn't the daughter of a sinned official.
And the imprisonment on Dai Mountain...
shouldn't be considered
a crime of deceiving the Emperor.
Your Highness.
Did I say something wrong again?
You are right.
To save Luo Mingxi,
we must focus on this detail.
Since the Di family's name has been cleared,
whatever he's done back then and now
was done out of loyalty to his master.
[Prison]
Your Highness.
It's quite filthy in here.
Mind the steps.
You tortured him?
Yes.
He did commit the crime of deceiving the Emperor.
Dismiss.
Yes.
Why would a man of your prestige
come to this filthy place?
Sorry.
I had a lavish life as a kid.
When the Di family was framed,
I had managed to save my neck.
But despite my young age,
I live like an old man.
Hang in there.
Why bother, Your Highness?
You shouldn't waste the fine medicine
on someone like me.
It's empty.
You always keep her safe better than me.
You can do the same.
You announced her real identity
to the public.
That saved us a lot of trouble.
Thankfully,
you are unlike your father.
Unlike him, you didn't go back on your promise
or betray anyone.
I failed to keep Ziyuan safe.
I failed ten years ago.
Even now, I still failed her.
You are the Crown Prince.
You can't have your mind
filled with romantic affairs.
If your father learned about this,
he'd be furious.
Luo Mingxi.
I know you turned yourself in
to keep Ziyuan safe.
But it no longer concerns the Di family.
It concerns the whole nation.
The Minister of Justice is sent to prison
for the crime of deceiving the Emperor.
This is a serious matter.
I know what you mean.
But if I...
I'd save you
if I were you.
I'm not doing this for Ziyuan,
but to maintain order in the nation.
There's no way to absolve me
of the crime of deceiving the Emperor.
You may be the Crown Prince,
but what can you do?
The Di family are no longer traitors.
Ziyuan is no longer the daughter
of a sinned official.
So she never needed
the imprisonment on Dai Mountain.
You do not disappoint.
I can't stay here too long.
I should get going.
I will figure out a way
to send you better medicine.
Take care of yourself.
[Prison]
I've talked to the guards inside.
When you visit him,
they won't stop you.
Thank you.
He hasn't been treated well
in prison.
If he sees you,
he should feel much better than seeing me.
No one would be happy to be locked up
in prison.
It's not right for His Majesty to punish him.
I'll do my best to argue with this decision.
But it's far more difficult than it seems.
Isn't it obvious enough?
His Majesty is out for a payback.
Don't bother apologizing on his behalf.
What we seek
is never your apologies.
Ziyuan.
You may hate me,
but you've always trusted me.
Isn't that right?
Yes.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't have given you that hand fan.
Trust me once more.
I will get Luo Mingxi out of there.
You will get the justice you deserve.
Very well.
Ziyuan.
The poem on the fan you gave me
does not mention the end
but only the beginning.
Is your feeling for me real or false?
The truth hasn't been announced to the public.
Between the two of us,
there is no room for love.
Don't give me that look.
I'm fine.
You call this fine?
I am fine.
But you, on the other hand,
is quite amazing.
You come and go
as you please in this prison.
I can do great things,
but your body isn't doing very well.
You know what kind of a place
the prison is.
Whoever comes in here
will never leave unscathed.
You're too delicate. All this torture
could have killed you.
You should have...
Ziyuan.
I know what you want to say.
But there are still uncertainties.
Do not act recklessly.
And you're being careless
for coming here.
If anyone sees this...
I'm here to see you.
How is that careless?
It's not what I mean.
I'm happy to see you.
Look at yourself.
How can you still be happy?
I was born to serve the Di family.
These wounds are nothing.
I don't regret what I did.
Don't let this bother you.
See this place?
Most of the torture devices were designed by me.
I know how to make it less painful.
Trust me on that.
See?
Before I came here,
I even brought good medicine with me.
Mingxi.
I'll get you out of this place.
Han Zhongyuan faces scrutiny
from everyone in the imperial court.
He wants to get rid of everyone close to you.
When I stood up, of course
he wouldn't have spared me.
Don't be concerned about me.
Above all, remain steadfast.
What do you mean?
Do you plan to stay here forever?
Do you want to die here?
Have you lost your mind?
Keep a level head.
For the past ten years,
we've had each other's backs.
Nothing else matters to me.
I can't give up on you.
(His Majesty learned that it was Luo Mingxi)
(who did a switcheroo)
(to save Di Ziyuan.)
(His Majesty was furious.)
(His Majesty ordered to strip Luo Mingxi
of all ranks and have him jailed.)
[Ministry of Justice]
(With that, the villains rejoice,)
(and the corrupt cheer.)
(Now, I must raise a question.)
Had it not been for Luo Mingxi's act of loyalty,
could Ren Anle have been able
to clear the name of the 80,000 lost souls?
Luo Mingxi protected the innocent,
so what crime has he committed?
(The Jing State is a nation of integrity,)
(a land for the honest.)
(How can we allow such injustice to take place)
once more?
His Majesty must have let anger
get the better of him.
Yes.
He arrested Marquis Zhongyi
to clear the Di family's name,
I bet he will listen to the people.
Official Luo, defender of the innocent!
He is not guilty!
[Ren's Residence]
Young Lady.
What's on your mind?
Have some oranges.
Is the crowd still at Chongyang Gate?
Yes.
The people are upset.
The Empress Dowager is gone,
but His Majesty has never charged her
with any crimes.
He even sent Official Luo to prison.
This is utterly unfair.
How unacceptable.
Everyone is rooting for you.
More and more scholars are kneeling
outside Chongyang Gate.
The people are enraged.
Things might get out of hand at this rate.
I've ordered Huang Pu to tighten the security.
He is honorable and rational.
Nothing could go wrong.
If His Majesty doesn't clarify,
he will lose all of his support.
He's been on the throne for over a decade.
He won't be wavered so easily.
No.
I can't wait any longer.
Today is the day
the matter with the Di family
comes to a conclusion.
[Lanqing Hall]
Greetings, Your Majesty.
You've always sided with the Di family
and forgotten your own family name.
Do you even care whether or not I am well?
I've never forgotten
that I am the Crown Prince of Jing.
Stand up.
One must first become upright
before one can be a ruler.
An emperor must not go back on his word.
As the Crown Prince,
I only speak the truth.
But I've failed as a son.
I am willing to accept my punishment.
Are you here to plead with me
to release Luo Mingxi?
Yes.
Luo Mingxi is imprisoned.
He was tortured.
His life hangs by a thread.
I think
it's time to release him.
What if I refuse?
You've kept him alive
for so long.
So, you mean to release him eventually.
Besides,
you know very well
that Luo Mingxi's action
wasn't the crime of deceiving the Emperor.
He did it out of his loyalty.
What he did
saved the Han family's reputation
because we didn't wrong Marquis Jing'an as badly.
I understand
that you have your frustration.
Therefore, you're reluctant to release him.
I shall share your worries.
So I propose
that Luo Mingxi is released.
Aren't you a sensible one?
Your Majesty.
I have another matter to mention.
Speak.
Outside Chongyang Gate
are scholars kneeling to plead
for the Di family.
When will they relent?
These fools
believe in baseless rumors
and think they can be the judge
of what is right or wrong!
Calm down, Your Majesty.
I must
congratulate you.
My imperial court is turned upside down!
Why are you congratulating me?
The 80,000 soldiers died.
All officers of the Di family
were wronged for ten years.
All of these happened because the Han family
acted out of greed.
If these scholars are willing to plead,
it means
they have faith in the Jing State.
They have faith that you will set up an example
by clearing the Di family's name
and bring justice to the world.
♪If I bet my all on it desperately♪
♪I know my heart will be uneasy♪
♪I give up on my light and hide it under a bushel♪
♪You're the moon in my heart♪
♪I can't dream to own you♪
♪But I'm willing to forsake my life for you♪
♪I'd go the distance for you♪
♪May the light stay with you♪
♪Romance aside♪
♪I fight for your destiny alongside you♪
♪You're my dream from the bygone youth♪
♪Arriving at the end of my life♪
♪I bear no regrets.
But when we reunite in our next life♪
♪Will you still remember me?♪
♪I've concealed my yearning for you♪
♪And guarded your smile♪
♪Please don't leave me in oblivion
when we part ways♪
♪I'd go the distance for you♪
♪May the light stay with you♪
♪Romance aside♪
♪I fight for your destiny alongside you♪
♪You're my dream from the bygone youth♪
♪Arriving at the end of my life♪
♪I bear no regrets.
But when we reunite in our next life♪
♪Will you still remember me?♪