♪By the riverside♪
♪I sow a seed of karma♪
♪Forlorn fates intertwine♪
♪Written in the stars♪
♪Should your passion smolder out♪
♪Will you give up on your ideal world?♪
♪Our past can only be entrusted to memories♪
♪I'm mooning over you♪
♪Amidst loneliness♪
♪Berthed in sleepless nights♪
♪You're my desire♪
♪That teems underneath♪
♪I'm drowned in your beautiful eyes♪
♪I'm mooning over you♪
♪Next to the Three-life Stone♪
♪I cross the Bridge of Forgetfulness♪
♪Gazing at moonlit nights♪
♪The moon appears brighter because of you♪
♪Leaning against the tower, it returns my gaze♪
♪Gazing at moonlit nights♪
♪The moon appears brighter because of you♪
♪Leaning against the tower, it returns my gaze♪
[The Legend of Anle]
[Adapted from a novel by Xing Ling]
[Episode 11]
Anle.
Bow.
[Han Zi'an's Tomb]
I thought Your Highness
was asking me to bow to you.
Why did Your Highness
bring me here?
The inscription on the tombstone
is left by the head of the Di family.
The late Founding Emperor stated in his will
that he wants to be buried in Cang Mountain alone.
Aside from the descendants
of the Han and Di families,
outsiders are not allowed.
Not even the Empress Dowager?
His Majesty commented
that His Late Majesty's action was preposterous.
It caused controversy over the imperial family.
Looking in this direction,
there's Jingnan.
Considering what you've mentioned earlier,
since Your Highness brought me here,
isn't that against tradition?
I want His Late Majesty to have a look at you.
His Late Majesty must be pleased.
Anle.
I can foresee
that we'd bring the Jing State
to greater heights together.
We wish the Crown Prince
a safe journey back to the capital.
Your Highness
meant more than that, right?
You're indeed capable.
The imperial court would not let this slide.
After we're back in the capital,
I'll officially report to His Majesty
that the credits of disaster relief
and the finding of evidence
of Zhong Liwen's corruption
belong to you.
You're aware that I've offended Marquis Zhongyi,
but you still want to officially report
to His Majesty for me, Your Highness.
You're forcing me
to side with you
and support you from now on, Your Highness.
Anle.
You're already involved in this tumult.
And you can't escape it.
As the Crown Prince, I would like
to ask you to stay by my side.
You refuse to marry me,
yet you're trying to tie me up with you.
Do you still remember, Your Highness?
I told you previously.
As long as it's your wish,
I'd try my best to fulfill it.
Since Your Highness wants to be friends,
let's be friends then.
As your friend,
I should be content
that I'm visiting
this imperial restricted area, Your Highness.
I'm glad
that you agree with this.
Although I can't be the Crown Princess,
I'll still try my best to achieve it.
We can still join sides
even if we're not married.
What about my betrothal gift
of the 30,000 naval forces?
I won't give up on that easily.
Your Highness.
That is not my way of doing things.
Even if I can't be the Crown Princess,
I want to stay close to you.
I would like to see whom you'd fall in love with.
It's that restless someone.
You're agile, Your Highness.
You're better than me.
I knew Your Highness would come
to Cang Mountain today.
I didn't expect that Official Ren
would be the surprise
in my plan.
I didn't expect this either.
We're both tricked by His Highness.
Your Highness.
What a good move.
You're killing two birds with one stone.
Your Highness tricked me
into coming to Cang Mountain.
Why did Your Highness use yourself as bait
just to lure me out?
You're the leader
of Marquis Zhongyi's hidden guard,
the expert swordsman of the Jing State.
When did Your Highness discover my identity?
You served me for seven years.
I trusted you indeed.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have
become my personal bodyguard
and led the Imperial Guards
of Crown Prince's Residence.
However, during the trip to Jiangnan,
Marquis Zhongyi has been too impatient.
You must give this
to Luo Mingxi,
the Minister of Justice, in two days.
[To Mingxi, Minister of Justice]
Yes, Your Highness.
He has left.
When did Your Highness
find out that he's suspicious?
The night of my assassination.
I told you
that we have a mole among us.
The ones who stay close to us
are Yuanqin, Yuanshu,
Wen Shuo, Jili,
and Jian Song.
The day when I acquired
the rice shop's ledgers,
I told him about the location
of the copper mine with a four-hour difference.
If anyone among them
is a mole...
Zhong Liwen would take action that night.
I see.
The assassination
wasn't meant to kill me and Anle.
It was a warning.
It was you, right?
Your Highness
discovered my talent and gave me opportunities.
Yet you still betrayed me.
I owe Marquis Zhongyi a favor too.
I have to do this.
Your Highness.
Take that.
He's no match for Han Ye.
Your Highness.
You're kind and lenient to me,
so you can't kill me.
I know
that you've been my friend for seven years.
It's worthwhile
knowing Your Highness!
Your Highness has expected this all along.
So, you didn't bring any of your guards
to Cang Mountain,
as you meant to spare his life.
However,
he was too proud,
and he refused to be much obliged to me.
He was obliged to Your Highness.
Otherwise, you'd be hurt, Your Highness.
Come on.
Your Highness.
We now call each other friends.
One day, if I turned against you,
what would you do, Your Highness?
Ren Anle.
If you doubt a person, do not use him.
If you use a man, do not doubt him.
I'm willing to believe in you.
The Crown Prince brought Ren Anle
to visit the late Founding Emperor's tomb?
That's right.
Is Ren Anle right about this?
That she helped to solve
the Crown Prince's problems,
so the Crown Prince has fallen in love with her.
Zhao Fu.
Why are you laughing? Be honest with me.
I dare not, Your Majesty.
I'll pardon you.
Think about it, Your Majesty.
Official Ren went on the Jiangnan trip.
She offends
Marquis Zhongyi's party again.
If His Highness
is really in love with Official Ren...
The Crown Prince abhors what is evil.
I always knew
that he's upset with Gu Yunnian.
He's trying to cow Gu Yunnian now.
Although he offends the official,
he builds his reputation
among the citizens as a just crown prince.
If so,
His Highness and Official Ren make a good team.
They didn't disappoint Your Majesty indeed.
The Crown Prince has my support.
However, Ren Anle has made a tough enemy.
If she only has the Crown Prince's support,
she's skating on thin ice.
What is your plan, Your Majesty?
After they return to the capital,
I need to discuss this with the Crown Prince.
Yes.
[Ministry of Justice]
Hua Zhen.
Do as I say.
Noted.
Come out.
Sir.
The newly appointed governor
has arrived safely at Jiangnan
under the protection of Qianyue Pavilion.
The flood control has started.
Well done.
How would you deal with Zhong Liwen?
It's rumored that Zhong Liwen
likes to find fault with those who disobey him.
What about we
make him a pair of shoes made of steel?
Let him be in the shoes of those men
and taste his own medicine.
You're trying to please Official Ren, right?
Zhong Liwen has always been opposing Ren Anle.
Now that he's in my hands,
I won't let him off easily.
However, Official Ren has affected
Gu Yunnian's influence in Jiangnan.
If she returns to the capital,
he will surely take revenge on her.
I'm worried about this too.
So, I sent someone
to submit a memorial to Han Zhongyuan.
Our forces
don't have enough power to protect Anle now.
Send someone
to keep an eye on Marquis Zhongyi.
All right.
[Marquis Zhongyi's Residence]
Jian Song is dead.
Ren Anle is still in one piece.
Looks like
I'm at the eye of the storm now.
That's right.
Lately, there has been a decrease
in the number
of officials visiting our residence.
They're afraid that they'd end up like Zhong Liwen.
How foolish of them.
If I fall,
they'd be affected.
My Lord.
What should we do now?
Don't worry.
We're still influential in the imperial court.
His Majesty wouldn't do anything
to us recklessly.
What about Ren Anle?
As long as she's still alive,
I can't live in peace!
Where are you going, My Lord?
I'm meeting His Majesty
to claim credits on Ren Anle's behalf.
My Lord.
Why would you do that?
She has done a good job.
I can't possibly
oppose her openly.
What do you think?
[Ande Gate]
After we pass the gate,
we'll be back in a worse tumult.
I have a question, Your Highness.
When we were at the peak of Cang Mountain,
you played a good game, Your Highness.
When did you include me in your game?
How did you find out about my trick then?
Well, that's because
you were honest with me.
Ren Anle.
Ever since you claimed
that you brought your naval forces
as your betrothal gift for me,
every step that you've taken aligns with my plan.
Is this a coincidence?
Instead of labeling it as a coincidence,
let's call it fate.
Why are you here?
I brought my naval forces along
because of you, Your Highness.
I don't care about your origin.
But I know
that you're kind and righteous.
I'll help you reach your goal.
I believe you'd be a good official.
You always think
that you know me well,
yet you never face your inner self, Your Highness.
You said that you never fall in love with me,
but I don't believe you.
I need to hurry back to the capital.
His Majesty needs to see
his future daughter-in-law.
Ren Anle.
You should spread your wings and soar.
You shouldn't limit yourself because of me.
Tanghulu for sale!
(Ren Anle has partnered with the Crown Prince.)
[Lingxiang Pleasure House]
(And they solved some big cases.)
(The disaster relief trip to Jiangnan)
[Caiwei Pavilion]
(has been nothing but a major success.)
(The flood victims gathered
at Wangjiang Terrace.)
(The disaster relief troops were bullying them.)
Suddenly, a woman stood up
and sliced the bucket of rotten soup in half
with her sword.
Who was she?
Ren Anle from Jingnan.
Great!
[Ren's Residence]
One day, if I turned against you,
what would you do, Your Highness?
Ren Anle.
If you doubt a person, do not use him.
If you use a man, do not doubt him.
I'm willing to believe in you.
Young Lady.
You were not around these days.
The capital has been really happening.
What happened?
Over one night,
news about you spread all over the capital.
It's bigger than when we first came to the capital,
asking the Crown Prince to marry you.
It's also rumored
that you're the key to the success
of the Mutian Prefecture trip.
Our young lady is indeed incredible.
However,
who's behind this, fueling the news?
I'm sure it's not a one-man job.
Aside from Official Luo, who else could it be?
His Highness.
Yes.
His Highness
cares for you very much.
Heaven is eminently fair.
The ruler is not biased.
He's a good crown prince.
However, I'm only Ren Anle.
Young Lady.
Have you
fallen in love with His Highness?
Yuanqin.
Do you still remember
the day when you barged
into the mountains of Jingnan?
I do.
If it weren't for you,
I'd have frozen to death.
You must always remember that day.
Apart from yourself,
no one would remember your own past.
Without the past,
we won't be who we are today.
Please don't
say that again.
Noted, Young Lady.
Luo Mingxi.
[Gu]
Congratulations, Anle.
Almost every official in the imperial court
owes you a favor.
In addition, we've finally
fostered our influence in Jiangnan.
The credits belong to me, Han Ye,
and you, who's staying away from the limelight.
What have you found during the trip to Jiangnan?
I followed the trace of the lotus silver pendant.
I found an old scholar named Zhong Hai.
Unfortunately, it has been ages.
He's nowhere to be found.
However, in the flower vase
in Zhong Liwen's residence,
we found the name list of the 80,000 soldiers.
There are ten survivors.
Their names have been circled.
Zhong Hai is one of them.
Looks like Zhong Hai is crucial.
I'll have Qianyue Pavilion investigate this.
Anle.
Half the officials
of the imperial court are siding with us.
Even if you don't join
the Crown Princess selection, you could still...
My father once said,
if one wants to rule the world,
he needs power and the people's support.
When I, Di Ziyuan, disguise myself as Ren Anle,
I'm using myself as bait.
If I don't step into this tumult,
how can I cause a commotion in the capital,
make the culprits drop their guard
and give themselves away?
Only then can I get closer to the truth.
But I'm scared that you might
get too invested in this
and forgot about the revenge.
Han Ye has managed the flood at Jiangnan well.
Regardless of his breadth of mind or wisdom,
he'd be a good ruler.
The Han family
annihilated the 80,000 soldiers
and my entire family.
He's
Han Ye.
I'm glad that you understand.
[Yuchen Hall]
I was talking
about the Crown Princess selection,
yet you're talking about Ren Anle.
Since you're well aware of the issue,
you should know that it's all Ren Anle's credits.
Did you know that before you came,
[Grand Historian, Wei Guan's report. Gu Yunnian]
the Minister of Justice and Gu Yunnian
were here to claim credits for Ren Anle?
She's here for the Crown Princess selection.
However, along her way,
she offends Gu Yunnian.
No matter if her only agenda is to marry you,
this woman
isn't simple.
I've allowed her to join
the Crown Princess selection.
She's yours now.
Please take care of her.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
However, I still want to say
-that I'm not...
-Hold on.
I'll host a celebratory feast today.
You can save your words
for Ren Anle.
Your Highness.
Can't you see me, Your Highness?
Here, Official Ren.
Cheers.
How is the dissection method
for the Ministry of Justice?
Your method is really helpful.
I officially reported to His Majesty
as I hope to work with you, Official Ren.
Don't let those matters of the heart
affect your career.
Well, I can't help it.
I'm all about romantic affairs.
Looks like
I'd let you down, Official Luo.
Besides, I'm the one who suggested
the Crown Princess selection.
If I quit before the selection,
all my efforts will be in vain.
Am I right, Your Highness?
Your Highness.
You criticized my tea etiquette.
Why are you sipping the tea like this now?
I...
Official Ren.
Congratulations.
Even the Marquis is congratulating me.
I'm really flattered.
You're too humble, Official Ren.
Everyone who's present
has experienced your capability.
Well...
Aside from you, My Lord.
You need to be careful.
Who knows, one day you'd experience it too.
You've successfully solved some cases.
You should thank me for that too.
You're right, My Lord.
Gu Qishan and Zhong Liwen
have become my stepping stones.
Speaking of which,
here's to you, My Lord.
This
goes to your daughter.
May she aid me in being selected
as the Crown Princess.
Ren Anle.
This is the main hall of the Imperial Palace.
So?
We're not on good terms.
Why can't I upset him, so he'd act recklessly?
Perhaps we could gain something.
Come on, Official Luo.
Cheers.
[Ren's Residence]
We've arrived.
It's your fault. You couldn't drink
and you didn't drink on my behalf.
So, I'm drunk.
You're not drunk.
Stop pretending.
Get up.
Aren't you pretending as well?
Ren Anle. Stop using
the Crown Princess position as your excuse.
Excuse?
We've been through so much together.
Do you still think like that?
Although I lost
to the late Founding Emperor's will,
I didn't lose to Di Ziyuan.
No matter what you say,
she's going to leave the mountain soon.
We must observe the etiquette.
Who said that then?
When we were at the inn in Jiangnan,
you said that a decade of dwelling
stays in the past.
I would see Ziyuan every day from now on.
Of course the dwellings
will eventually turn into bygones.
I didn't expect Your Highness
to go back on your word.
Ren Anle.
I must keep my promise and protect her.
I don't care!
Let's go to the Ministry of Justice.
Yes.
I didn't expect Your Highness
to visit me at this hour.
As friends,
can't I visit without notice?
We can grow closer to each other
or grow apart from each other.
What would we be, Your Highness?
That's a question.
When I was in Jiangnan, I thought
that it'd be great if you were there.
Then, I could talk to you
about my problems.
You could have intimate conversations
with Ren Anle too.
Am I right, Your Highness?
I can't tell her about it. Not at all.
Why not?
She didn't know what happened a decade ago.
However, Ren Anle is smart,
so she'd understand it right away.
How would she not understand you, Your Highness?
As for you, Your Highness,
the more you insist,
the more doubtful you sound.
That's not the case.
Yes, it is.
Luo Mingxi.
I admire her character and talent, that's all.
Aren't you the same?
So, Your Highness is visiting me
to ask about
why I claimed credits on Ren Anle's behalf.
I was just wondering.
Why do you care about Ren Anle so much too?
"Too"?
What an apt choice of word.
I'm curious.
You're just and never collude
with anyone in the imperial court.
You're a lone wolf.
Since when you're close to her?
I told you, Your Highness.
Please let her work with me.
In the Ministry of Justice?
As I'm all alone in this world too.
I'm not sure since when
I can't fathom your thoughts.
Look.
You said that you want to marry Di Ziyuan,
yet you refuse to let me get closer to Ren Anle.
Why is that so?
[Crown Prince's Residence]
Your Highness. You've repainted it, right?
I didn't expect Your Highness
to lose your nerves.
I haven't seen her in a long time. That's why.
It'd be a happy ending once you meet each other.
Congratulations in advance, Your Highness.
However, is this the end
of your relationship with Anle?
Although I've never seen
the one who's living in Dai Mountain
that you've talked about,
from your words,
she sounds more like Anle.
What a shame.
Any other news?
Your Highness.
After the announcement
of the Crown Princess selection,
the young and unmarried ladies
are competing fiercely.
Lingxiang Pleasure House is creating
more bets.
Some bet on the daughter of General Zhao.
If Ziyuan leaves the mountain
and comes to the capital,
she'd be everyone's target.
Ren Anle advised His Majesty
to allow the orphaned girl
from the Di family to leave the mountain.
What is she up to?
This isn't as simple as it looks.
Ren Anle often acts erratically.
You know it too.
She's taking advantage of the situation.
The bigger the mess, the better it is.
The orphaned girl of the Di family
must never leave the mountain.
My Lord.
We were ordered
to confiscate the Di family's assets.
The orphaned girl of the Di family
saw everything.
[Marquis Zhongyi]
If she returns to the capital,
she'd surely take her revenge on us.
She's just an orphaned girl.
She's incapable of that.
Moreover, there are people who don't wish
to see her here.
Even if His Majesty agrees,
Empress Dowager won't allow that.
My Lord,
let's just wait and observe.
I saw that a lot of officials
are recommending your daughters.
Perhaps your daughter
would be the Crown Princess.
Are you teasing me?
The Crown Princess selection
is the state's priority.
I'm at the eye of the storm now.
Any missteps would bring us down.
They're really oblivious.
They keep submitting memorials to the Emperor.
Everyone is rooting for your daughter.
My Lord.
There's no need to sigh over this matter.
[Marquis Zhongyi's Residence]
Ask them to stop submitting memorials
to His Majesty
to appoint the daughter
of Marquis Zhongyi as the Crown Princess.
Take note that do not
stop the submission of memorials all at once.
Do it gradually.
Noted.
[Jingxin Hall]
(Zi'an.)
(As long as I'm still alive,)
(Di Ziyuan can never leave the mountain.)
(Since she wants to leave the mountain,)
(she can't be Di Ziyuan.)
[The Emperor orders Di Ziyuan to change her name
to Di Cheng'en before leaving the mountain.]
Your Highness, His Majesty orders
Di Ziyuan to change her name to Di Cheng'en
before leaving the mountain.
What?
Di Ziyuan has to change her name
to Di Cheng'en to leave the mountain?
Di Ziyuan could leave the mountain
due to His Majesty's grace.
Hence, from today onwards,
she'd be named Di Cheng'en
to commemorate the imperial family's grace.
Why are they tormenting Ziyuan like this?
Your Highness.
Do you think that Miss Di
would change her name?
The incident that happened a decade ago.
Ziyuan
would never think
that she was pardoned by His Majesty.
[Lingxiang Pleasure House]
Where are you going, Your Highness?
I'm going to the palace to see His Majesty.
How could His Majesty
humiliate Ziyuan like this?
This isn't His Majesty's order, Your Highness.
The Empress Dowager is behind this too.
If you offend His Majesty now,
Miss Ziyuan would be
in a more difficult situation.
I need to be alone.
A stab in the heart.
His orders are rather harsh.
Looks like Han Zhongyuan is not
as kind as we thought.
No matter the treatment, it's the Emperor's grace.
You don't have to be upset.
If you have a strong heart,
I'd be relieved.
You can be relieved then.
He killed my whole family,
yet he spared my life.
So of course it's a favor from him.
Changing my name to leave the mountain
is of course a huge favor...
That's enough!
I know you well, Anle.
You would never succumb to your enemy.
(Ziyuan.)
(It has been a decade since we last met.)
(How are you doing?)
(Judging from your character,)
(you'd never change your name
to leave the mountain.)
(I might not see you for the rest of my life.)
(I hope that you're doing well)
(on Dai Mountain.)
[Yongning Temple, Dai Mountain]
It isn't right.
[Di Ziyuan]
This isn't right either.
We play weiqi all day and all night.
It's so annoying.
What's there to learn?
You must know how to play weiqi,
since she's good at weiqi.
But I dislike playing weiqi.
If you refuse to play weiqi today,
we'll play it another day.
Mu Qing.
I heard four bird calls today.
Why are there only three birds?
[Di Ziyuan's bodyguard, Mu Qing]
One of them flew away.
It's all right.
It doesn't matter
how many birds there are.
This is the 590th feather
that I've embroidered.
How much more to go
until I can leave this place?
The fake Di Ziyuan on the mountain.
If she gladly accepts the order,
people would be doubtful of her.
You can address me as Ziyuan.
I'll call you Mingxi.
If it weren't for you
who sent me to Jingnan back then,
I wouldn't be who I am today.
She's a poor girl with a pitiful background.
Because of me, she's been trapped there
for a decade.
To survive,
she changed her name.
I can't destroy her life
for my own agenda.
We should let her leave the mountain.
We should
return her freedom to her.
[Caiwei Pavilion]
[Yin Wenzi]
It's his handwriting.
I'll have this.
All right.
I will take this book.
Your Highness?
This book is meaningful to me.
Can you go with another one?
I'll buy you whichever you want.
Another book?
Your Highness always promises me
something I don't want.
What's the rule of Anle Abode?
We want it, and we get it.
If we can't get it,
we snatch it.
Hence, I must get this book.
You can have this gold
if you want.
Yes.
Anle.
This book is useful to His Highness.
I can pay you twice the gold.
Do you think that we're poor?
Ren Anle.
If you really like it,
I can produce a copy of this book for you. Okay?
Well,
I'm okay with that.
However, you must tell me
why you must get this book.
This was the belonging of Ziyuan's late father.
So I'm getting this for her.
So, it's for my love rival.
All the more reason why I can't let you have it.
Give it to me.
Take it if you can.
Stop it, Ren Anle.
You need to catch it, Your Highness.
Catch it if you can.
My gosh.
I'm sorry, sir.
Stop laughing.
Clean up the mess.
Let's go.
Come on.
Ren Anle.
Listen.
I know that you're a good friend
who tells right from wrong.
This book contains
Ziyuan's father's handwriting.
His Majesty ordered Ziyuan
to change her name so as to leave the mountain.
If she decides not to obey,
she can have this book as a temporary comfort.
I heard that Your Highness
has sent her
loads of books throughout the decade.
What if she's lazy
to read through the books?
She won't.
Are you sure?
When Ziyuan was little,
she was already smart and hardworking.
Yet, she's imprisoned on Dai Mountain for a decade.
Let alone reading books,
I'd be lazy to even utter a word.
You're not her.
You will never understand.
When Your Highness talks about Di Ziyuan,
you're boring.
If she doesn't leave the mountain,
I'd be at an advantage.
How about this?
If she doesn't leave the mountain,
I'll return this to the rightful owner.
Deal?
Let's see if she'd leave the mountain.
A table for two esteemed guests.
[Don't simply use an official.]
(It's indeed your handwriting.)
(Father.)
(I'll surely clear the Di family's name.)
♪If I bet my all on it desperately♪
♪I know my heart will be uneasy♪
♪I give up on my light and hide it under a bushel♪
♪You're the moon in my heart♪
♪I can't dream to own you♪
♪But I'm willing to forsake my life for you♪
♪I'd go the distance for you♪
♪May the light stay with you♪
♪Romance aside♪
♪I fight for your destiny alongside you♪
♪You're my dream from the bygone youth♪
♪Arriving at the end of my life♪
♪I bear no regrets.
But when we reunite in our next life♪
♪Will you still remember me?♪
♪I've concealed my yearning for you♪
♪And guarded your smile♪
♪Please don't leave me in oblivion
when we part ways♪
♪I'd go the distance for you♪
♪May the light stay with you♪
♪Romance aside♪
♪I fight for your destiny alongside you♪
♪You're my dream from the bygone youth♪
♪Arriving at the end of my life♪
♪I bear no regrets.
But when we reunite in our next life♪
♪Will you still remember me?♪