♪By the riverside♪
♪I sow a seed of karma♪
♪Forlorn fates intertwine♪
♪Written in the stars♪
♪Should your passion smolder out♪
♪Will you give up on your ideal world?♪
♪Our past can only be entrusted to memories♪
♪I'm mooning over you♪
♪Amidst loneliness♪
♪Berthed in sleepless nights♪
♪You're my desire♪
♪That teems underneath♪
♪I'm drowned in your beautiful eyes♪
♪I'm mooning over you♪
♪Next to the Three-life Stone♪
♪I cross the Bridge of Forgetfulness♪
♪Gazing at moonlit nights♪
♪The moon appears brighter because of you♪
♪Leaning against the tower, it returns my gaze♪
♪Gazing at moonlit nights♪
♪The moon appears brighter because of you♪
♪Leaning against the tower, it returns my gaze♪
[The Legend of Anle]
[Adapted from a novel by Xing Ling]
[Episode 35]
Yuanqin.
We barely met,
and now, we have to part ways.
Please take care of yourself.
Don't get hurt.
Safety is a luxury
at the moment.
Take good care of yourself too.
I'm powerful.
Don't worry.
Once the war is over,
I'll go and see you in Jingnan.
Okay.
Take this.
You embroidered it for me?
I'll carry it with me.
Yuanqin, Wen Shuo.
We're leaving now.
Keep the pouch with you.
It'll protect you.
My. It's the Flower of Longing.
Yuanqin.
Wait for me in Jingnan!
Your Highness,
we have circulated the info
as per your instructions.
Good.
I want Lengbei to know
that the Di Troops await him at Qingnan.
Noted.
[Qingnan City]
Your Highness.
Look.
Yuanqin gave it to me.
Turns out that when the Flower of Longing blooms,
it can be so stunning.
Your Highness,
after the war,
let's go to Jingnan
to visit Anle and Yuanqin.
If you fancy Yuanqin,
don't wait.
Go to her now.
But the war isn't over.
I can't leave you now.
Even when the war is over,
I won't leave you.
Wen Shuo.
Remember what I said when I gave you
your name?
Yes.
You want me to become a fine, virtuous
gentleman
who shines as bright as a star.
Jinyan.
You
have lived up to that name.
Your Highness.
What did you just call me?
Your real name is Di Jinyan.
You are Ziyuan's younger brother
and the heir of the Di family.
I faked your death
and gave you a new identity.
You were young back then,
so I did it
without asking for your permission.
I'm sorry.
Your Highness.
Why
tell me the truth now?
Because no one knows what will happen
in this war.
I don't want you to die ignorant.
And I hate to make you miss the chance
to meet your family and loved ones.
You are the descendant of the Di family.
I understand if you resent me.
But I do not regret
what I did back then.
Because you grew up
so well.
Your Highness,
why would I resent you?
You protected me for a decade.
You taught me how to read and write.
You taught me what's right and wrong.
Everyone in the capital
knows that you raised me.
Everyone had their eyes on you.
And you were only a teenager back then.
Yet you took me under your wing
despite the scrutiny.
Without you, there would be no Wen Shuo,
Your Highness.
Why would I resent you?
Good.
Jinyan.
You're a grown-up now.
It's time to return you to Ziyuan.
Head to Junxian City now.
No.
I'm staying here with you to defend Qingnan City.
Jinyan.
Ziyuan has carried the burden of the Di family
for far too long.
You're the only family she has.
It's time
for you to keep her company.
I protected you
not only because you are the descendant
of the Di family,
but also because I want to protect the peace.
Jinyan.
Be a wise subject.
Don't let me down.
Ziyuan.
Mingxi...
You're still alive.
I am indeed.
You hid your survival from me.
Do you know how many tears I shed for you?
It was an emergency.
I didn't have the time to tell you.
I'm sorry.
But I owe it
to Han Ye.
He saved me.
(Han Ye?)
(He saved Mingxi?)
He could have told me.
You were hell-bent on rescuing me back then.
But the soldiers were mad.
He didn't want to risk it by telling you the truth.
The more you hate him,
the more convincing the whole act will be.
That's the Crown Prince, all right.
As shrewd as ever.
Anle.
We're close anyway.
Can you tell me more
about your brother?
If Jinyan was alive,
he would be around your age now.
You're like a brother to me.
Gentlemen.
He is my younger brother
who boasts a photographic memory.
Don't try to fool him.
(In the capital,)
(I have passed by
the Residence of Marquis Jing'an many times,)
(but never once did I care)
(about what people said)
(about the Di family.)
(It was all in the past.)
(Besides, I was Wen Shuo.)
(The Di family had nothing to do with me.)
(But now, I want to ask my sister.)
(How does it feel)
(to carry the burden)
(of the injustice of the 80,000 souls)
(alone?)
(Was it exhausting?)
(When she needed me the most,)
(I wasn't there.)
(Perhaps)
(I should stay by her side now.)
Your Highness.
[Loyal Souls of the Di Family,
Steadfast Noble Characters]
(I, Han Ye, hereby swore)
(to protect and defend)
(the justice)
(of the Jing State.)
I make it my lifelong duty
to bring peace
and prosperity
to my subjects.
It's nearly impossible to reconcile
the differences between the Dis and the Hans.
But time has changed.
Whether I'm Wen Shuo or Di Jinyan,
I should stay by His Highness.
For he had raised me.
I would share
your duty with you.
I would use my life to serve you,
to help you fulfill your duty.
My ancestors from high above,
bear witness to the oath I'm taking today.
Grant upon my nation longevity.
Long live
the Jing State!
Your Highness.
Why are you here?
I'm staying.
I aspire to be like you.
I want to fight fearlessly
on the battlefield.
I will not back down.
Do you know what's at stake?
Are you trying to throw your life away?
Leave now!
Sorry, I cannot comply.
Leave!
No!
Guards!
I don't want to go to Junxian City.
Take him to Junxian City.
No, Your Highness.
Let go of me!
Your Highness.
Ziyuan is in good company.
But you only have me.
Just like my bloodline, it is irrefutable.
I was raised by you alone.
No one can change that.
Your Highness.
Please let me stay with you.
Okay.
We're in this together.
Yes.
And we will defeat those Northern Qin men.
Everyone from Jing will know
that you
have a formidable
and loyal subordinate.
Let's go.
Let's go to Qingnan City.
Okay.
[Northern Qin Outpost]
I have news!
Yes?
Your Highness,
our scouts reported
that the Di Troops
are patrolling Qingnan Mountain.
Our spies also added
that Di Ziyuan stationed the command center
in that location.
Qingnan Mountain?
[Qingnan Mountain, Qingnan City]
That's a good place for a grave.
Since Di Ziyuan is eager to stay there,
I will grant
her death wish.
[Northern Qin Outpost]
I heard from other soldiers
that the Northern Qin
is less active now in the vicinity.
But my intel told me
that
they are coming to us.
Things can change in an instant on a battlefield.
And it's difficult to determine
the veracity of the information.
Wait.
What is happening?
The Northern Qin Army at Qingnan Pass
is on the move.
They are divided into two groups.
One went to Qingnan City.
The other went to Qingnan Mountain.
Qingnan Mountain?
What for?
The location is the stronghold of His Highness'
forces.
What?
Let's go.
Beware of falling rocks!
Your Highness, your plan is working.
Stay calm, my comrades.
Climb up!
We have thousands of men.
We are not afraid of them!
Charge!
Your Highness,
nearly all of Lengbei's men
are deterred by the falling rocks.
Don't celebrate too early.
Lengbei mobilizes all the troops of his nation.
We are severely outnumbered.
It's just that we have
the geographical advantage
and Lengbei was caught off guard.
That's why we have the upper hand now.
However, their losses here
will only make them more desperate.
Brace yourself.
Yes, sir.
Your Highness?
I have been waiting for you.
Even if you want to kill Ziyuan today,
you'll have to protect me first.
We are not far from Junxian City.
Powerful as you may be,
you are unable to protect her.
We're in a dire situation.
If I fall in Qingnan Mountain,
what will killing Ziyuan achieve
for His Majesty?
You're using your life
to trap us with you.
Why are you taking this unnecessary risk?
Is Di Ziyuan
worth the sacrifice?
I am the heir of the Han family.
I will own up mistakes my family made
and atone
for their sins.
Whether Ziyuan is worth my sacrifice or not,
that will be decided
by our subjects in the future.
Why are you doing this, Your Highness?
Our nation is in peril.
Our enemy is at our doorstep.
I am a man of Jing.
I fight.
Even if Ziyuan was out of the picture,
I would still be here to fight my enemy
to my death.
Oh, no.
The Northern Qin men
walked over their fallen brothers
and charged in.
Those madmen.
All right then.
At your command, Your Highness.
Charge!
Prince of Northern Qin, Mo Bei.
I have been waiting for you.
Han Ye.
Why are you here?
Di Ziyuan isn't in Qingnan City?
You lied to me.
It's the oldest trick in the book.
To scale this mountain,
I lost 30% of my men.
If I can't kill Di Ziyuan,
I'll just make do with your life.
Take it if you can.
The Plum Blossom Agents?
The Jing State even deployed
its own secret forces
to ambush me.
It seems like both our nations
have played the trump card.
You're mistaken.
The much stronger Di Troops are not here yet.
There are only my men
on this mountain today.
And we are enough
to avenge Anning.
Arrogant fools.
Wipe them out!
Charge!
He planned
around your safety.
It was his plan to use the letter
to lure me here too?
Han Ye is...
-Young Lady.
Han Ye.
Eat this.
Using poison?
You're shameless.
You are a skilled fighter,
but you're nothing without your vision.
Your Highness!
You think the Plum Blossom Agents
can trap me here?
Whoever kills the Crown Prince of Jing
will be promoted three ranks above
and awarded a thousand gold taels.
Shoot!
Don't just stand there.
Attack!
Your Highness.
Your Highness!
Han Ye.
This ambush was meant for Di Ziyuan.
(I'm glad Ziyuan doesn't have to)
(suffer this.)
Your Highness.
Wen Shuo.
How many people do we have left?
Your Highness,
not many.
But your plan worked.
The Northern Qin Army was defeated.
Only Lengbei and his hundred-odd men remain.
Your Highness,
we turned the tide
thanks to your strategy.
Hang in there.
Capture Han Ye alive.
I'll use him to negotiate
with the Jing State for some land.
Advance if you dare.
Come!
Let's see how long
you can last.
Wen Shuo, go.
We have achieved our goal.
The threat of Northern Qin is no more.
We're now stuck
in a stalemate with Lengbei and his men.
And the only thing they can have now
is my life.
No, I won't leave you.
I won't let them hurt you.
I
have been
waiting for this moment for a long time.
The fate of Anning and me
was predestined
the moment the Di Troops
died in Qingnan Mountain.
Even our death
cannot redeem it.
No.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, you're not going to die.
Fetch a message to Ziyuan for me, please.
Tell her
that my dream
is to see
a peaceful and harmonious
Jing State.
Ask her to witness it on my behalf.
No, you'll tell Ziyuan all that yourself.
You'll do it yourself.
(Han Ye.)
(Why did you have to do this?)
Lengbei.
To kill Ziyuan, you exhausted all your men.
You are hardly a threat now.
It's a shame
that I couldn't kill you to avenge Anning.
But I'm the Crown Prince of Jing.
You will not capture me.
Because I would rather die
than surrender
to my enemy!
Your Highness!
No!
Your Highness...
Your Highness!
-Your Highness.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, this is bad.
Di Ziyuan and her army are here.
Retreat!
Wen Shuo.
Where is Han Ye?
He...
He jumped off the cliff.
What?
His Highness was shot before he made the leap.
One arrow hit his vital.
He knew he wasn't long for this world,
so he jumped to his death
instead of letting
the Northern Qin
defile his body.
His Highness
is dead.
He was shot?
An arrow hit his vital?
Han Ye is dead?
No way.
He promised to clear my family's name.
I protected the world.
I protected the people.
If he's dead,
who's going to share the joy with me?
This can't be it.
Ziyuan.
Official Di,
His Highness used his life
to save yours.
He did
everything he could.
He wanted you to live.
I don't need anyone's protection!
He owes me an explanation.
So many people from my family died in vain.
Does he think his life
is enough to make amends?
-Official Di.
-Ziyuan.
Official Di.
Ziyuan.
Let go of me!
-Let go!
-Official Di.
Let go of me.
Ziyuan, I'm Di Jinyan.
Ziyuan.
I'm Di Jinyan.
I'm your younger brother.
(Ziyuan.)
You're not alone.
You get along with Wen Shuo, don't you?
He is fond of you too.
You can view him as your little brother.
Ziyuan.
Don't leave me.
You are
Jinyan?
His Highness asked me to tell you
that his dream
was to see a peaceful and harmonious
Jing State.
He entrusted this world to you
and hoped
that you would witness
the prosperity of this realm
on his behalf.
Han Ye...
Han Ye.
Han Ye!
Han Ye...
Yuanqin.
What brought you here?
How is Ziyuan doing?
Young Lady kept to herself inside the tent.
She refuses to see anyone.
She is grieving.
She won't dwell on it, I'm sure.
She just needs some time.
I know you're sad too.
But you need to eat something.
Take a few bites.
Okay?
Thank you, Yuanqin.
Leave it there.
I'll eat it later.
Yuanqin,
I keep wondering
if things would be better
if I were the one
who jumped off the cliff.
His Highness and Ziyuan worked so hard
throughout their lives.
It shouldn't have ended like this.
Wen Shuo...
It's okay.
I know what you're about to say.
I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
His Highness is gone.
So I need to protect Ziyuan now.
I'm sure His Highness
would be immensely proud of you
if he saw you here.
I want to grow up.
I want to become stronger.
Perhaps I can never
be like His Highness.
But at least, I want to be
someone who shines like a star,
as he used to tell me.
(What I said)
on Cang Mountain still holds true.
If you want...
No, I don't.
When the Flower of Longing blooms in Jingnan,
will you write to me and tell me?
No.
Your Highness, you said
that you wouldn't let me affect you.
The same applies to me.
Forget the melancholic farewell.
Until the war is over,
we stay in our respective roles.
We shall not see each other again.
Ziyuan.
It's me.
Come in.
Ziyuan.
How are you feeling?
Come. Sit down.
Jinyan.
How have you been
all these years?
Good.
I asked even though I know the answer.
Han Ye saved you?
Back then,
His Highness sneaked me into his residence.
He raised me.
I see.
He raised you well.
When did you find out?
Not long ago.
His Highness wanted me to follow you
to Junxian City for my safety.
But I refused to leave him.
He then told me the truth.
So he already planned to give his life away
when he bode me farewell.
Everything was within his plan.
Ziyuan.
Please don't...
Worry not.
I won't do anything stupid.
I have to look after you.
Ziyuan...
Jinyan.
Give me a moment alone, please.
I'll be fine.
Ziyuan.
Just leave me alone.
[Jiaxian Gate]
(The Crown Prince jumped off the cliff)
(and had since gone missing.)
(Mo Bei has fled.)
(The Northern Qin Army lost its leader.)
(Taking advantage of this situation,)
(Di Ziyuan attacked fiercely)
(and defeated the Northern Qin,)
(bringing an end to this war.)
(As fate would have it,)
(the Dis and the Hans worked together)
(to protect our homeland.)
(Now,)
(the Crown Prince's sacrifice
has broken the impasse,)
(and Di Ziyuan returns to the capital
in a sorrowful victory.)
(After more than a decade of grievances,)
(is there still a chance for reconciliation?)
[Yuchen Hall]
Your Majesty.
So?
Any news about Han Ye?
Your Majesty,
we searched far and wide
around Qingnan Mountain
but to no avail.
I'm fine.
Keep on searching.
Search for him.
Yes, Your Majesty.
[Crown Prince's Residence]
♪You and I are distant
like the clouds and the oceans♪
♪Contemplating and remembering,
but where do we belong?♪
♪Wondering about the past,
scrutinizing the feelings of resentment♪
His Highness was an avid reader.
He had read every book
in this hall.
♪Time whispers impermanence in our ears♪
In addition to his reading,
he also monitored my studies
so that I could become a wise subject.
He put the Jing State
above himself.
There is no better crown prince
than him.
♪Despite having regrets,
sadness overwhelms them all♪
For the greater part of his life,
Di Ziyuan was his object of obsession.
The only woman he ever loved
is
you.
♪Love has died as raging waves did us part♪
♪The ocean is embracing the sky,
but it was merely a dream♪
♪The broken strings reverberate♪
♪Unable to feel each other in our hearts♪
In the past decade,
His Highness would try to draw Di Ziyuan
when he was bored.
But every time, he failed.
Until you showed up.
He once told me
that the one who stole his heart
wasn't the Di Ziyuan in his imagination,
but the Ren Anle he knew.
♪Contemplating and remembering,
but where do we belong?♪
♪Wondering about the past,
scrutinizing the feelings of resentment♪
(I once fell for a woman called Ren Anle.)
♪Time whispers impermanence in our ears♪
(But in this life,)
(I will keep Di Ziyuan safe.)
♪It was meant to be a moment's pleasure♪
♪I turn around, hiding my loving gaze♪
"Many moons have passed since we last met.
Our reunion marks the beginning
of another thread of yearning."
♪Despite having regrets,
sadness overwhelms them all♪
♪Frowning on the moon on a desolate fall night♪
♪Alas, my yearning has come to naught♪
♪Love has died as raging waves did us part♪
♪The ocean is embracing the sky,
but it was merely a dream♪
"Many moons have passed since we last met.
Our reunion marks the beginning
of another thread of yearning."
♪Unable to feel each other in our hearts♪
Ziyuan!
[Ren's Residence]
♪Lamenting how love and hate
can become a cruel joke♪
Young Lady.
Take a sip.
I implore you.
♪If I bet my all on it desperately♪
♪I know my heart will be uneasy♪
♪I give up on my light and hide it under a bushel♪
♪You're the moon in my heart♪
♪I can't dream to own you♪
♪But I'm willing to forsake my life for you♪
♪I'd go the distance for you♪
♪May the light stay with you♪
♪Romance aside♪
♪I fight for your destiny alongside you♪
♪You're my dream from the bygone youth♪
♪Arriving at the end of my life♪
♪I bear no regrets.
But when we reunite in our next life♪
♪Will you still remember me?♪
♪I've concealed my yearning for you♪
♪And guarded your smile♪
♪Please don't leave me in oblivion
when we part ways♪
♪I'd go the distance for you♪
♪May the light stay with you♪
♪Romance aside♪
♪I fight for your destiny alongside you♪
♪You're my dream from the bygone youth♪
♪Arriving at the end of my life♪
♪I bear no regrets.
But when we reunite in our next life♪
♪Will you still remember me?♪