KKULBEE EDUCATION
It's been so long. It feels like…
A prison.
What was the point of
spending late nights at school?
Ja-yeon.
Yeah?
Why did you transfer
so suddenly back then?
Did something happen to you?
Where is she? I want her back!
Hand her over!
Where's your mom?
Who's the bastard she ran off with?
Nam Ja-yeon! Where the hell are you?
-Get out.
-Let go of me!
-Nam Ja-yeon!
-Get out!
-Get off of me, you bastard!
-Stop it!
Come out!
Come out here, Nam Ja-yeon!
Ja-yeon.
He left. It's okay now.
You must've been so scared.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Don't apologize.
It's all right now.
It's okay.
He'll come back, again and again.
He'll show up at school too.
Ja-yeon, look at me.
That won't happen.
You can transfer schools
and we'll find you a new foster home
where you can stay temporarily.
Auntie and I will protect you
no matter what.
Okay?
I told you
that my body and mind are one.
My body is where my mind is right now.
JA-YEON
Ma'am?
What a relief.
That could've been bad.
What?
10 MINUTES AGO
HAE-YEONG
So you're telling me,
Ahn Woo-jae was watching…
-Because of him, you--
-Wouldn't it look suspicious
if you left with our wedding picture
and your luggage
right after the housewarming?
He left a while ago.
Did he come back?
No way.
Did he notice?
How is that important right now?
You just kissed me.
I…
Was that your first time?
I'm so sorry.
I mean it.
The thing is,
you left your phone
and Woo-jae was looking,
so I was worried we'd get caught.
So you can just kiss someone
whenever you see fit,
with no feelings behind it?
A kiss?
That was a peck, not a kiss.
Our lips barely touched.
Ji-uk,
earlier…
I want to know…
how far you can go
to keep up this fake act.
If you can do whatever
without feeling anything,
then I just want to have fun with you,
Son Hae-yeong.
EPISODE 8
-Take care.
-Thank you.
Oh, jeez!
Money first, please.
Right, of course.
-You need to pay first.
-Right, I was just about to pay.
-Come this way.
-Okay.
SALINE SOLUTION
I saw something disgusting
and had to wash my eyes.
That's not enough.
You have to wash your brain too.
Sorry?
-But my brain…
-It's 1,500 won.
Of course.
-I have a question.
-Yes?
The old man who collects waste paper
said something earlier.
What did he say?
He mentioned an angel part-timer
who used to work here.
Oh, Ji-uk?
As in Kim Ji-uk, right?
He's our neighborhood angel.
I heard he disappeared a few months ago
and recently moved into a rooftop room.
So I heard, but I haven't seen him.
Well…
But why do you ask?
I'm a regular here and I was just curious.
A lot of women asked about him
after he quit.
And now a man?
Keep this between us, okay?
Ji-uk isn't seeing anyone.
I've never seen him on a date.
-Really? Never?
-Never.
The brave
gets the stud!
No, I'm not into that.
Thank you. Take care.
Ms. Son's place is nice.
Excuse me, sir.
-Please stop by a convenience store.
-A convenience store?
Make a right turn
at the end of this alley.
All right.
Where's my watch?
Did you check your shoes?
Have you seen my phone?
It's probably under the mattress.
I guess you didn't get any new furniture.
Nothing's changed.
How do you know that?
Oh. Well, the thing is…
You and Ms. Son are quite…
Something's in the air.
-How are you feeling?
-What?
You said you were going for a walk
to settle your stomach.
Right. I feel better now.
How can the store manager not know
that his long-time part-timer got married?
And if he disappeared a few months ago,
that's right after the wedding.
Did they live apart right away?
What's with the rooftop room?
I'm so confused.
I want to know
how far you can go
to keep up this fake act.
So you're capable of kissing someone
with no feelings behind it.
A kiss?
That was a peck, not a kiss.
Was that your first time?
I'm so sorry.
Then I just want to have fun with you,
Son Hae-yeong.
What got into you?
How can you sleep after all that?
I'm not the one
who made things confusing first.
Why can he do it, but not me?
I'm so tired.
Enough is enough.
I can't hold it in anymore.
Brother-in-law!
I'll call you that for now.
Where are you off to?
The bathroom.
Are you going to pee outside?
The bathroom's this way.
Well…
I'm actually going to the bathhouse.
Have breakfast first.
The thing is,
I need to let go of what I put in.
Where are you going?
-The bath…
-He's headed to the bathhouse.
-What about breakfast?
-Well…
He wants to scrub on an empty stomach.
You should eat first.
I really need to take a bath right now.
I bought delicious food for us.
Butt-clenchingly good kimchi soup.
And tender braised short ribs
that'll glide right down your intestines
as soon as you take a bite.
Doesn't that sound good?
It does. You three enjoy breakfast.
Step aside.
Please get out of my way.
Brother-in-law!
Thank you for the food.
-Isn't the kimchi soup good?
-Yes.
Try the ribs too.
-Here.
-Thank you.
Make sure you try everything
with Son Hae-yeong.
We're going to exercise at the park.
Do you want to go with us?
No.
-I…
-Why not?
You don't want to exercise
with Son Hae-yeong?
Stop acting cute. I'm losing my appetite.
Did you two
argue yesterday?
Yesterday?
Did something happen?
The thing is…
What happened?
They kissed on the rooftop!
She kissed me first
without my consent.
You twisted my arm,
grabbed me, and kissed me.
So you two did kiss?
Are you dating?
She can kiss someone without dating
as long as Ahn Woo-jae's watching.
Can you not tell a kiss and a peck apart?
I gave you a peck
-and you--
-How childish.
This is just poop and diarrhea
arguing over which is worse.
-Who's the poop?
-She's the diarrhea, right?
That's gross.
I told you to come to my office.
How dare you make me come to you?
Are you testing my aggressiveness
as a developer?
Why did you ask to see me
on the weekend for no reason?
We don't need a reason to meet.
I just wanted to have a chat
and hear your briefing on
Ms. Son's housewarming.
It was good.
Did you see your writer friend?
I guess.
-How is she?
-She's good, I guess.
How was she? You know, health-wise.
Will she continue writing?
Did she hint at quitting or anything?
She's still quite popular and…
Oh, look at that. I shut it again.
Why don't you just call her and ask?
She won't…
find it comfortable.
Imagine a boss
calling his secretary's friend.
CHILDREN'S STORY WRITER NAM JA-YEON
A latte for you, right?
Hey, Ja-yeon.
MS. YEON BO-RA
She's ignoring my texts.
"If you don't call me,
the life of your muse,
Yeo Ha-jun, will be…"
Hello, Ms. Yeon. It's the hater.
-Yes, all right!
-Your latte, sir.
That damn Fuck-gyu!
I apologize for the trouble I've caused,
Mr. Bok Gyu-hyun.
I withdrew my suit.
I'm also willing to sign an NDA.
-Ms. Yeon.
-I asked to see you today
to plead that Hae…
-Ms. Son Hae-yeong isn't penalized for--
-Ms. Nam Ja-yeon.
I'm here to see Ms. Yeon Bo-ra,
not Ms. Son's sister Nam Ja-yeon.
I wanted to apologize
for hiding my real identity
on top of writing those hate comments.
But if you do this,
who am I supposed to apologize to?
Should we meet again some other time?
I accept your apology.
You don't have to go
to the orphanage anymore.
I'll complete my community service
as promised.
No, I want to end things here.
I don't want to see you ever again.
Wait, if this is the end…
If this is the end for us,
could we go eat somewhere?
No.
I don't want to make
any memories with you anywhere else.
I just want to…
Come out, Nam Ja-yeon!
Come out!
Nam Ja-yeon!
Come out here, Nam Ja-yeon!
Ms. Yeon.
Run.
Sorry?
-Run!
-Wait.
Why am I doing this?
That bastard's the one
who wanted to take care of Baby.
I do all the work
and he gets to feel good about himself.
Hey, Kim Ji-uk!
Where did he go?
Jeez.
Let's see how beautiful
you are today, Ms. Lee.
You're as strong as a bull.
You're here.
Father.
Ms. Lee, he's not your father.
It's all right.
You look like a young lady today.
I guess you read my mind.
I brought you a gift.
Mom.
Who does your daughter take after?
She's not like you at all.
She's like a racehorse
with a one-track mind.
She runs full steam ahead
without noticing that I've fallen for her.
It's like she chooses
to ignore my confessions.
You know what your daughter said
after kissing me?
Her ex--
-Hae-yeong?
-Yes, your daughter, Hae…
What did you just say?
My daughter,
Hae-yeong.
Do you remember her?
Wait a minute.
I'll video call her right…
Mom,
do you think
she'll forgive me?
Let's keep running
Until light shines on your face
Together
Let's run away
Ms. Yeon.
Do you know this one too?
-Sorry?
-I love this song.
Keep breathing
Until you feel
There is nothing left inside you
Even if you run out of breath
I'm here to see Ms. Yeon Bo-ra,
not Ms. Son's sister Nam Ja-yeon.
I wanted to apologize
for hiding my real identity
on top of writing those hate comments.
Are you all right?
You're Writer Yeon Bo-ra?
So you meant for the comments
to be hurtful but not fatal?
I truly felt regret
and I sincerely wanted to
apologize to you.
Ms. Yeon!
Your boyfriend was so worried.
He carried you to the ER.
You're a writer.
You can't hurt your hand, can you?
I'm deeply sorry
for causing you unnecessary stress,
especially when you're so busy.
How could I possibly understand
Someone's sigh
and heavy breath
I may not understand the depth
Of your sigh
But it's all right
I will hold you
I'm sorry. Here.
It's all right.
It's okay, I'm fine.
Thank you
for singing
for me.
I want to thank you too,
for letting me be with you elsewhere.
You did all that
at the orphanage the other day
so Ha-jun wouldn't find out
that I was Yeon Bo-ra, right?
Yes.
Thank you for that as well.
Could you keep it--
Don't worry. Your secret is safe with me.
Okay.
In that case…
So,
is this our last time seeing each other?
Yes.
Unless you write more hate comments
and get sued again.
Come and eat, Baby.
Come eat.
Are we having pasta and toast for lunch?
Could you get me
the tomato sauce, Ja-yeon?
Okay.
-And the jam too.
-Okay.
"Ji-uk, thanks for opening the lid."
That's it.
Let's do this.
The lid's on so tight.
Stop. You'll hurt yourself.
I can open it.
You'll hurt yourself.
"Ji-uk, the remote isn't working."
Of course, it does.
Is it not working?
-I bet you gave your father a hard time.
-Not compared to you.
-There we go.
-Quit smoking, okay?
Are you…
"Ji-uk, the bathroom light is…"
So the bastard with my last name
is lying down, waiting for fruit to fall.
And the bastard who doesn't know
he's a Bok is satisfied with a car?
I thought a rival would get him
off his butt and at least make him sit,
but the rival's even more useless.
Don't ever have kids, Mr. Jang.
Raising them will only let you down.
I can't have kids, sir.
And raising them involves planting seeds,
nurturing, and harvesting.
Since you never did the latter two,
all you did was plant your seeds.
Should I look for other seeds, sir?
No, two is all I have. I'm sure of it.
Then I'll try convincing Mr. Kim again.
What about his wife?
-Do you mean Ms. Son Hae-yeong?
-Yeah.
She seems ambitious and bold.
However, sir, that may result
in a succession battle
between your daughters-in-law
and not your sons.
I wouldn't mind if it means
either one of them
will come to their senses.
Hello, ma'am.
Mr. Jang.
Yes, ma'am?
Isn't it Director Jang's
death anniversary soon?
Yes.
Thank you for remembering.
He was very loyal
to my father and husband.
Yes, considering his last words
to his son were,
“Remain faithful to Chairman Bok.
If he tells you to die, die."
And?
I'm sure he said more.
To get up and respond to your call,
even if I'm dead and buried in the ground.
You don't need to get up.
Just a signal will do.
I thought you'd leave alone.
I'm not that petty.
What about the door?
Open it for me.
Forget it.
What are you doing?
I'm petty.
POPCORN AI PLAYGROUND
Is something bothering you?
Yeah, you.
Aside from me. What is it?
If I tell you, will you solve it for me,
Mr. Mere Newbie?
Is it about work?
Just tell me. Who knows?
I might come up with a fresh, new idea.
Our target base rarely switches services
unless there's a proven learning method.
So we need to give them a solid reason
to choose Popcorn AI Playground.
Perhaps by showing them
tangible results from trial users,
such as improved academic…
Ma'am.
Have we made up yet?
No.
Good luck.
Did you just say "good luck"
to your team leader
who's stressed about this?
Hey, back in my day…
Forget it.
Did anything come to mind when you first
heard about the new business plan?
Why did you even apply to work here?
I was curious about the employee discount.
Where would you even use it
if you could get a discount?
At the orphanage.
The kids there don't go to academies,
so I thought it could help.
The orphanage…
The orphanage?
I'm Son Hae-yeong, the leader
of the New Business Development Team One.
Here is the progress report
on Popcorn AI Playground.
The program allows children
to both learn and gain experiences,
boosting both brain activity
and physical strength…
You told me to run.
By managing learning times and promoting
good studying habits through the program…
Do you know this one too?
I love this song.
Popcorn AI Playground is gaining traction
as an alternative learning model
as it lessens
the burden of private education
and strengthens
children's motivation to learn.
Lastly, I'd like to talk
about the marketing strategy.
So, is this our last time
seeing each other?
I want things to end here.
I don't want to see you ever again.
I don't like that!
Sir.
Are you not happy with our strategy?
POPCORN AI PLAYGROUND MARKETING STRATEGY
The new business is innovative,
but the marketing strategy
is dull.
Director, are you going to try to
fit a square peg into a round hole?
I need you to direct your attention
to the New Business Development Team.
Yes, sir.
Let's reconvene
once you've come up with a new strategy.
I'll look forward to it.
Keep up the good work.
Goodbye, sir.
Excuse me, Mr. Bok!
There is a marketing plan
that's still in the works.
I'd like to open the first
Popcorn AI Playground branch
at an orphanage.
We'd offer a free service to children
left behind by private education.
Are you suggesting ESG marketing?
Yes, sir.
Following our child abuse
prevention campaign,
we could offer underprivileged children
with equal education opportunities
and appeal to consumers
who value social good.
Ms. Son, you should discuss that
with the marketing team
-and report to me first before--
-Ms. Son.
Get in. Let's try a new approach
to reporting too.
Yes, sir.
She took her chance, huh?
She should know her place.
What if things go wrong?
Unbelievable!
She really took a risk with the CEO
in this situation.
She's bold, I give her that.
You mean, she's reckless.
Oh, my goodness.
Strangers would think
you've fallen in love with her
with that look on your face.
-Look here.
-Okay.
-I already explained this to you.
-I see.
You need to separate this. Got it?
I'm sorry.
Ms. Lee, your phone's ringing.
“Not my partner”?
Leave it. I'm ignoring it on purpose.
Did you guys argue?
My husband might think so,
but I taught him a lesson.
Ms. Lee.
What can your husband do
to make you feel better?
Did you argue with Ms. Son?
That's why her blinds are down.
That's not good, Mr. Kim.
Ms. Son holds a grudge for a long time.
Exactly, so I'm not sure what I can do.
Don't think about doing anything.
Think about it.
You did something to make her mad, right?
-Yes.
-Exactly.
So instead of doing something,
vow never to do whatever you did again
for the rest of your life.
What?
But that's…
If you wanted to do whatever you wanted,
you shouldn't have gotten married!
-Anyway, listen up.
-Yes?
-So instead of doing this…
Do this.
But that's…
TVC 10TH EXCLUSIVE FEMALE VOICE ACTOR
1ST EXAM QUESTIONS
Hello, my name is Cha Hui-seong,
an applicant for TVC's 10th exclusive
female voice actor exam.
I'll begin.
"The small village sits next to the sea."
"The merciless fire has extended
its evil hand into this village as well."
Come here, Hui-seong.
Let's listen to that last take again.
Once your auditions are over,
I'm going to cling to you for a week.
That's not when we meet.
You're with Min-ji and I'm with Hyeon-gyu.
Oh.
Then how about a trip to the hot springs
the week after?
Sounds great.
Great, I'll make reservations.
-Wait, let me check my calendar.
-Okay.
FEBRUARY
MARCH
KKULBEE EDUCATION
I look forward
to Popcorn AI Playground's first branch.
I'll exceed your expectations, sir.
Thank you for putting your trust in me.
Keep up the good work.
Let's keep the orphanage
under wraps for now.
I want you to take charge
and keep it a secret from your husband.
I also heard you have a friend
who's more or less your sister.
Don't let either of them know
until everything is finalized.
Yes, understood.
Goodbye, sir.
Your car's over there.
Why keep it a secret from Mr. Kim?
He's on her team.
Just because.
He'd be the happiest to hear about it,
so I want to surprise him.
You seem to be fond of him.
What is it?
Are you jealous?
It's not that.
I just think
he'd make an excellent secretary.
And you'll be
an excellent one too, someday.
Yeah, someday.
APOLOGY LETTER
“I, Kim Ji-uk, will never, ever
kiss Son Hae-yeong again
for the rest of my life.”
What's this?
It's my gesture of apology and regret.
Or you're just messing with me.
She really does hold a grudge.
Just start driving.
We need to go somewhere.
Where?
A place to peacefully lay you to sleep.
I assumed we'd be looking
for a gravesite for me.
Are you buying a bed?
What type of mattress do you prefer?
Something firm or soft?
Are we…
Are we going to share a bed?
Are you crazy?
We're here to buy yours.
A bed just for you.
Right.
You should've made that clear.
I got the wrong idea.
So what do you prefer?
Soft or firm?
I've never thought about it.
I've only used the one at my gosiwon
and second-hand ones.
Follow me.
How's this?
Not bad, right?
This one's not bad.
This is so comfortable.
Do you like it?
It's comfortable, but it's a bit small.
Look how adorable this is.
So this is a kid's room.
Where'd he go?
Ji-uk.
I wouldn't mind this either.
I wish I lived here.
A bed is an investment,
so you should buy the right one.
Did you like any of them?
There was one,
but it's out of my price range.
I don't get paid much
as a mere entry-level employee.
Pick the one you like.
It's on me.
It's okay, I'll just get a cheap--
Ji-uk.
I want you to sleep in a good bed
with a soft blanket.
So that even after a long, tedious day,
you come home to a bed so comfortable
that you don't envy
the king of any kingdom.
You're your one and only king
and only subject.
So you need to make sure
your king is comfortable and taken care of
and your subject is well-fed.
So sleep in a good bed, Ji-uk.
I'm
not confused at all.
No matter how much
you beat around the bush,
I hear you loud and clear.
I…
like you too.
My land has been conquered
by a tyrant next door.
You know what happens
when a king is taken over by lust?
His subjects fall into distress
and starve to death.
Well, I can't starve my subjects.
Let's go!
Please add avocado to mine.
You like avocados?
Yes, I do.
-You do?
-Yeah.
You're confessing again.
Thank you.
Just to be clear,
I wasn't confessing to you.
I know.
This is the one with avocado.
I'm just grateful for your marketing idea.
I…
like you too.
I like you too.
I want to see you.
Don't say anything cheesy
like "I'm full just looking at you."
I need to eat to feel full.
Do you like it?
It's amazing.
Ji-uk.
Can you wait for me?
Take your time washing up.
I'll be upstairs.
Not that.
Listen.
I want us to start dating when I can
forget about work and getting promoted,
when we don't have
to worry about getting caught,
and when I can focus
on just you and me.
That's when I want to
make things official between us.
So you mean…
That's what I wanted to say that day,
but Ahn Woo-jae ruined it.
So can you wait for me?
I'll wait for you so patiently
that you won't even realize I'm waiting.
Are you almost done?
Oh, let me ask.
Should I wear this or this?
This?
You'll be working
outside the office today, right?
Yeah.
With Ms. Son?
What? Yeah.
Woo-jae,
I could move you to a different team
if working with her bothers you.
Yi-lin.
I'm not some toy for you to play with.
I have thoughts and feelings of my own.
Don't cross the line.
I told you we should carpool.
What a waste of gas.
Do you know why work pays for gas?
They want us to make money
and not worry about paying for gas.
Wait for me!
I've heard everything I need to hear.
We'd love to have a room
dedicated to studying for the kids.
In exchange, we need to collect data
on the children's grades
and take videos for promotional materials.
We need your consent,
as well as the children's.
I'll ask them,
but I'm sure they'll say yes.
They've always wanted to study
using tablets.
Thank you, Kkulbee Education!
It's a win-win for us.
Hello.
-Hello.
Please have some tea.
-Thank you.
Oh, do you know Mr. Kim Ji-uk?
He joined Kkulbee this year.
Yes, Mr. Kim is part of our team.
Really? That means he'll visit often.
That's good news for you, Yu-na.
Don't say that, Director.
-We should get--
-Ma'am.
How do you know Mr. Kim?
He's volunteered as a tutor here
for the past seven or eight years.
Yu-na helps as his assistant
and I think she's doing it
because she has feelings for him.
But Mr. Kim is a married…
They're both still too young
to be married.
I'd just love to see a lovely young man
and woman start dating.
Ms. Son.
Son Hae-yeong!
Are you actually married to Kim Ji-uk?
Answer me.
You're not actually married, right?
If you don't answer me,
I'll ask the director
why she doesn't know he's married.
Hey!
Be honest.
Is your marriage real?
It's fake, isn't it?
Damn it.
Why did it have to be you?
So it is fake.
Hae-yeong.
I'm sorry.
You didn't have to do that because of me.
-What do you mean?
-You did it to spite me.
You resented me for getting married
so you got married to rub it in my face.
What the hell are you talking about?
Hae-yeong, just give me some time.
Whether I divorce Yi-lin or not,
I promise
I'll man up and take care of you.
So what you're saying is…
Let's get back together.
Come here.
Why?
I want to make it up to you
for ruining your life.
Make it up to me for pissing me off first.
Come here!
-Come here!
-I swear I'll make it up to you.
-I said, come here!
-Come on!
Have you seen the script
for the Spice Up Our Love adaptation?
Yes, it looked great.
I'll proceed with casting then.
I was thinking,
maybe Cha Hui-seong could…
Of course, I'll call her.
-Thank you.
-And can you
start uploading new episodes
starting next Monday?
I can do that.
Great, resume uploads next Monday.
Oh, about that hater…
I withdrew my suit.
It's not that.
It seems he's really changed.
He's re-rating and leaving new comments
starting from episode one.
-Thank you for your work, Ms. Yeon.
-You too.
-Have a good one.
-Bye.
I spent all night
binge-reading the series.
I even passed out
and went to the hospital.
Her writing shines
behind the explicit language.
The couple's story of saving each other
warms the heart and body.
I'm becoming a huge fan.
King Sejong created
the Korean alphabet for his subjects,
and Ms. Yeon created this series
for her lonely readers.
You're the best, Ms. Yeon.
I don't want it to end.
I really want more.
Hello?
Are you busy, Ha-jun?
Yeah, but only my eyes are.
What's up?
Not much. Just wondering how you are
and if your boss is bothering you.
I see.
He's planning to bother me tomorrow.
We're volunteering at the orphanage.
Volunteering?
The writer agreed to drop the charges
for 100 hours of community service.
It'll finally be over tomorrow.
Did you go with him every time?
Yeah.
I need to repent too.
For what?
To tell you the truth…
I will use hate comments
to break the writer's pen.
So you take over from episode 51.
-Take over what?
-Writing hate comments.
Are you outsourcing writing hate comments?
I'll accept
your transfer request.
Deal.
So you wrote hate comments
because he ordered you to?
You wrote them?
Yeah.
I think I started from episode 51.
Found it.
Ja-yeon, now my arms and legs are busy.
I'll call you later.
What about this comment in episode 51?
I filed the suit because of that comment.
It falls under spreading false information
and defamation.
It can't get worse than this.
So Ha-jun wrote the comment…
on episode 51.
Mr. Jang.
You look happy to see me.
Right, I shouldn't be.
Well, it's been a while
so I'm glad to see you.
Things have changed.
I was just fired.
Was it because of me?
Strictly speaking,
it's because of my deceased father.
So what brings you here?
Knowing this in advance
won't change anything,
but I had to ease my mind.
Ms. Seon Jeong-a
knows about your true identity.
I just briefed her on it.
-Why…
-That's not what's important.
You have to think about
what you need to do to protect your wife.
Listen.
Staying alert in a lion's den
will only make the bite hurt more.
To survive the lion's den,
you must become a lion.
This is advice I'm giving you
of my own volition,
not under anyone's order.
-Did you take out the trash?
-Yes.
I could've helped you.
Thank you.
There were alcohol bottles.
Why did you drink?
Is something wrong?
Yeah, it's something about us.
I have something to tell you too.
What is it?
Ma'am,
let's talk later tonight.
Right now, let's take care of this.
Oh, it arrived.
Insert the sharp part upward like this.
Be careful.
Don't put it in too deep.
-Like this?
-Yeah.
You're doing great.
Just a bit higher. It's too far down.
-Is this good?
-Yeah.
Fit the bands around the mattress.
Hang this up there.
Dress shirts go over there.
That was the last one.
Aren't we too close together
in this confined space?
I'm an angelic dog, not a man.
Well, I can be quite charming
like a chew toy.
You said you'd wait.
Wait.
You said
your mind's only attracted to
what your body is.
And you said your mind and body are one.
We're not even officially dating yet.
Are you sure about this?
I want to respect your principles.
Mr. Bok?
Mr. Bok Gyu-hyun?
You.
Are you really…
My father…
You're not Kim Ji-uk.
You're Bok Ji…
Are you the chairman's son
born out of wedlock?
EPILOGUE
How to make your wife talk
to you first after an argument.
One, "Could you open this for me?"
Note. You will fail if you can't open it.
Two, "The remote doesn't work."
Note. Let's hope she isn't tech-savvy.
Three, "The bathroom light won't turn on."
Note. You'll fail if she's handy.
100 percent success rate, my ass.
Unsubscribe.
MARRIED LIFE TV
THANKS TO LEE SEUNG-JUN
FOR HIS SPECIAL APPEARANCE
I'll talk to Mr. Bok.
Do you think I'll be safe if you quit?
Are you preparing
because you might get fired?
I won't get fired.
There's only one way out of this mess.
Could I sign the contract right away?
Send him abroad so he can never come back.
I'm scared you'll suffer because of me.
It's your call.
Either ruin your mom's life
and stay with Ms. Son
or leave on your own.
Son Hae-yeong isn't between us anymore.
Subtitle: Ji-hun Lee