♪Parting brings sorrow,
then fate misleads us♪
♪Loneliness remains, and time flies by♪
♪Until we meet again,
with hair turned white♪
♪Words lost in choking silence,
sorrow fills the night♪
♪Seasons pass—helpless as before♪
♪Do you know, my love?
I sip old memories to keep you close♪
♪Cold window and the faded letter
speak of longing♪
♪The spring wind plucks
the last pipa string♪
♪Still we await the wind
to end these fleeting years♪
=She Is the Phoenix=
Am I beautiful?
Of course, Lady Bingqing.
Why call me that now?
Out!
=Episode 12=
=Pawn=
Didn't I tell you to go?
Who upset you this time?
(I almost forgot)
(though she's engaged
to the Crown Prince,)
(she still can't let go of Xiao Jingchu.)
You're here to prepare
for the Spring Banquet in three days.
We'll formally introduce you
to Yun City's noble families.
Thank you, Bingqing.
You've always been so kind to me.
I wish to do something for you as well.
What help can you offer me?
Bingqing,
would you like to invite Lord Xiao
for a walk?
(If I wish to truly earn her trust,)
(I can't simply obey her)
(like Rong'er did.)
(I must help her,)
(like the God of Matchmaking.)
Today is the Death Anniversary
of your mother.
His Majesty's arrival
is surely to honor her memory.
Stop! What are you doing?
Why all the noise?
Consort Xi was feeling unwell.
She didn't like these peony blossoms.
Father.
These were Mother's favorite flowers.
They're all she left me.
She was just a palace maid,
one whose name I can hardly recall.
Must I really honor her now?
Keep smashing them until they're gone.
Take this. Use it to keep yourself safe.
Mm.
Jingchu,
go to Mother's room,
help bring me a pot of peony blossom.
I'd do anything for Mother.
Go on, then.
What brings you here?
Looks like you've recovered.
You can walk around.
Thanks to your medicine.
Thank you, My Lord.
Gratitude and repayment
aren't really your style, Leyao.
Speak. Why did you come to me?
I'd like to discuss,
working with you again.
Tomorrow,
can you accompany Ning Bingqing
on the lake?
I'm not free.
In return,
I'll grant you one request, My Lord.
How did you know about this?
Lighting sky lanterns
guides the departed.
Xiao Jingchu,
you can write down
your longing and wishes.
The lantern will send your words on.
I've never believed in the afterlife,
let alone in sky lanterns.
The realm of the dead
was always born of tales.
How could my words be sent?
A wandering soul among mortals.
Dark spirits roam free.
Family waits below in the afterlife.
Sometimes I wish,
that world was truly real.
Xiao Jingchu, hurry, write it down.
Jiang Leyao,
tell me,
is it harder for those who leave first,
or for those left behind?
Those who leave first
will build our next home.
Those left behind
live on with sorrow and longing,
but as long as we live,
there is still hope.
♪Words lost in choking silence,
sorrow fills the night♪
Some live on for love,
while others
cling to life fueled by hate,
and that's how they endure.
♪Cold window and the faded letter
speak of longing♪
Be it love or hate,
as long as it gives strength,
it's enough.
(Sky lanterns send your wishes afar)
I'll count to three,
then we release it.
One, two, three.
♪I rest by the sails
under scattered clouds♪
♪Countless words to share♪
♪Words of joy never run dry♪
♪If fate allows, two hearts will meet♪
♪Beneath old trees, we make our wish♪
♪Let longing be sent with the breeze♪
(Xiao Jingchu,)
(too much hatred burdens me.)
(I cannot return your feelings.)
(You will find the one)
(who'll never let you be alone.)
(Jiang Leyao,)
(I hope you never leave me.)
We've found something.
Speak.
The roster we found
in the Ruyi House
matches the missing girls' list
from ten years.
It seems
Ruyi House is just the beginning.
What we're looking into
is more complex than we thought.
However,
we've already raided
the gambling den.
For now, we can follow the clues
from these missing girls
and keep investigating.
When?
Ah.
When should I meet Ning Bingqing tomorrow?
Oh, at the Xu Hour.
Alright.
Weren't you the one trying to match them?
Why are you so anxious now?
I'm not anxious at all.
I'm just worried,
that Xiao Jingchu might make a mess.
Why isn't he back so late?
I'll go take a look.
I never wish to meet
such shallow women again.
My Lord.
Miss Jiang is here.
How is it today, My Lord?
She is well-read and polite.
Spending time with her
feels like basking in the spring breeze.
Indeed.
After our boat ride,
we visited the Washe Theatre,
and watched
Romance of the Western Chamber.
That was wonderful.
I enjoyed talking with another lady,
but you didn't seem upset.
Today's outing was my arrangement,
and everything went as I wished,
so why would I be angry?
Jiang Leyao,
look into my eyes and tell me,
have you never felt a thing for me?
Not at all.
If anything, My Lord,
you're the one pressing me.
Could it be...
you are the one with feelings for me?
I...
Of course not.
Glad to hear that.
Leyao,
how do you truly feel about me?
I've already said,
it's merely cooperation.
There's nothing beyond that.
Then why?
Why did you help with the peonies?
It was just out of convenience.
Jiang Leyao,
I can't hold back anymore,
nor do I wish to.
No matter how cold your words are,
I just want to tell you,
I...
I am fond of you.
♪Jade hairpin binds your hair,
shows your beauty♪
♪Slender fingers, gentle smiles♪
♪Silver garlands shimmer
under soft moonlit♪
♪Leaves turn gold,
moon bright and still♪
♪A thousand candles light up the hall♪
♪I long to chat among flowers
beneath the moon♪
♪Wine is quick to intoxicate,
and cups to break♪
♪Pour a cup, drink it up♪
♪My tears cascade down
when I play high art music again♪
♪A single boat of memories,
blown by wind♪
♪Drunken whispers fade,
and I fall asleep♪
♪I fear the past will linger,
and time won't regret♪
♪Wine is quick to intoxicate,
and cups to break♪
♪Pour a cup, drink it up♪
♪My tears cascade down
when I play high art music again♪
♪A single boat of memories,
blown by wind♪
♪Drunken whispers fade,
and I fall asleep♪
♪I fear the past will linger,
and time won't regret♪
♪A single boat of memories,
blown by wind♪
♪Drunken whispers fade,
and I fall asleep♪
♪I fear the past will linger,
and time won't regret♪