I just want you to know
no matter what,
I'm fond of you.
It's not because you resemble someone else.
I simply like you for who you are.
I'm telling you this
because I want to cherish the present moment.
I'm afraid something unexpected might happen in the future,
and I might never have the chance to let you know.
My father was the butler for the Situ family.
Ever since I can remember,
I've known Miss Yun'er from the Situ family.
She would take me on the swing,
and she would give me delicious treats.
But ever since that big fire,
I've been left all alone.
Hong Guo,
Hmm?
come here.
I have something to tell you.
Actually,
I am Miss Yun'er from the Situ family.
What?
You are Miss Yun'er?
Mm-hmm.
Then why did you keep it from me for so long?
What I've been doing is too dangerous.
I didn't want to involve you too much.
If something happened to me,
not knowing my identity,
you wouldn't have much burden when leaving.
How could you think like that, Yun'er?
When my father was at the Situ family years ago,
you even let him be the butler.
You've been kind to me since I was little.
You provided me with everything I needed.
Just for this kindness alone,
even if you asked for my life,
I, Hong Guo, would be willing to give it.
Silly girl,
what would I do with your life?
You are my only family left in this world.
Miss.
From now on,
we are sisters.
Mm-hmm.
Sister Qing Dai.
I know you're looking for the Green Ghost,
to find out what happened to your mother.
But have you ever considered
that your mother might have really eloped with the Green Ghost?
I know
you still remember the Green Ghost's life-saving grace.
Don't worry,
if the Green Ghost is innocent,
I won't wrongly accuse him.
But if he really hurt my mother,
I will end him with my own hands.
As long as we find all four Beauty Screens,
the truth will come to light.
However,
will the Green Ghost really show up
for just a few screens?
The technique of the Nightmare Palm is hidden in these four Beauty Screens.
The Green Ghost will surely be tempted by it.
I can't believe it's true.
I thought it was just a rumor.
This is what my master told me.
I haven't actually seen it myself.
However,
once we gather all four Beauty Screens,
we'll know for sure.
Don't worry,
Sister Qing Dai.
I'll find the whereabouts of the third screen as soon as possible.
Sister Qing Dai,
the person who made you decide to reveal your identity to me,
it wouldn't happen to be Commander Mo from the patrol, would it?
Are you drinking to drown your sorrows?
Or are you practicing your marksmanship?
Brother,
why are you here?
My little brother is getting married,
how could I, as your older brother, not come to see?
That was just a joke.
Brother, you don't need to take it seriously.
I'm not taking it seriously,
but as your older brother, I should at least know
what kind of woman has captured your heart so.
Come, let's go to the Sanxiang Tea House.
I've heard their lotus leaf tea is exquisite.
Brother,
lotus leaf tea should be brewed with spring water collected in the early morning
for the best taste.
Why don't we go another day?
Alright,
let's go tomorrow then.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Miss Hong Hongguo.
I, I, I...
this month's salary.
Lord Xiao, your credit is quite good.
You pay what you owe.
It won't be hard to borrow again.
Remember for next month too.
So punctual, aren't you?
Otherwise, I'll go to the police station
and tell everyone about how you took advantage of me.
That's not...
You...
If Lord Xiao finds it difficult,
I have other ways too.
Alright.
It's not that I'm unwilling to part with the money.
You have other methods?
I'd like to hear about them.
Lord Xiao,
if there are any other
ways for me to make money,
that could work too.
Miss Hongguo,
you really
only love money.
If I didn't love money,
do you think I'd love you instead?
The weather is dry,
be careful with fire.
Well,
I...
Yes?
I was just patrolling and passed by here.
I saw the lights were still on in the teahouse,
so I came in.
I'm going on duty.
There's no need to be nervous.
I'm just here to have some tea.
You jest, brother.
What do I have to be nervous about?
The owner, Qing Dai, will be here soon.
I apologize for keeping you waiting.
I'll serve tea for both of you right away.
The proprietress looks like someone I used to know.
Wan Nan.
Aren't you being a bit too strict with Yun'er?
She lied to protect A Ze.
Her intentions were good.
Zhi Zhen,
a parent's love for their child
is to plan for their future.
I see Yun'er is already lying at such a young age.
Who knows what she'll be like when she grows up?
You've already taught Yun'er very well.
Ah.
It's a pity A Ze is born of a concubine.
He can't be raised in the Feng household.
His manners are still not as good as A Chen's.
I think A Ze is quite fine.
Why don't we make him my son-in-law in the future?
That mouth of yours!
Brother Feng Chen.
I'm fine.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
This is the white medicine from the palace.
It wouldn't be good for a girl to have scars.
Yun'er thanks Brother Feng Chen.
It's my fortune to resemble Your Excellency's old friend.
It's my blessing.
I heard you're from the capital.
Where exactly do you live there?
Yi Chu Pin Yi
Beijing National Fashion Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Horgos Daobo Spring Film and Television Culture Media Co., Ltd.
- Production -
- Art Director -
You Jianming
- Cast -
Baidian Pictures
Visual Effects Production
Yan Ruhua
Music Production
Beijing Landuo Music
Chizhou Haochen Culture Media Co., Ltd.