GRID
SEO KANGJUN
KIM AHJOONG
KIM MUYEOL
KIM SUNGKYUN
LEE SIYOUNG
GRID
EPISODE 10
Two murders and one assault.
I've agreed to step down if we lose him,
so we must not lose him.
Not because of our bureau's mistake.
- Yes, ma'am.
The Ghost is where Kim Manok is.
You all wanted to go out to the field.
This is your chance.
- Yes, ma'am.
About what we heard
at the lobby earlier...
Was Ms. Choi mistaken?
A misunderstanding?
Do you also want us
to pretend to be deaf and dumb?
No.
I think, Ms. Chae,
he just answered your question.
I think so too.
He doesn't deny it.
Why did she bring you back so soon?
There must've been a lot to find out.
Let's use Kwon Saeha as bait too.
If it wasn't the Ghost who released Manok
and she still needs him,
she'll show up.
No.
Even if that's the case,
she wouldn't come here voluntarily.
Then we should let him out.
The culprit?
And him?
I think you should see this.
106 MICROTESLA
Let's use Kwon Saeha...
...as bait too.
He's not completely useless.
Along with the culprit.
It's time to put
all our cards on the table.
Find all organisms
emitting over 100 microteslas
of electromagnetic radiation.
- What's the upper limit?
- No limit.
Are you sure the Founder emits
electromagnetic radiation?
You're also a scientist.
What's the normal level of electromagnetic
radiation emitted by a human?
You don't need a scientist for that.
I think you should see this.
A normal person emits
a very small amount.
Over 100? That means...
this person has frequently been
exposed to magnetic fields.
Exactly.
There, 106!
No, that's Kwon Saeha.
The measurement has to be
much higher than this.
Please.
Let's split.
Ms. Chae.
Mr. Kwon.
Whatever you do, do it alone.
- Don't drag Saebyeok...
- I won't drag you into anything.
Alpha has appeared. 34K3756.
That way!
That's 34K3756. 3755!
It's the next alley!
C1 and C2, stay in your position.
You're to watch for Beta.
Over there.
Alpha.
Alpha 25K1754.
He's right next to Beta.
Damn it.
Halt. Stand by.
Inform us of Beta's position. I repeat.
Inform us of Beta's position again.
We don't see him here.
What do you mean, you don't see him?
He's right between you two!
What are you doing? What?
Beta has removed the GPS tracker.
He's out of our sight.
What the hell is going on?
Gosh, I can't locate him.
We've lost Kim Manok.
As for the signal,
I think the Ghost showed up on purpose.
What do we do? Do we continue?
Retrieve Kim Manok.
Tell me this is the only way.
Tell me this is worth it.
As long as the sun exists,
the solar wind is a threat.
Both to your generation
and mine.
Did many people die in your time too?
They would
without the Grid.
How many more
need to be sacrificed to complete it?
Are there more left?
Among the people I know?
We've repeated this dozens of times.
To find another way.
Though it doesn't matter since
you are all people in the past to me.
Yes.
It's for us to be born.
For my mom and me.
Then what about my mom?
If I'm gone too...
If she has no one to look after her...
I'm not going to die for you.
Figure something out
for your mom yourself.
You're shameless.
I know.
When will it happen?
When will I...
How much time do I have left?
Mom...
I'm sorry, Mom.
I wanted to make it.
But I couldn't.
Kwon Saeha!
Saeha!
Darn it.
Damn it.
Are you okay?
Detective. What are you doing here?
Why that...
Kwon Saeha!
He came this way for sure.
- I mean Kim Manok.
- Yes, he's nearby.
Did you let him go on purpose?
A murderer in this crowded place?
That's why you shouldn't be here.
Where is that bastard?
My higher-ups already know
that you're here.
Northwest?
It's that way.
Kim Manok recognized me.
How all of a sudden?
Hey!
Beta has removed the GPS tracker.
He's out of our sight.
Is the deputy director out of her mind?
She's your boss. How could she put you
in danger instead of protecting you?
Let me see.
Did he do this?
Did he?
Kim Manok must be full of spite now.
So you must be careful too.
He's more dangerous than ever.
That piece of trash.
Whatever happened when he was little,
he's been like that because he was
hopeless in the first place.
I should've shot him
when I first saw him.
- Did something happen?
- Nothing between me and that jerk.
You didn't
happen to spot Manok, did you?
You came
to the Administration Bureau, right?
Why?
I...
He and I...
Go on.
There's something I have to check.
And if it turns out to be true,
I'll nip it in the bud.
What the hell...
What is it you have to check?
We'll lose him. Let's go.
No.
- What was that noise?
- Call 911.
- What?
- Please call 911.
- My gosh.
- Call 911.
Hurry up! Over here!
Look at me, Saeha.
Saeha. Look at me.
You'll be fine.
Just keep breathing.
They'll come save you soon.
You can't die because of me.
You...
You knew...
Saeha.
The Ghost is right next to you.
Ms. Choi...
- Saeha is...
- She's right next to you!
It's not me. Can't you see it?
You'll save him, right?
You're here to save him, right?
Are we really connected?
- What happened?
- There were people here.
- Where did they go?
- I don't know.
- They were here for sure.
- Where did they go?
Why?
I can't find her. We've lost her.
Go back one minute.
Is it broken?
That can't be. What's wrong with this?
It wasn't just one.
Ms. Choi.
Saeha is dead.
Ms. Choi. Can't you hear me?
CONDOLENCES
LATE KWON SAEHA
KWON SUKEUN GRAVE
Goodness.
She's outlived not only
her husband but also her son.
How is she going to live now? Goodness.
How unfortunate for her.
You took him.
You.
I clearly told you
that I wouldn't allow it.
I told you I didn't want my son to work
for the IRR or the Administration Bureau.
But you made...
You made him work...
at the place where his father died.
Didn't you?
He said he was on leave.
Why did he suddenly go to work? Why?
Why was a public officer
beaten to death by a murderer?
Why?
What on earth were you guys
doing then? Why?
- You took him!
- Yes, go ahead, sir. It's okay.
Then there were two of them,
not just one.
It wasn't an error.
We'll keep searching.
But I don't see the point of it.
What do you mean, why?
Only the Grid Control Team
has the facilities.
How can the Secretariat afford such
pricey machines with our current budget?
I'll tell you when I get back.
No, we're done here.
Yes, sir.
Open it.
Can you drop me off on the way?
I'm going home.
Then drop me off there.
MEMORIAL GATE
Are you going to take a cab?
We're almost here.
Yes.
Thanks.
Do you want to have a drink?
Yes?
Hello?
The deputy director
pushed him to admit it.
That's how I found out what he had done.
What are you talking about?
Kwon Saeha.
I was going to ask him that evening
how he was entangled with Kim Manok.
I was determined not to let him go
until he gave me a proper answer.
Where are you?
But why do I have to ask you about this?
How do you know all this?
Why are you the only one left to ask?
Did you drink all evening?
Alone?
You turned me down, so...
I didn't like him.
I never liked Kwon Saeha
even before he got involved with you.
Involved?
I didn't even know him that well.
I wish I hadn't known him at all.
Then he wouldn't have died.
He'd be sad to hear that.
You're pretty much the only person
who remembers him properly.
At first, I thought
he was just acting tough.
You can kill me later.
If I use it for some other purpose,
you can shoot me. I don't care.
When he told me to kill him...
I thought he was saying
such a thing so easily.
There's old footage
on the 13th floor of your office.
All the information about her is
on the 13th floor of my office building.
Footage of the woman
when she first appeared in 1997.
You saw that?
In the footage, the woman kills
Kim Manok's foster father.
And someone helps her.
That must be Kwon Saeha.
Why did she kill him?
If she hadn't, neither the woman
nor the Grid would exist.
You too.
Why me?
You captured the woman.
And while doing so...
...you were hurt.
Seriously.
I guess that's how
he could go back in time.
If I had been fine, I wouldn't have
given up the chance for anyone.
You helped him.
No way. Do I look like the type?
Song Eojin.
You helped your colleague
and saved me.
Was it worth it?
I don't know exactly what happened
in the past either.
But time was turned back,
and you came back to life.
Though I'm not sure
if that's the right way to put it.
But...
the person who turned back time
suffered a bigger loss while doing it.
Even after that...
his family was constantly used
by the Administration Bureau.
It must have been
how Mr. Kwon felt all his life.
He was ready to die at any time.
He lost his dad as a child,
managed to grow up...
and eventually died like that.
I wish he had just lived his own life.
Why couldn't he?
Get up. I'll take you home.
Though I don't know where to take you.
We were married for seven years,
and I don't even know where you live.
But lately, we see each other
pretty often.
Right.
Now that it's all over,
let's become strangers again.
Is that what you wanted to tell me?
If you come see me
like nothing has happened,
I'll have to act like that too.
I don't want to go back to the old days.
So that was...
when it happened.
The other day...
you suddenly asked me if I was okay.
That's when it must've happened.
It wasn't just a bad dream.
The Secretariat is reborn today.
We turned from
an insignificant secondary department
to the core department, recognized
for its competence and importance.
But we mustn't be content with it.
After time passes, those who try
to diminish our power will rise again.
To stop them, we must always
produce satisfactory results.
We must produce concrete results.
Yes, ma'am!
1 YEAR LATER
Just grill and eat one of them.
They're for sale.
My goodness.
You won't live forever.
Stop living like that.
Gosh. Your mom is here.
Mommy.
My goodness.
Sweetie. Your mom is here.
Are you finished?
- Yes, I'm done.
- I see.
Oh, my daughter. Did you have fun today?
Time to go home.
She's just a baby.
She doesn't know what's fun yet.
Thank you for looking after her.
Don't mention it.
I'm doing this because you pay me.
- I'll get going then.
- Okay.
Oh, right. I left some scorpionfish
in the kitchen, so snack on them.
Thank you, as always.
- I'll be off.
- Bye.
Oh, dear.
It's time to eat.
All right.
Ooh. Ooh...
You're eating so well, my daughter.
You must've been hungry.
My daughter.
When will you grow up and
follow me to the sea to see me work...
and to many other places?
I hope time passes quickly...
No.
Time doesn't flow.
That's not how it worked.
Time...
Let's go. You need to leave here.
What are you saying,
popping out of the blue?
I'll explain on the way.
If you don't leave now,
you and Byeori will be in danger.
How do you know her name?
Who told you?
You did.
Maybe this child isn't the one.
Even when she's grown up
and a long time after that,
maybe nothing will happen.
But I've made my decision...
to finish what hasn't even begun yet.
Just like our traces have been erased,
we don't see the path ahead of us.
Drinkable water, breathable air,
thick forests,
and many living things in them.
I couldn't prepare
a car seat for the baby.
This child may not be able
to enjoy those things in the future.
Even without the solar wind,
we've already taken so many things
from future children.
If I can give even
one of those things back...
If my choice can protect them...
But...
I didn't expect that day
to come so soon.
Sir. It's all set.
The Grid is all gone.
From all the times and layers.
You never know.
No one knows.
Is there really an end?