(The location and characters described in this play
Organization, scenes and events are purely fictional)
Dominant Species
Who are you?
Put your hand into my pocket
your…
Pants? Are you crazy?
Coat pocket
left
You'd better not move
Do it
I said to the left
What's this?
Is this true?
He called Kim Sung-sun and arrived in Vietnam this morning
(Rewards of 30 million won)
He may get a fake passport there
Just find out his new identity and tell me
Why do you want us to find people in Vietnam?
You guys have a connection there
All the agents know the local forgery group
Intermediary?
But this bounty...
This number...is not enough
Stop talking nonsense
Would you really give 30 million?
It seems you're very curious
Give me the information
Hello
Call soon
It's me, I'm looking for your boss
Call him to listen, bastard
Dominant Species
(2025 US Embassy Year-end Party)
STL President Li Nanzhen
(Episode 4)
I didn't expect you to work so close
I was very sorry that I didn't have a chance to meet
It seems you're better now
Things that aren't
Park Dae-sung of Shanghe Group
I never thought of these wealthy presidents
Finally want to take a photo with a newcomer like us
It's time for them to find out that we're better.
Han Jihao of Technology Game
BF's Yin Zi
It's one of them
Who are they greeting?
-Father
-good
Did you come as my son or as prime minister?
Of course it's the Prime Minister, President Xianyu
Yeah? I'm so honored
Hello
A strange rumor came from a country in the south
It's about your company
Have been searching for someone
Found it?
So is it true?
are you free?
You mean me?
Yes, Representative Yin
I've seen you on several occasions
But because of your entourage
I haven't had a chance to say hello
Not a escort
Just a flatterer
Why do you want to see me?
Of course it is for business negotiation, otherwise?
-Representative Yin
-yes
You're in trouble
You also know there will always be some ups and downs
Sell ​​it to me
-What?
-Your company, BF
How about 32 trillion won?
Buy lab and cell culture technology
You can keep the fashion department and other subsidiaries
Just hand over yours
Headquarters, laboratory and cell culture technology are good
32 trillion won
(VIP ward)
Let me apologize to him, please
Let him in
When I was in Yazoran
Are you next to me?
Yes
There were two officers at that time
Escort me
Except for you
There is still next to me
An officer
How is he doing?
He sacrificed his life for the country
I don't know he's dead
No one told me
We're not able to protect you
Sorry, Mr. President
When did you
Tell the peers to work hard?
Does anyone know in advance?
What did you say?
Who said he could come in?
Who let this bastard come in?
It's me, he's here to apologize
Father, you are not wrong?
He didn't even know that there were bombs in his military camp
You actually went there to encourage these idiots?
Where is your team leader?
Tell him to come here to kneel
He went overseas
Investigate this attack
How dare you look me in the eyes?
Don't do this, it's enough
Captain Yu
Let him go
You should also be calm
He's a wounded soldier
Even though you're injured
But our president is now disabled
You made him unable to walk again
He is the president of our country, my father-in-law
32 trillion won
With that money...
Other people's opinions are different from those of the company's boss
They all say that the money you make belongs to the company
We can't even spend it at will
You should enjoy the life of a young, successful woman
You should spend money and enjoy life
I've encountered many merger and acquisition invitations
But I didn't expect you to bid
So you have rejected a lot of bids
Until now
I believe you know very well
The meat-cultivated market will soon enter the Warring States Period
Under the development of technology, similar products are launched
Will make the competition very intense
Representative Yin
This is exactly what I want to say
Can you hold on?
Dominating the market is not easy at all
That's right
I've learned this since I was a kid
This market will face an ice age
Just like the previous home appliance market
But Dawson can bear it
Because it has many subsidiaries
Can the BFs of only a few subsidiaries hold on?
Who knows how long that period will last?
10 years? 20 years?
Representative Yin
You must not lose
Your market dominance
You reject those bids
It's for this day
For me
For this meeting
This meeting is indeed very precious
But this decision is not easy
I'm sure you'll need some time to think about it
I have time
I have
Very plenty of time
I will visit and reply to you soon
Are you leaving?
Why are you the only one?
Mr. Yu left in an emergency
He said that to me, too
Didn't he report to you in advance?
Sorry, he will notify you before leaving
She said she had a lot of time
Delegate Yin said she has plenty of time
That might be how she feels now
She's still young
If you are missing outside, you will be dead. Let's go
I don't know you're still in touch with him
-who?
-He's that guy
The person in the hospital
You've known it a long time ago
Of course I know
Why did he send him to monitor Yin Zi?
What's wrong? I think this decision is good
"Representative Yin, I'm not an ordinary bodyguard
When you are in danger, I'm by your side."
Who made this good decision?
Your grandfather?
He actually used me to install his people
You agreed at the time.
You said we should try our best to install our people
I thought it was your idea
If it weren't for me
Yin Zicai won't hire former officers as bodyguards
Grandpa didn't use you, he just didn't have the chance to tell you
I know you're divorced
But you should go and see your ex-father-in-law occasionally
I'll ask you, the old man has installed a letter
Have you found out what happened to her?
His informant seems to have not yet gained the trust of Representative Yin.
That's not easy
Unfortunately, his informant has found nothing
If he doesn't do anything well
We can always find other uses for him
32 trillion won
I can remove the public identity
Use that money at will
I won't use it again
Worry about production results or force yourself to meet investors
I can only focus on my research
But why did he offer that price?
He has everything
Why is he so anxious?
Sorry, it means
I'll make sure he won't leave his post again
I'll call him and ask him to come back soon
He
What's wrong with him?
-He has scars on his face
-I asked him
Did you get beaten up by someone else
But he's the same as me
It's a type that won't say anything easily
He should have told me first before leaving
That's right
He even depends on me when he enters the company building
He always asks me to help him open the door
What's wrong, representing?
fine
I'm going to the hospital
Why are you looking forward to it?
The point is not me, it is Miss Hong
She just woke up
That's it
I'll tell her that you're very excited when you hear the news
Director Wen, if...
We can sell part of the company
Do you think we can only sell the cultivation meat technology?
Sell ​​only that?
Sales company or laboratory
Is it possible that the other party will not know about other facilities?
Who are you talking about?
Dawson's Fresh
He will soon doubt our intangible assets
He will also doubt our tangible assets
After all, it's Dawson
But you're still moved
The conditions must be very attractive
What's up? What's wrong?
What conditions did he get...
Really
(Yu Caiyun)
What's this?
Professor Kim flew to Cambodia and got a Thai passport
His new name is Songchaitlan
He is not in Vietnam?
Wait a moment
Yes, represent
What?
etc.
Professor Kim ran from Vietnam to Cambodia
Then get a Thai passport?
I'll report it now
I'll go back soon
How did he...
I'm lucky
"luck"?
Even though he passed by land, I found him
I synced it
It will connect to our application as soon as it is launched
You mean Jiang Yingshi?
Thank you for your hard work today
Did I do something wrong?
If you want to lie, just lie, but don't push it to luck
You mean I got his photo?
Why am I lying to you about this?
People who appear at critical moments of an accident
It turned out to be a bodyguard
Don't touch her
And I'm looking for a bodyguard
And he was working somewhere else
But he just resigned
If not for this
I feel like I'm stealing without hiring him
Then I found out that he had experienced the same hack
This is a symbol table in Russian and Korean
Our company has just been scared
Not only that
He has been to Azoran like me
And today...
How about my bodyguard
Always have something I need?
When I saw that photo
I admire you for finding him
But this time when you come back
I thought to myself...
"How could he have this photo?"
Why don't you speak?
You should be angry
I'm questioning you, not grateful
You should say I'm hitting your morale
It seems I haven't done it yet
If the client feels suspicious and uneasy, I am dereliction of duty
You should make...
The final decision
I can get his photos
It's because I'm determined to catch him
Even if the attack is not a citizen X
I still want to catch it
Anyone who spreads ransomware
Naval Intelligence Command was hacked
What is your military rank?
Captain
Captain?
So you have to take responsibility
right
That's why you were sent overseas?
It was my own voluntary
Because you want to serve overseas?
no
Because you feel bored?
Don't want to wait for the intelligence unit?
I'm adding to the salary
I heard that I have no place to spend money overseas, so I can save money
Not bad
I regret it very much
But now
I want to make a difference
I've talked to the migrant agent
I think they know the most about illegal immigration
That's the only place I can help
Has the police found him?
Prime Minister
BF's Kim Hon is heading to France
-Who told you?
- Director
Take me over
According to BF's line report
We traced a 56-year-old man named Songchaitlan
Departed from Cambodia
Arrival at Paris Charles de Gaulle Airport in three hours
And arrested by airport police
French authorities
He also issued a red wanted order from Interpol
He will be deported to South Korea soon
We'll arrest him tomorrow morning
(Son: What did you do?)
Why don't you tell me?
I'm not sure if there will be any gains
But the bounty is 30 million
That's my money
Your money?
You should have asked for the payment before.
How to say it?
That wouldn't be cool
-Do you want to drink it?
-I'll do it
Director Zheng will send you the money
Including you promised to give
The bounty of those in Vietnam
No
But promise me one thing
If you leave BF, you won't work for other companies
-What?
-May I?
I'm afraid I can't do it
I can't allow that kind of thing
That scar...
Those agents beat you up?
Those terrible and lawless people?
I'm not beaten
We fought
but…
Madam, you have new information
The sender is the director
Jiang Yingshi, read it to me
"It's a pity, but Kim Son saves it
Died on a flight to France
The cause of death is suspected to be acute myocardial infarction
I will give you more details.”
If you want to reply
Please say "Jiang Yingshi, reply"
I know he ran away from the company with the money
But did Yin Zi really kill him?
Maybe it was her fabricating rumors that he stole money
(BF Jin Nan was suspected of being killed by poison)
So scary
How did Jin Shen die when he rescued him? Is it really a myocardial infarction?
(Michimori)
You already know
You claimed before that you didn't know he was a blackmailer
Some people think that it's strange that you still paid the ransom
What do you think about this?
It would be even more strange if I knew who paid the ransom
Some people rumored that you poisoned him, what do you think?
I have no idea
I think poisoning someone on the plane
A plot that only a movie
hateful
No toxic substances were found in the autopsy results
His coronary artery is blocked...
(Fresh root)
It's okay to leave traces
The deceased are a very powerful scientist
He is the best
Yin Zi killed him cruelly
He also used heart disease to cover up, why?
Because he is the person who reported that the culture medium was contaminated
The late Jin Shin-sun rescue
Tell them about their culture solution
Full of bacteria
She slandered him as a useless blackmailer
He also killed him
So, the murderer must...
(Exit BF)
Punished
We want Yin Freedom to disappear
Representative, don't come to the Seoul branch
(Director Zheng Haiden)
You can't come here
Take me to the headquarters
Sorry, are there any other options?
If you mean my home, construction is underway.
No, I should have told you earlier
These protesters are looking for you
Will first lock in the headquarters and Seoul branch
It's easy to guess that you'll be in one of them
After the hacking incident
You shouldn't step in
Laboratory, headquarters or Seoul branch
Should I not go to work because of a South American gangster?
Now is the era of globalization, and they may...
Come running all of a sudden
Ask Director Zheng to find a restaurant
Is there any problem that way?
No
It is impossible to be unobtrusive in a hotel
(High-quality meat)
I can't find a hotel with free rooms on the entire floor
But Agaolo Hotel will check it out
How many rooms can be cleared around the suite
So wait a little longer
But we've been wandering around for 30 minutes
Most hotels have been fully booked these days, so I'll look for them again
Take me to the headquarters
Just go there
yes
Damn, why do they insist on protesting on New Year’s Eve?
represent
Please bear with it for a day
Where are we going?
-To this address
- Start guiding the route
City gate hole?
What's there?
You can stay here
There are only three entry points here, crossing this wall...
And the walls between these houses
Can't see the inner wall from here
We have to watch from the yard
Then I'll go patrol first
Anyway, we have to take turns
good
May I have your name?
Trouble
This is your home
Can I get in?
good…
This is your room
We'll take turns patrolling you'll be able to sleep
What? You little scoundrel
What's wrong?
Why are you like this, Manzhi?
You never welcome me home
Do you don't like your master?
Don't answer that question
It's suffocating
Because its name does not match
Its handsome appearance
Its name was taken by my mother
Better than your name
It will live a long life
It was originally a stray cat
That name is hope it has a strong head
It was originally petite
"Manzhi" must be the strongest name in her mind
But it hides when it sees a man
Never come out to greet me
Has anyone hurt you on the street?
Your house is beautiful
This house?
I grew up here, not paying attention
I'm at your parents' home?
Then your family...
It's OK, they're in the United States
My sister is there
My mother has moved here recently
She lives with her daughter
That must be not very comfortable...
Didn’t you already know?
I thought you did a background check
I won't remember everything on my employee resume
There are a few thousand people
It's going to melt in your hands
I owe you once
How are you?
You must feel unfair
You are not familiar with Li Wenkui
But I suspect you are his confidant
Doubt your motivation to join BF
You know people related to Yazolan
I'm also asking for trouble
Even if you regret going there
I'm asking if you're OK, not me
You should be more unfair than me
Yesterday I was the murderer of the animal industry
Today I was accused of poisoning and killing people
What's the difference?
The former is a tragedy
It is an inevitable result of changes in the world
You did speed up that process
But if you didn't kill Jin and save him, that was a misunderstanding and slander
I'm misunderstanding
So what if you feel unfair about slander?
Then what?
As long as you are innocent
It should deny the allegations and prove your innocence
After that
I can't do anything suspicious anymore
But I don't plan to do that
I'm not going to stop
I think you and I are destined to doubt each other
Because you seem to be insinuating
I may be guilty because I don't seem to be very sad
I know you have nothing to do with his death
-Is she here?
-right
Oh my God, this is so heavy
Wait, give me a minute
This box is so heavy, what is inside?
Go inside and open it
Please enter
I understand, it's a real house
Protect her if necessary
-Loaded?
-No
You can take it apart
Have you used it?
- Are these bulletproof?
- Just do not shoot directly at close range
We're going to deal with more lunatics now
Getting permission is not easy, carry them with you
yes
I'll hire more bodyguards as soon as possible
They can temporarily live in the next house
So you can stay
next door? Where are the residents there?
I offered 10 million a week and they moved away
I borrowed the entire house
Can I rent it for the same price?
-I…
-I'll leave tomorrow
Do you feel uncomfortable?
So...what will happen after New Year's Day first?
All the hotels are full of people
May I?
certainly
Good night
When will Miss Hong come back to work?
She will come back after New Year's Day
Please come to see me then
yes
Very comfortable
Should I stay here overnight, too?
-No
-Good night
Give me a minute
Do you know I have nothing to do with his death?
Then what are your doubts?
Have you ever killed someone?
Is it his family? His wife who has cancer?
Please come in, Director Zheng
I'm very suspicious
You'll kill people because of personal factors
But for your business?
Is it possible?
Ask Director Zheng...
Come in
(No blood)
Her hands and feet died of degenerative brain disease
She doesn't interact with her family
After two crises, she severed relationship with her family.
The first time she was in the early days of BF
When you owe huge debts
The second time was after her mother successfully listed on BF
Convicted of financial fraud in 2022
Two years later
Yin Zixian announces that she will stop paying debts for her family
(delete)
(Do you want to permanently remove the file?)
Happy New Year
He has gained more than just her trust
Was he ordered to tempt her?
I didn't expect that she likes the military type
But how could she go to the bodyguard's house? How shameless
What did your grandfather say?
After Yu Caiyun lured Yin Zi to his house
Must have already returned to him
The bell ringing ceremony has just ended
I haven't had a chance to talk to him yet
You call me as soon as you finish the conversation
I'll call him tomorrow, it's very late
So education is very important
I can't believe she's sleeping at his house
She has no morality
Those stupid nouveau riche
I wish you all your wishes come true this year
I've received enough blessings
I just need one thing
goodbye
good
Representative Yin rejected his father's offer
He doesn't want to do any mergers and acquisitions now
BF is like that woman's child
But children are not as precious as their own life.
She will give up
I know it's there
They just hide it very well
Grandpa, did Captain Yu repay you?
Thanks
The unique features of BF sensing installation
It's its special fabric and structure
Do you think that is entertaining?
This is an advertisement
Advertising must also be entertaining
But that's like a manual
It means that the function is very important...
But we will use the second version
Hello, Prime Minister
Am I available? Now…
I see
It's okay, I was in the car
goodbye
Does he want to see you?
There has never been any good thing when I received the call suddenly
He didn't mention me, you can go there by yourself
-Go to go
-yes
Representative Yin
What's wrong?
Sorry, but I have to go out
Where are you going?
A police station's bullet room was robbed
terribly sorry
I have to go over and decide whether the president wants to be present.
It's okay, go quickly
I invited you here
-I'm rude
-You don't need to explain
It's time for you to set off
You're over?
Yingshi, searching for "Today's police station's armed bullet room was attacked"
Have you received the list?
Eight pistols
Five hunting guns
150 live ammunition, two magazine rifles
Four radios
Three grenades
Grenade?
The Prime Minister will arrive in 30 minutes
(BF Center Road)
Yes, the report just released
But this is the latest news
It said, "A large number of police station ammunitions were stolen."
Dare to steal the weapon room, there must be some shameless scumbags
(In construction)
(Please do not pass)
(Traffic Police)
We are working on the construction, please turn around
Do we want to take a detour?
Turn around
Reversing, lowering your body
-Why?
-Download your body
Open the window
Hold tight
hurry up
come out
English, police
OK, do you want me to call the police?
Walk
Are you scared?
Why?
This will be better
How to die than a brain hole
This will be faster
Just get one injection
represent
represent?
It's fine
No one will get hurt, okay?
I will protect you, I will accompany you
Have you heard it?
You're OK
Breathe, keep breathing, you're fine
Subtitle translation: Song Meijun