(The location and characters described in this play
Organization, scenes and events are purely fictional)
Dominant Species
Hold tight
(Episode 5)
Jiang Yingshi, what's wrong?
Detected gun use within a central radius of 2 km
Causes the alarm to start
Jiang Yingshi, turn on the screen
This is a video of the video of the video
(Go to BF Center)
Send a drone
-Hello?
-Hello
The location is 37.4769 degrees north latitude
Hello? Where are you?
West longitude 127.1592 degrees
Sounds like a game
what happen?
(Check the criminal record)
I've found Yin Zi Representative
Between Qinggeshan Pass and BF
There are about ten militants
You're OK
Breathe, continue breathing
They are there, and our people
-superior
-There are four people
One woman and three men
Two of the men had weapons
Don't shoot at them, they are bodyguards
Here
Deal with the injured first
Dominant Species
free
He needs a blood transfusion now, otherwise he will die of life
I'm a doctor, come here, please move it away
I've helped him
One and two
Representative Yin, it's time to leave
- Director Xu, go quickly
-yes
Representative Yin
Just a bullet passed
I'm fine, he needs help
I can't do anything now
-Jiang Yingshi
-yes
Start the basement of the head office
Go to the basement of the headquarters
one two three
OK, let's go
Give him a bandage
-yes
-Get out
Fast movement
Jiang Yingshi, open the bed
Mr. Yu
Does he have no pulse? Too late?
Jiang Yingshi, starts a medical scan
Still jumping
But it's very slow
Does he need a transplant?
No, his organs are not injured
But the muscle was torn to pieces and blood transfusion was not enough
(No blood)
We're not ready yet
What about the necrotic part?
We will use culture organization
Is it done?
Just think this is our first clinical trial
This is not an experiment
This is
Our first success
(police)
They attacked while there was only one person on duty
It can be seen that they must have been here before
We are analyzing the monitor screen
To identify their identity as soon as possible
Eight people died and five were arrested
A total of 13 people have been arrested
Mr. President, but we have bigger problems
What's worse than a gangster?
The messenger of this incident
It seems that many criminals have been summoned
Use drugs as bait
Yes, drugs
They took the gun
Then launching an attack in Qingge Mountain means...
"A group of ex-confessors conspired to kill
Business celebrities in exchange for drugs
The police equipment that should have protected the people was still used.
Gossip will say that
Someone was injured or killed in BF?
Who is it?
The injured person is unknown
However, when the rescue arrived, the injured were unconscious and had severe blood loss
We believe the injured cannot survive
I will report the latest casualties in person. Goodbye
South Korean Police Department will report details of casualties after confirmation
Let's go
Shooting in broad daylight is already amazing
Their boldness and viciousness are unprecedented
BF's Yin Zi Representative and her employees
Escape from the scene...
Jiang Yingshi, call Yin Zi Representative
Yes, call Yin Zizhong
Your phone will be transferred to…
Jiang Yingshi, call Yu Caiyun
Yes, call Yu Caiyun
(Yu Caiyun)
Receive the call
Call Jin Haosheng
(Dashboard)
Is it immune rejection?
All we can do is that much
They must be fused
What's going on?
breathe
Continue to breathe
Mr. Yu
His vestibular cochlear nerves were damaged
Yingshi, is there any infection?
Mr. Yu's vestibular cochlear nerve and cochlear nerve
The damage is up to 60%
His left ear may lose hearing, tinnitus or dizziness
But his right ear is fine. Is it an old injury from the past?
It's an explosion
explode?
Was he injured by the grenade?
No, it looks like an old injury
At least a few years
Where is your injured part?
No impact on current job
You retired due to injury
No effect on me
Did he not receive treatment?
Isn't it?
Look, it's successful
Oh my god, I...
I can't believe it's successful
I haven't seen this before
We don't have
Director Xu
What's up?
Now only trauma needs treatment, you can leave
That's it...it's okay
Hello?
I'm fine
I'm really fine
The police are coming now?
Wait a moment
Director Xu, you will be escorted to the hall in five minutes
Yes...is it?
I can't believe I'm going to have a bodyguard
"They detoured because of construction
The gunfight happened there."
That's fine
Police are concerned about the injured who were seriously injured during the rescue
represent
I'm fine
Is the police outside?
Yes, they want to know what happened
But what about your bodyguard? How do you walk alone?
Tell them that we will cooperate with the investigation
As for the injured, he was said to have been taken to the hospital.
-Who is the injured?
-My bodyguard
Are both?
Five minutes later, someone was sent to escort Director Xu home
The last time I saw Delegate Yin, she was about to go to the basement
basement?
Yingshi, floor plan showing basement
Sorry, you don't have the relevant permissions
Monitor screen in the basement
-English
-yes
Don't let anyone in
Yes, ma'am
Yingshi, turn off the noise
Currently, the measured value of external noise is 27 decibels
I did not detect special noise
Turn off that noise
What noise are you referring to?
Please turn off that noise
His surface antigen is being replaced by cultured hemocytogenes
His heartbeat...
Miss Hong is right
She said you look extremely calm
Did she and Director Xu leave?
Yes, you should go back and rest
Where should I go?
The owner of that house is here
When will your house be built?
A few more months
I'll stay here tonight
Those people are chasing you
It's not him that you should worry about now
Who will take care of Manzhi?
Your phone number is unanswered and will be forwarded to you...
(Emergency Center)
They came to me
(BF is afraid of attacking the suspect, Yun Nan)
They promise
As long as I cooperate, I will provide the right to supply
He said "they"
It refers to a gangster named "Archit's Forest"
Yes
They're kidnapped
Notorious with the murder of a rainforest environmentalist
Last year they even issued a hunting order to BF Yin Zi's
The suspect said
As long as he cooperates, the gang will provide him with the right
Then what is the "right to supply"?
Methamphetamine
This overseas gangster
Convincing a Korean drug addict
Murder the CEO of a company in exchange for drugs
Sounds too exaggerated
Can't believe this really happened in South Korea
The suspect is also very bold
In fact, he ransacked the police station's bullet room
Prime Minister Mr. Xian Yuzai
I have just publicly apologized for this matter
We are unparalleled in this unprecedented
I feel deeply sorry for the lack of safety
Promise to your dear nation
We'll target this
Improve relevant measures
About Yin Ziyi
Or new news about the safety of her employees?
Fortunately, no one died because of this
What's even more shocking is
Although it is a minority opinion
But some people believe that this gun battle was directed and performed by Representative Yin himself.
They claimed that Yoon represented the murder of the BF's Kim surnamed Superintendent
And plan this gun battle to distract the public
This representative almost died
Why are they still criticized?
We must think about cell culture technology for this society
Pros and cons
They criticized me...
(Park Jeon-won)
(Captain of fishing boat)
Say I'm destroying the environment, saying I'm sticking to the rules
Now they want to raise fish?
How do I...
Father
That's what you said
Have you found other uses for that soldier?
What's the meaning?
Yin Ziyi will try his best to save him
After all, she's sleeping at his house
If BF saves him, it means the time has finally come
If they fail, it means they are not ready yet
Thanks to you, I can wait and see
Your imagination is too much, Father
I'm the Prime Minister
Those lunatics robbed the bullet room
Destroy our peace and security
The people were scared and trembling
But do you think I am behind the scenes?
How dare you pretend to be innocent in front of me
I'm not pretending to be innocent
Do you think of me this way?
You really think
I ordered those people
Fired a gun at Yin's bodyguard for observation
Did her reaction?
So it's not you?
Of course not
All right
We can almost confirm the full effect of Omega Company
It is about to withdraw from the meat cultivation market
I'm not sure if the United States and Europe will have different reactions
We said we will
Put more money into microbial plastics
But we never said we would give up on cultivating meat
Representative Yin?
Contact Quanji Omiga Company
It's not the meat culture department, it's the microbial department
Tell them
We are interested in investing in their microbial technology
But we never invest in biological products
We won't
We express interest in biological products
Only to find out their voice
Then they will decide whether to make the meat
-good
-I understand
We will have a meeting later after we have the results
yes
I have to go to a place
It's handed over to you
All right
What?
Look at you
I'm fine, it's nothing
I patrol the whole house again
You don't have to worry, it means
Thank you
You all depend on it
Listen to my instructions carefully
Full plant
hello
Very sorry
You must be lonely and scared
Why is it coming again?
What's going on? Where is Mr. Yu?
I want to ask you
you do not know?
-Is he not with you?
-No
By the way, are those people newly hired bodyguards?
(Please check it out)
(The bed has been turned on in manual mode)
(heart)
(Small intestine)
You woke up? How are you?
Representative, are you okay?
I'm fine
Why am I okay?
You took the bullet from me?
Yes, you've been shot
but…
I didn't see the wound taken out
Will you feel pain? Can you move?
Where are your ribs?
They're broken
It must be painful when moving, do you feel it hurt?
Have you put these into me?
「这些」？
Pig's organ
Have you transplanted them?
No
None, no pig organs, no transplants
So they are human organs
Go out now
You were in this lab
Cultivate human organs
I'll tell you to go out
I know why you guys now...
Worry about the government's close attention
Who are you talking to?
Go back to bed, you can't move
I'll explain everything later
No, I've heard enough
Mr. Yu
Go back to bed
I'll do as you say
You were seriously injured at that time and your life was in full swing
I know you don't remember
But you don't have the right to blame us
You shouldn't have left so early
I don't know what to do
Say it
(Material storage room)
You shouldn't let him go
Then you ask him to come back, he will probably go home
I've tried my best, okay?
They don't obey
Am I too strict?
Maybe I should thank them first
Hello?
Who are you?
However, when the rescue arrived, the injured were unconscious and had severe blood loss
We believe the injured cannot survive
By the way
My grandfather fell asleep
He didn't sleep yesterday
He's worried that you're injured
After all, he sent you there
Please apologize to him on my behalf
Of course it's fine
That's why I'm here
Please sit
I'm fine
You really look fine
I'm really relieved
Someone reported to me before
A civilian was seriously injured
He's fine, either
You two
All recovered very quickly
This is a good sign
Please tell Mr. President
I'll visit him again soon
He is so weak, don't irritate him
You agree with whatever he says
That way you can make him happy
I should
What's the matter with him?
Don't tell me
You really think there are other terrorists running away
The severity of the situation
Severity of the situation
The identity of the victim
All our investigation resources are used to investigate the mastermind
Your locked comrade has not been framed
He's the mastermind
My grandfather has long accepted the facts
Until he heard that there was a delusional retired soldier
For the whole incident
Have some doubts
I've sued
You have no power
You can't reverse the outcome of that case
What about you, Prime Minister?
If I catch the real mastermind, you have a way
Face the consequences?
You're asking me
If your delusions come true
Can I openly and cope?
Listen, Captain Yu
You're so confident
Just show evidence
Then I'll show you
You will witness in person how I deal with those
The bastard who broke the legs of our president
Want breakfast?
I'm almost frozen to death here
It will get colder at night
What do you want to eat?
(Ringer sound volume)
(Ten years ago)
Is it that painful?
No therapy can defeat aging
How is your treatment?
Great, thank you for inviting me
It's my honor to know NBA players
How great it is to be able to live forever with your body
Do you want to exchange it with your company?
Can't use my company
But it is good to trade money for your youthful strength.
Don't be so sure, you want to be young?
Young and not long
Yes, Ruz?
There are novices who want to play me at any time
18, 19-year-old boys, they never feel tired
I hate them
I hate death
I hate death, that's terrible
I don't need to be reincarnated, I'm not interested in the next life
You will probably be the fourth richest man in the world in your next life
I have endless money to spend
With my power, I can handle everything in one sentence
I should live a thousand years
Is there a way for the human body to survive for a thousand years?
More than a thousand years, the life of a human body living for ten thousand years
Will definitely come
I'll make it happen
Then I want to be the first, Mr. President
Of course it's fine
Then you will have one or two hundred years
Can play like a teenager
And I will always be there to watch the game
Ten years have passed
Loose skin
Fragile teeth
Aging organs
I want to replace them with new organs, and I will live forever
I'm more worthy than anyone
Life is forever
Why wait? You've confirmed it with your own eyes
His wound may not be that deep
Maybe the bullet just brushed him
He will know if it is dissected
Dissect him?
That person is still alive
That way, I know what transplant he did
Only by comparing us with their replication technology
Find out their secrets for success
I'm going to fire all my researchers
Before dissection
I've been waiting for a lifetime
In case of transplant
What if he was rejected by his body and rotten inside?
I understand your doubts, you can wait, you are still young
I'm not young, I'm almost 40 years old
And I'm almost 70 years old
You don't look like someone who is almost 70 years old
But I can feel
Even if you have a good night's rest
The whole body still hurts as if it had been beaten
Representative Yin has just been involved in a gun battle
If something happens to Captain Yu, it will only make them more alert
Are you standing with them?
Why do you always protect Yin Zi?
Boldness and recklessness are different
I don't want to listen to your preaching.
This is what you said
I learned it from you
Father
He is now like a goose that can lay golden eggs
We're going to take it slowly
Can be done like someone chasing her
Not caught her, but instead caught her bodyguard
Having said that, we owe those people, as...
What are their names?
-Aqi Forest
-right
Thanks to them, her bodyguard was injured
We finally know it's time to take over BF
What?
It doesn't matter, he's his own
but…
Where have you been?
Let's go in
(Chest scan treatment)
Because you're seriously bleeding
We lost 1.6 liters of cultured blood
Also added to cultivate muscle fibers in your wound
Your broken ribs and arm muscles
The surgery itself is very simple, it cannot be called a transplant
The point is whether they will
Fusion with your cells or being rejected by your body
But according to your current situation
The result is very successful
Artificial hematopoiesis may cause the number of red blood cells to go wrong
Causing heart disease
Am I wrong?
No
You have the only screening test
and obtained approved artificial blood
Don't I know the only one?
It has not been approved yet
There are no side effects in cultivating muscle fibers
We're not sure yet
Over-dividing of cells
There are also derivative cell cycle problems
We don't know when that will happen
Don't you know?
You exercise frequently, you must know
It is strong muscle fibers
Let your fractures and gunshot wounds recover so quickly
Blood is also bone recovery
Very important factor
Then why treat my ears?
Your ears?
-Is there any?
-Yes, wait a moment
(Audio inspection)
(12000 Hz)
What's that sound?
Turn it off
(Audio inspection)
(30,000 Hz)
It was 30,000 Hz just now, and the human ears probably won't hear it.
Did you help him implant the chip?
You want to try it too
If he can be fixed, why bother to hesitate?
「修好」？
Did you implant the chip?
If you don't like it
-We can remove it at any time
-Inlet
Extremely angry
That electronic chip...
It should be said that electronic skins are not illegal
It is still in the development stage
But it's almost exactly the same as the real skin
It can cure you
Who wants you to cure me? I don't have
Did you tell the doctor this way?
Don't heal your ears?
Why not treat?
Why do you punish yourself?
I didn't say that
You deliberately chose not to undergo surgery, why?
I'm afraid I'll become useless
Why is it useless to receive treatment?
My injuries are close to the vestibular system
Treatment may hurt it
The doctor said I might not be able to walk
I don't want to be a burden to my family
So choose not to operate
The sound is small now
Without noise reduction, it makes me deafening
Everything sounds like an explosion
How can I cure me?
Have you activated the noise cancellation function?
But can you still hear us?
Freedom, our technology has made great progress...
Enough
I said enough
Let him go
-How high is the setting value?
-Highest
Are you crazy?
I did the first time and don't know how to set it up
I asked him to stay yesterday, but he left
Lower it quickly
Get treatment
Keep your promise
You told me that everything will be fine
It's fine
No one will get hurt, okay?
You said no one would be injured
You're leaving, you're lying
Keep your promise?
We meet on the first day
I want you not to use me as a cultured meat for experimentation
When will you treat wealth as your life?
How much do you plan to use these organs?
Stop talking nonsense, you don't know...
Hello
(Class A)
Subtitle translation: Song Meijun