♫ Ask the sword, the knife, to cast away resentment ♫
♫  I fear that new and old grudges will add to my troubles ♫
♫ Ask each tactic, each trick, to test who is more skilled ♫
♫ The ups and downs of life are difficult to predict ♫
♫ Ask the road and journey across remote lands  ♫
♫ Where is my soulmate? I'm so lonely ♫
♫ Ask the rain and clear skies about the troubles on my mind ♫
♫ Face the moon every day and night ♫
♫ Ask the flowers and leaves, their colors are perfect ♫
♫ Happiness and pain are fleeting; how many springs remain? ♫
♫ Ask autumn and winter, the snowstorm continues ♫
♫ The rainbow scatters easily but the days are hard to endure ♫
♫ No one knows why the flowers blossomed early ♫
♫ Heaven doesn't laugh, for it has grown old ♫
♫ The pugilist world is small, but the rest of the world is vast ♫
♫ I've forgotten those who are gone ♫
♫ No one knows why the flowers withered early ♫
♫ Heaven feels no sorrow for it has grown old ♫
♫ The heroes have died and little time is left ♫
♫ I've forgotten those who are gone ♫
[Word of Honor]
[Episode 1]
Twenty years ago, after the evil Rong Xuan was killed in Mount Qingya
by the Five Lakes Alliance and other heroes,
he left behind an armory that could make someone become invincible overnight.
However, in order to open the armory, one must first find the Glazed Armor.
Afterwards, the nursery rhyme spread across the land, causing various forces to start
yearning for control over the armory's treasures
and searching for the Glazed Armor in secret.
Prince Jin, who was located far out in the North, also started to make his move.
[Military Governor's Mansion]
- What happened?
- Look.
Over there, too!
Archers, get ready!
Shoot!
Prince Jin is secretly training assassins in the Window of Heaven
in order to kill important court officials.
He intends on rebelling.
[Officer Li - Military Governor]
[Swordsman in Green - Military Governor's Guard]
My Lord, the Window of Heaven's assassins have arrived.
Hurry and go with me!
Who are you?
Hand over the confidential letter.
No way!
[Zhou Zishu - Leader of the Window of Heaven]
Officer Zhou.
You... You are from the Window of Heaven?
I'm here to see Officer Li off.
Zhou Zishu, all actions have consequences.
You are taking the side of evil.
A future of disaster starts today.
I die without regret.
Officer Li, my apologies.
[Princess Jing'an - Military Governor's Daughter]
Senior Brother Zhou.
Princess Jing'an.
This is...
The Military Governor conspired with corrupt officials
in an attempt to revolt and has already been killed.
Impossible. Impossible.
My father's heart belonged solely to the nation and its people!
Although it is a pity,
he deserves punishment for his impure heart.
I am paying you a visit right now in order to let you make a choice.
Thank you, Your Highness. In the midst of chaotic circumstances,
you escorted my junior Qin Jiuxiao's body all the way back to me.
I will never forget your kindness.
Your Highness, you have high status.
If you choose to commit suicide, you will spare yourself from humiliation.
Then shouldn't I be thanking you, Officer Zhou?
You killed my entire family,
and you're willing to give me the dignity of dying unscathed.
Where did you bury...
Jiuxiao?
Four Seasons Mountain Villa.
He is lying next to Master.
The flowers bloom throughout all four seasons,
knowing everything in the world.
[Qin Jiuxiao - Former Younger Lord of Four Seasons Mountain Villa]
How ugly.
Give it to me. Give it to me!
So annoying.
Junior.
If you have found a girl you love, then I am very happy for you.
He once told me
that after he retired from his position,
he would take me to live with him.
[Window of Heaven]
Everything has been taken care of.
Only a few stubborn generals tried to resist.
I killed them.
Leader, Bi Changfeng made a huge mistake
during the mission to assassinate the Military General.
He insisted on leaving the Window of Heaven
which infuriated Prince Jin. He ordered you to deal with it personally.
Uncle Bi.
[Bi Changfeng - Guard of the Window of Heaven, former Member of Four Seasons Mountain Villa]
My Lord, you're here.
Uncle Bi,
you and I are the only remaining members of the Four Seasons Mountain Villa.
Eighty-one of our brothers came to Jinzhou with you.
Now it's just you and me.
Even Jiuxiao is dead.
How could Four Seasons Mountain Villa still remain?
How come your wounds still have not healed?
Shadows without traces. Entry without exit.
Know everything. Be everywhere.
These were the four tasks
that Prince Jin requested of me when I first created the Window of Heaven.
Once you enter the Window of Heaven, you cannot leave.
You know that.
I know that I can't walk out,
but can't I be carried out?
Even if I can only live freely for one day,
it's still better than continuing to be Prince Jin's running dog.
You'd rather become a cripple
than continue working for me?
Over the years, we've followed the Mountain Villa through thick and thin.
I did everything you asked me to.
However, the members of our Four Seasons Mountain Villa were continuously persecuted.
It made me unable to not begin questioning Prince Jin's intentions.
Now that we have come this far, I really cannot continue.
Let's not even mention the seven nails.
Even if I have to endure thousands of blades, I would still quit!
I know you have no other choice, and I don't blame you.
If our relationship over the years still matters to you,
please give me the nails.
That's true. All I can do is send you off personally.
Don't worry. I will take care of your family.
I won't even know
whether I should rest assured or feel worried.
My Lord, please.
[Han Ying - Commander of the Window of Heaven]
[Duan Pengju - Vice Leader of the Window of Heaven]
That Old Bi Is really a tough man.
No ordinary person can endure the Nails of Seven Orifices and Three Autumns.
Brother Zhang, what exactly are the Nails of Seven Orifices and Three Autumns?
The Nails of Seven Orifices and Three Autumns promises death in three years.
Once you are pierced with these nails,
you will not only lose your martial arts,
but you will also slowly start to lose your five senses.
In the beginning, you will be unable to speak,
hear, smell, or see.
Then, you will become insentient.
Only this way will you be unable to leak the secrets of the Window of Heaven outside.
Although you become a cripple, you still understand what happened.
You are allowed to live for three years before it's lights out for you!
Th-Then why would anyone want to suffer through that?
Wouldn't it be better to just die?
Look at you. Would they really let you die so easily?
This is the rule of the Window of Heaven.
They make you feel an immense amount of fear in order to make sure that you do not dare to think about leaving!
If one day, you lose your mind and don't want to stay here anymore,
pretend to accidentally fall on your blade during the mission.
You'll die quickly without torment.
After you die on a mission,
our lord will even take care of your family.
No, I dare not.
I will only be loyal to the Window of Heaven
and our lord for the rest of my life.
What did you call me?
My Lord.
No, no, no! Leader.
I'm sorry.
I thought all of the elders referred to you like that.
The last member of the Four Seasons Mountain VIlla is gone.
Don't ever say "My Lord" again.
♫ The East Wind blew my heart to the empty city last night ♫
♫ Descending silently onto the mortal realm ♫
It's been ten years.
Ten years on this path of no return.
I remember each and every face of the Four Seasons Mountain Villa members who died in front of me.
They're all dead.
I am the lone survivor.
Why?
Of course, it's because I don't deserve a good death.
It serves me right to keep living.
The Leader of the Window of Heaven.
I am above hundreds of thousands of men and only below one.
I live showing off my military power like this,
yet I can't even save a single person I want to protect.
♫ Am I only able to achieve my dream after letting
a few others down? ♫
♫ The wind is rising ♫
♫ Suddenly bearing witness ♫
♫ People are all gone in an instant ♫
[Lichun Hall]
How come Zishu still hasn't come to see me?
[Prince Jin]
Have his injuries still not healed?
Your Highness.
The treacherous official has rallied many people who are skilled at martial arts.
Leader hadn't fought anyone for a long time.
This incident must have aggravated his internal injuries again.
He has been resting in isolation for the past few days.
How long has it been since he spat blood and fainted
at the news of Qin Jiuxiao's death?
About a year, right?
Your Highness.
Yes.
He becomes like this just for Qin Jiuxiao.
He won't be of great use.
Tell him to come to see me as soon as possible.
Yes.
[Chongming Court]
The flowers remain in all four seasons,
knowing everything in the world.
Eighty-one of our brothers came to Jinzhou with you.
Now it's just you and me.
Even Jiuxiao is dead.
How can Four Seasons Mountain Villa still remain?
In order to leave the Window of Heaven,
I spent a year and a half
inserting the Nails of Seven Orifices and Three Autumns in my body.
There are actually two ways to insert the nails.
If you insert all seven nails in at once,
the person being tortured will quickly lose his senses,
and he can only live as a cripple for three years.
However, if you insert one nail every three months
and let the nail gradually start to meld with your skin
and become part of your body,
you will still retain half of your martial arts skills
even though you will only have three years of life,
and your senses will only disappear slowly
until death.
You just have to endure the extreme pain
that will last for three years and another 18 months.
Senior Brother, don't!
Jiuxiao?
Why are you crying?
What's there to cry about?
It's what I deserve.
The eighty-one brothers from Four Seasons Mountain Villa
all died in my hands.
Our heritage is terminated.
I couldn't protect a single one of you.
I even killed your lover.
After I die,
how can I face you?
I wonder...
whether you and Princess Jing'an have met or not by now.
She's telling on me, right?
How could such an evil senior brother like me even exist?
How could my meeting gift with my sister-in-law
be a bottle of poison?
Guard Zhou Zishu is here!
Come in!
Greetings, Your Highness.
Please get up.
You really don't look well. Get some rest.
You are a pillar of this country.
I need your help to achieve my goals.
I was an ordinary man in Jianghu,
only fit to be your weapon.
Now that Hedong is peaceful,
you need people who know about government to help you.
I can only fight... and can't be of great help to you.
Zishu, what do you mean by this?
Zishu!
My will has broken.
My wounds are not recovering and I cannot be a big help.
My bones yearn to go home.
I've already left the Window of Heaven.
I asked myself for the punishment of the Nails of Seven Orifices and Three Autumns,
and I applied it to myself.
These nails... I've already inserted six of them.
If I insert one more, I'm afraid I won't get to say goodbye to you.
I hope you can consider the merit of my hard work, even if I have no merit of any achievements,
and fulfill my wishes.
Good.
Very good.
Zhou Zishu, no wonder you're the Leader of the Window of Heaven.
You're cruel and decisive, even willing to hurt yourself like this.
Your Highness, please calm down.
Since you don't want to live, I could've fulfilled you!
Why would you go through so much trouble?
You saved my life.
If you allow it, I can drag this crippled body along for two extra years.
If you don't, then take my life.
You all lied to me!
Yunxing left.
Beiyuan...
Beiyuan is gone, too.
I'm really alone in this world now.
Zishu, you were lying to me, right?
If I spare you, are you willing to help me
to achieve my goals?
Please give me the last nail.
You'd rather be a cripple
than be my trusted official?
Fine!
I understand your intention now.
Nails of Seven Orifices and Three Autumns, death in three years.
Zhou Zishu, you must live properly!
Three years.
Within three years, I will rule the nation and ascend the throne!
I'm going to show you that I
am the chosen one,
and I will be successful no matter who I lose!
I will try my best.
Pengju, do as he says.
From now on, you are the Leader of the Window of Heaven.
Leader, His Highness means...
Congratulations to us both.
We both got what we wanted today.
The rivers flow.
Heaven's window leads to the underworld.
Rumors endanger justice.
The clouds hide the sun.
Just you wait, Zhou Zishu.
I will let you go for now.
♫ Ask each tactic, each trick, to test who is more skilled ♫
♫ The ups and downs of life are difficult to predict ♫
♫ Ask the road and journey across remote lands  ♫
♫ Where is my soul mate? I'm so lonely ♫
♫ Ask the rain and clear skies about the troubles on my mind ♫
♫ Face the moon every day and night ♫
♫ Ask the flowers and leaves, their colors are perfect ♫
♫ Happiness and pain are both short;
how many springs are left? ♫
♫ Ask autumn and winter, the snowstorm continues ♫
♫ The rainbow scatters easily but the days are hard to endure ♫
♫ No one knows why the flowers blossomed early ♫
♫ Heaven doesn't laugh, for it has grown old ♫
♫ The pugilist world is small, but the rest of the world is vast ♫
♫ I've forgotten those who are gone ♫
♫ No one knows why the flowers withered early ♫
♫ Heaven feels no sorrow, for it has grown old ♫
♫ The heroes have died and little time is left ♫
♫ I've forgotten those who are gone ♫
[Hanging Ghost - Ten Devils of Ghost Valley]
[Ghost Valley]
That treacherous Hanging Ghost
suddenly jumped off the cliff with a vine.
We were caught off guard and could not stop him.
Useless!
We need to see his person if he's alive, his body if he's dead.
Where is his body?
There wasn't a body under the cliff.
[Changing Ghost - Ten Devils of Ghost Valley]
Good. Very good!
It's my fault! I should die a thousand deaths!
Chief, please forgive me!
Please spare my life! Spare my life!
Chief, please forgive us. Kneel down.
Chief, please forgive us.
Hanging Ghost stole my Glazed Armor!
Glazed... Glazed Armor?
Give my order to all 3,000 ghosts in Mount Qingya.
From now on, I want everyone to go out and kill the traitor.
Whichever one of you monsters who can get the Glazed Armor back for me
will be promoted to the head of Ten Devils!
Kill Hanging Ghost! Retrieve the Glazed Armor!
[Three months later, Yuezhou]
Come, come!
After being a beggar for three years,
I wouldn't even switch places with the emperor.
Master! Master, look! That beggar is pretty optimistic.
[Wen Kexing]
That beggar doesn't even have a bowl before him.
[Gu Xiang]
He didn't get any money, yet he's still so delighted.
Maybe he's a fool?
He is... sunbathing.
Sunbathing?
What's the point of sunbathing?
He's already so skinny.
If he keeps sitting in the sun, wouldn't he become dry?
Master, don't look down on me for not having as much experience in life.
He looks like he hasn't had a full meal for three years.
He may die at any moment, aren't I right?
I bet that he's definitely a beggar.
What's the stake?
If I win, you have to play cards with me for three days!
What if you lose?
Then I'll play cards with you for three days.
Little girl, you're trying to trick me?
Xiao Wu, give him some money.
[Zhang Chengling - Mirror Lake Mountain Villa's Young Master]
Master! Master, look!
Someone gave him money! I won.
How come he's rejecting someone's money?
Young Master, look at him.
He didn't even thank us after we gave him money. No wonder he's a beggar.
Who told you to throw it onto him?
[Fu Ding Pavilion]
Beggar!
I'll treat you to a meal, all right?
Kind lady,
how about you treat me to a drink instead?
Master! Master! He called me a "kind lady."
A kind lady!
Let's bet! Let's bet again!
Okay! I'll treat you to a drink.
Here.
Are you not afraid that it's poisoned and you'll spill your guts after drinking it?
Good wine.
It's worth it even if I die from poison.
Toast to you!
Thank you, kind lady.
Kind lady.
Here.
Miss, your martial arts are really good!
Let me ask you. Why don't you want their money?
You want wine but not money.
You're such a picky beggar!
Who says I'm a beggar?
I'm just here to sunbathe.
You're trying to trick me into giving you wine? Give it back!
I can't give back the wine, but you can have my life.
Do you think I don't dare to take your life?
Miss, how could you bully a sick person with such good martial arts skills?
Martial artists should help the poor and the weak.
You should be righteous and just!
Little idiot, are you lecturing me right now?
Be careful. I might cut off your tongue!
Kind lady, you have quite a sweet face but such a fiery temperament.
I don't believe it!
♫ The sky is gray as I cross the cold river,
my duties taken care of ♫
♫ Smiling at the absurdity of the moon's reflection in my cup ♫
♫ Who allowed me to roam around the world on horseback? ♫
♫ Who is drunk in their dreams but can't find
the homeland when they wake?  ♫
♫ The cold rain of autumn kisses my windows ♫
♫  I don't mind hate and slander, but my melancholy persists ♫
♫ The spring breeze brings greenery along the river  ♫
♫ But can't warm the ice in my heart ♫
♫ Is that our light that appeared out of nowhere? ♫
♫ I resent being unable to meet you earlier, but it is not too late ♫
♫ Don't let the flowers of the seasons down ♫
♫ Give up the adventures on horseback for a peaceful,
quiet life by the stream ♫
♫ The lights of thousands of families light up thousands of hills ♫
♫ The past disappears like smoke waves in a sandstorm ♫
♫ I will clear away my cold past and happily spend the rest
of my life making wine and tea with you ♫
♫ No matter the height of the mountains or distance of the sea,
I will be with you ♫