♫ Ask the sword, the knife, to cast away resentment ♫
♫  I fear that new and old grudges will add to my troubles ♫
♫ Ask each tactic, each trick, to test who is more skilled ♫
♫ The ups and downs of life are difficult to predict ♫
♫ Ask the road and journey across remote lands  ♫
♫ Where is my soulmate? I'm so lonely ♫
♫ Ask the rain and clear skies about the troubles on my mind ♫
♫ Face the moon every day and night ♫
♫ Ask the flowers and leaves, their colors are perfect ♫
♫ Happiness and pain are fleeting; how many springs remain? ♫
♫ Ask autumn and winter, the snowstorm continues ♫
♫ The rainbow scatters easily but the days are hard to endure ♫
♫ No one knows why the flowers blossomed early ♫
♫ Heaven doesn't laugh, for it has grown old ♫
♫ The pugilist world is small, but the rest of the world is vast ♫
♫ I've forgotten those who are gone ♫
♫ No one knows why the flowers withered early ♫
♫ Heaven feels no sorrow for it has grown old ♫
♫ The heroes have died and little time is left ♫
♫ I've forgotten those who are gone ♫
[Word of Honor]
[Episode 23]
Uncle Shen, let me show you out.
Does your wound... from back then hurt?
It's nothing.
I owe the Wen family
much more than just this debt.
Then... where do you plan to go?
I at least have to find your Sister Xiaolian.
It's just that she's been gone for so long, I am worried that she...
That's impossible!
My master said Uncle Gao destroyed the Glazed Armor during the Heroes Conference
just to protect you.
The people who kidnapped Sister Xiaolian definitely won't hurt her!
I hope so.
My eldest brother has only a few kin.
If I can't even protect her...
Chengling, now that I've seen that you've become a disciple of the Four Seasons Mountain Villa,
I feel so happy for you.
We brothers owe the Wen family a deep debt.
You must be obedient and filial to your masters.
That will help us make up for some of the mistakes.
Uncle Shen, I understand.
If I find Xiaolian, I will take her to the Mount Dagu Sect.
However, if one day, I am no longer living,
no matter whether or not Xiaolian is your fiancee, can you look after her some?
If you can, take her to Four Seasons Mountain Villa.
She's a lone girl with no one to rely on. Will you?
All right. Even if you did not say so, I would still take care of Sister Xiaolian.
Good child.
I'm leaving now.
Take care.
[Li Residence]
He still hasn't woken yet?
A'Xiang, has Old Wen coughed up blood and fainted before?
No.
But when I was young, Master was often sick in bed.
After I grew up, it stopped happening.
Since when did you follow Old Wen?
I have been with Master for as long as I can remember.
Then...
when did he get there?
Get where?
It's nothing.
Little girl, go rest.
I'll look after him.
No, I'm going to stay with Master.
Then you aren't going to take care of
that Young Warrior Cao who isn't eating or drinking because he's staying with you?
Why should I care for him? Master is more important!
Good girl, go rest a bit.
I'm here.
Fine, but if Master wakes up,
you have to let me know right away!
A'Xing was wrong. Chief, please punish me again.
That's right.
You must remember that this is the Ghost Valley.
Not valley as in mountain valley, but as in venomous parasite.
(T/N: Valley and venomous parasite are homophones)
Only the strongest king of the valley, who is venomous and cruel enough to destroy everything,
has the right to live.
In a place where tens of thousands of dark souls reside,
if I am to live, you must die.
Everyone is afraid of pain, but you are not.
Instead, you enjoy pain.
Then you will live, and they will die.
A'Xing, you entered the valley young.
Being able to live to today
and become the talent you are now was not an easy task.
I am teaching you only because I have high hopes for you.
A'Xing is thankful and will remember from the depths of my heart.
Good.
Whether or not you can become the next Thousand Venom King and Thousand Evil Chief,
will depend on your luck.
Old Wen, you're awake.
A'Xu.
You've been unconscious for a whole day and night.
Hurry and adjust your inner breath.
Your pulse is normal, so I didn't dare to give you any random medicine.
It's all right.
My inner breath flow might have just been interrupted.
Where's Shen Shen?
I've already driven him out.
Why would you?
Although Shen Shen is an ignorant and selfish person,
he ultimately was tricked and does not deserve to die for that.
These years, those brothers have also been tortured by their consciences.
Conscience?
Zhou Zishu, do you think everyone has a conscience?
Since Shen Shen was shameless enough to ask where my parents were,
I should've sent him down there to see them!
Old Wen, in the end,
the sinner was the one who placed the poison, Zhao Jing.
Everyone else had their own difficulties.
Now you're telling me everyone has difficulties?
Did my parents not have difficulties?
The difficulties of evil people are difficulties, but good people should just obediently accept death?
You can be the Bodhisattva if you want to!
I would rather be the chief of thousands of devils and stay in Hell forever than suffer silently like that!
Old Wen...
I'm sorry.
This was your own personal grudge, after all.
I shouldn't have decided for you.
I'm sorry.
I just didn't want to see your hands get stained with fresh blood again.
Well, no matter.
If Shen Shen died by my hand,
that would give him the chance to atone for his sin with death.
That would be too cheap of a price.
Let him live well then! Let him watch the dogs in the Five Lakes Alliance.
Once you've fully recovered,
I'll go with you to take revenge on Zhao Jing.
I was fine, anyways. Just a little parched.
Hurry and serve me.
Do you need me to change it to wine for you?
If we're going, then we're going after you've fully recovered.
These Five Lake Alliance people are full of talk about righteousness and morals,
but actually, easily betray others. Coincidentally, the position of leader of the alliance
fell into the hands of a heartless, ruthless bastard.
Doesn't this count as karma?
When I look at these dirty, rotten dogs biting each other,
it's even more satisfying than killing them myself.
Master!
Master, you scared me to death!
You're so noisy.
Master, how do you feel? Is your head still dizzy? Are you still hungry? Should I cook something for you?
I just think you're super noisy right now.
You guys talk. I'll go see if Chengling finished making the food.
Master, you—
It's Water of Oblivion.
If My Lord does not betray me,
I will not betray My Lord.
Beloved Jing.
- Master.
- Beloved Jing!
- Beloved Jing...
There are many people in this world named Zhao Jing.
Perhaps the Zhao Jing this crazy woman calls for is merely coincidental.
I'm not going...
But if it's really a misunderstanding, why did Father specifically order Lustful Ghost to kill her in order to shut her mouth?
Beloved Jing...
Beloved Jing... If My Lord does not betray me...
I will not betray My Lord.
Beloved Jing...
What do you want to do?
What can you do?
I just want to check her pulse, that's all. Move aside.
Do you want me to butcher you as well?
She's become like this
because she drank the Water of Oblivion?
No.
The Water of Oblivion will only make people forget what they are most obsessed about.
It won't damage their consciousness.
My master originally had an old illness.
Perhaps someone agitated her Soul Leaving Illness,
which led to this.
Forget what they obsess most about...
That means that what she wants to forget
is the person who failed her.
How do you heal this?
If My Lord doesn't betray me...
Forgive me, Scorpion King. I've never drunk the Water of Oblivion.
I didn't enter the Valley voluntarily.
I had nowhere to go.
When I wanted to commit suicide, it was Master who saved me
and took me back to Mount Qingya.
The chief took pity on me and allowed me to be an exception.
You are the one who should drink the Water of Oblivion the most! What exception?
Because I thought as long as I remembered everything,
I wouldn't make the same mistakes.
If you remember everything as you wished,
then why did you go back to Yu's side?
Scorpion King, have you ever seen those who are addicted to gambling?
The more you gamble, the more you lose, but the more you lose, the more you gamble.
Giving your heart away
is the greatest bet.
I bet on the wrong treasure.
I thought I could happily lose my life for him,
but thanks to Master's help,
I lived some extra years as a partial human, a partial devil.
Actually, when Lustful Ghost came to kill her,
I thought I should block the attack for her.
Might as well lose everything.
But who expected that Heaven
would actually let me win a round?
Silly idiot.
How did Ghost Valley
raise a human like you?
Department of the Unfaithful.
Why is it called that?
Because Master previously said
since ancient times, men have been unfaithful while women have been unfortunate. (T/N: unfaithful is literally "poor in emotion" and unfortunate is literally "poor in luck")
She wants to uphold justice for all women who have been harmed by unfaithful men
and kill every traitor to love in the whole world.
Being fickle and lacking in righteousness is the natural disposition of people.
What does it have to do with gender?
Ridiculous.
What kind of person lives a life without turning their backs on others,
and who hasn't ever been betrayed before?
Your life has been too full of suffering.
I no longer want to take it.
How about this?
I will give you one chance to make a choice.
If you are willing to pledge your loyalty to me,
do not even mention that person with the surname Yu,
whatever wishes you have,
I will promise to you.
I do not care what method you use.
Find the recipe for the Water of Oblivion.
Give it to me,
and I will let you go.
Master, when you entered the Valley, you were only seven or eight years old.
Why did you also have to drink the Water of Oblivion?
There were some people who didn't want me to remember certain things.
Apologies, for I have disappointed them.
But you drank the Water of Oblivion,
so how do you still remember?
Such a deep hatred is hard to forget even after one's teeth fall out.
Don't even mention swallowing one measly bowl of Water of Oblivion.
Even if my corpse were torn apart by five horses going in different directions and burned to ashes that were then scattered,
even if I had to crawl back from hell, step by step,
I would still find them and take revenge.
When I was young,
I often had headaches, coughed up blood, and fainted.
That was the consequence of continually defending against the effects of the Water of Oblivion.
This problem hasn't acted up in a long time.
Recent days have constantly been triggering old events.
Perhaps, there will be some effect.
One day,
the migraines might torture me into becoming a madman.
But before that day arrives, my enemies
must all die before me.
Don't be afraid.
Before that day arrives,
I'll make sure you're in a good place.
What would I be afraid of? I'm just angry!
Master, I was raised by you.
If you had such qualms, why didn't you tell me earlier?
I'd risk my life to help you!
I don't want your help.
A'Xiang, let me ask you.
Do you genuinely like Cao Weining?
- Master, what are you saying? I'm asking you about serious matters! Don't interrupt—
- Answer me!
If you don't like him, I'll gut him.
M-Mast...
Then you do like him.
If you like him,
leave for Gentle Wind Sword Sect with him tomorrow.
That Mo Huaiyang is highly skilled in martial arts and has a cunning mind.
He probably won't let his sect get caught in these troubles.
You will be very safe staying there.
Master, you don't want me anymore?
Stupid girl. The road I am taking points towards the netherworld.
You were originally a lost soul that accidentally entered the Ghost Valley by chance.
Right now, you still have a chance to live under the light. Why are you still following me?
Although I have hundreds of complaints against this Cao Weining,
at least he's easily controllable.
Go back to the human realm with him.
Live a simple life.
I doubt he's capable of creating big troubles.
Master, there's something
I haven't had the chance to tell you yet.
I followed Cao Weining
because he said there was a high chance that Gao Chong
gave the Glazed Armor to their
Gentle Wind Sword Sect.
I went together with Cao Weining
because I actually wanted to
help you find out where the Glazed Armor was. That's why I was with him.
But...
But I... I also don't know why
I... I just really ended up together with him.
Master, I beg you. Can you
not attack the Gentle Wind Sword Sect?
I'm sorry, Master. I know I shouldn't say this,
but...
but I don't want him to hate me!
He... He's not related to me, anyway.
I...
I just don't want him...
want him to be in trouble.
Don't worry. This little thing is not worth crying like this over.
But, Master,
I'm scared.
They all say that
humans and devils can't walk on the same path.
Eldest Brother Cao and I aren't the same.
All I know...
is how to kill people, harm people,
and how to prevent others from harming me.
Even my motive for getting closer to Eldest Brother Cao
was impure.
He's only good to me now
because I hid it well.
But once he finds out who I am someday,
if he doesn't take his sword
and kill me,
that would already count as a kind act.
He dares!
If Cao Weining dares to fail you, I'll massacre his whole sect.
Master!
I'm the one who failed him, not the other way around!
Master, I'm so scared.
I think...
the better he treats me now,
the more I think everything is fake.
Just like the snowman you built for me.
Once the sun came out,
it melted.
Didn't I make a bunch more for you afterward?
Don't cry anymore.
But I only liked the first one!
No matter how big and how perfect the snowmen you built for me afterward were,
they were all incomparable to the first one you built together with me.
Master, think about it.
If one day, Zhou Xu found out your identity,
would you kill him and find a new friend?
Enough! Gu Xiang,
don't forget you're the Heartless Amethyst Fiend.
You've only been around humans for a bit, and you've already become as sentimental as a grandmother!
Can I forget? How could I forget?
An ugly wife can still meet her in-laws,
but... but the Ghost Valley's Heartless Amethyst Fiend can't see the light!
All right. I've made my decision.
Listen to me. You've grown up in the Ghost Valley.
You've never walked in the martial arts world.
They don't have any reason to know your identity, so just hide it until the end.
I promise you. I won't hurt the Gentle Wind Sword Sect.
In the future, don't get involved in any more Ghost Valley business.
If I don't call for you, just stay on Gentle Wind Mountain.
Then... Then you don't want the Glazed Armor anymore?
I don't want it anymore.
That Glazed Armor...
was a cover anyways.
Master Wen, you're awake? Are you okay?
I'm all right. Come with me for a moment.
I have something to say to you.
Uncle Wen. Brother Cao. Don't leave!
I don't know how to cook!
Master Wen, you suddenly called me out... Is there something wrong?
I...
When I was half a child myself,
I picked up A'Xiang.
The first time I fed her congee,
I burned her mouth.
The place we lived in when we were younger
wasn't a place for humans to reside.
I could barely take care of myself,
and I originally didn't want that burden anyways.
There were many times where I wanted to throw her away.
But that little thing who could barely speak
was like a little stubborn beast begging for life.
Wherever I went, she followed.
Her mouth was already burned,
but she still smiled crookedly at me,
her only fear being that I would throw her away.
A'Xiang told me about these things before.
I know she's suffered a lot growing up.
The fact that she followed a person like me
and didn't end up too slanted of a person, is already a blessing.
A'Xiang isn't actually my maid.
It's because I saved her, and once she grew up,
she said she would serve me like a slave. That's where she got that title.
Actually,
I've only now realized
that I didn't save her,
rather she saved me.
If there wasn't a little thing like her beside me,
warming the last of the passion in my heart,
I—
I'm telling you all this because I want you to know that
A'Xiang is like my younger sister.
If we exaggerate it, I raised her.
She is more or less like my daughter.
In this life of mine, not that many people ever treated me well.
For the few who did, I will risk my life to pay them back for it.
A'Xiang counts as one of them.
In the past, there were some things
I didn't even dare to think about, for they were too far away.
But now,
they don't seem to be that far anymore.
I want that girl to live well.
I want her to one day
be able to live the simple, happy life of a normal person.
Cao Weining, can you give her that kind of life?
Yes! Of course, I can!
Although I can't give her riches, I can—
I don't need you to give her riches!
Tomorrow, take her back to Gentle Wind Sword Sect with you.
But you must promise me!
Never fail A'Xiang.
In the future, no matter what happens, you must protect her.
Stand in front of her, and make sure she's safe and happy
without a care in the world.
Can you do that?
Master Wen, I understand. Don't worry.
Today, I vow to the heavens in front of you.
The heavens and the earth will hear my vow.
I, Cao Weining, from now until death
will not for any second of any day
do anything that fails A'Xiang!
If I go against it, the gods and devils will abandon me!
Don't speak with such finality yet.
After all, you have only known each other for a short while.
She might not be what you expected her to be like.
If you didn't vow, I wouldn't have forced you to,
but since you took that vow today,
don't think gods and devils aren't real.
In future days, if you fail A'Xiang, I'll be the first to strike you down.
I understand. Of course, I understand her.
To understand someone doesn't have to do with how long you've known each other.
From the first time I ever saw A'Xiang,
I wanted to be good to her for the rest of my life.
Since my wish was granted today,
I couldn't be more happy!
If I fail her later,
you won't even have to say anything! I'll slice my own throat to apologize for my sin.
All right. You're the one who said it.
If you can't live up to your word, I won't let you off even if I became a devil.
Then it's a promise!
A promise.
What sort of father-in-law is so violent?
Aren't you afraid that your son-in-law will regret his words?
Were you eavesdropping on our conversation?
I wasn't eavesdropping! I listened right out in the open.
Weining, if your father-in-law bullies you,
I can take care of him. You just pay attention to treating A'Xiang well.
All right. We're leaving tomorrow. I'll go prepare our things.
Although your little son-in-law is good,
why are you in such a hurry to send A'Xiang away?
Aren't you afraid her stepparents won't treat her right?
Who would dare?
Old Wen,
why are you in such a hurry to entrust A'Xiang to someone else?
Because I already have someone I'm entrusted to,
so I ended up loving matchmaking. I want to settle A'Xiang well
and live a carefree life in the mountains and woods with you as immortals would.
Then Philanthropist Wen,
why don't you practice generosity by matchmaking for me?
Uncle Wen, don't call Brother Cao away for so long!
I don't know how to cook! That pot looks burnt.
What do I do?
He went down the mountain to buy good food. You don't have to cook anymore.
Look at that. What immortal-like life were you speaking of?
With this little brat here,
we will only have a chaotic and noisy life in the future.
A'Xu, is this vinegar or wine?
You can swallow something this nasty?
In this pitiful place,
how could there be good wine anywhere? Just deal with it.
Once we're at Four Seasons Mountain Villa,
I'll dig up the wine I buried under the plum forest
for you to taste.
Master, our villa has a plum forest?
Not only a plum forest.
The martial arts world gifts our villa with the phrase
"As long as the flowers of four seasons are abloom, there is nothing of we are not aware of"
[Address to Five Lakes Alliance Leader Zhao]
Father!
Scorpion, you've come at a good time!
You dealt with the Immortal Dawn Sect well.
Those people Pretty Arhat purposefully let go of ran all the way to Mount Song.
They knelt in front of Shaolin Temple for three days and three nights
to beg the lead monk to help them seek justice.
Guess what that old man Ci Mu said?
He couldn't sit still anymore!
He's currently calling all sects to attack Ghost Valley together.
"Inviting the Honorable Alliance Leader Zhao to attend when the time arrives.
We couldn't be happier."
What do you say?
I naturally have nothing to say.
These fake righteous sects
watched safely from their side
when Ghost Valley was attacking our Five Lakes Alliance.
Now that the knife is on their necks, they understand the pain.
Inviting my Five Lakes Alliance to come out of the mountain
is not that easy. If you want me to come out,
go ahead.
Express your sincerity.
Father, I don't understand.
Child,
you are still too inexperienced.
Gao Chong was also like this back then.
He lived his whole life without understanding this fact.
Think about it. Ghost Valley comes out to do evil,
but aside from some small grudges,
the big problems are all pointed at our Five Lake Alliance.
But Gao Chong decides to hold some Dog Bear Meeting at this time.
The ones that came were only small fries who wanted in on the fun.
Out of the true big sects,
who came?
That's right.
Not one sect leader from the Eight Great Sects came.
Even the Changming Mountain Valley Sword Immortal
only sent a disciple.
That's why,
my child, those so-called righteous sects of the martial arts world
all either have ulterior motives or are no longer strong.
Their schemes only grow from one to the other.
You want them to band together to attack Ghost Valley?
If only for the sake of righteousness and no benefit,
it wouldn't work.
If only for the sake of benefit, but no righteous goals? That wouldn't work either.
Therefore, we can only draw a large circle to include both righteousness and benefit.
Only then can we draw them in.
Good horse, after you are full, make sure to carry our A'Xiang well.
Don't be frisky, be good.
Who's yours?
Little Red and Big Red. Choose one and ride away.
I already prepared food and water for you.
Let's part ways here.
A'Xiang, why are you still upset with me?
What do I have to be upset about? I'm Master's maid.
Naturally, I'm following my master. Go back to your Gentle Wind Sword Sect.
A'Xiang, I was wrong, so don't be angry anymore. Okay?
Who said you were wrong?
You are a great young warrior from a famous sect.
I'm just a wild girl. We don't walk the same path.
Who said you're a wild girl?
Brother Wen!
Master?
Aren't you my maid?
Then, have I become a wild person?
Cao Weining, did you bring your sack?
I brought it, I brought it.
I don't want this girl anymore. I'll sell her to you for three thousand silvers.
Do you want her? If you do, then give me the money, and I'll hand her over.
One gets silver, the other gets their person. No regrets.
Master, y-you bastard!
Look at that! This savage slave is bullying her master.
How can I still have her?
How about this? I'll give you a discount.
A thousand and a half silvers. Don't think that's expensive.
My A'Xu is so hardworking but was only three thousand silvers.
What are you laughing for?
Zhou Xu, why aren't you stopping him?
How can I stop him?
If you don't stop him, then who will?
And she's so fierce.
I'll give her to you for free. I don't want her.
Hurry and take her.
Brother Wen, the heavens are my witness.
I have never treated A'Xiang as if she were a maid.
With your favor, you've entrusted her to me.
Once I've reported to my master,
I'll definitely follow the tradition of dispatching three matchmakers for negotiation and ask for her hand in marriage with ten streets of dowry.
I don't dare to treat her with anything less.
Ten streets of dowry? Doesn't that happen when a family's daughter is getting married?
What do you know?
A'Xiang!
[Li Residence]
Scorpion, help me make a List of Devils.
Publicize it throughout the martial arts world.
But we've already allied with them, so why are we going back on our word?
Father, if you publicize the List of Devils,
isn't that blocking off their path of retreat?
Then... Then how do I order them around in the future?
Scorpion, right now, even the Shaolin Temple has come out.
The time is already ripe.
Anyways, why would we still need those devils?
The wide web is ready and waiting to entrap its prey
within its webs.
Still don't understand?
We want to destroy Ghost Valley,
but the devils are all outside. Who are we destroying then?
As soon as they lose my protection
and cannot move freely in the martial arts world,
where do you think they will go?
You mean...
you want to force them into a dead end, so they can only return to Ghost Valley?
But, Father, if they leave and talk of our plans...
Who would believe their nonsense?
Besides, Gao Chong's alliance with Ghost Valley cannot be confirmed.
It's still unconfirmed even now.
Although we can place that aside for now,
it's still more or less of a negative influence on our Five Lake Alliance.
So during this time,
I just want these evil devils to bite each other.
We can then find an evil Devil to corroborate for us.
"Ghost Valley framed the Five Lake Alliance."
"Their motive was to divide the martial arts world."
Then, our Five Lake Alliance will have been unjustly accused.
Once we've been cleared of blame,
Eldest Brother Gao Chong won't be able to see it.
Wouldn't the sects within the martial arts world be filled with remorse?
At that time, I'll lead all the sects to destroy Ghost Valley.
I'll have power and righteousness
while carrying the remorse from all the sects.
If we were to choose a supreme leader of the martial arts world then,
who could it be but for me?
Father,
how are you so smart?
Even if military general Zhuge were still alive,
he would pale in comparison to your tactics.
You know how to talk.
All you know is how to make me happy.
How can my little tactics match with our virtuous ancestors?
It's just... I have still heard nothing from the Lustful Ghost.
Technically, Yu Qiufeng is not his opponent.
Has that bastard realized something is wrong and gone into hiding?
No matter. Right now everyone in the martial arts world is helping me look for you.
Let me see where you can hide.
♫ The sky is gray as I cross the cold river,
my duties taken care of ♫
♫ Smiling at the absurdity of the moon's reflection in my cup ♫
♫ Who allowed me to roam around the world on horseback? ♫
♫ Who is drunk in their dreams but can't find
the homeland when they wake?  ♫
♫ The cold rain of autumn kisses my windows ♫
♫  I don't mind hate and slander, but my melancholy persists ♫
♫ The spring breeze brings greenery along the river  ♫
♫ But can't warm the ice in my heart ♫
♫ Is that our light that appeared out of nowhere? ♫
♫ I resent being unable to meet you earlier, but it is not too late ♫
♫ Don't let the flowers of the seasons down ♫
♫ Give up the adventures on horseback for a peaceful,
quiet life by the stream ♫
♫ The lights of thousands of families light up thousands of hills ♫
♫ The past disappears like smoke waves in a sandstorm ♫
♫ I will clear away my cold past and happily spend the rest
of my life making wine and tea with you ♫
♫ No matter the height of the mountains or distance
of the sea, I will be with you ♫