♫ Ask the sword, the knife, to cast away resentment ♫
♫  I fear that new and old grudges will add to my troubles ♫
♫ Ask each tactic, each trick, to test who is more skilled ♫
♫ The ups and downs of life are difficult to predict ♫
♫ Ask the road and journey across remote lands  ♫
♫ Where is my soul mate? I'm so lonely ♫
♫ Ask the rain and clear skies about the troubles on my mind ♫
♫ Face the moon every day and night ♫
♫ Ask the flowers and leaves, their colors are perfect ♫
♫ Happiness and pain are fleeting; how many springs remain? ♫
♫ Ask autumn and winter, the snowstorm continues ♫
♫ The rainbow scatters easily but the days are hard to endure ♫
♫ No one knows why the flowers blossomed early ♫
♫ Heaven doesn't laugh, for it has grown old ♫
♫ The pugilist world is small, but the rest of the world is vast ♫
♫ I've forgotten those who are gone ♫
♫ No one knows why the flowers withered early ♫
♫ Heaven feels no sorrow, for it has grown old ♫
♫ The heroes have died and little time is left ♫
♫ I've forgotten those who are gone ♫
[Word of Honor]
[Episode 18]
Chengling, carry this little brute on your back.
Let's get on the road.
Stinking brat, your lower body martial arts skills have improved.
Master!
You're making a fuss over nothing. Where's your propriety?
The road ahead is dangerous. If you don't want to die, follow my footsteps closely.
Qin Huaizhang's disciple, watch this foolish disciple of yours.
Stinking brat, I advise you to make better judgments.
Your cheap mechanism tricks won't work at all on me.
I can excuse your first offense, but if you dare try again,
I'll let Wen Kexing break your fingers.
Why me? Don't you know that my nickname is Philanthropist Wen?
How could I carry out something so torturous and cruel?
- A'Xu, you sort it out.
- Shut your mouth.
Master, why does the Dragon Pool Cabinet Leader live in such a remote place?
In a big world, there are all kinds of people.
(T/N: idiom, "In a big forest, there are all kinds of birds")
But living in such a remote place
with so many hidden mechanisms is frightening at every step.
What if he goes out alone and also gets lost?
Isn't that like putting mousetraps under your own bed?
Putting mousetraps under your own bed?
Once, a mouse came into my room. I couldn't catch it no matter what I did.
So I put two mousetraps under my bed.
However, when I woke up the next day, I forgot.
I took one step
and broke my foot by stepping on the mousetrap.
Stinking brat, people only ever hide
for the same few reasons.
Either he always feels like there's an enemy hunting him down,
so he must hide in a place that no one can find.
- Or else...
- Long Que is a rotten good person.
All his life, he's only ever been taken advantage of. He's never made enemies.
Qin Huaizhang's disciple, your master understood this best.
Then it must be the second reason: grief.
He will never be able to see the person he wants to see ever again,
so he might as well hide and see no one ever again
so as not to be reminded of it by every single person he sees.
If your master dies in the future,
I'd also want to find a place like this to hide in
and see no one.
- Just like... just like Yu Boya breaking his qin?
- What?
(T/N: After Yu Boya's musical soulmate died, Yu Boya abandoned his love for music by breaking his qin into pieces and never playing music again)
Don't worry. It won't happen.
Master's internal skills are superb, and he always does good deeds. He will surely live a long life.
"Those who kill and burn wear a golden belt."
"Those who repair bridges and patch roads have not even a full corpse." (T/N: Old saying that bad people live long lives of prosperity while hardworking good people suffer)
Do you want to die, stinking brat?
Elder Ye, lead the way.
Without entering the tiger's lair, how can you catch the tiger cub?
Don't you want to enter the Dragon Pool Cabinet?
It's right on the opposite side. What?
Are you afraid I'll trigger a hidden mechanism in an attempt to plot against you?
With three great masters escorting me,
can I really create a stir?
Silly brat, I'll carry him.
Let's go. Slowly.
Young Cabinet Master Long, forgive me.
In that case, I'll go over first, A'Xu.
Who said it's your turn? I'll go first.
- Elder!
- Old Monster!
I'm joking with you!
Childish.
Come over!
I'll cross first.
Careful!
I faked my fall, you're falling for real?
Master!
Uncle Wen!
Old Wen.
Old Wen!
A'Xu.
Don't speak.
I'm not in much trouble.
It just feels like my internal organs switched locations.
I just need to get used to it.
- I don't know...
- Where's that stinking brat?
I didn't think he would really have the courage to burn his bridges.
If I'd been smashed into confusion,
shouldn't he have been a pancake?
He never fell down.
Can he actually fly?
Odd.
I watched the position of Ye Baiyi's every step.
How is it that his step didn't trigger anything,
but my step tripped a switch?
This trap...
must've been triggered by weight.
Ye Baiyi's weight alone was not enough to trip it,
but the combined weight of us three set it off.
I originally thought that as long as we had Long Xiao in our grasp,
they would not attack for fear of harming him.
I never expected that Dragon Pool Cabinet's
traps would be so remarkable.
Where is this place?
Why is it so dark?
I thought I'd arrived in the underworld.
This place isn't all that deep.
If you hadn't done that for me...
things wouldn't have been bad enough to cause you to pass out.
As we fell,
we must've triggered the second trap, which is how we ended up in here.
Master!
Uncle Wen!
Enough, enough, enough! Get up, get up!
Stop howling in anguish.
Little fool, use your brain!
That stinking brat set off a trap and was the first one to fall down the gorge.
Do you think he would want to die with that pair?
There must be a trick.
That's right! Master surely wouldn't die!
Uncle Wen wouldn't die either!
Don't worry.
"Sinners live forever." Those two sinners
won't die that easily.
(T/N: Full saying: "Good people don't live long, but sinners live forever")
Old Wen, are you really nervous?
Why would I be nervous?
Then, why are you grabbing on to me?
I'm not.
Drug Men!
At first, I wanted you to die a grave-less death,
but then I thought, this is such a wonderful setting.
If I make you die in confusion without letting you admire it,
what a terrible waste that would be.
Look at these adorable children.
My most delightful work.
This is the group of first Drug Men I produced. They are indeed a little dim-witted,
but anyhow, they are still my firstborn children.
I couldn't bring myself to destroy them,
so I've raised them here in secret all this time.
Sometimes when people passed by, I would open the trap
and toss them down to feed my children some blood and meat.
I've been gone a while, so my children must be starving.
Children, dinner will soon be served.
Turns out the Drug Men were created by the Dragon Pool Cabinet.
Uncle Long was righteous all his life.
I never thought his beloved only son would be such a sociopath,
working with the Venomous Scorpions to create the Drug Men.
Righteous!
He was an unparalleled idiot!
I am his only son.
He knew that there was something in this world that could fix my illness,
yet he allowed me to continue living with an appearance that was neither monster nor human!
This is an affliction you were born with. No cure could fix it.
Even a magical pill that can cure the dead
would not be able to cause you to grow.
What do you know? Miracle Healer Valley's treasured Yin Yang Book
can cure all the strangest and worst afflictions in the world!
Back when Rong Xuan was severely ill with torn arteries,
Yue Feng'er could still save his life.
It can surely cure my affliction! Definitely!
All right. If you say so, it must be so.
“You are the knife, I am the meat."
As long as you are happy.
You!
Why am I wasting my breath on a dead man like you?
The old devil won't help me, but Heaven will.
Even without him, I can open the Armory all the same!
Too bad, you won't get to see
what I will look like when I stand up.
Even if Rong Xuan's life was saved by the Yin Yang Book back then,
so what? He turned evil and became a monster in his madness.
Doesn't that matter to you?
I almost forgot. You always were a madman.
Of course, you don't care.
What do you know?
You want to know the secret of the Ying Yang Book.
You are talking to the right person.
However, I don't like to talk to others while tilting my head up.
Do what you will with that.
You are a descendant of Miracle Healer Valley?
You could say that.
Bastard, who are you trying to trick?
All of the true disciples of the Miracle Healer Valley
are long dead.
Oh dear, I didn't manage to trick him.
Children, eat them clean!
Let's kill them all first.
Fuck! Why are there so many of these damn things?
A'Xu, can you carry on?
Does it make a difference whether I can or cannot? Don't waste your breath on useless questions.
If we can't get through this,
wouldn't it mean I dragged you down?
Take back those depressing, useless words.
Old Wen, "As I have gained a noble friend
I have not wasted my life."
"I am fortunate to have gained one's heart that is like mine."
Listening to you recite poetry gives me a headache!
Long Que! I, Ye Baiyi, am here!
Aren't you going to come and greet me?
Elder, do we go in?
It will be full of traps inside. I'll go in and check the situation first.
Wait right here, don't move.
Mere little tricks.
Elder Ye, watch out!
Kid!
Long Xiao! Get your ass out here!
No wonder no one is able to find the Dragon Pool Cabinet.
Turns out that the pavilion is just an illusion.
The Dragon Pool Cabinet is in the bottom of a deep abyss.
Master!
You didn't die after all! Where's my master?
At this moment, your master has probably begun his journey on the Bridge of Helplessness.
If you walk briskly,
you might be able to catch up with him.
You're lying!
Thank heavens!
I can count on one hand the times I've been chased till I've pissed my pants.
Why have they all been for you?
Your predicament is called, "When you show off too much, you get struck by lightning."
A'Xu! Lord Zhou, have pity on me.
Little old me has hardly suffered much in the lifetime.
Now, I've fallen into the schemes of others and have been put in this bad situation.
If I hadn't met you, my luck would have been all used up.
I've just had eight lifetimes of bad luck!
Let's go.
We seem to be in the belly of the mountain.
I'll scout ahead. You hold them off for a minute.
What? Do you think I'd survive if you threw yourself into danger?
It's not like we've never entered the tiger's den before.
I've thought of a story.
- Once upon a time there was a man in the desert—
- Philanthropist Wen!
I've heard this story before.
I'm leaving!
♫ Heaven is ever-changing ♫
♫ There is no path to run back to ♫
A'Xu! Come on over!
♫ Can cross through dawn and dusk, and scrape the heart ♫
♫ The mortal realm breaks, heaven and earth crack,
the river runs dry ♫
♫ If we don't return, all resentments melt into cloud and smoke ♫
♫ How many reincarnations will it take to fill the gap ♫
♫ before the life and death of the shattered soul resolves? ♫
♫ The waves of the rivers and lakes return,
the universe remains ♫
♫ Our inseverable fate
I guiltlessly steal the sun and moon in your eyes ♫
♫ if I follow the hero's way ♫
♫ I will rise and fall with the wind yet remain
between Heaven and Earth ♫
Many thanks.
♫ If we don't return, all resentments melt into cloud and smoke ♫
♫ How many reincarnations will it take to fill the gap ♫
♫ before the life and death of the shattered soul resolves? ♫
♫ The waves of the rivers and lakes return,
the universe remains ♫
What? You still don't want to get up yet?
♫ If I follow the hero's way ♫
♫ I will rise and fall with the wind yet remain
between Heaven and Earth ♫
All right!
♫ If I follow the hero's way ♫
♫ I will rise and fall with the wind yet remain
between Heaven and Earth ♫
Turns out there's a paradise here.
Old Brother!
Where is this place?
Old Brother.
I never would have thought Dragon Pool Cabinet's mechanical puppetry
had already reached the levels of god-like creation.
What is this devilish thing?
I never would have thought I'd live to hear you call something else devilish.
Watch out!
I just criticized it a little.
Isn't blowing itself up in anger a bit extreme?
A'Xu, this fellow's temper has almost caught up with yours.
Fool!
As expected, sinners live forever.
That silly kid was crying like he lost his parents.
And here you are, entertaining yourself with cringeworthy jokes.
Elder, where is Chengling?
He asked you a question, Old Monster.
Where's our foolish disciple?
Lost.
Little Kid, you run pretty fast.
This Dragon Pool Cabinet of mine is crammed with traps and has thousands of holes and paths.
At your level?
Even if I let you run free,
do you believe me when I say that even if you were to starve to death, you still wouldn't be able to make your way out?
You are very stubborn. Not bad, not bad.
I like stubborn children.
The more stubborn and unbendable your bones are,
the more incredibly crisp the sound is when I knock on them.
Have you figured it out?
What are you rushing me for? Shut up.
Our foolish brat is still in Long Xiao's hands!
I suppose because he's not your kid, you can just lose him!
Old Wen, this formation is complicated and constantly changing.
It's not something that can be solved quickly.
Then forget solving it. Smash ten of them with a blow.
Worst comes to worst, we can just force our way in. I'll clean the whole thing out with a fire.
Foolish young man. Do you know what purple molten gold is?
That's right, you don't know.
Just by looking at that ignorant look of yours, I can tell you definitely have no idea.
Old monster, you still have the spare energy to make fun of me? Hurry up and solve it!
Let me tell you. All you need to know is
that all the traps in this valley come from purple molten gold.
Once the gold catches fire, it will explode.
The force of it can send all of this up to the sky.
This is...
This is a map of the Dragon Pool Cabinet!
Let me go! Let me go!
Why are you holding me captive? If you've got the guts, just kill me!
Youngster, of course I'm not going to kill you.
You are the son of Zhang Yusen, right?
Twenty years ago, your father and my father
were good friends.
Why didn't you say that sooner?
Your father is also good friends with my grandmaster.
Since we have this relationship, we can just speak directly if we have anything to say!
If we didn't have this relationship,
I could've let you die quickly.
However, exactly because your father was a good friend of Long Que's,
I will never let you die an easy death.
Don't worry. The two of them are experts trained by me.
They will make sure you are very comfortable.
Where should we begin?
How about I dig out your eyeballs first?
The human eyeball is a good chemical ingredient for forging machines.
Wa... Wait a moment!
Do you know why I like to be active underground?
Because from the moment I was born,
I have lived in endless darkness.
Since my fate is to belong to the darkness,
I have made it my home.
What's happening?
You like moving around underground so much.
Could it be you were born to be a big sewer rat?
Purple molten gold?
That's right. Your rat hole is full of twists and turns. Even if there was a map,
who would want to crawl through them?
Might as well blow through them all.
My children!
What have you done with my children!
That's my child's heart!
Drug men are your children. Mechanical people are also your children.
You're a rat that specifically breeds a mixed bag.
This place of yours cannot reach the heavens or touch the earth. Where would I have found explosives?
Luckily, you've got enough children.
They were incredibly generous and prepared to sacrifice themselves.
Here, I have one left.
- You can have it back—
- Old Wen! Wait! Wait.
Here, you tell us. Can we remove the needle from my disciple's head?
Zhou Zishu, you killed my children
and used their hearts as explosives.
I will never let your disciple go!
Even if I die, I will take him as retribution!
Stinking brat, you'd better think this through.
As far as I know,
a whole person and a person with four crippled limbs
will have two completely different reactions.
Would you like me to help you experience it?
I was born crippled.
You can't scare me!
I never intended to let you go anyway.
Elder Ye.
Why's this little thing stuck here?
Don't!
Why not?
What are you afraid of? It won't kill him.
If he dies, I'll owe you another.
Master, you came to save me again.
The word "again" is quite on point.
A'Xu, why didn't you check his birth sign and your year's luck before you accepted him as your disciple?
What an unlucky life this disciple of yours has.
Meeting trouble at every step, calamity everywhere he goes.
Master, they were going to dig my eyeballs out.
Cabinet Master Long was a compassionate man for all of his life, yet you are vicious to the core.
Compassionate?
That old fraud!
Watching his own son living a life worse than hell.
You can spew this garbage when you meet your father.
Master, this puppet and this villain
look so similar.
This is the puppet that helped us find the entrance to the underground palace.
Long Que must have created it in his filial son's likeness.
Some people are born to their parents in order to collect a debt.
Master, what's that smell? It stinks so much.
As a walking corpse in a desolate mountain dwelling,
I am unable to treat my guests well, I beg your pardon.
[Long Que, Dragon Pool Cabinet Master]
This is Long Que?
Uncle Long?
Zishu, it really is your voice.
I thought I was dreaming.
Is your master well?
Uncle Long!
Uncle Long, you still remember me?
Master... is no longer around.
I remember. How could I not?
When a person is in so much pain that he cannot face reality,
all he can do is immerse himself in memories of the past.
The moment I close my eyes, I can remember how foolish
you looked when you first entered
the Four Seasons Mountain Villa.
Huaizhang has also passed.
That's right. For some people, even after they die, it's as if they are still alive.
Some people live even worse than death.
Considering the way this son of yours lives, it would've been better if he had been strangled to death at birth.
He is not my son, he is an animal. My son died long ago.
I'm too lazy to give a damn about your messed-up father-son issues.
I also don't give a damn if you want to shut your eyes, plug your ears, and lie to yourself.
However, this little animal of yours is out in the world, lying and harming people,
making up stories under the banner of the Dragon Pool Cabinet. Are you not going to do anything about it?
I can't do anything about it!
Uncle Long!
This evil creature has imprisoned me here
for who knows how many years.
You did such an evil thing to your own father?
You're even worse than an animal!
I'm an animal?
Then, what good is he?
"A tiger is vicious but does not eat its young."
Yet he was so cruel to me.
He knew very well there was something in this world that could cure my illness,
yet he allowed me to worthlessly continue existing, not truly alive or dead.
Even though I treated him in this way, he still wouldn't help me.
What kind of nonsense is that?
Your father worried his heart sick over your illness. Who doesn't know that?
What he's talking about is wanting me to retrieve the Yin Yang Book for him.
The Yin Yang Book in the Armory!
♫ The sky is gray as I cross the cold river,
my duties taken care of ♫
♫ Smiling at the absurdity of the moon's reflection in my cup ♫
♫ Who allowed me to roam around the world on horseback? ♫
♫ Who is drunk in their dreams but can't find
the homeland when they wake?  ♫
♫ The cold rain of autumn kisses my windows ♫
♫  I don't mind hate and slander, but my melancholy persists ♫
♫ The spring breeze brings greenery along the river
But can't warm the ice in my heart ♫
♫ Is that our light that appeared out of nowhere? ♫
♫ I resent being unable to meet you earlier, but it is not too late ♫
♫ Don't let the flowers of the seasons down ♫
♫ Give up the adventures on horseback for a peaceful,
quiet life by the stream ♫
♫ The lights of thousands of families light up thousands of hills ♫
♫ The past disappears like smoke waves in a sandstorm ♫
♫ I will clear away my cold past and happily spend the rest
of my life making wine and tea with you ♫
♫ No matter the height of the mountains or distance
of the sea, I will be with you ♫