♫ Ask the sword, the knife, to cast away resentment ♫
♫  I fear that new and old grudges will add to my troubles ♫
♫ Ask each tactic, each trick, to test who is more skilled ♫
♫ The ups and downs of life are difficult to predict ♫
♫ Ask the road and journey across remote lands  ♫
♫ Where is my soul mate? I'm so lonely ♫
♫ Ask the rain and clear skies about the troubles on my mind ♫
♫ Face the moon every day and night ♫
♫ Ask the flowers and leaves, their colors are perfect ♫
♫ Happiness and pain are both short;
how many springs are left? ♫
♫ Ask autumn and winter, the snowstorm continues ♫
♫ The rainbow scatters easily but the days are hard to endure ♫
♫ No one knows why the flowers blossomed early ♫
♫ Heaven doesn't laugh, for it has grown old ♫
♫ The pugilist world is small, but the rest of the world is vast ♫
♫ I've forgotten those who are gone ♫
♫ No one knows why the flowers withered early ♫
♫ Heaven feels no sorrow, for it has grown old ♫
♫ The heroes have died and little time is left ♫
♫ I've forgotten those who are gone ♫
[Word of Honor]
[Episode 13]
It's raining and the girl is marrying.
The kid has grown up. We can't stop her.
Why should you hold her up?
I think Brother Cao looks like a responsible man.
His appearance also suits her.
Suits her?
Bullshit!
Suits her, my ass.
You were the one who asked A'Xiang to find you a son-in-law,
but you're also the one who can't stand seeing your girl get taken by someone else.
Old Wen, aren't you contradicting yourself?
You're the one who finds all sorts of ways to hide from me,
but you're also the one who says you want to wander around the world with me.
Aren't you contradicting yourself?
Then let me ask you.
In that speech you used just now to coax Cao Weining,
which words were true? Which were not?
Some were true, some were false.
Have a guess.
[Chongwu Hall]
A thousand feet deep the Peach Blossom Lake may be,
it cannot be compared to how deep Wang Lun's love for me is.
(T/N: Presented to Wang Lun, by Li Bai)
What is love supposed to be?
Why would lovers die for it?
(T/N: Yanqiu Poem, by Yuan Haowen)
Why are you annoyingly reciting so many scriptures?
A'Xiang, I'm feeling emotional.
A person has only one life, grass has only one spring.
You see, those like Brothers Zhou and Wen, who can become soulmates and go through thick and thin together,
are incredibly lucky.
However, we must blame the heavens for deceiving them.
Brother Zhou is severely ill.
If he passes away one day,
Master Wen will lose his soulmate.
Why are you worrying about him?
He can't just pour all of his hope on one sickly person.
(T/N: Literally, "he can't just hang himself on one crooked tree")
You're wrong.
A'Xiang, let me tell you a story.
I don't want to hear it.
I want to tell you.
My junior master Fan is a handsome man, but he has never married.
I was naive when I was little, so I once asked him why he didn't marry.
He told me that in a man's life, he might meet many people through fate,
but there's only one person who truly belongs to him and suits him.
If he can't find this person, he might as well spend his whole life muddling around.
It doesn't matter who he stays with.
He would be happy, too.
But if you really do find that one person...
It's like a sword and its original scabbard.
Once they have experienced the taste of intimacy,
if it loses its scabbard,
it will never find another one.
Isn't it just a scabbard? It's not expensive.
You can find someone to make another one.
A customized one.
It will definitely fit.
You can do that with a sword, but what about with a person?
You mean my master and Sick... Zhou Xu?
They are good together.
I grew up with my master since childhood,
yet I've never seen him so... so lively.
♫ The delicate fingertip leaves a red twisted mark ♫
You...
Did your master treat you well?
Of course. There are not many men in our sect,
so we are as close as a family.
Our sect will come to Yueyang Sect soon.
I would like to invite you to meet them.
No.
I would like them to meet you.
What's the point in meeting me? I'm ugly and fierce.
That's nonsense. I like how you look!
How are you ugly?
When I was young, I couldn't understand my master's story
about the sword and the scabbard.
But...
But I hope to... I hope to show you to many of my relatives.
I want to let them know that
I have finally understood it.
You want to use me as an example?
You shouldn't bring me then.
A'Xiang, you're so well-behaved and beautiful.
There is certainly a suitable man who secretly
admires you greatly.
A suitable man?
Why can't I see one?
I can only see an...
Idiot!
"Suitable man"? Nonsense!
I'm only here to take care of Chengling
and join in on the fun while I'm at it.
I shall also learn how to be a human.
What sword and scabbard?
Idiot.
[Hanbi Pavilion]
"My white hair streams for thousands of miles,
stretching just as long as my sorrowful worries."
(T/N: The Song of Qiu Pu by Li Bai)
Master, we have sorted the medicine out for you.
Please remember to take them on time every day.
Shall I find a girl to remind you every day?
Don't nag. Never hold things up.
If that lunatic gets in one of his mad fits again, I won't save you.
Don't worry. I'm well aware.
Master, please take care of yourself.
Qianqiao, come back as soon as you finish your task.
Remember. Never cause unnecessary trouble.
I understand.
I'll leave now.
[Falling Leaves]
Qianqiao.
Master, do you have any command?
Remember to bring your rain gear.
There will be heavy rain tomorrow.
All right.
[Great Wisdom]
Elder Huang.
Apologies for arriving so early in the morning without prior notice.
Sect Leader Yu, a nobleman never comes to such inferior places.
You're the leader of the Mount Hua Sect.
Why are you here at the beggars' territory so early in the morning?
I'm here today to bring some gifts to the Beggar Gangs.
Good.
Your Mount Hua Sect and my Beggar Gangs don't have a close enough relationship for this.
Leader Yu,
do you know that Gao Chong has already turned against me?
You're interacting so closely with me right now,
but don't you fear that your master will be angry with you?
I, Yu Qiufeng, became blindsided and treated an enemy as a friend.
I'll take the blame if you look down on me.
Even so, the grief from my son's murder is absolutely irreconcilable.
No matter how huge of a coward I am,
I still cannot let them get away with it!
Who had the guts to kill the son of Mount Hua Sect's leader?
Ghost Valley?
It was the Five Lakes Alliance!
This Soul Winding Spell sure was useful.
Long-tongued Ghost didn't deceive me.
Considering the strength of your Mount Hua Sect,
how could you have dared to join in on the fight for the Glazed Armor? Bullshit!
You have no proof.
The witness has died.
You lost your evidence.
Just going off of your words and the connection with the Soul Winding Threads,
even if the Mount Tai Sect makes an accusation,
overthrowing the Supreme Leader of the Five Lakes Alliance
will be extremely hard.
Elder Huang, I know another enormous secret.
It's enough to utterly ruin the reputations of Gao Chong and the Five Lakes Alliance.
Say it.
Twenty years ago,
the Five Lakes Alliance led heroes all across the world
on a crusade against Rong Xuan, who had become a demon.
After Rong Xuan died,
the Five Lakes Alliance split the five pieces of Glazed Armor among themselves secretly.
Each of them hid a piece.
It's just a pity that those heroes didn't even know that their sacrifices
were a waste of effort to fulfill the greed of those people!
Elder Huang, the casualties of your Beggar Gangs
were not caused by our Five Mount and Sword Sects.
Once this is exposed,
even if the Five Lakes Alliance doesn't collapse right away,
they will still never have the right to rule the remaining Glazed Armor ever again.
In terms of virtue and ability, the only people who are best suited to lead the martial arts world
are the Beggar Gangs.
By then, we shall force the Five Lakes Alliance to hand over their Glazed Armor
and let the Beggar Gangs lead the heroes to initiate a crusade against the Ghost Valley.
Even this turtle who hides his head in his shell is turning his back on the Five Lakes Alliance now.
The trend has changed.
Gao Chong's end is coming.
[Good Luck Inn]
A'Xu.
What are you doing?
What the hell!
Why are you suddenly disguising yourself?
Remove it.
Don't touch me.
Don't use this face to talk to me in A'Xu's voice.
It's terrifying.
I'll have nightmares!
Isn't it so manly?
How about...
I go back to what I looked like in the past?
Don't! Don't!
This looks better.
I shall make myself handsome then.
Your original state is the best. Stop disguising yourself.
This is for you.
I don't need it.
My face is Heaven's masterpiece.
Staining it is like ruining Heaven's treasure.
The heavens will punish you.
Jokes aside.
The Heroes Conference is being held soon.
Although Chengling has handed in his Glazed Armor,
Gao Chong hasn't announced it publicly.
Therefore, many people will
have their eyes on the orphan of the Zhang family.
Our actions have been revealed.
The enemies are hiding in the shadows, but we're out in the open.
That's why it's necessary to disguise ourselves.
Your face...
is too outstanding.
I don't need it.
Did I mishear you just now?
A'Xu,
finally, you've admitted that I'm good-looking.
Don't worry.
I, Wen, am a troublesome forefather.
All troubles that meet me will immediately retreat.
No need to worry.
Now, you're not playing the role of Philanthropist Wen.
You've decided to play a troublesome forefather?
When have I ever pretended anything?
I'm a kindhearted man to begin with.
What is this for?
You applied this on your face?
This can change the structure of a person's face.
For example, a person's nose or cheekbones.
What about this?
Stop touching!
I just want to know.
Butt pads.
What about this red one?
Since you want to know everything,
why don't you kneel down and kowtow to me three times?
Call me Master and I'll teach you everything.
It's just an insignificant skill.
Why be so picky with who to pass it onto?
(T/N: Literally, "you'll pass it onto a man, but not a woman, a son-in-law, but not a daughter-in-law)
So are you learning or not?
Let me ask you.
Can your transformation skills
really turn you into anyone else?
It's not hard to imitate a person's appearance and voice.
However, every single person has their own speaking habits and unique posture.
Everyone has their own way of presenting themselves.
Therefore, you must either be very familiar with the one you are imitating,
or others must be unfamiliar with the one you are imitating.
Otherwise, you'll be exposed easily.
Then I suppose that if I imitate you,
I will definitely be able to successfully trick your silly disciple.
Just you?
You dare to imitate my incomparable elegance?
The once vast sea has stilled into a plain land.
The snow on the mountains disappeared among the clouds.
Thousands of years pass in the blink of an eye,
yet my heart is still as before.
Why?
Make others do the dirty work.
Let those righteous dogs bite each other.
Isn't that good?
I mean...
Why do you want... me to do this?
Since you left the valley, you often spied on this man.
Did you believe that I didn't know?
Chief.
In this case,
I might as well let you take a good look at him.
Die early and revive early.
I thought I had forgotten everything,
but it turns out that I have forgotten nothing.
I remember everything about you so vividly
as if it had all happened yesterday.
Beloved Feng,
I've lived through two lives.
Why am I still unable to reduce my yearning?
[Yueyang Sect]
[Sword Immortal of Changming Mountain, Ye Baiyi]
I, Supreme Leader of the Five Lakes Alliance, Gao Chong, am here to welcome you, Sword Immortal.
Greetings, Sword Immortal.
Are you talking to me?
Where did this brat come from?
How dare you?
Eldest Brother is here to welcome the Sword Immortal of Changming Mountain.
How dare you simply accept my eldest brother's greetings?
Shan'er! Where's the Sword Immortal?
He's... He's this young master.
You're Gao Chong?
So you're Shen Shen then.
You punk! How dare you call my eldest brother's name?
Young Master,
are you here on behalf of the Sword Immortal of Changming Mountain?
I'll return your Token of Honor!
[Token of Honor]
Young Warrior, you are...?
Ye Baiyi.
Young Warrior Ye, what are you doing now?
The Sword Immortal of Changming Mountain
swore with the first generation owner of the Token of Honor
that once Ghost Valley brings harm to the martial arts world,
the person with the token can invite the Sword Immortal to come out of his mountain
and demolish the ghosts and wipe out Ghost Valley.
Aren't I here?
Young Warrior, the Heroes Conference is being held soon.
Righteous men from the martial arts world have gathered here
to discuss the ways to demolish Ghost Valley together.
The Sword Immortal is an unearthly master and a famous senior.
It's glorious that you're here on behalf of the Sword Immortal.
- However—
- However, no one promised you
that we'd attend that conference or whatever of yours.
The day that the Token of Honor is reunited
is the end of Mount Qingya.
When you're done wasting your words,
the Sword Immortal will keep his promise and help the person holding the token
to wipe out Ghost Valley at Mount Qingya.
Don't bother me with anything else!
This man is young, but why does he have such great power?
He looks firm and lofty.
Men of the Sword Immortal are indeed enigmatic and unpredictable.
Sister Xiang.
You are... Who are you?
Master?
I missed you so much.
Let me have a look at you first.
It's been just a few days, but you're already so haggard.
Did you not rest well?
I can't sleep on any day.
The Heroes Conference will be held in a few days.
I am anxious.
This isn't something a child should worry about.
When the time comes, you just have to stand up
and prove that the Mirror Lake Sect is not without a successor. Demonstrate your devotion.
After that, I'll take you away.
It won't be too late to worry about the disputes
in this martial arts world after you've grown up.
Master, I don't know.
That day, Uncle Gao suddenly came to me.
He was determined to betroth Sister Xiaolian to me.
That way, she can help me support the Mirror Lake Sword Sect in the future.
During the Heroes Conference, he will announce this news.
In two years, after I've grown older, we will have our wedding arranged.
Master, I've already handed them the Glazed Armor.
Why is Uncle Gao still treating me so well?
The truth is that Sister Xiaolian also treats me well.
When the time comes, if Uncle Gao really does announce this news,
won't they be in an awkward situation after I leave with you? I didn't dare to refuse, either.
Chengling has already handed over the Glazed Armor.
What worth does he still have to Gao Chong?
That's why I kept tossing and turning, unable to sleep at all for the whole night.
Don't think too much for now. We shall keep an eye on them.
No matter what, I'll protect you secretly.
Master Zhang, are you done with your dinner? Do you need anything else?
N-No need.
Then I'll go in and clean up?
I can clean them up by myself.
All right.
Gao Chong does not have a son. He only has Gao Xiaolian, a daughter.
No matter what his reason for winning Chengling over is,
he still doesn't have to go to this step.
Could it be that Gao Chong is changing his beliefs?
Does he want to make up for his wrongdoings against Rong Xuan?
If I'm not mistaken, Old Wen is Rong Xuan's son.
[Chongwu Hall]
I must find a chance to resolve their grudges.
[Luo Mansion]
[Frosted Dew]
So annoying.
Nobody's accompanying me to the toilet, yet they still insist that we're sisters forever.
- Kill them!
- Yes!
[Luo Mansion]
- Master, I've searched through them. Not a single one is alive.
- Good.
A total of 47 devils were killed.
[I'd say fall days excel the spring morns]
How satisfying! We finally released the resentment in our hearts!
Very good.
Everyone in the martial arts world says that Ghost Valley is like a great scourge.
Now I see they are just a motley crowd.
How many casualties are there?
Unfortunately, four junior brothers died.
There are five with severe injuries and four with minor injuries.
Eldest Brother.
All casualties were caused by this demonic woman.
Owner of the List of the Unfaithful. White hair and a red dress.
Are you Tragicomic Ghost?
Don't waste your words.
Kill me if you have the capability!
How dare you?
Bring her back to the Five Lakes Alliance! Watch her closely!
This demon's skull will be the sacrifice of the Heroes Conference!
Yes.
[Upright and Auspicious Ethos]
Waiter, where does this man come from?
Sir, this guy is amazing.
He's so thin, but it seems he has an abyss in his stomach.
Tell me. Where do you think all of the food he's eaten has gone?
He's really an incomparable foodie.
- He has been eating for almost six hours.
- Yes.
My legs are already numb from standing!
Sir, aren't you tired of chewing?
No.
This man's appetite can beat ours put together.
This man looks young,
so why does he give me the feeling of an unparalleled master?
Like a supreme master under the surface.
I'm done eating!
Sir, you're finally done. This... Can you pay now?
Who's treating me?
What?
What did you say? What do you mean, who's treating you?
I'll offer my help to whoever treats me.
I'll treat you!
All right!
- All right.
- Go. Let's go!
I'll treat you.
Good. What's your name?
Wen. Wen Kexing. Brother, what can I call you?
Ye Baiyi. Thank you for the meal.
What?
Give me money.
Wait a minute. Which one of you is treating me?
You can treat me, but you cannot.
Brother, I apologize for not knowing.
Do we need to have specific qualifications in order to treat you?
No, but I am not able to help you.
I haven't even opened my mouth yet.
As it turns out, you were the one who asked for death,
but even an angel must endure five symptoms before death.
It's miserable.
How can you, being a dying person, wander around in such a lively way?
The young really are constantly replacing the old.
There are many more interesting people in the Central Plain's martial arts world.
How about this? I'll go back and think about it.
Why don't you treat me to some wine next time?
I might be able to think of a solution.
[Shimei Pavilion]
I still haven't gotten any news about that child, Tianjie.
Is there really so much disaster everywhere?
Beloved Feng, what are you upset about?
Are you going to harm me?
Qianqiao.
Qianqiao, you aren't dead?
Of course, I'm dead.
Your wife was superb in martial arts.
I suffered from two hits and one stab from her.
How could I not die?
However, those injuries could not kill me.
Then your wife stripped and disfigured me.
She ruined my disguise and forced me to parade the streets for three days.
She let everyone in the martial arts world know that
I, Liu Qianqiao, the Green Demon, was not only licentious and shameless,
but also a disfigured, ugly woman.
Which woman in this world can endure such embarrassment
and still live without purpose?
Qianqiao, stop talking.
I'm begging you, can you stop talking?
Why?
I just mentioned it, but you couldn't bear to hear it.
Then, what about the pain I've suffered personally?
Beloved Feng, although I'm an unlucky woman who doesn't deserve pity,
why should I be the one to endure all of the blame
for the wrongdoings of us both?
Qianqiao,
I know that you hate and resent me.
I have nothing to say.
Even if you kill me, my sin can't be offset.
But I'm begging you, can you stop saying such things?
These years, haven't I suffered the same torments?
I wholeheartedly wanted to kill that evil woman and avenge you,
but after all, she gave birth to Tianjie for me.
I wholeheartedly wanted to commit suicide and accompany you down there,
- but, I—
- Yes. You should have died.
Didn't you promise that if worse came to worst, we would die together?
Look! I've already been turned into a ghost.
What about you?
Qianqiao.
But I think that I haven't earned the right to die yet.
I'd made you suffer so much.
I deserve to have to yearn for you every day.
To be tortured every day.
Qianqiao, since I've seen you once again today,
then even if I die right now,
I will not bear any resentment.
The once vast sea has stilled into a plain land.
The snow on the mountains disappeared among the clouds.
Thousands of years pass in the blink of an eye,
yet my heart is still as before.
A sinful fate.
Forget it, Beloved Feng.
You can't harm me. I knew it.
You know it, too.
Leader Yu.
There will be a disaster if you see a ghost during the day.
I, the Alluring Ghost, am here to give an obituary notice.
Leader Yu,
you can never see your wife's only beloved son again.
How did my son die?
Did you kill him?
I wanted to,
but unfortunately, I was too late.
The chief of Ghost Valley personally saw your son
die under the Soul Winding Spell.
Soul Winding Spell?
Do you mean Hanged Ghost's Soul Winding Spell?
It was Ghost Valley.
Leader Yu, there's something you don't know.
Mount Qingya's Ghost Valley is back in the martial arts world now
to capture the Hanged Ghost who defected.
Your son died under the Soul Winding Spell,
so you have the same enemy as my Ghost Valley.
That's why I'm here to give an obituary notice.
It's better than making you suffer for the rest of your life.
Qianqiao,
I, Yu Qiufeng, am sorry.
I shouldn't have suspected you.
I know. No matter how is the world changes...
Even if everyone in this world lets me down,
you wouldn't harm me.
Qianqiao, I, Yu Qiufeng, swear to the heavens.
As long as you ask for it,
I'm willing to compensate you with everything.
Qianqiao.
Qianqiao!
Chief was right.
Die early and revive early.
But I've died and cried,
so why am I still unable to let this man go?
If I knew long ago that this would be the case,
I really should've drunk the Water of Oblivion.
(T/N: A drink created by the Goddess of Forgetfulness, Meng Po. It wipes memories to prepare mortals for rebirth)
[Good Luck Inn]
- Four! Four! Five!
- Six! Six!
A'Xu, you lost again.
It seems like you lied about having the Invincible Hand of Jinzhou.
If I knew that you were so lousy,
I wouldn't have suggested playing Truth or Dare with you.
It seems like I'm bullying you.
Say it. Truth or Dare?
Truth.
All right.
I'll be serious then.
Let me ask you.
Today, the strange, pretty boy at the restaurant
said that you're dying because of your own actions.
Is he talking about your old injuries that keep acting up?
Is this your question?
Of course not.
I want to ask, where did you get your injuries?
The promise you make when you drink is just like a military command.
Don't you be a sore loser.
What if I say it was karma, an appropriate consequence?
Will you believe me?
No.
I believe that we shall uphold justice on behalf of Heaven.
If Heaven won't punish those criminals, I will do it personally.
I've been alive for so long.
I've caused too many troubles.
After death, I will most likely go to hell.
Therefore, I shall atone for as many sins as I can when I'm still alive.
I got my injuries to atone for my sins.
After all, we must go through the Cauldron of Boiling Oil after death anyway.
(T/N: One of the eighteen punishments in Chinese hell where the victim repeatedly fries in a cauldron filled with oil)
Being fried for 80 years...
is still better than being fried for 100 years.
Won't you have me to accompany you in the Cauldron of Boiling Oil?
We shall get twisted into one single Youtiao.
(T/N: Fried, lightly salted Chinese snack like a fried doughnut. Created to represent traitorous prime minister Qin Hui and his wife being boiled together after executing a beloved general.)
Won't that be nice and tasty?
Don't change the subject.
This can't be considered as an answer.
I did it to myself.
Why?
That's another question.
If you want to know, you must win again.
Fine. I'm not afraid. Here we go!
- Eight! Eight!
- Five! Five!
- Six! Six!
- Four! Four!
- Three...
Don't be a sore loser.
A sore loser?
I won't even mind paying you with my life.
I choose truth! Just ask.
All right, I'll ask then.
You can't lie to me.
Since when have I ever lied to you?
Old Wen,
is your surname Rong?
You're Rong Xuan's son.
You blame the Five Lakes Alliance and the whole martial arts world
for causing your father's death,
so you replicated many pieces of the Glazed Armor.
You wanted them to bring punishment onto themselves for their greed.
I understand your feelings.
- Old Wen, but—
- Is this your question?
No wonder.
You accompanied me to play this game and drink with me just for the purpose of asking this question.
Can't you just ask me? Would I not give you an answer?
My surname is not Rong.
I'm angry that I didn't get a chance to meet the guy with the surname of Rong.
Otherwise, I would've killed him every time I saw him!
Forget it. It's the middle of the night but we're not chatting or drinking,
we're provoking anger!
Did I guess incorrectly?
But Old Wen's actions
and his hatred of the Five Lakes Alliance...
Besides being Rong Xuan's son,
how else can they be explained?
It's me. Ye Baiyi.
Follow me.
You treated me a meal, so I have to do you a favor.
I found a way to heal your injuries.
However, let's make it clear.
Don't you blame me if you die during treatment.
Brother, when did I ever ask for your help?
Who exactly are you?
Intangible and traceless.
You are the disciple of the Four Seasons Mountain Villa's Qin Huaizhang?
You're right.
My master is Qin Huaizhang.
Most people in the martial arts world
would call that old man "Leader" if they ever met him.
Old man?
How could an immature man dare to show off his experience in front of me?
Come. Show me more of your skills.
Let me have a look at what kind of thing that hothead, Qin Huaizhang, had the ability to cultivate.
Even if you're highly skilled in martial arts, even if I can't defeat you,
I would never allow others to insult my deceased master.
What? Qin Huaizhang died?
Right.
It's been so many years.
All of them have died.
The martial arts world belongs to you young people then.
You said that I was insulting him?
Let me tell you.
Even if Qin Huaizhang was standing right in front of me right now
and I scolded him directly in his face, he wouldn't dare to make a single sound.
Please show me your skills.
Your master passed his sword to you?
Let me have a look.
Idiot!
Did you think that I would snatch your sword?
What a silly thought!
You're the same as your good-for-nothing master.
Didn't I tell you?
I'm Ye Baiyi.
Ye Baiyi?
Baiyi?
Is the inscription on the White Clothes Sword
(T/N: Baiyi means white clothes)
this brother's name?
But the White Clothes Sword was made by the Magic Craftsman a hundred years ago.
How old is he?
I gifted this sword to your master.
The sword and its owner should be together.
Now its owner is gone,
but the sword is still here.
I didn't recognize you and was being rude.
Please forgive me, Senior.
Since you're the disciple of that dumb brat,
I can't simply cause your death when treating you.
Let me have a look at your injuries.
What are you doing?
♫ The sky is gray as I cross the cold river,
my duties taken care of ♫
♫ Smiling at the absurdity of the moon's reflection in my cup ♫
♫ Who allowed me to roam around the world on horseback? ♫
♫ Who is drunk in their dreams but can't find
the homeland when they wake?  ♫
♫ The cold rain of autumn kisses my windows ♫
♫  I don't mind hate and slander, but my melancholy persists ♫
♫ The spring breeze brings greenery along the river  ♫
♫ But can't warm the ice in my heart ♫
♫ Is that our light that appeared out of nowhere? ♫
♫ I resent being unable to meet you earlier, but it is not too late ♫
♫ Don't let the flowers of the seasons down ♫
♫ Give up the adventures on horseback for a peaceful,
quiet life by the stream ♫
♫ The lights of thousands of families light up thousands of hills ♫
♫ The past disappears like smoke waves in a sandstorm ♫
♫ I will clear away my cold past and happily spend the rest
of my life making wine and tea with you ♫
♫ No matter the height of the mountains or distance
of the sea, I will be with you ♫