♪The evening breeze swirls in the moonlight♪
♪Falls on the corners of your mouth♪
♪With a shy smile on your face♪
♪Who should speak first♪
♪Maybe I can be a bit noisy♪
♪Don't want the atmosphere to get boring♪
♪Love is quite wonderful♪
♪I like you but don't dare to tell you♪
♪Oh, you are the shooting star
breaking into the night sky♪
♪Listen to the sound of the heart♪
♪Encounter you at the right time♪
♪Accompanied by courage♪
♪Oh, love needs no explanation♪
♪You are the meaning I strive for♪
♪About your tomorrow and mood♪
♪Will slowly be occupied by me♪
♪Oh love, blame you for not understanding♪
♪I just want to come with true love for you♪
♪Enough anticipation♪
♪Starlight falls into the arms♪
=Treasures Around=
=Episode 1=
(Flower Pavilion)
(Yuncui City's top art house)
Mr. Pei.
You're here again, Mr. Pei.
Is what you said true?
Of course.
Look at the color.
Look at the transparency.
Look at the craftsmanship.
(Pei Pei, Qipei Pavilion's Young Master)
Though now Suyu Pavilion
overshadows Qipei Pavilion,
(Shan Dandan, a money-grubber)
Back in the day,
Qipei Pavilion was unmatched.
Had some things to do.
Just got here today.
Mr. Pei, you're here.
These two tables' drinks are on me.
Look at Mr. Pei.
Always treating you to drinks.
Thank Mr. Pei.
Thank you, Mr. Pei.
Enjoy your meal and drinks.
Look closely again.
Mr. Wang.
Look at the quality of this jade.
I really want it.
Take your time.
That Mr. Pei.
(Hetian Jade, Third Grade, Efficacy Third, Bad)
Always treating others to drinks.
Never plays himself.
(Hetian Jade, Third Grade, Efficacy Third.)
(Bad.)
(Huanglong Jade, Third Grade, Purity Second.)
(Good.)
(Emerald, Second Grade,
Translucency Third, Excellent.)
Mr. Pei.
The girl secretly selling jade is upstairs.
Ms. Huadian, do you like it?
Yes.
Then I'll buy it for you.
Thank you, Mr. Wang.
- This...
- My family name is Shan.
Doesn't matter.
Can you let me have this jade pendant?
Don't worry.
I won't
let you suffer a loss.
Thank you, Mr. Wang.
I really like it.
Honestly,
this jade pendant is the only thing
left by my late fiancé.
Take it.
Thank you, Mr. Wang.
Like it?
Yes.
Great.
Look how beautiful this jade pendant is.
I heard there's good jade for sale here.
Who are you? Wrong place?
I just heard from this lady.
She seems very familiar with Qipei Pavilion.
But why do I feel this jade pendant
is just...
- What are you doing?
Let me tell you. I'll buy this jade pendant.
Huadian likes it. I'm happy.
Let's go, Huadian.
Don't let me see you again.
Take care, sir.
Crazy.
Did you enter the wrong room?
No.
I came to find you.
I'll have the maid clean the room.
No need.
I don't mind.
The girl next door, Chunyu,
dances better than me.
She sings more songs too.
Shall I invite her to serve you?
What Chunyu?
I'm not interested.
I'm here for the jade.
(A business opportunity delivered to my door.)
(No reason not to earn this money.)
Sir.
You came to the right place.
Come.
I can tell
you love and understand jade.
Look at this jade.
Look at the color, the transparency.
It's extraordinary.
This is Qipei Pavilion's former...
Stop.
This jade pendant.
I can buy it.
And I'll buy as many as you have.
Alright.
But
this is an art house.
If you serve me well,
everything else will be easy to discuss.
What do you want?
Dance for me.
Dance?
I'm new here.
I can't dance yet.
Not fully trained?
Bring Madam Yang here.
No, no.
Don't bother Madam Yang with everything.
It's not good.
Dance.
(Little liar.)
(Let's see how long you can keep this act up.)
(Rogue, what do you want?)
I'm really going to dance.
Dance then.
No, no. Stop, stop.
Stop, stop.
You better not dance.
Really.
Then
sing a song.
Sing a song?
Can't dance
or sing.
Looks like I really need to call Madam Yang.
No, no.
I do know one song.
Which one?
The song about evil lust.
Madam Yang, someone here...
Shh.
Madam Yang!
I told you to keep it down.
Forget it.
Then
take off your clothes.
(Liu, Pei Pei's attendant)
Look, a bunch of customers.
Not good.
What's going on?
Who is this?
(Flower Pavilion)
Hurry, hurry.
The Madam is coming to catch him.
Yes.
What?
Do you need help undressing?
This is an art house, not a brothel.
I sell art, not my body.
You can't sing or dance.
What kind of artist are you?
I'm done serving you.
Pretending to be an artist.
Actually luring customers to buy jade.
Then selling these inferior goods.
You don't understand. Don't talk nonsense.
This is top-quality jade.
Top quality?
This is made from low-grade material.
This southern red jade bracelet
is a failed piece.
And this hairpin.
This is fake jade.
Smells of alum.
And you call this good stuff?
You...
If you don't like it, don't like it.
Why say so much?
Looking at this craftsmanship.
There should be leftovers
from Suyu Pavilion.
Dare to sell these things to me?
You cheated the wrong person.
I...
Tell me.
Were you sent by Suyu Pavilion?
- Move.
- You are...
No, no relation to Suyu Pavilion.
I just sell these to make some money.
Alright. I know I was wrong.
Sorry, sorry.
You're magnanimous.
Don't hold it against a little girl.
(Madam Pei Qin, Qipei Pavilion's Master)
Madam.
He's upstairs.
Young Master.
Hello, hello, Young Master.
Why are you shouting?
Do you want everyone to know I'm here?
I saw the Madam at the door.
What?
Why didn't you say earlier? Let's go.
- Okay.
- Young Master.
Where are you going?
Young Master, there's no time.
Move aside, please.
Since you're here,
just sit down.
Sit down.
Young Master, didn't you want to hear me sing?
I'll sing for you.
Let go of me.
Get her off me.
You, you, you. Let go.
Let go.
I find...
What do I have to do to make you let me go?
Buy them.
Too late, Young Master.
- Hurry.
- Give her ten taels of silver.
Fifty taels.
Fifty taels? Why don't you go rob?
My dear.
Someone is coming to catch you.
- Give it to her.
- If you leave, what should I do?
- But...
- Give her.
Don't shout, don't shout.
Don't shout. Be quiet.
Here.
Thank you, Young Master.
Don't let me see you again.
- Young Master, goodbye.
- Let's go.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
- Go, go, go.
- You don't know, Young Master.
As soon as I saw the Madam, I ran over.
- Young Master.
- Can you be more reliable?
I am reliable.
Who wants to see you?
Madam.
Young Master has never been treated like this.
I didn't expect
someone to teach him a lesson for me.
(Li Guixiang, Madam Pei's maid)
This girl
is interesting.
Like you when you were young.
Fearless like a newborn calf.
These jades.
- Oh, no.
- Sir, are you okay?
- Where did this wild girl come from?
- I'm fine.
Watch where you're going.
Who are you calling blind?
I tell you.
These are tribute jewelry from Qipei Pavilion.
(Pei Chufeng, Qipei Pavilion's Master)
If they're damaged, you'll be in trouble.
Do you know who you bumped into?
The master of Qipei Pavilion.
You...
You're Pei Chufeng?
Since you're Pei Chufeng,
you should be more worried
about damaging your own jewelry.
Why are you acting so arrogant now?
Allowing your attendant to bully a little girl.
- What sense does that make?
- You...
Do you want to be fired?
Doesn't matter.
Without me,
it's your family's loss.
You, stop.
(Unifon)
Please come in.
(Suyu Pavilion Jade Shop,
Fine Gold and Good Jade)
This jade is excellent. Top quality.
Shopkeeper, the bill.
Ms. Dandan.
You sold the goods so quickly.
The jade pendant from last time is sold.
Looks like you made quite a profit.
How much I make is none of your business.
I only pay the set price.
Calculate it.
Alright.
I'll calculate.
Tell me.
Which jade has been selling best recently?
(Shan Shuangshuang, Suyu Pavilion's craftsman)
Red jade and Hetian jade are selling very well.
For example, this red jade.
- The texture is very...
- Dandan.
I know.
Thanks.
- Shuangshuang.
- Why are you here?
I...
Went to Flower Pavilion again?
You're a girl. It's too dangerous.
Alright, Shuangshuang.
The shopkeeper just raised my monthly salary.
Take it and buy something nice.
Suyu Pavilion is really generous.
But I'm grown up now.
I can't take your money.
Shuangshuang, you keep it for yourself.
You're my only sister.
Of course, I'll spend my money on you.
Wait until I hang in there a bit longer.
My monthly salary will increase again.
Suyu Pavilion is really nice.
I want to work there too.
No way.
I can't bear to see you suffer.
Ms. Dandan, I'm done.
Shuangshuang, wait for me.
It's 60 taels short.
Good.
- Shuangshuang.
- Listen to me.
Hurry back.
Don't run around anymore.
I'm leaving then.
(Dandan,)
(Suyu Pavilion is such a dangerous place.)
(It's enough for me to be there alone.)
(I can't let you take the risk.)
Shopkeeper.
I need a favor.
I want to be a jade appraiser at Suyu Pavilion.
I'll do anything.
Even if you can't get me a job,
just give me a chance to be introduced.
My master will attend
the auction on East Street.
I can take you there.
Then it's up to you.
Alright.
Shopkeeper, you're so kind.
You'll live a long and happy life.
I'm off then.
Bye.
Young Master, have you ever thought
this pomegranate can't be peeled?
Young Master.
What's wrong with you?
Don't ask.
It's bad luck.
(Cuiliu, Pei's Mansion's maid)
Liu.
When the young master goes out, I can't follow.
How did you take care of him?
What can I do?
Should I hit a woman?
A woman?
Don't mention this again.
You're useless. Can't do anything right.
Young Master.
Did you go to Flower Pavilion again?
What?
Are you prying into my private affairs now?
Young Master is joking again.
How dare I pry into your private matters?
The Madam earned all this wealth.
Just to let the young master enjoy life.
Besides,
when you go out for fun,
I can still serve you when you return.
Hey.
Who let you sit here?
I think
you want him to marry you, right?
Madam.
Mother, why are you here?
A maid speaking and acting
so improperly, with no manners.
I think we need a new one.
Madam, I'm sorry.
I just wanted to make the young master happy.
Please don't drive me away.
Pei.
Are you not participating
in this year's Jade Competition?
No.
Mother,
I don't understand jade.
I'm not interested.
It's been so many years.
Mother.
If there's nothing else,
I'll go out to play.
Liu, let's go.
Pei.
I'm not finished talking.
Young Master.
Pei.
Watch your manners.
- Mr. Su.
- Mr. Pei.
Mr. Su is here.
Mr. Pei.
It's been years since you cared
about jade carving and family business.
(Su Jue, Suyu Pavilion's Master)
Why are you interested
in coming here today?
Firstly,
looking for something new and fun.
Secondly,
to snatch what you want
and dampen your spirits.
Little Qipei Pavilion may not be strong,
but it talks big.
Let's see then.
Young Master.
You'll all go later.
Shopkeeper.
Ms. Dandan.
This way, please.
I found a great spot for you.
Here, you can see everything.
Did Mr. Su come?
Mr. Su is upstairs.
(This guy again.)
Ms. Dandan.
You can bid for Suyu Pavilion.
But if you make a mistake,
and the price is high,
you'll pay for it.
No problem. I'm ready for this.
Alright.
I must tell you. These are...
Young Master, look at that girl.
Is the guy next to her from Suyu Pavilion?
She's indeed from Suyu Pavilion.
What do we do now?
Follow her bids
- and teach her a lesson.
- Alright.
Be sure to win.
Got it.
Leave it to me.
Come.
- Bravo!
- Bravo! Bravo!
Distinguished guests.
Everyone,
thank you for coming today.
The auction starts now.
- Alright.
The first item.
A pair of emerald bracelets.
The starting price is one hundred taels.
A hundred taels. That's expensive.
Don't think it's too expensive.
Look at this luster and color.
- Young Master, should we take this?
- It's a rare find.
It depends on who can recognize it.
One hundred ten.
One hundred twenty taels.
- The carving is exquisite.
- One hundred fifty taels.
- But the material is average.
- This gentleman bids 150 taels.
- Suyu Pavilion won't want it.
- A rare chance. Only one pair.
Is there a higher bid?
One hundred fifty taels once.
One hundred fifty taels twice.
One hundred fifty taels.
Sold.
- Alright.
The second item is a Hetian jade pendant.
A Hetian jade pendant.
Gentlemen.
It's a Hetian jade pendant.
- Ms. Dandan, how is it?
- Its importance in daily wear.
- This Hetian jade is glossy and clear.
- Needs no further explanation.
- It's a treasure.
- This piece of jade.
In terms of both material and craftsmanship,
it can be said,
to be a top-quality piece.
Young Master, this one looks quite good.
The starting bid today is only 120 taels.
Bid on it.
Gentlemen, what are you waiting for?
130 taels.
- 130 taels.
- 140.
This gentleman bids 140 taels.
150.
This lady bids 150 taels.
160 taels.
170.
180 taels.
Any higher bids?
180 taels, going once.
180 taels, going twice.
180 taels.
Sold.
Good!
Congratulations to this gentleman.
Congratulations, congratulations.
Congratulations.
Such a nuisance.
Next, the third treasure.
A gold inlaid double-heart jade lock.
The starting bid is 80 taels.
- 100 taels.
- This gentleman bids 100 taels.
110 taels.
Any higher bids?
130 taels.
- 140 taels.
This gentleman bids 140 taels.
Any higher bids?
150 taels.
Alright, 150 taels.
This gentleman bids 150 taels.
160 taels.
Young Master, Young Master.
Look at the luster. It's so clear.
Young Master, did you see it?
Do you think I can see it?
170 taels.
- Young Master.
- 170 taels.
- Look, look.
- This gentleman bids 170 taels.
Any higher bids?
170 taels.
- Young Master, how about it?
- 170 taels, going once.
Such clear luster in white jade.
Young Master.
- How much is it worth?
- Any higher bids?
It's now at 180 taels.
- Worth thousands of taels.
- 180 taels.
So expensive.
But I'm curious.
- Why are others increasing by ten taels each?
- Any higher bids?
That gentleman bids 190 taels.
They don't have your keen eye, Young Master.
- That's understandable.
- Now it's at 190 taels.
Now the gold inlaid double-heart jade lock.
- 82% luster, faint blue.
- Bidding at 190 taels.
Any higher bids?
190 taels, going once.
190 taels,
- going twice.
- I shouldn't be mistaken.
- Bid.
- Alright.
Now it's at 190 taels.
200 taels.
250.
300 taels.
350.
380.
400 taels.
420.
450.
480.
500.
520, 530.
550.
600.
I give up.
Sold.
Congratulations.
Young Master, we did it.
Congratulations to this gentleman.
- Congratulations.
- Good.
Look, look.
Young Master, amazing.
Bought for 600 taels.
Next, we have
a jadeite pendant.
Look carefully.
600 taels. You can pay now.
In terms of color.
- Young Master.
- Material.
- It's top-notch.
- Something's wrong.
Its luster isn't the same as before.
What's going on?
Young Master, this isn't worth 600 taels.
- At most 200 taels.
Little liar.
Did you tamper with it?
Your family is wealthy.
You won't back out, right?
Exactly, wealthy.
Of course.
- You bought it.
- Pay for it.
- Yes, pay up.
If not, I'll buy it.
Liu.
This...
Take it.
It will be sent to your mansion later.
You have a good eye.
You misjudged, didn't you?
Stop.
What did you do
to the jade?
What could I have done?
Just used my brain.
If you don't explain clearly,
you can't leave.
What are you doing?
Young Master.
- Make way.
- Young Master.
- Stop.
- You little girl.
- Make way.
- Move.
- Stop.
Make way.
Move now!
- I...
- Young Master.
Young Master.
Young Master, you're wet.
Alright, I know. Get a towel.
Get a towel.
Young Master, wait for me.
Mr. Su.
I'm the one who just embarrassed your rival.
Here's the thing.
I want to be a jade appraiser at Suyu Pavilion.
I never get involved in these matters.
You should talk to the shopkeeper.
I did,
but he said he couldn't make the decision.
Mr. Su,
these are my sales records over the years,
as well as each customer's preferences.
I've also analyzed the competitive landscape
of the jade industry in the entire city.
I know many maids from official households,
so I understand the preferences
of the rich and powerful.
I've been preparing for years.
Please give me a chance.
Miss, let me ask you.
Have you ever worked at any large jade stores
in the Four Borders Eight Cities?
I...
Does your family have any unique skills,
or do you
have any special sales techniques?
I mean special ones.
Charming.
Young Master,
about the jade appraiser position,
our shop's veteran,
Mr. Wang's son
also wants to be a jade appraiser.
What do you think?
We could discuss it tomorrow.
Alright.
Mr. Su, please give me another chance.
Stop wasting your time.
(Yu, Su Jue's personal guard)
You have nothing.
You're not qualified to work at Suyu Pavilion,
let alone be a jade appraiser.
You should give up early.
(You have nothing.)
(You're not qualified
to work at Suyu Pavilion,)
(let alone be a jade appraiser.)
(Suxuan Clothing Shop)
Stop.
You shameless thief, swindler!
Let's see how I'll deal with you today.
Why are you staring?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Weren't you quite talkative before?
Keep going.
What? The cat got your tongue?
Come on. I find you
very strange.
Hey.
What are you doing?
What do you think?
Why is life so unfair?
I've worked so hard, been so diligent.
Why can't anyone see that?
I just want to be a jade appraiser.
Why is it so difficult?
Tell me.
Don't touch me.
I haven't done anything to you.
Don't try to extort me.
A gentleman doesn't argue with a lady.
I'll let you go today.
I'll deal with you another day.
Ms. Li,
find this girl's home.
Post a hiring notice on her door.
Write that Qipei Pavillion
is hiring a jade appraiser.
No.
Hiring a maid.
Yes, Madam.
(Hiring Notice)
These requirements are quite exciting.
(Qipei Pavillion)
(Headquarters, Qipei Pavillion Jade Shop)
Good morning.
Get busy.
Miss, you are...
(Hiring Notice)
I'm here for the job.
Where should I go?
Alright. Keep busy.
(Kylin of Auspiciousness)
Qipei Pavillion,
though second in the jade industry
in Yuncui City,
its grandeur
is undeniable.
They even pave their paths with jade.
Did we have a thief at the Pei's Mansion?
Are you the lady of Qipei Pavillion?
Do I look like it?
My aura is so obvious, isn't it?
No, no.
We're just maids of the Pei's Mansion.
Maids? We're all maids.
Then we're colleagues.
Nice to meet you.
Who wants to be your colleague?
I'm a maid now,
but who knows in the future.
Country bumpkin.
Come on.
Your red blouse with a green skirt,
yellow skin with pink lips,
and clothes to narrow your shoulders.
Don't you know it makes your head look big?
What did you say?
Shh.
You're caked with makeup.
You wretch!
What's all the noise?
You're Shan Dandan, here for the job, right?
Madam is waiting for you.
Follow me.
(Expensive, Exquisite, Prestigious, Noble)
Madam.
Hello, Madam.
I've read the job requirements.
I don't quite understand
and don't want to admit it,
but
(Hiring Notice)
this is exactly who I am.
However.
However what?
To be honest,
I think women
don't necessarily have to do servant work.
I've always
wanted to be an excellent jade appraiser.
If you want to be a jade appraiser,
why did you tear down
my hiring notice for a maid?
If I hadn't taken it down,
how could I be standing here talking to you?
You're indeed honest.
Tell me then.
In your opinion,
what makes a jade appraiser?
An excellent jade appraiser
should
recognize jade,
understand jade,
craft jade,
(120 taels, 200 taels, 500 taels, 280 taels)
and sell jade.
They should speak eloquently
to the rich and powerful
and maintain relationships.
Madam, look.
These are my sales records
over the years.
It has various customer needs
and my analysis of the competitive landscape
of the jade industry in the entire city.
It seems I can't do
without you as a maid.
After all that,
I'm still a maid?
This maid is different.
Young Master, wear this jade today.
No.
This one?
This mutton fat jade doesn't match the silk.
Use this red jade instead.
Alright.
Young Master.
By the way,
are you really not going to see the new maid?
No.
Whoever hired her should see her.
But...
No buts.
Say one more word, and I'll hit you.
Young Master.
She's about to arrive.
(Peace and Tranquility)
(I can be a maid.)
(Endure hardships)
(and start anew.)
Young Master, hello.
I'm the new maid, Shan Dandan.
Anything you need help with?
Young Master?
What's all this?
- Why is it you?
Rogue!
Little liar.
What are you doing here?
I'm the maid chosen by Madam.
I don't know what you're so proud of.
I'm the young master of Qipei Pavilion.
Come with me.
♪Maybe the leaves falling from the tree♪
♪Maybe the lights reflect on the water♪
♪The butterflies in your eyes♪
♪Also dancing joyfully in my heart♪
♪Maybe it's the wind kissing your cheek♪
♪Maybe I feel your specialness♪
♪Stuck by your side♪
♪Feels like owning the whole world♪
♪Like a reflection,
distant yet close and overlapping♪
♪ Accompanying you day by day, year by year ♪
♪Occasionally the thoughts of you♪
♪Ripples on the surface♪
♪You can hear my unspoken thoughts♪
♪Like a reflection,
distant yet close and overlapping♪
♪ Accompanying you day by day, year by year ♪
♪The plot of that story♪
♪Contending in beauty with you♪
♪Quarreling and noisy♪
♪The blooming flowers become a celebration♪
♪Maybe it's the wind kissing your cheek♪
♪Maybe I feel your specialness♪
♪Stuck by your side♪
♪Feels like owning the whole world♪
♪Like a reflection,
distant yet close and overlapping♪
♪ Accompanying you day by day, year by year ♪
♪Occasionally the thoughts of you♪
♪Ripples on the surface♪
♪You can hear my unspoken thoughts♪
♪Like a reflection,
distant yet close and overlapping♪
♪ Accompanying you day by day, year by year ♪
♪The plot of that story♪
♪Contending in beauty with you♪
♪Quarreling and noisy♪
♪The blooming flowers become a celebration♪