♪The evening breeze swirls in the moonlight♪
♪Falls on the corners of your mouth♪
♪With a shy smile on your face♪
♪Who should speak first♪
♪Maybe I can be a bit noisy♪
♪Don't want the atmosphere to get boring♪
♪Love is quite wonderful♪
♪I like you but don't dare to tell you♪
♪Oh, you are the shooting star
breaking into the night sky♪
♪Listen to the sound of the heart♪
♪Encounter you at the right time♪
♪Accompanied by courage♪
♪Oh, love needs no explanation♪
♪You are the meaning I strive for♪
♪About your tomorrow and mood♪
♪Will slowly be occupied by me♪
♪Oh love, blame you for not understanding♪
♪I just want to come with true love for you♪
♪Enough anticipation♪
♪Starlight falls into the arms♪
=Treasures Around=
=Episode 3=
Also.
Also?
The young master is really fond of me.
The young master wants you
to serve him tonight
to bathe him.
To bathe him?
I have to go to the workshop tonight.
Aren't you also a maid?
You can serve him.
You go.
Stop pretending to be nice.
Do you think I haven't tried?
The young master specifically
wants you to wash him.
He wants me?
Don't you think
I'm showing too much for this?
No way.
Young Master,
you have such small arms and legs.
If you don't show a bit more,
who will you seduce?
Come on, open up more.
This little spy.
I've sacrificed a lot for you.
That's right.
Young Master, show more here.
Don't touch me.
Young Master.
Calm down.
- She's here. I'm leaving now.
- Go, go, go.
Young...
Young Master.
Why aren't you wearing
the clothes I bought for you?
Didn't you give them to me?
Are you taking them back?
No. I've given them to you.
Good. I asked the servant to sell them.
What? Sell them?
I don't like dressing up.
It's a waste for me to keep them.
So I sold them for money
to buy some food and drinks.
You're about to bathe me.
How are you?
Are you looking forward to it?
Yes.
Do you want a wet rub or a dry rub?
Everything is ready.
Let me help you undress.
- No.
- Let me help you.
Wait, Young Master.
- Young Master, why are you running?
- Don't rush.
Aren't you going to bathe?
Come on, don't be shy.
- Let me help you undress.
- Stop.
I'm not bathing anymore.
Alright, I'm leaving.
Wait.
No bath.
Let's have a massage instead.
Alright, Young Master. Please.
- Come.
- I...
Young Master,
I'll start the massage.
Young Master, let me smooth your hair.
Young Master, I have a strong grip.
Is this pressure okay?
Stop talking and hurry up.
Young Master, I'll stretch your muscles.
Stretching helps you live longer.
Young Master, let's do "Little Swallow Flying".
What's "Little Swallow Flying"?
Flying.
Do you feel it?
Feel the blue sky and white clouds.
Imagine flying in the sky.
(I'll endure this for now.)
(Let's see how you'll explain
when my mother arrives.)
Let's fly higher.
Do you feel the wind?
Madam, right up ahead.
Yang Yuhuan, why are you here?
Get down quickly.
We're almost there.
What's the matter?
Why did you insist on bringing me here?
Liu told me
someone is trying to seduce the young master.
It doesn't seem like it.
(You jerk, Pei Pei.)
(I knew you staged this)
(to get rid of me.)
Madam, we have to go work on the jade.
Excuse us.
Pei,
what show are you putting on for me now?
(Delight and Peace)
What's wrong, Yuhuan?
I...
I messed up the carving again.
It's almost finished.
It's already good.
Alright, alright.
Don't cry.
I'm too stupid.
How can it be your fault?
My ideas are too tricky.
But if we don't do this,
we can't make a breakthrough, right?
Alright, alright. Stop crying.
It's all this jade's fault.
This third-grade South Red Jade is too brittle.
I'll go to the stone shop
to see if they have the material we need.
Stop crying.
By the way,
if Mr. Pei comes to trouble me,
help me out, okay?
Okay.
What about me?
Fill your stomach first.
Stop crying.
(Zhang's Fabric Shop)
Miss, welcome.
Take a look at our shop's treasure.
Alright, feel free to browse.
Sir, you're here.
Is my order ready?
Yes, it is.
Here.
That piece looks good. Let's check it out.
Let's go look.
This one will definitely yield something good.
This is it.
Boss, this material is nice.
You have a good eye.
This piece is top quality.
But it's already reserved.
Boss, it doesn't matter who you sell it to.
Sell it to me.
I can't offend that person.
It's not possible.
I'm a jade appraiser from Qipei Pavilion.
Please make an exception.
The person needing this material
is Mr. Su Jue from Suyu Pavilion.
You mean Qipei Pavilion
is inferior to Suyu Pavilion?
I didn't mean that.
- Then you...
- Dandan.
Shuangshuang, what are you doing here?
You're here to...?
I'm here to buy this material,
but the boss won't sell it.
Boss,
I'm a gold and silver craftsman
from Suyu Pavilion.
I heard everything just now.
I'll explain to Mr. Su when I get back.
Please sell this material to my sister.
How can a mere craftsman
decide for the young master?
That's not possible.
Who says she can't decide for me?
Mr. Su.
You're here.
- Look.
- Shuangshuang,
what's going on?
Mr. Su,
this is my sister, Shan Dandan.
She wants that material.
But you reserved it.
I remember her.
I heard she's working at Qipei Pavilion now.
Yes, it's her.
Shuangshuang, I'll be leaving.
Goodbye.
What's the rush? You want the jade, right?
You already know I'm from Qipei Pavilion.
Of course, you won't give me the jade.
I'm not that petty.
Since you are Shuangshuang's sister,
you are also a sister of Suyu Pavilion.
You can have the jade.
- Thank you, Mr. Su.
- Really?
A gentleman helps others succeed.
I don't need it anyway.
If it can help you
in the Jade Competition,
it'll be well used.
How did you know?
Just a guess.
Wrap it up.
Also,
Shuangshuang can make any decision
for Suyu Pavilion.
Watch your mouth.
Mind your attitude.
Yes, Mr. Su.
Thank you, Mr. Su.
You're welcome.
(Jade Shop)
Mr. Su,
you are so talented and generous.
Pei Pei is not even a fraction of you.
No, not even one ten-thousandth.
No, no.
Not even your little toe.
Ms. Dandan, you flatter me.
Thank you.
You little spy.
You're praising your true master.
What are you doing?
You bought this with my family's money.
I can smash it if I want to.
I searched the whole city
(Jade Shop)
to find this piece of material.
You smashed it.
What about the Jade Competition?
You little spy.
I caught you. Stop acting.
Pretending to be a good person.
Dandan,
Mr. Pei is so rude.
You should leave there.
No way.
The madam trusts me.
I can't let her down.
Shuangshuang, don't worry.
I'm fine. I can handle it.
Then I'll go now.
Young Master,
I'm worried about my sister.
I want to check on her.
Miss, look at this bronze mirror.
Finely crafted.
See? It works well, doesn't it?
If you like any,
we can give you a discount.
Our bronze mirrors
are the latest models.
See? It makes you look like a fairy.
Any you like?
If you like any,
we'll give you a discount.
These models
are the best sellers.
These are too expensive.
This price is already cheap.
What are you doing?
- Are you taking advantage of me?
- No, I'm not.
- I just...
- Are you taking advantage of me?
- No.
You're harassing me.
I'm not.
Someone just pushed me.
I don't care. You're harassing me.
Everyone, look!
He's harassing me.
You're still denying it.
Why were you winking at me?
Clearly lusting after my beauty.
Bullying a virtuous girl like me.
How dare you laugh after harassing me?
I'll report you to the authorities.
- Let's go.
- No.
- No, no.
- Everyone, look!
Let's go.
I...
Didn't expect you to apologize so quickly.
Alright then.
I'll forgive you this time.
Don't do it again.
Sir,
I'll wait for you to marry me.
Uncle.
Jue'er.
(Wang Jiu, Suyu Pavilion's shopkeeper)
Find the best materials
for hollow and fine carving.
Buy them all.
I just ran into Pei Pei.
He's looking for these materials.
Why are you involved with the Pei family?
If I don't,
how will I know what materials
they're using for the Jade Competition?
Got it.
No materials, no competition.
This is a good plan.
Let me, let me.
Thank you.
You're here. Come and sit.
We found the jade,
but time is tight.
We'll work through the night.
Thank you.
Dandan.
Someone proposed to me today.
Proposed?
Who? Do I know him?
It's Mr. Li, the gardener.
I've secretly liked him for a long time.
Congratulations!
If we win first place
in the Jade Competition,
it'll be double the joy.
Dandan, this marriage was arranged by Mr. Pei.
It was hard for him to agree.
He gave me a month off
to get married
and even helped with the dowry.
A month?
But the Jade Competition will be over by then.
I...
I'm in a tough spot too.
But you know,
it's not easy for someone like me
to find a person I truly like to marry.
But...
Dandan,
we don't always have to be so strong.
We've worked hard and tried our best.
What competition
is more important than personal happiness?
It's okay.
Your happiness is what matters most.
Thank you.
Then,
I'll go prepare.
Alright.
Go ahead.
(Pei Pei,)
(you won't get away with this.)
This is really ruthless.
Liu,
is there a chance
that this egg should be peeled?
Stop.
Is this egg raw or cooked?
It's raw.
Could it be
that we need a cooked egg?
Young Master, wait here.
I'll get you a cooked one.
Why are you doing this?
Breaking
into my room at night.
Get out.
Why are you doing this?
What did I do?
You keep targeting me, causing me trouble.
You're the young master, so I can overlook it.
But you've gone too far.
To stop me from entering the Jade Competition,
you took away my only helper.
You little spy.
If I let you represent our family
in the competition,
we'd be doomed.
I said I'm not a spy.
What do I have to do for you to believe me?
I only believe my own eyes.
Just because you're the young master,
do you think you can slander people?
Being the young master makes you special, huh?
You think you can destroy someone's hard work?
I just want to be a jade appraiser
and enter the Jade Competition. Is that wrong?
At least I'm better than you,
a useless man who does nothing.
Shut up.
Useless?
What right do you have to call me that?
You keep talking about your dreams
of being a jade appraiser,
but you can't even draw a design,
let alone carve.
I think you just want
to cheat for more money.
If I can't draw, I can learn.
If I can't carve, I can learn.
Not everyone starts
on the same path
or has the right to pursue their dreams.
But even so,
I've never given up,
and I work hard every day.
What about you?
As the young master of the Pei family,
you live in luxury,
eating and drinking in the mansion,
while watching your mother struggle.
You can do everything,
but you choose to do nothing.
Mr. Pei,
what are you
if not useless?
Enough.
Get lost.
Even without help,
no matter how much trouble you cause,
I won't give up.
I'm going
to the Jade Competition.
(Peace and Tranquility)
Useless.
Everyone thinks
I'm willing
to be useless.
Did you know?
The young master was angry yesterday.
- Really?
- Yes.
He was furious.
(Peace and Tranquility)
Why are you so late today?
The young master has a temper.
He fought yesterday.
He can't wake up early.
Are you crazy? Talking like that?
Everyone in the household knows.
I heard Shan Dandan caught a cold
in the rain and is bedridden.
Serves her right.
That serious?
Give me that.
Go.
Young Master, you're awake.
Come. Eat while it's hot.
Young Master.
Who were you talking to outside?
Cuiliu.
Seems you're used
to Ms. Dandan's cooking.
Oh, my big mouth.
I heard people outside
talking about Shan Dandan.
It's Cuiliu's fault.
I'll scold her later.
No one should mention her in front of you.
Good.
Young Master,
Cuiliu said Shan Dandan is so sick
she can't get out of bed.
Should we call a doctor for her?
This season, catching a cold
is no small matter.
Such an ingrate.
Who knows what spell he's under,
calling me a spy?
I think he's the delusional troublemaker.
And Su Jue.
When I begged you
for a job,
you ignored me.
Now I've finally found a job,
you suddenly help me.
I can't clear my name now.
Both of them are jerks.
Didn't you say
she was very sick?
That's what Cuiliu said.
Who knew she'd be so lively?
Yuhuan is gone.
Relying on myself to learn carving.
How long will it take?
So stupid.
Who's outside?
No one.
You really are clever.
Well...
What are you doing here?
This is my home.
I can go wherever I want.
This room was given to me by the madam.
Leave.
You're sick. Stop that.
None of your business.
I said you were stupid, and you really are.
- Liu.
- Yes, Young Master.
Enough.
When I was little,
my hands were full of scars.
With your technique,
you can't even carve silk patterns.
It looks like all of our stone materials
might be wasted by you.
If you'd broken fewer stones,
we'd have plenty.
(Hanging Earring)
That's a hanging earring?
Good idea.
Too bad
your technique is poor.
Thanks to you,
the raw stone is shattered into pieces,
only enough to make a pair of hanging earrings.
Alright.
Switch to the Knife No. 3.
Hurry up.
Hold the jade with your left hand.
Hold the knife with your right hand.
Press down.
The handle is too tilted.
Too much force. Reduce by ten percent.
Now slowly push down.
Go.
Withdraw.
It worked.
It...
You're sick. Don't drink cold water.
Who is useless now?
Ms. Dandan, you should rest.
Here's some good medicine for your cold.
Remember to take it.
Madam, this is my sample work.
I know my skills are not great,
but if I had a better craftsman to work with,
I could improve significantly.
This is a hanging earring?
Though crudely carved,
it has a clever design.
I've never seen this type
of hanging earrings before.
The droplet-shaped design above the earrings
lightens the customer's burden.
It's creative and practical.
Very nice.
Very nice indeed.
Thank you for your praise, Madam.
Ms. Dandan's design is indeed clever,
but from the patterns, style,
and knife technique,
I can tell this wasn't done
by Ms. Dandan alone.
This design appears simple
but requires someone skilled in carving
to understand.
Dandan,
did someone help you?
(It turns out this rogue is quite skilled.)
Someone did give me some pointers,
but
I guarantee on my honor,
this hanging earring is my idea alone.
No one else helped me.
Using your honor as a guarantee?
I believe you.
But Madam…
Shopkeeper Hao,
our pavilion
needs to change.
I like Dandan's enthusiasm
and cleverness very much.
Thank you, Madam.
Come.
Dandan,
this piece of jade
is of medium quality
and too small in size.
If you want it to stand out
or be presentable
at the Jade Competition,
you need a complete piece
of high-quality Hetian Cyan jade.
Actually, I found a whole piece before,
but unfortunately,
I ruined it while carving.
Alright, it's okay.
Take care of your health first.
Mr. Hao will handle
the stone material.
Thank you, Madam.
(A few days later)
(Qipei Pavilion)
Mr. Hao.
Ms. Dandan, are you feeling better?
Fully recovered.
Mr. Hao,
is the Hetian jade you mentioned
in the storeroom?
Take me to see it.
In the past few days,
our shop assistants
have searched every shop in town.
Not a single piece of Hetian jade can be found.
How is that possible?
How can there be no Hetian jade at all?
Mr. Hao,
now,
money doesn't matter anymore.
The Jade Competition is so important.
As long as the jade is good,
it's worth it even if it's expensive.
You think I'm worried about money?
There's none for sale.
You can't buy it even if you have the money.
Go check for yourself if you don't believe me.
Mr. Hao,
that's not what I meant.
Young Master,
we've searched for so many days
and still can't find any Hetian jade.
It's too strange.
Stop complaining.
Check the Jade Pavilion up ahead.
(Jade Shop)
Young Master,
I've found out.
There's no stone material for sale
anywhere in the market,
except for the black market.
The black market?
Where is it?
At the East Street market for groceries.
Let's go then.
Not a good idea, Young Master.
The black market is chaotic and dangerous.
If one wants to buy
and the other wants to sell,
as long as we have the money,
there's no danger. Let's go.
(Liquor)
No.
Young Master.
I must find some helpers.
If anything happens to you,
I can't bear the responsibility.
Fine, do as you wish. Let's go.
(Jade Shop)
Thank you, Miss.
(Feels like raw stone.)
Sir, where are you delivering this?
This? I'm delivering it to a seafood boss
at the East Street market.
Thank you, Miss.
Take care.
(Sauce Area, Black Market)
Bet big or small.
- I bet big.
- I bet small.
Alright, no more bets.
Hurry. Let's bet.
(Fresh Goods)
Careful, sir.
What? Are you buying groceries?
No, just looking around.
If you're not buying, what's there to look at?
Go home.
Sometimes you buy without buying,
and not buying is buying.
Got it. We're in the same boat.
Thanks for your help earlier, Miss.
No problem.
- Okay.
- Sir, please.
(Fresh goods)
(I haven't been here for days.)
(These black market stalls
are getting even more secretive.)
(In the black market,
they've always mixed fish and jade.)
(They sell seafood openly.)
(In reality, they deal in smuggled goods.)
(The stall selling stone materials...)
Sir, do you have any materials?
Miss,
I'm an old man selling fish.
If you want materials for sauce,
it's over there.
We're in the same boat.
Miss, please forgive me.
Government officials
are getting stricter with this.
- Big.
- Small.
All my good stuff is here.
Is it the same over here?
Yes.
This piece is good.
You've got a good eye, Miss.
Hetian Cyan, top quality.
How much for this?
800 taels.
You've brought it to the black market
and you're still holding out on the price?
600 taels.
600 taels won't sell.
Alright, alright. As you say.
800 taels.
- Big, big, big.
- Small, small.
- Big, big.
- Small.
Open it!
Do you know how to do it?
- What's going on?
- Seriously.
- Sir.
- Next round, I'll bet big again.
Do you have any materials?
Come again.
I don't believe it. I'm sure to win.
Alright, come.
In the same boat?
That's right.
The boat.
Is he a government official?
Go and see. If it comes to worse,
grab our weapons.
I'm here this time
to buy some Hetian jade.
What materials do you have here?
Bring them out for me to see.
(Pei Pei?)
(What's he doing in the black market?)
(To smash my jade again?)
Sir,
you might be mistaken.
We only have shrimp and crabs here,
nothing like Hetian jade.
Never heard of it.
No, look. Why are you hiding things from me?
If you don't bring them out,
I'll find them myself.
What are you doing?
Sir,
are you deliberately looking for trouble?
This...
♪Maybe the leaves falling from the tree♪
♪Maybe the lights reflect on the water♪
♪The butterflies in your eyes♪
♪Also dancing joyfully in my heart♪
♪Maybe it's the wind kissing your cheek♪
♪Maybe I feel your specialness♪
♪Stuck by your side♪
♪Feels like owning the whole world♪
♪Like a reflection,
distant yet close and overlapping♪
♪ Accompanying you day by day, year by year ♪
♪Occasionally the thoughts of you♪
♪Ripples on the surface♪
♪You can hear my unspoken thoughts♪
♪Like a reflection,
distant yet close and overlapping♪
♪ Accompanying you day by day, year by year ♪
♪The plot of that story♪
♪Contending in beauty with you♪
♪Quarreling and noisy♪
♪The blooming flowers become a celebration♪
♪Maybe it's the wind kissing your cheek♪
♪Maybe I feel your specialness♪
♪Stuck by your side♪
♪Feels like owning the whole world♪
♪Like a reflection,
distant yet close and overlapping♪
♪ Accompanying you day by day, year by year ♪
♪Occasionally the thoughts of you♪
♪Ripples on the surface♪
♪You can hear my unspoken thoughts♪
♪Like a reflection,
distant yet close and overlapping♪
♪ Accompanying you day by day, year by year ♪
♪The plot of that story♪
♪Contending in beauty with you♪
♪Quarreling and noisy♪
♪The blooming flowers become a celebration♪