=Love Actually S5=
We can play frisbee now.
Come on.
Go easy at first.
Easy.
Can you catch it?
Yeah, almost.
So close.
You need to throw it flatter.
Like this, babe.
Throw it flatter.
Like this.
Pancake.
Yeah, almost.
That scared me.
This seems dangerous.
Forget it, I'll step back.
(Running away)
I'll just throw it to anyone.
(Afraid)
Shall we take a walk?
The sun will set
very soon.
Carry on.
We'll go for a walk.
Keep playing.
Finally,
cooling down.
Yeah.
Feels good.
I thought we'd just play a little.
But
we really got into it.
But it was fun.
It's good to exercise.
Oh no.
What's wrong?
My glasses.
Your glasses?
I forgot my silver glasses.
I forgot
where I left them.
It's okay.
Just run around blindly.
I brought contact lenses.
So,
which glasses are better,
today's or yesterday's?
They both look good.
The black frame
is...
Business-like.
No.
In the past few days,
you weren't wearing glasses.
Then you wore those black-framed ones.
It just feels...
Different.
Contrasting.
Docile without glasses.
The coffee is hers.
Thanks.
Want to see my cooking
from when I first arrived in the UK
ten years ago?
I want to see what you looked like.
(Curious)
Not exactly cooking though.
Looks good.
This is inedible.
This?
Looks questionable.
Then later on,
I made kimchi fried rice.
And some other stuff.
"Haven't cooked in a long time.
It's amazing."
Yeah, and I made udon.
At this point,
you started to improve.
Yeah.
I made egg waffles at home.
You even bought a waffle maker.
Yeah.
What else did I make?
I made quite a lot.
Like shrimp head oil.
Singing alone at home.
Fried rice with shrimp head oil.
You think
you've changed a lot since then?
Since ten years ago?
Yeah, your style back then...
I transformed my balcony.
Yeah, my balcony.
So trendy.
I'd be alone,
sitting on the balcony, eating,
watching the sunset and stuff.
And I would put some fruit here.
Tired.
Let's go back and rest.
I can play badminton
for three hours now.
Impressive.
Two hours
isn't enough.
We have a badminton group
in Shanghai.
We play every Monday.
There are many.
There are many clubs
in Shanghai.
Every club or court
has that kind of group.
You just pick a day of the week,
and a time slot.
I was...
But I've ignored their sign-ups
many times.
I would go.
Playing with friends
is different from
playing with strangers.
With strangers, you really play.
Yeah.
You play seriously.
With friends, you're just
fooling around.
But I think
I was playing seriously just now.
Quite skilled.
Alright.
Will you take a shower?
It feels cool in here.
Yeah.
I'll dry up
very fast.
Let's head back now.
Should we buy some food?
Okay.
(Target)
Anything in mind?
Do you still have coconuts?
Can you open these coconuts for us?
Or...
Open four coconuts for us.
Okay.
Wait.
Two iced, two room temperature.
Some girls might not
have iced ones
at that time of the month.
Let me carry them.
I'll carry some too.
You just stay pretty.
It's fine.
Okay, thanks.
Let me.
Give me that.
No need.
It's okay.
Isn't it like
weight training?
Mine are not heavy.
Give me one.
Take another one.
Give it to me.
What's this?
It smells so good.
Flatbread.
What's inside?
You can choose the filling.
Want some?
Is there a meat filling?
There are pickled vegetables and meat.
Let's get some.
Four yuan each.
Three for ten yuan.
(Ready to go home)
Is there
somewhere you want to go
but haven't been?
I've barely been to Europe.
Just a trip to London and France.
I haven't been to Germany or that area.
I'd like to...
I like Spain.
Me too.
And
I think Venice is nice.
Venice.
There's a city
in Spain.
I forgot what it's called.
But that city
feels really energizing.
Ibiza.
Buy tickets.
Let's go.
The house looks amazing from here.
I haven't paid attention.
Look at your sea-view room.
So luxurious.
Now it's...
Really.
The center of the house.
Should we make some rice?
Make rice.
Right?
Yes.
With that apron on,
you look like a chef.
(The chef)
(Chef Xiao)
Smells so good.
Your hair looks so smooth today.
Xiao Wentao.
Suddenly a bit cute.
Suddenly going for a cute look.
(Cute Wentao)
Cute style today.
Well-behaved.
Homey vibe.
(Homey-vibe Wentao is a must-have)
You're actually quite photogenic.
Xiao Wentao.
Come on, smile.
Come on, one, two, three.
That proud little smile.
It's amazing.
Here.
It smells amazing.
Try it.
How is it, Xuan?
You like it?
It's good.
Smells so good.
Impressive.
Awesome.
Great job, Xiao Wentao.
So you actually cook often?
Not really.
I rarely cook
now that I'm back in China.
Just getting by.
I used to cook a lot when I was abroad.
(Really)
You know?
You doubted me before,
thought I couldn't cook.
Does anyone
want to eat rice cakes or something?
Can you cook?
You may like it.
Yeah.
I can make some for you.
(Awkward)
Yeah.
So I was completely wrong about you.
Completely wrong.
Any other assumptions?
(Careful)
I dare not say anything rashly now.
Nothing.
I haven't shown you the big dishes yet.
(Impressive)
What big dishes?
(Proud)
There are too many.
I can make a lot of things.
Don't tell them.
If you tell them,
I'll be the one cooking here every day.
It'll become a cooking show.
I saw you prepping the ingredients.
(So smoothly)
And I realized that
you could cook.
"This guy can cook."
He can cook.
"He can cook."
Yeah.
When you
bought the rice cakes,
why didn't you get anything else?
When I was buying those,
I thought
we could add some random ingredients
we had at home.
Then we came back,
and you were looking up recipes.
I was like,
"He's just learning now."
No, I've made it before.
I just forgot a bit.
Time to check Moments.
(Start checking Moments)
Why are we so cool
about this?
So chill.
Relaxed.
Indeed.
Acting like nothing's up.
We're all good at pretending.
Deep down, we're flustered.
We can start.
Go ahead.
One by one.
Okay.
(Xiao Wentao chose to check
Jia Peixuan's Moments)
I checked Peixuan's Moments.
She posted,
"Great chef.
Looking forward to those rice cakes."
The four of us went to the supermarket
last time.
We said
we wanted to make some rice cakes.
Does anyone
want to eat rice cakes or something?
Want some?
I'll eat if you make some.
Yeah.
I can make some for you.
But we came back
and went to the barbecue.
So we didn't make it.
My Moments today is for Xiao Wentao.
I didn't believe he could cook.
But he's cooked several times,
and everything was amazing.
(Earlier tonight)
Look at these hungry kids.
Xiao Wentao.
Everyone's eager eyes.
How is it, Xuan?
It's good.
Smells so good.
(Jia Peixuan chose to check
Xiao Wentao's Moments)
Today, I'm checking
Xiao Wentao's Moments.
(14 vs 13, Go easy on me next time
to pay it back)
14 vs 13 today.
Go easy on me next time to pay it back.
I didn't get it.
Today's Moments
is also for Peixuan.
I'm actually quite competitive
in sports.
So next time we play tennis,
let me win.
(Let me win once. I'll pay you back)
I talked with Ruita
about many details of her life,
and her views on some things.
So I want to know
what she thinks
of me.
(Lu Bingkun chose to check
Wang Yi's Moments)
I checked Ruita's Moments.
(Cherry blossom,
Mushrooms are better than flatbread)
She posted something about our date,
the cooking,
and the flatbread we bought.
She had a nice time too.
(This afternoon)
What's this?
Flatbread.
There was a time
when I really loved flatbread.
Pickled vegetables and meat.
Then let's get some.
Come on, how much?
I'll pay you first.
Four yuan each.
Three for ten yuan.
It's a sweet memory
for us.
A nice day.
I recorded things
I did
with BK today.
He cooked mushrooms.
We bought some flatbread.
And we watched the cherry blossoms.
I'll take your pic.
I'm a bit shy now.
I saw you snapping away over there.
Selfie together.
That was
a date.
We watched the cherry blossoms.
At that moment,
it felt a little romantic.
So I wanted to post something for him.
(Wang Yi chose to check
Lu Bingkun's Moments)
I checked BK's Moments.
(Spring brings cherry blossoms)
He wrote about the cherry blossoms.
My post is for Ruita.
It was addressing
the beautiful scenery we saw.
Not just the scenery,
but also the people.
Your turn.
Should I carry him?
Let's go.
Together.
Let's take a look.
If he taps on something,
you can see two posts.
(Dong Zhuoran chose to check
Chen Danqi's Moments)
I'm checking Chen Danqi's Moments.
(Had fun playing badminton)
It was about badminton.
I don't know
who it's for.
She could be sending it
to herself.
"Had fun playing badminton."
My Moments today
is for Zhou Youling.
I had fun playing badminton
this afternoon.
Super happy.
Zhou Youling
is great at hyping up the vibe.
And,
I feel like whenever he's around,
everyone is happy.
And I feel great.
When we were playing badminton,
Zhou Youling was quite charming.
Let's go.
You brought Brother there?
Yeah.
Mr. Dong
looked after me many times today.
(Tonight)
When I was playing the piano,
Mr. Dong
quietly listened there.
Although
I stumbled through it,
he encouraged me.
Impressive.
Beautiful.
I was just practicing.
Really.
This environment.
Thanks.
It's nice.
When Xiao Wentao was cooking,
I was cheering him on.
It was
a wonderful time.
Your hair looks so smooth, Xiao Wentao.
Suddenly going for a cute look.
Cute style.
Well-behaved.
(Chen Jianying chose to check
Zhou Youling's Moments)
I checked Mr. Zhou's Moments.
Because today,
I only spent time alone with him.
Let's both look at the lake
with Brother.
Reflection.
Lean over, Brother.
Join us for the shot.
Brother, come here.
Here.
Baby.
He left.
I'm curious what Mr. Zhou will post.
(Connected by heart)
He posted a parenthesis,
"Connected by heart."
But I'm not sure who he sent it to.
I don't really know
what he did today.
It probably has nothing to do with me.
Yeah.
I checked Zhou Youling's Moments.
I wasn't sure
what "connected by heart"
was referring to.
Handsome.
(Xu Lvyang: Slow to catch on like me)
Today, I checked
Xu Lvyang's Moments.
She said,
"Slow to catch on like me."
I was confused.
Actually, I just wanted to know
what she posted.
I hope she feels better soon,
and stops overthinking.
Ling Lizheng, done?
I'm done.
(Zhou Youling: Connected by heart)
I checked Zhou Youling's post.
Because I was curious
what he had to say.
So I checked it.
I thought about it
for a long time.
I posted "connected by heart"
for Liu.
I woke up and opened the door
only to find her there.
I think we wanted to see each other.
I later guessed.
Maybe it was about that moment.
I walked to his door
and was about to knock.
Suddenly it swung open.
Then he popped his head out.
(Earlier tonight)
I was about to knock.
And you just opened up.
Nothing, just checking on you.
I was asleep just now.
Keep resting.
I tapped on the house manager.
I can try again, right?
You can go.
You're out.
Lost your chance.
(Xu Lvyang: Slow to catch on like me)
Liu's Moments is
"Slow to catch on like me."
I thought about it.
It's probably not about me.
I didn't do anything
to make her slow to catch on.
A little disappointed.
"Slow to catch on like me."
It's how I feel right now.
It's like,
Ling Lizheng's feelings,
Zhou Youling's feelings,
or BK's feelings.
I'm actually slow to catch on.
I didn't expect Ling Lizheng
to pick me up at the gate
and help me.
Hello.
How did you know I was coming back?
I was passing by
and came to check.
You came out for a walk?
Yeah.
I didn't expect Zhou Youling
to open the door
right after
he heard my footstep.
It's the same with BK.
I just can't grasp
other people's thoughts.
I need some fresh air.
Together.
Come on, baby.
Do you want to find someone
who likes you more,
or someone you like more?
It has to be someone I like.
Even if someone likes me a lot,
it'd be pointless
if I don't like them.
Why should I put on a show?
(Clear-minded)
If you like someone,
will you always
have that heart-fluttering feeling?
Or is it just
at the beginning?
I think
if I truly like someone,
that feeling
won't fade away.
But if
I liked him
and we didn't make it,
or
he wasn't really into me,
my feelings could be gone very soon.
It depends on his response.
Yeah.
I need responses
to sustain a relationship.
It has to be in sync.
You take a step,
I take a step.
Yeah.
That's crucial.
Or it's just unrequited love.
One-sided.
Yeah.
Everyone
might have
their own rhythm and bottom line.
If you feel
you're willing to move forward,
then go ahead.
But if
you've reached your limit,
then stop.
That's all fine.
But relationships are complicated.
We may encounter many things
that wear us down.
Yeah.
Especially,
we're all adults.
There are many things
to think about.
Yeah.
You may want someone idealistic
while trying
to keep it down to earth.
It's really hard.
Yeah.
Before I turned thirty,
I didn't even
think about
having kids and stuff.
But now at thirty-three,
I think I'm moving
towards that direction.
Yeah.
So would you want a family?
I'm not against it.
I used to think
I didn't really need it.
But now I think
I'm open to the possibility.
And I think
I'm starting to want it
because
I've figured out...
What you want in life.
Yeah.
Or rather, I've figured out
what I need to give
to have a family.
If I want a family,
I might have to
devote a lot of time
and energy.
Work.
Yeah.
And everything.
Am I willing to do so?
Is it balanced?
Yeah.
Now I'm willing to do so.
So I think I can try
to start a family.
This is the best part
about
being in your thirties.
You've figured out
what you want.
(Clear-headed)
Yeah.
How come this face
is packed like sardines?
I vote for Park Hae-jin.
I only recognize my big brother.
Makes me look like I have no EQ.
Cut.
Like this.
Okay.
A teacher with a student in class.
Preschool teacher.
Have a seat.