Hello, everyone.
(Wang Yi)
I'm Wang Yi from Love Actually S5.
Hello, everyone.
(Ling Lizheng)
I'm Ling Lizheng from Love Actually S5.
Thank you.
Hello, everyone.
(Lu Bingkun)
I'm Lu Bingkun from Love Actually S5.
Hello, everyone.
(Chen Danqi)
I'm Danqi from Love Actually S5.
Hello, everyone.
(Chen Jianying)
I'm Chen Jianying from Love Actually S5.
Hello, everyone.
(Yang Xihui)
I'm Yang Xihui from Love Actually S5.
Actually, the show
has aired many episodes.
So, do you have
any bullet comments
or reviews
that left a deep impression on you?
24 years old
yet appears more aged than 36.
Rapidly gained maturity.
My perceived age shot up instantly.
(Blame my overly mature demeanor)
The comments that stuck with me were
about my long neck and sloped shoulders.
I was wondering
what big stuff an alpaca could handle.
Sloped shoulders can't bear much burden.
I saw comments saying, "Don't worry."
"Ying has already cheered herself up."
Well.
Comments said I...
You never take anything to heart.
Yes.
Model guy. Actor guy.
Rushing work schedules.
I'm actually working.
(Speak for me)
Clear my name.
He is genuinely
here to record the show.
Just kidding.
When I first appeared,
I told you my base is in Changsha.
Comments joked. Her base is in Changsha,
guitar in Beijing,
drums in Shanghai.
Okay.
I'm just a one-man band.
I'll perform for everyone right away.
(Guess the person from the drawing)
(Portrait drawn by a mysterious guest)
Portrait. This one?
(Guess which guest this is)
They say there are some...
So abstract.
(Minimalist abstract style)
Which artist's work is this?
This artwork
dazzles even my beginner-level eyes.
Have a guess, everyone.
(First question)
Ling.
I think it's Lizheng.
Yes.
Then this is
Ling Lizheng, right?
(Correct answer)
Yes.
(40% similarity)
(Second question)
A mole at the corner of the mouth.
Is that the key point?
You.
(Confused)
How could they draw you like this?
Bad review.
(10% similarity)
Who drew this?
Who drew this portrait of me?
I even thought it was a man.
Get out of here.
Which mysterious guest in the house
drew me
based on their first impression?
I think it must be...
It must be Big Bro who drew it.
He didn't even see my face.
How could he draw me like this?
I disagree.
Next one, let's take a look.
(Third question)
This is Danqi, right?
Very iconic earrings.
With such a square face,
it might well be me.
Your face isn't square.
Then who is it?
(Correct answer: Yang Xihui)
It's Xihui?
Who exactly drew this?
Let me replicate it for everyone.
(0% similarity)
(Answer revealed: Xiao Wentao)
Xiaowen.
Who?
Wentao drew it.
(During Xiao Wentao's
backstage recording)
I finished.
Chen Jianying has classic
willow leaf eyebrows.
(Portrait of Chen Jianying)
And I noticed
she has
(Identifying by the mole)
a beauty mole right here,
so I drew it on.
This one is clearly Lizheng.
(Portrait of Ling Lizheng)
Lizheng's arms are shaped like
candied hawthorn skewers.
And this one is Xihui.
(Portrait of Yang Xihui)
Xihui
always looks cheerful
and smiling every day.
So she's
a really sunny girl.
Bro, what's up with you?
Xiao Wentao.
Nice artwork,
go back to your trumpet instead.
Come on.
Next, let's check out
today's full episode.
In the early days in the house,
who was the one that caught your heart?
Chen Danqi.
We both deeply felt,
in the moment of conversation,
that there were many sparks.
Who did you write the exclusive note to?
I wrote it to Zhuoran.
My first time making coffee in my life.
Delicious, Zhuoran.
When you're eating,
the childlike side of you
just bursts out.
So cute.
It's like a Monet painting.
What is this? Rural Love Story?
But those
early fondness and chemistry
mostly stemmed from
our interests and hobbies.
Crush and fondness
may gradually turn into
pure appreciation between friends.
I think that's how it is. Yes.
My feelings for Xihui
are still stuck
at the stage of wanting
to know her better,
lacking
the genuine thrill of a crush.
Hui still makes my heart flutter.
Very comfortable.
If I see her hesitating,
thinking things through,
and having her own thoughts,
I don't want to put any pressure on her.
I'm content
just staying by her side
to accompany her.
But we're only
halfway through the trip, right?
There's a long way to go.
Let's wait and see.
Maybe I'll jump on the wagon.
Ji Yu has cheered himself up again.
Hello, friends.
Hi.
Bro, what's up with you?
♪If you're happy, clap your hands♪
Ji Yu is so cute.
Is your heart set on someone clearly?
Only one person.
That person is Yang Xihui.
I realized
I need to be my true self
and wait for someone who appreciates me.
This editing is so...
You really have a comic-like face.
Comic? I'm okay, I guess.
I like this side.
I also like this side.
There is a dimple on that side, right?
Handsome.
Are you a DJ?
Who made this weird looped edit?
The DJ is spinning records.
Is your heart set on one person,
multiple people,
or no one at all?
One person.
Zhou Youling.
This burst light shot is so beautiful.
Just press it.
Because I don't want
to play with others.
I just want to play with him.
Shall we leave?
Let's go.
Is Danqi your second choice?
Definitely not.
Danqi is also one of the girls
I want to get to know.
Do you think the only direction
from now on is clear?
I think
it's quite clear.
But maybe
it hasn't reached
that point of true attraction.
So I didn't choose to burst light.
In the first two to three days,
or two to four days,
I had some physical attraction
for BK.
He might have figured it out
earlier than I.
After we get to know each other,
one side will always realize it sooner.
So I think with BK,
there's no regret.
I choose not to press.
Because of my own dullness
and my cowardice,
I didn't dare to
clearly indicate my preference.
I just felt like
I didn't know what I was doing.
I would want to escape the house.
It's okay.
I want to be alone for a while.
Then I'll go first.
It's okay.
Can we stop making choices?
I think my direction of attraction
is very clear.
It's one person.
This person is Ruita.
One person, Lu Bingkun.
I just like him.
I like him very much.
The seventeenth person to my right.
It is still him.
Really.
Seventeen is my luckiest number.
So sweet.
So intense.
Good thing you're here.
I was thinking...
I watched my previous self...
I can't pick anyone else
to ride this thing with me.
- So nice.
- Great.
Hi.
Come on, you go first.
Ladies first.
Together, three, two, one.
You two press it together.
There are fireworks.
Paw and Meow.
- The familiar "Paw and Meow" again.
- So happy.
My neck looks even longer.
Mutual love.
Nothing beats your own romance.
My cheekbones are
almost falling from grinning.
Did you see the fireworks just now?
Who set them off?
Dude, just zip it.
I'm speechless.
Isn't it?
Our neighbor.
The hotel next door set them off.
I saw from afar
that the people getting married
at the hotel next door were kissing.
Did you really see it?
Actually, he told me.
We both pressed the lights.
So, under the fireworks, a little kiss.
That line sounds really cheesy.
But it's really sweet.
Really sweet.
So I have a question for you two.
When did you both confirm
that you're ready
for the next relationship phase?
I think the island
is totally full of romantic vibes.
We rode jet skis,
went grocery shopping,
and cooked for everyone together.
Those heart-fluttering moments
have turned into little bits
of daily life.
Yes.
For the rest of our time in Hainan,
we are
(Early retirement)
like an old married couple,
just sitting there.
I'd like to ask BK.
When you first kissed Ruita,
how did it feel?
Soft lips.
Anyone who's too stubborn to back down
must have something to hide.
If he is stubborn,
he is a bit conflicted.
Then I want to ask everyone,
in the first part you just watched,
was there anything
you didn't know back then?
Actually, after watching that part,
I just realized
that Zhuoran mentioned me in it.
And I was actually very touched
by the appreciation
and synchronicity between us.
But indeed, at that moment
on a certain day in the house,
we both felt
that our beautiful moments
could only go that far.
I never knew
that Zhuoran and Danqi had...
Yes, this is indeed...
Plus due to my schedule,
my progress was a bit behind.
What I didn't know
was about Liu.
Because I did see Liu
was crying
after she came out of that dark room.
I didn't know what exactly happened.
I found it out here.
What about you, Chen Jianying?
I didn't know
everyone's storylines.
Because as the days went by,
I was caught between the lovely moments
shared with everybody
and the sorrow of realizing
I'd soon depart.
But now I see
in love,
each has their own sweetness,
and their own little struggles.
So, during the final selection round,
what were your thoughts and feelings
at the time?
I think in that environment at the time,
I definitely cherished the limited time
in the house and on the island.
And now looking back,
I also think I was very brave.
I live in the moment as well.
And I'm actually a very brave
and direct person.
Let's applaud for all
who bravely and directly pressed
the burst light.
Let's continue watching.
This was on the table.
Who wrote this?
Here's someone in the know.
She kept silent the whole time.
Is this something we shouldn't read?
(No, and there's also...)
Hiding my inner emotions.
Cooking frantically to cover it up.
Hello.
So beautiful.
No spark happened.
Bye-bye, island.
Falling for someone as an adult
is really hard.
But
even if I don't feel a spark,
I won't
pretend that I'm falling for someone.
I probably should leave them.
Everyone wants a sweet love
on the island,
but it's okay if I don't have it.
Even if I can't get it, I still shine.
Still shining.
Well said.
I think the saddest thing for me
- Let me hand out some tissues first.
- (is I'm about to leave this fun castle.)
I'll take one too,
just in case.
Just in case.
You take two.
I think that in the family
of Love Actually,
everyone was so pure.
The happiest moment was...
This is really hilarious.
And we had so much fun.
I haven't had so much fun
in a long time.
♪Listen♪
Everyone is falling in love.
Why am I crying like this?
This is the sincere, real,
and lovely Chen Jianying.
No one needs to be sad.
Don't be sad, I'm telling you.
Don't.
Just take care of yourself.
Don't worry about us.
But you must be brave.
You must be well.
You must be especially
Okay.
My story in the house ends here.
It's time to come to an end.
I think Chen Jianying is really
grand and passionate.
She is someone
so ethereal, like a fairy.
And she left in a grand
and passionate way.
When she came, she was a white rose.
When she left,
she was a red rose.
Both are moving.
Thanks, babe.
Chen Jianying, always the best.
Thank you.
Was that the only time
Ruita cried?
Such a fickle.
Such a fickle made Ruita cry.
I just feel that
we can actually say a proper goodbye.
Mainly because back then,
none of us actually realized.
Yes, it happened suddenly.
Suddenly.
I hope you won't make me suffer in love.
So sweet.
Just finished crying.
Now I need some sweetness
to heal up.
My mood goes down and up.
This is a brand-new version
I haven't seen before.
Do you like massages?
I get massages when I'm tired.
Do you prefer Thai or Chinese massages?
I can't handle Thai at all.
It's too painful.
I'm very afraid of pain.
Thai massages aren't painful.
Chinese massages are very painful.
Thai massages are kneading.
Really?
Yes, you can try it out.
If you want to go, I can take you.
It's all written on your face, Lizheng.
Do you want some, Ling Lizheng?
I don't like desserts.
Lizheng really
didn't want to eat sweets.
Chen Jianying was still in her emotions.
That day, anyway,
it was such a scene.
As soon as we came back,
we found the notebook.
Actually, from when I decided to leave,
to when I left, there should be
about one or two days.
During the day,
I was writing in that notebook,
and at night, I kept
trying to spend more time with you.
I stopped my day-on, day-off eating.
I ate together for two days straight.
Every meal, I ate with you.
And I really couldn't bear to leave you.
Just like I said in there,
in the adult world,
being able to not feel lonely
is a very fortunate thing.
Yes, so I kept looking back
with every step.
I really didn't want to leave.
But when everyone
is on the journey of pursuing love,
if I no longer have romantic feelings,
I can't stay there.
I really wondered
how everyone's doing later on.
I was so worried about each of you.
Worried your heart out.
Yes.
But overall, I feel
you are very brave,
because I think coming to the house
is very brave.
And the decision to leave the house
is also very brave.
Thank you.
What brought tears to my eyes was
when Chen Jianying talked
about childlike innocence.
I feel that in the house,
we were like children again,
having so much fun
as a group.
And after you left the house,
we're back to the adult world.
Ji Yu was always encouraging me.
And he said,
"It's okay.
You'll get what you want.
You will have everything."
I was just...
Yeah. That was
a very joyful
atmosphere.
I was the first to know at the time.
My thought at the time was
that maybe you would go back
to Shanghai with us
and say a proper goodbye.
And
I even specially planned
how to say goodbye
and prepared a gift, and then...
Yes.
Suddenly, the confession was...
At night,
back in the room, I was alone.
And then I saw
the box written for me.
I saw all the flowers had withered
and
the empty bed.
Because at the beginning,
when we moved into that room,
the flowers were blooming beautifully.
Yes.
But the day you left,
even the flowers had withered.
I wouldn't necessarily expect
that love must happen.
But I'm eager
for a heartfelt love
that makes me
want to give my all.
As I became more and more certain that
I didn't have those feelings,
I knew that I probably couldn't
continue to spend time
with such lovely people
anymore.
Because I think
each of us coming to the house
is actually a re-understanding
of ourselves.
What do you think about
your self-awareness?
Or do you feel you've grown in any way?
I feel that here
I actually
received a lot of kindness
and encouragement.
Because
in my life and work,
over ninety percent of the voices
are full of denial
and criticism.
But after coming to the house,
no matter what I did,
everyone encouraged me and stood by me.
Because you are really great.
Thank you.
So I feel that in the house,
I was
recharged.
It restored
my energy to deal with
many things in life.
Because I was the only one
who knew at that time.
Yes.
And that day when I saw she was
not doing her day-on, day-off eating,
and
when I saw her emotionally break down,
I told myself
I must hold my emotions together.
If I break down...
But later, after we went back
to the room,
we even hugged and cried together.
And she was super cute.
She gave me all her de-puffing pills.
She said she wouldn't need them anymore.
I won't need them anymore, all for you.
(Besties must be beautiful, too)
Besties must be beautiful.
Then let's continue watching.
Okay.
Let them see your story.
Take them into your reality.
Welcome to the real world.
It's over.
As soon as I left, you returned
to the real world.
For me, the utopia ended.
The turning point of utopia.
Miss you, thinking of you.
Already daily sweetness.
Okay.
Let's start, Mr. Lu.
Home visit mode.
Okay.
Any questions to ask?
No.
What questions do you have for me?
Zoom in.
I'll have only gotten
the work part done.
Maybe.
Working by the age of 30.
Okay.
These two parts can actually
be combined into one part.
You mean combining work and sleep?
No.
Sleep and dating.
Work.
Make him practice piano
for eight hours a day?
Really looking forward to this day.
Playing piano for eight hours.
It already feels like
a couple planning their future.
After communication,
I think we're on the same page
with our plans.
We share the same direction.
We'll just take it slow
and work on the plan together.
I think this model is great.
Really quite good.
When I'm in a relationship later,
I'll make one too.
Yes, these two notebooks, right?
Compare these two notebooks.
Everyone syncs up.
Align the granularity.
Who is that?
Why are you so restless?
I feel uncomfortable
every time I see myself.
From king of the kids to...
So you went abroad for graduate school?
No, the last year of undergraduate.
You two are quite funny.
Do you want a boy or a girl?
Oh, my!
Maybe you could go experience Xiamen?
I'll experience Changsha.
How about that?
Sure.
Actually, the reason
we've gotten along relatively well
is that
he's always been able
to give me the answers I was looking for
when it comes to my questions.
And today,
after reading his life profile,
I feel like things are much clearer.
But I think
we still need to continue getting along.
So I can understand this person
more thoroughly.
I come from a single-parent family.
So do you live
with your dad or mom?
My mom.
My dad passed away
when I was 16.
He was doing
volunteer teaching in a village
when he was diagnosed with lung cancer.
This matter
was a huge blow to me at the time.
Do you want a tissue?
Tears fall again.
Get a new tissue.
Get a new one.
New tissue.
Even when I dragged
things out like that,
you didn't get upset?
What perspective is this?
Our massage perspective.
That day was super funny.
I wasn't sure
if he could accept my past.
It could also be that between us,
it just pauses here.
Brave.
But I'm only interested in Xiao Wentao.
I want to leave a chance for us.
Go for it.
Now I've known about her experiences.
While reading the profile,
I was thinking,
later,
how can I talk to her about these issues
up there?
I remember at that time,
Xuan was actually
quite anxious.
So
you're saying on this matter,
your perspective and mine are different.
Is that what you mean?
I think so.
You're right.
Maybe our perspectives are different.
Then what kind of person do you think
is from the same world as you?
I don't know.
You can be straightforward.
For example,
if you mind this matter,
you can say it directly.
You can say,
"I never thought
you were in this situation."
"I feel I can't accept it."
"It's not suitable," or whatever.
You can be straightforward.
I would care.
I still care.
I think since I dared
to say it out loud,
it proves at least
I'm telling the truth.
Okay.
Get some rest.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
He's thinking about the gap between us.
I just think
if the other person
wants to keep a distance,
I will definitely leave enough space.
I don't need to let him know
that I wrote these things.
I also don't want to push you
to accept
the kind of person I am.
If he doesn't want to take it further,
some things can just remain
at this beautiful image,
and that's enough.
This is Love Actually.
I didn't expect
it to be heartbreaking.
They are both mature, I think.
Wentao honestly spoke out
all his concerns and feelings.
I think, including what I said,
honesty is the most important
and the most beautiful quality
in a relationship.
Yes.
Only by being honest
can we face problems
and solve them.
Xuan was also very brave
to express these things honestly.
I think the two of them truly
possess the semi-mature ability
they need
to face and test each other's love
after returning to reality.
Actually, I think
now that the two of them
have encountered such a trial
in the house,
if they can get through it,
they will definitely be better
and stronger.
Yes.
At the beginning,
none of us had an omniscient view.
Right.
Nor would we know from the start
that Xuan is a mother with a baby.
So at the moment
Xiaowen found out,
he must have had
a huge shock or surprise inside.
Yes.
So he was also digesting this emotion.
I think it's just like
feelings.
It's very complex.
You need to understand
that it's just like a sphere.
And whether
it's Danqi, Xuan, or Ruita,
at that time, I felt
revealing my vulnerable side
was a crucial step
towards the relationship.
Yes.
After watching the life profiles,
what were your feelings and thoughts?
Because
BK and Ruita
watched together.
So what kind of feelings did you have?
My feeling at the time
was that I could suddenly understand
why BK is so mature
at the age of 24.
(What about you?)
When I looked at Ruita,
there was a feeling like,
as shown in the clip,
although we were
in different time periods,
whether it was in Jiaxing, Zhejiang,
or later on,
I actually think
we have a real connection.
Real connection.
When I watched Lizheng's life profile,
there wasn't a substantial
step forward at that moment,
but
I would feel
this person became
more three-dimensional to me.
And I still wanted
to get to know him further.
Okay, then let's continue watching.
Do you want to go?
If you don't want to go,
just tell me secretly.
Dear Youling.
What is Mr. Dong doing?
Getting in the way.
Suddenly giving a massage.
Xihui, when Ji Yu
asked you out at that time,
what were your thoughts and feelings?
Did you guess he would ask you out?
In the house,
actually, I never really
felt Ji Yu's feelings
for me.
It was only after he told me that I...
So when he asked me out,
I just thought,
it was okay to go out
and have fun with him.
So Lizheng, at that time,
when you heard Ji Yu ask Xihui out,
how did you feel?
Because back in Sanya,
Xihui was probably
under the impression
that we had already
reached a stage
of getting to know each other.
And then we faced the reality
of a long-distance relationship.
And Ji Yu mentioned
he's usually in Hangzhou.
Xihui told me
she has more opportunities
to be in Hangzhou.
Take the geographical factor
into account.
Yes. So maybe
they would get to know each other.
Really.
I feel like I left
right when the utopia
was at its most beautiful.
How come the plot afterwards was really
entering into adult love,
family, future, and planning.
Very realistic.
Really need to use wisdom
to solve many problems.
I also think so.
Actually, Chen Jianying's departure
was also a turning point of this utopia.
Actually, after we came back from Sanya,
we had only spent
about half a month together, right?
Yes, and then facing reality,
there will be some tests
or some adjustments.
It's very normal.
Because love can't
only exist in utopia.
True love
must withstand the test of reality.
Actually, I think one fortunate thing
for all of us is that
we also gained
such a precious experience.
I think all of us
leveled up after recording this show.
Yes.
The house is also the path we came from.
In that case,
let's each use a few keywords
to preview the next episode.
Xiamen.
Reality test, part two.
I feel the exact same way.
(Reality setting in)
That feeling of reality setting in.
Drawing.
All right.
You're all right.
I can't think of anything else.
But I think it's just
that it will get
more and more exciting later.
Everyone can stay tuned.
Look forward to it.
Okay.
Then our watch-along
for Love Actually S5,
Episode 7, ends here.
Let's look forward
to the next episode together.
- Bye-bye.
=Love Actually S5=