=Love Actually S5=
(Extra Episode)
(Back to the house)
What did you just want?
Do you need something?
I don't.
I'm just checking if the rice
has started cooking.
No, I don't need anything.
Do you need any help?
No, thanks.
Don't worry about it.
Then I'll just stir-fry the eggs, onion,
and tomato
all together.
Yes, that's exactly what I mean.
Like a hodgepodge.
Okay, we'll take turns being the chef.
You know, there's a pattern
in dating variety shows.
The chef never finds love.
Really?
He's whisking the eggs right now.
I cooked a few days ago.
It's okay.
Everyone just...
I cooked too.
Right.
We all take turns together, so...
So just stay out of the kitchen.
But I think
friendship is the most important
thing here.
You're absolutely right.
Because I think love
includes friendship.
(Deeply agree)
Romantic love and friendship.
Friendship is just
a very small part of love.
Human beings have a great love.
Love for the Earth, for animals.
That's so well said.
Let me cook tomorrow.
We'll just have one dish?
I'll come and help too.
I'm coming.
What are you doing, Ruita?
What are you doing?
Joining the chef squad.
Put it down.
Let go.
(Switching to an idol drama scene)
Don't be like this.
Let go.
(Should I take this or not?)
Don't be like this.
- Don't be like this.
I'll be unhappy if you keep this up.
To Xiaowen.
To Mr. Xiao.
You are always so smooth with words.
Are you trying to ask me for something?
You'll owe him once you eat
what he makes.
It's okay?
Watch this.
We can watch TV now, right?
We can only watch WeTV.
I'm a WeTV Premium member.
Does this have a membership?
I don't know.
I just finished downloading it.
I want to watch TV.
What are you guys doing here?
Fiddling with the TV.
TV dramas.
Can this speaker connect to
this TV?
You can use
the karaoke app.
Your microphone
should be able to connect via Bluetooth.
Connect to the Bluetooth speaker.
- Then turn it off.
- Welcome to use Bluetooth microphone.
This is the microphone
for that karaoke app.
Bluetooth mode.
It matches this.
That's perfect.
Pick.
Pick a song.
Pick
"Empty World".
"The One And Only" is also fine.
Who'll sing?
You.
Come on.
I don't know how this will sound.
♪Not as simple as breathing♪
The mic is a bit low.
Can't tell, but...
But this microphone...
There can't be a better microphone.
Unless we buy some.
I actually have one at home.
Let's go and see how their cooking
is going.
I feel like the scrambled eggs
with tomatoes
should be ready soon.
It's about to turn golden, right?
(The chef is cooking.)
- It smells so good.
- It smells great.
Scrambled eggs with tomatoes.
CCTV.
When I was in Beijing before,
I was told how to learn Beijing dialect.
Well,
"Xiong shi chao ji dan"
[*Chest is scrambled eggs]
is "xi hong shi chao ji dan".
[*Scrambled eggs with tomatoes]
Are you the queen of bad jokes?
(Such a dry joke)
Huh, Danqi?
What?
She said when pretending to speak
like a Beijinger,
"xi hong shi chao ji dan"
[*Scrambled eggs with tomatoes]
is "Xiong shi chao ji dan".
[*Chest is scrambled eggs]
"Xiong shi chao ji dan".
"Xi hong shi chao ji dan".
[*Scrambled eggs with tomatoes]
Tomatoes.
Queen of bad jokes.
That's a good one.
Hello.
Are you busy?
When I saw the messages blowing up,
I got a bit anxious.
Okay.
Then just watch quietly by yourself.
Is our food almost ready?
I'll call you when it's ready.
Thanks.
Aren't you guys eating?
We are.
Don't keep this leftover one.
That's amazing.
(Tasty)
I need to get some too.
No rice paddle?
It's good, delicious.
The king oyster mushrooms are so good.
Perfect, really delicious.
Delicious.
Very flavorful.
So delicious.
Where's a charging port here?
Go look in the living room.
Over here.
Lizheng, there's food over there.
So, Xiaowen,
when did you start
being so good at cooking?
When I was abroad.
I started learning to cook
around 2022.
I could cook before,
but it was just...
Okay,
but to become a chef is still...
I'm not a chef.
Chef.
Amazing.
What's wrong?
I dropped something on the lawn.
What is it?
It's just...
it's just something of mine.
I'll ask them to get it.
They can contact the groundskeeper
and ask them to help
look for it.
(Contacting the venue staff)
Because we were sitting right there.
Did you find it?
What kind of thing is it?
Jewelry?
It's okay.
Who exactly? Is it me?
Your phone probably
automatically connected to that speaker.
(The ring from Ling Lizheng)
I'm so frustrated.
It's okay.
There will be new ones.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
- I'm really sorry.
- There will be new ones.
It's okay.
(I could see she was very anxious.)
(The only thing I could do
was comfort her.)
It's fine.
Come, come sit down.
Don't squat.
I'm contacting them urgently.
It's just an object.
Don't take it...
What is it?
I didn't see you with anything.
Is it something very valuable?
No.
Not valuable.
What is it?
Is it something very valuable?
No, it's my own thing.
Personal item?
It's okay. Don't be too anxious.
Are you worried you can't find it?
Yes.
No, it will be found.
Worried.
Are you worried you can't find it?
- Yes, I'm worried I can't find it.
- No.
It'll be found.
That's funny.
Okay.
Let me.
I'm just right here.
Thank you.
- I'll help you.
- Don't wash them.
Let me wash them.
No worries. I'm just right here.
Sit for a while.
Don't fight me for it.
I'm really going to wash them.
Want to do some work?
Yes, I want to work.
Right now, I really want to work.
Okay.
So,
you've found another outlet
to release your emotions.
Yes, just work.
I support you.
Burying yourself in work.
Right.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Good luck at work, bye-bye.
(Everyone is heading out to work
one after another)
We're all in black, the three of us.
Right?
Yes.
I'm in black too.
Look, if I tie this on,
- I'm in black too.
- It's a sea of black in the mirror.
This way,
the four of us
look like
some kind of mysterious organization.
Let me take a photo for you.
Here.
Here we go.
We probably shouldn't be wearing black.
So cool.
Cool.
Pretty cool.
Really cool.
I like this.
Please send me this photo.
This is awesome.
Too cool.
Well, Danqi.
Danqi can join too.
Danqi, you surely have black clothes.
Look at the four of us.
Danqi, let me show you a photo.
Top real estate agent.
The Matrix.
What's this called?
Intellectual black.
Right?
It's called semi-mature black.
When is it fully mature black?
You, you are fully mature.
We are semi-mature.
Put you on the grill.
You'll be fully mature soon.
[*Homophonic to "fully cooked"]
(The fully mature guy got hurt)
Is there a small onion inside?
Yes.
I want to eat this onion
tomorrow morning.
It must be incredibly fragrant.
Put it away first.
Did we buy yogurt?
Yes.
- You can drink yogurt.
- I can drink a little yogurt.
Does anyone want some yogurt?
It's a really big jar.
I'll have some.
Then we'll split a jar of it.
What container should we use?
Oh no.
I can't get through, guys.
Let me.
Take it from this side.
Here, take this.
Can't get it open.
You try.
Why do you blink at me all the time?
Because I think you look gorgeous today.
You are beautiful every day.
- You all are beautiful every day.
- Beautiful every day.
Beautiful every day.
At least let me peel an orange
for you by hand.
You don't eat it.
But you enjoy the process of doing it.
Hello.
Teke a little cup.
Let's toast.
Have a pleasant journey.
(Off to Hainan)
We're about to head out.
We'll be away from the house
for a while.
Okay.
Hello.
This is your hostess, Danqi.
Now I'm going to interview
Our beautiful ladies one by one.
Xuan.
We're about to head out soon.
How do you feel?
Very happy.
I want to go surfing.
I feel surrounded by love
even as we're about to leave.
This sandwich is from Ruita.
This is Mr. Dong's ruby cake.
Looking forward to the Sanya trip.
Hope to meet the sixth male guest.
What's wrong?
Did the previous five male guest
disappoint you?
Don't always blurt out the honest truth.
Let's go.
We're off now.
Going on an outing.
- Going on an outing.
- Outing.
Hello.
- Hello.
- We're about to head out.
We're going out.
Where are we going today?
Hainan.
(Protection)
Ready to go.
Let's go.
We're heading to Sanya.
Our spring outing plan begins.
We're here.
We've arrived at the airport.
We're about to set off.
(On the other side, the guys
with a completely different vibe)
(Three semi-mature brothers'
airport fashion show)
We're about to set off.
(Arrived at
Haikou Meilan International Airport)
We're here.
My left side looks better.
Then let's put the camera on the left.
Now we've arrived in Haikou.
(Arrived in Haikou)
Haikou.
Your arm strength is really good.
My arm strength is really...
My deltoid muscles.
Found our car.
(House layout)
This is good.
Okay.
We can just swim at night.
Today is a really wonderful day.
Today the three of us
have already sworn brotherhood.
We'll stick together.
The three of you?
Eldest Brother,
Second Brother, Third Brother.
(Third brother, Eldest brother,
Second brother)
Fourth brother.
(Fourth brother)
You really are the fourth brother.
You are Daoming Si.
(Daoming Si)
Daoming Si.
Look at me.
- You guys look great.
- Cool.
How about we take a big group photo?
Come on.
We're taking a big group photo
before everyone's here?
This is a small group photo.
Small group photo.
Yes, small group photo.
Still missing...
Amazing.
(Being goofy)
- Feels good.
- So funny.
This place is pretty good.
Is this a bedroom?
The first floor is ours.
There's another room over there.
Then we only have four beds.
Three rooms.
No, three rooms.
There's another room over there.
- Okay.
- Why are you two together?
As soon as I got off the plane today,
I thought, when I saw Zhuoran,
I must ask him if he missed me.
But when I saw him, he said first,
"I missed you."
I said, "I miss you too."
Stick together.
Seriously?
Daoming Si.
You two are already together.
Are they all here?
Coming.
Hello.
Let's start eating.
Nice to meet you all.
Welcome.
- Welcome.
- Cheers.
Welcome aboard.
So where do you usually stay in Beijing?
You mean where I live?
Yes.
I just returned to Beijing last year.
Recently I've been living in Changping.
That's quite far.
Beijing is too big.
What's your school?
Peking University.
Yes, Peking University.
Do you want dipping sauce?
I don't need dipping sauce.
I'll just eat it raw.
- You're often in Beijing and Changsha.
- Changsha.
And Hangzhou.
She lives in Wudaokou.
Three places.
You live in Wudaokou?
I live right next to the school.
Because I just stay in hotels.
I don't rent a place in Beijing.
Is that Qingbuliang?
Yes.
- I really want to eat it.
- What you wanted.
What I've been longing for.
You wanted Qingbuliang,
coconut chicken,
and...
And what?
Come on, think of it.
Stuck here.
Hurry.
What other delicacies does Hainan have?
Can't help you.
What we think of
isn't what Liu can think of.
And Hainan rice noodles.
Hainan rice noodles, here.
Then you can have all three today.
Yes, very happy.
You're not using this bowl, right?
No.
Then can I serve her this?
Thank you.
Look at those guys.
They're in a completely different vibe.
Sitting over there.
Super serious.
Go over to them.
Do you want to go sit over there?
Super serious.
- They're all gathered over there.
- Okay.
Okay.
Here, baby.
Thanks.
Friends over here.
Anyone want coconut rice?
- It seems like it's only at our table.
- Thank you.
Do you want some?
I don't.
So where are you from?
I was born in Zhengzhou, Henan.
Then we're both from the four provinces.
[*Shandong, Shanxi, Henan, Hebei]
Now I can tell you're an extrovert.
Just a bit tired.
- Tomorrow you'll see me in another state.
- It's okay.
Okay.
What is it?
What do you mean? Is this what you ate?
Tsk.
You're from Wuhan?
Yes, I'm from Wuhan.
But my company is in Shanghai.
When can I say,
"But my company is in..."
- When can I say something like that?
- Get a job.
Go to Xuan's company.
Then you can say, "My company is..."
I'll give Xuan
emotional support.
Like, "Are you tired?"
I'll play you a tune.
(Considerate Wentao)
Play what?
The instrument
I've played since childhood is
the trumpet.
Did nobody hear
- he play reveille?
- I heard it.
I said in my room,
"This guy is so hilarious."
(Out of the loop)
What? What's going on?
When the three of us
were about to head out,
there were probably still
people upstairs not up.
I played the trumpet at the stairs,
bum-bum-bum-bum-bum.
(Shot on Zhou Youling's phone)
It felt like being back
in military training.
But I heard the piano sound yesterday.
Was it you playing the piano yesterday?
Around two a.m.
I didn't hear it.
Around two?
It should be when BK and I were...
No.
We had already gone upstairs.
I was already in bed.
Then it should be Story.
Did I play the piano?
(She didn't know)
Three a.m.
I don't remember.
You don't sleepwalk, do you?
- I was sleepwalking and playing piano.
- You scared me.
Sleepwalking and playing piano.
So scary?
It wasn't you.
It wasn't the two of us.
It wasn't Story.
Then it might be Liu.
(Last night)
(How can human memory be so confused?)
Can you play all instruments?
No.
I just
have been playing the trumpet.
Proficient in blowing, pulling,
plucking, and singing.
I'm proficient in blowing.
Pulling...
Erhu.
I'm not really good at that.
That's a bit too different.
Plucking, just so-so.
- Piano.
- Singing is okay.
When we first met on the first day,
I was especially nervous,
- and I would.
- Would be shy.
Be very guarded.
So when I watched it,
I really wanted to slap myself.
Anxious minds bring clumsy hands.
Of course not.
I was making coffee.
This part is so sweet.
Xuan, listen to this.
Here comes the handsome guy.
The handsome guy is here.
Girl, work on your facial expressions.