♪No more retreat♪
♪Let love run wild and free♪
♪Devouring the silence♪
♪Filling the void with light♪
♪All the love I hold♪
♪No need to hide♪
♪For you♪
♪I've found my path♪
♪I cannot live without you♪
[Fatal Allure]
[Adapted from "In Her Year"
by Xian Sheng Zui Ye on Qimao]
[Episode 13]
[Wish you a hundred years of happiness]
You're still my fiancée.
Scoundrel.
That's right.
Let go of me.
Song Sipu.
Song Sipu, let go of me.
Do you hear me?
Let go of me.
Song Sipu.
- Do you hear me?
- Sipu.
Don't trust this woman.
She can't be Min Jingya.
Song Sipu.
How do you have the time
to care about me
before you've taken care
of so many of your affairs?
Who are you to talk about me, impostor?
Lin Yaxin.
If you ever point a finger
at her again,
I'll send you out again.
Sipu, I'm doing this for your sake,
but how can you say that to me?
This is my business, not yours.
Miss, it's good for you
to take this opportunity to see
how cold-blooded this man is.
Shut up.
See? I advised you nicely,
but you wouldn't listen.
Then I can only wish you
a hundred years of happiness.
Ji Chan.
[Min's Ancestral Temple]
Sipu, she doesn't like you,
so can you not put your mind on her?
Lin Yaxin.
Don't put your mind on me.
I don't like you.
Ji Chan.
[Min's Ancestral Temple]
Sweetheart.
Don't cry.
I'm here with you.
Who bullied you so much
that you're so aggrieved?
Sipu has never
been so mean to me.
It's Ji Chan's fault.
She stole Sipu from me.
Dad, I don't care.
Avenge me.
Ji Chan again?
I have to get rid of her.
Okay.
Don't cry.
How do you want to take revenge?
I'll do what you want.
Master.
This is all the title
you've recovered for Min's Union
in the past three years.
Would you like me
to transfer it to Ms. Jingshu?
Not yet.
Since Ji Linjiang
wants her to become Min Jingya publicly,
he is trying to get Min's Group back
from me fair and square.
Master.
Ms. Jingshu
doesn't care about your feelings at all.
She became Min Jingya without warning
and broke off the engagement.
Please give her back her things.
Let's stay out of her business.
Her business is mine.
If I give them back to her,
she'll be targeted,
so it's better to keep them with me
so they can point their fingers at me.
You really don't care about yourself.
Master.
Ms. Min has been taken.
Put these away.
OK.
Hello?
Master Ji, Anjiang
is going to do something to Ji Chan.
Let her go. Don't kill her.
Hello again, Ji Chan.
Lin Yaxin, what are you doing?
I'm going to destroy you.
I'll spread the video
of you being raped
so that you can't
hold your head up anymore.
Then you won't be able
to compete with me for Sipu.
Lin Yaxin, you better stop.
Now you want me to stop?
If you didn't shamelessly
pretend to be Min Jingya
to seduce Sipu,
I could spare your life.
To put it bluntly,
you had it coming.
Then I'm afraid you'll be disappointed.
I am Min Jingya.
It doesn't matter
whether you are Min Jingya or not.
You got in the way of me and Sipu,
and I'm going to get rid of you.
Lin Yaxin, you'd better think it over.
Is it worth it
to do this for a man?
If you hurt me today,
the Min family will not let you go.
The Min family is dead,
so how dare you threaten me?
What are you looking at?
Isn't what I'm saying the truth?
I've been by Sipu's side
for the past three years.
Why did you take away all his attention
as soon as you appeared?
I just want to destroy you.
I'll see if Sipu still likes you
after you've been raped.
Do it.
Come on.
Behave yourself.
What are you doing?
Let go of me.
- Don't move. Behave yourself.
- Let go of me.
Let go of me.
- Behave yourself.
- Don't come any closer.
Don't come any closer.
Don't worry. I'll be gentle.
Boss, the boat for Ji Chan is ready.
Behave yourself.
Don't rush.
Let Yaxin play a little longer
until she's happy.
Let go of me.
That's what you get
for touching me with your dirty hands.
Go.
Don't come any closer.
What are you waiting for?
Go protect Yaxin.
- Now.
- Yes.
Ji Chan, you...
Put the knife down.
The knife.
Go away.
Ji Chan.
Next time you want to hurt me,
don't use such dirty tricks.
Don't forget you're a woman too.
Ji Chan, what are you trying to do?
This is how I repay you.
Lin Yaxin, don't forget.
I'm not that easy to mess with.
Miss, are you okay?
Put the knife down.
Don't come over.
Stay back.
Take off her clothes.
How dare she hit me?
Don't come any closer.
Chop off her hand.
How dare you hit her?
Now.
Teach her a lesson.
How dare she hit me?
Let go of me.
- Ji Chan, you're finished.
- Let go of me.
Behave yourself.
Let go of me.
♪Our love is on its way back♪
♪Returning♪
♪Love is back♪
♪Let love run free♪
♪Destined to be♪
♪I come for you♪
♪Love is back♪
♪No more retreat♪
♪Let love run wild and free♪
♪Right now, right here♪