♪No more retreat♪
♪Let love run wild and free♪
♪Devouring the silence♪
♪Filling the void with light♪
♪All the love I hold♪
♪No need to hide♪
♪For you♪
♪I've found my path♪
♪I cannot live without you♪
[Fatal Allure]
[Adapted from "In Her Year"
by Xian Sheng Zui Ye on Qimao]
[Episode 12]
[Just yell. You're my fiancée anyway.]
Welcome back, Min Jingshu.
I'm Min Jingya.
Why?
Min Jingshu was dispensable
in Song Sipu's mind,
but my sister was the one he loved.
Back then, he may have suffered a lot
when he caused the death of his lover
for the sake of profit.
Then I'll make him
lose everything as my sister.
I'm really growing
to love your madness.
[Ji's Union]
Ms. Ji.
Master Ji.
Master, what happened to you and Ms. Ji?
She's away for a few days.
Why did she suddenly abandon the plan
and return to Ji Linjiang?
Did Ji Linjiang abandon his plan
to keep Jingshu with me
to get business information
and let her leave me
because he had other plans
or sensed something?
Master.
A few days ago,
I asked you to investigate
Ji Linjiang's malicious competition.
How did it go?
Mr. Liu's evidence is enough
to put Ji Linjiang in jail,
but Master,
why don't we just expose
what Ji Linjiang did to the Min family?
Only public opinion without evidence
won't be enough to bring him to justice.
So rare.
Your malicious competition
has already violated the law.
If you want these photos
not to be exposed,
you'd better stay away from Ji Chan.
That's not good.
I can't.
[Ji Chan]
If the screenshots
of these chats go public,
I did break the law,
but Ji Chan
is the most important part of it,
so do you think
she can get away with it?
You're threatening me with her?
My cousin.
Let's change the rules of the game.
I now want not only everything you have
but also Ji Chan.
Ji Linjiang.
You should know better than me
what Ji Chan has been through.
And you're still using her like this?
People have their own destinies.
It's her destiny,
and it's yours too.
When you use her as a weakness,
you're at a disadvantage.
It's time.
Let's watch a show.
Hello, everyone.
I'm the sole survivor
of the car accident
that happened at Min's Union back then.
I'm
[Min's Group “Return” Launch]
Min Jingya.
Min Jingya is alive?
Min Jingya is really alive.
There are still people alive
in Min's Union.
My sister Min Jingshu
and my grandmother
both died in that car accident.
The crash was not an accident
[Min's Group “Return” Launch]
but a calculated murder.
Murder?
Murder? Do you know who did it?
- Who did it, please?
- I've been holding back for three years
[Min's Group “Return” Launch]
looking for evidence
to find out who's behind the accident.
Ms. Min, how did you survive?
Who is behind this?
Do you have evidence
to prove your suspicions?
Ms. Min.
Of course.
I'll reveal it all
[Min's Group “Return” Launch]
at the right time.
Ms. Min.
Please make it public.
Min's Group has now been
almost completely acquired
by Song's Group,
so are you venturing back now
because you have any special plans
or arrangements?
I am the sole legal heir to Min's Group.
I will hold the succession ceremony
in a week's time.
At that time,
I will take back all the properties
belonging to the Min family.
Ms. Min, does your engagement
to Mr. Song Sipu still stand?
[Min's Group “Return” Launch]
Of course not.
Please look forward
to all the activities of the Min family.
Ji Linjiang, why didn't you tell me
that Ji Chan is Min Jingya?
What's the point of telling you?
You could have killed her.
You asked me to eliminate
the Min family back then.
Now you've gotten away with it,
but what if Ji Chan came after me?
I'm telling you now
that she's sure it was Song Sipu,
so you'd better
be quiet
and not do anything stupid.
The day will come when things are known.
Listen.
Ji Chan is now my biggest problem.
What are you doing?
Why did you reveal yourself
as Min Jingya?
What?
Do you think I'm not
or do you think I'm not qualified
to be Min Jingya?
Or
are you angry because
I canceled my engagement
to you in public?
Really?
Are you still daydreaming
about marrying me?
I've known for a long time
that you're from Min's family.
The reason why I didn't publicize
that you're a member of the Min family
is because there are a lot of people
watching the Min family secretly.
Do you know how dangerous it is
for you to go public like this?
I'm taking you out of Jiang City now.
Stop being hypocritical, Song Sipu.
Besides,
I don't have any relationship with you,
so who are you to control me?
Don't have any relationship?
Can you stop doing whatever you want,
Ji Chan?
If I could do whatever I wanted,
then the first thing I'd do
is erase what I had with you.
What did you say?
Ji Chan, I'm taking you home.
Let go of me, Song Sipu.
I'm going to yell.
Go ahead.
Even if your public identity
is now Min Jingya,
you're still my fiancée.
Scoundrel.
That's right.
Let go of me.
♪Our love is on its way back♪
♪Returning♪
♪Love is back♪
♪Let love run free♪
♪Destined to be♪
♪I come for you♪
♪Love is back♪
♪No more retreat♪
♪Let love run wild and free♪
♪Right now, right here♪