♪No more retreat♪
♪Let love run wild and free♪
♪Devouring the silence♪
♪Filling the void with light♪
♪All the love I hold♪
♪No need to hide♪
♪For you♪
♪I've found my path♪
♪I cannot live without you♪
[Fatal Allure]
[Adapted from "In Her Year"
by Xian Sheng Zui Ye on Qimao]
[Episode 20]
[Love cannot be fulfilled by meeting.]
Song Sipu.
Please.
Yes.
Will you really marry me?
Yes, I will.
Then we'll tell Mr. Ji
the news tomorrow and ask him
to choose a good date for us.
Zhou Ye.
Bandage Jingya.
Yes, sir.
Master.
Mr. Ji has sent another reminder.
They said you have to go
to the family dinner tomorrow,
or he...
Any clues about the dash cam?
So far we've found
that Master Qi secretly
kept the dash cam
when he disposed of the car
because he was worried
that Ji Linjiang would betray him.
What he gave to Ji Linjiang was a copy.
It'd be great if he had it.
We have to get this over with
before the wedding date.
So are you going
to the family dinner tomorrow?
Sipu.
You'll get the Min family's power
when you marry me,
and I'll have something to fall back on.
It's the best thing
for both of us.
Ji Chan.
This is the first family dinner
after our engagement.
I want you to always remember
that you're my fiancée.
I know
you didn't want to talk about this,
but you promised to marry me
in front of Ji Chan,
so there's no reason
for you to back out.
Is this what you want to see?
I can't lose her again.
What about me?
This is our destiny.
I'm tired.
Take care of her.
Let's all go back to our places.
I can overlook your affair
with Song Sipu last night,
but remember,
I'm the only one for you.
Got it?
Ji Linjiang.
Don't push it.
Let go.
Isn't this what you want him to see?
I heard you guys have a wedding date.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I'll congratulate you with my wife.
Grandpa.
Mr. Ji.
Jingya is here.
Good.
Sit down.
Make yourself at home.
Okay, Mr. Ji.
Let's eat.
Okay.
Ji Chan.
My grandpa is good at picking dates.
Let's get married on the same day
as my cousin.
No problem.
We can even have
a wedding banquet together.
It'll be more fun that way.
How about it, Ji Chan?
Excuse me.
I want to go to the bathroom.
Ms. Ji.
What happened that night
is not over with me.
Sipu has agreed to marry me,
but I still have to remind you
that as a normal woman,
you should have basic principles.
Stay away from our lives, please.
Ms. Min.
I don't want to be your enemy.
I know,
but we are already hostile.
You, as Ji Linjiang's fiancée,
seduced my fiancé
in your room.
Is that how your parents taught you
to seduce other men?
I get it.
Is that how you made them
take pity on you
with this aggrieved expression?
It's disgusting.
Ms. Min.
You don't have to say that.
I just want to ask you.
Are you really happy
to be married to Song Sipu?
Of course.
You don't know
how much my marriage
to Song Sipu
means to me.
My sister.
Your happiness
is more important than anything.
That's good.
It would be better
if you weren't in the way.
♪Our love is on its way back♪
♪Returning♪
♪Love is back♪
♪Let love run free♪
♪Destined to be♪
♪I come for you♪
♪Love is back♪
♪No more retreat♪
♪Let love run wild and free♪
♪Right now, right here♪