♫  Open to page 64 ♫
♫  We'll study what came before  ♫
♫  Books are binding but there is so much more  ♫
♫  This little school's just a race   ♫
♫  But I can tell by your grace   ♫
♫  History will one day know your face  ♫
♫  Cause you got the wit  ♫
♫  And you got the drive  ♫
♫  You hold the whole world between your eyes  ♫
♫  Oh it's so easy to see  ♫
♫  Just don't forget about me  ♫
The Midnight Romance in Hagwon
Put them here.
Choeseon's Analysis of Grammar
Analysis of Expository Writing
Analysis of Literature
You don't have the copies or anything like that, right?
Even if you did, there's nothing we can do.
It's not like we haven't been betrayed before.
Well...
No, it's okay. You can leave.
Shouldn't you give me a receipt for returning the textbooks?
What?
What if you say you didn't receive them later?
D-Don't you trust adults?
Lee Si Wu returned textbooks
Here. Happy? Go now.
Why aren't you leaving?
Sign this, too.
Park Gi Seong
Lee Si Wu,
write that you won't release our textbooks.
Episode 8
Here.
What's this?
I thought you should get a new tablet.
Why would you...
I bought one while I was getting a new phone.
It looked pretty, and it reminded me of you.
Director.
Come on. Take it.
I got a job offer from another academy.
Really?
When?
Recently, unfortunately.
But take this, still.
There's such a thing as a goodbye gift.
I want something bigger when it comes to that.
- If so—
- I'm not leaving.
Really?
- Should I?
- No, it's not that.
Give this to Nam Jeong Mi instead.
- Ms. Nam?
- She's working harder than anyone.
Encourage the new teachers, too.
I knew I was right about you.
Team Leader Seo, you're a superior person.
You're caring and courageous.
It's not that. I really want to grow the Huiwon High class.
- I have a class soon.
- Yes, you should get going.
It's your busy day. I'm sorry.
Wait.
By chance,
can you tell me where you got the job offer?
What do you think?
- By chance-
- By chance?
Choeseon Korean?
Gray Witch, that cunning old woman.
Send an announcement to the mothers of Chanyeong High.
There's no special lecture for the finals this time.
Can't another teacher still have a lecture instead of you?
Mr. Park.
are you telling me to eat the crumbs right now?
I'm sorry.
Bring the Chanyeong High material I looked through last time.
Okay, I will.
You can leave.
Okay. Well, by the way...
Here.
What is it?
Have a look.
What's this?
I got it from Lee Si Wu when he came to return the textbooks.
I wonder if he's resentful because he's poor,
or maybe he's overcompensating for his insecurity.
He wasn't regretting his action at all—
Did he write this of his own volition?
No, I told him to write it.
Get out.
Hey.
Honor, reputation,
prestige, pride, or money.
Which of those did you get out of this?
How dare you get this piece of crap in the name of Choeseon Korean?
From a kid?
I'm sorry.
Get out.
Get out of my face forever!
I-I'm sorry.
Teacher.
Hey, how's everything?
Did you see the class material I sent?
Yes, it's true. Ms. Seo seemed concerned.
It's not like I'm a kid.
See you next week.
Study hard wherever you go.
I'll always support you.
Choi Hyeong Seon of Choeseon Korean.
Is Team Leader Seo worried about something?
It's about a Huiwon High student who's coming from Choeseon Korean.
She saw him returning the textbooks.
I should nag a bit.
At me, do you mean?
No, Team Leader Seo.
I know she made up her mind, but going there openly
would cause people to talk.
Why?
I thought you knew her plan.
She changed her mind.
She told me she was going.
You should hear directly from her. I don't want to speak for her.
Oh, okay.
Oh, thanks for the information.
Go home, you goofballs.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
I'll wait for you until you're done with the morning class.
I hope you come.
Did you promise a ratio adjustment or other incentives?
No.
She apparently wants to focus on the Huiwon High class.
How could that be the reason?
I looked through her contract one more time.
I made it difficult for her to take the students with her,
but maybe you should warn her—
- Assistant Director.
- Yes.
We shouldn't be berating someone who's on our side right now.
Berate?
How could you say that?
Gosh, what a world.
The academy industry is like a jungle.
That's what I'm saying.
Especially at times like this, we should provide the teachers
with unwavering trust and support. Don't you think?
We have ten minutes left. Should we look at another short text?
Or not?
But I highly recommend the text at the end.
I knew it.
You did, right? It's Erich Fromm's "The Art of Loving."
"Love is the active concern for the life and the growth of that which we love."
You can find that great sentence in there.
It's proof of my deep love for you, right?
Have you eaten?
I'm full without eating right now.
I brought a boxed lunch. Let's share it.
It's for two people.
I don't think you brought the other half for me.
You're right.
I won't return the favor for eating that, okay?
You sure are shrewd.
The house will feel so empty once Jun Ho moves out.
There's no point in working so hard to raise a son.
A captain named James Cook.
Looks like he's planning to come home early before he moves out, at least.
He must have some conscience.
- I'm home.
- You're home early.
- I'm back.
- What's that?
I wanted to start packing.
Already?
I don't want to wait until the class starts and rush.
Hey, but still...
I had dinner, Mom. I'll let you rest.
Good night.
Give me the lunch box.
What's that?
I found a good side dish store.
Look.
I brought this from home since it's the best drinking snack.
But I didn't know you wouldn't be drinking.
Sorry. My throat gets dry if I drink when I have a morning class.
You're so unbelievable.
By the way, why did you want to see me on the weekend?
For some reason, I didn't want to go back to the empty house tonight.
Do you feel lonely, too?
Do you think I'm not a human?
Should we start working on the blind date project again?
Should I? I'll get you the ones with the best qualifications.
I'm too old.
I don't deserve to be in a relationship.
Hey, even people in nursing homes date,
have love interests, and love triangles. Don't you know?
Even when I go to a nursing home, I won't be a center of romance.
I think I'll just watch others' romance.
Why would you say something so scary?
I don't know. I feel like that stuff has nothing to do with me.
Why?
Why? Why? Why? Why?
I think...
my cogwheels are misaligned.
What cogwheels?
People around the same age tend to
have similar tasks they're facing, you know.
Entering college is the priority until high school.
Studying or dating is important in college.
You worry about getting a job when you're about to graduate,
- and when that's set, you start considering marriage.
-  Yes.
And if you get married and have a kid, you worry about the college entrance again.
That's right. But when my college classmates were studying and dating,
I worked my butt off to make money. I hadn't even graduated when you took the bar exam.
Seriously.
The debt collectors were after us every day, but my brother hadn't finished his studies.
When I was free from debt,
I started prioritizing my students' college entrance. So
my clock was a bit out of sync with others, right?
So, you think you'll continue to be out of sync until you go to the nursing home?
I've been working hard
on each task in my life,
but I never got to have a proper relationship. It's unfair.
I'm just saying it's unfair.
You sound really cowardly right now.
I passed the first round of the bar exam when I was hot and heavy with my husband.
Don't you remember?
Right.
I remember.
It was a hot summer.
Not only was there no AC but there was no soundproofing in that tiny student apartment.
- So crazy.
- It was so sticky and hot.
For some reason, I didn't want to wear even the thinnest clothes.
Seriously.
- It didn't matter who initiated—
- Stop, stop, stop.
- I was like—
- Stop! Why do I have to listen to this?
Drink. Drink.
You had to mature faster than others,
but I don't think that's why you didn't get to date.
What is it, then?
You're either a fool who has too many expectations for love,
or a fool who looked down on love too much.
Which one do you think I am?
You looked down on it.
I'm really impressed you paid off that much debt at a young age,
but you became pretty successful, too. Money, car, and home.
Money, car, and home.
You got everything people value, one by one.
It's easy to even fool yourself
by saying, "I don't need love."
I pretended to be cool a lot.
Yes.
After being like that, it gets a bit embarrassing to say,
"I want to be in love, too."
That's why you have no choice but to lie to yourself again.
But...
what if I keep lying to myself,
but I don't buy the lie anymore?
What do I do then?
Does this have to do
with what you mentioned before?
You said you can't go back to the past anymore.
Just one can would be okay, right?
Tasty.
It really could've been dangerous today. You know I've been acting like his mentor.
But I almost had lunch with him after I finished the class early today.
It was so hard to hold back.
So what if you have a lunch with him?
Hey, I was once his teacher. I can't get seduced by him.
At least I need to step on the brake.
He has a lot going for him.
He's fun,
sweet,
and responsible.
My job is to help him reach his goal.
I don't want him to get involved in a silly rumor.
Aren't I so cool?
Okay, okay, okay.
I understand why you want to think that.
But...
But you said you can't fool yourself anymore.
How do you really feel? Huh?
You've seen him, right?
I've seen him.
How could you...
not like Jun Ho?
Tell me if there's a way to resist.
Wow, I had this.
Why are you crying?
I don't know.
Gosh, I'm drunk.
I suddenly got scared.
Why? About what?
Well...
He says I'm his first love.
If he knew how lame I was
he'd stop fantasizing about me completely.
Hey, why do you want to be fantasized about?
Just give in to your desire.
It's not so easy.
How frustrating. Geez.
I already know this is Jun Ho.
- Can you bet a million won?
- Yes.
How do you know?
"Did you get off work?
Did you get home safely? When will you go to bed?"
He's the only one who asks me stuff like that.
Thanks to him, I learned what it's like to be lonely.
Why would you be lonely?
I'm jealous you get texts from a young man at night.
Right. It feels so empty if I don't hear from him at night.
He's probably asking if I got home safely.
I didn't get to see him tonight.
Why? What is it?
I won't demand a million won. Who is it?
It's Jun Ho.
So?
What?
These are the notes you gave me.
Seo Hye Jin, the tenacious woman.
You worked so hard to make me study.
The day I studied hard.
The day I skipped the class and went to the internet cafe.
The day I did well on the exam. The day I did poorly.
The hot day. The cold day.
The day we found a fun book at the library.
The day we rented a comic book together.
The day we solved a math exam together.
The day we started to countdown until the exam day. The day before the exam.
The day I took the entrance exam.
The day I got the acceptance letter and...
even when nothing was going on,
you must've had a lot to say to me.
Why are you crying? Huh?
Wow, you were a good teacher.
I wasn't a good teacher.
No, he's saying
he endured a difficult time in his life thanks to you.
This is basically...
I didn't do that for other students.
What?
I only did that for Jun Ho.
After I took a break from school,
I didn't want to live.
When you guys went on a school trip, studied,
and went on dates, I...
handed out... flyers in the morning, cleaned during the day and taught at night.
I...
I thought I'd go crazy because life was so hard.
But I stopped thinking that at some point.
It wasn't that my life improved.
I just felt really good on some days.
Not because I made money.
It's that... when things felt hopeless,
I hung in there because of him, I think.
♫  You walked in my door  ♫
I'm not waking you up because it looks like you had a very long day
♫  ... a star above the clouds  ♫
♫  I knew it then  ♫
♫  I know it now  ♫
I'm so glad you started to enjoy reading
Congratulations, you've been accepted
♫  Years ago I let you pass me by, but now's our time  ♫
I got in!
♫  You walked in my door, and the love I had for you before  ♫
♫  Came shining through just like a star above the clouds  ♫
♫  I knew it then  ♫
♫  I know it now  ♫
Thank you for working hard for the last three years
Seo Hye Jin
Hey, answer it. It's Lee Jun Ho.
- Answer it.
- How could I answer it?
- Hello? Mr. Lee.
- Hold on.
- Yes, this is Cha So Yeong. Yes.
- Give it.
Yes, we've met before, right?
I...
Did he hang up?
You must be crazy.
- Hey, come here for a second.
- Oh, no...
- I'll send him a text.
- Don't do it.
- Wait.
We're too drunk right now.
Wait. Wait.
I need to go home now. I'll go home.
What's going on here?
Give me that. I can get a ride home.
No, I'll make my old man pick me up.
My phone. Where's my phone?
- Give me that.
- I'll make my old man pick me up.
We'll be all lovey-dovey on the way back.
How could I just put you in a cab?
You're out of your mind.
Hello? Hey.
I think you need to come over here.
Who are you talking to right now?
- You're talking to Jun Ho, aren't you?
- No.
- It's Jun Ho, isn't it?
- I told you I wasn't!
Give it!
Here, there, somewhere! Where's my cell?
Dear, there's a fabulous couple right here.
- A fabulous couple is about to be born—
- Stop it!
It's a crucial moment.
Come on. You should've drunk alone. Why ...
Okay. There's one table left.
Okay, okay.
Yes, okay, okay.
Okay, okay. Okay, I will.
Sir.
Sir?
I'm sorry, but we're closing.
I'm sorry.
Huh? Mr. Lee, hello.
Oh, hello.
- Nice to see you here.
- Yes, yes. Hello.
- You're here to see Seo Hye Jin, right?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Hey, be careful.
Watch your head.
- Get home safely.
- I will.
I'll buy you a drink next time.
Sounds good. I'll look forward to it.
- Okay.
- By the way,
I'm not sure if I should tell you this, but...
Gosh, you really are a pro.
Aigoo, you did a great thing.
She has a class tomorrow morning.
You'd be shocked if you knew what I did just now.
Aigoo, don't be so proud.
They would've worked out even if it weren't for you.
What? Did you know they were like that?
Seriously.
How?
I knew it the day she first brought him.
Wow, Seo Hye Jin really is a fool.
It's so obvious to everyone. How come she's the only one in the dark?
It happens when it comes to you.
I didn't know there was probation in love, too.
That sounds like a pop song.
♫  I didn't know there was probation in love  ♫
I hope they have the greatest love affair.
Go all in.
Be careful.
- The door is closing.
- Gosh.
You can't go in if you keep messing it up.
That won't be good.
Press it for me. 03...
What if someone hears it?
Then... lend me your ear.
Pardon?
Your ear.
Can I leave when you fall asleep?
Do you want to?
Come on in.
You saw through my lies, didn't you?
I told you not to bring up first love.
And I said I wanted to go back to the past.
What else was there?
You said there's no such thing as a highlight in life.
And you said you got sick of teaching me.
You should've forgotten about it.
I forgot it now.
Jun Ho.
My head hurts.
Good job, Lee Jun Ho.
I wasn't an animal. I was a gentleman.
Yes, good job.
Good job.
My head.
Gosh. Well done, Seo Hye Jin.
I have classes all day.
You scared me.
I didn't want to go through your stuff.
So I picked up soup and medicine.
You didn't forget what happened, right?
Let me wash my face.
Teacher?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
- Last night, I—
- I have a few announcements for you.
Tell me.
First of all, what can you eat?
Even the water makes me sick.
If so, I'll take over your morning and first afternoon class.
What nonsense are you talking about? I've never—
You'll feel better quickly if you get IV treatment and get some sleep.
I'll explain things at work.
No, they're my classes. I'll do it.
I'll tell Team Leader Choi we were together last night.
But I heard if she knows, the entire world knows.
I found a hospital that opens on Sundays. Okay?
What's the next announcement?
We need to go somewhere after work today.
Where?
We need to go on a date. A historical one.
D-Date? Date?
First of all,
I'll tell you where my class material is.
My notebook should be on my desk at the academy.
Hold on.
There's another announcement left. It's the most important one.
What is it?
I completely...
run out of patience now.
What?
Don't avoid it.
♫  Days go by  ♫
♫  Life is short  ♫
♫  Something I know now even more  ♫
♫  But I'm still here  ♫
♫  Like I've always been  ♫
♫  Waiting for the time when I can hold you again  ♫
♫  Wherever you are, you know I want to be  ♫
♫  Together with you  ♫
♫  Where I want to be, right by your side  ♫
♫  For all of my life  ♫
Hello.
Hello. Hello.
Let's see.
Ms. Nam,
if someone's filling in for your class,
do you submit a report or just tell the assistant director?
Ms. Seo is sick, so I will be teaching her early classes.
Are you that happy that she's sick?
Do I look happy?
I'll fill in for her.
No, I'll do it.
Talk to me for a second.
Team Leader can't report herself right now?
No. She's probably getting IV treatment and sleeping now.
- I'll report on her behalf.
- No, I'll do it.
How did you know she was sick?
Telling people I found out first would be better for world peace.
I knew you were the best.
I'll fill in her classes, too.
You really don't have to. I'll do it.
Okay, let's do that, then.
Okay.
Please don't take food into the classrooms
Gosh.
Shouldn't you just be keeping her company?
How do I return this favor?
No, you don't have to.
I've been paid in advance.
The tablet. Team Leader would know.
Paid in advance?
What are you doing, Chae Yoon?
- Hello.
Why are you two coming out of there?
Well...
Team Leader isn't feeling well. We discussed what we should do with her classes.
Is she sick?
Sounds like she has a bad flu.
Oh, okay. Got it.
No Entry
Team Leader...
Managing health is a skill, too.
Would you be able to fill in all day?
Of course.
Tell her to take the whole day off.
Tell her to recover completely before the special lectures.
Okay, I will.
By the way,
looks like you're close to Team Leader Seo.
I'm not close to anyone in particular.
Don't half-ass it just because you're filling in.
Only amateurs do that.
Pros know how to take advantage of opportunities.
The competition will be fierce during the break, you know?
I understand.
Tell Team Leader Lee to see me.
Okay.
Team Leader Yun Ji Seok
You must be in a good mood.
Yes. I'm just filling in,
but teaching again makes me feel so excited.
Teaching must be your calling.
I get along with students.
This neighborhood is different than the one you were in.
Yes.  I'm not trying to say anything else.
But I've worked at this academy longer.
I think you should've discussed what happened today with me first
instead of talking to Mr. Lee privately.
Both you and Su Rim have classes all day today.
Either Mr. Lee or I had to fill in, anyway.
So we just wanted to figure it out on our own.
Of course, I know that.
You aren't offended, right?
I'm saying I'm willing to help if I can.
Although I'm younger than you.
When did he leave? He even skipped breakfast.
Gosh.
He thinks he grew up on his own.
Both his parents and teachers worked so hard to raise him.
You can take it out in 30 minutes.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Sure.
Team Leader, it's me.
Why did you call so many times?
How sick are you, exactly?
How could I not worry
when someone who's never been late once has fallen ill?
You're okay, right?
I guess I'm getting old.
I suddenly lost all my energy.
Yes, I'm really okay.
Shouldn't you be in class now?
I'm sorry.
Go back inside.
Yes, see you on Tuesday.
Bye.
How are you feeling?
Why are you here already?
Did the classes get canceled? They can't be—
No, no.
Don't worry.
Someone almost as trustworthy as me is filling in.
A Special Vacation Lecture
Let's reach the SKY together!
I suddenly have too much time.
I don't know what to do.
Don't you know?
Did you forget my announcement?
The door is closing.
♫  Open to page 64  ♫
This is where the academy used to be. Why are we here?
You'll see once you go inside.
♫  These little school's just to race  ♫
♫  But I can tell by your grace  ♫
♫  History will one day know your face  ♫
♫  Cause you got the wit  ♫
♫  And you got the drive.  ♫
They're demolishing everything tomorrow to start a new academy.
That's why I wanted to come here with you today.
It might not be cool, but isn't this the best first date spot?
You couldn't say that if you knew why the old academy was shut down.
Some teachers started dating, and things got disastrous.
The academy had to shut its doors
and the teachers can no longer teach in Daechi-dong.
It's just a rumor I heard.
It wouldn't have lasted if it shut down due to some love affair.
♫  I'd be a man you could hang your hat on  ♫
♫  Cause you got the world in the palm of your fist  ♫
♫  You could move mountain tops  ♫
It's not working.
It's okay.
♫  Oh the greatness I foresee  ♫
I realized too late that Seo Hye Jin,
who worked here, was just a college student.
You acted like an adult because you were my teacher.
And I was intimidated by that title for no reason. I realized that too late.
It's so unfair.
Whoa, I'm glad it's dark in here.
I don't know what face to make whenever you say stuff like that.
I don't want you to see me making a dumb face.
♫  My heart's an open book, I profess  ♫
You can tell me now.
I...
spent so much time with students,
so I know the latest slang.
But I don't know what women my age talk about,
what they watch, listen to, or think about.
So whenever you stay stuff like that,
I think about what expression I'm supposed to make.
You don't have to think in moments like this.
You're right.
I've been pretending to be an adult for a long time.
But I can only put on that show in a classroom like this.
I guess I'm kind of... how should I put it...
slow and awkward with everything.
What I'm trying to say is...
that I'll still be goofing around a bit.
I hope you can understand.
I will.
♫  So, open to page 64  ♫
♫  We'll read about what's in store  ♫
♫  Books are binding but there's so much more  ♫
♫  These little school is mundane  ♫
♫  But I can proudly proclaim  ♫
♫  History will one day know your name  ♫
This has to stay a secret.
- Why?
- Remember when we gave the free lecture?
A lot of people are waiting for us to slip up.
I can't create the schedule if people find out about us.
If they're not happy about something,
they'd say, "Seo Hye Jin went crazy since she seduced her young student."
Tell them the young student seduced you first.
Your recklessness would become my fault, too.
They'd say you act out because I have your back.
The problem is, all of that would become our reputation.
Wouldn't that be bad?
Don't get out. Just take the car with you.
You want me to just leave?
Well, we just had our historical first date.
Shouldn't you offer me tea or ramyun at your place?
Hey.
- No, I can't do that.
- Hold on. Stop.
I need to study.
Get home safely.
Teach.
Yes?
This isn't good enough.
Geez, I said we should make another trip.
Can I come in with my shoes on?
No, I just cleaned the floor. Hurry up.
Stop pushing.
Geez...
Gosh, I'm tired.
So cold.
Where's the water?
In the fridge.
Gosh, I'm tired.
Hey, you moved a lot of stuff already.
I've been moving it little by little.
Don't you use your father's car these days?
No, I use Ms. Seo's car.
Who?
Seo Hye Jin. She lives nearby.
What?
What? Why are you looking at me like that?
I thought everyone already knew.
You liked her forever ago.
I don't care how long ago it was.
Your hunch is correct.
You two are dating?
Hey. I can't listen to this sober.
Do you have a beer?
I have a ton in the fridge.
Feel free to finish it.
- How about you?
- I need to take a shower and go to work.
It's the special lecture period.
You bastard.
I haven't had a day off for months.
Seriously.
Where's the light switch?
- Hey!
- You scared me. What?
What am I supposed to call her when I see her?
Teacher? Sister-in-law?
Or Hye Jin?
It's sister-in-law, you bastard.
"Hye Jin," my foot.
Bastard.
Hello, Ms. Seo.
Wow, already?
Can you tell that the semester is ending?
You're right. It feels like the entrance exam ended yesterday.
Go to the director's office. He wants to see you.
I'll be done quickly. Let's decorate this together.
It's my favorite thing to do.
I'd love to.
Hello. Hi.
Hello.
Wow, I'm getting a year older already.
Do you want to decorate it together, Mr. Jang?
I'm a Buddhist.
I see.
I'll join you.
Gosh, thank you.
Yes.
- I heard you wanted to see me.
- Hey.
Because of the emergency supplementary class,
I don't get to see the teachers and team leaders.
I just wanted to catch up with you.
Have a seat.
Do I look that weird? Why can't you look at me?
It's not like that.
Okay, then. Look at me.
Look at me.
It's okay.
My mother heard something somewhere.
She said it'd make the academy grow bigger
and I'd stop being a bachelor, too.
I hope it works.
I heard he's good. Do you want their number?
No, I'm okay.
Aren't you curious if you'll make someone the top of the class again?
Looks like you're more curious about that.
Aren't you curious about it?
I was curious whenever there were exams,
but not this time.
Why not?
Everyone will do well.
I did everything I could.
Chanyeong and Huiwon High happened to have Korean exams on the same day.
You'll get the results all at once.
You're right.
What did you think? Did you enjoy the class?
- Yes.
- Good.
I'll nag you for the hundredth time and let you go.
The short-answer questions and essay questions
aren't simply important because they're worth a lot of points.
The ability to summarize your thoughts and knowledge within a limited time
will be an asset for your lifetime.
I'm not telling you to become amazing writers like the poets Baek Seok, Kim Chun Su,
or the novelist Kim Ae Ran you learned about today.
I think you are acquiring the basic knowledge you need to complete high school.
Review those materials until the end, okay?
Okay.
Well done, everyone.
If you've kept up with my class, you can be confident about tomorrow's exam.
I'm confident.
This is your moment now.
Go home.
Thank you.
Good job. Good job. Good job.
Bye. Take care.
Well done.
- Well done.
- Good luck. Good luck. Fighting.
Well done.
Well done, Lee Si Wu.
Ms. Seo, is there a class next week, by chance?
Why do you ask?
Can you give a literature lecture?
Just like the old free lecture.
Hey, everyone would hate us if we had a class right after the exam.
I think it'd be fun.
I'll have to if you think it'd be fun.
Okay.
Thank you.
- You've worked hard.
- See you.
- Fighting.
- Bye.
Well done, Mr. Lee.
You've worked hard, Ms. Seo.
It's finally over.
Well done.
We need to run away before anyone suggests celebrating.
Wait for me at the subway station.
People might see us in the parking lot.
♫  Days go by  ♫
♫  Life is short  ♫
♫  It's something I know now, even more  ♫
♫  But I'm still here  ♫
♫  like I've always been  ♫
♫  Waiting for the time when I can hold you again  ♫
♫  Wherever you are I know I want to be  ♫
♫  Together with you  ♫
I wanted to catch a late-night screening.
The exam is tomorrow.
We might hear from them.
Let's catch the movie next time.
All right.
♫  My heart is yours  ♫
Seriously.
♫  I feel it pound  ♫
♫  I still see your sparks whenever you're around  ♫
♫  Each passing day,  ♫
♫  that you're not here  ♫
Oh, I ran out of milk. I forgot.
♫  You are near  ♫
♫  But wherever you are  ♫
♫  and no matter how far  ♫
♫  I always want to be  ♫
♫  Together with you  ♫
Do you want a bag?
The bag is 100 won.
♫  Together with you  ♫
♫  For all of my life  ♫
Do you need a receipt?
Ma'am?
- Yes.
- The payment went through.
Go home.
I'll walk you home.
It's just around the corner.
♫  Or is it just another dream where you told me  ♫
♫  I love you,  ♫
♫  What I would not do  ♫
♫  If could make it come true  ♫
♫  Together with you  ♫
♫  Where I want to be, right by your side  ♫
♫  Where I'll always be, right by your side  ♫
♫  Together with you  ♫
Change the entrance passcode.
I feel like...
I shouldn't know it.
Oh, I changed it.
I see.
Go inside now.
Lend me your ear.
Huh? What?
That was a lie.
Change it as soon as you get home.
I actually had milk at home.
Didn't I seem really smooth?
Let's go up.
Let's go up, I said.
♫  Steady as she goes  ♫
♫  It seems like everybody knows  ♫
The Midnight Romance in Hagwon
See you at the academy.
Why are you coming from here?
Come out later. Take the elevator when you come up.
I'm asking what the academy wants from me.
I didn't even think about opening the contract.
You get assessed by the grades, not words.
Yesterday, this bastard...
Give me the passcode for the apartment in return.
- Hello, Ms. Seo.
- Oh, hey.
I thought I'd lose my title as your favorite student.
Does it not matter? Because I'm your boyfriend, not your student anymore?