(The scars on that corpse)
(are far different from You Chen'an's.)
(The one who died
was indeed not You Chen'an.)
(The three-day deadline has arrived.)
(His Highness and Jing Yi)
(have been sentenced
to immediate execution.)
(Nanzhao assassins raided
the Commandery Prince's Mansion,)
(intent on silencing me for good.)
(Wu Jiang died protecting me.)
(The mansion ran with blood.)
(How many more lives
must be sacrificed before)
(Nanzhao's ruthless ambition ends?)
♪Embark on a farewell
without saying goodbye♪
♪Build a bridge between life and death♪
♪Hear a voiceless declaration♪
♪Break disguises, cross illusions♪
♪A fleeting life and delusions♪
♪The surface always conceals♪
♪Separate cause and effect♪
♪A twisted path, rising and falling♪
♪Seek the path amid the hazy unknown♪
♪Writing oblivion with a sharp blade♪
♪No matter how far, I gaze at the light♪
♪Fearing no wild lands, I press on♪
♪To see the tides of the world
once more♪
♪The deeper truth is buried, it grows♪
♪Until it is set free♪
=The Imperial Coroner S2=
(Adapted from Idle Girl's The Constable's Wife)
(This story is entirely fictional.)
=Episode 19=
Summon
the Commandery Princess Consort An.
Wu Jiang!
Chu Chu.
Leave this to me. Go.
Why are you...
Your Majesty.
This case is in doubt.
The dead is not You Chen'an.
Commandery Princess Consort An.
What do you mean?
Your Majesty.
In the meditation chamber
at Weiguo Temple,
there is a secret passageway
to a small shrine outside the city.
Inside are two sets
of very similar footprints.
One belongs to You Chen'an.
The other
belongs to the true victim.
Before the incident,
the victim had lived
in the passageway for days.
From the living traces,
it coincides with the time
when Nanzhao's chief envoy
proposed entering Weiguo Temple.
The mechanisms were set by You Chen'an,
but the one meant to die
was the stand-in hidden here.
He lured the man out,
then knocked him out with incense.
He calculated the angles,
set the crossbow,
and ran the trigger beneath
the victim's wrist.
He then slipped away,
escaping through the passageway.
So,
You Chen'an is still alive?
Yes.
But he has fled for days.
In that time,
has he been silenced by someone
who knew the truth?
Absurd!
To evade your guilt,
you would invent such a laughable claim.
If this spreads,
are you not afraid of being mocked
by neighboring states?
Nanzhao will never accept such mockery.
Jiang Daohai.
Here, Your Majesty.
Has the Capital Prefecture verified what
the Commandery Princess Consort An said?
Reporting to Your Majesty.
Deputy Prefect of the Capital,
Leng Baichuan did take part
in the investigation this morning,
and found some traces,
but no conclusive evidence.
Commandery Princess Consort An.
Lady Jing is desperate
to save her husband,
yet without proof,
you fabricate
such a shocking tale out of thin air.
It is impossible for me to believe it.
Who says there is no evidence?
When I went to the inn today
to pay my respects,
by chance,
I saw old scars on the corpse.
At the scars,
there was clear stagnation
of qi and blood,
leaving marks from blocked meridians.
The marks spread outward,
like blood obstruction.
This is a sign
of severe scarring disorder.
This condition is congenital.
Even minor skin injury,
or an insect bite,
can easily cause
such distinct scars.
What is strange about
Second Prince having this condition?
Or the Commandery Princess Consort An
has seen the real
Second Prince's body yourself?
I have.
When You Chen'an studied forensic skills
at the Three Judicial Offices,
he often bared
his upper body for practice.
That was nothing unusual.
Moreover,
the scars on the corpse
were still faintly red,
indicating recent injury.
You...
Besides this,
I have another piece of evidence,
to prove the dead man's
identity at once.
I ask Your Majesty to allow
the presentation of physical evidence.
Granted.
Commandery Princess Consort An.
This is...
When I went to pay my respects,
I brought a bouquet of flowers.
By chance,
the dead man's hand
was stained with balsam juice,
and inadvertently,
it transferred onto my sleeve,
leaving this fingerprint.
Coincidentally, when You Chen'an
was at the Three Judicial Offices,
he also left fingerprints.
(You Chen'an)
These are for your future use
as protective clothing in the mortuary.
Thank you.
Here.
Another handprint is needed here.
Another handprint?
Those are the rules
of the Three Judicial Offices.
All items issued within proper limits
for official duties
how many, what items,
and their purpose must be recorded.
Commandery Prince An
was indeed thorough.
(You Chen'an)
A person's fingerprints never change.
Second Prince of Nanzhao
has rare reverse whorl patterns.
A comparison alone will prove it.
The dead man at the inn
was not the Second Prince of Nanzhao.
Of course,
Vice Envoy Gao
would not accept my evidence.
So,
I asked Lady Jing to go to your inn,
to await Your Majesty's order,
to collect the corpse's fingerprints.
If Commandery Princess Consort An
had such insight,
why not present it earlier?
Now it is too late.
Your Majesty,
by the rites of the Nanzhao court,
the rites for Second Prince
were completed this morning.
By this hour,
the cremation
should already be done.
You burned the body?
We did so for harmony
between our states.
I wish more than anyone
that the chief envoy were still alive.
If Great Tang can produce proof,
Nanzhao will not oppose Great Tang.
Vice Envoy Gao makes it sound easy.
The body has been destroyed.
Unless I bring You Chen'an
before you alive,
what other proof could there be?
So please, Commandery Princess Consort An,
spare no effort and find him,
no matter where he is.
According to
the Commandery Princess Consort An,
if the one who left
truly was Second Prince,
then by now he should
have gone south out of the city.
Why not send a group
to search the south?
But Your Majesty
and I agreed on a deadline,
and the time is now up.
I fear...
(Eighth Quarter of Hour of Si
on the third day)
No need for shackles.
You two.
Please step out and board the carriage.
Thank you for the kindness.
Proceed by the law...
You're innocent.
Nanzhao has gone too far.
Though I cannot save your lives,
I will not let you
suffer humiliation.
Shackles and the execution blade
are not a disgrace,
but proof that records
our honor for posterity.
Please.
Vice envoy of Nanzhao, how do you prove
that the body you burned
was Second Prince?
Second Prince died
in the temple before all eyes.
What proof is still needed?
Originally,
there was no dispute.
But now,
the identity of the dead is in doubt.
Great Tang law is founded on
law for all under heaven,
thus creating an age of clear justice.
Imperial power may not
overstep the courts.
According to the Great Tang laws,
under the provisions of On Adjudicating Cases,
this matter constitutes
a case of doubtful guilt.
Senior Jing is right.
The laws of Great Tang
stand above the Emperor's word.
At present, even I
cannot sentence
the Commandery Prince An to death.
Senior Jing.
As for this doubtful crime,
how should it be ruled?
At most, a doubtful crime is redeemed
with 120 jin of copper.
For the Jing family,
though it would ruin us,
I
will still do his utmost to pay
the copper for my son and His Highness.
You are abusing power to oppress us.
Our Second Prince of Nanzhao
died unjustly in Great Tang.
And now you mean
to settle this with a fine.
Senior Jing.
You...
You are insulting Nanzhao.
It seems conflict between our states
is unavoidable.
I will report this to our King at once.
Vice Envoy Gao.
The matter is not yet clear.
There is no final ruling.
Why rush to report it?
With all this evasion,
who knows when it will be resolved.
Commandery Princess Consort An.
Do you have a definite deadline
for the investigation?
Send the death squads.
Leave no survivors.
Chu Chu.
Leave this to me. Go.
Quickly send the Commandery
Princess Consort An back to the manor.
- Yes.
Your Majesty.
In Commandery Princess Consort An
current condition,
she likely cannot investigate further.
Does Your Majesty intend
to keep me and Second Prince
waiting any longer?
Great Tang
has no shortage of capable men.
The true culprit
will not escape justice.
Take the suspects back
to the Court of Judicial Review.
Your Majesty.
Jinbao.
Escort Vice Envoy Gao back to the inn.
See to him properly.
Yes.
Guards.
Vice Envoy Gao.
This way.
An imperial oral decree.
His Majesty withdraws the order.
Judgment postponed.
I obey the decree.
Remove the shackles at once.
Your Highness, I told you
we are hard to kill.
We always find a way out.
Did Commandery Princess Consort An
have an audience with His Majesty?
Yes, Your Highness.
Commandery Princess Consort An
found proof
that Second Prince
of Nanzhao faked his death.
Where is the Princess Consort?
Why did she not come with you?
The Princess...
The Commandery Princess Consort An...
She...
Chu Chu.
Leng Yue.
Hold on a little longer.
Physician Qi will be here soon.
Does it hurt?
It is just a minor wound.
It is nothing.
This is my fault.
Do not say that.
Women protecting women
is only right.
Before,
you said the same.
But I failed to protect you.
Do not be sad.
You saved me.
You are a heroine.
Chu Chu.
Physician Qi.
The imperial physicians
have examined her in turns.
They only found signs of poisoning.
Nothing else is clear.
Chu Chu has taken a ginseng pill
to sustain her breath.
Any external injuries?
When I changed her clothes,
I found none.
Near the heart meridian,
the silver needle turned black.
It is a deadly poison.
Deadly poison?
The Imperial Medical Bureau,
the Three Judicial Offices, the mansion,
all have antidote pills.
Physician Qi, tell me what is needed.
I will fetch it at once.
Lady Jing, do not panic.
We must first find
the source of the poison.
In this emergency,
I
can only use extraordinary means.
This is bad.
It is a wasp stinger.
Poison this potent,
I have never seen before.
It was certainly not taken
from an ordinary wasp.
For now,
I can only give Her Highness
medicine to ease the pain.
As for the rest,
I must study it further.
Thank you for your trouble.
For His Highness,
you truly risked your life.
♪Time drips away
like fading crimson scent♪
♪The hardships of arrival pass
in a fleeting blink♪
♪Palm lines carry
the footprints of memory♪
♪Leading us out of every winding turn♪
♪If two hearts can fly as one
then storms are part of the way♪
♪Looking back the sky
has already cleared♪
♪Your branches entwined with mine♪
♪Bound together in mutual reliance♪
♪Rugged roads become
the paths of sun and moon♪
I won.
My dear, you have deft hands.
I cannot compare.
Losing to skill calls for a punishment.
How many taels of gold
did you set aside?
If you help me solve it,
I will reward you well.
♪This love was never easy,
so life and death will not part us♪
♪Like sinking into the deep sea,
the first breath upon awakening♪
♪This bond will never waver♪
Three years ago,
I tied a red cord
beneath the Tree of Love
in Guanling County,
and my wish was granted, to marry you.
If there truly are gods in this world,
I hope Yue Lao will tie our red thread
a little tighter.
Together, morning and night,
for all our lives.
How can I stay calm?
I said Chu Chu is my bottom line.
His Majesty and Physician Qi are here.
Chu Chu will be fine.
Jing Yi.
I have decided.
I will go before
His Majesty and confess.
What nonsense are you saying?
Only if I confess as the real culprit
can you get out quickly
and stop Gao Luoqian's next move,
and save Chu Chu,
then break this deadlock.
You trust me this much,
you have even put Chu Chu's
life in my hands.
I will not say more.
We have known each other
since childhood.
I treat you as a true brother.
I know you feel the same.
I cannot get out right now.
Chu Chu's life
is in your hands.
Your Highness, do not...
I promise you.
Even if I must go to the underworld,
I will bring Chu Chu back alive.
Sir.
(Universal Post Station)
A secret order from His King.
His King is truly wise.
With this in hand,
let us see how
the Emperor of Great Tang can evade it.
Your Majesty.
I have reported to the King of Nanzhao
that Commandery Prince An
and Vice Minister Jing
were ruled as a doubtful case.
His Majesty was furious,
saying Great Tang trampled on the dignity
of the Nanzhao royal house,
and treated the life
of a Nanzhao prince as nothing,
seeking to brush it aside.
Nanzhao will therefore send troops
to Jiaozhou at once,
to console the soul of Second Prince,
and quell the anger
of the Nanzhao people.
Great Tang has its own laws.
Nanzhao has no place to interfere.
For the sake of amity,
I have shown restraint time and again.
Yet Nanzhao
continues to press further.
Do you truly think
Great Tang fears Nanzhao?
Your Majesty, please calm your anger.
If Your Majesty can punish
the true culprit severely,
I believe my own efforts
to persuade them
may still leave room
to turn things around.
After all, King of Nanzhao
values peace above all.
Enough.
Since you are set on taking up arms,
then we fight.
When Nanzhao is defeated,
do not say Great Tang relied on force.
Vice Envoy Gao.
Please.
Your Majesty.
Word has come
from the Court of Judicial Review.
The killer of the Nanzhao Second Prince
has confessed.
Confessed?
Who confessed?
That day at Weiguo Temple,
I had been intent on
protecting Second Prince.
You Chen'an remembered this kindness,
and invited me to Master Shenguan's
meditation chamber to speak at night.
When I arrived as agreed,
You Chen'an suddenly turned hostile,
and tried to attack me.
In the moment of panic...
- I happened to arrive.
- I...
I saw You Chen'an
about to harm His Highness.
To protect His Highness,
I struck and killed Second Prince.
Jing Yi...
This matter had nothing to do with
the Commandery Prince An.
He feared I would
surely die if arrested,
so he wished
to bear it together.
It was clearly me...
Your Highness,
at this point,
hiding it for me is useless.
Once you are released,
look into what followed.
There may still be
a chance to save my life.
It is well known that Vice Minister Jing
and Commandery Prince An are close as brothers.
Who is to say that today
he is not taking the blame for him?
There were three arrows that day.
One struck You Chen'an
squarely in the back.
That was the fatal blow.
Even so...
I have made myself clear.
Vice Envoy Gao, do you still doubt it?
Besides,
His Highness has no strength to kill.
How could he commit murder?
That still does not prove
the Commandery Prince An is innocent.
What if he was an accomplice?
Vice Envoy Gao,
you are the vice envoy of Nanzhao.
You must speak with evidence.
Where is it?
You cannot rely on clever words alone
and speak at will.
Very well.
Since the real culprit has confessed,
Your Majesty,
will you not issue the order?
Wait.
What is it?
Is the Commandery Prince An
trying to excuse the killer?
Jing Yi did kill someone,
but not the true Second Prince.
Only a stand-in.
Since the dead was not
from the Nanzhao delegation,
a Great Tang official killed
someone within Great Tang.
How it is handled
is not for Nanzhao to decide.
Enough.
Commandery Prince An,
you and your wife
truly have no new argument at all?
As far as I know,
Chu Chu found evidence,
and Vice Envoy Gao burned it.
You are the one delaying this case.
You...
Vice Envoy Gao,
why the hurry?
I am in custody. I cannot flee.
Commandery Prince An, Xiao Jinyu
is released without charge.
You are ordered
to find the Nanzhao chief envoy,
You Chen'an, at once.
No matter how far,
you must give
the Nanzhao delegation an answer.
Commandery Prince An,
rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
As for Jing Yi...
Your Majesty,
place the suspect under the supervision
of the Nanzhao delegation.
The Jing Family's influence
is widely known.
If Vice Minister Jing
were to disappear in custody,
I could not answer
to the King of Nanzhao.
Your Majesty,
I have already yielded.
I am willing to wait
for Commandery Prince An's result.
I ask Your Majesty
to approve my request,
to show fairness.
Your Majesty,
I'm willing.
Very well.
The Nanzhao delegation may not
enter Great Tang prisons.
Jing Yi shall be confined
at his residence.
Only then will I consent.
Order Vice Minister Huang
of the Ministry of Rites
and the Nanzhao delegation
to guard him together.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Commandery Prince An, I hope you
will uncover the truth quickly
and give Nanzhao an answer.
I will.
Vice Envoy Gao,
return and inform the King of Nanzhao.
If he insists on his own course
and sends troops to Jiaozhou,
Great Tang will not fear it.
Our armies
will advance without delay
and take all of Nanzhao.
Rest assured, Your Majesty.
I will do all I can
to persuade His Majesty,
and promote peace and amity
between the two lands.
(Zichen Hall)
Your Highness.
Please help me
deliver this letter to Yue.
♪Who can escape falling
into the river of time♪
♪With flesh and blood,
I see you across life and death♪
I am leaving.
♪Those unresolved grudges♪
♪Still rest in my heart because of you♪
♪One thought of longing
loosens clenched hands♪
♪Only to smooth the crease
of that page of the story♪
Commandery Prince An.
His Majesty orders you to go
to the Imperial Study at once.
(Zichen Hall)
Outrageous.
The title I bestowed upon you
is not something you may resign at will.
I acknowledge my guilt.
I ask Your Majesty to punish me.
You two brothers
staged a farce before me,
rushing to confess,
yet never reported it to me first.
You treat the Three Judicial Offices
and the court
as if they were your own backyard.
If my life
buys Great Tang a moment's respite,
it is worth it.
Jinbao.
Help him up.
Xiao Jinyu.
Punishing you would
be letting you off lightly.
You must clean up this mess for me.
Did you think you could play your part
and then leave it to me?
I understand.
I will do everything in my power
to quell caused by Nanzhao.
In prison,
you suffered quite a bit, did you not?
The prison of the Court of Judicial Review
is run by my old subordinates.
They did not mistreat me.
I know you well.
To come up with such a plan,
you must have been pushed to the brink.
You already know
about Chu Chu being poisoned?
The best medicine from the palace
has been sent to your mansion.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I will not fail Your Majesty,
even at the cost of my life.
Chu Chu.
You are back.
Or am I
dreaming?
I am back.
Was I good?
You were.
You saved me.
Your Highness.
I am so sleepy.
Then rest a while.
I will be here when you wake.
Chu Chu is still asleep?
She just fell asleep.
Leng Yue.
To get me released sooner,
Jing Yi confessed before His Majesty.
I am sorry.
Your Highness,
from the day we chose to follow you,
we were ready to give our lives.
What Jing Yi did
was not only for you,
but for Great Tang.
Nanzhao has been plotting for years,
infiltrating Great Tang from within.
Their ambition
is far greater than it seems.
From Zhao Senyao
to Wan Qianshan,
then Chu Chu,
Jing Yi, and you,
every move was part of their scheme.
Now the only one
who can save Chu Chu and Jing Yi
and turn this around is you.
Do not worry.
What Nanzhao owes us,
I will take back myself.
Wu Jiang has been settled by Lian Qiao
in the right wing hall.
I will go see him.
Your Highness.
I will stay with him.
Yes.
♪Bonds are like the wine in a cup♪
♪That can wash away endless sorrow♪
♪Do you remember
Those years when we stood back to back♪
♪Laughing as the past
drifted away like clouds♪
♪Turning into a haze of mist and rain♪
♪Who can escape falling
into the river of time♪
♪With a sword as a boat,
I carry you across life and death♪
♪I stand guard on the shore♪
♪Grasping the hand that overturns fate♪
♪On a long road, mountains
and seas apart, we go our ways♪
♪If worldly ties remain unfulfilled,
they endure through cycles♪
♪When flowers bloom again♪
♪Their fluttering means
I am by your side♪
Your Highness.
Lian Qiao.
Take my tally. Go at once and summon
the Imperial Medical Service.
Also,
Huichun Hall,
Hongbu Clinic,
Mengyu Hall,
and the physicians of Xuanhu Clinic.
Bring them all.
Yes, Your Highness.
Where is Chu He?
He is still being held.
He has said everything he can.
It is now for you to handle.
Jing Yi asked me to give this to you.
(Letter of Separation)
Your Highness.
Please pass this letter to Yue.
♪Time drips away
like fading crimson scent♪
♪The hardships of arrival pass
in a fleeting blink♪
Do not worry.
I promise
I will never tarnish
Miss Leng's reputation
in the martial world.
What do you mean by that?
I am warning you.
Do not get any twisted ideas.
If you scheme behind my back,
I will not forgive you
in my next life,
or the one after that.
Alright.
♪Rugged roads become the paths
of sun and moon♪
♪Fireflies like stars circle
through the seasons♪
What a mess.
Such a mess.
Everything I said
went straight past him.
And he even wrote
a Letter of Separation.
I should go to the prison right now
and knock some sense into him.
He has been taken home
and kept under watch.
You cannot see him for now.
Once we get Jing Yi out,
you can teach him a lesson.
I will not stop you.
♪This love was never easy,
so life and death will not part us♪
Fine.
I will spare him for a few days.
What matters now
is to capture You Chen'an.
Only then can Jing Yi be cleared.
If he returns to Nanzhao,
it will become a real problem.
Your Highness, tell me
what I should do.
Take men from
the Three Judicial Offices at once
and intercept You Chen'an
on the roads toward Nanzhao.
Issue warrants immediately to
every prefecture and county along the way.
Your Highness is certain
he will return to Nanzhao?
You Chen'an wants to live too badly.
No matter the time or place,
he would never wait to die.
What is more, he infiltrated Chang'an
and rendered great service.
He was even praised
by the King of Nanzhao
as a pillar of the state,
righteous and loyal.
This is his best chance
to establish authority in Nanzhao
and trade it for survival.
As long as he is alive,
he will seize the chance
to return to Nanzhao.
Understood.
I will go now.
Do not bother me.
Leave the food on the table.
He.
No missing arms, no missing legs.
I told you, An would never harm me.
Chu Chu was worried sick.
So something really happened?
Then...
Then I...
We have already found out.
You were used.
You had nothing to do with the case.
You can leave prison now.
Let us go back to the pharmacy first.
He often came to drink and talk with me,
to pour out his troubles,
and curse his elder brother.
Did he have close dealings
with your shop assistants
or regular customers?
No.
Your Highness,
did he do anything wrong here?
Since when did you
start keeping pigeons?
Pigeons?
They were left behind
by the previous owner.
I simply kept them.
You Chen'an seemed
to like them quite a bit.
Every time he came,
he would play with them for a bit.
Who was the previous owner?
♪Time drips away
like fading crimson scent♪
♪The hardships of arrival pass
in a fleeting blink♪
♪Palm lines carry
the footprints of memory♪
♪Leading us out of every winding turn♪
♪If two hearts can fly as one
then storms are part of the way♪
♪Looking back the sky
has already cleared♪
♪Your branches entwined with mine♪
♪Bound together in mutual reliance♪
♪Rugged roads become
the paths of sun and moon♪
♪Fireflies like stars circle
through the seasons♪
♪Shining with the hope of dreams♪
♪This world is no longer in rags♪
♪Only by holding you in my heart
do I dare embrace fear♪
♪Quietly waiting for rumors to fade♪
♪Together we face the tides of fate♪
♪Turning the course of heaven and earth♪
♪This love was never easy♪
♪So life and death will not part us♪
♪Like sinking into the deep sea♪
♪The first breath upon awakening♪
♪This bond will never waver♪
♪So we stay together
till our hair turns white♪
♪I ask time itself to hold the pen♪
♪And write the ending of eternity♪
♪This love was never easy♪
♪So I believe without doubt♪
♪Like a thousand sails passing by♪
♪Reaching shore
at the first light of dawn♪
♪This bond will never waver♪
♪So joy and sorrow
are no longer ours to choose♪
♪I will prove it
with the rest of my life♪
♪Together at the edge
of the world without an end♪