What is it? What's going to happen now?
Seo-jin, quiet.
That's it.
-Hey!
-What?
Hey, come and watch this.
I don't think the girl will come.
Kim Jong-min was baited.
He was totally baited.
Why'd you turn it off?
I told you to watch Seo-jin,
but you're watching TV again?
Who cares about a celebrity's blind date?
I shudder
when I hear the words "blind date."
Because of you.
If I studied more instead,
I'd be a judge or a doctor
and have a great life.
Do you think it's a good memory for me?
A judge or a doctor? As if.
Not all good students become those.
The good students are the ones
who become judges and doctors.
Well, right. Whatever.
Anyway, if you hadn't hit on me that day,
I wouldn't be living like this.
You hit on me first,
doing this with your eyes.
You kept winking at me.
I thought you had a broken eye.
You're remembering it all wrong.
You gave me the eye first
and looked like
you'd kill me if I didn't choose you.
Like this.
You did that first.
You even acted cute like this.
Don't you remember?
I chose you because I was scared.
You hit on me first.
You kept winking at me like this.
No, I seriously didn't. This is insane.
You hit on me first.
Let's call everyone and ask.
You're in Professor Hwang's class, right?
These are notes from last year.
It was hard to get.
You can use it.
It was hard to get, so you use it.
Nam-gil, this is new. You should try it.
It's new, so you drink it.
COLLEGE OF SOCIAL SCIENCES BULLETIN BOARD
Look who that is.
He still looks so tall and handsome.
He grew to be a good man.
Why did I turn down a guy like him
to date a petty loser like that?
Hello.
Nam-gil.
Are you here for a lecture?
"Are you here for a lecture?"
Would he be there to shoot pool?
Are you insane?
Or do you suddenly
feel lonely overnight and want a guy?
Why? I was just happy to see him.
I see, you were happy to see him.
After you humiliated him
like that yesterday?
What?
-It's Nam-gil. He's so hot.
-My gosh. Oh my gosh.
Hey.
Go out with me.
-No way.
-He asked her out.
No thanks.
Why not?
You smell like sweat.
How can she turn him down?
What's with her?
-I feel so bad for him.
-Who does she think she is?
I can't believe it.
Seriously.
That's ridiculous. When did I do that?
You did that yesterday.
My gosh. You didn't like him yesterday
because he smelled,
but you were happy to see him today?
You're so scary.
My goodness. I can't believe this.
That's why he looked at me
with such sad eyes.
Goodness, what's wrong with me?
Why did I say that?
How would I know?
Yes, I'm sure he was sweaty
because he was training,
you germophobe.
Right.
I must've been insane.
I was completely insane.
Are you sick?
HANGUK UNIVERSITY CIVIL ENGINEERING
It's not that kids nowadays are scary.
Kids have always been scary.
Upperclassmen are upperclassmen!
I know our department kids are dumbheads,
but I won't allow a rebellion.
Mind your manners.
Your seniors will deal with other seniors!
Look at these punks.
At least they play fair.
Gosh, this is tiring.
How long do we have to do this?
I'm about to die.
Don't be a baby.
Maintain your positions
until a girl comes into this room.
A girl in Engineering?
He's telling us to stay like this forever.
Damn it.
A girl.
Hey, it's a girl.
Come in. Please come in.
Come in. Please.
I'm sorry I'm late!
That jackass.
Dok-jae, right. Your hair.
Get down on the ground, all of you!
I mean, have you no conscience?
A young man like him
would naturally smell like sweat
after training.
How could you reject him so meanly?
Seriously, Jin-ju. You idiot.
-Hi, Jin-ju.
-Hi.
-What was her name?
-She was a student rep.
-Hey, who's the student rep?
-Erase the blackboard.
-Okay.
No, she was the student rep.
Hey!
Seol!
Seol, right?
What's with you?
She's not your long-lost sister.
The professor is here. Sit.
Goodness.
Right, the three of us
always stuck together around this time.
But she suddenly took a leave,
then cut us off.
Did I do something to upset her?
I'm not sure.
What did she do this morning?
Everyone's talking about it.
Everyone is so quick.
Why did she take a leave
without telling us?
PRINCE HEUNGSEON VS. EMPRESS MYEONGSEONG
WHOSE POLICY WAS BEST?
Now, are you all ready
for your group presentation?
-Yes.
I can't believe it.
I'm back taking lectures in school.
Prince Heungseon
was Empress Myeongseong's father-in-law.
They continuously fought for authority
and power over different policies.
Even Empress Myeongseong
couldn't avoid her in-laws.
How awful.
This led to the fall
of the Joseon Dynasty.
Let's see what argument you came up with.
The modernization
of the country was belated
due to his isolationist policy
on refusing to trade.
We're with Empress Myeongseong.
You're with the daughter-in-law.
Yes, you'll go through this later in life.
Good, next group.
Next presenter.
-What are you doing?
-What?
-Go.
-Go where?
Next presenter?
You're our presenter.
-Go.
-Me?
-Just go.
-Wait, it's me? Wait, what?
Just go. Go.
Group Three, Ma Jin-ju?
What do I do?
Well, I…
I forgot what arguments we came up with.
Did Group Three meet up ten years ago?
How did you forget already?
Then just tell us your take on it.
Is it the prince or the empress?
Well, I think
Emperor Gojong was wrong.
Emperor Gojong? Why?
I mean, his wife was fighting his father.
He should've stepped in.
He needed to step in
and moved out or something.
But this was the palace.
During the Joseon Dynasty.
Yes, right. Anyway.
When families get in such disputes,
the husbands are always at fault.
They don't intervene wisely.
No daughter-in-law
can defeat her father-in-law.
But it's not like she can give in
and do everything he wants.
It's not like
we daughters-in-law are slaves.
"We"?
So are you saying
Emperor Gojong caused the fall?
I believe he played a part.
That's a fresh take on this.
Good. Who was in her group?
UNABLE TO GET A GRASP OF THE SUBJECT
What happened?
How was I supposed to remember
something I did ages ago?
We discussed it yesterday.
Fine, let's say you forgot
what we discussed.
But what now? Emperor Gojong?
I mean, she asked for my opinion.
And you have no idea
how awful fathers-in-law can be.
He's so particular. He won't eat kimchi
made with sand lance extract.
I was reminded again.
-Of whom?
-Just someone.
A father-in-law
who's more like a mother-in-law.
May I?
Open up.
Sand lance extract?
I only eat anchovy extract!
Redo it! I won't eat this! Redo it!
I won't eat this!
He's like a mother-in-law.
She's so mean.
I mean, she asked for my opinion first.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe you.
Is this your new thing today?
FILM CLUB
I haven't seen an actual film in so long.
My gosh.
TOP SECURITY
Le Grand Bleu.
Hey, Flashman too?
Man, Brad Pitt.
Yes, I remember.
Dok-jae, your Brad Pitt hair.
You young rascals.
I can't believe I get to see you
so young again. Come here.
Gosh, you're so cute. So cute.
Stop talking nonsense.
Gosh, you're so cute.
Man, you're so cute too.
Gosh, it has been forever.
I'll kill him.
Hey.
Even so, he's an upperclassman.
No, I meant that jerk.
Are you hammered already?
Why did you laugh back there?
Do you see my hand shaking?
I almost lost my arm because of you.
Are you bored?
Does life seem trivial and insignificant?
So? Do you want your life to be dramatic?
Goodness, kid.
My life is already very dramatic.
What's that jackass saying?
Are you still drunk?
Fine. Let me explain this to you.
Listen up, babies.
I have no idea what's going on either.
But there's more than meets the eye.
You'll probably see me as Ban-do.
But I'm not the same Ban-do
you knew before.
If you're not Jin-ju, then who are you?
I'm saying I'm not 20 years old right now.
I came back to the past.
How can I remember
what happened 18 years ago?
So you're 38 years old?
No way. With a face like that?
I still look the same.
I woke up this morning and I was 20 again.
Back in 1999.
Right. So basically you time traveled.
Sort of like that movie
Back to the Future?
You're right.
Back to the Future. That's it.
As always, Jae-u. You're a smart one.
So what am I like in the future?
-You?
-Wait.
My hand won't stop shaking.
Can you massage it?
Your hand?
Geez.
Hey, how much
do I have to work out to look like you?
Take it easy.
You shouldn't get hurt at our age.
You two are
what we shouldn't look like at our age.
Hey, watch it.
Work out a little, will you?
My batting isn't so bad, is it?
But my coach keeps saying
my batting isn't as good as before.
I feel good about this season.
We have to make it
to the Korean Series this year.
CHEERLEADER FAIRY
You become healthy. Very healthy.
What about him?
-Will he still look like this?
-Come on.
Hey, watch it. He'll lose his hair.
Cut your hair. I hate it.
I'll beat you.
Hey, you can't say that.
No, Dok-jae.
Do whatever you want with your hair.
Perm it, dye it, bleach it, do whatever.
But don't shave it off.
-You can do that later.
-What are you talking about?
What about me?
Do I have a girlfriend?
A girlfriend? Right.
-Doing okay?
-Yes.
Don't worry. I'll do everything.
Honey?
You don't just have a girlfriend.
You have a wife too.
A director of a dance academy
and a women's rights activist?
Me?
YUN BO-REUM AEROBICS
Get his face.
Your husband is before you.
Get his face. Slap him!
And now, his stomach. Get his stomach.
Kill him. End his life!
Kick his head! Good!
Your husband is still there. Kick higher.
Keep it up.
If you hit somewhere wrong,
it'll be your loss. Keep it up.
I wouldn't say an activist,
but something like it.
I see. It sounds very believable.
Well, I have no idea what's going on,
and I'm dumbfounded by this.
Until last night, that cheap jerk…
Well, never mind.
Think of how absurd this is for me too.
I can't get into the details
with young boys like you
even before my deep wound is healed.
Anyway, if I seem odd,
just remember I came
from the future, and try to understand.
-I see, you're also hurt.
We had no idea.
It's fine, man.
Moron.
She's crazy. She's completely insane.
Is this a rerun of April Fools'?
She went crazy from all that studying.
He took his lies to another level.
Where's your time machine?
Is it parked at home?
Let's go see your time machine.
I'm hungry. Let's go eat.
Smart girls are very meticulous.
How does she add
so many details to her lie?
It's not like
this is believable to me either.
Wait for me! I don't know my way around.
Who would believe me?
Man, those little rascals. Wait up!
Hey, I don't know my way around!
-Hey--
-Excuse me.
I've been looking at you.
You're so pretty.
Me? Really?
Yes.
If it's all right with you,
may I have your number?
Goodness, what's going on?
He said I'm pretty.
Well, I…
I don't think
I have a beeper or a cell phone.
I see. You don't.
Then may I have your home number?
My home number? What was it?
How could I remember that?
I can't remember my number.
I'm not making it up.
I really don't know it.
Then can you tell me
your major and where you live?
Oh my gosh. Wait…
Look, a beeper… I have a beeper.
Goodness.
Isn't he that English major?
What? Did you reject another one?
Give him your number.
It's not like it'll cost you anything.
It's not like you have to date him.
The pretty girls always play hard to get.
He really keeps saying I'm pretty.
Whenever I pass by,
he goes, "You look pretty as always."
He must be trying to sell you something.
Who's pretty? You? Are you high?
That's not true.
He says it only to me
even when I'm with other women.
You must look the most gullible.
That's not true.
It's because I'm actually pretty.
He was always somewhere around here.
You look pretty as always.
Goodness, thank you.
If it's all right with you,
may we talk a little?
CREATIVE THINKING WITH A FUN STORYBOOK
This is a children's workbook.
This is completely sold out in Gangnam.
On top of being pretty, you look like
someone who values education,
so I'll give it to you for half price.
Man, this is practically free.
Goodness, ma'am.
You have such beautiful skin.
Your skin is so dewy.
It shines so brightly that it's blinding.
You're so perfect.
It's completely sold out in Gangnam.
On top of being pretty, you look like
someone who values education,
so it's half price for you.
Goodness, ma'am.
You have such beautiful skin.
You have skin
as smooth as a baby's bottom.
Goodness, I didn't know
there were so many pretty ladies here.
I thought it was just you.
Anyway, that handsome young man is
also good at sales.
He'll make it big.
Let's go home, Pretty Lady One.
-Hey, girls.
-What?
Aren't I really pretty?
Let's go.
You need a good beating.
-Hey, wait.
-You deserve a good beating.
Jae-u.
Ban-do.
Drink this and wake up.
COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING
What's that?
"Nostradamus"?
THE LAST PROPHECY BY NOSTRADAMUS
Man, right. The doomsday prophecy.
Now that I think about it,
who would believe this?
Did you decide yet?
What? Decide what?
What will you do
during that very last moment
on July 24th?
Seriously.
Hey, don't believe a word of this.
It's all bull.
It is not.
Hey, the planets are lining up right now.
A big disaster will strike.
The planets may crash, killing us all.
Some say a war will break out.
Don't get me started. The weather anomaly?
Some force is behind this
to keep the population in control.
We're going to die. Complete annihilation.
Quiet. I'm reading.
Hey, can you two stay here?
Where are you going?
-Move.
-Ma'am.
It hurts.
Have you gone crazy?
How dare you touch her?
That one punch
made her forget about this affair.
She looked really dense,
so it was easy to get her to marry me.
But that woman
is getting sharper with age.
-Ye-rim.
-Hey.
What should we eat?
You jerk. I said
I'd kill you if we met in college.
You're dead.
The Med Students' Night
comes only once a year.
-You must be sad.
-I know.
I'm a little sad, but what can I do?
I have to study.
My gosh.
Goodness!
My gosh, I'm so sorry.
My mind was elsewhere.
Watch where you're going!
I'm all right.
I'm fine. It happens.
Man, I'm so sorry.
Here, you can have this.
Okay, thanks.
I'm sorry, okay?
Why did you let him go?
You're way too nice.
What's the point?
He didn't do it on purpose.
I told you that I'd kill you, jerk.
It would've gotten him square in the face
if not for his glasses.
What a bummer.
RAMYEON: 800 WON
RICE MEAL: 1,500 WON
No way. 1,500 won?
The rice meal is 1,500 won?
That's unbelievably cheap.
It's a bag of chips.
Hey.
EXPLAIN THE PRICE INCREASE!
FOOD PRICE INCREASE!
WE DEMAND AN EXPLANATION
FROM THE CHAIRMAN!
What kind of gold-dipped chips
do you eat that cost that much?
It's good. This is good.
Why aren't you eating?
Let's eat.
I'm full.
You are? I'll eat this then.
Me too.
It tastes bad.
How's the galbi-tang?
Let me have a taste.
The broth is good because it's boiled
in a large pot for a long time.
It's nothing like this
when I make it at home.
Did you starve for a few days?
You never share food with others.
And why are you eating so quickly?
-You'll understand once you have a kid.
-What?
A kid?
What? Nothing.
No, it's nothing. Eat up.
The spicy pork is great with rice. Eat up.
My stomach is about to burst.
I ate so well.
You always ate a little
so your belly wouldn't stick out.
I have to enjoy being able to eat a lot.
Do you know how sad it is when you eat
just to survive
because you're too busy raising a kid?
What?
All right. It's about time Jin-ju changed.
-I'm very glad.
-Yes.
-Good.
What are we doing after lunch?
Why do you ask? As if you don't know.
Why? What are we doing?
Date date date, group blind date
A group blind date? Like a real one?
What's with him?
Yes.
Why am I running into him again?
Let's not get involved with him.
Come on, Jin-ju.
Let's not run into each other, please.
Why is she here?
What's this? Wait, is this…
The day we met?
The day I first met this jerk?
Let's see how many of you
become a couple today.
Hey, are they raising those seagulls
on their eyebrows?
And did they get punched in the mouth
as a group or something?
Hey, did you plant that grenade?
Did you see their hair?
Are they traffic lights?
Red, green, yellow.
Forget them. Look at him.
-Oh my gosh.
-Seriously.
What's with him?
Yes, this is the group blind date
where I first met Jin-ju.
Why did that have to be today?
No, this is better.
This is my chance
to never get involved with her. Forever.
What a nightmare.
I cursed this moment and this day
every moment of my life, kid.
Let's not get involved.
-Don't get involved.
You can take it first.
Thanks.
-Darn it.
-Come on.
-Don't get involved.
Then let's introduce ourselves.
Eom Won-hui, freshman, civil engineering.
It's not "Oh, Money," but Eom Won-hui.
Freshman, civil engineering major,
self-proclaimed Kim Won-jun.
I'm Lee Dae-hyeong.
I'm Go Dok-jae.
And it's not Dok-jae.
Please call me Go Dok.
I'm An Jae-u.
I like listening to the radio,
and my specialty is…
Well, I'm wondering what I should go with.
-A cockroach!
-Where? Where is it?
-There it is!
That's my friend's specialty. His speed.
He's such a kidder.
Just don't get involved with her.
Right. Hi, I'm Choi Ban-do,
majoring in civil engineering.
I'm 20 years old.
I was born in Byeonsan-bando,
hence Ban-do.
I'm always grateful
my parents didn't name me Byeon-san.
That's all.
You're just byeon, a load of poop.
That's it for the guys.
Shall we move onto the girls?
Let's start with you, Bo-reum.
How did you know my name?
What?
It's written on your book. "Yun Bo-reum."
YUN BO-REUM
Right.
Yun Bo-reum.
Gosh, that was close.
That totally slipped out.
My gosh, I thought he was like me.
Looks like we're all freshmen.
I'm Yun Bo-reum. I'm a history major.
He can't get
into this painful relationship again.
Don't go there, my friend.
History major, Cheon Seol.
I'm a history major too. Ko Eun-bi.
Wait, I see someone in you.
You look a bit like Suzy.
-Kang Susie?
Oh, no. The Suzy
I'm talking about isn't that Susie.
There's this young and cute Suzy.
You'll come to know her later in life.
No way. He couldn't be.
History major, Seol Hyeon.
What?
Seol Hyeon.
I'm Ma Jin-ju. History major.
-Ban-do.
-Yes?
Your turn on bomb disposal.
Make sure you take her.
A grenade? Don't be so immature.
-Just go with the flow.
-But it's…
-It's your turn today.
-My turn?
But how do I know
what the grenade will put in?
They don't put their names
on their belongings.
If I don't know, I can't do it.
Don't play dumb with me, man.
It's not your first time.
Do your job right.
Why is she keep staring at me?
She's scaring me.
Wait, does she want me?
Right, I remember.
She hit on me first on this day
and made my life a total mess.
Sweetie, you make me shudder.
He said "Suzy."
"Suzy."
Okay, who wants to pick first?
Okay, go ahead.
My life was ruined because of her.
I curse her.
I hope she burns in hell.
I feel so bad for myself.
I feel so pathetic.
My life was ruined because of her.
Yes, Jae-u. You're supposed
to choose your own destiny.
I'll help you.
What's this? What is this thing?
What?
What? You picked one.
A giraffe earring? Hey, Suzy.
-It's mine.
-What?
How is it yours? It's obviously Suzy's.
Even if you like him,
you need to stick to the rules.
I always wear mismatched earrings.
So the other one was a giraffe?
It's hers.
-What?
-I said it's hers. It's not mine.
These brats.
I hear some people
wear mismatched earrings.
You have no idea
how this will ruin your life.
Not her, okay?
Whatever.
Look at this guy.
There are only two left.
Ban-do, your turn.
Ban-do, you came back too?
And you completely ignored me?
Are you looking to live a new life?
Man, what's with her?
There will be turmoil if we get together.
I'll never get involved with her.
Please do your job, my comrade.
I'll pay you back
on our next group blind date.
So you won't get involved with me?
What?
You traitor!
Why? I threw myself on the grenade.
What? The grenade?
Hey, does she look like
the grenade to you?
That fat, ugly girl is the grenade!
You really have no idea, do you?
She's the real grenade.
She's like dynamite.
She has an awful temper.
She's a shopaholic,
a germophobe, and has anger issues.
She's the biggest grenade.
She has anger issues?
What the heck is that?
It's when they have an awful personality
and get angry out of nowhere.
But how do you know that?
How else? I lived with…
Lived?
It's a rumor that I heard.
Everyone knows except for you.
Come on out.
Really?
Everyone knows?
Except for me?
Something doesn't feel right.
Hey, but still,
I really don't like that fat, ugly girl.
Hey.
Now that we're paired up, let's split up.
We'll head out first.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
We'll get going too.
Anyway, I don't see
Dok-jae and his partner.
"That fat, ugly girl"?
Hey. Are you freaking kidding me?
How dare you call me the grenade
with your ugly face?
Jae… Jae-u.
Jae-u.
-Jae-u.
-Hey, look at me.
I'm going to go grab a drink. Follow me.
After completely ignoring me,
what is he up to now?
I picked her to dump her for good
and never see her again.
But how should I do it?
Aren't you two leaving?
What? Well, we don't have to.
But she does look kind of pretty
now that I see her like this.
You should've grown old like this, woman.
Wait, no way.
Is this jerk trying
to work things out with me again?
What a psycho.
No, no. I went crazy for a moment.
I'll put an end
to this awful relationship.
Well, Ms. Ma Jin-ju?
Now that I get a good look at you,
you have the physiognomy
of someone who should study.
Ms. Ma, aren't you a good student?
Stay-at-home moms
have no appeal, you know.
What will you do at home?
You never get full no matter what you eat.
Then what? You pester your husband
who brings a tiny little paycheck.
Listen to this punk.
Not only did you pester me,
you completely destroyed me.
Anyway, so don't dream
of finding a guy and getting married,
but keep studying.
You should study hard and pursue a career.
Isn't that cool?
Single, successful, and rich.
What did you just say?
I know. I get it. I offended you.
I know that. I do.
But once you get older,
you'll understand what I just said.
Anyway, keep studying.
Study hard. You can do this!
Goodbye, then.
Right, I don't want you
to take this the wrong way, so here it is.
I just rejected you,
and very cruelly at that.
Man, I can't believe that guy.
That little…
What a hero.
How many lives did I just save?
You wanted to study.
Become a judge or a doctor
and have yourself a great life.
I was nice enough to be with you.
Other guys would've divorced you already.
You have no idea.
What?
Min Seo-yeong?
Don't you remember my first love,
Min Seo-yeong, the dance major?
I should've hit on her,
but I was way too naive back then.
Even if you go back in time,
there's no way you could get her.
If I go back in time, I'd date her.
Why would I date someone like Jin-ju?
That crazy jerk.
Did he choose me to tell me that?
I pest…
pestered him to death?
How dare he give me that bull…
Where did he go?
Did you think you were the only one
who came back? What…
Excuse me.
You're Min Seo-yeong, right?
What?
Wait, is she…
Goodness, I'm sorry.
Hi.
Well, by any chance,
do you know me?
You don't?
I wouldn't say I know you,
but I wouldn't say I don't either.
That means you do.
What?
You're really something, Ban-do.
You already found your first love.
How did he survive
if he missed Seo-yeong so much?
Did you give me this miraculous day
just to show me this?
That I lived my life in vain?
It's great, I guess.
I already divorced him,
so it's a good way to move on.
Seo-jin.
Oh my gosh.
That's dangerous.
Come here.
What's wrong with me?
You jerk.
To 31 Seongbuk-dong, please.
Mom…
We're here.
And down.
Fall out.
Hello, Chairman Jeong.
You're such an embarrassment.
Just go.
It's not like we have
a good father-and-son relationship.
You rude punk.
I told you to join the student council,
not that useless ROTC.
Why not do everything
I tell you not to do?
You even ended up majoring in history.
Go date someone while you're at it.
That's a great idea.
-It's Nam-gil. He's so hot.
-My gosh. Oh my gosh.
Hey.
Go out with me.
-No way.
-He asked her out.
No thanks.
-She's crazy. How dare she?
-What's with her?
How can she turn him down?
What's with her?
Why not?
You smell like sweat.
What's with her? Jin-ju.
That fool.
What's with her?
In movies, you go back in a time machine.
If that's not it…
When I wake up?
Aren't you going to sleep?
Right, no.
I'm not going to sleep. I won't.
TO MY DEAR MOM
DIVORCE, TIME TRAVEL?
DREAM? A ONE-DAY MIRACLE
That's hilarious.
He looks exactly the same.
He's the funniest guy ever.
I think so too.
What is it? What?
Either watch TV or go to sleep.
Why are you making me so uncomfortable?
Did I feed her something weird?
What's wrong with her?
Is she hitting puberty now?
As if.
Don't you remember?
She was awful in middle school.
If she has a conscience,
she wouldn't relapse.
You're right.
Then why is she doing that?
It was nice to see you again, Mom.
Mom.
She's scaring me.
Me too.
No.
I can't fall asleep.
No, wake up.
What's going on?
What is this?
Why am I still here?
I didn't go back.
THE REAL 1999
Hey.
Hey, are they raising seagulls
on their eyebrows?
And did they get punched in the mouth
as a group or something?
Hey, did you plant that dynamite?
She's about to blow up.
There are only two left.
Ban-do, your turn.
Hey. It's your turn to take the grenade.
It's your turn today--
Everyone, let's take a picture.
Who knows? A couple here may get married.
What are you doing?
Give me every single penny
that our family has.
He's going to get into huge trouble.
Did you ignore me to live a new life?
You're such a good actress.
So now that I'm here,
I'm going to enjoy my life.
May I have your number?
-Move aside!
-Don't flirt with me.
I'm sorry!
I can't believe
I came to a nightclub with you.
What got into you?
If I don't do it now, when would I?
That's the guy who fell for me.
Director Park?
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon