♪Falling into darkness,
wandering alone in the mist♪
♪In the search for traces of love,
blurred and unclear♪
♪Catch the murky tears♪
♪Tread through solitude,
traversing time♪
♪Like a stubborn illness
in the heart, incurable♪
♪Why do mere words
etch deeply into the soul?♪
♪I see you, like a timid soldier,
crumbling to escape♪
♪Let pain bury the exclusive territory
of love♪
♪The wind slowly tears apart
the evidence of passionate love♪
♪Washing away the worn-out memories
in a monochrome world♪
♪I should be grateful,
the gods are fair♪
♪Allowing me to delve
into the depths of longing♪
♪Time scattered in the sky,
falling into the crevices of memory♪
♪Inverting the seasons and days,
just to find you♪
♪All things renamed,
encounters redefined♪
♪Embrace you between day and night♪
♪Dawn rises in endless light♪
♪Hold you tightly, like a distant past♪
♪Cross through the days in the wind,
entwined in the endless sea♪
♪Even if lost, the ending is certain♪
=A Tale of Love and Loyalty=
=Episode 20=
Wan, you're usually resourceful
but why are you so careless
when it comes to this matter about Yan?
A marriage concerns Yan's happiness
for the rest of her life.
Forcing her
to marry a man
she has never met in the south
will only hurt her.
(Chancellor Su)
This marriage was decreed by the emperor.
Why are you, a woman, getting involved?
Father, I...
Wan.
Father, Wan and Yan share a deep bond.
Don't blame her anymore.
Wan, tell me.
Where have you hidden Yan?
I always thought
Your Highness was merciless.
But the mere mention of Yan
will bring out the inferiority
and cowardice you hide in your heart.
This is extremely laughable.
You truly love to jest.
Yan,
I don't want to fight with you.
If you change your mind and leave,
no one will stop you.
Chancellor, someone has seen Miss Su Yan
near Mount Lancheng.
Bring her home.
Oh, of course.
There is one thing I don't understand.
Don't we already have help
from the crown prince?
Why are we roping in a feudal lord?
What do you know?
The Prince of Nanchuan
rarely returns to the capital,
but he has won many battles
at such a young age.
This time, the emperor is critically ill
and has sent a secret edict
requesting his presence.
We can't be sure
who will become the next emperor yet.
You are wise, Chancellor.
Yingren, I've spoken out of turn today.
Yan.
(Why do you only have Yan in your heart?)
I heard there is news about Yan.
Is that true?
As a monarch,
you couldn't bear to be merciless.
As a husband, you fail the ones you love.
Aren't you afraid you will end up alone?
(Yingren, why can't I ever
enter your heart?)
- Yan, you're finally...
- Your Highness, where is Wan?
(Yan.)
Wan.
You're back.
I missed you, so I came back.
(I wanted to give you
another chance to choose.)
(Why must you come back again?)
I'm glad you're back.
(So, you are the second daughter
of the Su family.)
Yingren, she is the lady
I mentioned in my letter.
I will marry no one but her in this life.
What are you talking about?
Wan, don't...
Wan.
Yuan,
you asked Father
to decline the engagement just days ago
and now you want to marry her.
Such a childish game is an insult
to someone of Chancellor Su's stature.
Yingren, I didn't know
that this marriage
was arranged by our old man.
But it isn't too late to know about this.
I will marry
the one I want to marry
no matter her status.
I will deal
with our old man myself.
Yan,
you ran away from the marriage
because he is the Prince of Nanchuan.
Now, you seem close to him.
What does this mean?
Wan, I ran away from the marriage
because I don't want to marry
someone I don't know.
Later, I met him on the road.
I really didn't know who he is,
and I didn't know
that he is the Prince of Nanchuan.
Do you love him?
Remember me, your savior, Yu Yuan.
I'll come back for you.
I don't hate him.
I love you more, Wan.
Oh, you're such a sweet-talker.
We'll never be apart again.
Okay.
Your Highness, it sounds like
you are willing to accept
the Duke of Lu's help.
Tell me.
What condition does he have?
It's nothing major.
The Duke of Lu has a daughter.
Her name is Ruyu
and has long adored Your Highness.
If Your Highness is willing
to marry the daughter of the Duke of Lu,
this cooperation
will surely proceed smoothly.
I'm afraid the Duke of Lu is confused.
I am already married.
I heard that your first wife,
Su Wan, has been ill for years.
I'm sure it is normal for her to die
if her illness goes untreated.
You're an intelligent person,
Your Highness.
You should understand what I mean.
Su Wan is my wedded wife.
She wholeheartedly
stood by me through thick and thin,
and never did anything wrong.
I will never hurt her.
Your Highness,
I'm sure you
can weigh the importance
of a momentary responsibility
against a lifetime of power.
If you insist on this,
I'm afraid the Duke of Lu
will not let this go easily
due to his love for his daughter.
Your Highness should know
that soft-heartedness
stands in the way of great accomplishments.
If you can't hold onto the kingdom,
how could you talk about
protecting your wife
and your infant child?
We await good news from you,
Your Highness.
The Duke of Lu is hard to predict.
You cannot let him overstep his limits.
Did you think you can rest easy
as the crown prince
after giving up
part of your military's command?
How ridiculous.
The Tiger Talisman of Military Command.
Everyone knows
that he is eyeing the throne.
Tell me.
The Prince of Nanchuan has returned.
If he finds out that you intend
to surrender the kingdom to make peace,
what would he think?
What do you mean?
Your Highness, if you trust me,
then leave the rest to me.
Your health is important.
Rest and recover first.
Wan dislikes bitterness.
Remember to bring
her favorite osmanthus candy
when giving her medicine.
Your Highness,
it's time for your medicine.
It's too bitter.
His Highness knew
you would try to talk your way out,
so he asked me to bring osmanthus candy.
Bring me paper.
Yes, Your Highness.
(For Su Yan Only)
Nanny, when the time is right,
give this letter to Su Yan.
You must personally hand it to her.
Why are you doing this, Your Highness?
His Highness will...
You're the daughter
of Chancellor Su's first wife.
Are you willing to marry me,
a powerless prince?
His Majesty's health
has been deteriorating over the years.
The imperial court
is already divided into factions.
I'm afraid I'll have to marry.
Instead of being forced to marry,
I might as well marry someone I love.
You love me?
(The feelings I gave him)
(cannot be returned
with just a few words.)
(I've spent
more than half my life with him.)
(I don't regret marrying him.)
Your Highness.
Nanny.
I didn't expect
this candy
to be so bitter.
♪There's a kind of powerlessness,
watching you leave♪
♪Pretend to be indifferent,
but my heart can't breathe♪
♪I dare not imagine our future,
what kind of relationship it will be♪
♪Praying for time to slow down,
not to erase my memories♪
♪From then on, I lost you♪
♪But I still think of you,
unable to let go♪
♪You always appear
in every dream of mine♪
♪Coming close and then going away.
I can't love you anymore♪
♪From now on,
I am the only person to stay♪
♪Dare not disturb.
I can only hold tightly onto memories♪
♪How can I leave someone I've loved?♪
♪It's impossible to return to before♪
♪Tell me, how do we settle our regrets?♪
♪Because I loved you too much,
I let go of my pride♪
♪I can't learn to leave you so easily♪
♪You left with just a goodbye♪
♪Letting me linger in the same spot,
heartache for years♪
♪From then on, I lost you♪
♪But I still think of you,
unable to let go♪
♪You always appear
in every dream of mine♪
♪Coming close and then going away.
I can't love you anymore♪
♪From now on,
I am the only person to stay♪
♪Dare not disturb.
I can only hold tightly onto memories♪
♪How can I forget someone I've loved?♪
♪It's impossible to return to before♪