♪Falling into darkness,
wandering alone in the mist♪
♪In the search for traces of love,
blurred and unclear♪
♪Catch the murky tears♪
♪Tread through solitude,
traversing time♪
♪Like a stubborn illness
in the heart, incurable♪
♪Why do mere words
etch deeply into the soul?♪
♪I see you, like a timid soldier,
crumbling to escape♪
♪Let pain bury the exclusive territory
of love♪
♪The wind slowly tears apart
the evidence of passionate love♪
♪Washing away the worn-out memories
in a monochrome world♪
♪I should be grateful,
the gods are fair♪
♪Allowing me to delve
into the depths of longing♪
♪Time scattered in the sky,
falling into the crevices of memory♪
♪Inverting the seasons and days,
just to find you♪
♪All things renamed,
encounters redefined♪
♪Embrace you between day and night♪
♪Dawn rises in endless light♪
♪Hold you tightly, like a distant past♪
♪Cross through the days in the wind,
entwined in the endless sea♪
♪Even if lost, the ending is certain♪
=A Tale of Love and Loyalty=
=Episode 8=
Your Highness, if you're really fond of
the Palace of Hanning.
You might as well move in here.
That will save me much time
going back and forth.
The situation outside the City is pressing.
Why are you still competing
with His Majesty for a woman?
Do you dare to say that again?
What are you waiting for?
Come here and report to me.
Your Highness, outside of the City,
troops are gathering from different parties.
At the camp in the capital suburb,
Duke of Lu alone
holds an army of 200,000 soldiers.
Cao Ruiji of the Northwest Lu'an Army
has also come
with the son of Prince Yu.
They have troops of half a million in total.
They have almost half the men
more than we do.
Troops of half a million.
Concerning the current situation,
how about we just
leave the Palace for Nanchuan?
Are you afraid?
Who's there? Who allows you
to eavesdrop on military intelligence?
I didn't know you were talking about that.
I'll bring you some tea.
How many men are left
in the Imperial Army?
General Meng says there are 8,000 available.
Do you want to discuss this with him?
No need for that.
Tell Meng Chuang to fortify the City.
Are you going to...
Tell him
I don't need the Imperial Army
to fight outside the City.
Even if the sky falls,
he doesn't need to open the gate.
But if his 8,000 men
fail to defend the Imperial City,
don't blame me
for executing all of his relatives.
It's a military order.
General Chu.
General Chu, what's the matter?
Why do you care about him?
How would you let him trust you completely?
I will find an opportunity
to keep an eye on him.
Let me help you grind the ink stone.
Your Majesty, why are you fawning over me?
Is there anything else you want from me?
No.
I'll be happy as long as you're not mad at me.
You can focus on your work.
I'm good at grinding.
General Chu says
these record the anti-gunpowder
observation decks inside the City.
There are plenty.
If you want to fortify the City,
you have to review them
as soon as possible before giving orders.
Well.
I didn't know
you were interested in military affairs.
I happened to hear your conversation
while passing by.
I didn't mean to.
Don't worry about it, Your Highness.
You dare to enslave me?
Then... You could just drop it.
Won't you make the tea for me?
I will.
Does Yuwen Yingren summon you
into the Palace
to serve people?
You're rather good at doing a maid's work.
(Even though he's been temperamental,)
(he's never done anything)
(that hurt me.)
I think...
The amulet by my pillow last night,
I think it's gone.
What do you mean?
Are you taking back a gift
that's been given?
As long as it's not missing.
What would you like to have for dinner?
I'll prepare it for you.
Whatever.
Your Majesty, Her Majesty has someone
to the Palace of Xuyang
to invite His Highness
to have dinner at the Palace of Hanning.
I suppose he's about to arrive at this time.
Please forgive me for the extra words.
I'm afraid His Highness may be wronged
when confronted
with that moody Prince of Nanchuan.
Go ahead.
Also, rumors have been going
around the Palace lately. It is said...
What do they say?
It is said as long as the Nanchuan Army
stays here one more day,
the people in the Palace
can live one day longer.
- Nonsense!
- Please calm down, Your Majesty.
Only Go pieces.
I can just leave them.
Go outside of the Palace for me.
Set out at night
to get outside of the Palace.
Don't let others see you.
Yes, Your Majesty.
(Palace of Hanning)
I've invited Cheng to have dinner here.
Please don't go out of your temper.
Is that alright?
Cheng has dinner with me every day.
I hate to see him eat alone
in the Palace of Xuyang.
Your Majesty, you enjoy being a stepmother,
and want me to have dinner with him.
Do you know? I'm fine with doing anything.
But the last thing I'll do
is to be a stepfather.
That's not what I mean.
Your Majesty.
Mother.
What's wrong? Do you think I'll eat kids?
Cheng.
It is Cheng'an who acted rudely
and misunderstood Uncle Yuan that day.
I am here to apologize to you, Uncle Yuan.
If you want to punish me,
I would love to take the punishment.
In that case,
how about you call me Father?
You're not my father.
I have my own father.
You're never my father.
Cheng.
Uncle Yuan is only kidding.
The dishes are getting cold.
Today we have steamed bass,
Cheng, your favorite.
Take a bite.
Careful. It's hot.
The fish is delicious.
Mother and I can't eat it all.
Uncle Yuan, you can have some too.
If I, Prince of Nanchuan,
want to eat fish,
do I have to eat your leftovers?
Cheng,
Uncle Yuan
prefers to fish stock rather than meat.
But thank you for your sharing, Cheng.
If you like it, you can have more of it.
Are Uncle Yuan and Father really related?
Why are they so different?
Father worries Mother is occupied
taking care of me at dinner,
so he always lets her eat first.
How much do you know
that you dare to criticize me?
This afternoon,
your mother has had various pastries.
It will be strange
if she can eat more now.
And don't compare me with your father.
Without me,
you will be paying respects
in front of his tomb.
Cheng,
Uncle Yuan is only joking.
What's to cry about?
Aging, diseases, and death are inevitable.
You don't have a choice.
The only choice we have
is how to die for whom.
After your father succeeded to the throne,
having witnessed the regent
hold court behind the scenes,
he fell sick from overworking.
That's incurable.
He's dying for the people and the kingdom.
That's his choice. Even if you cry,
that'll be of no help.
(Now that I realize
you're still the same as before.)
(Although the sword was put to his neck,)
(you still didn't do that.)
(You're still the man
sticking to the right thing,)
(devoting himself to the kingdom,)
(and being loyal to the wise emperor.)
(Is she crying for Yuwen Yingren?)
Why are you so reluctant to see him die?
Let go of my mother!
Stop crying!
Mother is fine.
Come.
Zhilan.
Take Cheng to rest.
He's not your blood.
Is it because he's that sick man's son,
you love the boy as you love the man?
He's not only His Majesty's son.
He's also my sister's son.
More than that,
Cheng is still young.
But he will gradually understand.
Stop saying those horrible things to him.
You'll terrify the kid.
He's even reluctant
to call me Father.
I'll go to prepare the bathing water for you.
Why are you eavesdropping as a man?
Come out.
A new message from our eyes.
Let's talk outside.
The bathing water is ready.
You can discuss work with General Chu first.
I'll wait for you to come back.
♪There's a kind of powerlessness,
watching you leave♪
♪Pretend to be indifferent,
but my heart can't breathe♪
♪I dare not imagine our future,
what kind of relationship it will be♪
♪Praying for time to slow down,
not to erase my memories♪
♪From then on, I lost you♪
♪But I still think of you,
unable to let go♪
♪You always appear
in every dream of mine♪
♪Coming close and then going away.
I can't love you anymore♪
♪From now on,
I am the only person to stay♪
♪Dare not disturb.
I can only hold tightly onto memories♪
♪How can I leave someone I've loved?♪
♪It's impossible to return to before♪
♪Tell me, how do we settle our regrets?♪
♪Because I loved you too much,
I let go of my pride♪
♪I can't learn to leave you so easily♪
♪You left with just a goodbye♪
♪Letting me linger in the same spot,
heartache for years♪
♪From then on, I lost you♪
♪But I still think of you,
unable to let go♪
♪You always appear
in every dream of mine♪
♪Coming close and then going away.
I can't love you anymore♪
♪From now on,
I am the only person to stay♪
♪Dare not disturb.
I can only hold tightly onto memories♪
♪How can I forget someone I've loved?♪
♪It's impossible to return to before♪