♪Falling into darkness,
wandering alone in the mist♪
♪In the search for traces of love,
blurred and unclear♪
♪Catch the murky tears♪
♪Tread through solitude,
traversing time♪
♪Like a stubborn illness
in the heart, incurable♪
♪Why do mere words
etch deeply into the soul?♪
♪I see you, like a timid soldier,
crumbling to escape♪
♪Let pain bury the exclusive territory
of love♪
♪The wind slowly tears apart
the evidence of passionate love♪
♪Washing away the worn-out memories
in a monochrome world♪
♪I should be grateful,
the gods are fair♪
♪Allowing me to delve
into the depths of longing♪
♪Time scattered in the sky,
falling into the crevices of memory♪
♪Inverting the seasons and days,
just to find you♪
♪All things renamed,
encounters redefined♪
♪Embrace you between day and night♪
♪Dawn rises in endless light♪
♪Hold you tightly, like a distant past♪
♪Cross through the days in the wind,
entwined in the endless sea♪
♪Even if lost, the ending is certain♪
=A Tale of Love and Loyalty=
=Episode 13=
You're here, Yuan.
Since you're here,
why don't you have a meal with us?
It seems like
you don't really want me to dine with you.
I don't see my tableware
prepared in advance.
It was my fault
that we never do things together.
Kid, I just saved you
a couple of days ago.
Why aren't you showing respect now?
Who taught you manners?
You're so unruly.
Uncle Yuan.
I haven't seen you in days
and you've gained weight.
It's time to lose it.
You should follow me
to the army camp and train.
Train?
It means commanding a large army
in battle to regain lost territories
and secure victories in wars.
Mother, can I go play with Uncle Yuan?
Cheng, don't make trouble.
Cheng.
Cheng is the crown prince.
He has to learn the duties of a monarch.
If he goes with you,
it will affect his studies.
With me around,
he doesn't need to learn how to rule.
Without me,
the Great Yu Dynasty would be gone.
He wouldn't even need
to learn theories about war.
You...
Come.
Prince of Nanchuan.
What you are doing now is similar
to what our ancestors did
when they used the emperor's authority
to control other fiefdoms.
If you hadn't mentioned it,
I would have forgotten.
Rumors have been spreading
in the palace lately.
In that case,
I will turn them into truths.
What are you doing?
I won't do anything.
I only know
that whatever you want to do,
I will not let you have your way.
Yan.
Are you now satisfied
with how this situation has turned out?
What do you mean, Your Majesty?
What do I mean?
You suspect that I would harm Cheng,
but you let Prince of Nanchuan
take him away.
If something happens to Cheng,
how will you explain it to Wan?
Forget it.
Cheng trusts Yuan.
In that case,
I hope he will not
direct his frustration towards you and me
onto the child.
You're right, Your Majesty.
But I believe
that being exploited by a close relative
is far more unacceptable
than any harm Yuwen Yuan
will bring upon him.
I'm taking my leave.
Please don't be angry, Your Majesty.
Get out.
(After today's incident,)
(Yuwen Yingren and Yuan
have completely turned on each other.)
Without me,
the Great Yu Dynasty would be gone.
You...
What are you doing, Your Highness?
I won't do anything.
I only know
that whatever you want to do,
I will not let you have your way.
Kid,
am I better or your master?
You, of course.
Not bad, kid.
You picked the wooden sword
I carved myself.
I don't deserve your praise.
I really like this sword.
Can you give it to me?
Cheng, what did I tell you?
You will not ask for things from others.
Have you played enough?
Come back with me.
Do you want this sword?
Yes.
If you want this sword,
defeat me and I'll give it to you.
Mother, I want to play with Uncle Yuan.
Your Highness must be busy.
Don't let Cheng stay here and disturb you.
Your Majesty, are you trying
to burn the bridge again?
(Did he take Cheng away on purpose?)
Cheng.
Cheng, are you hurt?
My bum hurts a little.
He is just a child.
Can't you go easy on him?
When faced with life or death
on the battlefield,
those who want to kill him
will not see him as a child.
He is the heir to the throne,
and you wouldn't let him
endure a little bit of pain.
A loving mother fails a son, indeed.
Shall we continue?
Yes.
Mother.
Uncle Yuan, you lost.
Are you hurt?
Are you worried about me, Your Majesty?
A child's strength
can hurt you this badly.
I suppose the god of war isn't
impressive after all.
You brat,
you aimed for my injury.
I'm sorry, Uncle Yuan.
I didn't mean it.
It's fine. Tell me.
How did you find out that I'm injured?
You hardly used
the right side of your body
when you fought me.
So, I guessed.
You're indeed the son of Yuwen Yingren.
You already understand
what it means to win
by attacking the enemy's weakness
with one move.
Let me take a look at your injury.
Chu Li.
Your Highness, your injury is...
Her Majesty and I have
something to discuss.
Take the child away.
Cheng, you go first.
Take it easy.
Su Yan.
Did that hurt you?
No.
Your Majesty, you're no longer scared
when dealing with injuries now.
(Eight years ago)
Don't speak if you want to live.
Over there. Go.
Who are you?
Wake up. Hey.
I'm not afraid, so why are you afraid?
If you dare to run,
I will kill you.
(She is such a fool to trust me so easily.)
Stop crying. What is your name?
Su... Su Yan.
You're still injured.
Why are you trying to be a hero?
Are you worried about me, Your Majesty?
Shouldn't you hope
that I die soon,
so that Yuwen Yingren can
take back the military power in Nanchuan
and solve the kingdom's trouble?
Su Yan, have you gone insane?
We need to stop the bleeding.
You should bear with it, Your Highness.
All right, I'll be leaving now.
Su Yan, why wouldn't you trust me?
I know you're being defensive.
Being defensive is the best.
But I'm curious
if you are showing the same defensiveness
towards Yuwen Yingren
as you are towards me.
This has nothing to do with you.
Does what you plan to do
have nothing to do with me?
I merely want to find Cheng
a chance to live in this troubled times.
You can fight for power all you want.
It has nothing to do with me.
What if I am fighting for
more than just the throne?
You...
I'm a very greedy person.
I want both the throne and the beauty.
Don't bite off more than you can chew.
Beware that you don't suffer a loss,
Your Highness.
I'll gladly endure it.
Uncle Yuan, Mother.
Can't you watch a child?
He wants to find Her Majesty.
Mother, has Uncle Yuan gotten better?
Thanks to you and your mother,
I am still alive.
Does your word hold true?
What?
You can have it.
Thank you, Uncle Yuan.
Cheng, his injury hasn't healed.
It's fine. Come.
How about we go outside
and have a sword practice?
Okay.
(Palace of Jingcheng)
Come.
Cheng.
Yuan, stop it.
Give it to me.
Cheng.
Uncle Yuan.
Cheng, be careful.
All right, stop it.
Meng Chuang, take a look.
Do the three of them
look more like a family of three?
It seems like
I am the extra person here.
Your Majesty, the empress
and crown prince are also helpless.
Helpless?
Right now,
Prince of Nanchuan holds power
and the crown prince is
being held hostage.
Her Majesty is only doing this
to protect the crown prince
and you, Your Majesty.
Yes, she is also doing this for me.
Go.
Yes, Your Majesty.
♪There's a kind of powerlessness,
watching you leave♪
♪Pretend to be indifferent,
but my heart can't breathe♪
♪I dare not imagine our future,
what kind of relationship it will be♪
♪Praying for time to slow down,
not to erase my memories♪
♪From then on, I lost you♪
♪But I still think of you,
unable to let go♪
♪You always appear
in every dream of mine♪
♪Coming close and then going away.
I can't love you anymore♪
♪From now on,
I am the only person to stay♪
♪Dare not disturb.
I can only hold tightly onto memories♪
♪How can I leave someone I've loved?♪
♪It's impossible to return to before♪
♪Tell me, how do we settle our regrets?♪
♪Because I loved you too much,
I let go of my pride♪
♪I can't learn to leave you so easily♪
♪You left with just a goodbye♪
♪Letting me linger in the same spot,
heartache for years♪
♪From then on, I lost you♪
♪But I still think of you,
unable to let go♪
♪You always appear
in every dream of mine♪
♪Coming close and then going away.
I can't love you anymore♪
♪From now on,
I am the only person to stay♪
♪Dare not disturb.
I can only hold tightly onto memories♪
♪How can I forget someone I've loved?♪
♪It's impossible to return to before♪