[English subtitles are available]
[You are My Fateful Love]
[EP08]
Look over there.
The flowers are nice.
Coming.
Hello.
Hi.
Are you Ms. Ruan,
Ruan Yu?
Yes, I am.
I'm the property manager
for this complex.
Here's the thing.
Early this morning,
there was a drunk guy
lurking downstairs from your place.
He didn't bother you, did he?
A drunk guy?
Bother me?
No.
Good.
Make sure to lock
your doors and windows at night.
Stay safe.
We'll also
step up security patrols
around the complex.
If anything happens,
just give us a call
right away.
Then I'm leaving.
Hold on a sec.
That drunk guy,
have you found him?
He was taken away last night.
Good to hear.
Honestly, it was kinda creepy.
He was right downstairs
from your place,
pacing around that tree,
talking to himself one minute,
then singing and dancing the next.
[What kind of sick behavior is that?]
Li Shican,
I can do it too!
Is Li Shican
that famous now?
Which crazy male fan
is out there fanboying at this hour?
Was that when it happened?
Why would
Li Shican's fan
come to my place?
Thanks.
I'll get going then.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
A drunk guy.
Kinda scary.
Late-night drinks
with someone.
Nothing special.
Just one word.
S-L-
E-E-
P-Y.
Sleepy.
Mr. Liu is pretty funny.
Gentlemen,
can I ask you something?
Do you know
how to deal with a creep?
If some drunk guy
harasses you in the middle of the night,
what should you do?
What's got you so happy, Mao?
Don't ask me.
Ask the man himself.
Ask Huaisong.
Is our firm
that slow right now?
We don't have any
legal consultation cases?
If that's the case, Liu Mao,
we might not need to keep our interns.
We do!
I've got over a dozen cases today.
I... I'll get back to work.
-Ms. Zhang.
-I'm free.
Why don't you tell me?
How are you free?
You've got so many domestic violence cases,
and then all those
disputes at construction sites.
I don't want to waste your time
with my small problem.
I'll head back now.
How small?
since you put it that way,
I'm even more curious.
Ms. Zhang,
curious?
Let me show you.
Check this out.
Does the guy
in this video
look kinda like
Mr. Xu?
You got this.
Xu Huaisong,
you can do it.
We need to stay rational.
Yes, rational.
Image matters.
We can't go into
battle unprepared.
So think about
those keywords:
Elegant.
Aloof.
Yeah.
She likes that.
Aloof.
There's one more besides aloof.
Singing and dancing.
Li Shican, singing and dancing.
How hard can it be?
If Li Shican can sing and dance,
I can too!
Li Shican,
I can do it too!
Property management?
I just got up to use the bathroom
and noticed someone downstairs
who's totally hammered.
He's acting crazy.
Come over quick.
Hurry up.
Elegant.
Aloof.
Singing and dancing.
I can do this.
Ruan Yu,
here I come.
Where are you going?
No time to ask.
Just drag him away.
What?
What are you doing?
-Wait!
-Come on.
What...
Not kinda.
At least a little, right?
Barely.
A little bit, right?
I say, he looks just like him.
Good moves.
Shame you aren't a dancer.
What a shame.
Even Ms. Zhang says it's a shame.
Ruan Yu. Ruan Yu.
I've asked
a cop I know.
That guy
in your neighborhood last night
was just
some heartbroken dude.
He drank too much
and lost his mind.
The cops
gave him a talking-to.
Don't worry.
He's probably
learned his lesson by now.
Relax.
Nothing else will happen.
Talk about your bad timing.
You were just about to
ring her bell, and you got caught.
Too bad.
Not too bad.
It's a good thing.
How so?
With Mr. Xu,
love's like a courtroom.
He has to avoid
any ill-timed recklessness.
He'll never rush to slam the gravel
until it's time to close the case.
But love
is not a courtroom
A courtroom is about evidence.
Love is about tug-of-war.
Any relationship
is a tug-of-war.
All's fair in love and war.
I'm off.
Time to hit the construction site.
Good advice.
Yeah, Mr. Xu.
Let me say something.
I really think
when it comes to dating,
you can't treat it
like a case.
If you wait until you're sure
to win before you act,
won't someone else
snatch her
up first?
You're not leaving?
I... I...
I shouldn't have said that.
I'll get back to work now.
Bye.
He's getting cuter and cuter.
Until I'm sure to win...
[He's probably]
[learned his lesson by now.]
[Relax.]
[Nothing else will happen.]
Nothing can't be overcome.
Just can't go back anymore.
What a cheesy line.
When did I accidentally
like that?
The anti-plagiarism report
is ready to finalize.
Pre-litigation work is basically
done at this point.
At least he didn't nitpick
my Chapter 23.
Adults
know how to
leave each other some dignity.
Mr. Liu, Mr. Xu,
thank you both for all your
hard work on my case.
If you're free tonight,
let me take you out to dinner.
Looks like Ruan Yu's doing fine.
She didn't see that
amazing video of yours.
Alright.
Let's do Cantonese.
Is this place okay?
Mr. Xu is recovering,
so something light is better.
If Ruan Yu knew
how Mr. Xu was
acting last night...
Ruan Yu, sorry.
I've got a blind date tonight,
so I can't make it.
You and Mr. Xu enjoy.
Him and me?
So?
Got your back, right?
Is that a real blind date?
Of course it is.
Let's both do our best,
see who gets there first.
It better be.
A piece of advice for you.
Don't drink when you
have dinner with Ruan Yu.
You can't
handle your liquor well.
It feels a bit strange
without Mr. Liu here.
Braised pork intestine.
Someone aloof
wouldn't eat this.
Crispy roast duck.
He just got out of the hospital.
He probably shouldn't eat
something this greasy.
But this roast duck
looks so good.
Century egg and lean pork congee.
Cured stuff is
hard on the stomach.
Braised Chicken Feet.
Need to use hands.
Not graceful enough.
Beef's no good either.
Too hard to digest.
Garlic's no good.
Smell's too strong.
Seafood's no good either.
What if his stomach
is inflamed?
Chicken cartilage, no good.
Too noisy to eat.
Ready to order?
After all that,
they only ordered two bowls of congee?
A guy can be average-looking
but can't be stingy.
Looks don't pay the bills.
Mr. Xu,
you don't have
to save me money.
We can order more.
It's good enough.
Have there been more trolls
harassing you lately?
No.
Ever since I sent out
that cease and desist,
it's died down.
Have you still been
checking comments much?
Occasionally.
I've been handling it a lot better.
Don't worry, Mr. Xu.
Good.
A lot of people think
it's no big deal to like a post
or leave a comment online.
But when there's a lawsuit,
those actions
can be seen as reflecting
a client's position.
I did accidentally like a post.
But I unliked it right away.
Would that affect the case?
What did you like?
The trial is coming up.
We can't afford any complications.
But it wasn't really
related to the case.
It was just some
melodramatic post.
Then why'd you
unlike it?
It was something about
never being able to go back.
I thought it was too corny.
I mean, I write
romance novels,
but even I can't
handle that style.
Good to know.
What did you say, Mr. Xu?
I said,
good to know.
Let's eat.
[You're the one who started chatting with me.]
Excuse me, Mr. Xu.
Ruan Yu, check out the video.
That drunk guy from the other night
was so hilarious.
This drunk guy
kinda looks like...
Drunk guy?
Looks like me?
No.
Just the build, kind of.
Mr. Xu,
someone as disciplined as you
would never drink that much.
And even if you did,
you wouldn't be
acting like that.
The video quality is pretty bad.
You can't assume he's anyone
just because he's in a suit.
And a piece of advice,
when you get home,
tell your property management
to step up security
around the complex.
That guy
is probably
a fan of Li Shican.
Looks like he was dancing
one of Li Shican's routines.
But it was pretty ridiculous.
Let's eat.
The congee's getting cold.
Li Shican dances well?
Everyone has their specialty.
He is
a professional after all.
Mr. Xu, you know Li Shican too?
I should be asking you that.
Who doesn't know a big star?
But being able to sit
under the same roof,
on the same couch,
you must be very close.
You mean last time?
I've known Li Shican
since before he was famous.
We were college classmates.
Is that all?
You're also townmates, right?
I remember Li Shican
is also from Su City.
Yes.
So you knew him in high school?
Not exactly.
He went to Su City No. 2 High.
I went to...
Which high school did you go to?
I...
Sorry, Mr. Xu.
It's okay.
Let me.
-So sorry.
-No problem.
Thanks.
Mr. Xu, let's eat.
The congee is getting cold.
That cup of water
did you a big favor.
Stop laughing.
Xu Huaisong had been
abroad for years.
How does he know
Li Shican's from
Su City?
Is Li Shican
that famous already?
Not Li Shican's problem.
You're the one who brought him up.
But I do get the feeling
that Xu Huaisong
has some kind of issue with him.
I know.
It must be because
of that misunderstanding last time.
Didn't Xu Huaisong
call the cops?
True.
But talking to Xu Huaisong
is like walking
through a minefield, filled with traps.
I'd better avoid
seeing him alone in the future.
Otherwise, I'd
slip up sooner or later.
In my opinion,
rather than
being on edge
all the time,
you should just be brave
and come clean.
If you really
don't care about Xu Huaisong anymore,
just let it go
and move on with your life.
Okay?
It's two completely
different issues.
I just don't want
to rip off that last bit of dignity
from my youth and leave it
out in the open.
It's too embarrassing.
Mom, Dad, I'm home.
Yu, you are back!
Hold on. Let me turn it off.
What's for dinner, Mom?
Tomorrow's the winter solstice,
so I'm
making sweet rice balls.
Your favorite.
Awesome.
I'm gonna have it
with osmanthus wine.
Of course. I know.
Let me wash my hands and help.
Come on.
How are you going to help?
You'll just get in the way.
Right?
Way to kill my enthusiasm.
Mom, where's dad?
Your dad?
He was just here.
-Yu, you are back!
-Dad.
We're in for a treat.
Thanks, honey.
Come on,
let's go get some sun in the yard.
Mom, I'll go outside then.
You two are really
leaving me here alone?
This weather is amazing.
Have you talked to Liu Mao lately?
Here we go again.
I told you last time,
we're not a good fit.
Not to bug you,
but being a lawyer is
a good profession.
If you ever run into trouble,
he can stand up for you.
Dad,
do you really want your daughter
to run into trouble that badly?
Silly girl.
Can't you tell your dad's
just worried about you?
Exactly.
Here.
Oh, Yu,
your mom and I are thinking
about making a trip back to Su City.
Don't.
It's been so windy and rainy lately.
Today's the only
nice day we've had.
If you take
a trip now,
your arthritis will act up.
That house
has been vacant for years,
still needs a cleaning
for the winter solstice.
Right.
And your mom's been
wanting to go back anyway.
Alright then.
I'll go with mom.
You stay home and rest.
That way, mom and I can have
some quality time together.
You silly kid.
Girls at your age
all spend time with boyfriends.
You want to hang out with your mom?
Yes.
Fine.
I guess I'll just
have to be okay with it.
And I'm looking forward to it.
Then I'll
have to accept it.
Alright.
You two have your fun.
The weather is so nice.
Why don't you message Mao?
Young people need
to spend time together
to have a chance
of going further.
Remember when we were young?
If Yu had
even half your skill,
I wouldn't have to worry so much.
Who does she take after?
She takes after me.
Mrs. Ruan just messaged me.
She's still thinking about me,
especially for an occasion like this.
Looks like someone
hasn't seen Ruan Yu
in a while since
the case prep.
Makes sense.
No chance to see her.
Not like me,
I got an invitation.
My neck's
been so stiff lately.
Must be from overworking.
Overworking, huh?
Yeah, right there.
A little harder.
Here you go.
Good technique.
[Mao, you mentioned]
[that you travel to Su City for work often.]
[Do you have any plans]
[to go there soon again?]
[Maybe you could give]
[Yu and me a ride to the old house]
[to pick up some things?]
[If it's too much trouble,]
[don't worry about it.]
[You can always come by]
[for a meal some other time.]
How about this, I'll let you
make the decision.
Just reply however you want.
Just tell her
I don't have time.
Or tell her I'm not
compatible with
her daughter.
I'm willing
to sacrifice my good name
for your happiness.
There's something else.
The matchmaking agency
next to our office
is closing next month.
I was thinking
we could rent it
and expand
our firm.
Make it bigger and brighter.
I'd be honored.
I'll be out working on a case tomorrow.
Tomorrow night's no good.
I have a date.
From that matchmaking agency?
You sure a place
that can't even pay rent can handle
your happiness
for the rest of your life?
Rent runs on money.
Love doesn't.
Won't take much
of your time tomorrow.
And it definitely won't interfere
with your date at night.
[No wonder my mom wouldn't]
[let me buy train tickets.]
[If I'd known it was a ride like this...]
Mr. Liu, sorry
to trouble you.
No trouble at all.
It's on the way anyway.
Are you really going
to Su City for a case?
Yeah. A site visit.
An old classmate
of a client
happens to be in Su City.
You even have to interview old classmates?
That's rough.
Tell me about it.
Sometimes clients
can be really difficult.
Hey, Ruan Yu,
I saw the house location
you sent me.
It's very close to Xu Huaisong's
grandma's place.
Xu Huaisong?
[My mom taught]
[Xu Huaisong Chinese for half a year.]
[Would she still remember that?]
[That'd blow my cover!]
Really? What a coincidence.
Mom, when we get there,
do you want to try that...
The name Xu Huaisong
sounds so familiar.
I can't remember at all.
It's okay, Mrs. Ruan.
Don't force yourself.
It's not someone important.
Just remember me.
I remember you.
I'm telling you,
getting older
is no joke.
I used to remember
every kid
in the alleys
and all my old students.
Now, so many
of them have slipped my mind.
It's okay, Mom.
My memory's not so great either.
See? You should
spend less time on the computer.
You two keep chatting.
So, I've safely
delivered Yu
and her mother.
You can rest easy.
Also,
got some intel for you.
In the car,
I heard Mrs. Ruan say
she's going back today
to meet up with some old colleagues.
Not sure if Ruan Yu
will stop by the school.
Something to think about.
Liu, the wingman,
mission accomplished!
Mom, it's raining.
Use the umbrella.
See? I told you.
Young as you are,
sitting at the computer
all day, and you
get back pain at the slightest movement.
What?
Are you as old as I am now?
Message received.
I'll start working out.
Take a look.
Appreciate it while we can.
I just can't bear
to part with these
old houses and flowers.
Back in the day,
your father and I
got married here.
You used to run all over
playing here when you
were little.
Remember?
I loved going there.
And you were chased by two dogs,
remember?
Come to think of it,
your grandparents
were still around back then.
Mom,
the memories are still
here with us.
You know,
we'll have fewer and fewer
chances to come back.
That's not true.
Transportation is so easy now.
I'll get a driver's license.
If you and dad want to come back,
I can give you
a ride anytime.
It's tiring for you to drive that long.
It'd be best
if my son-in-law
did the driving.
Mom,
why do you bring that up again?
I didn't want to
say anything in the car.
Actually, Mr. Liu
already has
a matchmaking date.
So, don't go
bothering him again.
Really?
I thought he seemed
kinda interested.
I thought...
You already asked him,
and he's
a helpful person.
How could he say no?
Now I feel bad.
Alright, it's fine.
If he's taken,
there'll be someone else.
I'll keep looking for you.
Alright,
you take your time.
I'm going to go get some water.
Go ahead.
Let me enjoy the view.
Sure, Mom.
Sir.
What do you need?
Soy sauce.
Over there.
Sir,
which of these two
is better for stir-fry?
The Ruan family, right?
Your parents use this one for stir-fry.
This one works too.
What about for a dipping sauce?
Which is better?
For dipping, let's see.
This one.
This works.
Is it just for dipping?
Can I use it for cold dishes?
Sure.
You can use both for cold dishes.
So...
which of these two
is a better value?
Which one won't stick to the pan?
Let me take another look.
Thanks.
He finally looked at me.
But why does he
look at me like I'm an idiot?
Ten years.
Everything's changed.
Done yet?
Yes.
Sir, I'll take this one.
Coming, Mom.
It cleared up!
That's just how it is down south.
On and off.
It's almost noon.
Let's go grab something to eat.
Sounds good.
What do you want?
You pick.
I'm fine with anything.
In that case,
I'm kinda craving the dishes from
the school cafeteria.
Going to the school cafeteria at noon,
I'll run right
into Xu Huaishi.
Mom,
let's go to that
Zhou's Steak House.
I've been craving it.
You said you were fine with anything.
The more I think about it,
the more I crave those
meatballs from the cafeteria.
They are so good.
And I can
go catch up with
Ms. Guo and Ms. Li.
So looking forward to it.
It's settled. Let's go.
Little foodie.
Eat your jelly.
Let's hit the cafeteria.
Grab the umbrella.
It might
rain again.
That's right.
Let's go.
Being young is great.
I always thought
the uniform was ugly before.
Now I don't even get a chance to wear one.
If you're not young anymore,
what does that make me?
Mom, you're young.
We're both young.
Tell you what,
how about I go borrow
two uniforms from them?
We can change into them.
Maybe someone will
come up and ask,
"Excuse me,
how do I get to the art gallery?"
What did I teach you?
Sharp tongue.
No shame.
Well said.
Ma'am, I'll take three drumsticks.
-Alright.
-Hungry?
Ma'am,
is Mr. Cai
still working here?
Which Mr. Cai?
The one
who used to
update the menu.
Not ringing a bell.
Ms. Zhu,
I'm Mrs. Ruan.
Nice to see you.
Give me two more vegetable dishes.
Okay.
Since we're here,
make up for all the drumsticks
I didn't get to eat back then.
Yum!
Good, huh?
Huaishi, we're leaving.
Brother,
right here.
What's wrong?
Mom, you eat more.
You'd look better with some weight.
You just said
you were hungry and wanted
three drumsticks.
Lost your appetite already?
How can I finish
three all by myself?
[Why is Xu Huaisong here?]
[I just dodged]
[his questions last time.]
[If he sees me sitting]
[in the No.1 High cafeteria,]
[across from]
[his old Chinese teacher.]
[He's going to figure out]
[I went to No.1 High.]
[Then he'll ask me]
[what year, what class.]
[He might remember something he shouldn't.]
You know,
back when I was young,
your father said
I looked like Xue Baochai.
I'll send you the revisions
later.
Okay, bye.
Brother, why are you suddenly back?
Felt like it.
Let's go have hot pot
for winter solstice tonight.
How about it?
Tonight?
I'm busy.
Liar.
You're clearly free.
You're watching me eat.
Who said I came to see you?
Do you have another
sister at No.1 High?
Stop looking around.
Just eat.
It's really good.
I'm leaving.
So soon?
Go back to class after lunch.
Get some rest.
Wait for me.
Yu,
I'm going to see
Ms. Li later.
You go take a walk around.
It's good?
I'll have one.
There you go.
Just eat it if you want.
Knew you couldn't resist.
Down low.
Pass it to me.
Come on.
Defense! Defense!
Left foot, go.
Nice.
[December 21st. Winter Solstice.]
[Sunny.]
[Today I went back to Su City No.1 High.]
Watch out.
You okay, Miss?
I'm fine.
Did I bother your writing?
No, just jotting in my journal.
Don't worry about it.
People still
write in journals these days?
Just jotting down life.
That's so artistic.
Are you a writer or something?
I guess
you could call me a writer.
What do you write?
Romance novels.
So you must be good at dating.
Shouldn't you be focusing
on your studies right now
instead of dating?
Adults say
we can't date
because it'll affect
our grades.
My grades
can't get any lower.
The way you put it is quite...
Honest.
If you can't have good grades,
at least have a good attitude.
If you had neither,
that would really suck.
So does the person you like
like you back?
Like?
I'd be grateful if she
went one day without hitting me.
So that means
you've got
a crush.
Wouldn't have guessed.
Someone like you
having a crush?
Even the most carefree person
gets a little nervous
around the one they like.
Everyone just shows it
differently.
That's true.
So can you tell me
what I should do
when I like someone?
I can teach you
how to get better at Chinese.
I was really good at Chinese
back in the day.
What do you say?
Adults are
so boring.
What's your name?
Zhao Yi.
It's Yi,
not Tie.
Tell her
how you feel
on graduation day.
Mr. Liu.
Ruan Yu.
Sorry,
something came up.
During my site visit,
I ran into two
important clients. I need to
drive them back to Hang City tonight,
so I might not be able to...
Don't worry.
I'll just get two high-speed
train tickets.
Don't
book tickets yet.
There's still
one seat available in my car.
I can drive
your mom back.
It'll be more comfortable for her.
Just be careful
on your way back, okay?
Okay.
Thanks, Mr. Liu.
No problem.
Alright then.
Bye.
Sorry about that.
Mr. Liu,
we don't want to trouble you.
We can just take
the train back.
It's okay.
No trouble at all.
And my boss
insisted that
you two
ride back with me.
Well...
Okay.
Sir, how cheap is "a steal"?
You are finally here!
Any later,
I couldn't have held onto
the good stuff any longer.
You've been waiting for me?
Is it because I'm the only one
who wants to buy it?
Of course not.
As you know, we've been
here for years,
That guy also
came by a while back.
Which guy?
You know,
that one.
Oh,
the one who
fought you over Galactic Empire.
Remember?
Who?
Can't remember.
Alright, take a look around.
We'll catch up later.
Okay.
Talk later, Sir.
See what I need.
June 2013.
That was the month
I was about to become a senior.
Sir, I'll take this one too.
Okay.
Here you go.
Zhao Yi,
you're not coming?
I'll catch you guys later.
Alright, let's go.
What's your name?
We're not in the same class.
I was worried all break.
Siyu, she picked Liberal Arts,
but she's not in our class.
She got put in Class Five.
So we're not together?
I don't know why.
Everyone has their
strengths and weaknesses.
I'm not following the crowd.
My passion isn't in Sciences.
I'll go for
Liberal Arts.
Not too bad.
Now we're deskmates.
We can always go find her.
What do you want for dinner tonight?
Hello, class.
Take your seats.
The Chinese class rep.
Here.
Let's take attendance
and get to know each other.
Ms.
Chen Yan.
Here.
Wang Haolin.
Zhao Tie.
Excuse me.
You're the Chinese rep.
Can't you read?
Is that "Tie"?
That's Yi.
Y-I, Yi.
What?
Chinese reps
can't be nearsighted?
What are you thinking, Zhao Tie?
You spacing out?
Zhao Yi.
Mr. Zhao.
You know, because of you,
my name was
mispronounced for almost a year.
It's too late to fix it now.
Where are you going?
I need to study, okay?
Listen to yourself.
I don't buy it.
Sir, I'm leaving.
Okay.
Yu,
I'm in Mao's
car now.
Take care and be careful.
Keep me posted.
Who are you?
I don't add strangers.
I'm the new cafeteria contractor.
If there's anything you want to eat,
let me know.
My name is Cai.
No wonder they had
the class reps collect
everyone's QQ numbers.
You guys are really on top of things.
You should make more drumsticks.
They're always gone when I get there.
You got it.