[English subtitles are available]
[You are My Fateful Love]
[EP06]
I think we have to talk about
the performance.
Yeah, I think it's a good idea
to talk about it.
So what ideas have you got?
[Honey?]
[Are you... Are you home?]
Ruan Yu?
Yeah, yeah, I'm almost home.
[Okay.]
[You're picking me up at the crossroads?]
[Alright.]
[I'll be there in five minutes.]
[Are you being followed?]
Stay calm.
Head to where there are people and lights.
[Tell him]
[I'm on my way to you right now.]
I'm already heading your way.
I'm almost there.
Uh,
it's okay now, Mr. Xu.
I'm home.
[I guess I just overreacted.]
Glad you're safe.
Get some rest.
I'm already dealing with
those posts online.
Honey?
Are you... Are you home?
Well,
I'm so sorry.
I meant to
call a friend just now,
but I dialed your number by mistake.
What's wrong?
Mr. Xu,
there's
a black van
parked downstairs.
[It wasn't there]
[when I just got here.]
Can you make out the license plate?
Not really,
but it looks like
the kind of van used for abductions.
It's probably not
what you're worried about.
Even if it is,
they won't just break in.
I need you to do two things right now:
First,
send me your location
and your property management
or security office's number.
Second, grab your phone
and check the peephole.
Okay.
Done.
Stay quiet first.
[If you see someone suspicious]
[and they]
haven't made a move,
don't lock the door yet.
Step back away from the door,
turn on speakerphone,
and call my name loudly.
Say you're doing laundry
and tell me to get the door.
Understand?
Understood.
If they don't leave
after you do that,
lock the door immediately
and call the police.
What's wrong?
Hello?
[Sorry,]
[the number you've dialed is powered off.]
Ruan Yu? You home?
It's me, Li Shican.
Shican?
What are you doing here?
Didn't we agree
to meet at our usual spot?
I thought you called me
about your livestream?
You watched my livestream?
Mingying and I were bored
at home the other day,
so we caught your stream.
You two really cared about me.
Can I come in?
I'm kind of worried...
Yeah, of course, come in.
Shican,
I don't have men's slippers here.
Just keep your shoes on.
Still no boyfriend?
You weren't this gossipy
before you entered show business.
Have a seat.
Alright.
Uh...
It's fine, really.
I tune out
everyone else's gossip,
but not yours.
You're my...
most trusted senior.
So you do remember I'm your senior.
Couldn't even call me that earlier.
My bad.
This is my apology gift.
I passed by the shop on the way,
so I grabbed one for you.
Wait, this is the milk tea shop
from the university town!
It's still open?
Here.
Thanks.
Double bean milk tea,
full sugar, no tea base.
Swapped cow's milk for soy milk,
red beans only, no mung beans.
I still have the memo from
when I ran errands for seniors
back in the day,
just without the names attached.
Lucky I got it right, otherwise
I'd be making things even worse.
That's so thoughtful of you.
I don't have much
to offer here,
let me get you a glass of warm water.
Sure, warm water is perfect.
I'm resting my voice these days,
so I'm laying off sugary drinks.
Alright, one second.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Oh, by the way,
is that your car downstairs?
Yeah, that's mine.
It's a mess.
It rained on my drive
from Su City,
got all splashed with mud.
You came all the way from Su City?
You could've just told me
you were doing that for the game.
It's definitely not for the game.
I wanted to see you anyway,
the livestream just gave me
an excuse to call.
There's something
I need to apologize for in person,
I couldn't live with myself if I didn't.
Give me one second,
I need to take care of something.
Sure.
Mr. Xu,
I'm so sorry.
My phone died just now,
so I couldn't
check in with you.
Sorry.
A friend just came over.
You weren't looking at Li Shican.
You just saw him
and got reminded of that Xu guy again.
Mr. Xu?
Hello.
Sorry about that.
Don't check in with me.
Check in with the police instead.
Police?
He's your retained attorney?
Yeah.
I need to take this.
Hello?
[Shican,]
[the cops just arrested me downstairs!]
[Come help me!]
Just a moment, you two.
Thanks.
Let's wait over there.
I'm so sorry.
I overreacted,
and got you and your friend
dragged into this investigation.
My bad.
I should be the one apologizing.
I didn't handle things properly
with Cen Sisi.
She told me
you two were childhood friends?
I'm from Su City,
she's from Hang City.
How could we be childhood friends?
Her dad moved to Su City
for business back then,
so she transferred schools here.
We were classmates for two years,
then went to the same college.
I guess that's why
she thinks we're practically
childhood friends.
She's had
a crush on me for years.
I have a private Weibo account
that follows your Lily Vale account,
she tracked you down through that,
and probably got the wrong idea.
So how did you know I'm Lily Vale?
You asked me
to fix your computer back in college,
remember?
I saw your pen name
on a file name,
remembered it,
and started following you.
You've been hiding it well.
I figured you creators
like to keep your online
and real lives separate,
otherwise it's like
baring it all online.
But don't worry,
I don't stalk your account.
That's why I only found out about this
after I came back to China.
If I'd known earlier,
I would've handled it right away.
Someone's been deleting comments,
and leaking Cen Sisi's
personal info.
Was that your PR team?
I told them to moderate the comments.
I had no idea
about the info leak.
Could it have been done by netizens?
Really?
Either way, I got you into this mess,
and I'll clean it up.
The hype's died down now.
Just focus on your lawsuit,
leave the rest to me.
No need.
This isn't your fault anyway,
and you're swamped right now.
Don't waste your time on this.
I have a lawyer handling it for me.
Oh, by the way,
I saw your
lawyer's letter was signed
by Zhikun Law Firm.
Is Mr. Xu
with Zhikun?
Yeah.
Is he reliable?
Don't worry,
he's extremely professional
and experienced.
Finally found you,
Xu.
Looks like you've found her too.
Did you find
your Hanazawa Rui?
[Mr. Xu,]
[I'm so sorry about today.]
[I made you worry for nothing.]
[Mr. Xu,]
[have you read the document?]
He hasn't replied to a single one.
Well, fair enough.
Anyone would be upset
after being messed around like that,
especially when the police got called.
Plus,
he's super busy to begin with.
Or maybe
he just hasn't seen them?
[Mr. Xu,]
[have you been busy these past two days?]
[When will you have time]
[to go over the case with me?]
[In ten minutes.]
[I'll go turn on my computer.]
[No need.]
[I'll be downstairs]
[at your place in ten minutes.]
No need to rush.
Sorry to keep you waiting,
Mr. Xu.
[All because of a silly mix-up,]
[the great Mr. Xu]
[didn't reply to a single word from me]
[for two days.]
[How dare I keep a big shot like you]
[waiting even a second longer?]
Get in. We're going to the firm.
Well,
what are you doing near my place?
On the way from the airport to the firm.
[On the way from the airport to the firm?]
Thanks for picking me up.
Hello?
Ms. Zhang?
Got it, I understand.
Mr. Xu,
Ms. Zhang ran into an emergency
on a case at the construction site,
I have to head over there.
Then drop my luggage off
at my apartment once you're done.
Sure.
Should I get a taxi?
Or we can talk at my place?
We can do it another time.
I'll head back to the office first.
No, it's totally fine. This way please.
Watch the steps.
[He's only mad at you for two days,]
[and look at you groveling like this.]
[Oh shoot.]
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Just a moment.
Come on in.
Sorry,
I don't have men's slippers here.
Just keep your shoes on.
That's where I sat
for my videos earlier.
A friend was over just now.
Can I
get you something to drink?
Coffee's fine.
Is instant okay?
Alright, have a seat.
[I was so focused on]
[not wasting his trip,]
[I forgot about the jet lag.]
[I should've told him to go home.]
Mr. Xu...
Sorry,
I fell asleep.
Hello?
I just fell asleep.
Haven't eaten yet.
Bye.
You haven't eaten?
Do you want to go get something first?
It's too hot out.
Then should I order takeout?
You don't eat takeout.
How about I make you something?
I have food at home,
we can make do with what we have.
If it's not too much trouble.
It's no trouble at all.
Come to the kitchen,
see if there's anything you want.
With the ingredients we have,
I can make sandwiches or pasta.
Whatever you prefer.
This one.
Your stomach
hasn't fully adapted to Western food yet.
How do you want it cooked?
Fried.
Go sit in the living room for a bit.
[These aren't really good for frying.]
[He probably wants]
[Su-style lard rice cakes.]
You know,
I swapped it
for Su-style lard rice cakes.
You probably
don't get to eat these often abroad.
Thanks.
How did you know
I'm from Su City?
I looked it up.
There are news articles about you.
Why did you look into me?
Just
basic background
on my attorney.
I also know
Mr. Liu is from Hang City.
Eat up
while it's hot.
Alright.
[He's eating so politely.]
[Does he like it or not?]
Want some?
I'm good.
You eat up,
I'll go wash the dishes.
[Well, his appetite sure isn't polite.]
[The frying turned out great today.]
Are you full,
Mr. Xu?
I haven't read it yet.
Have you been busy these days?
Haven't checked WeChat either.
[So he wasn't ignoring me on purpose.]
[I knew it.]
[He wouldn't be that petty.]
Hello? What's up?
The cat food is in the
lower cabinet in the kitchen.
Yeah.
Just do whatever you think is best.
First off, he has a cat.
Second, he doesn't bathe
the cat himself.
So
who does?
Are you saying
there's someone else at his place?
He has a girlfriend?
He could just
take the cat to a pet groomer,
but what you're saying
is definitely possible too.
Ruan Yu,
I need to sleep for a bit.
What,
you're sleeping here?
How about...
Hey...
He fell asleep that fast.
Being a lawyer
really is such an exhausting job.
Mr. Xu,
you've barely been in the office lately.
It's been half a month
since we last saw each other, right?
Want a tea egg? My treat.
No, thanks.
I overate last night,
still haven't digested it yet.
What did you eat
that's still sitting with you this long?
Fried lard rice cakes.
How fancy of you.
Naturally, it's a Su City specialty.
Making fried rice cakes for yourself?
Nice.
Actually, I didn't make them.
What's the story?
Ruan Yu made them for me.
Who?
Ruan Yu.
Why would she
make you fried rice cakes?
What's going on between you two?
Is it weird for a client to make
fried rice cakes for their attorney?
Are you kidding?
What client? What attorney?
Since when do clients make
fried rice cakes for their lawyers?
Depends on the client,
and the attorney.
How so?
Well, it can't be an attorney
who's getting ahead of himself.
Being likable is a gift, after all.
Now grab your bag.
It's time for work.
Did you just insult me?
I swear you did, but I have no proof.
[When are you gonna update?]
[My comfort read,]
[please come back soon.]
What writer doesn't get writer's block?
This time's different.
The male lead's based on someone I know.
How am I supposed
to keep writing like nothing's wrong?
[I'm convinced the author's innocent now.]
[Just curious, is this book]
[really based on her real life?]
[Same here.]
[This whole thing blew up so bad.]
[Does the real-life male lead]
[even know about it?]
Anyone still working at this hour
must be the elite of this city.
[Mr. Xu,]
[I got your email.]
[Thank you for working]
[on my case so late.]
[Just killing time]
[while I get over my jet lag.]
[If you're still up,]
[we can go over the case.]
[Sure. Video call?]
[Voice call is fine.]
Sorry,
hold on one second.
I need to go grab a document downstairs.
Alright.
Mr. Xu?
I'm here.
Well,
is it raining where you are?
It's pouring right now.
Guess we're
under the same rain cloud then.
I'm back.
Alright.
Let's
start with the third section.
This part is about
the female lead, who's scared of thunder,
caught in an art museum by heavy rain.
She overhears the male lead playing piano,
and it calms her down.
[This isn't in]
[the other novel at all.]
Do we need to bring this up?
The descriptions of
the piano room in both novels
are actually quite similar.
All piano rooms
look pretty much the same.
Did you forget?
Forget what?
Did you forget
to switch to WiFi?
[Your connection seems bad,]
[I can barely hear you.]
I already switched.
It's good now,
I can hear you clearly.
Alright, let's keep going.
In the next section,
the female lead publicly turns down
a male classmate who's been
harassing her,
telling him to stop
disturbing her studies.
The male lead
sees this,
and he won't disrupt her studies either.
So he never confesses
his feelings to her.
Right, I checked, The Poet
hasn't written about
why the male lead
never confessed yet.
This part won't be called a trope copy?
But this trope
is a bit unreasonable.
[Is my writing that unreasonable?]
But the biggest worry for high schoolers
is their studies.
What other reason
would the male lead have
for not confessing?
Not every high schooler
is that lucky.
I was being too absolute.
Will this trope
affect the lawsuit?
It's fine,
I'm just giving you a heads-up.
You still need
to keep updating your novel,
so if you sort out your train of thought
and resume updates soon,
it'll help turn the public opinion
around for the better.
Yeah.
The rain stopped.
It's pouring so hard.
I should've never come
to feed the cats today.
[Is that him?]
[Xu Huaisong,]
[your bright,]
[untainted boyish charm]
[cleared up every single]
[rainy season]
[of my youth.]
Hello? Dad.
Alright, I'm coming out now.
The rain stopped here too.
Let's keep going then.
Alright.
Ruan Yu?
What's wrong?
I'm so sorry,
I accidentally fell asleep
last night.
Why didn't you hang up?
I must've fallen asleep too around then.
Alright,
I'll hang up then.
What's that noise?
An ambulance.
Why is there
an ambulance siren?
I'm at the hospital.