[English subtitles are available]
[You are My Fateful Love]
[EP07]
What's that sound on your end?
An ambulance siren.
Why is there
an ambulance?
I'm at the hospital.
Mr Xu, what happened?
I have a stomachache.
Nothing serious.
Get some rest.
Hope you feel better soon.
What are you two doing here?
You look a lot better.
Does your stomach still hurt?
No.
No? Then eat something.
There.
Okay.
I'm not hungry.
You need to eat.
Ambulance sirens?
Mr Xu,
why are you listening to that?
Nothing.
Just trying a new kind of music.
That's rare.
Never heard of
anyone switching to
ambulance sirens.
What,
life is too boring
so you're looking for a thrill?
Mr Xu,
Ms Ruan is here
to see you.
Let her in, please. Thanks.
How did Ruan Yu know you were hospitalized?
Huaisong,
you sly fox.
I thought you were
chasing thrills.
Turns out you're chasing a girl.
Take the thermos away.
You can eat it yourself.
I'm taking it now?
Yeah.
How could I
know you skipped lunch?
You didn't tell me.
I didn't tell you?
I sent you a WeChat message.
You must've sent it to the wrong person.
I never got anything.
[Bring me some porridge at noon.]
[Room 106, New District Hospital.]
[So that message wasn't meant for me.]
[Do I go in]
[or not?]
I want my porridge now.
Fine.
I'll go get some.
Ms Ruan?
Mr Liu,
are you going to buy porridge?
How did you know?
Please, come in.
Ms Ruan,
what brings you here?
Mr Xu,
your porridge.
That message was meant for Liu Mao.
I sent it to you by mistake.
I'm really sorry
-  for the trouble.
- It's okay.
Mr Xu,
I didn't know you were sick.
Otherwise,
I never would've
kept you on the case so late last night.
It's fine.
[At that time,]
[he wasn't even admitted yet.]
[On the way to the hospital,]
[he kept staring]
[at signal bars,]
[afraid the call would drop.]
[In case he woke others up,]
[he didn't turn on his mic.]
[Love does make one act like a fool.]
Mr Xu,
are you feeling better today?
Not really.
Huaisong,
you need to
take good care of your stomach.
Do you know
the stomach is sensitive to emotion?
When you're in a good mood,
the pain will be gone.
Ms Ruan,
you're a writer, right?
You must be great with words.
If you have time,
come keep him company.
Better mood,
faster
recovery.
It's an old issue.
Don't trouble her over it.
How is that troubling her?
Not at all.
I'm already here,
and I don't have other plans today.
You heard that?
She's so considerate.
Alright. Thanks.
Why are you eating it like that?
That's how we do it in Su City.
All locals eat porridge this way.
How did you know
I'm from Su City too?
I looked into it.
It's in your WeChat profile.
Ms Ruan,
you're here to see Mr Xu too?
Mr Xu,
didn't you just say you weren't...
Alright, alright.
Drop it.
We should get going.
Still got work back at the office.
Gotta go.
Oh right, Mr Xu,
I just saw
the email you
sent at 3:00 AM.
I'll send the files to you right away.
[3:00 AM?]
[Xu Huaisong said]
[he fell asleep too,]
[so he didn't hang up the call.]
You mean I was sleepwalking
at 3:00 AM?
What he means is...
You probably dreamed it.
Yeah.
I sent it to you, remember?
- I sent it to him.
- Really?
I sent it.
Let's go.
See you.
Seriously?
Have a seat.
Wait, Mao,
that email was definitely from Mr Xu.
After all these years,
you still can't
read between the lines?
Think about it.
Come to think of it,
Ms Ruan does act weird
when Ms Ruan's around.
Like the day he got back.
He made me put on that act
about Ms Zhang being in trouble.
Then I called to ask
when to pick him up
but he said he hadn't eaten.
He really is a sly fox.
Mr Xu, you finished eating?
Yeah.
Okay.
Thanks.
It's nothing.
Get some rest.
I should head back.
I've sorted out and brought along
the plagiarism
rebuttal files.
Take a look when you got time.
Okay.
Can you hand them over?
Here.
Thanks.
[She made you fried rice cakes]
[and visited you in hospital.]
[She's clearly got a thing for you.]
[Why not make a move?]
[You might have a shot.]
Mr Xu,
I'll get going then.
Alright.
Okay. Have some rest.
Wait.
There's always
been a chapter missing
from your document,
Chapter 23.
Huaisong?
Yu,
would
you like...
Can I
take a look?
No.
Why?
It's a
transition chapter.
It has to be important.
It's...
It's not that important.
I'll decide
after I read it.
Right now?
Right now.
Have a seat.
Mr Xu,
I didn't bring the original file.
It should be in the website backend, right?
[How does a male lawyer]
[know so well about the novel website]
[for female readers?]
Mr Xu,
the signal in here is terrible.
I'll send it to you when I get home.
The hospital has Wi-Fi.
Password is 66668888.
I just sent it.
I should get going.
Mr Xu, what's wrong?
Is your stomach acting up again?
I'll go get a doctor.
I'm fine, really.
I've just been straining my eyes,
and they hurt.
[Wasn't he]
[admitted for stomach pain?]
My eyes are bothering me.
Could you read the original for me?
Thanks.
What?
I still remember the plot posted
by The Poet online.
Just read your original.
If there are no overlaps,
then we can wrap this up.
[Sure, no problems for you.]
[I'll be the one in big trouble.]
No need, Mr Xu.
I've already checked it.
That chapter is clean.
The most dangerous place
is often the safest,
and vice versa.
The more convinced you are there's
no problem, the more likely there is one.
[It's fine, it's fine.]
[It's the female lead's dream.]
[Not mine.]
[It's just]
[a romantic scene.]
[I can survive the embarrassment.]
Chapter 23.
He Shiqian...
He...
Never mind.
I'll read it myself later.
Okay.
Mr Xu, I gotta go.
Bye.
[Huaisong,]
[which ward are you in?]
[Mom and I are coming to see you.]
Mom, here we are.
Stop eating so much candy.
You're not a kid anymore.
And start using floss.
We came for a dentist appointment.
Where are we?
Mom, you're already here.
Just go in and check on Huaisong.
He's sick.
This is exactly
when he needs family around.
I've told you
I don't have a son.
He is not my family.
Oh, come on.
Don't be upset. Don't talk like that.
Go in by yourself if you want.
You lied to me.
Mom...
Huaisong.
Let me take a look at you.
What happened?
Are you okay?
You look so pale,
like you're on your deathbed.
If you can't say anything nice,
just shut up.
Why did you come alone?
Mom's really worried about you.
She's just been
swamped with work
these past few days.
So she asked me to come
check on you.
Mr Xu,
I forgot something.
Come in please.
Who's that pretty lady?
Not worried about me,
but interested in a pretty lady?
Sorry.
Thanks.
I'll head out now.
Miss?
Hi.
I'm the little sister
of this difficult but handsome guy.
I'm Xu Huaishi.
Hi, I'm Mr Xu's
client.
Client?
Let me guess.
You must be
Ruan Yu, right?
How did you know?
Huaisong mentioned you before.
He said he's been working on a case
for a writer named Ruan Yu.
You look like someone
who's well-read
and cultured.
I figured it out right away.
Can't believe Mr Xu has
such a sweet and cute sister.
Huaisong, you should
reflect on why she's so surprised.
I didn't mean it like that.
It's fine.
Everyone knows what he's like.
If Mr Xu
were half as sweet as you,
he'd probably
double his client list.
Lawyers win cases
through competence,
not by being smooth talkers.
I don't know
if being sweet would
get him more cases,
but it would've kept him from being single.
[Doesn't he have a girlfriend?]
Well,
even if pigs flew,
he'd still remain single.
He's been
single for 28 years.
I'd like to remind you
spreading others' personal information
could constitute a violation
of personal data rights and defamation.
I'm not spreading anything.
Spreading is when you tell lots of people.
I only
told Yu about it.
She won't tell
anyone, right?
Of course.
Your secret is
safe with me.
Then go wash
some fruit for this lady
as hush money.
On it.
Please don't bother.
I'm just here to grab my things.
You're leaving?
No trouble at all.
I'm gonna have some fruit too.
How about this? I...
Let me wash the fruit instead.
I need to wash this lunchbox anyway.
You're too kind.
It's fine, really.
Let me help you.
No need, no need.
Close the door.
What are you doing?
When you're with her,
don't say anything you shouldn't.
Huaisong,
I'm on your side.
Think about it.
With just a few sentences,
I let her know you're still single.
If she thought
you had a girlfriend,
even if she liked you,
she wouldn't dare take a step forward.
Stay out of grown-up business.
If I don't step in,
how much longer are you going to wait?
Mr. Big Shot Lawyer,
why are you and Yu
still stuck as
client and attorney?
Have you ever thought about that?
I know exactly why.
Because
she doesn't know I recognized her.
Wrong.
It's because you two
haven't seen each other in years.
You don't know
if she still has feelings for you
or if
she'll fall for the real you.
You're not sure,
so you don't make a move.
You're afraid you'll scare her off
if you move too fast.
Let's put it this way.
Knowing how to win a case
doesn't mean you know love.
Knowing love doesn't mean you know women.
You might understand women,
but you don't know sin²x
plus cos²x equals one.
You're just being annoying.
You're just
a high schooler,
yet here you are
teaching a 28-year-old man how to date.
You think that makes sense?
You can underestimate your rivals,
but never underestimate
a Gen Z girl.
I'm done talking to you.
I'm going to
bond with Yu.
Don't say anything reckless.
Let me help you.
It's fine, I've got it.
I insist.
Let me stem the cherry tomatoes.
Yu,
Huaisong specifically
told me to keep busy
and talk less,
or I'd annoy you.
He's pretty considerate, right?
He's a little too considerate.
Honestly,
I really enjoy talking to you.
Who do you like talking to more,
me or Huaisong?
It's different.
Talking to you makes me happy.
Talking to him makes me feel at ease.
He's incredibly professional
when we discuss the case.
What else
do you think of him?
What do I think?
Well,
writers like to create
character archetypes.
What kind of character
would he be?
If he were a character in a novel,
he'd be
the handsome, aloof,
elite type.
[Good news.]
[His cold and aloof image is still intact.]
Yu,
you're so pretty.
I bet lots of guys like you.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No.
Then what kind
of boys are you into?
No, men.
Sweet-talkers, just like you.
[Crap.]
[I played my part too well.]
[But even without my help,]
[Huaisong]
[is sharp-tongued and never sweet.]
[Is he already out of the game?]
Huaishi,
where did you come from?
Su City.
You're attending high school there?
Yeah.
I'm studying in Su City No. 1 High School,
just like Huaisong did.
Yu,
how's that case you
entrusted to him going?
The hearing is coming up soon.
Are you running into any trouble?
We're missing
one piece of evidence we'd planned on,
but it shouldn't affect anything.
[That must be]
[the purchase agreement]
[I was supposed to submit to the court.]
[But the whole thing was made up.]
[I can't fabricate]
[transaction records.]
[Submitting false evidence is illegal.]
Yu,
don't worry.
If you need help, just go to Huaisong.
He's the best.
I'm back.
Huaisong, have an apple.
I'm good.
Just give one
to her.
Yu, have one.
Thanks.
Can we add each other on WeChat?
Huaishi.
Sure.
Show me your QR code.
Let's keep in touch.
Mr Xu,
I won't disturb you any longer.
Get some rest.
Thanks for the apple.
Thank you for the porridge.
I'll head out.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Take care.
Huaishi,
what did you say to her out there?
You don't even like apples.
Big ones,
small ones,
red ones, or green ones,
you don't like any of them.
That's because what you really want
isn't an apple.
Stop talking in riddles.
You don't get it.
Huaisong,
you've still got a lot to learn.
It's fine. No rush.
Take your time.
I gotta go. Bye.
Red apples and green apples?
Bye.
What's wrong with red apples?
[Wrong.]
It's because you two
haven't seen each other in years.
You don't know
if she still has feelings for you
or if
she'll fall for the real you.
You're not sure,
so you don't make a move.
You're afraid you'll scare her off
if you move too fast.
Hello, Huaisong?
It's me.
You're discharged?
[Yes.]
[I want to ask you something.]
What were the red apples
and green apples
you mentioned earlier
all about?
Took you
long enough.
But it's not too late.
Cut the crap.
Get to the point.
I asked Yu today
what her type is.
What did she say?
She said...
What?
I'm a bit tired.
She said she likes someone sweet-talking.
She likes someone sweet-talking?
But here's
a friendly reminder.
I don't think
you should overdo
the cold and aloof act.
I think what she actually likes is...
Is what?
Is...
What is it?
I'm thirsty.
Alright.
Your water, please.
Both cool and sweet-talking.
Both cool and sweet-talking?
Can someone
actually be both?
I know
it's quite difficult.
But
I know someone
who's a perfect example.
Who?
Huaishi's Romance Class is now in session.
Guaranteed results, affordable fees.
One-on-one coaching.
Only 666 yuan.
Transfer's done.
Who is it? Tell me.
You remember
when I asked you for money
to go to a concert?
Yeah. And?
Shican has
this incredibly versatile
stage presence.
When he plays the guitar and sings ballads,
he looks both elegant and aloof.
Ballads?
- That's right.
- Elegant.
- Aloof.
- Exactly.
Like this.
Like this?
No, like this.
How are you so bad at this?
Then what should it look like?
- Like this.
- Like that?
This is aloof?
Correct.
When he raps
and dances,
he looks fierce and cool.
Fierce and cool?
Fierce. Cool.
- Fierce.
- Cool.
No.
No?
Fierce.
Cool.
Like this?
Yes, yes.
- And this?
- Exactly.
Just like that.
You're a natural.
- It's nothing.
- Besides,
And when he meets fans,
he's incredibly kind
and sweet.
You're so charming!
What should I say to sound cool?
Say something sweet.
Sweet?
Something sweet?
Your hair looks great.
You're so hot!
Good job.
Now
you can look up
his videos online
and really study him.
So who exactly
have you been talking about?
I forgot to introduce him.
His name is Li Shican.
Li Shican?
So let me get this straight.
The money I gave you
was spent on this guy?
And now you want me to copy him
to win over Ruan Yu?
That's right.
And while you're at it,
remember the Rule of Six Hearts,
a caring heart,
a patient heart, a loyal heart,
a sincere heart,
a devoted heart,
so she can see your true heart.
You have absolutely no heart.
Check your phone.
Why did you cancel the transfer?
Not just the transfer.
Your allowance for next month
and the month after
is gone too.
Wait, you...
It's ridiculous.
[Stop the gossip.]
[The fact]
[that Lily Vale wrote this story]
[means she's totally]
[over that guy]
[from her past.]
[Why else would she name]
[the male lead He Shiqian?]
[The name means]
[celebrating the passing of time.]
[One will learn to move on eventually.]
[It's just that there's no going back.]
Hello?
Wanna grab a drink?
Are you trying to
kill yourself?
You were just hospitalized yesterday
for stomachache.
[One will learn to move on eventually.]
[It's just that there's no going back.]
Hello?
Did the alcohol get your tongue?
You've been
drinking in silence since I got here.
Do you know what time it is?
I keep regular hours
and take care of my health.
I'm already feeling sleepy.
If you won't talk, I'm out of here.
Stop drinking.
Say something or I'm leaving.
Talk about what?
Your blind date?
Oh come on,
that's what this is about?
How many times do I have to tell you
that blind date was over
before it started?
In less than five minutes,
she became my client.
And you
fried rice cakes
with her
and made video calls
across time zones.
How could you
never say
a word to me?
What's the point of that?
If you don't tell me anything,
how am I supposed to help you
figure out if there's still a chance?
What's standing
between you two?
Just spit it out.
You're killing me here!
If I told you,
your jaw would hit the floor.
Try me.
What kind of
jaw-dropping story could
possibly shock
a thirty-year-old man?
In that case,
you fell for her
before you even got a good look
at her face.
Why...
Why didn't you just
tell her you liked her back then?
You know what my family was
going through at that time.
Get out of this building.
Your family are a bunch of
parasites.
What did you just call me?
I'm talking to you,
accomplice to a murderer.
So what's your plan now?
I don't know.
I'm not afraid she never liked me.
I'm afraid she did.
I get it.
Unrequited love isn't the worst part.
The worst part is
finding out years later
that you two
could've
been together.
The male lead
in her novel is named
He Shiqian.
He
means "to celebrate".
Shiqian means
"as time passes, things change."
So the name
means celebrating the passing of time.
Dude,
this is real life,
not some TV show.
You can't just write
"ten years later"
on a line
and move on like
nothing ever happened.
I don't think
Ruan Yu has zero
feelings for you.
But have you heard of something called
a phantom crush?
What is it?
Let me tell you a story.
I have a friend
who fell for
a girl right at
the start
of college.
But neither of them ever
made a move.
Right before graduation,
someone told him
that she'd liked him all along.
And then?
He went all in
and chased her.
Then they got together.
But once they were together,
he realized something was off.
They didn't
know each other at all.
All that time
they'd been in love,
they were just
in love with the idea
of each other.
That's a phantom crush.
He told me later
when he was
chasing her
like crazy,
he was actually
driven by the fear
of regret and
obsession.
He thought
if he didn't go for it,
he'd miss the chance.
After he cooled down and they broke up,
he regretted it.
He wasn't being rational.
They could have
stayed perfect in
each other's memories.
But he shattered all of that
the moment he
acted on impulse.
So I'm just trying to say
sometimes
having regrets isn't a bad thing.
Chasing it might
give you a different kind of regret,
right?
Think it through
before you act.
Right. Act.
Act?
I said all that,
and you just heard one word
'act'?
Hello?
Where are you going?
I'm in a cab.
Back to your apartment?
To her place.
To Ruan Yu's place?
What are you doing?
I just told you
to stay calm.
What's gotten into you?
Are you going to confess?
He hung up on me?
[In that case,]
[you fell for her before you]
[even got a good look]
[at her face.]
Sir,
has the Galactic Empire
comic come in yet?
Sorry, you missed it.
Someone just borrowed the only copy.
The good-looking guy over there.
Judging by the uniform,
he's from your school.
Why don't you go talk to him?
Looks like he's asleep, though.
Never mind.
I'll wait till he finishes
and borrow it after.
Alright.
There's nothing better than
dozing off over
your favorite comic on a sunny
weekend afternoon.
Life
should be full of
happy moments like this.
Exactly.
[Do you have any idea]
[how much pressure]
[I'm under now?]
[No, I don't.]
[Why did you have to]
[throw away our perfectly]
[good life?]
[Why did you have to]
[take this case?]
[It's my job.]
[I'm a lawyer.]
You're not
the only lawyer in this city.
Everyone else turned it down.
Why did it have to be you?
[Can't you just try to understand me?]
[You dare say]
[I don't understand you?]
[After all these years?]
[Have you thought about the kids?]
[Have you thought about us?]
[You're being unreasonable.]
[What if every memory of joy]
[is swallowed by grief?]
[I must search.]
[Even if the endless powdering of stars]
[in the Galaxy makes the quest seem hopeless,]
[and even if I must do it alone.]
[This line from Galactic Empire]
[is for you,]
[a stranger who read the same comic as me.]
[Life]
[can be bright]
[and carefree,]
[or it can drag you down]
[and leave you lost.]
[Should the bitterness consume you,]
[keep seeking]
[and creating moments of joy.]
Come on.
Xu Huaisong, you've got this.
You can do it.
Don't touch it. You'll cut yourself.
It's fine.
I'll clean it up later.
Well,
Mr Xu, just leave it.
I'll take care of it.
A cloth and some tape.
Got it.
Mr Xu.
This type of bowl
doesn't break into shards, right?
What if it does?
It's done.
Mr Xu,
go wash your hands and eat.
Okay.
Mr Xu, give it to me.
No need. There are shards on it.
That way.