I’m sorry I threw it away.
I’m back, Khao.
New.
Chad.
Thank you for today.
About the banner, I mean.
Som-O.
This gold is yours.
Without you, I wouldn’t have the drive I need to compete.
You’re always so over the top.
A television drama adaptation from the original Chinese novel A Love So Beautiful written by Zhao Qianqian
Do you feel lonely, Mr. Sassawat?
A little.
Since you call me every day, I don’t feel lonely anymore.
Urgh! Why do you keep making cheesy comments?
Hey, do you have an afternoon class?
Are you busy with school lately?
I’m going home this weekend.
Are you going with me?
I don’t know.
New, why don’t you say hi to our friends? You haven’t seen them for some time.
Hi, New.
How are you doing?
Will you be discharged from the hospital soon?
I need to stay here for some time.
The doctor said at least seven days.
Seven days?
Chad.
New.
Get well soon.
Thank you.
Chadjen, do you want to try wearing a nasal cannula?
I’m kidding.
Take it.
It’s my thanks to you.
Without you, I wouldn’t have the drive I need to compete.
Hey.
Chad.
Chadjen.
Why don’t you tell me what’s going on?
So I would know what I need to apologize to you about.
You, jerk.
I’m back.
She’s back.
- Hello, Dad and Mom. - I miss you so much.
Let me hug you.
The food is ready.
- Have a seat. - Mom, why do you cook so many dishes?
You can’t find food tasting like my cooking at your college.
I miss your cooking so much.
This is my way to get you to come home.
I have to warn you not to praise her cooking too much.
Otherwise, you need to pack her food back to the dorm.
Dad.
Do you remember when I praised that her green beef curry was delicious?
After that, she kept making green beef curry.
I had eaten it for several days.
Dad, how could you nag Mom like that?
Let’s eat.
Dad. Mom.
I have something to ask you.
Sure.
While you were dating, had you ever been mad at each other?
Of course.
Your dad was mad at me a lot.
Why do you ask us about it?
Are you…
No, Dad.
Are you secretly dating?
How can she have time to date?
She can do it because she’s living away from us.
I don’t trust you.
Dad, I’m not a kid anymore.
You don’t need to be overprotective of me.
If I had a boyfriend, I would have spent the weekend going on dates.
But I chose to come home because I miss you so much.
Right, Mom?
Fine. Don’t get caught by me.
When was the first time I was mad at her?
It started when we first dated.
I knew that your mom was very popular among men.
Because I was pretty.
Oh.
When I knew that she was approached by a man, I was mad at her.
I was mad at her.
She was popular.
Tofu, your favorite.
Give it to me.
You should come home often.
Hello.
I have something to talk to you.
(What?)
Did you notice that Chad was acting strange today?
Yes.
Do you know why he is mad at me?
How would I know it, silly?
What should I do?
Som, is there something between you and Chad?
(I can sense it.)
What do you sense?
Why don’t you look back and see if any strange moments happened between you two?
When New is in the hospital, I’m worried about him and want to take care of him.
I feel shy talking about it.
(Som, look at me and New. We were friends.)
But we are now dating.
It’s not strange.
Strange moments?
No, I don’t think so.
Fine if you say so.
Then you have nothing to worry about.
I’m hanging up. Bye.
Bye.
(New, I think there’s something between Som and Chadjen.)
(Huh? Really, Khao?)
(Why don’t you look back and see if any strange moments happened between you two?)
There are a few moments like that.
Maybe…
Silly.
Khao, you came early today.
Of course. I know you are lonely so I hurry to see you.
Thank you.
Who will take care of you after you are discharged from the hospital?
If my dad is not busy, he will stop by to see me.
That’s not good enough.
Your wound is not fully healed.
It will be healed soon. I’m doing fine.
Here.
I think I should move in with you.
Do you think it’s a good idea?
We are not married.
Silly.
You are sick. So I’m going to move in to take care of you.
But I think both my dad and your mom will oppose it.
Why will they oppose it?
We are not doing anything bad.
I mean we are still working hard at school.
You are sick and I’m just taking care of you.
That’s a good thing, isn’t it?
That’s true.
If you are afraid to talk to your dad about it, I’ll do it.
I think he will be okay with it.
Come on. Don’t you trust me?
It’s not that I don’t trust you.
Eat it.
Don’t worry about it.
It’s delicious.
Do you want to eat it?
I have been thinking about me and Chadjen for two days.
Today, I’ll ask him why he is mad at me.
One more thing.
I also want to ask him about that.
About what?
About that. Don’t make me say it again.
That’s good.
I encourage you to talk things over with Chadjen.
Stand up.
Now.
Why?
Are you going to wear the uniform to meet him?
Why? What’s wrong with the uniform?
I think if you do your hair and wear a cute outfit.
You look more mature and much prettier.
Really?
It’s time to transform Som-O into Cinderella.
It’s good that you came to visit me.
I haven’t seen Khao today.
She said she was going to see Som-O.
Chadjen.
Huh?
Khao said she’s going to move in with me to take care of me.
Do you think…
if it’s a good idea?
Good for whom?
You?
If it’s good for Khao.
I’m worried if other people find out, they may view her negatively.
You shouldn’t be worried about what other people think.
But…
Khao is doing this for you.
(Are you free this evening?)
(Can you come to meet me at the park? Don’t stand me up.)
(I have an important thing to talk to you.)
I got to go.
See you.
Thank you, Chadjen.
Chad.
What are you looking at?
You look different.
I’m just the same. You will get used to it.
Are you going to wear heels every day?
Nonsense.
Let’s walk.
See?
Let’s go.
(Training camp of Thai national team in South Korea)
Khao, can I talk to Som?
(If you want to talk to her, why don’t you call her?)
I called her but she didn’t answer it.
(Som said she is working in the studio with her friends.)
(She probably forgot to take her phone.)
Really?
(She probably comes back to the dorm late.)
(If you have a message for her, you can tell me.)
It’s nothing.
How is Nerd?
Is he fully recovered?
(He will be discharged from the hospital soon.)
Okay.
Please take care of him.
Chad.
Chadjen.
What?
This is hardly a stroll.
It’s like you’re walking away from me.
You still manage to catch up with me every time.
But it’s exhausting.
Do you have to be so cruel?
Are we still talking about the stroll?
We’re talking about my being in love with you.
(This fool finally realized how I feel.)
(This time, he will give me the answer, won’t he?)
(I just hope the answer is worth the long wait.)
Khao.
Are you ready to go home?
Yes.
Don’t you have class today?
I don’t have any class in the afternoon.
So I hurry to come to see you.
New, sit down. I’ll help you pack your bag.
It’s okay. I’m fine.
I can do it.
I’ll do it.
Where is your dad?
He’s on his way.
I made up my mind.
I’ll talk to your dad that I will move in to live with you at your condo.
Are you sure?
Yes.
If I wait for you to do the talk, we will probably graduate first.
If I didn’t have you, I would have had a hard time.
Thank you so much.
It’s okay It’s not a big deal.
Dad.
I…
What?
Who will take care of him after he is discharged from the hospital?
I’ll do it.
I can go see him in the morning and leave in the evening.
I need to ask you to take care of him when he is at the college during the day.
Or should you move back home?
No, Dad.
It’s far from the college. I don’t want to bother you.
It’s not a big deal for me.
How about this?
I’ll take care of him.
(Khao.)
Oh.
That will be great.
Your dorm is close to his condo.
You can go visit him often.
But there’s one thing I’m worried about.
Do you feel uncomfortable to do that?
Not at all.
You are a woman.
If you often come to visit him at his condo,
people may gossip about you.
I’m worried about that.
You don’t need to worry about it.
I won’t go to his condo alone.
Som-O and Chadjen can take turns to come with me.
Really?
That’s great.
I’ll go get the car and wait for you at the entrance.
See you.
Give me his bag.
Thank you.
See you.
You didn’t help me talk to your dad.
See? I told you that my dad would oppose the idea.
You can’t move in with me.
Then we don’t have to tell him.
Are you serious?
Yes.
Let’s go.
Here.
What do you want to tell me?
I’m going to give an update.
I talked to Chad.
I asked him why he was mad at me.
I also asked him what you have asked me.
So what happened?
What did he tell you?
He didn’t say anything.
You got me excited for nothing.
But…
He…
He kissed me.
Really?
Yes.
I’m happy for you.
But…
Does this mean we are dating?
Khao, stop it.
Stop teasing me.
Is this real?
You will know it.
Know what?
You will know what you need to do next when you are dating.
I have a tip to tell you.
What tip?
In our college, there is a sacred bridge for lovers.
Why don’t you ask Chadjen to go ride a bike there?
It’s believed that if a couple rides a bike and crosses the bridge without their legs touching the ground,
Their love will be long-lasting and it proves that this is a true love.
Did you do it?
Of course.
Why would I tell you if I haven’t done it?
How was it? Was it hard?
No. You just ride a bike as usual.
If you can cross the bridge, it’s done.
Do I need to lift my legs high?
I don’t think you need to you that.
Your legs aren’t that long.
Khao. How can you say that?
Hey.
Have you ever heard the myth about the sacred bridge for lovers in our college?
No.
It’s said if a couple rides a bike and successfully crosses the bridge
without their legs touching the ground
Their love will be long-lasting and it’s a true love.
A myth?
Who told you?
It’s believed that if a couple rides a bike and crosses the bridge without their legs touching the ground,
Their love will be long-lasting and it proves that this is a true love.
I think love is about two people.
The bridge has nothing to do with it.
You ride the bike.
You have to cross the bridge.
Come on, Chad.
Fine.
Chad.
Get on.
I’m getting on.
Hold on tight.
I’m doing it.
Don’t forget.
Your legs cannot touch the ground.
You should worry about your legs.
Why do I need to worry about them? My legs are short.
One, two, three.
Don’t let your legs touch the ground
Keep going, Chad.
Keep going. Keep going.
Don’t stop.
Chad, watch out for the rock.
Don’t let your legs touch the ground.
Chad. No.
Stay still.
Som, did your legs touch the ground?
No. Not at all.
I’m lifting my legs.
We are almost there, Chad.
- We’re almost there.
We’re almost there.
We made it, Chad.
Chad.
We made it.
Well done.
Did your legs touch the ground before we crossed the bridge?
No.
Did your legs touch the ground?
Are you sure?
Yes.
So…
Shall we do it again?
- Sure. - Shall we?
Sure.
Where are you going?
Your record is getting better.
If you keep doing well until you get a gold medal, it will be great.
What’s wrong?
I have something to ask from you, Dad.
Say it.
Can I go back to Thailand before the competition?
Are you crazy?
How can you leave the training camp before the competition?
It’s very important to me.
What’s more important than the competition?
Is it about a girl?
Can I go back for two days?
I’ll improve my record to 48 seconds.
The Asian record is 48.49 seconds.
Are you saying you can break the record?
If I’m going to be a champion, I want to be a memorable one.
I’m not kidding.
Fine, I’ll give you two days.
Don’t forget to keep your promise.
Yes, Dad.
Yes, Coach.
I’ll keep my promise.
Sometimes, it’s good if athletes have inspiration.
Som told me you would come to have a meal with us this weekend.
So I did my best to prepare the food.
Please enjoy it.
We haven’t had a meal together like this for some time.
We usually have a meal just the two of us.
It’s so lonely.
Chadjen, how are you doing?
Are you busy with school?
I’m doing okay.
Chadjen is doing well.
He will graduate from the med school soon.
Look at Som.
Mom.
Here is steamed egg, your favorite dish.
Som, how is school?
Do you enjoy it?
Yes, I do.
Is there any guy hitting on you?
I thought you weren’t listening.
I’m listening.
If a guy is hitting on you, you need to tell me right away.
You can’t choose a random stranger to date.
Don’t worry, Dad.
Chadjen is keeping guys away from me.
Is that true, Chadjen?
Yes.
Now, I am relieved.
If there’s a guy hitting on her, you need to tell us right away.
Sure.
Are you here to study or to sleep?
The library is cold.
Hey.
Can you turn the page for me?
I don’t want to take my hands out of the blanket. It’s cold.
Can’t you do it yourself?
I’m cold.
Hey.
Do it again.
Did you finish the page?
Yes.
Hey.
Aren’t you cold?
Do you want to share the blanket with me?
The blanket is too small for us.
It’s big enough for us.
The rabbit print is perfect for you.
It’s okay. You can use it.
Take it.
Didn’t you say you are cold?
Everyone, please come to take a look.
Come on, come to take a look at my photos.
Come on in.
Please come to take a look.
I proudly present this photo.
I named it “The Ultimate Shipped Couple.”
How is it? Don’t they look cute together?
I secretly took the picture.
The Ultimate Shipped Couple?
Why aren’t there any photos of our couple?
Here they are. The couple in the photo.
Does the photo look great?
The photo is cute.
Don’t you think?
You think so?
How is it? Does it look cute?
He must feel shy.
Khao.
Chadjen is mad at me.
Let’s get back to my photos.
Follow him.
Go.
Hey.
Chad.
Chadjen.
Are you that mad about the photo?
If people get the wrong idea, you may be negatively affected.
Are you that worried about it?
Or are you embarrassed if people know you are dating a mess like me?
Let go of me. I’ll take the photo down.
You don’t need to do that.
Everyone already saw it.
Forget it.
Let’s go back to our dorm.
Come on. Let’s go back to our dorm.
Fine.
Why are you so mad about it?
Hello. What’s up, Tao?
I saw the photo.
It’s not some kind of prank you, is it?
No.
Good.
Tao, I have something to tell you.
What?
Chad and I,
(We are dating.)
Congratulations, Som.
Thanks…
I got to go. Coach calls me to practice.
Bye.
(ONE WEEK LATER)
Come on, Khao.
- Hello, Chadjen and Som-O. - We are here.
The competition is over?
See? We missed it.
Tao won.
I tell you the result.
Khao, it’s because you took so long to make your hair bun.
Let’s eat.
Calm down.
Do you want another bite?
I won the gold medal for all Thais.
Thank you, everyone, for cheering on me.
Tao, do you have anything to say to your special someone?
Dad.
I’ll break the record.
That’s it?
Why didn’t he say anything about us?
He must be nervous. He only talked about Coach Yut.
This is strange.
Tao won. That’s a good thing.
Let’s take a selfie and send it to him.
Good idea.
Do you see the screen?
Khao, come closer.
Okay.
(Congratulations. We are celebrating for you.)
I look really cute in the photo.
Tao must be happy to see it.
Don’t I look cute?
So cute.
I told Tao that I am dating Chad.
Huh?
I have another thing I want to tell you.
I’m moving out to a dorm outside the campus.
Som.
Do you want to move in with me?
When you study late, you don’t have to worry about the dorm’s closing time.
Som lies to her parents that she moved to live with me.
If they find out, it will be a disaster.
Your dad is here.
What are you doing?
Why aren’t you wearing any clothes?
You should be fully clothed when you…
(We are going to visit you at the condo.)
My parents are coming here.
Dad.
There is no secret in this world.
If I tell them the truth, they will separate us. I’d rather keep lying to them.
Chadjen, Som-O, I have something to tell…
Damn it.
Did you call Chadjen?
So do you have a girlfriend?
I’m living in a condo.
Are you living with a girl?