The serial killing shaking the public, known as The Eye of Horus Murder Incident.
May 5th, when a new crime was predicted,
I encountered a person who seemed to be the suspect and barely escaped death.
Makoto! It's me, Makoto!
In such an extreme emergency,
I'm asking what you were doing!
Don't take the scoop she risked her life to get!
When nobody can remain calm,
the eyes of suspicion turning toward him...
Does that mean that the suspect stabbed another woman with blood type A before slashing you?
Unfortunately, there's a high possibility that the 5th crime has already been committed.
I'll protect you.
His true identity, gentle and warm, that only I know...
It's Hiroki who is the most dangerous ex I've ever had.
The 5th crime had happened after all.
Could this be an injection mark?
An injection mark?
The person who doesn't know the truth... maybe me.
Wow, he is here already.
It's too early.
Matsuoka, are you sure this is the 5th incident of The Eye of Horus Murder Incident?
What's wrong?
Hey, what's going on?
You smell good. It's soap.
Are you hitting on me?
You have high self-confidence.
I think so. The details will be investigated from now on.
Have they found new evidence?
That's yet to come.
If the DNA from Tsutsui Makoto's wound matches the DNA of this victim...
I said we’d investigate that from now on.
Please let me know if you find out anything.
Thank you for your hard work.
You're already here.
This is the 5th incident, after all.
Please let me know later if the police lecture about this incident.
What? Are you leaving already?
Hey, Tsutsui,
Ah, Mihashi,
I always share info with you, but when you got a scoop, you keep it all to yourself?
That's not true.
Then, why didn't you answer my call?
The 5th victim is Kanbe Kyoko, 42, working at an advertising agency.
Kanbe lives alone and was believed to be killed between 8 pm and 9 pm on May 5th.
Based on the scene and the method of the crime, it has been concluded that this is the 5th incident of The Eye of Horus Murder Incident.
This is the place where Kanbe was killed.
And this is the spot where Reporter Tsutsui was attacked by a suspicious person after 9 pm on the same day.
They're very close to each other.
Yes, and the DNA detected on my clothes and the wound...
The forensic analysis confirmed that it matched Kobe Kyoko's DNA.
Based on this fact, it has been confirmed that a suspicious person who attacked me is the suspect of The Eye of Horus Murder Incident.
Okay! It's our exclusive scoop! A viewer rating will skyrocket!
That's inappropriate.
Since the length from my wrist to my elbow is 23 cm, I believe the suspect must be at least 175 cm tall.
That's a bit of a roundabout way of saying it.
Wait, it's fine. You should proceed with caution.
The suspect looks like a man.
I can't say for certain, but I also think the suspect is a man.
Good job. It's better not to jump to conclusions quickly.
Being tall doesn't mean they're men, right?
That's a compliance issue, right?
Noda was way too excited.
Because your show has a lot more info than the other shows.
But even though it's an exclusive scoop, there still aren't many clues about the suspect.
How's your wound? Does it still hurt?
No, it's healing nicely.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm fine.
Because we can't hold hands.
You don't have to walk me home every day.
I know you're happy, right?
Something like that.
Makoto, you're the only witness, and you were actually attacked by the suspect.
That's true, but...
The suspect knows who you are.
But..
Since your place and my place are in a straight line, so it's not a big deal.
Wait a second.
I don't know where your place is located.
Have you finally noticed?
You don't intend to invite me to your house, and moreover, you don't intend to tell me your address, right?
My place is small and messy.
I'm talking about the address!
I'll tell you that one day...When I moved to the big house!
Fine, I'll tell you my address...Next month.
I'm just kidding. I'll tell you it once I clean my place up.
Don't follow me!
Come on!
I'll go home by myself!
Why are you laughing?
What? Don't you have time to come to my place today?
I have to finish the manuscript by the end of today.
I see, good luck. See you.
You can go now.
You first.
Everybody tells lies.
The lies I've built up to stay with you will eventually hurt you one day.
If I could rewind time,...where should I start over from?
Koi wa Yami (Love is Darkness)
What the hell is this?
The suspect's knife, gloves, and the sneakers were identified!
We identified the suspect's weapon and gloves.
Show me!
Damn it, it's matched...
Episode 5
What's going on?
The suspect's knife, gloves, and the sneakers were identified!
By Sagara Hiroki
He beat us to it again.
What the hell is he?
How is he able to know such things?
The police haven't even made an announcement.
He must have analyzed them from the footage Makoto filmed, right?
I wonder if a freelance journalist is even capable of that kind of thing.
Well, they usually have wide networks.
Oh no, Shitara is wearing the same sneakers as the suspect!
It says that he was also questioned by the police last month.
Makoto, did you know that?
No.
I didn't know you had the same sneakers as the suspect.
You're not the suspect, right?
What would you do if that were true?
I'll do an exclusive interview with you.
I'll kill you if you accept the interview with other sources.
I'm scared because you seem like you'd do it seriously.
That's right. I'll do anything for a scoop...Just like you.
Here's the reward for last month's scoop prize.
Thank you.
By the way, what happened to the Rolex watch I gave you?
I'm sorry, I sold it.
Well, since it's a gift for you, you can do whatever you want with it.
Don't worry, I sold the watch, but the love from you is kept safe.
Your talking skills have gotten worse.
That's harsh.
However, I pay you well enough, I don't think you have any money problems.
What are you spending so much money on?
Ah, a girlfriend?
And you're serious about her, so even those expenses can't be claimed as business expenses?
It's a secret.
The identified knife and gloves are quite common and widely available on the market.
So, it hasn't helped narrow down the suspect.
What about Shitara Kanji's trail?
His whereabouts are still unknown, but he was captured on a security camera near the crime scene on the day of the incident.
And we've got many more eyewitness reports of a man thought to be Shitara Kanji near the crime scene.
Then, Shitara Kanji is the suspect.
By the way, the forensic autopsy found a needle mark on the arm of Kanbe Kyoko, the 5th victim.
The arm was slashed to conceal the needle mark.
In all 4 previous cases, there was a large slashing near the inner joint of the arm that was different from a defensive wound.
Since there was no sign of drugs in the victim's body, I think the suspect may have taken blood from them.
For what?
The suspect may take it home as a trophy.
The suspect is a total weirdo.
Could you take a look at this?
This is a delivery notice found in the mailbox of Shitara Hiroki.
Upon investigation, I found that he ordered syringes.
Bingo! The piece came together!
The mastermind may be the son, Shitara Hiroki.
How did you get this delivery notice?
If it turns out that you conducted an illegal investigation, it'd affect the police's credibility.
Let's assume the father and the son are cooperating.
Kanji was captured on camera, and Hiroki bought the syringes.
Can you tell me which one is the mastermind?
But...
Capture Shitara Kanji as soon as possible! Dismissed.
Please wait!
Moron, it's obvious you'd get rejected if you confront them so directly like that.
There's no way the top would shift the investigation from Kanji to Hiroki so easily.
But it's too obvious...
If Hiroki is the suspect of The Eye of Horus Murder Incident, then there's a possibility he was the suspect from 10 years ago.
They don't want to admit now that Shitara Kanji was innocent.
They want to make Kanji the suspect no matter what.
Even though that's true, it doesn't make sense not to investigate Hiroki in this incident.
The suspects who killed more than one person are divided into 2 types, organized and disorganized.
Many organized-type suspects who commit well-planned incidents are hedonistic killers.
They repeatedly kill people with murder as their sole purpose.
It's the pleasure they once experienced. They do that again and again...
I'm sorry I made you cook.
It's okay since I wanted to check how sharp the knife was.
You read a difficult book.
Don't touch it.
Ah, I'm sorry.
Makoto, it's for you.
Thank you.
Hasegawa, it's for you.
The investigation of the stabbing incident of a female lawyer in Tachikawa city
Hiroki was the first person to discover Shitara Kumiko's body.
He was under suspicion as a suspect during the investigation.
But Hiroki denied it.
The lack of physical evidence such as the murder weapon made the investigation challenging.
However, the situation changed dramatically after Kanji, her ex-husband, started to confess.
The murder weapon was found exactly as Kanji described, and he was arrested.
Who sent this to me...?
The suspect is the son, Hiroki...
2-1-6, Nishikihara, Tachikawa city, Tokyo
Shitara Kumiko
Hello, Hiroki. You don't have to come to pick me up today.
I have somewhere to go.
Makoto!
You're early today.
Yes. Are you going to an interview? I'll go with you.
Ah, it's fine. Let's go home.
Okay.
Are you making tomato-based pasta?
Yes.
Yeah! It's my favorite food!
Hiroki, you're good at cooking.
But I can only make simple dishes.
I do it my own way and roughly.
However, this tomato-based pasta is the only dish from my mom's recipes.
My mom was a busy person, so she didn't cook much.
But she occasionally made tomato-based pasta for me.
It was very delicious.
I wonder why it was so tasty.
Makoto, prepare the plates.
Makoto?
Ah...Something is different.
It's tasty.
Something is different. Why's that?
Hiroki, I'll do my best.
What? What happened all of a sudden?
From tomorrow, I'll be fully active and find the suspect.
Let's eat!
Wait, I should add something.
That's fine. It's tasty.
I may add soy sauce...
Stop, don't do that. If you make a mistake, there's no way to redo it.
But I should add something...
Ah, what? Are you Hiroki?
Ah, hello.
What are you doing here?
I'm here for an interview.
I see.
Are you okay if someone sees us together?
No problem.
I'm the one who invited you.
I see.
Makoto is too considerate.
And Masakiyo doesn't see me unless I'm with Makoto.
Well, because he may have no reason to meet me alone.
You love him, don't you?
But he loves Makoto.
It's obvious, right?
It's a complicated love triangle.
It's a love quadrangle.
I see. I'm involved too, right?
They're both insensitive.
So, the relationship between Masakiyo and me has always been just friends.
It's comfortable, but to be honest, I want to get out.
Makoto told me that you take her home every day after work.
I can't hide anything.
Yes, so be careful.
I'm glad Makoto is fine.
She is the one who can push herself to work despite her fear, even after experiencing that.
I think when she says she is fine, it's not just pretending to be strong.
Makoto never be discouraged.
What do you mean?
Generally, once we get hurt, the wounds never fully heal.
No matter how much time passes, the things you've experienced once never disappear.
It may fade, but it can never be completely gone.
That experience chases me endlessly like a shadow.
I want the suspect to experience the same thing.
Even though they atone for their crimes, they can never truly start over.
I wish they lived forever haunted by the sins they committed.
I'm sorry for talking about such a dark topic.
That's fine. I think so too.
I'm not the right man for Makoto.
But I've decided to protect her.
Aoi, why don't you try asking him out on a date?
I won't let him have Makoto, no matter how much he loves her.
What the hell? I wish somebody would say that to me even though it's just once.
Tsutsui Makoto
I've been looking for footage of the suspect from security cameras,
but there's no luck so far.
Speaking of the devil?
She is looking for footage of the suspect.
I should join her.
Thank you for a coffee.
You're welcome.
See you.
Damn it. There're security cameras everywhere in town, but why can't I find the suspect on any of them?
I think the police have already collected most of them. So, it's not easy.
If I had captured the suspect's face more clearly at that time...
You never be discouraged...
Thank you.
Would you like to check this camera?
Excuse me.
I'm from JBC TV.
Assault?
Yes, the suspect arrested for theft claims that he was assaulted by Shitara Hiroki in Ushigome-Yanagi cho.
Arrest him before me! Leave me alone!
He was suddenly dragged into a back alley and had his neck injured with a knife by Shitara Hiroki.
This may be it.
If his testimony is true, we can take Shitara Hiroki here voluntarily.
Just voluntarily...
Ah, it's them.
We can't tell if he has a knife from this angle.
Damn it...
I see, so that's how it is...
No luck. There's nothing on the video.
What?
I saw something...Here!
This is...
Yes.
What's your relationship with this man?
He is the one whom I interviewed in the past.
He was a member of a special fraud group.
I chased him and wrote an article about him, and it seems that he has held a grudge against me.
Charge
Fraud
It seems that he's been wandering around me since he was released.
But since I have a lot of enemies like that, I didn't know who he was at first.
I think you're very smart.
Because you understand the camera angles.
In this shot, you seem to have a knife.
Give me a break, I didn't have a knife.
But I was panicked at that moment.
I don't care if he attacks me, but he was targeting her.
Are you talking about Tsutsui Makoto?
Yes. I noticed a suspicious man following her on this main street.
And this happened.
I think he tried to attack Makoto to get revenge on me.
Are you saying you did this to protect her?
Yes.
By the way, have you seen your father recently?
Ah, the police are keeping an eye on him, right?
I'm also looking for him.
Makoto.
Where's Hiroki?
He'll be out soon.
What's going on?
I can't say anything.
Makoto, where were you and what were you doing around 7 pm on April 26th?
Interview @ Ushigome-Yanagi cho
2 pm - 8:30 pm
Ah, I was doing an interview in Ushigome-Yanagi cho at that time.
I was handing out flyers and keeping an eye out for any suspicious people.
I see, he was telling the truth...
What's going on?
Nothing. See you.
Wait.
Do you think Hiroki may be the suspect of the incident from 10 years ago and now?
How did you know that?
Was that why you sent me those materials?
Those materials?
Nothing.
This is the security camera footage from the night of the incident on May 5th.
I believe the person in the footage is Itsuki.
Ah, this is me!
Amazing! I'm impressed that you found me in such a brief moment.
Just to confirm, what were you doing here?
I was doing deliveries.
Well, the order came in at 7:58 pm, and it was delivered by 8:45 pm. Check this.
Here?
I'm sorry for asking you to come here. You must be surprised.
Don't worry, I'm excited. I feel like I'm in the detective drama.
But it's a tough job to do deliveries in that heavy rain.
You should take a day off on days like that to avoid getting injured.
You're too overprotective.
Am I?
People order deliveries, especially on rainy days.
You're such a nice man. I'll give you candies!
Damn it, I don't have any! Sorry.
I gave you the last candy!
It's his fault.
Don't worry.
I now know the police actually do conduct interrogations.
It was a questioning.
Itsuki, wait!
Please take this!
Rice balls. You may be hungry later.
Are you all right?
I don't think Itsuki is the suspect.
He must have been doing deliveries. I feel guilty.
However, we must check all possibilities.
You shouldn't have any preconceived ideas, no matter who the person is.
So, what happened?
Ah, somebody I interviewed in the past held a grudge against me.
He picked a fight with me the other day.
Again? I told you to reconsider how you interview people.
I want to get scoops.
That's not a good excuse.
Who is it?
This is Tsutsui.
I'm Hanamura. Sorry for the sudden interruption.
It's fine.
We watched your show the other day.
Ah, thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm totally fine now.
I see. I'm glad to hear that.
Well, I'm sorry I couldn't capture the suspect.
We're really glad you're safe. Thank you.
Thank you for your kind words.
Please feel free to use our interview video if it can be helpful for anything.
Are you sure?
I'm sorry I was too emotional at that time.
It wasn't your fault at all.
Thank you for saying that.
Shitara sent us letters many times as well.
He said that he really wanted to express our anger and grief to the suspect.
We had lost all motivation to fight.
I felt somewhat relieved knowing there was somebody who continued to hold the anger for us.
We'll contact Shitara again ourselves.
Ah, he is here with me.
Shitara speaking.
I'm sorry for bothering you repeatedly.
Yes. Thank you.
Excuse me.
Are you crying again?
No, I'm not.
I didn't know you wrote letters to them.
Why did you not tell me that? That's why...
That's why?
Nothing.
Say it!
No.
Are you blushing? You're so cute.
I'm not!
Listen, I just got questioned by the police.
What? Why?
Because...Ah...
The other day, that weird forensics guy...
Hey, my ginger pork had 7 g less meat than his.
I'll have you banned from here.
That's totally customer harassment, right? And I'm just a delivery worker.
Matsuoka is a weirdo.
He is part of the privileged class.
What do you mean?
Please keep in touch.
I'm still working. What's up?
I want to ask if you'd like to have dinner with me somewhere tonight.
I see, by the way, are you with Makoto now?
No.
She hasn't joined you yet.
I want to go out with you alone...
What do you think about Makoto lately?
Makoto seems to ignore the suspicious things about Hiroki.
I'm worried about her.
Are you jealous?
What? Nothing of the sort.
It's about time you express your feelings to her.
If you don't express your feelings to her properly, she'll never notice them.
But I feel like now is the least suitable time for that, more than ever.
I guess so, she is only focusing on Hiroki right now.
You don't have to say it so clearly.
I do because I'm not backing you up at all.
You're so harsh.
So, can we go out for dinner tonight?
Sorry, I still have a lot of things to do. Some other time.
Okay, see you.
Did you tell her?
Did you tell her about Hiroki's creepy story?
Not yet.
Kinoshita
I got some amazing info
What about it?
There was a needle mark on the body of the 5th victim
A needle mark?
The suspect drains blood and keeps it as a trophy
What the hell is that?
Are you sure you pay me this much money?
Yes.
Yes. All you have to do is to keep quiet about the fact that I found that footage first.
Hey, can everybody collect some blood?
Is it easy to collect some blood even though one isn't a medical professional?
Well, if somebody practices...
But in principle, everybody shouldn't do that.
What's wrong all of a sudden?
Ah, it's something work-related.
Listen, Makoto,
What's wrong? You scared me.
More than 10 years ago, Hiroki worked part-time as a security guard at this hospital.
So, we started dating.
At that time, I was still a new nurse, so I practiced collecting blood on him at home.
Then, he said he wanted to try collecting blood himself.
So, I taught him how to do it, and he started practicing seriously.
He kept practicing on me again and again until he became good at it.
As a result, my arms were full of bruises.
It's weird, right?
Since he was my type, I tried not to think too much about it,
but thinking about it now, he was a dangerous man.
You're his girlfriend, right?
It may be none of my business, but getting involved with him may be dangerous.
Why did you break up with him?
Because he was suddenly unreachable.
He quit his part-time job, and I didn't know his address, so our relationship just faded away.
But after that, he became the No.1 host in Kabuki cho.
A host?
I'm sorry. You must be shocked.
I think Hiroki cares about you very much.
However, you're a very important person to me, too.
Hiroki is a reliable man, right?
Please don't tell this to anybody, especially Masakiyo.
See you.
Ah, Hikaru?
Hikaru?
I remember him. He was desperate.
What do you mean?
He was obsessed with money.
He stole clients from senior hosts without hesitation. He was fearless.
I warned him that such behavior is taboo in this world and would eventually be killed.
How long had he been working here?
It was less than a year.
He suddenly stopped showing up at work.
I heard that Odaka from Weekly Shinryu picked him up.
Do you know any customers who were close to him?
Ah, I remember him. He was a nice man.
He was thoughtful and had a good sense of humor.
I spent a lot of money on him.
But when I became his regular customer, he asked me for blood.
At first, I thought it was a joke.
But he brought out something that looked like a blood-collecting set.
Because of my job, I've been dealing with various people, but that was scary.
I was horrified.
Please wait a moment.
Thank you for your hard work.
Chief, was there any new info?
Nothing. Sorry.
Me neither.
My only info today was that the victim was a bully in the past.
When was that?
When she was a junior high school student.
There was a former classmate who held a grudge against her, and she made me listen to her bullying story for an hour.
She really wants me to broadcast her story.
It'd be better if that had happened a few years ago, but that woman is already 42 years old.
It's pointless to bring up an issue from almost 30 years ago now.
This issue has nothing to do with The Eye of Horus Murder Incident, right?
Really? We don't know whether it's related or not.
People can't erase any part of their past.
If a single drop of a foreign substance falls into clear water, no matter how much pure water you add, it'll never return to be clear water.
No matter how nice a person seems, his past sticks to him and won't go away.
Do you think this bully issue has something to do with The Eye of Horus Murder Incident?
I don't agree with you.
The past and the present are different...for sure!
Makoto?
I'm sorry. I'll be out for a while.
I'm going to stay at the office tonight, so you don't need to pick me up.
Did something happen?
A colleague who was supposed to edit the show for tomorrow got sick, so I'll take over her work.
I see. Do your best.
Hiroki, where are you now?
I'm at a cafe editing my article.
It'll take a little longer.
I see.
Hiroki,
Even for you, it must be hard to stay overnight at the office on such short notice.
Maybe it is.
Ah, yes, it's about the other day,
Tomato-based pasta, I remembered that my mom added mayo as a secret ingredient.
It tastes completely different. You'll be surprised.
I'll make it tomorrow, so please try it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Good night.
I'm his friend. I accidentally left my belongings in his room.
He told me to let you know what happened and ask you to open the door.
If necessary, I can call him and...
You were on TV the other day, right?
Yes.
Yes, that was you. I saw that show.
You have a strong sense of justice.
Thank you.
Wait a moment. It's Shitara's place, right?
Please let me know when you're finished.
Thank you.
What are you doing here?
Next episode
After all, it was all lies.
Why can't be analyzed within the police department?
How far have you reached the truth?
Don't do things on your own.
You keep in contact with your father, right?
You drive me crazy.
Are you prepared to come to our side?
Somebody will die in episode 6