On April 28th, the defendant
was first assaulted
by Iteya Minamoto, correct?
But you didn’t report it to the police.
-Was that because--
-I felt angry.
What?
I felt angry…
at myself for not leaving him
even after he hit me.
Did you sleep with that lawyer?
Did you sleep with that lawyer? Answer me!
Answer me! Where did you do it?
Answer me!
Iteya?
Wasn’t the training camp
running until tomorrow?
It ended early…
He saw me as a woman
who could be subdued with violence.
That thought made me feel humiliated…
and furious.
Sorry. Morning.
Morning.
Were you okay last night?
What?
The guy.
He was waiting for you, wasn’t he?
The man who attacked you…
Are you sure you didn’t see his face?
If I did, I’d have caught him by now.
Damn bastard chose a spot
with no security cameras.
Why bring that up now?
Here.
Understood. I’ll revise it right away.
Thanks.
Kajin Sensei…
your face…
Did you switch foundation?
No…
Is it heavier than usual?
Not at all!
You look more beautiful than ever.
I just wanted to know the brand!
Excuse me.
INCOMING CALL
ITEYA MINAMOTO
BLOCK CALLER
BLOCK ITEYA MINAMOTO?
YES - NO
YES
ITEYA MINAMOTO HAS BEEN BLOCKED
Hello?
I’m sorry about last night.
I didn’t mean for it to happen.
I'm in front of your apartment.
I want to see you.
Let’s forget it ever happened.
I don’t want to see you.
I’m really sorry…
Why…
did you do that?
Because you were with that guy…
the lawyer.
Mr. Konno?
Where were you with him?
What were you doing?
I told you. I was meeting a client.
He was there too, wasn’t he?
Was he the one you slept with?
Why does it matter who I sleep with?
I’m not your wife!
You made me this way.
I did?
When I wake up…
I think of you first.
When I sleep…
I dream of you.
You’re…
all I think about all day long!
I love you so much…
So why won’t you love me the same?
Who’s really to blame?
Don’t you…
have a home to return to?
You don’t get it, do you?
How it feels to leave youand go home.
All you want is a physical relationship.
Do you even try to imagine…
how much I’m suffering?
Don’t yell!
Did you…
attack Mr. Konno?
It was you, wasn't it?
It wasn’t me.
Ayame.
Did it hurt?
It’s over…
between us.
If you come again…
I’ll call the police.
You'd like to speak with us again?
Yes.
I’m Kajin from Naganami Law Office.
Please make three copies of this document
-before this afternoon's meeting.
-Got it.
No. Five copies please.
Understood.
Turning him down…
feels like I'm punishing myself.
Iteya?
Will you be home late again tomorrow?
Why?
I will finish work early.
I thought we could eat out.
We haven’t gone out together lately…
I’ll be late for a while.
The new students have night practice.
Oh… okay.
Yes?
POLICE DEPARTMENT
You said you wanted to
confirm something again?
You last saw the deceased, Okutaro Nada,
four weeks ago, correct?
Yes.
Are you sure that’s not a mistake?
What?
Is there any chance you met him
on the night he died?
Why would you ask that?
We haven’t found his phone yet,
but your number was in his call log.
It says you spoke
at 8:52 p.m. that night.
That night…
INCOMING CALL
OKUTARO NADA
Hello, Professor?
You were trimming his nails?
I did that sometimes at his office.
Why is this one nail left undone?
I was just about to finish that one when…
My husband came home
earlier than expected.
So that explains…
Did Yoko Mogami know about your visits?
The professor wanted it kept secret.
Why didn’t you tell us from the start?
It could put you at a disadvantage.
Even if I had told the truth,
I thought I’d still be a suspect.
It’s always been that way,
since I was little…
But I didn’t…
kill Professor Nada!
Do you believe Kanon Minamoto’s story?
She and her husband
provided alibis for each other
during the estimated time of death.
Could they be accomplices?
It’s possible.
Man, I’d totally fall
for a woman like that…
She’s not the only liar here.
Yoko.
No work today?
If you take too many days off,
it puts me in a tough spot.
I recommended you, after all.
The police called me in.
About Professor Nada.
You’re the one who…
If I was, I wouldn’t be standing here.
By the way,
the detectives said
they haven’t found his phone.
You wouldn’t know anything?
Why would I?
Maybe ask your husband first?
Still obsessed with him, huh?
There's something about you two
that would make the police suspicious,
right?
Are you two… really in the clear?
Excuse me.
You look down, Kajin Sensei.
Everything okay?
So what’s the guy like? The new one?
Not that you care.
Of course, I care.
Wait.
Is he hotter than me?
-Maybe.
-Really?
Is it someone I know?
Nah, can’t be.
But watch out.
I get fired up when there’s competition.
Kajin Sensei.
You have a visitor.
You were trimming Professor Nada’s nails
that night?
I told the police everything honestly,
and I think they understood the situation.
But I still wanted to consult you first.
That’s up to the police to determine.
Sorry.
I’ve been blamed for things my whole life.
I'm worried…
You’re… the only one I can turn to…
The autopsy results should be out soon.
Do you like orange carnations too?
Yes.
I love them too.
They're gentle and strong.
Just like you.
I’d love to thank you somehow.
How about a manicure?
That’s really not necessary…
You must be tired.
At least let me massage you.
Yeah?
It’s not much,
but it’s the only way I can repay you.
I’ve already received the lawyer fee.
How are things… with your husband?
No issues?
Sensei,
do you think I’m an idiot?
Huh?
I love you.
That’s what orange carnations mean.
You want last week’s schedule
for Mr. Minamoto?
Yes.
He said he had night lessons for a while…
No, he went home early.
I see.
It's over…
between us.
INCOMING CALL
YOKO MOGAMI
Yes. This is Kajin.
Thank you for…
Really…
Kajin!
-I’m so glad you came.
-Likewise.
Thank you for inviting me.
I'm always treating you terribly.
Please accept my apology.
-I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
Is this… okay?
Professor Nada’s case is still…
There’ve been strange rumors
and speculation about Nada, right?
That’s exactly why I thought
we should have a setting like this.
It’s a lot less formal
than a press conference, right?
-Director.
-Yes?
Let me introduce you to everyone.
Tough place to be, huh?
I respect Yoko.
That’s not what I meant.
See?
I invited him to apologize
for treating him like a suspect.
Mom… reluctantly agreed.
You came…
So that means you’ve forgiven me
for suspecting you?
If you believe in us… right, Iteya?
Yeah.
Thanks, my precious friends!
Let’s grab a drink over there.
Yeah.
Even if he killed Dad…
could you still love him?
What?
So, all the strange rumors
about my husband’s death
are all completely false.
With the truth behind my husband's death
still unknown,
I find myself in the midst
of a most difficult situation.
For the women enduring hardship
and for this country,
I am committed to doing everything I can,
with sincerity and an unwavering resolve.
Let me introduce
a highly dependable individual
who will walk this path with me.
Attorney Ayame Kajin.
Kajin, please come up.
She was my husband’s most trusted student
and a powerful ally to women like us,
who face many challenges.
Yeah! Go, women’s ally!
Kajin, would you say a few words?
I’m Ayame Kajin.
I’ll do my best to live up
to Ms. Mogami’s expectations.
Oh, is it raining?
It's raining! Please go inside!
Please come in! Hurry!
Jeez…
Let go of me.
You want some?
Sitting here like this…
brings back memories.
That side of you… suits you better.
I saw it,
that photo of you.
You looked beautiful.
ITEYA MINAMOTO
BLOCK ITEYA MINAMOTO?
NO
What are you going to do…
about your wife?
Just…
give me a little time.
I love you.
The people from Choga Construction
should be arriving soon.
-I’ll go check the conference room.
-Please do.
Wait. Excuse me.
Excuse me. Don't walk in uninvited.
I told her to wait…
Could you give us a moment?
What is it today?
I have an important meeting.
I can’t talk for long.
This office smells lovely.
But… for some reason,
it makes me want to vomit.
Did you know
some fruit seeds contain cyanide?
You’d have to eat a lot
to die from them, apparently.
Have you ever heard of that?
What are you trying to say?
Why Iteya?
You’re beautiful…
stylish…
successful…
So why?
He’ll…
probably never change.
If you truly care about him,
you should think…
long and hard.
So you’re saying
divorce is the best option?
There it is. Calling me an idiot again!
What's that?
It’s my charm.
No! Don't!
Hey!
Wait!
What's going on?
Give me that!
Stop it! Let me go!
Lawyer.
It doesn’t… have to be Iteya, right?
He’s all…
I have…
You’re off the Choga Construction case.
We're almost in the second half…
Please let me complete it.
I’m truly sorry.
You really think I can trust you?
A reckless lawyer
who fools around with clients?
I don’t want to see your face
for a long time!
About you, Kajin Sensei…
I’m disappointed in you.
Yes, understood.
Mr. Nada’s phone still hasn’t turned up.
He used it just before he died.
Someone definitely took it.
Maybe the killer.
Must’ve had
something seriously incriminating on it…
The autopsy report is here.
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
What is it?
What is it? Come on!
Okutaro Nada died of neck compression.
But the murder weapon
wasn’t the belt of the robe.
It was the same electrical cord
used to bind his wrists and ankles.
So they strangled him with the cord
then wrapped the belt of the robe
around his neck after?
Why stage it like that?
Maybe there were two culprits?
One who strangled him with the cord
and another…
who wrapped the belt.
Two murderers?
This is Nikawa.
Yes. Yes.
Yes.
Understood!
Looks like money was wired from
Nada’s account to an overseas account
around the estimated time of death.
And it was ¥5 million!
Five million? To whom?
TRANSFER ¥5 MILLION
FROM OKUTARO NADA TO JUN NADA
PROCEED WITH TRANSFER?
YES - NO
TRANSFER COMPLETE
Kanon is gone.
What?
She’s not here.
Come…
be with me.
I love you.
And so…
I lost everything.
I decided not to go.
He's waiting at home.
I was able to endure
the unpleasant things.
Where were you?
Who were you with?
So,
that's the kind of person you are.
You're sorry that
I'm so into your husband?