=Lost You Forever S1=
(Lost You Forever S1 Special Edition 6)
(Cheng'en Palace)
We've arrived.
Wen Xiaoliu was trying
to escape,
so I slightly punished him.
Stay for a meal together.
I'm a countryman.
It's my first time
seeing so much delicious food.
Please forgive me
if I behave improperly.
I've already asked the chef
to prepare Qingai Cake.
You can eat some
while listening to a story before bed.
I want to eat it
while my mother
tells me a story.
Master.
She's Xiaoyao?
(In fact, you've already
told me who you are.)
(But I was blinded by cruelty)
(and failed to notice it.)
♪For forever accompanying you♪
♪Let momentary sorrow and joy fly♪
(Break his leg.)
Xuan.
Does it hurt?
Take good care of him.
(If I had kept my promise)
(to pick Xiaoyao up in Mount Jade,)
(Xiaoyao wouldn't have been lost.)
Xiaoyao.
I'm going back to Zhaoyun Peak.
You have to go back, anyway.
No matter how hard the journey is,
I'm no longer embarking on it alone.
I decided to be the Princess of Haoling.
Are you doing it for me?
Not entirely.
Because I think
being a princess is not completely bad.
(Grandmother.)
(Father.)
(Mother.)
(Auntie. Thank you for helping me
reunite with Xiaoyao.)
(This time,)
(I'll protect
my little sister for sure.)
(Yiqing Garden)
I told Queen Mother
about you in the letter.
She agreed
to restore your look.
Great.
I'll go with her.
What a nice song.
If you want,
I'll make him play
for you.
Who's playing the flute?
It matches your zither so well.
The zither matched your flute perfectly.
I wonder if it's a woman playing.
The woman in the red gown
is Fangfeng Yiying.
It's her?
Go now.
Go.
Be careful.
Look after Nian.
Okay.
Let's go.
Fortunately, it was only
a shoulder wound.
It didn't hit any vital parts.
Do you think
this bamboo flute is his?
We can ask when he wakes up.
I hope we didn't save the wrong person.
You're awake.
Where am I?
Don't get up,
or you may tear your wound.
This is the Chenrong Mansion.
May I ask if Chenrong Yi is...?
Chenrong Yi is my father.
My name is Chenrong Xinyue.
Thank you, Miss Chenrong.
Is this yours?
Yes, this is mine.
Is it you who was playing the flute
on the lake?
It was me.
Could it be that you were the one
who played the guqin?
I'm Xuan,
from Haoling's Dragon Squad.
I'll leave now.
You should stay here to recover.
If you don't want your family worried,
I'll have someone
deliver a message for you.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir,
for agreeing to play with me.
Miss Chenrong, you're too polite.
Compared to your favor
of saving my life,
playing a song is just small-fry.
The flowers in the garden
are in full bloom today.
I'll take you around.
It's time for me to take my medicine.
I need to go back to my room now.
Then next time.
Alright, my wound doesn't hurt anymore.
Don't be angry with me.
Unless life is threatened,
no one likes
to act by hurting themselves.
I had someone investigate
Fangfeng Yiying
after the last time I got hurt.
She was probably instructed by someone
to assassinate me.
Could it be someone from Xiyan?
This matter is most likely
related to my uncle.
It seems that the Fangfeng Family
has likely sided with him.
If it hadn't been for me
wanting to hear her play the guqin,
you wouldn't have
had the chance to play the flute,
and Chenrong Xinyue
wouldn't have developed
a liking for you.
If I hadn't played the flute for you,
I wouldn't have lured their boat over.
If I hadn't lured them over,
I wouldn't have encountered them
and wouldn't have had
all these troubles.
I was the victim
of your unintended harm.
If you hadn't met Chenrong Xinyue,
how would you have met people
from the Chishui and Chenrong Families?
I should thank you?
The Chenrong and Chishui Families
were clans you wanted
to get acquainted with and win over.
I didn't expect such a chance,
and we actually met Chenrong Xinyue.
Whether the Chenrong
and Chishui Families
will stand on our side or out
doesn't depend on
Chenrong Xinyue's trivial liking for me,
but on the benefits
I can bring them in the future.
You are
too clear-headed, too rational.
Fenglong, let me introduce you.
This is Xuan
from the Dragon Squad of Haoling.
Nice to see you.
Nice to meet you,
Mr. Chishui and Miss Chenrong.
So the friend of Jing
is you.
You know each other?
I heard that a court official of Xiyan
impeached Mr. Chenrong.
Yes, father has been
worried about this matter recently.
If one must say
that Mr. Chenrong is colluding
with the Chenrong rebels,
there's nothing wrong with that.
Hundreds of years ago,
when Mr. Chenrong took over
the Central Plains, he said
his loyalty goes to common people,
and his pursuit is peace
and well-being all over the world.
He never said
he would be loyal to a single man.
What he has been striving for is great.
Isn't the peaceful life
of Central Plains' civilians
important?
After Mr. Chenrong
took over Central Plains,
with private negotiations,
many betrayers surrendered,
which stopped many wars.
If it weren't
for Mr. Chenrong's collusion,
as Central Plains enjoyed many people,
there wouldn't be
just tens of thousands
of betrayers left,
hiding in Qingshui.
Well done.
I toast you.
Miss Chenrong
was quite interested in you.
She looks serious
because I am Xiyan Cang Xuan.
But I'm not in a position to judge her.
I don't refuse her
just because
she is Chenrong Xinyue.
I can't offend enemies,
nor
get close to someone I like.
But this is
the price I need to pay
to return to Xiyan Mountain.
It must be a bloody path
returning to Xiyan Mountain.
I must stand on Zhaoyun Peak
on my auntie's
anniversary death next year.
Cang Xuan.
Let's
go home together.
Okay.
Let's go home together.
Mother.
- Auntie.
- Look.
Look, I picked
these Poinciana flowers today.
Have a smell.
They smell so good.
I have kept you waiting so long.
What is your purpose of coming back?
I want the Xiyan Mountain.
And there's another reason
you might not believe.
I missed you.
Your two royal uncles and a few brothers
all want the Xiyan Mountain.
If you want it,
find your own way.
I won't help you.
I understand.
Isn't it just like the swing
from our childhood?
Did you really come back
for our grandfather?
Yes.
He is not only our grandfather,
but also a king.
To become the master
of the Xiyan Mountain,
do you have to be like our grandfather?
Being strong and cold.
I'm not qualified to answer it yet.
Because I'm not yet.
There's still too little
I can do for you.
Xiaoyao.
You just need to stand by my side,
and that's enough.
This time, I came to see you
for important matters.
There is no need
for formality between us.
Since you chose to return to Xiyan Town,
I suppose you are determined
to claim that throne.
But you left Xiyan Town
when you were young,
and your uncles have been
ruling for over 1,000 years.
I'm not looking down on you,
but what do you have
to compete with them?
I do have the ambition,
and it's true
that I'm struggling in Xiyan Town.
You could say I'm barely surviving.
If you have any suggestions,
feel free to speak.
All of this now belong to Xiyan.
Cang Xuan.
Give up Xiyan Town
and come to Central Plains.
The center of the entire Dahuang
is Central Plains.
One day,
if you want to march south,
it will also be easy.
A word from you
woke me up.
I will never
forget this favor.
Xiaoyao kept chatting with me
and lost track of time.
If you fail her and break her heart
in the future,
I will definitely take your life.
If that day really comes,
kill me.
What's so good about this map?
It was extremely difficult
to come to Xiyan Town,
and now, it's also extremely difficult
to leave here.
Destroying
yourself
or abandoning
yourself,
which one would you choose?
This pill is called Free and Easy.
With just one pill,
you can forget all your worries.
Is there such a good thing in the world?
I won't harm you.
You must be punished.
You can hardly walk straight
and you're trying to support me?
Your Highness.
Come on.
Let's enjoy ourselves.
Your father was a renowned warrior
who died for his country,
and your mother was a heroine
with an unyielding spirit.
How could they have a son
who willingly degrades himself?
Aren't you just a snake demon
who luckily transformed into a Yinglong?
We gave you a bit of face
to let you guard the palace.
You've become so bold,
thinking of rebelling?
I will teach you a good lesson.
But now that you've chosen
to wreck yourself,
it's pointless to say anything more.
(Qi Garden)
Xuan.
Slow down.
Didn't you promise me yesterday
you wouldn't hang out with them anymore?
Women should butt out of men's business.
Xuan.
I've been acting for so long,
and sometimes
even I can't tell if it's real or not.
We are ordered to capture an assassin.
We have to search everyone's room.
You're too presumptuous.
Search for the assassin,
why are you going through
cabinets and boxes?
Even His Highness's bed
must be searched.
Who knows if there's an assassin?
So beautiful.
We should also search
His Highness's clothes.
There might be traces left
by the assassin.
I must make them believe
that I am already a useless person.
His Highness said
when the addiction strikes, he may
lose his senses and hurt you.
That's why I need to go in
and accompany him.
What if he hurts himself?
Your Highness.
Why not use this rope
to tie His Highness
to prevent him
from hurting you or himself?
No, thanks.
The only rope in the world
that can bind him
is his will.
Xuan.
Cang Xuan.
- Let go of me.
- Cang Xuan.
Xuan.
I'm Xiaoyao.
Please bear it.
Bear it a little longer.
Xuan.
Let me sing it for you, okay?
♪On the high mountain a vine grows♪
♪On each section of it
hangs a copper bell♪
♪When the wind blows,
the vine and the bell move♪
♪When the wind stops,
the vine and the bell stop♪
♪On the high mountain a vine grows♪
♪On each section of it
hangs a copper bell♪
♪On the high mountain a vine grows♪
♪On each section of it
hangs a copper bell♪
Xuan.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
♪Enduring all things in my life♪
♪I valued all but indifferent♪
♪To wealth and fame♪
♪Basking in the sun♪
♪I couldn't feel your sunlight♪
♪Only heatwaves retained♪
Xuan.
Don't be sad.
I'm here for you.
You are with me.
I'm no longer sad.
♪Everything seems sad♪
Are you alright?
The poison in your body
has been completely removed.
Congratulations.
You have recovered.
Thank you.
Now, mission is completed.
I really want to get drunk.
♪Without you,
even the best scenery is dull♪
I can't hold a feast for you.
I can only bring wine for you.
What a coincidence.
Today, I brought home-brewed wine.
Congratulations.
Congratulations to me.
Are you sure you want
to tie your family
to my uncertain future?
I'm willing to follow Your Highness
and never regret.
From now on,
you and I will fight side by side.
Xiaoyao, I need to tell you something.
What is it?
I've been secretly training troops
and have formed my own army.
If grandfather finds out about it,
it will cause the family extermination.
I'm tired of being unable
to protect myself.
I want to have my own army.
I do need Fenglong.
If you really don't like him,
you don't have to push yourself for me.
I'll try to see Fenglong as a friend
and be true to him.
Grandfather.
Please.
I will protect Xiaoyao.
Cang Xuan,
with your current abilities,
you can't protect her at all.
What's wrong?
My heart is racing for no reason.
Jun Yi, Xiaoxiao.
Take some people to Zhiyi,
and bring Xiaoyao to me.
Yes.
I'm heading to Zhiyi.
We searched all around
but didn't see her.
Get reinforcement
to look for Xiaoyao.
Split up.
Xiaoyao.
Your Highness.
Xiaoyao is in there.
She must be in there.
- Xiaoyao.
- Don't go in.
I have to save Xiaoyao.
It's a deadly formation.
She's in the fire.
It's already activated.
I must save her.
Let go of me.
Xiaoyao.
Where is Xiaoyao?
I've brought her back from the fire.
How is she?
When will she wake up?
She passed away.
Don't talk nonsense.
Impossible.
Absolutely not.
Jin Xuan.
Ask His Majesty to send best physicians
with best medicine now.
Yes.
Give her spirit power.
Xiaoyao.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
You can't abandon me.
Didn't we have a deal?
We will cover the Zijin Peak
in Poinciana trees.
And I will set up a swing
like the one we had.
We will make this place our home.
It was a well-planned assassination
with a clear target.
It took time to plan it.
Look into it.
Once you find them,
keep them alive at all costs.
Your Highness.
I tried three tortures on him.
He still hasn't named his accomplice.
You can remain silent and die.
I will send your son
to reunite with the entire Mu family.
You're a devil!
You killed my little sister.
I swear I'll claim your life!
Don't try to commit suicide.
Think about your son.
After investigation,
we confirmed that
there were four culprits.
The Fan and Zheng families said
that as long as you went easy on
Zhan Xueling and Jin Yuejian,
their families would pay back
by showing support.
You need talents at this moment.
The harm to Xiaoyao
can't be undone even if you kill them.
But if you spare them,
they will be your supporters
to help you achieve greatness.
If I choose to let go
of those who hurt Xiaoyao to gain power,
I'd be betraying my younger self
in the Zhaoyun Hall.
When you try to talk me out of it,
has it crossed your mind
that if I give up on Xiaoyao
for some reason,
maybe one day
I can give up on you
for something else?
I'm not a good man.
But no matter what happens,
I won't give up on my family,
you, Xiaoxiao, or Jin Xuan.
Whoever dares to hurt you
will never be spared.
I'm willing to follow an arduous path.
I'll fight through thick and thin
in the worst case.
Your Highness,
a message from Xiang Liu.
(Promise fulfilled.
Xiaoyao will soon return.)
Is it news about princess?
Xiaoyao will be back soon.
Xiaoyao.
Cang Xuan.
Xuan.
Don't call me that.
I think about you day and night,
but look at you.
You run to see another man
as soon as you return.
Xuan.
Don't you want me anymore?
It's not me.
It's you who abandon me.
I often thought of you
when I was unconscious.
After I saw Xinyue,
I asked about you.
This time, I was really scared to death.
I was afraid that you would
be just like my mother and...
It's okay now.
(Daming Hall)
Give it to Supervisor Liu.
Alright.
The auspicious time has arrived.
Let the ceremony begin.
I, Xiyan Cang Xuan,
lead the clans of the Central Plains
to pray for peace and safety.
It collapses.
What happened?
How did it collapse?
Cang Xuan hasn't improved much.
You made him build a hall,
but he made it collapse.
What do you
suggest?
Since the clans
suspect Cang Xuan of embezzlement,
I suggest
we send a commissar to look into it
and reveal the truth.
Proceed.
Your Highness.
I found the cause of the collapse.
The bucket arch broke.
They are crisscrossed and layered
upon each other
to share the burden of the beam
and support the eaves.
But our bucket arch
was made from Kunwood,
which was solid.
How did it break?
I found white ants
under the broken bucket arch.
I thought they were common ants.
But the experts said that
those ants were bred
by chalcedony from Mount Jade
and could eat Kunwood.
Someone must have placed them there.
Your Lordship. I went to arrest
the carpenter Peng Shan.
But he had committed suicide at home.
We lost our key witness.
You are drafting the restoration plan
for Daming Palace?
Grandfather hasn't issued
the imperial order,
but Daming Palace
still collapsed under my watch.
I need to do what I should.
Even if there's no evidence
of embezzlement,
Yue Liang probably
won't let it go easily.
I have never cut corners,
so I'm not afraid that he'll find out
any evidence of my embezzlement.
But I worry he would follow the clues
and find out other things.
Xuan.
I want to go to the Xiyan Mountain
to see my grandfather.
Are you going to plead
with him for my sake?
That's partly true.
I'll go see Grandfather
and say a few words by the way.
We can't let your uncles say everything,
and we don't even
have a chance to rebut.
I have something to say to you.
I'm going to get married.
I've already written to Grandfather,
asking for his approval.
Are you marrying Chenrong Xinyue?
No.
No?
I'm marrying Shen Shuhui.
Her family's the strongest
of the six major families.
Even the Chenrong royal family
had to marry them in the past.
The chief of the Shen family
has a good impression of me,
so he's willing
to take a risk to support me.
I don't care what method you use
or what you want to do.
I just want you to live well.
I've told you
I'd make Poinciana flowers bloom
all over the Chenrong Mountain.
Xiyan Cang Xuan,
please accept the decree.
Xiyan Cang Xuan was careless
and neglected supervision,
leading to the collapse
of the Daming Hall.
He should have been dismissed
for negligence.
Considering his sincere repentance,
he is specially allowed
to atone for his mistake
by rebuilding the Daming Hall.
Shen Shuhui from the Shen family
is gentle, kind
and beautiful.
She is specially granted to the prince,
Xiyan Cang Xuan, as a secondary wife.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
♪Looking up, I saw you♪
Put down the fan.
♪You appear in the snow♪
(Do not congratulate me.)
♪You appear as the smoke rises♪
The magpie brings good news,
and flowers bloom together.
May you two be filled with love,
and may you be blessed
with many children.
Congratulations.
(We'll never be apart from each other.)
(Deal.)
His Majesty was attacked.
You are summoned
to the Zezhou residence.
Is Grandfather fine?
It was a narrow escape.
Sorry to disappoint you.
How can you say so?
Something's fishy.
Your Highness can't go.
If you go,
you leave your fate to His Majesty.
Even if he lets you go,
Fifth King will try to kill you.
I have to go.
If I don't go,
my uncle can frame me
for planning a coup.
All my followers will be executed.
I don't want to die like that.
Neither do I want you talented people
to die like that.
Cang Xuan has been industrious.
You made all the clans
so grateful to you.
But you married Miss Shen
and truly hurt our feelings.
Your Highness,
you probably forgot all about
our old clans of Xiyan.
As the Prince of Xiyan,
I only married Miss Shen
to promote harmony with the clans.
One can only be their king
once he sees those clansmen
as his own citizens.
What are citizens?
What is a king?
In the beginning,
Dahuang was a united territory.
If Pangu, Fuxi,
or Nuwa comes back to life,
they'll see the Xiyan clan
and Chenrong clan
as their own citizens.
The Xiyan family
already rules the Central Plains.
How is Zhiyi different from Xiyan Town?
How dare you.
Were you only building the palace
on Chenrong Mountain?
I remember your teaching
and only do
what the Prince of Xiyan should do.
My spirit power is limited.
I can only afford three shots.
That's enough.
Assassins!
The ceremony begins.
First bow to the heaven.
Second bow to the earth.
Third bow to the mountains of Chenrong.
Finished.
I won't announce the Crown Prince,
but who becomes
the king of Xiyan Kingdom.
This king should have a great ambition,
a keen mind,
a broad heart,
and vigorous energy.
Deyan.
Father.
You did a good job.
Thank you, Father.
You arranged a good ceremony.
The new king ascends,
demonstrating his power.
Cang Xuan.
Come here.
From today,
Xiyan Cang Xuan is the king
of Xiyan Kingdom.
Greetings, Your Majesty.