=Fate of Beauty=
(The bead is a gift)
(from an old acquaintance.)
(First Young Master,)
(are you)
(interested in me?)
=Episode 10=
(Ripples)
(The Gu is fierce.)
(Every full moon night,)
(you'll suffer excruciating pain
in your heart.)
Do you feel better now, Young Lady?
If you can't bear the pain,
bite me.
The pain is less
compared to last time.
I suppose First Young Master
has fallen for you,
which is why the Mother Gu's backlash
has weakened.
(If the Child Gu host develops feelings
for the Mother Gu host,)
(the Mother Gu will become milder.)
(The deeper the feelings,)
(the milder the effects
of the backlash.)
Hai Tang,
you may go.
Yes, Young Lady.
(Since Xiao Yeting has already
developed feelings for me,)
(I'll push forward)
(and make him submit to me.)
Who's there?
I...
I didn't mean to disturb you.
Why did I always come
at a bad time?
Turn around.
Why did you use the window
instead of the door?
I noticed Hai Tang
was guarding at the door
until she fell asleep.
I didn't want to
disrupt her rest.
You're worried
she wouldn't let you in, right?
You know me the best.
What brings you here
late at night?
I noticed
you always suffer from pain
on every full moon night.
I looked through all medical books,
but couldn't find a cure.
However,
I thought of a great idea.
What's it?
I concocted a sleeping potion for you.
You'll
have a peaceful sleep
after taking it.
That way,
you can avoid the pain
every month.
Second Young Master,
thank you so much.
What I do is trivial
compared to your jasmine cake.
Did you take the herbal bath at night
to alleviate the pain?
Trust me.
Drink the sleeping potion
and go to bed.
Let me
help you get to the bed.
Why aren't you leaving yet?
I'll leave after you fall asleep.
Sleep tight.
(No matter who you are)
(or what you've done,)
(I don't care.)
(Ban Meng,)
(I only wish to lead a peaceful
and happy life with you.)
♪How do I redeem myself from it?♪
♪I'll end up scattered in the mud♪
♪I can't bear to see the wind
blow against you♪
♪Maybe by hiding my heart♪
♪I can escape from your sight♪
♪Lying to you that my love for you♪
♪Is only one ten-thousandth♪
Inform Xiao Muran
to join me to welcome Father back.
Second Young Master
went out early this morning.
Where did he go?
He said he went to the city gate
to wait for General
and request a marriage.
Marriage?
What marriage?
With Miss Ban Meng.
What's wrong with him?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
What's wrong with him?
Father,
don't agree to his request.
He's playful,
and isn't ready for marriage.
You came in a hurry.
I thought you were here to welcome me.
Father, congratulations
on your victorious return.
I'll think about
the marriage proposal.
Thank you, Father.
What did I instruct you before I left?
As of now,
you're the biggest problem
in this residence.
Look,
the residence is in a total mess now.
I'm very disappointed
in you.
Ran,
come with me.
I didn't ask for you.
I think
you haven't thought it through
about the marriage.
Whether or not I've thought it through,
are you the one
to decide?
Mind your attitude.
I'm just doing what I want to do.
I don't understand
what you're trying to do.
Yeting,
I can give you
anything you want.
But
I only want Ban Feng.
(Find your own pleasure)
Do you know
Muran wants to marry you?
What has this got to do with you,
First Young Master?
Do you really want to marry him?
I suppose
it doesn't concern you.
I don't understand.
Why didn't you admit
what happened that night?
Which night?
What happened?
Orchid Pavilion.
You and me.
Me
and you?
Drop your pretense.
You're my woman.
I didn't expect
the collected First Young Master
to have
such wild imaginations.
Don't agree to marry Xiao Muran.
Why?
Do you want to
marry me, too?
I won't let you marry him.
♪The rain that falls over♪
♪The green hills♪
♪Is vaguely blown♪
♪Into my dreams♪
♪I'm leaning on you♪
♪For a moment♪
♪Of refuge♪
♪I'm afraid that if my beautiful dream♪
♪Fades away♪
♪I'll wake up♪
♪Alone in a long silence♪
♪To love or to hate♪
♪I can't help it♪
♪How many♪
♪Courage of obsession♪
♪Do I need to break free♪
♪From this destiny?♪
♪Saying I love you♪
♪Maybe the past is too vivid♪
♪How do I redeem myself from it?♪
♪I'll end up scattered in the mud♪
♪I can't bear to see the wind
blow against you♪
♪Maybe by hiding my heart♪
♪I can escape from your sight♪
♪Lying to you that my love for you♪
♪Is only one ten-thousandth♪