=Fate of Beauty=
(Panic,)
(fright,)
(confusion.)
(Is that what you're feeling right now?)
(Can't you remember who I am?)
(I'm your nightmare
for the rest of your life.)
(From now on,)
(if I want you to be happy,)
(you'll be.)
(If I want you to be sad,)
(I want you)
(to never forget me.)
Young Master,
this is Miss Le's hairpin.
Where is she?
She's dead.
burnt to a crisp.
From now on,
you are irreplaceable
in my heart.
(Le,)
(you are irreplaceable)
(in my heart.)
=Episode 3=
(Get into A Trap)
Who are you?
Why did you try to harm me?
If I wanted to harm you,
why would I save you?
I don't care what you're up to,
stay away
from me,
from the General residence.
If you think there's something wrong
with me,
you can just strangle me,
take my life,
and make trumped up charges.
That's a piece of cake
for you,
isn't it?
What am I up to, you ask?
I'm thinking
about what you said to me yesterday.
You said
you don't know about flowers
or women.
If you really don't know,
I can teach you.
No one has ever dared
to tell me what to do.
(General's Residence)
Second Young Master,
why are you here?
Warm up your hands.
Thank you.
It must be hard
to open a flower parlor
in the capital
without your family around.
From now on,
if you have any problems,
you can come to me.
Any problems,
you mean?
As long as I can do it,
I'll do it
if you ask me.
Okay.
Young Lady,
do we have to come to this so soon?
Just burn down
such a nice flower parlor?
Don't forget
what we're here for.
(Within a year,)
(if he falls in love with you,)
(Fleeting Dreamland)
(if he gives you his true love,)
(you'll be out of this mess.)
(Otherwise,)
(you'll die.)
(Fleeting Dreamland)
(Remember,)
(you've only got one year
to get your revenge.)
Xiao Yeting!
Traitor!
Sinner!
You've failed my daughter!
At last,
it's all about to begin.
(General's Residence)
(I need to get into the General
residence as soon as possible)
(so that I can carry out my plan.)
(Xiao Yeting,)
(everything you've gained
by stepping on the corpses)
(of the Xia'an clan,)
(I'm going to take it all away.)
Did you really mean
what you said
about helping me?
(General's Residence)
(What's with the messy pulse?)
You're awake.
I've decorated this room
to look like your old room
with the help of Hai Tang.
I hope
it will comfort you for the destruction
of your flower parlor.
Thank you for your kindness.
I've already bothered you at your home.
You...
I was worried about you,
so I spent
the night here.
Lie down.
- You lie down first.
- Have I been asleep long?
Lie down.
Your pulse is messy.
You shouldn't get up in a hurry.
There's something unusual
about your pulse.
Something I've never seen before.
Maybe
I suffered a shock
in the fire.
Your pulse doesn't look like that.
It looks like...
I didn't expect you
to have medical skills.
I've been interested
in medicine since I was a kid.
I know a little bit about it.
This is
my private compound.
You can stay
as long as you want.
I hope
you'll make yourself at home here.
(Xiao Yeting,)
(your nightmare)
(begins now.)
♪The rain that falls over♪
♪The green hills♪
♪Is vaguely blown♪
♪Into my dreams♪
♪I'm leaning on you♪
♪For a moment♪
♪Of refuge♪
♪I'm afraid that if my beautiful dream♪
♪Fades away♪
♪I'll wake up♪
♪Alone in a long silence♪
♪To love or to hate♪
♪I can't help it♪
♪How many♪
♪Courage of obsession♪
♪Do I need to break free♪
♪From this destiny?♪
♪Saying I love you♪
♪Maybe the past is too vivid♪
♪How do I redeem myself from it?♪
♪I'll end up scattered in the mud♪
♪I can't bear to see the wind
blow against you♪
♪Maybe by hiding my heart♪
♪I can escape from your sight♪
♪Lying to you that my love for you♪
♪Is only one ten-thousandth♪