This drama is set during the Joseon Era
under the rule of a fictitious king.
Characters and events are fictitious
and have no historical basis.
Episode 7
You may return now.
I'm barely resisting the temptation
to go with you,
so please let me see you off at least.
Why are you doing this?
If, while I'm gone,
strangers come looking for you,
you must avoid them.
Are there any guests
coming to our home today?
You may never let someone
into your heart...
...nor may you have any relationship
with that person.
Do you understand?
The boat is coming. The boat!
Did you sleep well?
Despite the rocky journey,
you managed to sleep soundly.
Is it market day today?
Why are there so many people?
What?
You mean you came without knowing?
Today, at this village,
His Majesty will be visiting.
These people came
to catch a glimpse of His Majesty.
If you came without knowing,
it's your lucky day.
You have good luck. Good luck.
Yeon Woo...
...you are trying to make
His Majesty and I meet, aren't you?
When you arrive there,
please send my regards to the monk.
Seol, you must take her
and go home immediately.
I'm about to get a scab on my ears.
If you can't trust me that much,
leave her and take me instead.
Her mouth worries me more
than your obstinacy, that is why.
There's nothing to be envious of.
Since the nagger isn't here,
shall we have a bowl of soup
before we go back?
This is no ordinary tent permit!
The permit you've been waiting for
has finally come.
The opportunity to see His Majesty
up close is in this tent permit.
Oh, no you can't.
Watch His Majesty's royal procession
from a comfortable place,
this is an excellent chance.
You cannot.
We really cannot.
Now, let's see.
Oh, you have an ugly face.
No, we mustn't.
Let's pretend this didn't happen.
Seol...
-Where are you going?
-Forget it.
Take this.
I gave one away.
Don't worry. Just trust me and...
Hey! There's news that His Majesty
has just reached the entrance
of the village!
-Give me one.
It seems like we have come close
to the village, so raise the blinds.
The weather is chilly, so I suggest we...
I said to lift it.
Stop.
Set down the palanquin.
Despite the cold,
they have come to see me,
so how can I disappoint the citizens?
Then, making your expression bright
or showing our people
a benevolent smile...
Was Xi Shi of the State of Yue
a beauty for the ages thanks to a smile?
True beauty cannot be diminished
even by a frown.
Do you think it's easy to be the king
and have my looks?
Do you plan on wasting the day here?
Pick up the pace!
Lift the palanquin.
As we promised, just a glimpse.
We'll take a glimpse and go.
I said okay.
Yes. Yes. Go in.
Yes, that way.
We live in the neighbouring village.
My child really wants to see
the procession of His Majesty.
It's not possible. Go back. Next.
-Officer, just this once.
-This woman!
If you want to see
His Majesty's procession,
at least put one some silk clothes!
Rejected.
Officer, still just this once!
This woman really!
Aren't you being too harsh
to a weak woman?
What?
Poor and low-class people
don't have the right to see His Majesty?
Where is there such a rule?
Listen to this wench...
Who are you?
Let's hear it, who are you?
I'm a shaman.
A lowly shaman
dares to stare and talk back?
I ought to just...
Before I cut off this hand, put it down.
And what is this?
What are you, her pimp?
You look just like a girl...
Why? Do you like making money
off of a shaman that much?
Is it that great?
Do you want me to tell you
the reason your wife left you?
What?
It's exactly because
you tend to hit before you talk.
Whenever you drink, you hit your wife...
...so you deserve that
she ran away with a young man.
Hey!
Your wife cheated on you,
so she left home?
-Didn't she go to her parents' home?
-Who said she cheated!
You shut your mouth!
Whenever you eat,
you burn inside and feel sick, right?
At least drinking eases the pain
ever so slightly,
so you make drinking
your only meal of the day.
But that habit has gotten
to your stomach already,
so if you don't stop drinking
immediately...
...you will perish before your time comes.
At most, you have a year.
You wench!
Let it go.
Nothing good will come
of provoking a shaman.
What if she curses you with her magic?
Hey, you there! Do you want to die?
Stand there! Stand there! Stop!
Quickly, go in.
Milady, how can you pretend
to be a shaman again?
Didn't the master tell you
not to do that again?
I just did what I, a shaman,
is supposed to do,
so what would be the problem?
Pretending to have powers
you do not possess is a fraud!
But, wait.
If you have no powers,
how did you know about his wife?
That's not spiritual powers,
but power of deduction.
What?
Even though it's broad daylight,
he reeked of alcohol.
On top of that,
his nose was red from the alcohol,
so he must be a severe alcoholic.
He was aggressive even though
the situation hardly warranted it,
and from the fact
that he is quick to hit a woman,
you can guess that his drunk habit
is horrid as well.
He probably wasn't any different at home.
But that doesn't necessarily imply
that his wife would leave him.
I saw that a woman has not tended to him.
The holes on his clothes were big,
but not mended.
Most importantly,
when he saw a fine and pretty young man,
he seemed overly sensitive.
A man?
Do you mean me?
So, his wife positively ran away
with a young man.
Seeing as he is still very angry,
it hasn't been too long.
Then, what was his illness about?
It's obvious.
He's already an alcoholic,
so how much more would he have drunk
because of his wife?
His mouth had a peculiar smell
so it's proof
that his stomach illness is advanced.
With your power of deduction,
you should open up a fortune teller stand.
But, why were you so severe
with your words,
it wasn't like you.
Whenever there's a problem,
he tries to beat people,
so he brought it upon himself.
Although he is in a pitiful situation,
he has to get a severe scolding
to come to his senses.
Think how much his wife was beaten
to run away in the middle of the night.
Don't run. Stop there!
Stop there. Grab him!
Grab him!
Hold on. Let's talk after you let me go.
Come here.
Hold on.
What a temper!
Let's talk. Talk.
His Majesty is approaching.
I'll see you later.
Let's go.
Stop already and pay your respects.
Milady!
Milady! Milady!
Grab them!
Stop!
-Seize him!
-Stop!
Move away!
Seize them!
What is going on?
It seems a woman stood out of the queue
and caused a riot.
-A woman?
-Yes.
In case that there might be ill will
against you, the guards are chasing her.
So I will bring down the curtain.
Seize them!
Quickly!
Quickly, after them!
-Seize them.
Chase after them.
Chase them!
Milady, are you insane?
How can you stand
and look His Majesty directly in the face?
Seol.
What is it?
Like you and I were chased today...
...have we been chased like this before?
If we had already experienced this,
do you think we would still be alive?
Then...
...whose memories are these?
I'm sorry.
I mistook you for someone else.
What was I expecting?
She's already dead and buried
under the dirt.
Why are you acting like this,
Your Highness?
Is the water's temperature
not to your liking?
Is the fragrance not to your liking?
If that is also not it...
It irritates me.
What?
It really irritates me.
Not you, Hyung Sun.
Then, what is to your dissatisfaction?
Silk clothes.
Silk shoes.
Shiny faces.
What?
Everyone was dressed so elegantly.
You could not see a trace
of a crude person on the streets.
Even the animals we passed by
had glossy coats.
What a peaceful and prosperous nation.
I am definitely a sage king.
That's because they were just trying
to show Your Majesty the best...
Do you think I came all the way
to Onyang to see that?
Your Highness,
you have come to recuperate.
Try to forget
about government issues for a...
Woon.
At your commands.
I feel much better
after bathing in hot water.
You must be tired after the long journey.
Do you want to join me?
Ginseng!
Go and bring more ginseng and herbs
to put into the tub.
Your Highness, there are already rumours
going around at the palace,
so how can you joke like this?
Rumours?
What rumours?
You keep the Queen far away
and keep Woon close to you,
so you must like men...
Men...
Men among men?
No matter what the rumours are,
please don't joke about Woon
in such a way again.
Then...
...Hyung Sun, do you want to come in?
Herbs...
I will go check if the herbs are ready.
Finally...
...we're alone.
It can't be true. It can't be.
It can't be. I have served His Majesty
for so many years!
Then, did his preference change?
Oh, my.
My heart is pounding, my legs
are trembling. What is the reason?
I don't know what to say.
Do you have to use the restroom?
Why are you as nervous as a pup
who has left its mother?
Your Highness!
Your Majesty.
Prince Yang Myung wishes to see you.
Your Highness.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
What is wrong?
I can hear Hyung Sun's piercing screams
all the way here.
The scene from the procession
and this one...
...are starkly different.
Please give me some money.
My Lord, please give me some money.
My Lord, please.
I'm sorry, my Lord. I'm sorry.
Where are you going in such a hurry?
My sister is home alone,
so I was taking this to her.
Do you have no parents?
My mother passed away two years ago
because of the plague
and my father was forcibly taken
to work at Boyong Pavilion a month ago.
But I don't know what happened after that.
Are you sure it's the Boyong Pavilion?
What is your father's name?
Talk of Pi Han Dol of Yangigol in Onyang
and everyone will know.
I will find your father
and send him home for sure,
so until then,
take good care of your sister.
Look at you... You don't trust me?
Even though I look like this,
I hold a pretty high position.
Thank you, my Lord. Thank you.
-Your Majesty.
-What is it?
There's a spy.
I know.
He's probably a present
from the Chief Councilor.
Woon.
Yes, Your Highness.
He put in a lot of effort
following us this far...
...so shall we play with him?
He seems to have lost us.
I wonder what he is going to say
to His Excellency.
Are they secretly training troops?
Or maybe gathering followers
for a political ploy?
They're probably dying from anxiety.
I believe it will be better
if we stop our patrolling here.
Yes.
I believe so too.
It's Yeon Woo.
Yeon Woo will come down.
Your Highness!
If two people are destined to meet,
they will meet eventually.
There is no stronger magic than longing.
Is that why you called me here today
when His Majesty was visiting our village?
His Majesty's illness is serious.
The person who is supposed to protect him
is living another life,
so there is no improvement in his health.
Are you thinking of having the two
fulfil their destinies?
It's not something a person can do.
The heavens control this.
It's a destiny that cannot be averted
even if you tried.
You know that well, don't you?
Their fate has ended once already.
You could not end their longing.
Milady has lost her memories of her past.
So, she harbours no longing in her heart.
Those memories will return one day.
This will lead to bloodshed.
It's an inverse act of fate...
...so the price has to be paid.
She will fall again into a cruel fate.
How can we make her
go through that pain twice?
Milady...
...what are you thinking about?
Seol.
I figured it out.
What?
What did you figure out?
The owner of the memories from before.
Those are his memories.
What?
I was able to sense his memories and pain.
Don't you get it?
I now have spiritual powers.
Now, I have become a real shaman.
Milady.
To say that it was all spiritual power
is a bit...
Where are you going?
The mistress is taking too long,
I have to go out and see.
Let's go together, Milady.
It seems we've lost our way
because of the thick fog.
We've been walking around in circles.
I'm sorry.
What do you have to be sorry for?
It's because of my vision that we're lost.
Isn't that the moon?
I have been waiting for you.
Why are you coming only now?
Milady, do you not know
who those people are?
It seems as if
they were taking a private walk,
so let's pretend we don't know.
Then, you brought them here
knowing who they were?
They were obviously lost,
should I have just ignored them?
You were told to avoid strangers
by the mistress.
She never said to chase away people
who needed help.
The alcohol will help melt away the cold.
Because there is only one owner
to this house,
I could not prepare another for you.
Please forgive me.
Though it is a humble home,
please rest before you are on your way.
Who is the original owner of this table?
In the rain...
...who were you waiting for?
Is there...
...someone you are waiting for?
The mistress.
I was waiting for the mistress
who has gone out.
If you have nothing further to ask...
Did you say you were a shaman?
That is correct.
Is this really what a room
of a shaman looks like?
Or do you have unusual hobbies?
Are all the books on the shelves yours?
That is correct.
A shaman who reads the Classics.
It is definitely a noble hobby,
but what would a shaman
read Confucian classics for?
It is just to understand the world
a little better.
That's why I read them.
You read to understand the world better?
Even if you understand the world,
what is it to you?
Although I am just a shaman,
I do not read for personal interests,
but to help others.
Also, by reading the words
of ancient sages,
I try to understand the joys of the world.
I cannot stop.
A noble man does not resent the heavens
and does not blame the people.
You read the Analects?
A farmer does not blame the fields.
A musician does not blame his instruments.
This cannot be.
There's no way
for a dead girl to be alive.
She is just someone who resembles her.
Why are you looking at me like that?
This is a dream.
It's an illusion.
My dream has become reality
and is deceiving me.
Have a drink as well.
It's all right, so drink.
Didn't you get in the rain as well?
You are really disloyal.
You don't know who I am
or what I may have put into the wine,
so why do you refuse to taste it?
Are you only going
to escort him with your sword?
How did you know?
What are you talking about?
How do you know that
I am the king of this country?
Even if only as a spirit...
...did you want to see His Majesty?
Even though you did not come back
to see me...
...it was good to see you.
However, in the next life, please...
...look at me first.
Have you met me before?
I am just an ordinary shaman.
There's no way for our paths
to have crossed.
That's a lie.
How could I dare to lie to Your Majesty?
Then, are you really only a shaman?
Ever since being bestowed
spiritual powers when I was little,
I have lived as a shaman.
If you don't call a person bestowed
with spiritual powers a shaman,
then what else would you call her?
Then how did you know
that I was the King of this country?
That's because...
Tell me immediately!
Please forgive me...
...but I saw Your Majesty
earlier on your procession.
Woon.
At your commands.
The rain has stopped.
It is time for us to go back.
What is your name?
I'm sorry, but I do not have a name.
Even if you're a shaman, do you mean
to tell me you have no name?
Because she did not want me
to be bound by fate,
the mistress did not give me a name.
People just call me "lady."
She did not want you to be bound by fate,
so you were not given a name.
This brief encounter is fate as well.
I will name you Wol.
For your warm drink...
...think of that as my repayment.
Wol.
Did you hear?
I now have a name, too.
Your Majesty, how can you do this?
Do you want to see me dead and...
I do not want to see you die,
so there is no need to say
anything anymore.
Is that what you call
protecting His Majesty...
He protected me well...
...which is why I returned safely.
Have you been well all these years?
Why are you here?
After being gone for years...
...you are asking about my well-being?
You are still very good-looking.
Woon, I told you to come here
and sit as well.
Please pay no heed to me.
Just give up.
While working, he is someone
who will not touch a drop of alcohol.
Then,
do you want to make a bet with me?
A bet?
The person who makes Woon drink first
will hear the other's wish.
Did you hear?
Before I get angry, come here and sit.
After I receive gold and treasures
from His Majesty...
...I will give you half.
Look at him.
There is definitely nothing cute
about him.
-Woon.
-At your commands.
Come and drink.
It's an order.
Hyungnim.
Yes, I lost.
I will do anything you ask of me.
Do you still...
...keep that child in your heart?
Please answer me.
Your Majesty.
Didn't you lose the bet?
I am asking for your answer right now.
Even if I still have her in my heart...
...isn't she already dead?
You know how the soul works.
Say you forgot, and you miss her.
Say you miss her, and yet you forget.
I do not want to forget or miss her.
I just remember
that she is not in this world.
That's all I keep in my heart.
Only remember that
she is not in this world.
I see.
While I was out of the palace,
the ministers have worked hard.
Especially our Minister of Finance.
Inadequate as we may be,
in order to lessen Your Majesty's work,
we have spent sleepless nights
handling state matters in your stead.
Well said.
It's inadequate. It is very inadequate.
Why didn't you just sleep?
Especially this part,
about the construction of Boyong Pavilion.
No less than 3000 sacks of charcoal
had already been added to the lot,
and yet you ask the levies for next year
this much in advance?
Do you expect people
to just die for your sake?
Although it may be hard now,
the construction
is such an urgent matter...
What is so urgent about it?
It is a pavilion that the Queen Dowager
really cherishes.
If we were able to match
her birthday next year,
by shortening construction time
as much as possible...
So the birthday present matters more
than the lives of our people?
This matter has already
been permitted by Your Majesty.
I did.
But it wasn't to force hard labour
under the freezing cold upon our people.
"Summon every last one
down to fathers of starving children."
Did I ever give such an order?
But Your Majesty,
the size of the construction is large,
so manpower...
What I'm most curious about...
...is what was all that charcoal used for?
There are more than two hundred people
working on this project,
but where have all those people gone to?
That's what I'm asking.
Before leaving this hall,
compile a list of names
of the construction workers,
the progress of the construction
and funding details
as detailed as possible,
and submit it to me.
After I meticulously review it...
...I will seek who is responsible
tomorrow.
Did you ask for me?
How many years has it been
since you have returned to Seongsucheong?
What?
I'm asking how many years it has been
since you have taken over for shaman Jang.
Next year will be my eighth.
In due time, I was considering
making you Head Shaman
of the Seongsucheong.
I will not forget
Your Excellency's generosity.
Whatever order it is, just say the word.
But,
it seems like you're not worried
about His Highness's health at all.
I was told that
he is now in good health...
Am I wrong?
That is why I am worried.
When he needs to be healthy, he is ill.
When he needs to be ill, he is healthy.
While the king was away from the palace,
I buried a talisman there.
When you give the order,
you will be able to see immediate effects.
Thinking that tomorrow
I will witness his ailments reappear...
...I have already started to fret.
I am just an ordinary shaman.
There's no way for our paths
to have crossed.
Your Majesty, it is Hyung Sun.
Come in.
Your Majesty,
Her Majesty the Queen seeks audience.
Have you already forgotten my order
not to let anyone in?
Your Majesty, please.
Your Majesty!
Let her in.
Escort her in. Quickly.
Welcome, Queen.
Are you well?
As you can see, I am perfectly well.
What brings you here so late?
What did you just say?
I told you to take a royal concubine.
You wish to be a strong monarch,
more than anyone.
A king without a successor
is just the same
as building a home on sand.
Please have an heir
and solidify your legacy.
Queen.
I simply am no longer able
to face Their Highnesses.
It does not matter if it's a concubine.
Take a royal concubine and have an heir.
Are you telling the truth?
As the mother of this country,
how can I be swayed by personal feelings?
Indeed.
Now I understand why you receive
so much love from everyone.
I didn't see how far-sighted you were.
Because of me, how much
you must have suffered until now?
I'll do as you wish.
Tomorrow at the hall...
...I will talk to the ministers
about a royal concubine.
Your Majesty.
Queen.
Yes, Sire.
You know...
...I really hate your hypocrisy.
Saying words that you do not mean
to gain sympathy.
I hate your pretense as well.
If you are done talking, go back and rest.
It's very late.
Until when do you plan on keeping
a dead person in your heart?
How can a dead person
capture your heart so much...
...when it should throb
for someone by your side?
Does Your Majesty even see
my affection for you?
How much longer?
How much longer before I have to face
a dead rival for your love?
How much longer does Your Majesty...
...plan to look down on me so much?
Your Majesty!
Is anyone out there?
Call the physician. Quickly!
-Yes.
-Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
Fortunately, he is stable.
Why is that whenever he is with the Queen
these things occur?
I'm sorry.
Because the Royal Doctor does not know
the cause of the illness,
I was frustrated and without thinking...
If it cannot be cured by a person...
...then we need to entrust it
to the heavens.
When you say the heavens...
We need to bring back Shaman Jang.
The Seongsucheong already
has another state shaman, isn't it?
She is just a temporary head, isn't she?
The fact that the King's health
has gotten to this point
is because she is lacking skills.
In all of Joseon...
...there is no other shaman
who is as powerful as shaman Jang.
If it is her, not only will she be able
to cure the King...
...but also dissipate the hatred...
...between His Majesty and the Queen.
Go look for her.
Something about her eyes is bothering me.
Your Majesty.
I'm sure...
...she was hiding something from me.
I have to find her,
and confirm with her.
The house is already empty.
Please let it go.
You said you have never seen
that girl before, right?
They look alike.
If she were alive,
she would look exactly like that.
These eyes!
Eyes that are as swollen as chestnuts.
What am I to do with these eyes?
What are you going to do about these eyes?
You did not stop crying
until you fell asleep,
so it's only natural
that they'd be like that.
What were you doing while my eyes
became like this, Court Lady Min?
I told you repeatedly to stop,
but it was you
who chose not to listen, Princess.
You should have stopped me.
You should have stopped me even more!
You should have stopped me until the end.
I understand.
I committed a crime that deserves death,
so stop looking at this.
It's all over now.
What?
If my husband sees this face...
...he will hate it, right?
He will hate me, right?
I will be abandoned, right?
I will be chased out, right?
I will walk in the streets
and get sick and die, right?
Princess, your imagination
is out of control.
I never received true love.
I will never get to hold a baby
who resembles my husband.
I will become a pitiful wife who leaves
after guarding this empty room by herself.
Please forgive me, husband.
What's wrong, princess?
Why do you keep forgetting
about the date that was set?
Think about it.
As a woman...
...do you think it was easy for her
to bring up sleeping together?
The princess has no eyes but for you,
don't you feel any pity for her?
I'm sorry.
I was reading late at night
and eventually...
How can you be so similar
to your late father?
Perhaps, are you
intentionally avoiding her?
No, I'm not.
Then, why do you always
make the princess lonely?
The princess is still young...
...and it hasn't been long since
the three years of mourning have passed.
That is only because
the Princess' face looks young.
She is already at an age where
she should have a child of her own.
But she is still immature...
She is a woman.
Don't treat her as a younger sister.
You are a married couple.
You are not related as siblings.
For our family...
...she is someone who has done so much.
Your father as well,
until the day he died...
...told us to never forget
her kindness to our family.
I will take heed of your advice,
so please do not worry.
Mistress,
I haven't seen Seol since the morning.
I will go out and look for her.
If it's Seol, we know where she will be.
She will come back when it's time,
so don't think
of going out and stay inside.
-Jan Sil.
-What is it?
Take her and go inside...
State Shaman Jang!
Jan Sil, what are you waiting for?
Let us go to the side room.
Mistress, we'll be borrowing
the side room.
I had to read directions...
...the astronomy professor
had to read the heavens...
...and after the life science professor
had to fortune tell,
we barely managed to find you.
Do you know how much trouble
it was for us?
Why did you got to such great lengths
to find a nobody like me?
We came because of an order
from the Queen Dowager...
...concerning your return
to your position at the Seongsucheong.
Isn't the Seongsucheong doing well
with the temporary head shaman?
Doing well, I would not say!
His Majesty's illness is getting worse
as the days go by.
As the state shaman, are you just
going to stand on the sidelines?
My skills have already depleted.
You are probably turning away
the calling of Heaven.
Recently, the heavens have changed
their course of motion.
Sirius has become dark,
and the moon has become a deep red.
A few days ago, it turned brown.
We urgently need your help.
The Queen Dowager ordered us
to bring you back no matter what.
Why else would people forbidden
to leave the palace like us
venture out to get you?
No matter how many times you tell me,
my answer is the same.
I'm disgusted by scholars who try
to eliminate the Seongsucheong...
...I want to rest now.
The girl in the next room...
...is your successor,
the one you registered under your name a
few years ago at the Seongsucheong, right?
I will go see the Queen Dowager
in a few days,
and tell her my intentions...
...so for today, please go back.
Goodness.
Did she boil a beef tendon and eat it?
She is as stubborn as one.
I'm worried about facing
the Queen Dowager with this news.
We can't go back empty-handed
when we have come all the way here.
What?
Hey, you there!
Yes, sir.
If she's not even here...
...where in the world did she go?
Did my spiritual power disappear
in that short time?
Then.
What exactly did I see the other day?
In the past...
...have you met me?
Who are you?
Let's go.
Whose memories are these?