This drama is set during the Joseon Era
under the rule of a fictitious king.
Characters and events are fictitious
and have no historical basis.
Episode 10
I am extremely exhausted right now.
Moreover, the pain in my heart
that I can't bear...
...is completely occupying it.
Therefore, you need to help me forget
about all of it.
You have to put to rest
this pain in my heart.
Do you think you can do it?
Answer me. Do you think you can do it?
Please allow me to do so.
If Your Majesty permits,
I will prevent the misfortune and death
that threaten you from harming you.
Lift your head up.
Lift it.
That is an order.
I came because I was worried about
His Majesty's health.
Do not report this to His Majesty.
-Is anyone outside?
-Yes, Your Majesty.
Please give your order.
Call the royal physician.
What?
Is Your Majesty feeling unwell?
It's not me who is unwell,
it is that lady.
Your Majesty, that is not possible.
What isn't?
The royal physician
only treats the royal family.
How can he treat a lowly shaman?
Doesn't she block bad luck
and misfortune for me as a human talisman?
If she is not feeling well,
then it will also have an influence on me.
So this is not for her, but for me.
Call him immediately.
But Your Majesty...
It's a royal command!
Why did you come out?
He ordered everyone to leave the palace.
What is that?
While we were searching the shaman,
this came out. Looks like a letter.
It seems that wicked wench
wrote His Majesty a love letter.
Take a look at it.
Your Majesty.
It was definitely the gaze of a man
looking at a woman.
You have to put to rest...
...this pain in my heart.
I will prevent the misfortune and death
that threaten you from harming you.
What is this?
This was found
while searching the shaman.
I think that it was meant
for Your Majesty.
If you decline it, I will take it away.
Leave it.
"Need not beauty a weed to prosper."
Wild herbs are not beautiful
but they are useful.
"Need no humanity a shaman to serve."
Although shamans
are not deemed as humans,
we still want to be
Your Majesty's people.
You're not even a human...
...but you dare lay a hand on me?
"Shamans are your subjects and humans too,
so don't neglect us."
It's short and delivers a powerful blow.
It is amazing that a shaman knows
how to write in the learned man's script.
And it's even more amazing that a shaman
is able to write such beautiful words.
Look at these characters, Hyung Sun.
How can you say that
a 13 year old girl wrote this?
I thought she was wise,
but she's foolish, isn't she?
-I...
-...How can I ever forget you?
Your Majesty.
What is it?
That lady...
...is a shaman.
Who said she isn't?
I served you your whole life.
How could I not understand
what you are thinking?
Please, do not let your heart waver.
So you're suggesting
that I will waver because of a shaman?
That lady...
...is not Yeon Woo.
Similar as they might be,
Lady Yeon Woo is already...
Shut it. Shut your mouth!
Your Majesty.
I can't stand looking at you,
so turn around.
Last night,
the Queen came to the palace and left.
She threw away her pride as a woman...
...and came here with difficulty.
But when she had to turn back,
how do you think the Queen felt?
So please, understand
the Queen's feelings.
Your Majesty. Your Majesty!
What is the fuss about?
There is word that His Majesty
is coming to Gyo Tae Palace.
Hurry.
Hurry and bring my accessories over.
-Quickly.
-Yes.
Did you say His Majesty
has gone to Gyo Tae Palace?
Yes, Your Highness.
I saw it myself while coming here.
Thus far, the Queen has endured
a lot of heartache.
Her sincerity is what made His Majesty
open his heart to her.
It is truly remarkable.
What?
After receiving the shaman at his palace,
everything is becoming comfortable.
How can it only be thanks to that child?
Could it not be the heavens' way
of paying back all the affection
that Your Highness has shown for him
on a daily basis?
Just by being by his side,
his body has become stronger...
...and she has even managed
to resolve their troubled relationship.
She is indeed worthy of being
Shaman Jang's successor.
I think we should tell
the Office of Astronomy
to pick another auspicious date
for the consummation.
What?
A date has already been set, so why?
Because of His Majesty's refusal, every
time we put effort into picking a date,
it turned out to be a waste of time,
didn't it?
Now, His Majesty's body is strong
and it seems like
their relationship is improving,
so how can we elude this opportunity?
But if we consider the adverse weather
and the busy schedule that is to come,
there probably won't be
many auspicious days left.
The heavens are helping us.
How can we wait one month?
We have to advance the date
as much as we can.
You do not look well.
Is there a concern you have
that you cannot talk about?
For me...
...besides being concerned
about Your Majesty's well-being,
what else is there to be concerned about?
It is just that I was not able
to sleep well last night.
Last night...
...I heard you came by Gang Nyung Palace.
I apologize.
I know it was wrong, but I was
worried about your health, so I...
What were you trying to monitor?
What?
Monitor?
How can you say such improper...
No matter what you saw or heard...
...there was no one in my bedroom.
If you saw something...
...that was the talisman
that the Office of Astronomy used.
Was it in a month?
What are you referring to?
Our consummation date.
The royal physicians
and the Office of Astronomy...
...have asked for us
to distance ourselves until then...
...and focus on purifying
our body and soul.
Therefore, don't come
to Gang Nyung Palace again.
Is that what you mean?
Looks like you understand.
What exactly are you trying to hide?
What would you be so adamant to hide...
...that you're even concerned about
my presence in your quarters?
Is it love?
A dead girl was not enough.
Are you keeping a lowly shaman
close to your heart now?
Court Lady Jo.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Among the King's attendants,
see if there is anyone we can use.
What?
Why a secretive attendant?
If you find someone useful...
...tell her to watch the shaman
that is by His Majesty's side every night,
and report everything to me.
Your Majesty.
Shaman?
Look closely at my face.
The woman who came here
with me last time.
Don't you remember her?
Oh! I do remember.
Because she was so gentle and dignified,
I thought she was aristocratic.
She is a shaman?
Has she come again since then?
She hasn't, if I remember correctly.
All right.
Just hang on a moment.
I will take you to a physician.
And also, I am not an ahjussi, Kiddo!
She was filled with such evil
that we sent her far away to the south.
Although I am thankful
for your consideration,
I am in a safe place now.
She did not even register her name,
and committed a promiscuous offense.
Isn't it natural we would try
to apprehend her?
I am Wol.
One of the two is lying to me for sure...
...but for what reason would you lie?
Brother!
Brother?
You were alive!
Hold on!
From what I can see,
you shouldn't be a gisaeng...
Not a gisaeng, a shaman.
I am a palace shaman.
A palace shaman?
Don't you remember the mystical stone?
Mystical stone?
Before our knees can touch the ground,
the child who foretold everything?
Wow, you've become a woman already.
I almost didn't recognize you.
Have you been well?
Since the Mistress took me in,
now I am not a fake, but a real shaman.
That's a relief.
Just now...
...did you say you're a shaman?
Yeah. I belong to the Seongsucheong.
The safest place for a shaman
is inside the capital.
A place where shamans
can freely enter the capital.
Among the Seongsucheong shamans...
...is there a shaman named Wol?
Wol...
I told you to watch your mouth
so many times.
Do I have to sew your mouth shut
before you come to your senses?!
Even if you see, pretend you didn't.
Even if you heard, pretend you didn't.
I told you not to say a word!
Did I say something?
Moon or sun as they may be,
I dare you to say them again.
I dare you to talk about anything
regarding Milady!
On that day,
your limbs will be torn from your body!
I don't know.
I've never heard that name before.
Don't be like this!
Think about it carefully.
I really don't know.
There is no such name
at the Seongsucheong.
Hey, Jan Shil!
-I'm coming!
-You're not coming?
How long do you plan on chatting?
Brother, if it's in our destiny,
let us meet again.
Hey...
If she's not in the Seongsucheong,
then where is she?
You were excited about leaving the palace,
but why are you acting like this?
I'm sorry, Brother.
I'm really sorry.
Milady.
Milady!
What is it?
Did you have that dream again?
You haven't had it for a while.
Why are you having it again?
I know.
This time, weren't you able
to see his face?
This time, I really wanted to see it.
This time I would have been able
to see it.
Milady, are you really that curious
about the face behind the mask?
Every night, you are by
his side, protecting him.
I was taken aback by your letter.
It was more than enough
to show me how much you resented me.
I do not resent you.
You say you do not,
but your words were chastising me.
Am I wrong about what I saw?
A sincere remonstration
and personal feelings of resentment
are two different things.
So you were not resenting me,
but you were indeed chastising me.
All I wanted to say...
...is that just like rocks on the
street side exist for a reason.
I, as a shaman
and one of Your Majesty's subjects,
shall spare no effort in serving you.
So the intent was to chastise a king
for not taking heed of his people...
...not bringing to question
whether I was capable to run this nation.
Should a reader
ignore the writer's intentions
and let his judgment be clouded
by personal whims and prejudice,
then a misunderstanding will arise.
If Your Majesty felt that way,
would there not be a reason?
Now you seem to suggest,
that prejudice clouded my judgment enough
to make me ignore that letter's meaning,
which in itself is a criticism
of my tenure in politics.
I didn't mean that...
I treat you with benevolence
and yet you repay me with this affront.
Have you forgotten
who you are speaking to?
I am this nation, Joseon's...
Is anyone there?
Yes, Your Majesty.
How may I be of service?
I am exasperated.
I need to go for a walk,
so prepare for it.
The night wind is cold.
How about waiting until tomorrow...
Didn't you hear me say
I was exasperated?!
Hasten with the preparations.
What are you doing?
What?
I recall you saying
you would protect me from evil spirits,
so why aren't you doing your job now?
You are my talisman, so follow me.
Keep me at a distance.
I told you to follow me at a distance!
Woon.
You as well.
You stay where you are.
You are my talisman, aren't you?
Go further back!
Closed.
Let go!
Yeon Woo.
Yeon Woo!
By any chance, was this the place...
...where Your Majesty
buried your memories and sorrow?
Do the tears someone
shed here in the past...
...belong to you, Sire?
What on earth did you see?
Did you see it with your spiritual powers?
I did.
Then, use the same powers to guess.
Guess what?
What do you think I will be doing next?
Today, Hyung Sun
said something very strange to me.
What do you think about it?
Do you believe
that I can harbor feelings...
...for a lowly shaman like you?
Why are you doing this?
What are you doing? Go after them.
Tell me...
...who are you?
-I am Shaman Wol.
-No!
You are not Wol.
Then, who am I?
I used to live as a nameless shaman...
...until Your Majesty gave me this name.
Do you really...
...not know who I am?
Have you really never met me?
Whose traces
are you expecting to find in me?
Who are you seeing, when you look at me?
Yeon Woo...
...is she the one?
What is the reason you allow me
to stay by your side?
Is it because I look like that person?
But...
...I'm not who you're looking for.
Shut it, shut that mouth!
You are crossing the line now.
Does allowing you to be by my side
mean I gave you my heart as well?
You are nothing but a lowly talisman,
no more and no less than that!
Who are you to dare...
How dare you.
Who do you think you are?
Who would dare... ...confuse me this way?
Stay away from me.
If you cross the line again,
I will not forgive you.
I will be sleeping alone tonight,
so you do not need to follow me in.
Woon.
Without letting her know,
escort her back.
Also, on your way back, there
is somewhere you need to go.
Does allowing you to be by my side
mean I gave you my heart as well?
You are nothing but a lowly talisman,
no more and no less than that!
What are you doing here,
instead of being by His Majesty's side?
Did something happen?
Mistress.
Who exactly...
...am I?
You sensed spiritual powers in me
when I used to wander the streets
after being abandoned by my parents.
That is the reason you took me in,
you said at the time.
And why would you suddenly bring that up?
In the last few days...
...weird memories have kept
creeping up on me.
They are certainly
someone else's memories...
...but they feel so strongly as my own.
So I am confused.
It is but a result of your not being able
to control your spiritual powers yet.
So, do not let
those past memories affect you.
So...
...those memories will never
truly be mine, I suppose?
No matter how much I resemble her...
...I cannot be that person, right?
Who is it?
Prince Yang Myung, you startled me!
That was exactly my purpose.
What? Why do you climb over the wall
every time you come in?
That's...
...I've just gotten used to it
so I prefer it over the front gates.
And besides, we're past the curfew.
It was hard to slip past the patrols!
Come, now. Let's go in and have a drink.
Jae Woon.
What brings you here this late at night?
You startled me.
How can you appear without making a sound?
You didn't climb over the wall like me,
did you?
Given how late it was...
Did you come as a royal messenger,
or as a friend?
His Majesty has ordered
the Prince Consort to enter the palace.
Why did he seek my presence so suddenly?
Well... Unless Your Majesty
allowed you to disclose details,
you certainly wouldn't divulge them.
Since I have relayed the command,
I will be going now.
Already?
I have left my position long enough.
Yeon Woo said it was a birthday present
and made it for me.
Then, this is your sister's handwriting?
That is right.
Her handwriting is extraordinary.
Not just her handwriting,
but her deep understanding
of the Classics of Literature
was enough to pity the fact
that she was born a girl.
More than that,
she was a thoughtful and respectful child.
But, why do you ask that?
It is because her writing caught my eye,
so I asked.
Who sent you?
Why were you watching over
the Prince Consort's residence?
You're...
...Kim Jae Woon finally capitulates
for a woman.
Remarkable, indeed.
It is an unprecedented event.
What do you mean, woman?
It is not like that.
What else do you think it could be?
Anyway, a woman is a woman.
But I've heard that Your Highness
has found a lover as well.
I guess Princess Min Hwa tattled on me.
Is it true, then?
I thought it was a joke,
but I guess it is true.
What kind of person is she?
Well...
To tell you the truth,
I don't know either.
-What?
-Did you know this?
Eight years ago, the night before
the Crown Princess selection...
...I climbed over this house's wall.
Will you go with me?
I can throw away my princehood,
the title of Prince Yang Myung,
wrap you up and run away with you.
But...
...do you know what
your sister said to me?
You shouldn't jest like that.
Her sparkling eyes were so firm...
...that I could say no more.
Your Highness.
But you know, if on that day...
...I had not concealed my sincerity
by laughing...
Deceiving yourself and living like that...
...is an awful way of living, isn't it?
...If only I had more courage,
and extended my hand...
...If I had tried just a little harder...
...and asked her to run away with me.
Would that child...
...be by my side?
You haven't gone to bed yet?
Where have you been this late at night?
You got hurt.
How did that happen?
While practicing with my sword,
I cut myself accidentally.
Come here so I can take a look at it.
I said I'm all right.
Only my clothes were cut
and there is no wound.
Where exactly did you go?
I just...
...visited my previous owners' house.
They must have been wonderful people,
for you to visit them after all this time.
Yes.
They were really good people.
They took someone
who was treated like an animal
and gave me warmth
like no other did before.
They gave me a beautiful name, Seol.
That is the kind of person you were,
Milady.
Both of us are aging...
...but in my memory, your sister...
...remains thirteen.
Il Su Bul Toe.
"Once you put down a piece,"
"you cannot ever move
or change its place."
That is what you taught me, right?
A person's heart is the same thing.
Once someone finds a place
in your heart, it won't change.
So regardless of what the results
of the selection might be.
I will never forget the Crown Prince.
Are you a spirit or a person?
You are...
...It is me, Brother.
What are you doing here so late?
I am sorry, Brother.
I was wrong.
Sorry?
For what?
I will help you meet...
...that person you were looking for.
Brother...
...you saved my life,
so I will pay you back, no matter what.
I will do it even if I have to die for it.
I will make sure you meet her.
So don't be in too much pain.
Whose traces
are you expecting to find in me?
Who are you seeing, when you look at me?
Please return to your room.
I am well enough to be alone now.
No, it's all right.
Until you regain your energy,
I will not leave your side.
Thanks to you, Princess,
I am feeling much better.
I will not be sad anymore, so...
Mother.
Your Highness is here as well?
She was worried I would be lonely, so she
has not left my side since yesterday.
Thank you for being so caring
towards my mother.
We're a married couple,
so there is no need for such words.
Husband, are you going to the palace?
Yes.
I received a royal command last night.
Why are you only telling me now?
If you had told me,
I would have gone with you.
I did not even think of that.
Next time, I will certainly tell you.
I will be going then, Mother.
Beware of not being a nuisance
to His Majesty.
Are you angry because
he's going to the palace alone?
It is not that I am angry.
I feel uneasy.
Uneasy?
What are you uneasy about?
Because if Husband enters the palace...
Teacher!
How long has it been since we last met?
Had I not sought your presence,
how much longer would I have waited?
Your Majesty.
I shall first pay my respects,
so please sit down.
Respects... What respects?
Bring us refreshments.
Also, I will be chatting
with my teacher privately,
so do not let anyone enter
and take your leave.
What do you mean
the Prince Consort has entered the palace?
Is that even proper of him to do so?
He should live his life quietly
and then die.
He has become a Prince Consort,
so how dare he enter the palace
in broad daylight?
That is true.
As the princess' husband, he obviously
cannot participate in politics,
but the law states that he may not even
converse about the classics.
It is dangerous.
Because of him I've lost places
in the hearts of many a palace maid.
What do you mean by places?
If you had to rank
the most handsome men in the palace,
surely I would come right after Woon,
don't you think?
But if he comes and shakes everything up,
what am I to do?!
Is there even something to be shaken?
If this was an expedient by His Majesty
to gather scholars for a political ploy.
But Heo Yeom is not the kind of man
who would be able to shake up politics.
Heo Yeom has great symbolic value
for those scholars.
His presence alone could encourage
the scholars to build a united front.
He could even muster more influence
than his own father, Director Heo.
Heo Yeom.
Why would a downtrodden man
like him suddenly come to the palace?
What is this?
It is the last letter that my sister left.
At first I thought of burying it,
as a long time has passed.
But then I felt that it was my duty
to deliver this letter to whom it belongs.
Is this really...
...a letter that Lady Yeon Woo
left for me?
Indeed.
So these are Lady Yeon Woo's...
...final words for me.
While she was alive,
Your Majesty was the only one
she ever considered her soulmate.
Should you burn those words
for they belong to a sinner...
...and should you do so yourself.
Should you bestow her this honor,
she would find peace in eternal sleep,
and find solace.
So I plead with you...
...to forget my sister once and for all.
Her Majesty the Queen
is now by your side, Sire.
Please do not make the Queen
lonely any longer.
If Your Majesty continues living
in the shadow of that child,
I am sure she would never find peace.
My sister and I plead you
with earnest devotion...
...and hope you will accept.
Your Majesty.
All of you...
...keep telling me to forget her.
Your Excellency.
I hope you'll visit the palace
more frequently.
His Majesty might not make it obvious,
but he dearly misses you.
How can a Prince Consort freely roam
these sacred walls?
Please, stay by His Majesty's side,
and take good care of him.
It is you, Your Excellency...
...who should have stayed
by His Majesty's side.
Your Highness the Crown Prince.
I am writing to you
with the last of my strengths.
My last words might be destroyed...
...or never reach you, for all I know.
But I am still writing to you.
For me,
being able to see Your Highness
before death takes me...
...has filled me with happiness.
So please, stop blaming yourself.
And bury what happened to me
deep in your memories.
My Father shall soon
bring me that infusion.
Drinking it will mean
I might never see you again.
So please, forget about me.
And please be healthy enough
for the both of us.
Become a great king
who looks out for his people.
She was worried about my health.
Up until her very last breath...
...she mustered all the strength
she had left to write me.
But this fool instead...
...this fool...
Your Majesty...
...think of the pain...
...of how lonely she was.
That firm handwriting of hers...
...has become but a trembling jumble.
Hyung Sun.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Tell the Chief Court Supervisor...
...to bring her belongings.
Yes.
I cannot even remember.
I can't remember what
Yeon Woo's handwriting looked like.
I have to see it.
I have to see again...
...that letter she wrote me.
Your wish is my command.
After taking a walk at night,
His Majesty ordered the talisman
not to enter his room.
A walk?
They went for a walk together
that late at night?
He's always gone for walks
whenever he wasn't feeling well, so...
Did anything happen after that?
Not that I...
...after the Prince Consort visited
this morning,
His Majesty seemed very troubled.
He suddenly told a court lady
to bring a box.
-A box?
-Yes.
It looked like an ordinary box,
but the character for rain
was inscribed on the lid.
Did you just say rain?
Woon.
Yes, Sire.
Wol.
Bring Wol.
Bring Wol here immediately!
Do you...
...recognize me?