Do you know
that you attacked the wrong target?
"Wrong target"?
Zea and I attacked the real perpetrator.
Our target's name is Radit.
I'm sure he is working on his own.
He's not involved with any motorbike gang.
We are going to find out about Radit.
There is no one named Radit here.
Ares!
- Hey!
- Move!
Spin!
That's why I told you to refrain.
Don't be reckless!
My ears.
Baby!
I'm out of suspension.
What's wrong, Babe?
I want to break up.
I don't...
I don't understand.
Why?
Because I said so.
But we can talk about it, Babe.
Ardhan.
We're still in high school.
We should be having fun at our age.
Instead of being busy
with our own problems.
You also know that we've been
keeping our problems to ourselves.
It's toxic, Ardhan.
But, Babe.
I need your support right now.
Me too.
I also really need your support.
But Calderioz is your priority right now.
I can't keep on supporting you
when you don't even focus on me too.
Maybe it's best for us to be on our own.
Babe, I can't...
Please.
- But this isn't...
- Ardhan.
You once asked me what I want.
This is what I want.
And you promised
to fulfill it.
That you would do what I want.
But, Babe.
That's not what I meant.
Let's go home.
You go first.
I'm still going to accompany Karissa.
She just broke up with Ardhan.
"Broke up"?
Don't say it out loud!
I feel bad for Karissa.
- Okay?
- I'm going to wait here then.
You don't need to. Just go.
Didn't you say you're going to the base?
I'll be fine. Okay?
Zea.
I don't want to go home alone.
Ares, I want to go home alone.
It's okay. Just go to the base.
Please. Okay?
I'll share my live location, okay?
- Take care, bye!
- Bye!
Karissa.
Sorry I left in the middle of your story.
Aren't you going home with Ares?
It's okay.
I can go home by myself.
He's going to meet the other
Calderioz members anyway.
Maybe because you're also
a motorbike gang member, Zea.
So you understand Ares' activities.
I...
I can't.
I know I've been demanding a lot
from Ardhan lately.
Meanwhile, he's busy
taking care of Calderioz.
Poor guy.
But,
wouldn't this decision
makes him more miserable?
At least he'll be able to forget it
since he's preoccupied
with the exams and Calderioz.
But do you still love Ardhan?
Of course I do.
But maybe I just need time
for us to take care of our own things.
I understand.
Sometimes,
distance can be our way to show our love.
My advice is
don't regret it.
It's okay.
Oh, dear.
Chill, man.
Hey. Ardhan?
What's wrong with you?
He broke up with Karissa.
Shut the hell up, Richie.
Don't be such a know-it-all.
If he broke up with Karissa,
I'd be the first to know.
I always know your friend better than you.
Enough.
- Thank you.
- Sure thing.
Where's Ares?
He's with the guys.
He usually drops me home.
Enough with this.
What's wrong?
You have to see this.
Follow me.
She witnessed it.
- This...
- Look at that.
(Stop or Die!)
They're not playing around!
You're not safe here.
You have to come home.
But...
Don't argue with me on this.
When you're with the Wolves,
things like this never happened.
Except for my incident.
And do you remember how bad it was?
It's not about facing this on your own.
But this shows they're not playing around.
What happened?
See for yourself.
Where did you get it?
Let's talk outside.
Aeros, what are you doing?
You wait here.
- Aeros.
- You wait here. Come on, move it.
Ares.
You said you're going to
keep your promise.
So, what kind of terror is that?
Can you keep Zea safe?
If you can't,
I'm going to bring Zea back to Bandung.
Where were you?
Sorry.
I'm asking you one more time.
Can you keep my sister safe?
I assure you,
nothing will happen to Zea.
You can trust me.
Okay.
Aeros, this is not the time
to put blame on others.
We should find out about this together.
No.
You can't involve yourself in...
I'm not a kid anymore.
When you were in a coma,
I had to found out everything on my own.
And then Ares came
and helped me.
I just don't want anything
to happen to you.
Don't worry.
I'm going to discuss this
with the guys straight away.
Let me know.
(Ardhan: Baby. I'm sorry)
(Ardhan: Please don't break up with me)
(Ardhan: I love you so much)
(Ardhan: Babe, please don't avoid me)
Let me.
Okay.
Done.
Is there no one looking for you
if you're not home at this hour?
No one.
I only live with my maid and my driver.
Where are your parents?
It's a long story.
Your friends don't come here very often.
Yeah, they're busy with their own things.
By the way, why haven't you gone home yet?
Home where?
Wait, where's your home?
Here.
Seriously?
No.
I live in a house my Mom left for me.
But I'm here most of the time.
I see.
When I'm home,
especially when I'm alone,
I tend to remember her.
There used to be someone
asking me what time I will come home.
"Don't come home late,
there are lots of bad people."
But,
not anymore.
So,
whether I'm home or not,
there's no big difference.
We're not that much different.
I'm surprised, you know.
When you said you're friends
with the Calderioz members.
Why?
I didn't expect it.
My Mom was worried about bike gangs.
Because of their bad image?
Well, it depends on the gang.
But after listening to your stories,
your friends are good people.
They are very good people.
A far cry from that nasty news.
How did it go?
I heard there was a clarification video?
That's right.
Here's the story.
There's a bad person who intentionally
smeared Calderioz's name.
I thought
Calderioz was really going to split.
Thank God that didnít happen.
Well, I'm impressed by Ares.
He's
great at managing his members.
Even Aiden respected him.
Sorry.
What's wrong?
(Zea: Guys, take a look at this)
(Stop or Die!)
Do you remember
at the Gala,
someone vandalized the car
with the writing...
Stop or Die?
Yes, "Stop or Die".
That person terrorized Zea directly.
He broke Zea's window.
Oh, my God. I'm so worried
that they'll do much worse than this.
Let me drop you home, please.
I'm worried.
Okay?
You want me to send you the notes?
- Okay.
Baby. Babe.
Give me a minute to talk to you. Please.
- No.
- Babe!
Oh, dear!
Hello, my single friend.
What are you talking about?
Ardhan, when it comes to romance,
you're the expert.
But if it's about exes,
that's not your specialty.
Do you want to get back with Karissa?
You don't need to ask.
Of course I want that.
So, will you follow my advice?
- What?
- But,
you have to do everything I say.
Just say it!
Are you crazy? There's no way
I can do that!
- I'll be embarrassed.
- Then you don't want to be with her.
Do you want to get back with her?
Did you read our group chat?
Poor Zea. The terror is spreading.
It's horrible.
I can't stop thinking about it.
They attacked her house.
Is this the risk
of dating a motorbike gang member?
What if we accompany her?
Since she lives alone with her maid.
The house won't be as quiet
if we stay there.
Can you stay the night there?
I can. I also live alone anyway.
I need to ask for permission.
You know how my parents are.
I can.
How come you're being
loyal to your friend?
Make up, please.
Don't ignore each other for too long.
I am loyal.
Pfft!
I even willingly became single
to accompany you.
I didn't ask for that.
I have Serra for that.
Serra is with Jayden now.
You just don't know it yet.
No, you're talking nonsense.
Not yet.
"Not yet"?
So, you'll be with him?
To my fellow beloved Derlangga students,
I have an important announcement today!
Is everybody here already?
We're here!
Okay!
On this bright day,
I want to declare something!
That I
can't live without Karissa Andromeda!
Aka "My Baby".
Why am I standing here?
Because I want you all to be my witness
that I can't live without Karissa.
- Do you all understand?
- We do.
Baby.
You know I can't live without you.
So, please.
Be my girlfriend again, okay?
Baby!
Ardhan.
It was only your first try.
Am I right?
Do you know how embarrassed I am?
This was your idea.
I know you're embarrassed,
but at least you tried.
- We'll try again. I have a lot...
- No.
There's no need for that.
We're having a meeting
at the base tonight.
Any update?
I'll let you know later.
When will he stop saying "later"?
Can you shut your mouth?
Relax.
Aeros told me to go back to Bandung.
He's worried about
the situation in Jakarta.
But,
I will try my best to stay here.
Let's solve this together.
Zea.
I don't want you to be in danger again.
Ares, what are you talking about?
I was involved with a bike gang
before I knew you.
This isn't danger.
This is my world.
Zea.
Ares, I'm staying here
with you.
Ares, let's go to the class.
The teacher's here.
The class is going to start soon.
Just go first.
Okay. Don't be late,
our teacher's waiting.
Why is she so annoying?
Don't mind her. As long as
she's not bothering us,
just ignore her.
We can't. The more we ignore her,
the more annoying she'll be.
You have to...
Zea?
What?
Jealous?
No.
- What are you talking about?
- What's wrong, Babe?
What's your favorite drink?
Why are you asking that all of a sudden?
I just want to know.
Watermelon juice.
Wait, why are you still here?
You don't want to go back to Bandung,
so I'm staying here.
You're exaggerating.
Where's Ares?
Why didn't he drop you home?
He dropped me home
but he went straight to the base.
This is our only clue.
(Labos Helmet)
There's only one custom helmet shop.
And it's likely
connected to
Wolves?
Is Radit a Wolves member?
We don't know yet.
Whichever gang he is a member of,
we already know he's the perpetrator.
We know the location and the person.
So, what are we waiting for?
Let's just attack.
Didn't you learn your lesson?
The person's right in front of us.
Have you forgotten
how your attack ended up?
But it has been proven
that someone was recording it
- Someone...
- That's why I'm avoiding it.
You're too afraid to take action.
I'm thinking about the strategy.
It's time your "we'll see" principal
is changed into "what will we do".
Just attack first.
Enough.
We better divide our tasks.
We know that Ares is best
at building a strategy.
And Richie is good at attacking.
But only if there's a strategy.
Richie.
The attack the other day was cool.
But it had no strategy at all.
So, we better divide our tasks.
Moreo, Richie, and I
will do a stakeout around Labos.
If there's something,
Richie will act.
Moreo will contact Ares.
And I
will make sure no one escapes.
Because we're still lacking information,
you will be with Megan
to find the information out there, Ares.
Ask Wolves, anywhere.
We need to find out
the mastermind behind this.
Everybody agrees?
- Agree.
I agree with Ardhan.
Me too.
Hey!
There's nothing out there.
Calm down.
I was just looking around.
Haven't you slept yet?
Not yet. We're still chatting.
Why are you smiling?
What? I can't smile,
I can't be mad either.
You can't have her, she's someone else's.
Who?
Moreo?
It's not official yet.
So,
someone is waiting
for certainty from Moreo?
Zea, why did you tell them?
I don't like this!
I will not be his girlfriend. Never.
Why?
Right, why not?
Why should I?
Just because we're Calz Angels,
do we have to be with Calderioz members?
Serra?
She's with Jayden.
I know you like Jayden.
Stop it. Here's the thing, Selina.
If Moreo asks you to be his girlfriend,
what will you do?
Will you say yes?
She's thinking about it!
It's obvious you like him.
You're just too proud to admit it.
Let's stop this.
She's sulking.
(Moreo: If the perpetrator comes out,
I'll finish him)
(Selina: All by yourself?)
(Moreo: Yes, easy peasy)
- Were you peeking?
- No.
You're sick, you know that?
Didn't they teach you manners in New York?
- Calm down.
- Manners!
- Calm down? Are you crazy?
Can you shut your mouth?
Do you want us to get caught?
(Ardhan: Babe, I miss you)
What?
What is it?
Moreo is going to catch the perpetrator.
- Now?
- Yes, he's chatting with me about it.
You two are chatting. Lovebirds!
- Serra.
- Zea.
Can't sleep?
Since no one's home,
I've been having a hard time sleeping.
Quiet, isn't it?
Very.
It feels like
I'm all alone in this world.
Although I have Jayden,
sometimes something is
missing.
I still miss Aiden once in a while.
Am I being cruel to Jayden?
The important thing
is that you've come clean to Jayden.
Jayden knows about Aiden, doesn't he?
He knows.
Sometimes I tell him stories about Aiden.
Well, then he knows the risk.
Why are they taking so long?
Babe.
Babe, hang on. Please.
We've broken up, Ardhan.
But I can't, Babe.
No more "Babe".