Music
This is an international competition.
The athletes and the audience will be entering the arena immediately.
So, there can't be any safety issues.
Turn off the battery and move out.
Why is there no image?
Why is there a display that shows the signal is lost?
Look, I'm just saying that the airspace is not good.
I told you that it's all made up by spending money.
And it's all flying up.
So what's the situation now?
I have an automatic anti-aircraft. Wait a minute.
Let's look for it. I think.
Where do you think you're looking for it now?
You're here.
Comrade.
You are suspected of flying in the airspace.
Private drone.
Dangerous public safety.
Come with us.
No, buddy, your hats are too big.
And it's dangerous public safety.
We are drones, not bombers.
Comrade, please cooperate with us.
I can't cooperate. Why should I go with you?
We have to find the plane.
No need.
The plane has been hit by our guidance.
Please cooperate.
You hit my plane.
Do you know how much my plane costs?
It's enough to buy your life.
Don't pull me.
Comrade.
Please let go of my hand.
I won't let go.
Give me back the plane.
Comrade, please cooperate with us.
I won't let go.
You won't let go.
Don't you understand?
I want you to return the plane to me.
Comrade, be careful.
What's wrong with me?
Comrade, we are on a mission.
We record the whole process.
If you do it again,
we will take countermeasures against you.
What are you talking about?
Can you countermeasure against me?
How can I touch you?
It hurts.
I warn you.
I have an supervisor.
Let's talk.
Why are you hitting me?
How many times do I have to tell you?
Come with us.
Report, the two drone pilots are taking back the plane.
I won't let go.
I paid for the ticket.
You can't do this.
Your ticket is not valid.
No way.
I paid for the ticket.
What did you do?
You can scan the ticket.
Their ticket is not valid.
Okay, we will deal with it.
Your ticket is not valid.
It is not compatible with your personal information.
It's the same with yours.
No way.
Let's go find the ticket seller.
Your ticket is the same with yours.
I saved a lot of money to buy this ticket.
No way.
Can I stand inside and watch?
Okay, I'll go out and ask.
Thank you.
What's going on?
Report,
several spectators came with fake tickets.
We didn't let them in.
That girl was also cheated.
She is there.
Stop playing.
Your ticket is fake.
Are you sure I sold this ticket to you?
Yes.
Give me the money back.
Yes, give me the money back.
Girl,
we are all selling our tickets.
We have no reason to give up.
If you don't give me back, I'll call the police.
Go ahead.
You like to bargain.
What does it have to do with me?
Who can prove that this is a fake ticket?
Who can prove that this ticket is for you?
Girl, help us watch them.
We'll go to the police.
I have a transfer record.
Don't play tricks.
I'll deal with you.
Go.
I talked to the police.
They want to leave a message.
Let them help you.
Okay.
Give me the money.
No.
I'll go.
Girl,
remember to buy tickets through the right channel.
Wait here.
Do you want tickets?
It's on sale.
Guys, it's almost done.
We're leaving.
Go find a place to eat.
Brother,
where's the food?
Here, take a seat.
Who are you?
I'm An An.
Thanks, Captain Lin.
It's all about the team.
They haven't eaten yet.
Make sure they're well-prepared.
Why are you looking at me?
Don't talk.
It's all because of you.
Really?
Don't play tricks.
You're selling tickets too?
No.
I beat up Wu Jiaren.
It's not my style.
Hurry up.
Take it.
The front row.
Thanks, Uncle.
Go in.
It's about to start.
Thanks, Uncle.
Goodbye, Uncle.
How much is it?
I'll give it to you later.
1,680.
How much?
Are you crazy?
Normally, the ticket is 200 or 300 yuan.
Why did you spend 1,680?
Captain,
at this point,
we only have the front row.
Fine.
Let's just make it a dream.
There are three bottles of water in this bag.
Okay, I'll handle it.
Sir, we're going to start the bag check.
Your ID card and your ticket.
Please go out.
Take off your hat and knife.
Thank you.
Why are there three bottles?
I'll use one.
The rest is for my friend.
Have a sip.
Then, why don't you choose one?
The rest is for my friend.
I don't think it's suitable for me.
You have to drink all three.
Okay.
It's all herbal tea.
Here.
Thank you, Captain.
Okay.
Thank you.
You've worked hard.
Let's go.
He's so handsome.
He's indeed handsome.
He's even donated to the country.
Yes, he's so elegant.
I like the three of them.
I think the first one is good.
I'm not handsome.
Attention!
The candidates are entering.
Be quiet.
Captain, Captain.
I'll take a picture of you.
Here.
Look.
I'm so happy.
But I think this one is good.
Actually, this one is also good.
This one.
I think it's more comfortable.
Do you think so?
I'll open my eyes.
This is the little pineapple today.
How about this?
Can you lift this up?
Okay.
Uncle, your water cup.
Uncle, you left something.
Uncle.
Sister Wujun.
What's wrong?
It's like this.
Just now, an uncle left his water cup there.
I called him several times, but he didn't answer me.
Just call the committee's food and drink manager.
Where is it?
Go over there.
Okay.
Wait.
Leave it to us.
Okay.
Where is the seat of the owner?
Over there.
The second row of the first district.
Okay, thank you.
Ji Haichao,
bring the battlefield radar to the command post.
Over.
Yes, sir.
The battlefield radar.
Report.
We found three different types of particles.
They are being integrated into the water cup.
It could be a liquid bomb.
What's the situation?
Three different types of particles are being integrated.
When the water cup is heated by itself,
it will explode when it reaches a certain temperature.
It's hard to judge by the power.
Xiao Ran, put it in the fireproof case immediately.
Transfer the suspicious explosive.
Yes, sir.
Captain Linda.
We found a similar explosive.
Over.
Is it a vegetable?
I'll arrange the vegetables immediately.
No need for now.
I'm handling the explosive.
Close all exits immediately.
Over.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
I found it.
Captain.
What's the situation?
The suspect is locked.
Is it this one?
Attention, all units.
The suspect, male,
is about 175 cm tall.
The coffee cup is on the outside.
The black alarm clock is on the top of the black head.
The target is under control.
Over.
Report, I'm Chen Ansheng.
I've seen this person near the F passage.
I'm looking for him now.
Attention, all units.
Report at any time if anything happens.
Over.
I'll go and have a look.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to the international basketball competition.
The scene of the Yuehai Battle.
Next, let's welcome the players.
The first player is Chen Ansheng.
He's the first player to play in the international basketball competition.
The first player to play in the international basketball competition is Shen Yang.
The first player to play in the international basketball competition is Chen Ansheng.
Shen Yang, faster.
Sorry.
It's about to start.
Stop.
Don't move!
Don't push me!
I can't do it! Don't push me!
Don't move!
The suspect, Li Huaqing, is a 43-year-old male.
According to the suspect, his 13-year-old daughter died of cancer two years ago.
Li Huaqing thinks that his daughter's death is due to a drug caused by a anti-cancer drug
developed and produced by the Ruihe Biotech Technology Co., Ltd.
He has been complaining to relevant departments for the past two years,
but they were all rejected due to insufficient evidence.
He heard that Ruihe Biotech had sponsored this international basketball game
and made liquid bombs at home,
trying to create a terrorist attack on the field and attract the attention of relevant departments.
Of course, there is also a strong attitude of revenge society.
Now, the public security system has been handed over to the public security.
In addition, this time, the situation was sudden.
Comrade Qiu Tian's mind is calm and he is well-treated.
He has completed the security mission and the competition went smoothly.
This is worth praising.
Thank you, Chief.
Ling Zhenrong.
Yes.
Don't you have anything to say?
Report.
Comrade Qiu Tian's mind is clear and he is well-treated.
It is worth praising.
No, it is worth studying.
I think...
Don't think about it.
You are just saying this?
Yes.
Where is Chen Ansheng?
He is outside.
I will call him in.
Let him wait.
Good guy.
He knocked the female college student out with a single shot.
He is getting better.
Chief, the situation was urgent.
I think Chen Ansheng...
Don't think about it.
He is out of the hospital.
Yes.
I will let him reflect on himself.
Let him write a report.
No, I will write too.
Comrade, I really can't satisfy your request.
The task the leader gave me is to solve your problems properly.
Look, your classmate is out of the hospital now.
My task is completed.
As for the security you mentioned,
I really can't find him.
If you need to check your health,
I will arrange it for you now.
If you still want to make up for your health,
I can also apply to the leader.
As for finding someone,
I really can't help it.
I have to find him.
He saved my classmate's life.
We have to thank him.
You can give me some clues.
I can also give you some clues.
Classmate, let me tell you this.
The temporary leader's place is not a good place to rest.
When he left, he cleaned it up.
He didn't even leave a piece of paper.
They had a meal at our cafeteria.
They brushed the dishes.
They even dug the ground.
Where can I give you some clues?
The cafeteria?
They had a meal?
I remember.
They had a meal at my place.
After the meal,
they also cleaned my table.
They also brushed the dishes.
They also took off the floor.
Even the floor was cleaned.
Master, we all know this.
We just want to know which army they are from.
Where is the army?
I don't know which army they are from.
But I think they are near the Forbidden City.
Forbidden City?
Master, how did you analyze it?
Because when they were eating,
I asked them how the pancakes I made tasted.
A young man said
the taste of my pancakes was better than that of Forbidden City.
I was very happy then.
I told them about the pancakes.
So I analyzed that it was near Forbidden City.
I see. Thank you, master.
Thank you, master.
You're welcome.
Where are you going?
Master, I'm going to the Forbidden City's armed police force.
Forbidden City's armed police force?
I see. Come up.
Let's go.
We really found it.
I told you so.
Let's go.
Hello.
Brother Ding.
Hello, sir.
Who are you looking for?
I want to see your leader.
Chen Gai Sheng.
Yes, sir.
Have you figured it out?
I've figured it out.
If you've figured it out, tell me.
Why did you shoot at the civilians?
Sir.
I was using a web gun.
It was an unidentified weapon.
All right.
What weapon did I use to teach me?
You're reflecting on that?
Sir.
The man had already pulled the wire.
I was afraid I would be too slow.
It's not a matter of being slow.
It's a matter of influence.
The civilians don't know what weapon you used.
They only see the result.
It was you who knocked the bandits and hostages out.
Sir.
This is the best way I could think of at the time.
Come in.
Sir.
The girl and her classmate came yesterday.
They want to thank Chen Gai Sheng in person
for an interview.
Sir.
You don't have to thank me.
It's my duty.
Look.
All right.
Don't be so arrogant.
Go and explain the situation to them.
Don't cause any misunderstandings.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Hello, Sister Wu Ji.
Hello.
Please sit.
Sister.
Have I seen you before?
Yes, during the basketball game.
You gave me the three treasures.
Yes, it was me.
Did you find the master?
Yes.
Thank you.
I thank you on behalf of the master.
You're welcome.
Where's my classmate's brother?
Wait a minute.
He'll be here soon.
How's my business?
Not bad, right?
Not bad.
I'm not used to it in Changshun.
So you finally got a chance.
What chance?
They came to thank us.
Captain asked me to watch you
and take your low-key skills.
When the chief is happy,
he won't blame us.
I'm a man.
Why should I be afraid of being blamed?
Look at you.
You're so stupid.
Okay, you can judge me by my appearance.
Come in.
702 points.
That's scary.
You didn't study at Tsinghua University
but went to a special police academy.
What's wrong with you?
No, it's just my intuition.
After you arrived in the army,
you had a meal at the kitchen.
You had a car repair class.
Your comrades were on the flat road.
He was on the hard road.
Fortunately, he adjusted his attitude.
He didn't fear failure.
He overcame many obstacles and obstacles.
Just say that sentence.
The sword is sharp and sharp.
The plum blossom is fragrant.
Don't you want to interview me?
Remember this sentence.
Okay.
I remember it.
I'll continue.
Don't continue.
They came to thank Chen Hansheng.
Really?
Let him say a few words.
Okay.
You're being too kind.
You don't have to say thanks.
It's our duty to save people.
So that's how you save people.
I was kidnapped.
Shouldn't we negotiate first?
Why did you shoot me?
We're here to thank them.
If I don't say thanks,
can we come in?
Can you come with me?
Hey,
are you angry?
I misunderstood.
The gun is not a gun.
It's an unknown weapon.
It doesn't hurt human bodies.
How can it not hurt?
I was knocked out.
I woke up from the hospital.
You look pretty good now.
You don't have a toothache, right?
Yes.
Yes, I have a toothache.
What if I have a sequela?
What if I have a problem in five or ten years?
Let me explain.
The unknown weapon doesn't have a sequela.
I'm a special force.
I can only save your life.
I can't keep you alive.
What kind of attitude is that?
I'm just an attitude.
If I take one step later,
can you still sit here and talk to me?
Chen Ansheng, say something.
Don't worry,
we've contacted the hospital.
The doctor said that the possibility of having sequela
is very low.
Besides,
even if there's a problem,
our army will take responsibility.
Okay.
But he has to apologize to me today.
What do you mean?
He saved you and you're blaming him?
Don't you think he's bullying you?
I think you're bullying him.
Let me tell you.
If I knew you were here to cause trouble,
I wouldn't have come to help you.
I just think he's having a problem with his method.
Well,
we won't discuss the professional problem today.
You can discuss it.
Lei Feng, tell him.
Is there a problem with my method?
No.
You two go back first.
Okay, we'll go first.
Wait.
What's going on?
I told you to thank me.
You didn't even say a good word.
This is Dongguo's girlfriend,
Nongfu and Shi.
You're in the same college as her.
There's a difference between female students and female students.
Look at her classmate.
She's very sensible and reasonable.
She's kind-hearted.
You can make friends with her.
I'll ask her to contact Shi for you later.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
We're friends.
You're not even in a relationship.
Our leader has criticized Chen Hansheng.
So, don't take it to heart.
Sister, you're reasonable and have a good attitude.
Look at Chen Hansheng.
If he didn't talk like that,
I thought he was handsome.
The boys here may not be the same as the boys you usually meet.
They joined the army when they were young.
They went through many hardships to become special forces.
They have the most responsibilities and responsibilities.
I don't know how to deal with girls.
I think it's good.
It's real.
They're much better than those boys who talk.
If you say so,
they'll be happy if they know.
Actually, these boys are not worthy of being appreciated and understood.
You're praising them.
You're interviewing them.
They're going to be at the door of the house.
Isn't it embarrassing?
It's okay to do it.
Why should it be embarrassing?
No matter what you say, you have to punish them.
Okay.
Chen Hansheng is a soldier I led.
I told him to do it.
I'm responsible for it.
Nonsense.
Can you run away?
Chief, if you have to punish them,
I think someone has to be punished.
Who?
You.
You said that the army is about inheritance.
If I were Chen Hansheng, what would you do?
Chen Hansheng is a soldier I led.
I'm a soldier you led.
We three are one family.
If I want to punish them, I have to punish them together.
No.
That's it.
Wiring out a task.
Move your hand.
Thank you.
Where to?
What do you think of this child Chen Hansheng?
He is a talented man who could take hardships.
He's such a pushover.
Your
your
You said half inside and half outside.
What are you trying to say?
Do you know who Cheng Hansheng's father is?
I don't know.
I've seen his resume before.
His parents are all empty.
Later, I asked around
and found out that his parents passed away a long time ago.
You know Cheng Hansheng's father?
I know... who?
His father is called Cheng Weiguo.
Captain, his son's name is Chen Zai.
I've seen him many times when he was a kid.
After Captain Chen's death,
my wife didn't want to trouble anyone.
Maybe she didn't want to think about the sad things.
So she moved the child to another place.
She even changed her name.
She was afraid that everyone would look for her.
Later, my wife passed away.
The old captain adopted the child.
Sister-in-law.
I bought some things for Chen Zai.
I put them at the door.
If you need anything, call me anytime.
I'm leaving.
Sister-in-law.
Who are you looking for?
Where's Chen Zai?
He moved out.
Where did he move to?
I don't know.
Old captain.
Let me see you.
Drink less.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I lost my sister-in-law.
She thought I was annoying.
She's not well.
She's still a child.
Where did you go?
I'm sorry.
No wonder I've been looking for them for so many years.
They're hiding.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I only found out later.
The captain didn't want me to tell anyone.
Then I'm not a stranger to you.
If you told me earlier...
You're treating her better.
Of course.
I knew you thought so.
If you really treated her differently, you would have been late.
She graduated from a special school.
She had to come to Zhongnan base and collect the package.
So she's here.
You know what happened.
I'll leave Han Sheng to you.
Take care of her.
Yes, sir.
Why is he so efficient?
He's good.
Are you free?
Hello, sir.
What are you doing here?
Why are you crying in the middle of the night?
Sir, Han Sheng has been training with the captain of the squad.
He's been training hard.
Yes, so I'm using a machine gun to hit him.
Look.
What do you mean?
I'm just massaging him.
You're strong.
Let me give you a massage.
Fang Xiang and the others trained with you?
Yes.
What are you hiding from?
What did Fang Xiang do?
What did she do to you?
I told Captain Zhong to be cruel to me.
It's not their fault.
Then who's to blame?
What's wrong?
You're not working.
I'm not sure if they're the ones who are efficient.
Or you're lazy.
I'll go find them later.
I'll give you a raise tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
Keep fighting. I'm leaving.
See you, Captain.
You're hurting me.
You're fighting with that...
How do the other comrades rest?
I know.
I told you to keep your voice down.
Keep your voice down.
It's serious.
You're going to get a shock.
Go, go, go.
Keep your voice down. I'm going to sleep.
Thank you.
Hello, sir.
What is it?
I need you to sign a document.
What document?
The sponsor of this document
has sent us some post-mortem products.
What post-mortem products?
Some electronic products.
A tablet, computer, smartphone.
Is this a post-mortem product?
Yes.
We've received the letter.
But according to the regulations
of the military and the corporate network,
we can't take these things.
Yes, sir.
One, two, three, four.
We're here.
I'm sorry, Mr. Zhu.
We're not allowed to take photos.
I'll delete it.
It won't be completely deleted.
Instructor.
Who is this?
The sponsor of the basketball game.
Ms. Zhou Tianna.
The director asked me to take you around the camp.
This is our combat support team.
Hello.
Please give us your phone.
I deleted it.
The storage and delete function of the phone
will leave traces in the network cloud server.
The deleted photos will also be stored for a while.
It can be restored through technical methods.
So we have to deal with it.
Please understand.
I understand.
I don't understand the rules here.
This is fine. Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'll be careful next time.
I won't bother you then.
Let's go.
You're not allowed to take photos here, right?
We're all allowed to take photos.
Why are you stoping us?
Why?
Student.
The company has actually announced its donors for your college.
The money from the Administration
is very little.
Chen Jun.
Is there any problem with Dr. Shen's next season's fee?
Yes.
Shen Dongyang?
He's a Chinese guy.
Yeah, but the lab he works is not in China.
What's so special about him?
He has made a bunch of breakthroughs in the gene editing area.
Which means that this can help humans to break the hayflick limit.
Which means that this can actually change the fate of humanity.
Why do we care?
An analysis by a genetics expert shows that Shen Dongyang is obsessed with one-way gene editing.
And his research is actually to eliminate hereditary diseases for humans.
However, he has not noticed the greatest breakthroughs in this forbidden field.
What do you mean, forbidden area?
The flip side of an angel is a devil.
Which means that if we added Shen Dongyang's findings, we could make the greatest weapon in the world.
Sounds great.
It's a good business opportunity.
People contemplate their own ways.
But it's the God who directs the footsteps.
Amen.
God told me I must obtain the results of this man's research.
No.
God told me I must obtain this man.
Understood. I'll contact him as soon as possible.
No. Not you.
I've got someone more suitable.
Hunter.
Let Frank handle this.
I'm the God of God.
The God of God.
Or the God of God.
I'm the God of God.
Who can come to find this.
God.
I'm the God of God.