Do you know what reborn means?
It means getting another life
in addition to the one you already have.
I am getting married to Yi Jun.
Why?
Hold me.
Please hold me.
You said
you would hold me
and never let go.
That is what you said.
Actually, I...
I died once.
On September 19, 2025,
that is the 9th anniversary day when I met Jiang Jing Teng.
Yi Jun and I
are getting married.
And after he betrayed me,
I was killed in a car accident
not knowing the reason why.
I want to be
your one and only.
I
am reborn,
and I'm back to nine years ago.
I don't know
why I can go back to this time of life
to live it again.
But this time,
I want it to be the way I want.
I'll never let Jiang Jing Teng hurt me again.
Jiang Jing Teng.
I wouldn't be truly reborn
until I don't see you in school today.
I want to change destiny and
create my own
exciting life.
Shao Yi Chen.
Are you ready?
Coming!
This is not the excitement I wanted!
Mu Bai.
Let's split up.
I don't want to.
They will only go after me.
Friends should always stick together through thick and thin!
Loyalty is everything.
We don't even know you.
Our meeting is destiny.
Don't be so heartless.
I hate myself.
You getting beaten is none of my business.
Why did I stop and ask you if you're okay?
I know.
I hate myself too.
Being this handsome is a curse.
Turns out the girl I hit on yesterday
already has a boyfriend.
Why did you hit on another man's girlfriend?
Do you not have any morals?
They found us. Run!
Carry me.
Here is your breakfast, Jiang Jing Teng.
I didn't ask you to get me breakfast.
But I wanted to. Take it.
You damn assholes.
- Stop running.
- Stop!
Crime is really getting worse these days.
I have to go.
Jiang Jing Teng, take it.
Quick.
Here.
We should be
okay here.
Hey.
The gate is over there.
You really don't know the campus,
are you freshmen?
Hey.
You can not give up halfway when saving someone.
You better not let me catch you.
Hey!
What are you doing?
You spent two years writing that stupid fan diary.
From now on,
I have no strings attached
to this guy.
There was no such strings.
He's just a senior in school.
When we were freshmen in high school, he was a senior.
But...
Why are you looking at me like that?
After you fainted last month
and stopped breathing,
you have been acting weird
since the doctors saved your life.
Weird?
Weird how?
Take these diaries for example.
You used to value them more than your own life.
When we were juniors,
you got into fights because of the diaries.
Now you burn them without a second thought.
Let us just say I am too old for it now,
okay?
That is really random.
You are annoying.
Just hurry up and help.
If the sweet potatoes are still raw,
it's going to be your fault.
This is like burning ghost money.
It is gone.
My praise worthy youth.
Lee Mu Bai,
you really are an idiot.
From now on,
my destiny will be different.
Why is it suddenly windy?
How would I know? Help me pick it up.
It is all because you're burning stuff here.
It is not environmentally friendly.
Seriously,
Yi Jun has prepared breakfast for you every day
for almost a year now.
It could have warmed the coldest hearts
but you do not even care.
That is heartless.
I did not ask her to buy breakfast for me.
Why is it my business?
You're right,
you do not have to do anything.
You just have to be handsome.
Yup.
What is this?
Wow, the handwriting is beautiful.
Hey, Jing Teng.
When you go for a lay-up from the left,
you flinch your right shoulder.
Did you know that?
What?
It says so right here.
Hey,
go look for more.
What are you talking about?
Go.
Are you crazy? Why would there be more?
Idiot.
That's all for today.
Class dismissed.
Are you really going to take this class?
The professor is tough.
Maybe you should think it over.
Today is the last day for course registration.
There is still time.
I don't want to change courses.
Also,
it is a mandatory course
and only this professor is teaching it.
You can avoid it now
but you can't avoid it forever.
Why don't you take the course with me?
I can lend you
my notes.
I knew you're the best.
I love you.
Shao Yi Chen.
Which basketball team were you in in high school?
How long have you been stalking me?
Say it.
Why are you so scared of me?
Because you are scary.
Let go of this junior from other people's department.
He's a junior in your department?
Yes,
and he saved my life.
Right? Xiao Bai Mu.
You...
Shao Yi Chen.
Okay.
Xiao Chen Chen.
Xiao Bai Mu.
They are both mine now.
So, go back to the law department where you belong.
Did they see us?
I don't think so.
Hey,
what did you do to Jiang Jing Teng?
It has been a while since he found you in the classroom last time.
Why is he still chasing you?
How would I know?
The Civil Engineering Department is far from the Law Department,
why is he always around?
I didn't even see him
on the 19th.
Why is he chasing me?
You used to watch him secretly.
You didn't get in his way.
Maybe...
he found the pages
we couldn't find
so he wants to give you a piece of his mind.
How is that possible?
It could be possible.
Maybe
someone found it and gave it to him.
Even...
Even if...
Even if that is the case,
he'd never know they're from me.
Impossible.
He will never know
a junior named Shao Yi Chen
is hiding in the crowd, watching him.
Did you catch him?
No,
he got away again.
What did a freshman
ever do to you?
Yi Jun is always looking for your attention
but you ignore her.
Why do you keep chasing Shao Yi Chen
just for these pages?
I don't know.
I just have a feeling.
What feeling?
He should be mine.
Jiang Jing Teng,
what is wrong with you?
I have been running around these few days,
tiring myself out
for a feeling you have?
What?
Do you have a problem?
No.
You...
whatever you say.
So,
why would he suddenly come to you?
Or
he saw you somewhere before
and now likes you?
How is that possible?
In high school,
someone once said that
he'd be possessive
of anyone he likes.
No matter if it is a guy or girl,
as long as he likes you, that is enough.
No way.
Then why would he
keep bothering you?
This can't go on.
We can't even study.
I know.
Or
let's dig a hole
and bury him,
or turn him into a tetrapod,
and throw him into the ocean.
Don't be so merciless.
Don't you think bad people have a better life?
Good people die early,
bad people live forever.
No way.
Jiang Jing Teng has connections.
His dad is the dean of the law department in this school.
His mom is a judge.
His sister is a prosecutor.
He comes from a family of law.
Also, he is, as you know,
a well rounded athlete
who competed as an amateur boxer.
If you really want to do something to him,
you are going to be
doomed.
I know.
I was just daydreaming.
Sorry,
for dragging you into all this.
What are you talking about?
We are not strangers.
Besides,
I dragged you down too.
I finally found you.
President,
can you tell us
what exactly do you want?
My club
needs two freshmen to join,
so that we can continue operating.
Last time, you saved me
but ran away halfway.
To make up for the fault,
you can help to
save the universal research club I started.
- Huh?
He said he needs new members
but he just wants laborers.
What is this universal research club?
$80 for borrowing a book from the library.
$150 for lining up for tickets.
It is pretty much a servant agency.
At least
he splits it 30-70.
Hey,
he gets 70, we get 30.
At least it is better than being chased.
That's true.
Speaking of which,
I have not seen
Jiang Jing Teng's sidekick following us recently.
That's good.
I told you it was just a random thing.
You didn't believe me.
You worked the night shift again yesterday?
The night shift pays better.
I'll find the rest of the books,
you go find a place to rest
and I'll find you later.
It's okay.
It is faster if we look together.
Look carefully.
I found all the books,
how about you?
Not yet, wait a moment.
Why would I have feelings for you?
If I stop looking for you.
I'd even start missing you.
Shao Yi Chen.
Mu Bai,
ten more minutes.
Very good.
Thanks to all of you,
the income of our club is now
stronger than ever.
President,
it is just Yi Chen and I.
Of course.
Jiang,
are you looking for trouble?
I want to join your club.
Why should I let you join?
Xiao Bai Mu,
go get the application forms.
Hey,
can you do it?
Just cover it on top,
okay?
You got it.
You in the back,
can you set up the table here?
Thank you.
Do you need help?
You...
Hey,
is there any way
we can take care of that lunatic?
Which one do you want to take care of first?
Is it...
Lei Chong Jun, who only just thought of hosting a freshmen camping event
or Jiang Jing Teng, who solves his problems with money.
One is crazy about money. The other is crazy about you.
Hey,
Yi Chen.
Will you consider just accepting him?
Anyways, you like Jiang Jing Teng.
When he is bored,
you will be free.
You're speaking nonsense.
It doesn't matter if you are together forever.
It only matters if you were together.
Together my ass.
You really are an idiot.
Hey,
Yi Chen.
Have you realized your temper is worse now?
You were always whispering to me,
and now you not only yells
and also hit people all the time.
I've had an epiphany, okay?
If people do not offend me,
I do not offend people.
If people offend me,
then I shall offend them.
I used to be too weak
I let people push me around.
That is how I ended up like this.
After being reborn,
I will not be a soft pushover.
What do you mean reborn?
I mean,
when I passed out
and almost died in the car accident,
I realized
I have to live for my mom
and myself.
Hey,
why are you getting so emotional?
Yi Chen,
will you go help her?
Let me help you.
Why help her when you can help me?
Let go.
Why are you afraid of me?
I am not afraid of you.
I don't want you to be afraid of me.
Jiang Jing Teng, let go of me.
Jiang Jing Teng,
put me down.
Jiang Jing Teng.
Let go of me.
Jiang Jing Teng!
Put me down!
Let go.
I was not bothering you,
why won't you leave me alone?
I don't know.
I want to be
your only one.
Don't you think you can fool me with that for a second time.
It is the first time I said it,
there is no second time.
Or
did someone else use the same line on you?
No one says something so disgusting like you.
Let go.
Don't push me.
I will push you.
I checked.
You are my high school schoolmate
and also
my fan.
Who would be so tasteless
to think of you as an idol?
Where are the rest of the papers?
What?
Those things you wrote about me,
where is the rest of it?
How did you find out?
It is not important.
The important thing is
where is the rest of it?
I want to see it.
I burned it
and used it all to roast sweet potatoes.
Roasting sweet potatoes.
I didn't know there were so many pages
enough to roast sweet potatoes.
I really do have feelings for you.
The Jiang Jing Teng now
is even more shameless.
You have feelings for me too.
Let go of me.
Mu Bai!
Instead of doing this with you this time,
I'd rather die.
Shao Yi Chen.
Shao Yi Chen, stop.
Shao Yi Chen, watch out.
Jiang Jing Teng.
No.
Don't scare me.
Jiang Jing Teng.
No.
Don't scare me.
Jiang Jing Teng.
Breathe.
Somebody help me...
Anybody!
Jiang Jing Teng.
No.
Someone help me!
Yi Chen,
you have been taking care of him for days.
Why is Jing Teng not getting better?
Chong Jun says
he still can not get in touch with Jiang Jing Teng's parents
and he will keep trying.
You need to eat something
so you have energy.
Tell me,
why did he save me?
I don't know.
But...
Maybe,
he is serious about you,
that is why everything is like this.
Jiang Jing Teng.
Are you okay?
I'll go get the doctor.
Who are you?
Here.
Mom.
Jiang,
thank you for saving my son.
Please feel free to stay here
and don't give yourself too much pressure.
Mom.
Let Yi Chen take care of you.
Okay.
He just got out of the hospital.
He needs rest.
Okay.
You two get some rest.
I'll leave you two alone now.
If you need anything just tell Yi Chen.
Thank you, Mom.
Thank you, Auntie.
Mom, you should get some rest.
Get some rest.
I'm going to take a shower.
I always get
what I want.
Go back to sleep.
I'm going to wash up
and get ready for class.
Why was I on the bed?
How was your
first night of amnesia?
No comment.
So mysterious.
Xiao Bai Mu.
What's wrong?
Did you know,
ever since the day you saved me,
I have decided to have you.
And you're winking?
Are you flirting with me?
Don't you know that turns me on?
And you're closing your eyes now.
Is that an invitation?
President,
what do you want?
I want
you again.
Yi Chen.
Time to have breakfast.
Coming.
Jiang Jing Teng,
it is breakfast time.
Oh.
Jiang,
how did you sleep last night?
Does your head still hurt?
What's wrong with you?
My mom is asking you a question.
It doesn't hurt.
Here.
Thank you.
Later,
when you finish breakfast,
remember to take your medicine
before going to class.
Let's eat.
What's wrong?
Do you not like porridge?
Or do you not like eggs?
No, no.
I like them both.
So what's the problem?
Is your head hurting?
No.
Let's eat.
Didn't you know?
That guy was neglected since he's little.
No one cared about him.
I think
is it because
he is not used to the loving environment in your home.
You know,
everyone in his family is busy with their own stuff.
They only act as a family
in public.
How
did you know all this?
Did I never mention
that Jiang Jing Teng, Yi Chun and I
grew up together?
How is that possible?
You don't look like friends.
How can our relationship be good
when we were fighting for Yi Chun's attention all our lives.
But that is a long time ago.
Now,
I only have feelings for you.
You...
When did this start?
Why?
You like girls
and you will be married with children in six years.
Xiao Chen Chen,
don't try to be a fortune teller if you're not one.
Xiao Bai Mu,
if you dare trying to look for women,
you better watch out, or I will...
I brought him back from the classroom.
Jiang Jing Teng doesn't have class this afternoon?
No.
Then let's go home.
Home?
Yes.
Do you not want to?
No.
Let's go home.
Let's go home for dinner.
Okay.
Be careful.
Sorry, sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Shao Yi Chen,
I'm hungry.
Make me some food.
Quickly.
Okay.
Not like that.
It's the same.
Look at them,
you should just give up.
I don't want to.
You are making it hard for me to read.
I have to keep my head elevated.
You...
Did the doctor say when you can remove the stitches?
Why?
Are you sick of me?
You don't want to take care of me anymore?
No.
Because you
saved me,
I will take care of you
until you get better.
I am just concerned about you.
I think everything is great now.
Don't you want to remember the past?
You weren't there.
Why would I want to remember?
No way.
I can't be fooled again.
Shao Yi Chen.
Do not forget,
you're twenty nine years old now,
not nineteen.
Don't take this childish nonesense
too personally.
Hey.
Let go.
This time,
I will not let you get away.
You like me.
That's not—
You do like me.
Xiao Bai Mu,
let me ask you.
Hey,
hold on.
You're calling me Xiao Bai Mu too?
I got used to it.
That's not the point.
I'm saying,
how do you know you'd like someone
who you can't avoid
but you'd be doomed if you like him?
I think about that everyday.
Chong Jun loves money,
is irresponsible,
talks nonsense
and is a player.
How could I have feelings
for someone like him?
I don't want to like him
but I can't help myself.
All I can say is
I got dizzy
and fell under his spell.
I know I shouldn't
but I still go for him.
All I can do is surrender.
You are not
even going to fight it?
Can fighting it stop me from liking him?
There you go.
So before I stop liking him,
I could only like hime as it is.
I'm happy when I spend time with him,
there's no point in thinking too much.
What if
you got killed in a car accident
because you like him?
Killed in a car accident?
You've got to watch where you're going.
You are not one of those people
who commit suicide just because your crush doesn't love you?
That is impossible.
Then that's settled.
Maybe,
before you die for him,
he will die for you.
In truth,
after I was reborn
I selected another way to keep Jiang Jing Teng away.
Something are similar,
but something are not.
I still met Jiang Jing Teng,
but I also met Chong Jun
who I didn't know.
Run faster.
I don't want to,
they will only chase me.
Mu Bai had a girlfriend
but now he has a boyfriend.
You...
When did this happen?
You should only worry about the future
when the future becomes now.
Worry about the future
when the future happens.
That makes sense.
Why did you want to see me?
Jiang Jing Teng,
what is so great about Shao Yi Chen
that you will pretend to have amnesia just to be closer to him?
It has nothing to do with you.
Yes, it does.
I will tell your parents about it.
Stop threatening me with my parents.
I don't stand up to them
and do everything they say
but that doesn't mean I am scared of them.
I let you follow me
because I could care less to push you away.
Let go.
I'm telling you.
I hate people threatening me.
Remember that
and never do it again.
Do you hear me?
You don't have amnesia?
Are you surprised?
He has been lying to you this whole time
just to
get closer to you.
Go away.
I will go.
I will go as soon as I say what I have to say.
He is the type of person
who will do anything
to get the thing he wants.
Once he is interested in you,
he will haunt you for the rest of your life.
Cai Yi Chun.
Let me explain.
I am sorry.
I will deal with you later.
Shao Yi Chen.
That was close.
I still have my neck.
Why would you provoke him like that?
You scared the hell out of me.
Why didn't you signal for help?
Although Jiang Jing Teng has emotional issues,
he is not stupid.
He won't do anything to me.
Why are you doing this?
Believe me, if I don't do this
Jiang Jing Teng will pretend to have amnesia forever,
just to keep Shao Yi Chen by his side.
No way.
How can he pretend for the rest of his life?
By using Shao Yi Chen's
good nature and his guilt.
So that's why
you wanted me to tell Shao Yi Chen that you were here,
so that he could hear your conversation.
Hey, but
what good can come from exposing him?
Are you breaking them up?
Hey, am I that type of person?
That is exactly what you did.
I am just forcing him
to tell the truth.
Huh?
Him?
Who?
Isn't love about
mutual affections?
He uses guilt to tie someone down
because he is scared of being rejected due to his reputation.
What kind of man is that?
He will kill you.
I have you.
You will protect me, right?
Boyfriend.
When did I become your boyfriend?
A minute ago.
Buying you breakfast for a year was not a waste.
Shao Yi Chen.
Shao Yi Chen, listen to me.
He lied to me.
He doesn't have amnesia.
I'm such an idiot.
I am so naive to think
something with him will also change
if something has changed in this life.
Jiang Jing Teng
is a liar
no matter nowadays or in the future.
Why?
Shao Yi Chen!
Idiot!
Why didn't you run away?
Jiang Jing Teng
let go of me.
This is my house.
It is my house too.
What is yours is mine.
Are you crazy?
I am crazy.
I am crazy about you
because of those pages.
Those damn pages got me attracted to you.
You have
those pages.
Why didn't you keep pursuing me?
Why didn't you keep writing?
Let go of me.
I did not want to go on anymore.
Shao Yi Chen.
You started the game,
and I am the only one
who can end it.
I want you to see me.
I want to be your one and only.
Remember,
I just saved your life.
From now on,
your being,
your heart,
your body
belongs to me.
Have you lost your mind?
Yes,
I have lost my mind.
This is all your fault
so it is your responsibility.
You can not abandon me.
You can not take back
that feeling of being taken care of
and the happiness when we're together.
From now on,
everything you have is mine.
What do I have that is worthy of you?
You like me.
Jiang Jing Teng,
what is so great about Shao Yi Chen
that you will pretend to have memory loss just to be closer to him?
Let me tell you,
he is the type of person
who will do anything
to get the thing he wants.
Cai Yi Jun.
You started liking me a long time ago, didn't you?
You were worried that I didn't like you
so you pretended to have amnesia.
You wanted to use my guilt to tie me down.
You wanted me to confess my love first.
You're afraid that—
If I don't like you...
I would kill you.
If I can't have you,
no one else can have you.
You really are obsessed.
Lunatic.
I had a second chance
but I still like you.
I like you too.
I really like you.
Hold me.
Please hold me.
You said you would hold me
and never let go.
You said.
You killed Yi Chen.
It's all your fault.
Jing Teng was protecting him.
He didn't want his parents giving Shao Yi Chen a hard time,
so he faked the engagement with me.
Bullshit.
He just doesn't want to admit
he loves Yi Chen.
Mu Bai,
watch your mouth.
Shao Yi Chen!
Jing Teng.
Come back.
Jing Teng, come on.
Shao Yi Chen is dead.
He listens to me.
If I want him back, he will come back.
Shao Yi Chen.
I want him back.
Jiang Jing Teng.
- Shao Yi Chen.
- Jiang Jing Teng.
Shao Yi Chen.
Jiang Jing Teng.
What's wrong?
I just had a dream.
You were killed in a car accident.
I didn't believe you were dead.
I even dug up your grave.
What are you talking about?
Why did he dream
of what happened to me in 2025?
Why?
Did you dream of that
because I was in a car accident before?
I don't know.
I even dreamed of
faking a marriage with Yi Chun
so that my parents wouldn't find out about you.
That's why you left in anger
and got hit by the car.
His engagement was fake.
What is going on?
I, Jiang Jing Teng,
will never do something so lame as
using a woman to protect myself.
I'll protect my love
on my own.
You are mine.
No one else can touch you.
I still love him wholeheartedly
after dying once for him.
Jiang Jing Teng.
What?
No matter in the future
or in the present,
I
am my own person.
Say it again.
You are also mine.
As for who own's whom
the body
knows all the answers.
Jiang Jing Teng!
It tickles.
Jiang Jing Teng.