Grand Prince
Grand Prince: Drawing Love
Rabbit! Rabbit! Rabbit!
Episode 1
Father.
News of the king's illness cannot be spread.
We are taking extra measures to makes sure it does not.
Should a word of it get out, all those responsible will be beheaded.
Father.
But, he's bravely endured this for many years.
The king will rise again.
The crown prince is so young.
He will rise for sure.
This is for the Myung Rae palace.
Make way. Back from the north, this is His Highness, Prince Eun Seong.
The day's cold, and these crazy bastards are going around like this?
How rude of you. Have manners towards His Highness.
If you want to keep talking, show me an identification or an entry pass to the palace.
How dare you speak of Grand Prince Eun Seong who died long ago on an expedition and buried ever since?
He survived death. Go and report to the Great Hall.
Your Highness.
We just need to notify the chief eunuch or your attendant lady.
Once they come out and see you...
I can't simply let you leave like this. How dare you tell me to step aside while you're holding weapons?
To find out what faction you treason-planning beggar bastards are,
I'll have to take you away and punish you through the leg-screw torture!
Take them away!
Grand Prince Jin Yang, Lee Kang
The king is in a coma and nearing death. The queen is searching everywhere in vain. His whereabouts are unknown.
Yoon Na Gyeom
Good work. Be safe on your way back.
We're at the same level.
Half of the people are on the king and his mother's side,
and the other half are on our side.
What will you do? The king's illness is severe.
The king's mother is not meeting you or the ministers.
If you lose this timing before he dies—
Before the extreme event occurs,
we need to get the gomyeong (king's will including succession).
While Grand Prince Eun Seong is not here,
if you receive the gomyeong,
the throne will be yours, Your Highness.
I'm going to the palace.
Brother, ask the Chief Minister and all other ministers to enter the palace.
Yes, I will.
- I will bring you your palace uniform.
- Madam, a guest is here.
Royal family member Weol Yeong sent an offer of marriage to my house.
Please ask him to withdraw the offer.  He's one of your loyalists.
So, please resolve this issue.
Did you not want another groom to consider?
What are you saying?
You refused to be my woman for three years.
I gave you a different choice with great generosity.
Are you asking me to be a gold digger?
Hwi... is not coming back.
He is dead.
You should accept it.
The one who cruelly pushed away his brother
was you, Grand Prince.
He went of his own will. He had a sense of duty as this nation's prince.
Do you... intend to ruin my life in the end?
Weol Yeong is my cousin.
Being married to someone from a royal family means your life gets ruined?
Other girls would be shocked to hear that.
I am not looking for a marriage.
I don't want to be anyone's bride.
Do you dislike Weol Yeong that much?
If you really feel that way, just come to me.
I'll accept you even now.
I've said these words in vain.
In believing that there was a small slice of a decent man left in you,
I was foolish.
Be careful out there in the night. You will soon become a bride.
What are you doing, madame?
Is it not enough to ruin one grand prince?
Are you fearless or are you ignorant of the law?
How dare you carelessly meet a man from another person's household?
Are you that worried?
Do you still not have confidence?
Is that why you wanted to get rid of me this way?
Be thankful. If it wasn't for our effort, you would have died as a virgin ghost.
Have you forgotten all about the time when we were friends?
Don't you know that you're the one who ended our friendship?
When you started seducing the grand princes,
we stopped being friends or anything else.
My life and my fate
will not be determined by you and your husband.
If you hate getting married that much, why don't you commit suicide?
Let's go, Lady. Pretend you didn't hear it. Let's just go!
If you were going to die, why didn't you die three years ago?
That amazing love you had, if you'd died, you would've been praised for your devotion toward one person.
Let's go. Hurry, let's go.
I wish you happiness!
Do please get married, have sons and daughters, and live well!
The fact that you're like any other girl out there,
who's as materialistic as them, show it to the whole world!
Ah, really.
It's cold!
Ah really. Let me see, let me see. Come here.
It won't wash off.
Do you want to die?
Let's wash one more time.
My face is going to freeze!
Look at all that dead skin!
Blow, blow.
One more time. Wash one more time.
Will she be able to do it right?
She can't speak Korean very well.
The queen. It's fine once I find the queen.
Dowager. It's Queen Dowager.
That's right.
Dowager, Queen Dowager.
Entry Pass
You can go in.
No matter what, go forward.
Queen Dowager.
That's right.
Queen Dowager Shim
Your Highness! Your Highness!
This won't do.
Tonight, please rest in your chamber.
No, it's okay. I'll get changed and get back to the king.
If you continue this way, you will collapse first.
The queen will have a tough time if she's by herself.
How rude of you. How dare you block the path of the queen dowager?
Queen?
Ah, Dowager. Queen Dowager.
Did you not hear? Drag her away now!
Is there anyone there?
Call for the Royal Guards. Royal Guards!
Hwi
Your Highness.
Hwi.
This...
This is...
Hwi's blood.
My son, Hwi!
Yes.
Prince Eun Seong, Lee Hwi.
Your unworthy son
has returned now and
greets Your Highness.
You were alive.
Where did your jade-like face go?
How hard. How hard it must have been for you.
The king is...
on the brink of death.
The heavens must pity this mother
because they've returned you to me.
You cannot go in today.
Since His Majesty is ill, I've brought calming medicine.
I want to bring it to His Majesty, please let them know I'm here.
The queen dowager issued a strict order not to let anyone in tonight.
Are you treating His Majesty's younger brother as a simple visitor?
Please return in the morning.
I said I'd give His Majesty the calming medicine.
If something bad were to happen to His Majesty tonight
would you be able to handle the consequences in the future?
Move aside!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
Mother.
What is the matter?
What about His Majesty?
He passed away.
Chief Eunuch.
How could you let things happen this way?
How can you let His Majesty go alone without me, his closest family, by his side?
Who in the world will receive his last will and testament?
Don't worry.
Grand Prince Eun Seong?
I received the will and the succession edict.
Until the crown prince comes of age,
Queen Mother will act as regent
and the grand princes will pledge their loyalty to the crown prince.
This is...
the dead king's last wish.
You received
the last will?
I came back, Hyung-nim.
I didn't die.
I lived.
Please return to us, King!
- You have a lot of scars.
- Because I was on the battlefield.
It's a relief you've survived and come back.
I couldn't die because there was someone waiting for me.
Since you have returned at the unfortunate time of a royal death,
I cannot reveal my happiness for your return in the midst of the sadness of  king's death.
It must be hard for you since you can't run to the woman you've longed for.
But it'd be best not to see a woman who will marry another man.
I'm talking about Lady Ja Hyeon.
But, since you two have an old affection as friends,
how delighted she'd be to see your safe return.
Are you saying Ja Hyeon's getting married?
She's getting married to royal family member Weol Yeong.
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Who are you?
Hey, what are you doing? Where are you going?
Where is His Excellency? Where is the lady?
May I ask who you are?
What's all this noise?
What are you doing in someone else's house this early in the morning?
Your Excellency, it's me, Eun Seong.
Are you alive, or are you a ghost?
The king has passed away.
Your Majesty!
I must see your daughter.
Please tell her that I'm alive and that I've returned.
I cannot.
You, what in the world are you doing?
I will go into the mountains. I will become a Buddhist nun.
Silly girl.
The grand prince has come.
He is alive.
He came to see you.
My daughter is already
set to wed another man.
Your Highness, you cannot!
Lady, Lady Ja Hyeon!
Your Highness.
Please go back to the palace, quickly.
You must observe the royal mourning.
Lady!
♫   I cannot even laugh   ♫
♫   My loneliness has piled up   ♫
♫   Everything has been broken   ♫
- Your Highness.
♫   I try to fix it   ♫
♫   I can't do anything   ♫
♫   Because of you, it has rusted.   ♫
♫   What do I do with myself?   ♫
♫   It's because my chest feels tight   ♫
♫   I feel frustrated because my chest feels tight   ♫
♫    As much as it is sad, this mean love   ♫
♫   You don't know it yet    ♫
Prince Eun Seong, Lee Hwi
It's finished.
- How irreverent! How dare you do that in front of His Highness?
One moon shines on two places, two persons are thousands of miles apart,
willing to follow the shadow of this moon, night after night, I want to shine it on your side.
Hurry and go.
Are you telling me I can't go again?
This time, too? Are they saying I cannot go?
They said that due to palace troubles, they would summon you, not today but on another day.
Another day, it's always "another day!" When will that ever be?
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
Prince Jin Yang, Lee Kang
I'm going in today.
Your Highness!
My father's face and my mother's touch,
I cannot even remember them.
I will no longer live here alone.
They aren't telling you to not go because they dislike you.
Recently there have been troubling worries in the palace.
I said I'm going.
If there are such troubles present, shouldn't I be more informed?
I can't wait any longer.
I'm a prince of Joseon!
The prince is at the eastern entrance and is asking for permission to come in.
Tell him to go.
We've already stalled for many days.
If you have him come in and stay at the Grand Prince's Hall—
Can you say that while looking at the crown prince in this state?
It's not time yet. Not yet.
Move! Won't you move?
I'm the second prince of this country, Lee Kang!
We didn't hear that you would be entering the palace today.
Your Highness, you should go back.
After asking the Queen Mother, I'll come back with permission for palace entry.
I told you I'm not waiting anymore!
I have to go into the palace right now, today!
Your Highness, it's Gi Teuk.
Come in.
Is my brother here?
About that, uh...
Even if I dry up and die in front of the palace, I will not turn back!
I'm going to meet my father and my mother!
Your Highness, you can't do that today.
If you go back, then tomorrow you could get approval—
Hyungnim!
It was good of you to come.
You don't know how long I've waited for you.
You should go in. Mother has been waiting for you.
Your Highness, the prince cannot enter the palace today.
He can come another time.
How rude of you.
He is my brother. If he wants to enter the palace,
on whose order do you dare block his entrance?
Your Highness, it's not that.
It was an order from the higher-ups.
I'll take responsibility for this.
Move aside!
Let's go.
Did you not hear about the command issuing a postponement of your palace entry?
I heard about it.
Due to the unsettling atmosphere in the palace, I've ordered you to wait,
but a young one like you is acting stubborn.
Mother, I was the one who went out and brought him here.
He has not done anything wrong.
You relied on your childish brother here and disobeyed your parents.
I have met you, Mother, after countless years of waiting.
Because I longed to see you more than anything, my young heart had no choice but to defy orders.
Can't you understand?
Have you cleaned your older brother's room?
I'll use this opportunity to redo the door and wall of his room.
I've decorated his desk and table with only the best products.
But, Mother.
Does the law of the palace place a younger brother above the older brother?
Pardon?
Why are you, my younger brother, sitting in such a high seat and receiving my bows?
I'm sorry, Hyungnim.
Don't be upset, Hwi only wanted to see your face.
No, I was the one who didn't think it through.
You're not upset at your younger brother. You're upset at me, your mother.
Before you are my son, you are this nation's prince.
The reason I couldn't keep you next to me to this day and you were raised outside of the palace
was for the future of this country.
Withdraw your contempt and be prideful of yourself.
Imagining your return, I wrote this, Hyungnim.
One moon shines on two places.
Two persons are thousands of miles apart,
willing to follow the shadow of this moon.
Night after night, I want to shine it on your side.
Is it you and your brother written into the poem?
Yes.
Like the moonlight shining down, the reach of a parent's love extends far.
It reaches any and all places.
But the distance between Hyungnim and I has been a considerable.
Therefore, I expressed my feelings of wanting to follow the moonlight to where Hyungnim was, every night.
That feeling of yearning can be thoroughly found.
Your younger brother has a way with poetry.
When envoys from China arrive, they make a big deal out of wanting to bring his writing.
Hwi's poetry is the same as your mother's heart.
While waiting
and waiting, I longed for you.
Hyungnim.
If you had entered the palace on a good day, we would have been able to throw you a welcoming celebration.
Because of the crown prince's illness, the palace atmosphere is like this.
I've returned to the palace. I haven't "entered it," I have returned.
I've only returned to the place where I should be.
You don't know how long I've waited for you.
A boy like you, getting so close.
Yeon Hee, what are you doing?
I wanted to clean your shoes.
Haven't I told you to take care of yourself? Why are you causing these problems with an injured arm?
My other hand is just fine.
Doing this is not a show of your loyalty.
If you want to make me happy,
don't get hurt and don't get sick.
Didn't I tell you to take care of your body first?
Don't move and make the injury worse.
You can go and rest.
When you feel better, we can play hide and seek, which you like.
With my brother.
Really?
I apologize, Your Highness.
I could not stop His Highness.
Kang shouldn't have been brought here this early.
Hasn't Crown Prince's fever been getting worse?
With Kang, it could've been worse.
Hasn't he already grown up by himself for too long?
Although the other princes should grow up well, the crown prince must be healthy.
Then, everything in the court goes well.
Ever since Joseon was formed, the first-born son has never been the king.
You're really distracted.
Uncle!
Oh, the palace food must be good. You've gotten heavier.
Have you gotten used to the faces of the people in the palace?
Yes. Everyone is treating me well.
That's how it should be.
Grand Prince Yang Ahn
Due to their own greed, since you are the son who was thrown aside,
they should at least be good to you, even if it's because they feel sorry.
Do you know why you were thrown aside like that?
I heard that since I was too weak, it was for me to take care of my body.
Generation after generation, it wasn't the first-born son, but the second-born son who gained succession in the royal family of Joseon.
If you're here, the throne becomes more unstable for the crown prince.
The crown prince is unhealthy.
They blamed that on you and threw aside a newborn like that.
Isn't that ridiculous?
I was the oldest son, but the current king who rose to the throne
is trying to make the first-born son the crown prince and is threatening you.
What about Hwi? He is a younger brother just like me.
Why did they only chase me out and raise him in the palace?
Because you are the most dangerous.
Hwi's appearance is beautiful.
He's called a genius because of his poetry and writing.
If you, just like the other prince,
had received proper education in the palace, you'd definitely be better than him at poetry.
The person who has the qualifications to be the king, who poses a danger to the crown prince, is you.
So don't worry, you have this uncle by your side.
Although I shared the throne with the current king, I am still the oldest person here.
Practice with all that you have. With you, my nephew,
I want to go hunting as soon as possible.
I'll count to ten!
One. Two. Three. Four.
Five. Six.
Brother!
- Seven.
- This way.
Eight. Nine. Ten.
Found you.
Now it's your turn to seek.
I apologize. I couldn't recognize you quickly, Your Highness. Please hide again.
I will find someone else.
You think I can't play hide and seek?
That's not it.
You don't know the rules well, and I thought I should go easy on you for the first time.
You just want to find Hwi instead of me.
He hides well, so it isn't easy to find him.
That boy's good at this and that. He's good at hide and seek, too?
You're Yeon Hee, right? Starting today, come to my palace.
- But...
- Why,  is it something you can't do?
I already have someone I'm serving.
Don't you know that I am higher up than Hwi? Hwi's things, no matter what they are, I can own them.
I'm not some kind of object that can be given and taken.
No matter if it's a thing or a person, as long as I want it, it will be mine.
I'll tell the Chief Eunuch to bring good, young maids to you.
- Do you dislike me?
- That's not it, Your Highness.
I've been serving Prince Hwi ever since I was very young.
When you choose a master, you stay with that master. It's a palace rule.
Do you like Hwi that much?
Your Highness! Your Highness! Where are you? Please come out.
Have you lost it?
I was hiding. Why'd you make it so noticeable? Do you want me to be a seeker that bad?
- That's not the issue, Yeon Hee is getting attacked!
- What?
When a higher-up says so, you should go and come as they wish.
You're lower than me, and you're being stubborn about going and not going?
Your Highness, please calm down. I cannot leave my master.
Are you looking down on me for growing up in a normal house outside of the palace? I'm next in line after the crown prince.
I'm higher in rank than Hwi is.
Your Highness, what is wrong?
Don't disrespect me. I said to come to me.
No, the master I must obey is not you, Your Highness.
I'm not going to another palace. I can't!
What did you say?
Your Highness!
- Please save me.
- You hate me, don't you?
Please save me, Your Highness. Your Highness.
Then just die.
Hyung, where's Yeon Hee? Have you seen Yeon Hee?
Your Highness!
Yeon!
Go to the palace's pharmacy and get the doctors!
Yes, Your Highness.
Yeon! Yeon!
Why did this happen?
- How did she fall? Why didn't you go in and help her?!
- I don't know how to swim.
You should have called for someone! You should have tried to help!
How could you just watch her die?!
She was jumping all around because she was happy she found me. What was I supposed to do about her falling backward on her own?
Gi Teuk saw it.
I heard a different story.
What did Gi Teuk say?
What did he say that he saw?
I don't think we can help her.
Yeon.
Yeon, Yeon.
Welcome.
This was made by the person with the greatest skill in Joseon,
specially made for my nephew.
Uncle.
What is going on? Who made my nephew this upset?
Wh-What should I do?
Will I be removed from here?
Or will I go to prison?
Who will do that to a country's prince?
Don't worry.
Tell me what you saw.
The last person Yeon saw. Was there no one else other than my brother?
I was far away, so I couldn't hear what they were saying very well.
He seemed to be telling Yeon Hee to change to his palace.
But, he got angry when Yeon Hee said she didn't want to.
He got angry and led her to the water.
I thought I couldn't leave them to be so I went to find Your Highness.
He was angry.
She was jumping all around because she was happy she found me.
What was I supposed to do about her falling backward on her own?
Get me dry clothes from the laundry room.
I need to talk to my brother.
Yes.
Gi Teuk, are the clothes ready?
Uncle.
Are you trying to meet Kang?
Yes. I have something to ask my brother.
Go back.
Bury it. And forget it.
A person died.
Do you think that Kang's going to get punished?
A dead young maid and a living prince.
You know who the royal family would protect between the two of them.
The queen will get rid of the witnesses.
You are protected by your blood but everyone else will probably be taken care of, right?
Do you want to lose one more servant?
We shouldn't kill a living person because of someone who's already dead.
You need to bury this incident and your pride.
That way, this incident will pass and there will be no need to sacrifice any more innocent people.
Where is Gi Teuk?
That child has done nothing wrong.
Do you want to save him?
Do not threaten me.
Threaten? I'm the uncle who even gave up the throne for the sake of the country.
I only wish for the royal family's peace.
Your Highness.
Save me. Save me, please.
Your Highness. Save me.
Please save me.
Who... Who are you?!
Who are you!
The queen will get rid of the witnesses.
Do you want to lose one more servant?
Every day and every night,
you're saying you missed me?
Brother, I was like that too.
I missed the palace that I don't even remember.
I would dampen my pillow every night and fight back my tears.
How is it? Is it alright?
It's much better than what I've been using.
It's lightweight but shoots far.
This isn't just for use in training but for real.
It's an item used for war.
If Father and Mother find out about the maid, what should I do?
They won't find out. Hwi won't be able to tell them.
You weren't caught by your weakness.
Instead you beat your brother by his weakness.
Isn't it fun? Your secret became Hwi's shackles.
Don't feel bad about it. Don't let your conscience be bothered by it.
Firmly. Go further even stronger.
Power can cover up any wrongdoing.
For no one to question your wrongdoing,
you must have the power.
Do you remember when Yeon Hee hurt her arm?
Of course.
Just to get the dates from the tree for Your Highness, she climbed up but—
That young child who had nothing,
she always said she wanted to give me things.
She put herself in danger and watched over me.
Yeon Hee's gaze always followed me around.
No matter where I went, I felt her presence.
She was a sunflower that only looked at you.
I was worried that she depended on me too much, so I acted coldly toward her.
I shouldn't have.
Do you regret it?
I should have smiled more warmly.
I should have told her in a friendly way.
If I had known her life would be so short, I would have done everything for her.
Your Highness, because of me...
Listen well. From now on, you are to stay by my side.
Yes.
And this matter,
forget it ever happened.
Nothing can happen with my brother's name involved.
I can't lose any more of my people.
Your Highness.
I am weak because I am still young.
We can't even uncover Yeon Hee's unjust death.
All I can do is to protect you.
You and I need to become stronger. Only then can we protect one another.
Your Highness.
Yeon, have you been well?
I still am curious whether you are a child or have grown up.
Now I can't picture your face as well anymore.
♫   The places I want to go to  ♫
♫   The places I need to go to  ♫
Grand Prince Preview
♫   Perhaps I don't want to know forever   ♫
Today at the palace, they are playing the game of installing the crown prince.
He is the first successor to the throne.
He is a child full of greed, unlike Prince Eun Seong.
You were cut from the classes to be a bride.
I heard you ditched. Because of that, going out is prohibited.
You're not only rude but also shameless.
Who are you to be speaking informally?
Don't ever forget it.
My face. And my name.
♫   I'm wandering   ♫
Grand Prince