Look.
Darn it.
I'm sorry.
Let me
play a song for you.
Start
< Meet
> .
Do you want to play another one?
What else do you want to play?
Can you play with your left hand?
I don't think so.
This is
what I want to hear.
Play it. Hurry up.
I want to hear you play.
I've been looking forward to it for a long time.
There will be a boy sitting next to me.
Play the piano with me.
I can't believe
I actually saw such a scene.
The way he plays the piano,
it's a little different from what he usually does.
It was quiet,
and a little shy,
He would look up at me
as he played it. It was cute.
You played so well.
It's so fake.
Really?
This is my true level.
I'll show it to you.
It's really good.
It's better than I thought.
He always shows that he's cool.
But I like
his cute and lame side more,
It's all flowers from others.
Yes.
I'll give you a ride, too.
-I'll walk you out too. -Do
you want me to help you up? -Sure.
Because I helped you up.
I'm afraid we'll both fall down.
I think he has
a real intention,
More boys than he said.
This is for you. Take a look.
Thank you.
It's great to buy you coconut green every day.
The possibility of yours
is more attractive to me.
I think I really have
feelings for him.
Satisfied with this activity
Satisfied is what you want,
Yes.
Really?
I set a similar scene before,
in a restaurant.
I was too angry that day,
so I canceled the project.
No wonder.
It's good.
Just
It looks good when playing the piano.
Doesn't it look good when you don't play it?
When I was playing the piano,
I saw a different you.
You see a different me again.
You're the only one who's sitting there playing the piano.
It's very attractive.
It's very.
It feels like I can see you
as you are,
It's hard to describe
that feeling.
Is it what you like?
Yes.
He even canceled the piano program.
This is too sudden.
As for love,
I've given her the answer sheet.
It's a blessing from my heart,
so I'll finish this answer sheet.
This is my finish line.
It's also a new starting point
for my future relationship.
At least I'll give you a chance
to say goodbye.
Hello.
Hello, Wu Shi,
Tianchao,
Hello,
Tianchao. Hello.
Hello. Hello. Let's
enter the semi-cooked cabin.
It's an experience
I've never had in my life.
I'm very happy and excited.
To be able to enter
the initial state of this group,
Winter has come and the snow is beginning to fall,
the hut is bleak and the wind is listening,
I don't know.
how to open up this situation.
We're back.
Let's eat and have a seat.
But in the daily life
in the cabin,
Everyone is quite friendly.
You burned a lot of
real cows.
I've tasted it.
Eldest brother is the eldest brother,
you deserve it.
You're really something.
Do I feel like I'm flying?
Sure
Tread through the rough road and become a big road.
Okay,
I think slowly,
my heart is pounding.
When you smile at the beginning of your life,
winter may not matter anymore.
You'll feel warm.
This wonderful memory,
I will also record it well
in my mind.
We brought a lot of food.
Did you see this?
Who wrote this?
Lao Wu is gone,
this time he came to the cabin,
In fact, we don't have much time
to get together.
If there is such a time and opportunity
in the future,
I'm willing to
communicate more with you.
I also hope that everyone can get
the happiness they want.
Where are Yu and the others?
You're not back yet.
It's so exciting.
Who is this?
Big bags
and small bags. Look,
Okay.
Who is this?
You look so beautiful today.
Really?
You look so handsome today.
And the flowers,
the dress,
This windbreaker.
This is unique,
this little leather shoe,
Look at these small close-up pants,
these small high-waisted pants,
Look at
the white clothes,
Does my dress look good today?
So beautiful.
Amazing.
Is this dress ugly?
No.
Not ugly.
It's not your dress he's looking at, is it?
There's something wrong with someone's eyes.
Have you eaten?
-Yes. -Didn't you eat?
Yes.
You must have eaten it.
Can I post it on my Moments?
What's the order of friends'circle today?
I put a number on the Soy Milk.
Let's do it.
Sure
With light and unburdened soya-bean milk,
we can watch our Moments easily and unburdened.
Okay,
Come on.
That lucky number
will definitely be reserved for
drinking this bottle of bean flavor.
I hope everyone of us can see
the sweet plant-selected soy milk.
Tiantian's Moments,
let's start reading them.
Okay.
What I posted to Yu'an on my Moments
is a serious gesture that
I want to live a formal life.
To do a slow thing to her,
that is, to accompany her.
This is
what I want. I'm looking forward to it.
Come on. I'm number three.
I received a message this morning saying that
the cabin's
last self-selected date,
I'll talk to him,
come here
About what?
Do you want to go with me tomorrow?
Where are you going?
Are you thinking about it now?
Or what do you mean?
Do you want to go?
On the last date,
I hope I can be happy.
Don't think about anything.
The first moment I wanted to post it
on Moments tonight, I thought,
Today is really a day when the sweetness is off the charts.
I'm so happy.
I feel very sweet.
Is it over
if I eat myself?
It's over.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
I think
he's a bit upset.
It's just hard.
Today's Moments,
in fact, is similar to
what I imagined.
Not everyone
can have such good luck.
To start a relationship.
But I still have no regrets.
To complete the trip to the cabin.
The one holding hands.
Yeah,
that's what I thought. Okay,
It's so sweet.
Yeah, but I'm a little scared.
Are you afraid that it's just on the show?
Yeah, just a little bit.
I'm afraid it'll come too soon.
You walked too fast again.
It's just
very fast,
It's just very.
I think it's precious.
Yeah, that's why I want to take it slow.
Okay,
But from now on,
I won't put on makeup anymore,
I definitely won't wear makeup.
You're crazy.
I don't care if you wear makeup or not.
I'm just...
I'm not
worried about you removing makeup,
Are you serious
after removing makeup? You... You'll think
this is
a big step.
I think every step is a small step.
It's just not a big step.
I think everything is
a kind of emotional accumulation,
The accumulation of feelings,
and then,
When it comes to the right time,
I think it's time to do it.
I'll just do it.
What's wrong?
Have a look.
Do you know how I feel
when you look at me
like this?
I always feel like you're going to kiss me.
Thank you.
Fine.
As a chef,
come and cut some close-ups.
Okay, we'll take a long shot later.
From the very beginning until now,
my love for her has always been the same.
I like our relationship
that hasn't changed. I think
it's getting better all the time.
It's moving forward.
Burn it into a sharp shape.
You're sweating.
I'm sweating. It's already hot.
The last ball,
Come in,
Cool.
I want us to be together.
It's a natural rhythm.
Find a comfortable way to get along with each other.
So that we can develop in the future.
All right,
you can take photos now.
Yeah, your composition is pretty much the same.
Okay, you can eat now.
Do you want to eat this while it's hot?
My steak is the supporting role,
while yours is the leading role.
Not bad.
Not bad, right?
This one tastes better.
Delicious.
This is awesome!
Please act delicious.
Show that it's delicious.
You can do it.
Can you do this kind of berry?
Mulberry meat is good for tonifying kidney.
I don't need it.
The person who was protecting the liver yesterday,
it's protecting the liver, not the kidney. It's almost like
liver and kidney integration.
You have to make up for it.
Who are you looking down on?
Score it.
out of 200, right?
200 points,
minus 200 points,
I'll give myself a negative score.
I didn't expect you
to make it so delicious.
I think you're digging a hole,
you must want me
to do something else next time.
I didn't eat it. I don't know.
That depends on your performance.
Why are you still looking at my performance?
For example,
after eating,
Do you know what to do?
Go to bed.
Then you can earn your own living tomorrow.
Isn't it self-reliance?
Who can't earn their own living?
Whether you like to eat or not,
whether you like to cook or not.
This is so comfortable.
Rare
Play some music.
I heard the same thing.
I'll be at home when I fall asleep.
then
When I'm alone,
when I'm alone,
Maybe it's because I need to relax my pressure.
It's a sleep aid.
This kind of song makes me feel
comfortable being alone.
And there's a feeling of
crossing back to a certain moment.
And it can smooth it out to some extent.
This is the feeling I really want.
I think
when I first met you,
There's a reason for being comfortable,
as far as we're concerned about being comfortable and calm,
The feelings you experience
and want to experience are the same.
Have you ever felt this kind of feeling?
Because of one person,
in the past.
I don't
think so.
I know her life wasn't easy before.
There are some things I can't do.
I can't do it.
Not that versatile.
But I'm doing my best to keep you company.
Even if she's been like this,
I won't say that
my feelings give her a kind of binding pressure.
In the last relationship,
I lost my home.
So since then,
I've always been used to
living alone.
But in this scene,
his company moved me very much,
It makes me feel like we're in the same industry.
I haven't had this feeling
for a long time.
Does the light up there have to be on?
I would like this ship
to have a darker starry background.
Maybe this one outside,
this tablet computer,
I'll switch the properties,
and I'll take a look at the scene outside.
And turn off
the red ambience light.
You can do it.
This time, I brought her to the space I designed,
and wanted her to know
about my work,
I hope she can like this place.
I'm here.
Is this your work?
The atmosphere is good.
In this scene,
there are small petals and small broken flowers,
Yes.
It reminds me of the breakfast that day.
Right?
It's all my fault,
isn't it?
This is the space,
and the things on this screen,
I made them all.
Didn't I tell you that
there are many stars in the place where I work?
Yes.
It will change.
It has a lot of stars.
Yeah,
just take a look at the rest.
This is a particle special effect,
which works with music,
To combine with
an immersive light show like this,
It's just a bit like that photo exhibition.
I went to see it.
Have you seen it?
Yes.
The Light and Shadow Exhibition,
or the interactive space of light and shadow,
That kind of interactive,
interactive immersion space,
I've seen them all.
Yeah, so they're the same technology.
Got it.
Yes, that's it.
This is actually the state
we both want in our hearts,
I just don't want two people,
a lot of enthusiasm or something,
On the contrary, it's a very comfortable
two people
who can enjoy the space like this.
The calm at that time.
I remember you asked me back then,
did you meet anyone?
I once gave you this feeling of healing.
I don't think I've ever met anyone
who can give me this feeling.
But in fact, I've been looking for
someone like that.
I'm looking forward to it.
I don't know what that feeling is.
He won't give me
that kind of comfortable feeling.
But when I was talking to you,
I felt that way.
From the first day,
I also have
the first day and then including today,
When I was lying there today,
I felt very comfortable.
Yes, both sides are being appeased.
Yes.
Then I fell asleep.
When I was in the last company,
I would pass by every day after work.
First, I passed through the ginkgo tree forest,
and this,
I know which one.
I take this road to work every day,
do you work around here too?
From Xingguo Road,
I rode my bike to the Bund,
If you ride a long distance,
you'll pass by here.
This road leads me to the Bund
because of this road,
So every day when I ride a bike after work,
I feel a sense of happiness.
So for a long time,
we rode on the same road,
Really?
Yes.
I was wondering if I met you
when I was at work or off work?
Yes, I don't think so.
If you ride so fast,
I guess it's also a swish.
It's over.
I can't see it either.
Yeah, it's just a swish.
Did you get yelled at?
Did anyone tell you to get out of the way?
No.
Then it's not me.
I'm the only one who can ride beside him normally.
Next time, I'll know who told me to ride. Get out of the way.
I took a closer look,
Mr. Yu (Yu Tianchao) Hello,
It must be you.
Yes.
Everyone is here.
What's wrong?
You're suddenly shy.
The Matrix
is beautiful. It's really beautiful.
A handsome guy,
a handsome guy,
Yu'an,
why are you sitting here alone?
I've always wanted to say,
you have a
very fresh and sunny scent,
Is this the smell?
It's light, smells good, and feels like a teenager.
When I was washing clothes,
I would add gold-spun white-robed youth fragrance beads,
It has a fresh cedar scent.
Do you like it?
Yes,
I mean I like the scent.
I usually put
gold-spun incense beads myself,
But I use glitter,
which really lasts a long time.
I know.
It's rose-flavored.
The young man in white is very careful.
You also have a faint scent today,
when we were on a date today,
Glittering.
I think so, too.
I think frankly,
I said most of what I wanted to say.
But there's still one thing
that hasn't been made clear.
Do you want to go with me tomorrow?
I feel like facing such a sincere Bao Er,
I shouldn't be
so careless.
I didn't give him a real,
equal and sincere reply,
I don't think that's allowed.
I want to show my heart at last.
Make it clear to her.
Many memories.
Smile.
Actually, on the last date,
it felt like saying goodbye.
But after she finished singing.
I'm a little moved.
I don't know what to say.
I dare not look at her.
Okay,
Hold on.
And there's a song for you.
<
Comet >, I just mentioned it in the car.
Let me show you
one of my favorite songs lately,
This song is my old single,
White Shark's ,
When I went back, I joined the song list.
What does the scar mean?
And then I was frantically
trying to memorize this song,
The reflection in your eyes
is the shell that melts the ice and snow,
I tried my best
to arrange
the best date in my heart,
I know it's coming to an end.
But I still want to
spend a happy day
with a boy I like.
That's it.
It's so low. Don't laugh at me.
Don't laugh.
Not laughing
I'm so happy.
In fact, I've been thinking until yesterday,
is there a better way?
Will you just miss it?
Will you regret it?
Do you feel sorry?
It's really hard.
I just don't know how to respond.
Such a strong love,
will make me a little confused.
You can serve now. Thank you.
Are you hungry?
Hungry,
Thank you.
Ramen,
I chose a spicy one,
Thank you.
This is great.
I just took a picture like this for you,
and then you took a picture like this for me,
Hurry up.
Why do you feel so silly to me?
You just found out now?
Quack, quack,
quack. Let's take a look.
All right,
I'm going to lose a little job today,
Maybe you can play with your phone
once or twice. You can do yours.
Yes.
Did you choose
this place?
Yes.
To have music,
I wanted to find a live music venue,
But the live music venue is too noisy,
if I have to arrange it again,
I will also arrange
a live music venue,
Or a place where you can sing,
why do you even think the same as me?
How was your chat yesterday?
Didn't Tianchao ask you?
They said,
"Let me clean up my emotions. ".
Don't cry all the time,
just let me grow up and so on.
I don't know if I put pressure on him,
maybe it was me crying,
Then I scared him to death.
You need to clear up your emotions.
Didn't I tell you
when we were downstairs last time?
What?
Don't cry.
No, I'm embarrassed.
You're crying again.
I'm not crying.
I'm just embarrassed.
Okay, I'll leave my question
to him, okay?
You ask?
What do you think is wrong with her?
When it comes to feelings,
when it comes to feelings,
Yes.
Let's talk on our own.
We can talk about our problems ourselves.
Actually, yesterday,
when you were there,
I didn't want to say it,
just because I want to keep it till today.
Don't you know the least about me?
Every time I come into contact with you,
it's just
not like this time,
Or when you play tennis,
it feels like,
We get along like friends,
but once we get to know each other,
And then after we got in touch,
the way you and I used to be,
It makes me feel like
that feeling is back.
You know what?
It's just that I hate the old me.
What kind of person was I in the past?
In the past,
I was very sensitive,
And then the old me would,
for example, because of a look,
One,
or one, any move.
I've been depressed all day,
because I care about
whether the people around me are happy or not,
Are the people around me very comfortable?
When you were with me,
were you unhappy
because of me,
But I didn't come out.
It's not completely getting better.
... to be able to withstand all of these
things,
I haven't reached that stage yet,
so I don't think I can handle it.
When I confessed that day,
I kept telling you,
I said I think we are very similar.
But I don't think it's appropriate.
That's what I can't say.
No,
that image is not
a good image for me.
It's a kind of image that Tianran will put pressure on me.
Me
This time at the cabin,
I'm really happy
to meet you.
That's it.
I like you.
I do,
but.
I don't like who I am
when I'm with you.
You can call me a coward.
But I think,
I think,
Let's be friends.
That's enough.
Don't move.
If you were my friend,
I would hug you like this.
All right.
At that moment,
I felt that's the only way I could do it.
So that you can look more natural and unrestrained.
I'm happy to have met him,
but I'm also sad to have met him.
Exactly
Actually, that night,
when you told me a story,
I really want to hug you.
When you said three words,
I cried.
Because I feel sorry for you,
why should I feel sorry for you?
It's my turn.
Don't talk.
And actually, I think,
that night and today,
I'm happy that
you confessed everything to me.
Because you said these things,
told me,
At least let me know that you mean it.
I didn't mean to keep me away from him.
I also know what happened to you in the past.
I think I'm a little luckier than you,
I might not have your darkest moments.
It's so dark.
When you see me,
you think of yourself in the past.
I think there's really a lot of things that you,
you put what happened to you before,
What you think
is on me.
I'm not who you think I am.
I'm not who you used to be.
I thank her from the bottom of my heart.
Being able to like me so much all the time,
I feel a bit heavy and guilty.
I'm not crying.
It's just
a pity.
Although you said what you said today,
before you left the cabin,
I will continue to like you.
Then it might be
a little more obvious than before.
Because there aren't many days left
when I like you.
Stand up and give me a hug. Hurry up
and take advantage of me.
You.
Why are you filming me?
I'll take a picture for you, too,
Okay,
I'm not done hugging him.
What is BM?
Meng Bao.
Me,
Let's not,
Bye.
Side Dish Chicken,
Hit him.
It's possible that
it's just not suitable.
Here's the thing.
That last hug,
there was a moment of relief,
Let go of this relationship a little bit.
We can end it as friends.
Now that we've made it clear,
don't cry from now on,
I did it because of empathy,
and then I started,
But I was confused.
I'm sympathetic.
And then it started to hurt.
I feel sorry for you.
Look at the car.
You don't have to be so scared.
It seems to be in here, right?
Is the truth in it?
What place?
Hello,
photography studio,
I'm here to get the photos.
Yes, thank you.
Why are you so fast?
I lied to you just now.
I said
I was working.
For the whole thing,
I made two copies of all of them.
Here you are.
Why am I so dull when I eat? Then
I'll give it to you.
The grimace we made that day
compared to us,
You really … You still can't let it go.
I'm not even here.
I'm very open-minded.
I'm already like this.
I did look at that photo many times.
I think it's beautiful.
If someone likes you so much,
he must be lucky.
I thank her from the bottom of my heart.
We came to the Bund.
You have to go that way,
after all, our Oriental Pearl is at the back,
I don't know how to use it.
What should I do?
Give it to me.
We are still friends.
Well,
I really wish her well.
And then this will be fine.
Okay, I'll do it myself.
I hope she can find someone nice.
Someone who cherishes her very much.
I'll teach you how to say my name.
Zhang Baoer,
Zhang,
Zhang
Bao
Son,
Zhang Bao'er,
help!
It sounds so bad.
Meng Zhaobo,
Zhang Baoer,
Zhang,
But yours sounds much better than mine.
Zhang Bao Er,
Meng Zhao Bo.
It's not right
if the other party suppresses you.
It shouldn't have been suppressed.
Yeah, two people are supposed to encourage each other
when they're together,
Why do you keep mentioning Mr. Zhu Yawen?
Yu knows how to take pictures.
He must have led it first,
To Yu,
I was thinking about my hand,
So romantic.
Oh my god.
-He's really asleep. -Chaochao, wake
up.
Are you in a relationship?
When I took pictures of them that day,
Hello, guys, Iron,
Hello,
just put off your normal work and rest for five hours.