That should be Bao Er.
Fur in fur,
fur,
I think he's a bit cold and humorous.
Celebrate the beginning of a new life.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you.
May the four teams
chat more with our male guests,
I'm so embarrassed.
You can call him a male guest or a master.
You can drink as much sugar as you want with high fiber 0 sugar?
This program is broadcast under the title of Zhi Xuan Oat Milk,
which is delicious and not afraid of being fat.
The clothes are soft and anti-static. Semi-cooked and touching. This program is co-sponsored
by Jin Fang,
a clothing care expert.
Half-cooked with love and New Sanjiu Weitai,
this program is sponsored by New Sanjiu Weitai.
Hello and welcome to
the second season of "Half-cooked Lovers"
made by Tencent Video,
Here we are.
Everyone, the ending of the last episode was amazing.
Zhi Xuan wants to be with you,
wants to ask you out tomorrow,
Go out to play tomorrow,
Okay,
I'll go on a date with you tomorrow.
Yes, I'm asking if you'd like
to give it to me.
I failed.
Have you noticed?
The two male guests who were alone
are both very well-equipped,
And the two most popular ones
at the beginning,
Qiao Xin,
do you also like
Tianchao the most?
As I remember,
I like his profession.
On the first hand,
I chose Zhang Yan,
Because I think he's very steady,
and he can keep a good distance
from girls.
And then it's very decent.
I kind of like it.
It belongs to Ali (Yu Taoran),
Although there was no candidate at the beginning,
Yes.
Yeah, because I think
he's a very real person,
I washed the fruit for you.
Thank you.
And there's a puppy over there.
Where is it?
I'm going out.
Are you going out?
I really want him to be like this.
A very real person
can get happiness.
Before we watch the date,
we have to welcome the girls'counter-selection.
Yes, there are still two female guests who haven't been selected yet.
Ting He,
when she first came out,
I think her condition
is my favorite.
Because of her condition,
she is the image of a professional woman.
Yes.
So I'm thinking,
why doesn't He Ting
have a choice.
She's good in every way.
And then she's so confident,
if a girl
is in a better profession,
The so-called strong woman.
In this kind of person,
will boys think that
she is not so sexy?
Will a strong woman not be sexy?
That's so sexy.
Yeah, that's great.
You don't have to work.
I can also accept
lying on her side
and being willing to be a little man,
Take a picture of my head.
If a person has achieved something in his career,
or if he meets himself, it's very suitable.
What you like very much
is a lucky and rare thing.
If this person
happens to be my girlfriend or wife,
that would be a great thing.
But if she gives you very little time,
her time may be allocated to work more.
Because I have no choice,
I can go to work with her.
If a girl's career is very strong,
she is also very capable.
It won't make a boy lose confidence
in front of this girl.
I think it depends on
the boy's own self-confidence,
If he is confident and confident,
he can appreciate and respect
the charm of women,
If a woman succeeds in her career,
it will add a touch of
unique charm to her.
The girl chosen by this boy,
his career is much more successful than his.
I believe this girl,
when choosing him,
It must be this guy who will provide her
with emotional value.
or help
in life,
So that two people can be
matched together,
Because if she really succeeds in her career,
she must have her own way.
At the moment of dominating the world,
she has her own strong moments.
I don't think she's just
showing up in her work.
She might pop up this thing
all the time and sometimes.
For boys,
it's about whether there's pressure or not.
There must be pressure.
But I think in this process,
boys have to work harder
to overcome
some of their inner things,
Yes.
But I think this is
the mysterious part of love,
I think people like to compare.
But I think between two partners,
you have to
run each other's business.
You are a community of interests,
maybe you are moving too fast at this time,
You've got your benefits.
But you may affect our relationship.
At this time you have to wait for him (her) a little,
and don't compare at this time,
I earn more than you.
So I have the initiative at home,
which I don't think is the case.
It's about how we should treat this family well together.
If two people are together
and we're still competing behind closed doors.
I feel so tired.
Then I think the meaning of marriage
and love is boring.
So boring.
I wonder why we spent so much time
talking about this
at the opening ceremony.
It's because these are the questions
that we might have
and think about
at this stage.
So with these questions,
and this suspense,
Let's take a look. Girls are going to choose against each other.
Dizziness,
What?
Now it's our turn to choose.
But I don't know who to choose.
Hi.
Are you looking for him or me?
I'm looking for you.
So it seems to be an invitation,
and then I'll ask you out,
Do you need anything?
I think so,
Yes,
But no, no.
You can choose not to give it to me.
I want to give it to you.
No.
Because you were actually
looking for
Bao Er just now. I know.
I'll talk to you about it tomorrow.
If I were Yu'an,
I would say that
I don't really want to listen to this tomorrow,
Yes,
I finished it.
That's great.
But there is a point,
that is, I am on your side,
I don't think
I can use that again.
"Zhi" (I choose you,
Yes.
Hold on.
When you went to
Bao Er just now,
Did you bring this bottle
and this tape?
Yes.
Yes, but I've been chosen, haven't I?
Yes, you were chosen.
Then it becomes me.
I was chosen. I didn't choose you.
But you're giving it
to me now, right?
But I hope you can
ignore this sentence,
Ignore this sentence,
Yes.
Okay,
Let's talk tomorrow.
Then just remember the milk, right?
I'll give this to you, too. Yeah,
okay. I'm going to ignore that.
Okay,
I get it.
Let's talk about it tomorrow.
What time tomorrow?
Do you have any plans?
Yes,
Yes What do you want?
Now you want to know.
Yes, at least let me know
when I need to get up. What time?
You can get up as soon as you want?
It looks good on you.
Okay,
it's up to you tomorrow.
Ignore this sentence.
But it moved me a little bit.
Tianchao is fine.
He just wants to say,
The previous one was for someone else,
but I can't give it to someone else.
I don't respect you
if I show you this way again.
Yeah, actually, that's what he meant.
But he didn't make it clear.
That's all he needs.
I really don't want to choose.
I've never asked out a boy
since I was a kid.
If you meet someone you like very much,
if he really doesn't
ask me out,
Then I... I might
just forget about it.
But it's a pity to give up.
We'll lose one more chance to get to know each other.
So cool.
If you are stepping on thunder alone,
what if he is a partner?
Yes.
I'm definitely looking forward to it.
On a date with him,
he might arrange some fun
and exciting sports.
When I'm with her,
I like it very much.
I just expect the value to be full.
I'm looking forward to it.
For the first time,
everyone must be showing
their good side,
Because after all, we don't have many scenes
of being alone
and communicating for a long time,
The scene of long-term communication,
the scene of long-term communication,
So I wonder,
what would it be like for Ali (Yu Taoran)
to arrange a date?
What does it say?
It's for Yuan'er (Zheng Yu'an),
Okay,
Exclusive,
I like this kind of exclusive,
Did someone make breakfast?
To be honest,
I lived to be thirty years old,
The first time a boy cooked breakfast for me,
he wanted to keep warm,
He had that very thick glass cover
with a lavender on the side,
It's hard for a boy
to pay so much attention to details.
In fact, it will take a long time to remember,
which is a point that makes me very moved.
Is there anyone here all the time?
You're so quiet here.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
Look, he doesn't have a date.
I think his dark circles are heavier,
so I think it would be great if He Ting
went out with Zhang Yan directly.
What are you looking for?
You're here. I'm looking for an umbrella.
Have fun.
Okay,
Bye.
Why are you back?
There's one thing I didn't finish yesterday,
that is, yesterday I thought,
We had a great time
driving together, the three of us,
Three people driving together is very pleasant,
but there is a kind of long-lost,
It's the atmosphere
where friends go out
and drive together.
What a warm-hearted girl.
I'm happy, too.
It was yesterday when I finished talking about driving hard,
and I didn't have time to make up the second half,
Sometimes when I have a longer reflex arc,
I'll return it,
It's not that I walked too fast.
foot length
It's okay. Have fun today.
Okay,
be careful.
I'll get going then.
Bye.
In the face of such a girl,
I might be tempted, too.
Sun (Sun Muyu), come here.
It's actually quite cute to communicate with him.
Very cute.
Especially when this guy
is a little upset,
She will give him a lot of encouragement.
And I feel comforted.
Yes,
especially
when I think Sun (Sun Mu Yu)
He went out.
And then I came back to say this to him.
For him,
for him,
He thinks you care about me.
That's why you explained,
Yes.
Actually, I quite like Ting He,
decisive,
I think she gave up.
You think
she's a very proud girl.
Yes.
Actually, I can quite understand her.
If it were me,
I might give up, too.
What about you?
I'm sure
I'm already here.
Twenty-one days in total.
Because in my opinion, love
doesn't mean that I can have it if I fight for it.
Give it a try.
It's obvious that these men,
they don't like me very much,
She might think
it's useless to fight for it.
Yeah, she's asking too much for that purity.
Because I'm also very passive.
It's because you didn't take the initiative.
It's hard to take that step.
Unless you really like it.
I'm desperate,
but I don't think she got a girl either.
You don't have to take the initiative. How about that?
You kept showing up next to him.
Actually, she can
work in this room, right?
Yeah. Then
we'll have more time to spend together.
It's not my tricky
feminine side, Qiao Xin,
If I don't have a choice, I might … I'll
leave.
You left with your bag, right?
You don't have that kind of taste.
You really don't have a good taste, understand?
I'm leaving.
You're thirsty after talking for a long time, aren't you?
Really?
It's true that
all the dating groups,
It's already been revealed.
We're about to officially start
the planting date.
Let's have a selection of oat milk first,
so we can relax.
This one with 0 sucrose and high fiber,
you can drink it during the fat-reducing period,
Yes,
then it's pure plant milk,
Each bottle is rich in 10 grams of high dietary fiber,
making it full.
It can also be used as a meal replacement.
Not to mention the fragrance,
but the taste is also very smooth.
Not bad.
Because it has a unique oat
enzymolysis process. It tastes delicious
and has no burden.
It's really good. I'm not afraid of getting fat.
Planting is really a treasure and nutritious choice.
We're taking 50thousand to take a shower.
Dog.
Let's go.
What do you like to eat?
I love Japanese food.
I love Japanese food, too,
I love Japanese food,
then
I like fast food too.
It's amazing for fate.
One thing,
if we are so serious,
We're being so serious
and greasy.
That would be amazing. Really.
Who do you think you're interested in?
Have you made up your mind?
Yes.
No one else wants to know about you.
No.
Really?
Yes.
Then why did you sit opposite
Sun (Sun Mu Yu) yesterday,
Noon is also right.
Sorry,
what a coincidence,
I didn't mean to sit opposite you.
Don't be like this.
Me
Okay, it's my fault.
I'll sit opposite you next time.
I was so determined yesterday,
so I went straight to your place.
They also asked me,
"Do you know which room it is? "?
I said I know.
Why do you know me?
You did.
Did I say that?
I told you I wanted to pamper Lucky 3 today.
Am I right?
I still remember some things clearly.
When is my birthday?
Did you say your birthday yesterday?
I don't remember
if I said it was my birthday?
You didn't say that.
It's really,
it's a rainy day today,
What's wrong with rainy days?
Full of stories.
Not bad.
Hello,
Welcome. Please
let me
hug the dog for you.
Be careful.
Give me a hug.
Come on,
Here you are
Look,
they all rushed out. I think
all boys would like these dogs.
Like Bao Er (Zhang Bao Er)
A girl like her
has a good voice,
So cute.
these
Everything
is more passionate
than Wan Wan.
Over there.
You're really
feeding Corgi as a chicken.
I'm feeding the fish.
Like a couple,
they're going to be locked up.
Who feeds the dog like this?
It's amazing.
Me,
Sure
Got it?
Your treasure-feeding method,
treasure-feeding method
makes me laugh.
Help!
I think a good relationship
should be like this.
You laughed so hard.
This is great.
When you're with someone you like,
you're happy in everything you do.
Yes.
Look at it.
It has sticky hair now,
as ugly as it has no hair.
It's the ugly state
when we wash our hair.
Do you have less hair?
It should be quite few. Does the programmer
worry about baldness?
Not yet.
You look a little disappointed.
Are you...?
Do you expect me
to come here with a bald head.
No
You have a big forehead,
I think you might have a big brain.
That's smart.
We have the cake maker here,
the cake maker,
Yes.
Dog cake, right?
Wait a minute.
I'll put on your apron first,
Okay.
Your hair
is stuck in my mouth.
I'm sorry.
Hold it first.
Take your hair first.
Okay
I told you to lock him to death.
It's so cute that I didn't ask you
to lock your throat.
Yes, we lost a
Uncle Meng (Meng Zhaobo)
All right, I'll tighten it up for you.
We can draw a Corgi,
which is to paint on it.
Your nose
is so dark,
is
good.
It means it's healthy.
It should be a healthy dog.
The beginning of love is so beautiful.
I think everything tastes good.
I think,
Yes.
It's as dark as your heart.
That's too shallow. It's a black hole
in my dark self.
You know what?
Take a look at this dog first.
What does it look like?
The kind of ordinary conversation
they're talking about,
But the two of them thought,
they were laughing so happily.
It doesn't matter what you say,
it's just happiness.
Yes.
That's enough.
It's perfect.
So cute.
Here, plug this in.
Is there?
There's something,
right?
Actually,
it's okay. Yeah,
Actually, it's not bad.
What is B
& MB & M?
Meng Bao.
My reflex arc is so long.
I just felt like
it was a little bit fast. The two of you
are "locked",
All right.
Do you want to go in here?
Yes.
Hello,
Your reservation is for our color studio.
This way, please.
Welcome, puppy.
I'd like to have a look at this dress.
This one looks better. I'll take this off.
Look how manly I am, bro.
This is so stupid.
Why don't you press it?
Okay,
one, two, three,
They feel like
they've been together for years,
Anniversary celebration,
Yes.
It feels like they've been raising this dog for five years,
and this dog doesn't work
as well as it did on the first day.
It's really mine.
I'm not wearing this, am I?
It's supposed to be worn
by cats. Can't people wear it?
Put it on.
Cute.
Hurry up.
Come on, three, two,
one. Tell the truth,
It's even a bit of a dog abuser.
Really?
I actually want this toy.
Take it away.
I want another chance
like this,
I've never done it before.
So when I saw
so many props,
I find it very interesting.
It's so novel.
It's really a magnifying glass.
Or what?
I'll take all kinds of photos.
Edward Scissorhands,
let me get another pair of glasses.
You're still shooting
this. It's so funny.
I seem to be having fun.
This is so cool.
A little bit.
You're smiling happily.
Why?
Because it's fun,
girls are a little down
I think so,
It can't go on like this.
I'm screwed.
If you want to reduce (points),
that's enough.
How many times have you filmed it?
It's gone.
What else do you want to play?
No, there's nothing interesting.
It's gone.
That's all.
I think the first one just now
is okay. Is this one?
Yes.
Am I like this?
Why am I so ugly?
The takeout is here.
What takeout?
Thank you.
Yeah. The one I bought for you.
Why are you wearing this invisibility today?
I just don't feel
well, do I?
No, I'm just a little tired on my left eye.
I'm so careful,
You bought this?
-Right? -Right.
Yes
Put it there if you have nothing to do
Let's take a look Brother,
Open it.
I'm tired.
I'm tired too.
You want to go home?
He told me that
he wanted to go home,
Really?
So I think it's right.
So I think we can go home now.
Something bad happened.
I think there's something wrong with this.
This is the first time
that Bao Er,
Take his car
and look out the window.
Take a break.
Yes.
Do you think you are satisfied
with today's appointment?
It's okay.
Why do you like
making cakes? I think you like it.
Are you okay?
You like cakes.
That photo shoot is okay,
because it makes me
feel more relaxed, right?
But the photo studio part,
I'm not really interested in it.
It's me. Actually, I was very happy
when I got there.
Because when I'm with you,
I'll be happy.
But in the end, you play until you forget yourself
and indulge in it.
And you even forgot about my existence.
And then you'll
just say,
You can express it directly like this.
Actually, it's quite good.
Yes,
I do have a question,
It's me.
For example, I'm having fun,
After playing some things,
I do forget myself a little bit.
I know it's not good.
But just
You reminded me.
I can try to change it.
But it won't be so fast.
I do have a problem.
Because I really didn't pay attention to
girls'emotions,
I didn't pay attention to girls,
I was a little too immersed in myself,
I was there on my own and had a blast.
And in the face of this kind of emotion,
boys may be a little overwhelmed,
Let's not talk anymore.
Let's not talk about this topic for now.
Don't look at me.
I'm ugly now.
You sleep with your eyes
open. Are you a horse?
What am I?
Are you a horse?
Horses sleep with their eyes open. No,
horses sleep standing up.
Is that so?
Really?
I don't know.
I don't know either.
Why don't we go back and ask him?
You're always talking nonsense.
Are you tired?
Tired,
Not bad.
Now, with a breath of "immortal energy",
I just hold it and go back
to make up with you, right?
Some things are just so-so.
But I still think
they're cute like this.
They're moving too fast.
From sweet to awkward,
really?
Their progress is too fast.
Yes.
From a girl's point of view
because of something that she would be interested in
on her first date,
Why is there such a big loss?
To be honest, I didn't get it.
I think he had a good time.
I don't know why
this made her so sad.
I don't get it.
Actually, I think,
maybe girls have great expectations
for this date.
But I didn't expect to say that
in the middle of the process,
You become an accessory.
This guy is not paying attention
to his feelings at all.
He didn't even notice that
he was the only one who kept changing the props for the photo shoot.
He's the only one who's been changing the props for the photo shoot.
This girl is only responsible for
pressing that button on the side,
So I think in general,
in a girl's mind,
she will think,
It's so different from
what I imagined.
I've always felt that
Meng
has been in a state of excessive excitement
in the whole process
up to now.
He hasn't lowered himself yet.
When I saw Bao Er,
I was excited.
Yes.
He wanted to show himself when he was excited,
and he was always at this point.
He didn't come down a bit.
To observe others,
like this,
Let's talk about this,
okay?
For example, when a girl sees a boy,
which move does he make?
It will be very high.
Or it's really bad,
but I think it's a little childish.
I think when a guy wears a tie,
and then he loosens it,
There will be a move like this. It's
so cool.
If you pass by some real estate agents after work,
you can walk around.
Then it's too much for you
to talk about the next head.
You pick a few key points and say,
I think boys are pretty narrow-minded,
The pattern is small,
Yes.
Or you like to be reasonable,
so I think,
I'm not talking about your teacher,
I'm not talking about you.
If he makes sense
and I say one,
that would be the beginning,
When Ms. Shen went out,
she made me very high-ranking,
For example, just the two of us
going out for dinner,
Then eat.
I'm done.
As she was about to leave,
she said,
Can I order another bowl of rice?
Then she ordered a bowl of rice.
At the risk of being sharp,
she ate them all.
So cute.
I think he (Chen Xiao) is the same as me,
and the fact that he likes Andy Lau very much
makes me feel quite high-ranking.
This is very specific.
This one has that moment.
If this guy did something
unexpected to me,
I shot her in secret and she lost her mind.
Scared is not a surprise.
In fact, sometimes I see
some people do something,
It makes me want to do it myself.
But I don't have the courage to do it.
I told him some questions
that I had never thought about
from this perspective,
At that time, I thought he was so special,
and the last time I felt this way,
I went to university to study advanced mathematics,
but I don't understand this sentence.
I don't understand that either.
Every sentence is a brand new door,
I am that what,
We are together.
In some cases,
she would play some
stupid games with me.
I'll be so happy,
so I won't blow your head off.
Or did you tie your shoelaces?
Let me show it to Mr. Xiong. Please
cooperate with me.
Let's work
together.
I suddenly said,
"Honey, I want to play one of those.
And then we're like this,
and then turn your hand this way.
For example,
we'll just sit there and wait.
And I said, "Hurry up. "
You see, if there's no tacit understanding, you'll hit it.
It's a little game that
only you two can play on your own,
When we played for the first time,
we never played together.
Where's Qiao Xin?
On top of me,
I'm really a little,
I haven't gone too far for a long time.
It's really hard to get excited when you're old.
What do you mean?
If you don't record this show,
you'll be getting old,
Ladies, don't go.
Let me have a drink.
To ease my mood.
I need to calm down.
Maybe one thing I like about a guy,
I think he's cool.
He's with me.
It's different from what you look like
in front of outsiders.
He looks like a kid to me,
but if he's
in front of an outsider,
I think he's amazing.
He's amazing.
He's so cool.
Why do you look like
a bossy president after hearing it?
Isn't Daoming Temple
typical?
Yes I liked Daoming Temple when I was a kid,
did I ask for your opinion?
Now it's more specific.
I want to ask you, Mr. Xiong Hao,
if something happens to you
when you're with
the girl you like,
You are the first to look at it
from the perspective of right and wrong,
I'll still look at it
from the girl's point of view first,
I think I'll look at it from the perspective of love.
I will look at it from the perspective of love.
That professional judgment will disappear in the end.
At this time,
he doesn't look much like Professor Xue anymore,
Professor Xue will still say,
we still have to go back to economics,
And sometimes,
girls don't really want to listen to your reasoning,
In fact, she just wants to
vent her emotions
emotionally
and have an outlet.
That's right.
Let's take a look at a date.
Okay? Come on.
Hello,
let's go.
Let's go.
Is this a solo exhibition?
No, it's a museum.
But there's a fun thing,
there's a glass workshop over there,
It can make things.
It's quite interesting.
I've seen it.
Seattle should be
the coloured glaze workshop I've seen,
And then they made
all kinds of colored glass,
Have you tried it yourself?
I haven't tried it.
But I really want to try.
I have to do it myself today.
Sure,
Yes.
There are some exhibitions here,
so we can take a look around.
I brought her to the museum.
He does have his literary youth side.
This is more interesting.
It … It's a kid's whimsical
graffiti,
Sketch. Sketch it
out of glass.
As a glass work,
I like this one better.
What is this?
When I look at it from a distance,
I feel like it's
a geometric sculpture,
When I look closely,
I can see that
it's a sandwich.
Then take a closer look at the sandwich.
This sandwich is one
with feet,
The possibility that it has feet is a creature
that just looks like a sandwich,
It has a lot of
progressive associations,
It makes me think that this kid's thoughts
are progressive.
As for the other works,
what you see is what you get.
Look at what it is,
what kind of thing it is,
But I didn't guess that.
It turned out to be
such an idea of his,
Come on, let's practice first.
Just go down a bit.
-Yeah. -Don't
be afraid.
I'm afraid
I'm not. I feel like
my stick is shaking.
You can go down a bit.
All right,
I got it.
Sometimes you can't touch the fire,
hair
Move it up.
It doesn't matter.
So sweet.
Do you have one with your hair tied?
No,
it's okay. Just check the fire for me.
I'm so afraid of mine.
Why did you reject him?
If I were you,
I would fall down here.
You can tie up your hair, right?
But I don't have a rope
to make a hairpin today,
Tie it directly later.
Sure,
Sure
Light the fire.
Good at it.
Let's try to pull down slowly to both sides
Okay,
Pull slowly.
Kesong is here.
Not bad.
Ke Song can do it too.
As long as you like it, you can do it.
Come on,
Pull slowly.
Pull it slowly.
It's thin enough in the middle.
Okay,
this is
the lollipop shape.
You can do it.
You can
do it.
This mess is so ugly.
Don't worry about eating.
No way.
As long as you can eat it.
You can't
twist it. Got it.
Yes.
When it comes to making glass,
I was a little worried at first,
However,
he is very patient.
Do I look like him?
And the colors are very similar,
Yes.
The whole process was very pleasant.
I think it's a great experience.
They're a good match.
It's locked.
It's locked again.
I think he's great.
I saw it right at first glance,
so I'll use this white one.
Are you going to use it to make me
a smart stylus?
I'll look forward to it, okay?
Why are you laughing?
Do you think it's going to break?
No,
I think if you roll the big ball in front of you,
it will take you a long time to roll.
It's going to take a long time.
Oh no.
What if it gets more and more crooked?
Help!
Well,
Yes.
It's a nice color.
It's agate.
It's because of
the flame, right?
Yes.
It will be this color when it cools down.
I think this piece is very warm
and stylish,
You don't like warm ones.
Yes,
Because you're warm.
I think this one
looks like a dork,
It's quite cute.
Yes, it's perfect.
But what kind of pen length
do you usually use?
approximate
That short?
Is it short?
But if that's the case,
I need to pull my head, right?
It's too hot.
Yes, that's fine.
It's a little longer.
It can be corrected if it's wrong.
Come on,
Sir, let me do it.
It looks like a pen.
It's beautiful.
Yes.
This is still wrapped on it.
It's much better
than your Kosong.
Can you compare it?
It's really hot.
No way.
-Wipe it again. -Forget
it. It's already hot.
Give it a name.
I think it's called ballpoint pen.
What do you think?
Because it's my house.
Yes,
it's so spiritual,
Why is
this shape so spiritual,
Form it in one stroke.
The first date,
I think it was a very successful one,
Because what she made,
how beautiful is it?
How perfect it is,
that's not what we care about very much,
What we are more concerned about
is that this process,
This is to make me feel
comfortable and calm.
The feeling of letting nature
take its course.
Success.
He's good at it,
and he happened to take her to a place,
He is very capable of
showing off his bright spots.
It's very bright.
Take a break,
I need to go out and watch my eyes slowly,
My eyes are going to bloom.
It exploded.
How could this happen?
There is a certain probability that it is relatively small.
When did it explode?
There's no sound at all.
Yes. When it burns inside,
it means the gas is not burnt through.
I washed my hands.
You can think of this place?
He's pretty good.
Yes.
Few people can think of that.
And I don't think
there will be such a place in Shanghai?
Because it used to be in a city rich in glass
and maybe
some buildings were made
with
colored glass pieces and glass shapes.
When I saw it in Seattle,
you like colorful things, right?
I like colored ones,
Yes.
Why did you pick me last night?
As far as I'm surprised,
shouldn't you first answer
what happened last night?
Didn't you say you'd wait until today?
Yes,
it was me from the beginning,
From the first time
we looked at each other's Moments,
I chose to read
Bao Er's Moments,
I've always chosen
Bao Er
from beginning to end.
And then
you... You've always chosen me.
And then I think,
this thing is different.
What's the difference?
It means a lot to me.
It's how I feel about you,
it's a hindsight,
Yes.
I'm so.
stupid
You're either stupid
or dull
and you
haven't been convinced yet.
We can go now.
Which way?
Let's go this way.
I think this date is actually
quite good.
I think it's the ending,
it has a little bit of
an ending actually,
Here's how I feel. Let's start
with his expression.
He is indeed a bit dull,
but when he says it out loud,
In my opinion,
it's quite honest.
Yes.
But I don't think
girls are convinced.
I think he should at least say it,
because Bao Er
probably talks a lot.
So since I first started to contact her,
I would pay more attention
to Bao Er.
I'm a bit stupid.
That's why I found you.
In fact, personally,
he doesn't have to say anything.
Because he did a great job
on this date.
He showed everything carefully,
and he's talented,
He's aesthetic, capable and handsome,
what else are you talking about?
You chose to go out on a date with me,
and after this date,
Girls don't really care,
but who did you choose before and who did you choose later?
But now you're with me.
You made breakfast for me this morning. No,
you have to make it clear.
Why did you choose her?
I don't think it's necessary to say
no. How about you like it?
Make it clear.
Or I'll take back
50% of my love for you,
I think,
they talked about it yesterday.
When you're done,
you have to say it out loud.
Because you actually
went to see Bao Er just now.
I'll talk to you about it tomorrow.
If I hadn't mentioned it yesterday,
maybe you wouldn't have mentioned it and I wouldn't have asked.
Maybe I won't tell you today.
Eldest brother is so funny,
I went back and thought about it all night,
If Bao Er
comes back
to look for Tianchao,
will Tianchao turn around?
I don't think he will.
If I vote for one,
it will be like this,
We don't think so. Raise your hand, okay?
We haven't discussed
whether the three of us are men again.
The three of us,
did you say "dead" again?
You men really believe in men?
But we women don't believe it.
In my opinion,
he may not
take the initiative
to find Bao Er
as he did before,
But if Bao Er
comes to him,
I don't think he will refuse.
I think something happened over there,
and I think it's very likely to reverse
Yes,
Right?
Or do you want to come back?
I think it's him
who created this atmosphere.
will allow them
to be in this environment,
They will ignite each other.
So the date environment is very important.
Up to now,
I think the date I remember the most is still new,
It's in the school playground.
Where is the date?
It doesn't matter.
What matters is who are you with?
As long as you are with the person you like,
even if you squat in front of a public toilet,
You're sweet,
so you don't have to squat in front of the toilet,
No matter what he says,
I feel so happy.
The most annoying and unhappy thing
is to send me home.
I don't want to part with someone I like.
I don't want to be apart at all.
You will feel that time flies.
I just don't want to be apart.
Where's Yeon-hee?
We're really an old couple.
Because of Chen Xiao,
he really doesn't like going out.
Every time
it's my birthday,
That's why I told him, honey,
can you go out to see a movie with me?
Or go out for dinner with me,
you two only go out once a year.
Only on my birthday,
yes, on my birthday,
That's why I got up the courage to ask,
about this date before and after marriage,
Will it be different?
The difference is too great.
It used to be,
before we got married,
Is he really
going to sneak into my crew
on his birthday,
Then I went to my room,
and decorated it
with rose petals,
And then I wrote my name,
and I got into
a cake with balloons and a big cake like this,
Romantic,
Yes.
Is Chen Xiao so romantic?
It was really, really romantic
before we got married.
Yes,
but I haven't received
any birthday gifts
since we got married.
But the financial power of the family
is actually in my hands,
He might think
you can buy whatever you want.
But it feels different.
Yeah, so I changed my mind later.
If I really like a painter,
I'll look for some,
I like the artist's style,
so I asked him to choose one.
You like it, too.
And then with a painting like this,
I'll take it as a gift.
It's good.
It can be
a good wife,
Yes.
That's great.
I'm sure you won't be angry.
Because it's you.
I have a choice for him.
No matter how he chooses.
But in fact,
I still have a silent hope in my heart
that he can surprise you.
Take the initiative.
Seeing this episode of Chen Xiao,
Please be self-conscious.
I hope he can see
us. When the time comes, Aite,
Let's take a look
at their next date.
At this age,
most people tend to be rational.
For me,
the best picture of love
is happiness in plain life.
I only asked her out
because I only talked to her
the most that day.
I want to get to know her better.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's okay.
I'm sorry,
Is it blocked?
Not bad,
but I was delayed a little bit earlier.
The other half I like
is based on self-improvement, kindness and sincerity,
If it's another funny guy,
that would be great.
I don't think he's funny at all.
No, he had some funny moments.
But he doesn't know it,
he's funny and doesn't know it,
I brought you
Zhi Xuan oat milk today,
I usually make meal replacement drinks when I exercise.
It's 0 sucrose and high fiber. It tastes good
and I'm not afraid of getting fat.
I didn't expect you to know it well.
I'll take you to a fun place
later. You can drink this first
to fill your stomach.
Then I'll take you to a big meal.
Thank you.
That is to say,
you need to buckle the left and right sides here.
Look at this here,
is it buckled like this
and wound around this place like this?
Yes.
Okay.
Is this the same?
This one is wearing this one,
you have to take the big one,
Use mine to put it on you first.
Okay
Okay? Is it tight?
Yes, it's just right.
You can do it, right?
Thank you.
Your arms are a little thin,
but I have muscles.
Is it tight?
Not bad,
That one
When was the last time
you roller-skated?
In my
When I was five years old,
I haven't played for a long time.
Let's stand up later.
We will take off.
What do you mean?
Yu (Yu Taoran) chose someone
he's not good at, right?
Why did he come here if he can't skate?
Do you want me to help you up? Sure.
Because I helped you up.
I'm afraid we'll both fall down.
Then.
Hold this.
Hold this up.
And then?
And then
go inside.
Don't be afraid.
It's okay. Take your time.
No rush.
Yes, hold this.
Then take a walk,
and see what's the most
comfortable.
Come on. Give me a lift.
And then you hold that one.
That's good.
Don't be afraid. It's okay.
He always wanted to help her.
Do you feel better?
Much better.
Better than me.
When I first
skated this,
You helped me along the way.
It seems to be speeding up.
Yes.
You'll get it.
It's getting better than me.
I saw you.
Thank you.
I saw your Moments.
But I'm sure yesterday's look
made you feel a little different.
You were wearing white clothes and trousers yesterday, weren't you?
Or white clothes, black pants,
black pants,
And then I feel like
I'm a big brother in society,
What is it?
Brother Society,
so what's your position
for yourself today?
He's a warm man.
Now I feel like I have
a chicken coop on my head,
Me too.
My hair has never been
this high.
Yes.
Not only is yours more natural,
but I think I'm a little supernatural.
I get my hair cut every week.
I think I cut my hair very well.
I think your look
is pretty.
Thank you.
When I came out today,
I felt like a Taoist priest.
Think about it. No,
it's pretty.
It's really pretty.
Okay,
Do you know that my long hair
is connected?
I don't know.
Were you short before?
Yes.
How short
Round inch It's probably because
I had long hair before,
It's as long as you,
that's why I took your hair.
Is it possible?
When did you shave it?
When did you pick it up?
It seems to be when I shaved it.
After this lap,
I'll show you.
Okay, no problem.
Then my
first fall is for you.
In the process of getting along with each other,
he has always been very intimate.
He was thoughtful,
and took care of all my details.
Wait
a minute.
Sure,
just tighten it.
If you want to fall, you and I will fall together.
If you can't do it, just give it a hand. It's okay.
Did you drop it?
Are you wearing hair line powder?
Yes.
I even painted both sides of it.
If you wipe it now,
Well,
I don't know what will happen.
Because I've never applied it before.
Do you want to have a try?
A little cute.
Clean it up.
Why don't you eat that radish?
Which radish?
This one?
There was a radish on the table yesterday,
a red
Chongming radish. Try it.
I'm not used to this.
You didn't eat it. How do you know you can't get used to it?
Okay. I'll take a piece of it
as a sign of respect.
I don't really eat pickles like that.
But when I thought about it yesterday,
you already handed it to me.
Then I have to eat it.
Then you pretended to eat it and put it down.
Yes.
I ate the whole thing.
You can't frame me.
Okay,
So why did you want to
invite me last night,
We went out to play together today,
because I think
we talked a lot.
Because I communicate with others
less than you do.
then
I think you are
a very gentle person,
I don't know
if you're very good
after the first time you're familiar with it.
But "explosion" is quite good at all,
that is to say,
You're the one who was the first
to do the dishes,
So I think,
at least you're good at taking care of yourself.
She's quite independent.
Exactly
It really appeals to me.
That's about it.
Before I went there yesterday,
I saw those three flowers.
So many flowers,
I said,
We've already sent three flowers.
Why did you open the door for me?
Were there any other boys looking for you yesterday?
It should be behind me.
I think so,
but you've accepted me.
So you can't
accept him, right?
Theoretically,
if he is,
He's the first one.
I'll say yes.
I'll say yes to that guy. Knock on the door.
Okay.
It seems that the order of appearance is very important.
I think this is the answer
I really want to hear.
Exactly
You didn't mean because
maybe I wanted to hear
some answers and you said,
It's quite objective.
I think it's good.
That's what I thought.
That's what I said.
No problem.
You're quite independent.
Right?
Yes.
Maybe
after I came to Shanghai,
I was forced to adapt to my own life.
And then a few years later,
I started trying to prove that I could do it.
Yes.
So I spent some time.
You've come to this point.
Have you achieved
the result you want to achieve?
It's within the range
that you can control,
I think I've done my best.
That would be great.
Yes, I'm satisfied
with who I am now.
Then I think,
it feels like someone who has been through something,
She is indeed
a person with her own goals.
So you know what you want.
But also independent.
So I think she's quite good.
Let's say,
for example, we had a fight,
What kind of person do you want?
That's what it looks like.
You go first.
Shall I go first?
Anyway, now I think,
in life,
In fact, most of them
are trivial matters.
There's nothing
between you and me.
Because there are more,
in fact, more difficult problems
to solve at work. That's too much?
That problem can be solved.
What else can't be solved in life?
I said that before,
didn't I?
Yes.
There are too many,
bigger challenges to go,
Yes.
You have to face and overcome it.
But at the same time, I feel very contradictory,
and I feel that people are hard to change.
Your habits,
some of your habits,
I think so.
That is to say, it's hard for you
to get from zero to one.
But if you want to go
from one to 1. 5 and one to two,
Actually, it's not that hard.
Why is he talking again?
What I said yesterday,
from zero to one,
So liking is one
and fitting is a lot of zeros in the back,
Because there must be one first.
As far as I'm concerned,
if someone hadn't copied the homework,
It's impossible that even metaphors are the same, right?
When you quarrel,
you have to communicate with each other,
You have to say it.
Yes.
It would be better.
You can't keep it to yourself.
Yes.
I can't be in a state where you can guess why I am.
It can't just be a fight overnight,
original
There are so many similarities
between this guy and me,
There's a feeling that after reading the book,
what kind of girl do you like?
I think it's good that you're doing this.
There's a chance.
Because we've only been together for one day,
and we've only seen one side of you.
So we still need to see a lot of faces.
Give a score to your schedule.
200 points.
Let's get the base.
70 points?
Why is it only 70 points?
Arrange a 60-year-old one for me to have a look.
I won't give you the chance to experience it.
Who are you going to give it to?
Guess.
Don't guess what a woman thinks,
if I like you,
Or I love you and I have to say it.
And every day, he said,
"What a straight ball. ".
It's a complicated situation.
Let me get it for you.
His embarrassment is written on his face,
capitalized embarrassment.
These are your slippers?
My slippers,
Lao Yu. Come on,
I'm leaving.
Bye-bye.
It's a very complicated feeling.
I'm just a little upset.
I'm looking at my friends.
That's good.
Is this exclusive to his circle of friends?
She puts some pressure on me.
I don't know what to do better.
Come back with a straight face.
I think she should give up on Meng.
She didn't guess
right after reading it.
Why are you crying?
Hello, everyone.
We're Half-acquainted lovers.
Ladies and gentlemen of the first season,
I'm Lola,
I'm (Wang) Nengneng,
I'm (Wang) Yucheng,
I'm Shunshun (Zhou Jinshun),
and this Friday we'll accompany
all the audience
to watch "Half-time Lovers",
The second and third episodes of the second season.
Cheer up for our new friends.
It's so loud. I'll be waiting for you at 18: 00 this Friday
night.
Bye.
Be sure to come
when you're here.
That's enough. That's enough.
A little more towards the hairline.
Here?
Why don't you go in and take a bath with Wan.