[The ad is aired at this period of time]
[My soul is just like this.]
[A flower of hope on my head, love in my hands.]
[I think that's happiness.]
[Does life sketch out the arc of joy?]
[The sun is shining brightly because you came,]
[they want to shine on you.]
[Stay upbeat, just like I am.]
[About Love]
She takes our mom's side.
In the end, Mom's favorite wasn't her.
It was our little brother.
[Do you think she is happy?]
[I don't think so.]
[Be Myself]
[Yongji's Little Courage]
[With the windows to the outside world shut,]
[I start to listen to my inner voice.]
[Feeling isn't hard,]
[but how do you find empathy?]
[Expressing isn't hard,
but how do you embrace misunderstandings?]
[Forgetting isn't hard,
but how do you face it again?]
[The sun is shining today because you came.]
[Be Myself]
[The ad is aired at this period of time]
[Cimarong Village, Yajiang County, Ganzi Tibetan
Autonomous Prefecture, Sichuan Province]
[9:05 AM, The third day of raising courage]
Be it in the city or the village,
it's all the same.
[Ordinary people]
[Ordinary small family]
Everyone has an ordinary small family.
[Ordinary life]
[Everything ordinary]
[Start an ordinary day]
You're up?
Where is the black coat
I wore yesterday?
It was someone else's.
It must be upstairs.
I'll get it.
[She and friendship]
Give it to me. I'll carry it.
Go ahead. Have fun.
Let me do it.
Go ahead. Take pictures.
Okay.
Is it heavy?
No.
Have you ever thought...
You are so good at taking pictures.
Right?
Yeah.
And Nao also likes to take pictures.
So can we
take pictures for the villagers?
Yeah.
Right?
You can sit in the middle.
Why would I sit in the middle?
It's their family photo.
Taking pictures of me again?
Keep going.
Look back.
It's a souvenir.
[Good morning! Puppy]
Sorry to bother you.
Hello, Grandma.
Little Teddy, I saw you.
I won't come in, Grandma.
You sure?
Yeah.
Good kid.
[The pretty girl I've met]
What's its name?
Baozi.
Baozi, your grandma is calling you.
Baozi, let's go.
Baozi.
It doesn't know who to follow.
Baozi, aren't you coming with us?
Grandma called it back.
It chose Grandma in the end.
Yeah.
It chose its master.
We're here.
So close.
Good morning, Grandpa.
Good morning.
I brought you this to pack the tools.
Needle and thread?
It can hold knives and all these tools.
You can hang this here.
Hang it here.
Okay.
I brought it back to you.
Thank you.
Bye, I'm leaving.
I'll bring you candy next time.
Bye.
We're going home first, right?
Yeah.
Bye, Brother.
Bye, Sister.
Baozi.
Baozi Baby.
Baby.
Baozi.
It has curly hair.
Curly hair.
Curly-haired Baozi.
Curly...
Baozi.
You're so good.
You're so cool.
Very cool.
Bestie outfits.
Are you a male or a female?
Baozi, let me see.
You are a male dog.
Then we can't be besties.
Goodbye, Baozi.
Go.
No, not that way. Go back.
Baozi, go home.
Go back.
Go back, Baozi.
I'll come again tomorrow, Baozi.
Baozi.
It gave up on its owner.
Can it go to your house?
Can it go? Let me ask.
I'll ask.
It won't run away, right?
Will it run far away?
Will it?
Will it run to the top?
Should we keep it inside the house?
No need.
It will follow you.
Okay.
Bye, Grandpa.
It runs so fast.
It's too fast.
Going uphill is the most tiring.
Yeah.
Do you want to raise a puppy?
But you like cats.
Yeah.
I like both.
I like
all animals.
I find them heartwarming.
I brought back a "friend".
Where?
Baozi.
Now we can play, right?
Let's try it.
It's awesome.
[New friend visiting]
Hello, Rosy.
Hello.
My name is Zhaxicuo.
I wanted to visit you.
You're so pretty.
Thank you.
This color suits you well.
You're also very pretty.
We are from the village up there.
I want to invite you
to our village up there.
Is that okay?
No way.
Just kidding. It's okay.
Can you guys teach her how to play?
She wants to play too.
No,
I want to watch them play.
How do you know if it's fun without trying it?
Look, I can play too.
Look.
Sorry.
Come on.
I'll try it.
Grab it like this.
Yeah.
Tilt your body a bit.
Squat a bit.
Got it?
Feel it?
Yeah.
Try it.
Do you know how to serve?
Very good.
Careful. Like this.
Look.
Do you...
Do you want to eat something, Zhaxicuo?
Sure.
I really like you.
Yongji, get her something to eat.
Yongji's photos are amazing, you know?
Did you know before?
I didn't know.
Show her the photos.
She takes great photos.
Really?
Look, look at her photos.
[Photographer, Zeren Yongji]
She takes great photos.
She's even better than many photographers.
You look great in the Tibetan costume.
Me?
Yeah.
Thank you.
She takes great pictures.
Are you here for fun?
Yeah.
I came to hang out with them.
Really?
Yeah.
How did you...
Did you know each other?
We met when we were one year old.
We were born together.
No, we...
A bit like you.
This is my dad.
Good-looking.
Yeah.
Is this a cat or a dog?
It looks like a cat.
It's black.
My aunt has one.
Our cat gave birth to it.
[A new friend arrives
and brings a little disappointment.]
[Pride and disappointment are at odds, with a hint
of possessiveness, how can she express herself?]
You need to control its direction.
Your bat has been
facing this way.
You need to control its direction.
Keep it straight
and it'll hit the center.
Otherwise, it will go over there.
Where did you go, Yongji?
Where did you go?
Your brother brought you that thing.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
[Nothing.]
Something's wrong. What is it?
I won't know
what's wrong unless you tell me.
I can't guess what it is.
What's wrong, Yongji?
What's wrong?
[Nothing.]
[There is a touch of emotion hidden in "nothing".]
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Still "nothing"?
Tell me.
If you trust me.
If you tell me...
Trust me.
I will solve it for you, right?
Right?
Tell me.
I don't think
she wants to talk about her concerns.
I'm not very good at dealing
with this kind of situation.
Baozi.
Baozi, what's wrong?
Baozi, don't be afraid.
Come on.
Baozi, come on.
Let's go, Baozi.
It's okay, don't be afraid.
Let me touch you.
Don't be afraid.
Baozi, don't be afraid.
Why are you scared?
What's wrong?
Baozi, don't be afraid.
Come here.
Baozi, come on.
Baozi.
It was scared to tears.
But I don't know why.
It might have never left home.
Let's take it back.
We'll send the dog home
and come back.
Tudou and I will go.
Try to figure out
why you were upset.
Okay.
I think it can walk now.
Baozi, good boy. Let's go.
Look.
It might have been scared.
[It's normal for people to be upset.
But we have to know the cause.]
I just need to know why.
But I don't know
why she was upset.
She wouldn't tell me
when I asked her.
So I don't know what to do.
You don't really
talk about it when you feel upset,
do you?
No, we don't.
Then...
Then maybe she's just
upset inside
and doesn't want to talk about it.
[Do you think she is happy?]
[I don't think so.]
Baozi is back.
Bye, Grandpa.
Grandpa, bye.
Bye.
Let's go.
[She and emotions]
Do you know why she's unhappy?
No.
I have no idea.
But you're her big brother.
Does her mom know?
Does Mom know?
[Mom favors the little brother.]
She's the second child
among the three.
She can easily be overlooked.
The parents probably
invested the most in the first child.
And they have to
take great care
of the youngest child.
So I think...
[She needs attention.]
Firstly, her grades are not good.
Secondly, our little brother has good grades.
And Mom thinks
whatever he says
must be right.
[I was very much like her when I was young.]
I can even recall
the frustration from childhood.
I wanted to learn,
but I couldn't.
I have no siblings.
I also feel
that no one defends me.
And I had poor grades when I was little.
I was bad at everything.
I just felt
that I was unnecessary.
I'm an unnecessary member of my family.
She has said similar things.
She said that, right?
Yeah.
She tends to defend Mom.
She takes our mom's side.
In the end, Mom's favorite wasn't her.
It was our little brother.
She loves Mom more, right?
Let's sit a bit.
Dad sometimes
criticizes Mom.
It's Yongji
who defends Mom.
When your dad criticizes your mom,
Yongji usually takes your mom's side.
Right?
She speaks up for Mom.
But
when she needs Mom to defend her,
Mom is against her
and defends our little brother.
So,
do you think it's her fault
or her little brother's fault in this conflict?
Both of them are at fault.
Both of them are at fault?
So your mom shouldn't take a side.
Right?
They should acknowledge their mistakes
and apologize to each other.
In your perspective,
your mom
shouldn't defend either of them.
Right?
Yeah.
I see.
What do you want to do in the future?
Me?
What do you want to do when you grow up?
Be a soldier.
A soldier.
A soldier? You want to join the army?
Yes.
Enter the military academy?
What's wrong?
Sounds good.
And it suits you.
Soldiers suffer physical challenges.
Others suffer
psychological challenges.
You won't see your family for years.
It's okay.
That's called handsome.
That's called courage.
That's called willpower.
That is true.
My dad used to be a soldier in Beijing.
Before.
You can talk with him.
He also thinks so.
He often shows me
photos from
his army days.
I think that was when
he looked the most handsome.
Your brother is here.
He's coming.
He is here.
No wonder it took so long.
You're here all along.
Do you like your brother?
Yes?
Yes.
Although you're the youngest,
I think you are the most mature.
At home,
you are your brother's
best partner, right?
Yeah.
You are a man, right?
Yes.
You are a man.
Right.
A man must take responsibility
and have a sense of duty, right?
So you must protect
every woman in your family, okay?
Okay.
Not just your mom,
your sister too, right?
Right.
So sometimes, can you
let your sister choose what she wants?
Can you?
What should you do?
[Let her feel...]
You should let her feel...
Feel...
[Love]
Love.
Right.
[Love comes in many different forms, but it's
always something we can feel with certainty.]
[It is the sunlight in your arms,
broad and warm, long-lasting and bright.]
Xixi is here.
[She with her new friends]
Hello.
Hello, Nao.
They're Xixi and Yangyang.
Hello.
Are you two
from the same family?
Yes.
Understood.
Come to our place for dinner tonight.
He is very good at cooking.
I'm good at cooking too!
Okay.
Let me carry the bag.
It's okay.
Let me help.
I can do it.
Okay, thank you.
Who is this?
Someone is recording me!
M eyes don't feel good.
Uncomfortable?
It's okay.
What are you recording?
The kids in the village
are so real.
Look at them.
They gradually forget about the camera.
Just being themselves.
The store is right here.
This is our "village hunk",
I told you.
They met when playing football yesterday.
Hello.
Everyone's getting
used to each other.
Every little girl and boy here
are full of energy.
That kind
of innate strength
makes me feel that, I'd come sooner.
[Art World of Cimarong Village]
You can draw on the wall.
Who painted that mountain?
A college student did.
Others were painted by us kids.
Rosy, let's draw something together.
Okay.
Let's draw our team.
Alright.
Let's do it.
Draw here.
Everyone, draw your own face,
okay?
Okay.
Make it bigger.
Guys,
you know you're drawing yourselves, right?
Tudou, do you really know?
Look at what you draw.
Is that Nezha?
You've drawn a monkey's head.
Be serious.
Fu Bohan.
You should have a hat.
Draw
a hat here.
The most important thing is football.
Who drew this?
She did.
It's really good.
This one
is the most artistic among these.
Like a sketch.
Really?
You really
have some real artistic talent.
Look at me.
Okay, thank you.
Rosy, come and draw one.
I'll draw myself.
[Draw myself.]
What do I look like?
[What kind of self?]
You drew a flower on your head.
This doesn't look like you.
This is what my soul looks like.
[A flower of hope on my head, love in my hands.]
Nothing else.
[I believe love and hope]
[will grow in my life.]
I think that's
happiness.
Rosy, my home is right ahead.
Thanks for having us.
You're welcome.
What will we have today,
Chef?
There are a lot.
Quite a few?
Just about five or six.
Just?
He said "just" five or six.
Looks like he thinks there aren't many dishes.
Let's patiently
wait for Xixi's dishes.
[Fire danger. Do it with an adult watching.]
I'm cooking.
You're so amazing!
Rosy, can you eat spicy food?
Yes.
You can eat spicy?
Nao can't.
Nao doesn't eat spicy food.
Got it.
[Split the work with mom.]
Try this one first.
See if it's good.
Thank you.
This one has chili.
This one doesn't.
He looks great!
[Perfect model: Xixi, diligently cooking]
Chef, let me take a picture of you.
You look so handsome.
You've done so well.
Are you tired?
No.
Mom, move these things over there.
I need to put dishes here.
I'll help you.
Tell me what I can do.
Nothing. Just sit down.
Nothing?
Then I will just watch you do it.
I'm watching.
I'll keep frying it for you.
Okay.
Mom.
Help me pour it.
Isn't it just five or six dishes, Xixi?
This is too much.
Xixi, there's more?
This is the last one.
Too much, Xixi.
Last one, I promise.
Xixi, you're incredible!
We can eat now.
Amazing.
Let's all give applause to Xixi,
okay?
Xixi, you are awesome.
Master chef.
Awesome!
Shall we eat?
Yes.
If any dish is not tasty,
just tell me directly,
and I will improve next time.
No. Every dish is delicious.
Really.
Xixi, here you go.
Thank you.
Xixi, how often do you cook?
When
my family's busy,
I'll help them cook.
How many times has this been?
The fifth or sixth time.
The fifth and sixth.
How was the first time you cooked?
Cooked on your ow.
The first time?
When I first cooked,
I was clumsy.
I was scared when the oil splashed on myself
and I ran away.
The second time was much better.
Give him an honest praise.
You first.
Xixi.
The dishes you made
have warmed us up for the whole winter.
I feel
incomparable happiness and joy.
That's a bit exaggerating.
Okay, forget it.
Just eat.
Stop talking.
Meeting time!
Sit down.
Now we're clear on our roles, right?
You're so good at taking photos,
and Nao loves it too.
So can we
[Propose in the morning]
take photos of the villagers?
Okay.
How about taking a family photo
for each of their families?
[Discuss the specific plan at noon]
A family photo?
Not necessarily.
Taking a photo with anyone is okay.
Okay.
Let me think.
Make a plan name.
A person's life is just over thirty thousand days.
"Thirty Thousand Moments of Pause".
Better call it "Thirty thousand glances back".
That's great!
Why didn't you say it earlier?
Thirty thousand glances back.
That idea came one day when I was upstairs,
I saw photos in their house.
But every photo was shot alone.
Then I felt,
maybe in a village like this,
everyone is busy with their own things.
If there's one photo
can become a memory of this year,
it could be very meaningful.
[Beautiful times deserve to be remembered.]
How many themes do we have?
Two.
"Thirty thousand glances back"
and "Thirty thousand times of peace and joy".
"Thirty thousand times of peace and joy"
is a photo of the family.
The whole family.
Yes, a family portrait.
"Glances Back" is,
whoever he wants to take a photo with,
brother, mother, or father,
just someone
he truly cherishes.
Any of that is fine.
Understand?
Yeah, we get it.
You can now work together
to make the poster first.
Then, we'll start tomorrow.
Okay.
Head home now.
Hurry up and start drawing.
Yes.
We're "working overtime" today!
Okay.
[Be Myself Photography Team,
Village Portrait Project In Preparation...]
[8:00 PM]
Where did you go, Yongji?
Come over.
This afternoon
I asked you to think.
Have you thought about it?
Have you?
Why you're unhappy?
[Little night chat: Why being unhappy?]
What's wrong, Yongji?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Think about it,
why were you unhappy just now?
Have you thought about it?
No.
Why?
Because I don't want.
You have to face
all your emotions.
[Learn to face all your emotions.]
Why were you unhappy?
Just afraid you'd be taken away.
Afraid I'd be taken away?
That's the only reason?
Is that so?
Yes.
Then you can say it.
It doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter?
Your own feelings
is the most important.
In the future,
whenever you feel sad,
and you can't find someone to talk to,
you can talk to me.
Okay.
As adults,
we often put filters
over our eyes.
We'll assume kids
as what we imagine them to be.
Very good.
In fact, I think
kids are still kids.
[Kids are still kids.]
[Their understanding of love and the world
is as pure as a sprouting bud.]
Does your father love you?
Yes. Quite a lot.
Really?
[Little night chat: What love feels like?]
What about your mom?
If she can't figure out what we want,
doesn't that mean she doesn't love us?
So you need to communicate.
I'm teaching you to communicate.
[Love is communication, not guessing.]
For instance,
if you feel unhappy,
but don't say anything,
they will never know what you want.
The way they love you will always be wrong.
Like your mom,
your dad,
your older brother, and your younger brother.
They don't know what you want.
Because whenever you're angry,
you don't speak.
If so, everyone feels
very uncomfortable.
Everyone feels upset.
Your older brother, younger brother,
all feel uncomfortable.
They will wonder what's wrong,
why you're unhappy.
That's why communication is so important.
Although my mother
is not very close with me.
But whenever something happens,
we always stand together.
When I'm hurt,
or when I'm feeling helpless,
even if we haven't talked for long,
she will come to help me.
[The love of family]
[is the strongest armor life gives you.]
[Dinner from the night before]
This is what you took for me.
The photo she took for me.
It's very beautiful.
I think
she learns everything very quickly.
Singing, dancing, taking photos.
She has artistic talent.
Really.
Your mom too.
I don't think she doesn't love you.
Because
I can tell that she loves you.
Maybe she hasn't discovered
your special advantage.
Right?
She just thinks you're naughty,
or you don't study hard.
I'm just not good at study.
Who said that?
I can't learn.
Have you really tried?
If you haven't,
how can you say you can't?
Don't you think it feels good
to get better grades?
Do better on the test.
I'll be happy.
Right.
But if I don't do well,
I'm very sad.
Right.
What I mean is you have to work hard.
If you really tried
but still can't do well, that's okay.
I never blame myself
as a kid.
Because I really did try hard.
I was just bad at studying. I couldn't help it.
I understand.
Got it?
Yes.
[Knot untied, Good night]
[Day 4 of picking up courage, 8:00 AM]
[They and the photos]
[The second floor of Yongji's place]
[Woke up early]
[Checking the plan progress]
Hello!
Were you tired yesterday?
It's fine, not very tired.
By the way,
did Sir send
something to the group yesterday?
A poster.
Did he tell me
he sent it
to the group?
Did he?
I don't know.
First up, I'm scared
they didn't finish the poster.
If it wasn't sent out yesterday,
or sent out too late today,
it's possible no one will accept the invitation.
Then all our planning yesterday
was for nothing.
I felt
particularly nervous.
Wait a moment.
Morning! Where is Nao?
Great!
You finally came.
Quick, send the poster.
Didn't you come together?
Send the poster quickly.
Yes.
Great!
I came back.
Mom took me back.
Made it in the morning.
Early in the morning.
Take a look.
Amazing!
Come, let's take a look.
[Promotional poster is completed, to be perfected]
After they brought over the poster,
I felt relieved.
And then, I wasn't that nervous anymore.
[Today's task, Be Myself
Photography Team will shoot]
[the "Thirty Thousand Times"
series for the villagers.]
You pick one.
If...
I think the first one.
I like the second one.
But I need to think about it.
This...
Aren't the mottos written here?
Potato, potato, eggplant.
Okay?
Okay.
Wait.
I'll help you make a slight change.
This looks messy.
Paint this more.
Otherwise, it won't be visible. Okay.
[Welcome to join "Thirty thousand glances back",
"Thirty thousand times of peace and joy" event.]
[Hope everyone enthusiastically signs up.]
Thank you!
Is it that every family makes different dishes?
What's up?
It's nothing.
It's done?
I cooked
some rice porridge for you.
This is delicious.
Do you want to eat?
Do you want to try one?
Okay.
Do you guys want to eat?
I'll put it here.
Why is the food so delicious every day?
That scenery is so beautiful.
Just go up from the place
where we collect mushrooms.
It's a big prairie.
Collecting mushrooms.
We usually collect mushrooms
in the mountains for two days.
We collect all day on the first day
and until noon on the second.
We gathered everything
we'd picked up
and stuffed it into a box.
Then we weigh it.
We'd ride the motorbike
down to sell it,
and then head back up the mountain
when night fell.
But the road is very narrow.
But for them, it's like a racing track.
[The narrow road is their path through life.]
[First Spot: Chang Anzhu's house]
[Second Spot: Checkpoint, Xiarang Wengmu,
Third Spot: Basketball court, Nima Lozhen]
[Fourth Spot: Duoji house]
Requests came in.
Basketball court!
We will take photos at the basketball court!
Congratulations!
Congratulations to you!
We received two orders.
The first one is at home.
The second one is at the basketball court.
Okay! Congratulations to you all!
You are Group A. We are Group B.
Is it okay?
Okay.
Come.
Pack up and go.
This is for taking photos.
Come on.
I'll teach you how to use this.
[Teaching demonstration, First glance]
Look inside this.
Just their upper body is fine.
One, two, smile!
Okay, that's good.
Come here.
Cover it.
This must be covered?
What will happen if it's not covered?
Then, you need to put all your wishes into it.
You need to think about it while covering it.
Then, it will...
Let me tell you something!
Don't get loud.
[I have a little idea.]
Hurry up.
Look, if it...
Look,
after you take pictures for people,
[Cover the photo]
you all have to cover this together, right?
[Start wishing]
Then you focus on what you truly desire,
it can actually happen.
It will...
Really?
Yes, it will manifest.
You think first. Think.
I can't think.
You think.
Think about what you want to do.
Places you want to go.
Close your eyes and think.
Think of something you really want to come true.
What do you want to do when you grow up?
Be a soldier.
That's called handsome.
That's called willpower.
[The wish seed has been planted.]
Okay? Open it.
Did you see it?
Really amazing.
[Warm reminder: At normal temperature,
Polaroid usually takes 15 seconds to develop.]
[Looking forward to rooting and sprouting!]
I'm ready to leave.
Goodbye, Nao.
Cheer up!
See you at the basketball court.
[Be Myself photography team is about
to head to the shooting locations separately]
[Nao Group]
Who is Nima Loxia?
Lozhen.
Nima Lozhen.
Who?
"Village hunk".
Is it true?
Really?
Yes, really.
That's great!
[Rosy Group]
Which house to go to?
Zeren Dengzhu's house.
Which Zeren Dengzhu?
Zeren Dengzhu.
Zeren Dengzhu of Cika Village.
That's not correct.
Not correct.
Baozi! Hurry!
Let's go see Baozi.
Baozi!
Isn't it cute?
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
This is my home.
This is your home?
This is my mom's dad's place.
The one doing crafts is...
He is my grandfather.
My maternal grandfather. Right.
Grandpa!
He is my maternal grandfather.
Hello!
[Visiting the handcraft master again.]
What did we talk about yesterday?
Bring candy.
[Today's share of candy, Leave it to me]
What is he doing today?
Today he's preparing to make shoes.
Oh, right! My shoes.
Can I make you a new one?
I want it.
Then what size do you wear?
What size?
Right.
36.
Their family is quite complete today.
Let's take a photo of their family.
Okay.
Is that okay?
Getting excited. Look at this.
Getting excited, this is.
We brought a camera.
Can we take a family portrait for you?
Sure! We don't have a family portrait.
Yeah.
My wife went to a meeting.
Then...
Then, the children
can take a photo with the elderly.
Okay.
How is that?
Good.
Stand closer.
Closer.
Come on.
Look at me.
Quick, call the slogan.
Call the slogan.
Candy, candy, eggplant!
Don't do it like that. I'll teach you.
Say it. Come say it with me.
Candy? It's potato.
What candy?
What?
It's not candy!
It's potato!
Potato, potato, eggplant. You have to say it.
Say "Potato, potato, eggplant" with me.
Come. One, two, three, say it.
Okay.
Okay, try it once.
Ready, start.
Come, say it with me!
Potato, potato, eggplant!
This is good.
They need to cover themselves.
Quickly, cover with your hands.
Make a wish.
If your wish is good,
it will come true.
It will show the photo.
Yes, cover it.
Did it come out?
Okay. Open it and take a look.
Looks good!
["Peace and joy" with a wish attached]
Thank you! Bye!
Bye, Grandpa!
You're not leaving the village, right?
Yes, I am not leaving.
Bye!
Bye-bye!
[Nao Group]
Go this way. Go down.
This way.
[Registrant: Chang Anzhu,
13 years old, Likes photography]
This is Chang, right?
Hello.
Hello!
We're the clients of the Be Myself Team.
My name is Nao.
I'm Tudou.
I'm Xixi.
Zhaxicuo is also called Xixi.
Come. Let's go inside and chat.
Let's see how to shoot today. Go!
Let's go.
I feel this home
has a special atmosphere.
I think this home
[Photographer Nao's Certified Best Spot]
will look great for shooting.
Really.
Is it beautiful?
Yes, really nice.
To take the photos,
what is the message
[First Step of Shooting: Insight into Needs]
you want to convey?
Sometimes, when the scenery
is great,
it is just temporary.
I just want to capture it.
So, how about if I snapped
some atmospheric photos
[Second Step: Customized personal shots for you]
at your home?
Would you accept that?
Is it okay?
Yes.
Okay.
Do you have any dreams for the future?
[Third Step: Creative Thinking and Customization]
See if there's anything prepared for you,
like props or something?
I want to be a photographer.
Photographer?
Okay.
We have several cameras today.
You can take photos with them.
Okay!
How about it? Okay?
Alright. Let's go.
Let's go!
The light here is particularly beautiful,
right?
A bit dark.
Okay.
Is it okay now?
Then you can
leave a slight gap.
Okay.
Take this Polaroid and pretend to be shooting.
Make sure to show the Polaroid.
[Specific Movement Instructions]
Yes, I'll shoot from here.
Not bad!
Looks pretty good.
Raise the camera a bit higher.
Okay, got it!
This is fine.
Perfect. Great!
I like it. It's good.
Pretty good. Looks nice.
To take aesthetically pleasing photos,
you definitely need creativity.
For example, what is your foreground?
What is your background?
Or, how is your lighting?
I can take a frontal shot of you from here,
but there must be no one behind you.
Could you please move a bit?
Right, there shouldn't be anyone behind.
There shouldn't be anyone behind.
Right, you can come over here.
Turn around. I'll take a shot of your face.
Okay, smile.
Perfect.
Looks nice!
It's good.
I really like it when the light hits the face,
then dim the surroundings
so you just see the face
and the hasty backdrop around it.
Can we take a photo here?
Could you
go to the very end of the bed?
Just stand there.
Here?
Right.
Lighting technician, please add some light.
Okay, thank you.
Add the light inside.
Behind?
Right, here.
Okay, hold the camera.
Just shoot through the keyhole. Come on!
Exactly. Smile.
What to do? It's out of focus.
Okay, perfect.
Look, how is it?
This idea is interesting.
Guys, take a look and learn.
Lighting technician, can you light it here?
Could we get
another camera here?
Get another one on Chang's left.
This side, right?
Yes.
Is the cameraman stressed out?
Yeah, he's here to take my job.
I'll go upstairs and take a look.
Be careful.
It's a bit messy here.
It's okay.
It's for that messy feeling.
Hold the camera and shoot towards the sky.
Lean on this.
Then, enjoy your work.
It's good. I think it's great.
Turn your face a bit more. Good! Okay.
Smile. Lift your mouth a bit.
Look ahead and enjoy that feeling.
Can you lower your head a bit?
Sit down one more step.
Yes, lean your body back a bit.
Grandma.
Let's take a picture of you three. Come on.
Potato, potato,
eggplant!
Here. You do it.
Make your wish.
Yes, make your future wish.
Yes, it's very effective.
After making your wish, open it up.
Then, it will most likely be fine.
The photo will appear.
I want to be a photographer.
Monkeys! Nao, there are monkeys!
Where?
Really! Monkeys.
Ran away.
They ran into your house.
So many!
A lot of monkeys.
Yes.
Is this your first time seeing monkeys?
Not really.
First time seeing wild ones.
Cone one! Take a picture.
How about we
go to the stadium together
and take photos of the village hunk?
Okay.
Okay? Let's go.
And after we take photos of him,
we can play soccer, okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
Goodbye, Grandma.
Goodbye.
Okay.
Let's go.
Rosy.
Why are you here?
We came here to take photos.
Are most of your photos
taken by this camera?
No.
We take photos
with Polaroid.
Hello, Rosy.
Hello.
Why do you have this jacket?
My dad is the forest ranger here.
Hello.
Right.
And we want
to invite you to take photos today.
Okay.
Let's go watch the village hunk's basketball game.
Let's go watch the basketball game.
Right now in Yajiang,
forest fire prevention is strictly enforced.
I believe so.
The temperature is naturally high in this place.
Yes.
And it's very dry.
These are dead wood and stuff.
Right?
They can easily catch fire.
Yes.
Are those horses?
Those are the horses from our village.
During summer,
there is water here,
and it turns into a lake.
My dad and I
patrol around here every day.
You just walk around here?
So you check for any mountain fires
and other dangers?
Yes.
And if there were
any small mountain fires,
my dad would use the water in his bucket...
To extinguish them.
Yes, my dad is in charge of this area.
So he is in charge of this area.
This is one of our checkpoints.
Those who want to enter the mountain
must have all their lighters and such confiscated.
And there's a monitoring station here.
If by any chance there's a fire here someday,
we can know it immediately.
One person protects the entire mountain.
And
once the mountain is protected,
the villagers at the foot of the mountain
are also fully protected.
Yes.
Amazing, sir.
Let's take photos here.
You want to take photos here?
Yes.
There are trees and other things here.
We can take photos of them too.
Okay.
Then we can just
take the photos here.
Let's do it here.
Should we stand like this?
Yes, stand facing me.
Just like this, stand over there a bit.
Sir, let me carry this.
Let me carry it.
This?
Can I carry it?
A little bit...
It's not bad.
This is nice.
Okay, I'll carry it for you.
Let's take a couple of photos.
First, walk inside.
Then walk outside, okay?
Okay.
First, walk inside?
Yes.
Come on. Ready?
Go.
Turn around.
Does this feel uncomfortable?
Turn to one side.
From the middle.
Turn around and look from the middle, okay?
Okay.
From the middle?
Go.
Turn around and smile.
Good.
Come back.
Bao, let go of your dad's hand.
Run. Start running.
Okay.
Run.
Laugh.
I really want to laugh.
It's quite beautiful.
It looks great.
It's so funny.
When you look back,
it feels like you're protecting this forest.
And your dad is holding your hand.
It means he's also protecting you.
I think so too.
My dad has worked here as a ranger
for over 20 years.
Over 20 years?
So your dad started this job when you were born?
About right.
So what are you studying now?
Modern agricultural equipment.
You still want to work in agriculture.
You'll come back someday?
You want to come back?
[For their family,]
[at this moment,]
[it seems like being a ranger]
[is no longer just a job]
[but an accomplishment.]
[If someone guards something for 20 years,]
[I think the emotions are different.]
[His daughter is 20 years old.]
[And he's been doing this job for 20 years.]
[In front of this mountain he's been protecting,]
[a glance back with his daughter]
[is very moving.]
It's snowing.
I've never seen such heavy snow.
[The ad is aired at this period of time]
Our themes are
"Thirty thousand times of peace and joy"
and "Thirty Thousand Glances Back."
So you want to shoot
which one?
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
[One hour ago]
Village hunk, take a shot.
Nice.
I've taken many photos. They all look great.
Come on. Let's play soccer.
Okay.
Come on.
Come on. Start!
Nao.
Nice shot.
Nao, do you want to take a break?
No need. It's okay.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
What's wrong?
I'm too tired and feeling dizzy.
Dizzy?
I'm just too tired
and can't stand up.
Let me help you up.
Get up.
It's okay. He is just...
It's okay. I'm just a little tired.
I'm fine.
Sit down.
Sit on this stool.
Thank you.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
You go ahead and talk first.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Really, I'm fine.
I'm just feeling dizzy.
It's snowing.
Look at the snow.
It's so beautiful.
I will take some photos.
Do you need my help?
I'll take photos for them.
Keep inhaling.
Quick, the snow will be gone soon.
Okay, thanks, Grandpa.
It's so beautiful.
Look at the snow.
Pretty good. Looks nice.
It looks very clear.
Okay.
Where are you, Nao?
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
What did I tell you?
How many times have I told you?
Can you run here?
Can you jump here?
I didn't.
I felt uncomfortable while walking.
Wait...
How could this happen?
He didn't jump.
He suddenly had a headache while walking.
When you went to play basketball,
did he jump?
Yes, he did.
See?
You won't
feel uncomfortable as soon as you jump.
You will feel uncomfortable
in a little while after you jump.
Do you get what I mean?
Is it hot?
Here it comes.
Here, eat something.
Here, eat quickly.
Here, you guys eat too.
Eat.
Here, eat.
Thank you.
Have two more.
Replenish your energy.
Here.
Where do you feel uncomfortable now?
I'm a bit full.
You are stuffed?
What about your head?
It's fine.
What about your breathing?
Try to take a deep breath.
Okay, inhale.
Slowly, exhale.
Don't inhale so fast.
[The ad is aired at this period of time]
[Little night chat: Sharing]
Who took this?
Nao, who took this?
Half of your teammates are not in the photo.
Only you...
Only you are in it.
Xixi took this.
Don't you have a photo of you?
I took one for you.
Yes, that's right.
He took one of me.
Tudou took it.
It's good, right?
It looks good.
Your family has some talent.
This one is so cool.
Who is it?
Tudou.
Right?
He looks like a soldier, doesn't he?
Yes.
He was very serious about it.
Me?
I told him...
He was like this. And I said...
He was like this.
I said, "Tudou, be like a soldier."
Okay, today when taking photos,
which moment made you feel
[Writing an article about the special moment today]
very special and unforgettable?
Unforgettable?
During the photoshoot.
Very special and unforgettable.
Can I feel good
about my photo shoot?
Of course.
I feel like the photo I took through the peephole
looks really good.
You felt something, right?
When I was focusing at that time,
it took about a minute.
And when I finally managed to focus,
the photo turned out very well.
Right?
I was very excited.
This one counts.
Today I took a photo of someone looking back.
I took a photo of the mountain guardian.
There's a man
who has been a forest ranger for 20 years.
He has to check the mountain every day.
Right on the mountain.
The forest on the mountain
might start small fires.
If they didn't keep watching,
the small fires would turn into big fires.
So their job is very important.
Yes.
So do you understand their importance
to this?
Do you understand?
Anyway, I took a photo
of the glances back of him and his daughter.
It was in front of the mountain
he guarded for 20 years.
He looked back at his own past.
Yes, move a bit more inside.
Move inside.
I took this one.
So this should be the only one
of the glances back we took, I guess.
But it's quite meaningful, right?
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
What are you thinking about again?
Nothing.
Playing cards?
No, it just feels cutting.
What do you mean by "cutting"?
It's just...
Heart-breaking?
At that moment?
Yeah.
We got to meet someone
who can do one thing for 20 years.
Now let's each select
three of our favorite photos, okay?
Okay.
Alright, let's start.
Hurry and organize your favorite photos.
Okay.
This looks good, right?
How about this one?
I think this one is very nice.
What do you think?
Do you think it looks good?
It looks good.
This one.
Here, this one looks good.
Or this one looks better.
Baozi.
Good kid.
[I really like Baozi.]
All of these are candid shots.
Candid shots are so hard.
I'll throw it up and head it.
Did you capture it?
What's wrong?
Take a look.
This is really good.
One is "Thirty thousand times of peace and joy,"
and the other is "Thirty thousand glances back."
Yes.
Move a bit more inside.
Okay. Three, two, one.
Potato, potato, eggplant.
How is it?
This shot was well captured, right?
It's so professional.
Quick, make a wish.
Make a wish.
Yes, this is very effective.
Open up after making a wish.
Close your eyes.
Close your eyes and think.
Make a wish.
What about mine?
What about the one with grass growing on my head?
Four-leaf clover.
Isn't this okay?
I need more oxygen.
I laughed so hard that tears came out.
I really can't understand
what exactly you are laughing at.
As soon as I start laughing,
I can't stop.
I'll go record something.
The sound of kicking pebbles.
The sound of flowing water in the village.
I think all sounds are special.
There's nothing special.
It's coming.
It's scary.
When I got up in the morning,
I wrote a script.
Three, two, one.
So cool.
Alright, come on.
You can take a few steps forward.
And then you can stop
and not go any further.
The pace is too fast.
Don't rush.
Don't look at the camera.
You made that expression too early.
Too fake.
Again.
One more time.
We're having iron pot stew tonight.
This is awesome.
These rice noodles are really delicious.
Rosy's food is so tasty.
Do we have to leave tomorrow?
This is a hat
we kept for seven years.
I want to give it to you.
Thank you.
I don't want
to read the letter anymore. Is it okay?
["Be Myself" Performed by Duan Aojuan]
Through the tiny dust
See the light pouring down
Footprints of dozens of centimeters
Can depict mountains and seas
Lift the fallen body with both hands
Learn to start running
To chase the distant future
With the posture of shining meteors
From the small window sill
Imagine beyond the blue sky
The flower to bloom we've been waiting for
ten thousand times
And time will record
Every stay and departure
Little you
Little me
Exist with little courage
Big dreams
Big world
Can be carried by a heart
No matter the confusion,
still seek a ray of light
No matter the despair,
still use the last ounce of strength
Be Myself
Because we look for
The small yet immense love