[The ad is aired at this period of time]
You really like your hometown, do you?
I also like your hometown very much.
[Cimarong Village
The 5th day of gathering courage]
I feel like there are so many sounds to record.
[I feel like there are so many sounds to record]
Because I think all sounds are special.
Probably because I always stay here,
I don't think there's anything special.
How could that be?
[Sounds of the forest and the spring]
[Listening to the wind]
There are so many
changes happening every day.
It's just that we haven't noticed them.
[Listening to all sounds]
I got it.
[With the windows to the outside world shut,]
[I began to listen to my heart.]
[Feeling isn't hard,]
[but how do you find empathy?]
[Expressing isn't hard,]
[but how do you embrace misunderstandings?]
[Forgetting isn't hard,]
[but how do you face it again?]
[The sun is shining brightly today]
[because you are here.]
[Be Myself]
[The ad is aired at this period of time]
Production team,
tomorrow I want to collect
the sounds in the village.
So, can I borrow
professional recording equipment?
[Director: OK!]
I'm leaving, Yongji.
I'll go record something.
[Today is good for recording]
See you later.
This sound is very good.
First take,
the sound of flowing water in the village.
Start recording.
[Sound Collecting of Cimarong Village:
Sound of flowing water]
[Listening to the murmuring of the stream]
Is that okay?
Finished recording.
Add the falling stones sound.
Okay.
Hello, Rosy.
Hello.
Xixi.
[Two days ago]
We can eat now.
Let's all give applause to Xixi,
okay?
Xixi, you are awesome.
Do you want to go with me?
Yes.
Okay, then come with me.
Let's go.
Look, we're both wearing glasses.
Let me help you.
It's okay. I'll carry it.
I'll carry it.
There you go.
I can carry it.
Okay, thank you.
You're welcome.
You're so nice. Why are you so nice?
Tell me if it's too heavy.
Okay.
You can also listen
if there's any sound
you think it's special.
[Exploring sound]
Okay.
Let's record...
Let's record the sound of Zhaxi's footsteps.
How is it?
No need for that.
Don't you like it?
No need for that, I think.
There's nothing special about it.
The sound of footsteps is very special.
Everyone's footsteps sound different.
When everyone walks,
their center of gravity is actually different.
Tashi Delek.
[*May all auspiciousness be with you.]
Baby.
How old are you?
Tashi Delek.
He still can't talk.
He can't talk, right?
No, he can't talk.
Really stable.
Let's record when you can talk then.
Let's record when you can talk, baby.
So cute.
Tashi Delek.
[The sound of a child growing up
hidden in his grandma's bent back]
Come on.
Go record her footsteps.
Footsteps?
Yes, follow her footsteps like this.
Record the sound
of the old lady kicking pebbles while walking.
[Sound Collecting of Cimarong Village:
The old lady's footsteps]
Done.
[Sound Collecting of Cimarong Village:
The old lady's footsteps have been recorded]
That's enough.
I feel like there are so many sounds to record.
If you let me keep recording,
I think I can record for a year.
Because I think all sounds are special.
[There are ever-new sounds in silence]
I feel like I just can't record everything.
Probably because I always stay here,
I don't think there's anything special.
[There are sounds in silence]
How could that be?
I can feel
the birds in my community
only fly
around the window
which is
directly facing my bed.
But they never go to the window
in the back.
Isn't that amazing?
Yes.
They will fly over together
around 6 p.m.
That is special.
Punctual.
Right, so there is a lot to observe around us.
[There are so many changes around]
There are many changes happening every day.
It's just that we haven't noticed them.
[Melody Sealed]
Let's go, cow.
Can we record the sound of it eating?
Great idea.
Can we?
Of course.
[Sound Collecting of Cimarong Village]
[Sound of a cow eating]
Record the sound of the cow eating.
Be careful, Zhaxi.
Go record a...
There is one below.
No, it isn't eating.
It isn't eating, Zhaxi.
Alright.
[Sound Collecting of Cimarong Village:
Sound of a cow eating]
Failed.
Cut.
[Sound Collecting of Cimarong Village:
Sound of a cow eating; Recording Failed]
It's not eating.
Let's go.
Be careful.
We are so funny.
Let's take a photo together.
Raise the mic.
You need to hold the pole like this.
You need to do it like this.
I'll teach you, Zhaxi.
You have to do it like this.
Yes, like this.
That's right.
This is professional.
This is very professional.
Hold on.
This is the pole-raising guys'
most professional gesture.
Let's go.
Do you like dogs?
I like them.
You like them, right?
If you have the chance,
I can take you to see my dogs.
I have six dogs.
[Bawan, Laifu, Huang Meili,
Doe, Didian, Lele]
Six dogs?
So many.
Several of them were abandoned by others.
Baozi.
Baozi, you are here.
It's not barking.
Look, it's so nice.
Baozi.
Let's record Baozi's
ASMR.
[*Autonomous sensory meridian response]
Okay, that's enough. Cut.
Great, Baozi is enjoying its meal.
Go ahead, Baozi.
Take it.
It's gone.
Let's go.
Alright, let's go.
Rosy.
Someone in our hometown can translate.
Do you want to go take a look?
Okay.
Here, let's go.
Hello.
Guest from afar.
Tashi Delek.
[Yongzhong Tsering, nickname Yong]
My name is Yongzhong Tsering.
Yongzhong Tsering.
To summarize,
[Yongzhong Tsering means longevity]
my name means longevity.
Recently,
I've been studying
the translation of ancient poems.
I'm interested. Go ahead.
Yes.
This.
Translate them into Tibetan.
Yes.
Okay, Tibetan version
of "Prelude To Water Melody".
[Sound Collecting of Cimarong Village]
Yong's...
[Tibetan version of "Prelude To Water Melody"]
Yong's version.
Start.
[Tibetan Version of "Prelude To Water Melody"
Reciter: Yongzhong Tsering]
How long will the full moon appear?
Wine cup in hand, I ask the sky.
I do not know what time of the year.
It would be tonight in the palace on high.
Riding the wind, there I would fly,
yet I'm afraid the crystalline palace would be
too high and cold for me.
I rise and dance, with my shadow I play.
On high as on earth, would it be as gay?
Men have sorrow and joy; they part or meet again;
The moon is bright or dim and she may wax or wane.
There has been nothing perfect since the old days.
Thank you. Tashi Delek.
Amazing.
Record a couple of blessings.
Okay.
Start.
[Sound Collecting of Cimarong Village
Yong's Blessing]
Hello, friends.
My name is Yongzhong Tsering.
Wish everyone
good fortune in the new year
and may everything go your way.
I wish everyone a happy life every day.
May you be joyful every day.
Tashi Delek.
Thank you.
[Happiness is the most sincere blessing]
Are you happy, Ma'am?
Yes.
Happy. Tashi Delek.
Happy.
[Sound is the subtle yet full trace of life]
Tashi Delek. Happy.
Sir, we'd like to record
[The tranquil poetry in labor]
the sound of you building the wall.
[We catch the whispers of flowing water]
Very happy.
[Catch the whispers of the wind]
Still feel very happy as usual.
And, it's very meaningful.
[Sound is everything
It's Special and unrepeatable]
For me,
every sound I hear
is a picture
and a memory.
[Flag moving]
[Thoughts unfold]
I got it.
Today, while collecting the Five-Star Red Flag
when it was flying in the air,
why did you cry?
[Seeing the Five-Star Red Flag makes me excited]
Since childhood, seeing the Red Flag just makes me
excited.
I just had a kind of...
That atmosphere
just made my heart feel very surging.
Maybe when I saw
Zhaxi standing there,
I would recall
when I watched the flag raising as a child
and when saluting.
We were both
[We are all children under the Five-Star Red Flag]
in the same environment,
living under the Five-Star Red Flag.
[Reviewing yesterday's photos]
I think this time coming to the countryside
is far better
than I imagined.
Life in the countryside
is very free and relaxed.
Nice shot.
"Village hunk".
I feel this picture is quite fun.
Right?
Yes.
Moreover, the scenery here
is very different from the urban areas.
There are calves
and cow dung everywhere.
Some people would stick flowers on it,
considering it as a work of art.
It feels like
living in the countryside
can keep you always feeling
happy and joyful.
This morning, when I got up,
I used AI
to write a script.
I just wanted to capture the beautiful scenery
and the joy of the countryside.
[The little director]
[is ready to start filming]
[My first day back to Cimarong Village]
[I'm the village hunk. I like to play basketball.
I'm recognized as a handsome guy around here.]
[On my first day returning from the city
to build the village,]
[something happened.]
[To know what happens next, press 1]
Stop.
There's a goof here.
This part can be clearly seen.
Everything is captured.
[Director Nao's perspective]
[Filming reminder: Clear the scene]
Should we start filming from the door opening?
[Director Nao's filming rule: Adjust the angle]
Start from the door opening.
Yes, I'll stand here to shoot.
So where should I drive?
No, you don't need to drive.
Just get off the car and exit the frame.
Shoot a close-up.
Start from the door opening.
Look, it's like this.
It just shut off like this.
Look.
Yes, get down.
Don't pretend.
Hurry up.
Three, two, one.
[Director Nao's filming perspective]
That's cool.
Perfect.
So perfect.
Then I'll tell you how to shoot.
Well,
you just walk down like this.
"Why is there no network?"
Then, you come up and ask,
"We have spider webs here. Do you want them?"
Then, you go and touch that cow.
For village hunk,
just show a disdainful expression.
Oh no, the cow walked away.
Stop it.
The cow is an important actor.
[The new female lead is memorizing her lines]
It's the spider.
Come on.
[Act Two]
Why is there no network?
[Director Nao's filming perspective]
Why are you laughing?
Madam.
No.
Don't walk from this side.
Don't go.
Please, don't go.
Should I run up here
or go herd this cow?
Let's go.
Let's go shoot at the basketball court
over there first.
[Director Nao's filming rule:
Changing scenes to spark new inspiration]
We still need to find someone
slightly younger than you.
I'll call my little brother over.
Later,
you can just
dribble the ball by the sideline.
Yes, just dribble the ball here.
They'll be here soon.
Let's talk about the plot.
[Nao's crazy ideas: Extended edition]
In this scene,
he was found later.
Look, at the beginning,
he was not easily recognized, but a bit familiar.
Then, shocked.
And then he was especially happy.
Let's start shooting, come on.
[Director Nao's rule: You'll learn by shooting]
Come on.
Don't look at the camera.
Come on, let's do it again.
No, you were too anxious at the beginning.
You were supposed to dribble for five seconds,
but only dribbled for one second.
Come on.
[NG X2]
No.
You made that expression too early.
Yes, come on.
[NG X11]
It was too fast, too fast.
It doesn't look real this way.
Come on, let's shoot you again.
Come on.
Don't look at the camera.
Too stiff.
[NG X32]
"Bro", just like this.
[NG X41]
Come on, let's do it again.
[NG X68]
Come on, again.
[NG X77]
One more time.
Come on, again.
[Director Nao's masterpiece
Let's look forward to it]
Do you usually like watching this?
Do you like sitting on the mountain
watching this?
Yes.
Isn't there also a bridge like this up there?
And then it's flat, isn't it?
So I put both of my feet outside
and then watch.
I also like it very much.
I like sitting in one place and daydreaming.
Then taking some pictures and the like.
You alone?
And my friends.
Together?
Yes.
Great.
So envious.
You really like your hometown.
I also like your hometown very much.
I really like this song.
Have you heard it before?
It seems I've heard it before.
But I'm not sure.
Listen to it carefully again.
Sounds good.
Record Zhaxi singing.
The feeling that Zhaxi gave me is
a child with a soul
similar to mine.
It's quite a surprise.
It would've been great to know him earlier.
The one who left has gone to distant lands.
May he find peace.
Cut.
I think you sing very well.
You think your singing is not good?
I think it sounds good.
I don't think I sing well.
I think it's nice.
This is your first time listening to it.
You can sing so well.
You're impressive.
[Pleasant to hear
Because I hear your soul singing]
How about we record the sound of geese?
I don't know.
Go ask them.
Tashi Delek.
[May all auspiciousness be with you.]
Hello.
Hello, my name is Chang Silang.
[Elder sister Chang Silang]
Hello.
[Younger sister Zhaxicuo]
My name is Zhaxicuo.
Now I'm going to milk the cows.
You can take a look.
Okay.
Tashi Delek.
Woof.
[Voice receiving]
It doesn't sound friendly.
Woof.
Hello.
It's right here.
Doggie.
Cut.
Pause recording.
Forget it.
[Woof]
Come on.
I'm more interested in the dog
than the milk.
Woof.
This dog has a lot of antics.
Do you want me to let it out?
What would happen if you let it out?
What would happen?
Seriously?
We have quite a few people here.
One person, one bite.
This is very dangerous.
[Hidden behind the door]
[What kind of vicious dog is it]
Why do you seem so scared?
It's very small.
It feels wronged.
Come on, come over.
Speak.
Say something, baby.
Speak up.
It is scared.
Cut.
Then let's record
the sound of a calf drinking milk.
[Sound from Cimarong Village:
The sound of a calf drinking milk]
So cute.
Let's record the sound of geese.
Captured the goose sound.
So clear.
I think it sounds a bit unpleasant.
I don't feel...
I feel no one wants to listen to it.
I feel.
Because it sounds a bit unpleasant.
Is the goose angry?
Take it easy, Miss Goose.
Is it embarrassed?
Little goose, are you embarrassed?
Look.
The big goose is like this.
Look, it is protecting
the little goose.
The big goose is protecting the little goose.
Look.
Between the two,
the big goose shows stronger aggression.
Catch one to verify.
I can only catch the small one.
I don't dare to catch the big one.
Its mouth is so big.
I'll do it.
Be careful.
[The cameraman joins the battle]
Block it.
Be careful.
Come on.
It is coming to catch you.
You'll be caught.
[The cameraman is running away]
The two of them have a
surprisingly good relationship.
Their relationship is so...
This is the first time I've noticed that.
Once its brother is caught,
it comes to catch us.
It just didn't dare to bite us.
Try again.
I think...
I think it's so amazing.
["Catch the goose" Second round starts]
It's alone.
It's here.
[The cameraman skillfully runs away]
Zhaxi.
It's true.
The big goose is protecting the little goose.
The big goose is obviously afraid
of us.
How can they have such good emotions?
Let them play by themselves, Zhaxi.
We are about to
make buttered tea today.
Alright.
Okay, you can taste
this buttered tea.
What is this?
This is our lunch,
radish dumplings
Radish dumplings are so big.
Yes.
And this is
Za Tang we made a few days ago.
What is Za Tang?
[Highland barley honey candy]
Highland barley and honey
are boiled until
they can take shape in the water.
Sit down.
As if this is my home.
Can I taste it?
Yes.
Thank you.
Sweet.
Do you want to eat it with some buttered tea?
It has a wheat fragrance.
Yes.
Do you want to taste the radish dumplings?
But I don't know
if you are used to eating it.
What's wrong? What does it taste like?
You can taste it.
Taste it.
I will taste half of it.
Just in case, right?
It's okay.
It is a bit cold now.
Do you eat it?
Yes.
We use the tools made by grandpa
to grind it.
And then
add some fat meat to stir-fry.
Delicious.
I can get used to it. It's delicious.
After I came here,
I was used to the food
I eat every day.
It's delicious.
That's good.
Where do you attend to your school?
Suining.
Meishan.
Meishan?
The one we are familiar with?
Yes.
The Meishan near Leshan?
The one near Chengdu.
You go to such a far place to study?
It's not that far.
Meishan is very far.
It's okay.
Meishan...
Meishan is still far from here.
How long will it take?
Four hundred...
About five or six hours.
It's okay.
More than five or six hours.
Five or six hours is okay.
You are also from Sichuan?
I am from Chengdu.
That's very close.
So when you say it, I just...
How could you...
Sichuan dialect.
Where is your high school?
In Deyang.
My high school is also in Deyang.
Really?
So you just come back for the New Year?
Yes, we come back during summer vacation
to collect matsutake.
He is on our team.
Which one?
He is just on our team.
He is very well-behaved.
Yes, I think so too.
You don't know how much we like him.
Everyone says he's got the gift of gab.
Our whole crew also likes him.
He is very well-behaved.
My mom likes him very much.
She says you are not as good as Dengdui Zhaxi.
He is so young
but so articulate.
His thinking is so clear.
It turns out he is the golden child next door.
Do you usually hang out together?
We just
pick matsutake together.
We basically walk together.
You just hang out during the New Year.
We hang out together during the New Year.
How do you hang out?
Just dancing downstairs.
There are those kinds of activities,
village-wide activities, right?
Tug-of-war competition, and running competition.
We used to have horse racing.
Running from the bottom to here
to decide who is the first place.
It's exciting every day.
I went there every day.
Climb up there to watch that.
Horse racing?
Who is the first one?
Gradually, it won't be held.
It's still quite a pity.
Do you want to go back with us?
Where?
But I have to ask Tudou.
Because we are going to his house.
Let's go.
We arrived.
Grandpa.
I made two good friends today.
Brother.
These are the two friends I made today.
Look, this looks exactly the same
as your dog.
[20 minutes ago]
[Attracted by the smell]
Puppy, come here.
It's so lively.
Puppy.
Doesn't it look exactly the same?
[Similarity 80%: "Vicious Dog No. 1"
"Vicious Dog No. 2"]
Do you eat it?
Put it on the ground.
Eat it.
Eat until full.
Good boy.
Eat until full. You too.
Eat until full.
How about we call it "Full"?
Call it "Full".
"Full".
Because when we came here,
every day you say eat till you're full, sister.
Eat till you're full, brother.
Nao is back.
Nao.
"Full".
What's wrong?
I'm full.
What is this?
"Full".
Little dog.
Hello, little baby.
Little baby.
You went to her house today, right?
I went to her house to play with the geese.
Geese?
They have a pair of twin geese.
If you took away
one of them,
the other goose
would chase you and bite you.
Because its sibling was taken away.
What if you take them all?
Right, I didn't think of that.
Just take them all.
Wouldn't that be better?
[Dinner time]
Thank you for your hard work.
This is so lavish.
Let's dig in.
Is the corn delicious?
Yes, it's delicious.
So good.
Soaked full of the broth.
Good job.
It is homegrown.
Can you cook?
What can you cook?
I can cook most things.
[Chef Zhao's dish presentation]
I like to cook.
So full.
I haven't finished editing my video yet.
["Director Nao" is editing]
These are the stars I shot last night.
These are much more beautiful
than the ones in the big city.
I feel "village hunk" speaks very stiffly.
How about I dub it?
[Voice actor Tudou applying to participate]
Ok.
But you have to dub from start to finish.
Okay.
Let me do it.
Let's go.
Okay, let's dub it.
To dub?
This is a big-budget production.
Let's talk with the platform
to release it.
Go to my bedroom.
Alright.
You just...
This is much more beautiful
than the ones in the big city.
Come on.
This is much more...
[Slip of the tongue]
This is much more beautiful than
the ones in the big city.
Big city.
Speak a bit faster.
This is much more beautiful than
the ones in the big city.
This...
This is much more beautiful...
Don't mind.
Not recommended.
This flower was planted on cow dung.
Although it stinks a bit,
it is still
good-looking.
Do it again.
It is still
good-looking.
This is not right.
It is still good-looking.
Three, two, one.
This flower was planted on cow dung.
Although it stinks a bit,
it is still good-looking.
Really good.
Can you send it to us after it's done?
Of course.
Yongji is good at taking photos.
Really?
Take a photo.
I am not good at using this.
I can do it.
I am quite good at...
You're good at taking photos, right?
Yes.
[Taking photos of sister]
[Taking photos of scenery]
[Taking photos of Rosy]
[Taking family photos]
[Taking photos of wall paintings]
[Professional photography, two days]
Cheese.
So ugly.
Let me see, so ugly.
I've already seen it.
Don't look anymore.
Let me see.
No, don't look at it.
Don't take pictures anymore.
Why?
This is also taken by him.
He took this.
Beautiful.
Very artistic.
A dashed line and a solid line
represent that
in the life of both illusion and reality,
we're constantly progressing.
Moving forward, right?
Moving forward.
He has depth.
- With depth.
- Great photography skills.
Having depth.
[If that's the case]
[Try again]
What kind of photographer shoots like this?
Gali.
Both his eyes are closed.
Gali, you should take photos like this.
He even strikes a pose.
And then
I'm not used to this.
Alright, then you...
Just do it this way.
Yes, just like this.
Quite special.
[Dubbing return]
Let's guess
the sounds we recorded today,
okay?
Okay.
Xixi sure knows it.
[Xixi participated in the recording throughout]
He doesn't guess it.
Right, I don't guess.
Okay.
If he answered wrong,
his punishment would be
ten squats, okay?
How about push-ups?
Boys do push-ups.
Push-ups.
Yes, push-ups.
[Wrong answer punishment]
Ten push-ups, okay?
[Girls do 10 squats, boys do 10 push-ups]
Okay.
You need to listen to it carefully.
Ask.
In this audio,
[Q Whose footsteps are in this sample?]
which group of people's footsteps are?
Okay, get ready.
[Q: Whose footsteps are in this sample?]
Three, two, one.
All the staff.
[Yongji guessed one correctly]
Record the footsteps of
all the staff coming to this village.
The next one will be very difficult.
How difficult?
The next one is very difficult.
Yes.
The next one is
[Hint: In the air]
in the air.
No matter where it is,
you will always feel.
[Hint: In the air, dazzling, glorious]
it is very dazzling and glorious.
What this item is?
[Q What item made the sound in this sample?]
Start.
[Q: What item made the sound in this sample?]
Say it quickly.
Three, two, one.
Can't you hold it?
Say it.
Cow.
Is it a cow?
Bird.
Correct.
Incorrect.
Ten.
[Yongji gets to enjoy 10 squats]
Me.
National flag.
["Tudou" guessed one correctly]
Why?
How did you guess it?
I originally thought it was a drone.
But you later mentioned dazzling and glorious.
National flag.
Didn't you say it was in the sky?
Yes, the national flag waves in the wind.
Do it.
Finished.
Okay, here we go.
This is the one
that makes people feel solid,
[Hint: A solid carrier]
a carrier.
Building.
[Nao gets to enjoy 10 push-ups]
Ten.
Is there anyone else who wants to try?
You.
The one they used to take a photo.
The triangle machine.
Ten.
One.
Alright, the last one, begin.
[Q: What is the sound made?]
Cut. Very sturdy.
Three, two, one.
Fence.
Ten.
Tree.
[Q: What exactly is making the sound
in this sample?]
Cut. Very sturdy.
Very sturdy.
Wall.
Correct.
[Nao guessed one correctly]
Listen to
the wall they built themselves.
The sound of the house.
Go ahead.
One is right and the other is incorrect,
which is offset.
Three,
two...
Two, three, four.
Stop counting.
Seven, eight.
Are you adding weight to your waist?
You won't be able to stand up tomorrow.
Alright.
Watch our video.
Come, let's take a look at Director Fu.
I feel this time it was just average.
[Director Nao's bumpy creative road]
Why does it always feel a bit off?
What's going on here?
Do you mean a spider web?
Don't look at the camera.
You made that expression too early.
Too stiff.
[Welcome to watch "Nao's Little Creation"]
Alright, let's start.
Why is there no network?
Are you talking about a spider web?
These are the stars I photographed at night.
This is much better than that
in our big city.
This is the sunrise over the golden mountains.
Guess what this is.
What is this?
This is a flower stuck in cow dung.
Although it smells a bit,
it's quite pretty.
Let's have a match.
Okay!
This ball is a bit worn out.
You don't mind, right?
I don't mind.
Displaying the childhood.
- Let's have a match.
- Okay.
So dirty.
Take off your new clothes.
Wear those old clothes you used to work.
[The end]
It was great!
Amazing!
Learning from you, I'm also good.
I think your transition
was shot really well.
The one against the light,
and then the two brothers walk by.
The one where the two walk by together
was shot really well.
Just mainly trying to express something.
How to say...
I'll tell you later.
I want to express something more profound.
Got it.
Did you get it, guys?
- Got it.
Got it.
I felt it.
Actually, the depth...
Art is not...
Right?
Very perfect, right?
The brotherhood in this.
Mainly not about
brotherhood.
But there is, yes.
Well...
It just has some details inside.
It's like a flower growing on cow dung.
What it wants to express is
that not everything
is absolutely good or bad.
It is mainly through
your own perception
that you feel these things.
Then this...
There is a part...
It says in the clip
that this is a worn out basketball, right?
This ball is a bit worn out.
A worn out basketball is like,
he took off his adult disguise
and then became his childhood self.
Then, the next part goes back to his childhood.
- Let's have a match.
- Okay.
Isn't the last part about skipping stones?
At the beginning,
he threw while wearing urban clothes,
but found his sleeve dirty and stopped throwing.
Then he dusted off his sleeve.
Finally, his brother helped him
put on the clothes
he used to wear in the countryside,
the purest clothes.
I think this is from the low point to the climax
of this stage,
you can be yourself again.
You can be free.
Skipping stones is to show the use of uselessness.
It is these seemingly useless activities
that can bring you true happiness.
[The use of uselessness
helps you find true happiness]
After your explanation,
I can truly understand now.
In the countryside,
life is free from distractions.
The vitality of nature
and the life rhythms of the land.
I think this is what rural life
has brought to us.
[The free and vigorous wind in the mountains
will relax every tense heart]
Do we have to leave tomorrow?
Yes.
What time are we leaving?
Around dawn.
[Countdown to departure day - 1]
The three of us should take a photo together.
Pulled back again?
Gali.
What? Do you want that alluring pose?
Do you want me to take another picture of you?
[Nao will end recording early due to school start]
Nao.
Nao!
[At this moment, Nao]
[Writing a farewell letter with all his heart]
I stayed up late writing it yesterday.
After that, I got up in the morning
and wrote a few more letters.
Because during this period,
they were with me every day.
Just like my real mom and dad.
Taking care of me like real brothers.
So, I think
by writing letters, I cannot repay them at all
for their care over this period.
[A million words condensed in the small note]
I'll make iron pot stew, Tudou.
You will cook?
What are you going to do?
Tonight I will make iron pot stew
for them.
Really?
You've had it, right?
Have you eaten it?
Then, try it.
It's very delicious!
Northeastern food.
Stewed chicken.
Iron pot stew with goose.
We only have chicken.
Bring down the two geese from Silang's home.
Take their geese and stew them?
Tudou, today...
It's time to say goodbye.
Not today.
You're going in the pot today.
In the pot today.
Tudou, you're going in the pot today.
Tudou,
I can't bear to part with you.
Where did Yongji go?
Yongji is changing into Tibetan clothes upstairs.
That's too formal, isn't it? I think.
[A formal farewell banquet]
Today's sky is really blue.
Tudou, you're going in the pot today.
Tudou.
Sorry.
Do we have onions? Tudou?
There are no onions.
We can go out and buy some.
Tudou, wait a moment.
I also want to go.
Buy vegetables.
Where are the onions?
Do we have onions?
- No onions.
- None.
Do we have onions?
Onions.
The onions are sold out.
Sold out. There's other stuff.
Okay.
It seems they don't sell onions.
Let's go borrow from someone.
Let's go borrow some.
It's okay.
As long as we're brazen, it's fine.
Let's go.
There are no onions.
Let's go and ask this one first.
Ask this one.
So embarrassing.
What's so embarrassing? I'll go ask.
It's okay.
People might think there's a burglar.
Hello!
- Hello!
- But...
We'll just barge into their house?
- Is there anyone home?
- The door's open.
I've always been like this.
Grandma, do you have onions?
What onions?
Onions are the white, round ones.
Onions.
Come up, we have some.
They have. Let's go.
Okay. Thank you!
Not so proper, right?
Thank you.
Is this an onion?
A red one.
At that time, I also felt quite embarrassed.
Then I wanted to give her money.
But she raised hands
and refused the money.
I felt that
the people in this village are very hospitable.
And they always manage to move me.
Bye!
Bye, Grandma!
The people here are really nice.
[The people here are really very nice]
Does this count as trespassing?
I don't think so.
We never knock at the door.
We only knock once we are inside.
Really?
[Little village, huge relaxation]
Who exactly is so capable
to get the onions?
We borrowed them.
We found someone to borrow them from.
Teddy.
[Meeting with the little dog friend]
Doggie.
Don't bark, stop barking.
Alright.
Don't bark.
No barking.
[The most adorable encounter in the mountains]
Alright.
See? It's so quiet now.
It's very small.
Come. Come here.
Bark.
Bark, baby.
Baozi!
[Wagging a friendly little tail,
being unguarded and close to strangers]
Baozi!
See, this one looks just like
your dog.
[A "hello" in childhood leads
to rolling together in life]
Little puppy, come here.
Eat well. It also eats well.
Eat well.
[It is the softness and simplicity
forgotten as we grow up]
How about we call it "Eating Well"?
Call it "Eating Well".
Eating Well!
Eating Well, come here.
This...
Here...
Here.
Go ahead.
Don't be afraid.
It's a nest, not for grabbing you.
Don't be afraid. Look.
I'm not grabbing you, right?
Don't be afraid.
I'm not grabbing you.
Who?
Me.
I'm coming.
What do you mean?
You came on horseback?
Your costume today is
really something.
Let me help you.
Thank you!
You're cooking tonight?
Yes. You didn't expect that, right?
Yes.
I didn't expect it.
I'm going to cook.
Smells good?
Isn't it a bit too much?
Water?
Yes.
Wait for it to stew a bit longer,
and it will be ready.
Try one first.
[They and the dressing up]
[Dressed up Yangyang, village hunk]
So handsome!
This is what real handsomeness is.
Beautiful!
Yangyang.
Why is everyone dressed up today?
Nao, we...
No, you're okay, I...
You are dressed up.
A bit.
Then should I
go change clothes, too?
Wait for me. I'll go change.
Each of you
has a set of this, right?
Yes.
The most precious thing for boys is this.
Just this.
Red.
This one is handsome.
Do you want to change your clothes?
I must change, right?
Is there that kind of jacket?
The kind you can wear immediately.
Okay, she'll go find it.
Okay, thank you.
So handsome!
What does it mean?
Handsome. That's all it means.
Thank you!
So handsome.
Too handsome, really.
I'll lend you the hat.
I need to get something. Wait a moment.
Nao,
you are very handsome!
Everything looks good on you.
Thank you!
Gali.
Gali, I really admire you.
Hey! Looking good!
Put this on.
Wait a moment.
So beautiful!
Very good!
Looks great.
[All dressed up to commemorate]
What do you mean?
So dressed up.
So handsome!
You are very handsome!
Everything looks good on you.
Thank you!
Very good!
Looks great!
[This "different" reunion]
[Be Myself will come back soon]
[Be Myself continues now]
[The ad is aired at this period of time]
I uncovered it.
Sure, no problem.
Okay.
There are also pancakes.
Yes.
This is pretty awesome.
Okay.
Let's eat, friends.
We'll start eating.
Okay.
Let's eat.
These glass noodles are so delicious!
Have you eaten glass noodles?
Rosy's dishes are so delicious.
I want to eat more.
Tudou, you're flattering me.
Bring a little more.
This is the third bowl I am having.
It's much tastier than what I made.
I have to learn a lot.
I still have a long way to go.
[Being with friends and family
fills both mood and appetite completely]
Perfect!
Alright. We're full. Let's clean up.
[So full]
Tomorrow, Rosy and others leave at five.
Five o'clock.
They are leaving.
Will you miss me after I'm gone?
- Yes.
- I will.
- Really?
- Even go after you.
Have you all prepared your gifts?
Yes, all set.
Take them out later.
Let's give it together.
[Their separation]
Welcome back.
Nao,
this is the gift I prepared for you.
This is a hat our family has kept for 7 years.
I want to give it to you.
I hope this hat can bring you
protection from the wind and rain.
[May it shield you from wind and rain]
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Then, put it on.
Put it on.
Handsome.
Very handsome.
I find you really handsome like this.
Really handsome.
Pretty cool.
I'm about to cry.
This is our family's wild honey.
It's very good for health.
It's for the new friend from afar.
[May your life be sweet and healthy]
[Emotions of parting surge in the boy's heart]
There is a letter. Do you want to read it?
Here, take it.
Is this the life philosophy you wrote yesterday?
No, it's not.
What character is this?
Let me read it.
Dear friend Fu Bohan,
hello.
[A letter to Nao from Tudou]
Hello?
Your name is Nao, right?
You are probably 13 or 14 this year, right?
Your favorite hobby is playing football.
You love eating noodles.
These past few days, from your behaviors,
I found that you are a smart and lively
hardworking boy who loves to smile.
I hope you can
remember me, silly Tudou.
I also like you very much.
Since you came here this week,
I have always treated you like
a younger brother.
Not like an outsider.
You are also the first
buddy who would laugh with me.
I am especially
reluctant to let you go.
But didn't you say
this separation
is for a better meeting next time?
So, I am especially looking forward
to our next meeting.
Let me read it for myself.
I can't listen anymore, I...
The most expensive things
are not necessarily the most precious.
And the items that are looked down upon
are actually the most real ones.
Tudou.
[Our encounter is the most precious]
Alright, I will go get it.
Last night,
I wrote until three in the morning.
Tudou, Gali, and Yongji.
These three are written together.
Delicious potato (Tudou) mixed with curry (Gali).
Tudou and Gali.
Tudou, you are the first one I met.
On the bus,
Rosy
showed me your picture.
At that time, I was very curious about you,
but also afraid of not being able to fit in.
[To Tudou, you are the first one I met]
[I was very curious about you
when I first saw your picture]
[and afraid of not fitting in.
From Nao]
He really looks like a top student.
Right?
What's your name?
You can call me Nao.
As in "noisy".
I think you are very brave and determined.
Especially that early morning,
when you turned off the kettle,
it touched me deeply.
I was really scared.
And at that time,
he was so brave.
After the circuit breaker tripped,
he quickly took out the charger
and unplugged it.
You always bring us
unexpected humor and joy.
Which photographer would take photos like this?
Gali.
Both of his eyes are closed.
No.
He takes photos like this.
Gali, you are the cutest and the most nave one.
I always feel reluctant at farewell moments,
especially with close friends like you.
Once look at each other, we burst into laughter.
You understand what I mean.
I laughed to tears.
You are the most obedient.
The hateful look in the short drama
left a deep impression on me.
You always tidy up after meals
and pour the warmest water for us.
It makes me feel very warm.
Let's go in and sit down. Sit down.
Sit.
Okay. Thank you!
Are you all right?
It's nothing.
You go ahead and talk.
Is everything okay?
It's nothing.
Just feeling dizzy.
I'm reluctant and especially afraid
of saying goodbye.
I can't help but cry.
So, I secretly tell myself,
we will definitely meet again.
I'm already imagining the next meeting.
It's okay.
Don't cry.
We will meet again.
[We will meet again]
How could we not meet again?
Yes.
Weren't you talking about that?
What is a final farewell?
The next one.
That will be in the next life.
Bro.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
It's funny.
It's funny, but also amusing.
Last time, our family didn't take a family photo.
Today, we should take one.
Yes, let's go.
Grandpa. Bring Grandpa to the middle.
Ready, go!
Potato, potato, eggplant!
[Be Myself will come back soon]
[Be Myself continues now]
[The ad is aired at this period of time]
They felt happy
because of our arrival.
We felt healed because we came
to their hometown.
It was a very good farewell.
Thank you.
Best of luck with work. Travel safely.
My name is Rosy.
[We bonded over "Be Myself"]
You are Rosy Zhao.
Beautiful!
Perfect!
So cute!
One, two, three.
Tornado.
Grandpa, go now.
I was not saying hi.
I was really scared.
I'm so scared.
Hello, Grandpa!
[Sincerely being together
in the vast mountains and wilderness]
Hello!
Come closer.
I seem to be
getting the rhythm.
[We planted some beliefs together]
Okay, smile.
I really want to laugh.
Are you happy, Grandma?
I'm happy!
Tashi Delek!
[*Good luck and auspiciousness]
[Believe that mountains and ravines
will be equally illuminated by the sun]
The mountains are very high.
Then your vision,
the air you feel,
and the blue sky you see
will be different from before.
It's snowing.
[Believe that to open another heart,
you only need to knock at the door]
I've never seen such heavy snow.
So you will feel
[Gentleness covers firmness,
love and faith are always at reach]
more open.
I feel
myself even smaller,
caring less about
some of my own emotions
and things to do.
So...
I really like this place.
[Lights will guide you home]
[And ignite your bones]
Four,
three,
two,
[We will try to comfort you]
one.
[Be Myself - The nostalgia of leaving]
[End of the first stop of the journey
"Be Myself" to be continued]
Think of something you really want to come true.
Did you see it?
Looks good.
"Be Myself".
This program
was based on the idea
of going into the mountains for charity.
Because only by really going into the mountains
can you know
what they really need
and what we can actually do
for them.
This is
why after coming to their side
and getting closer to them,
we decide to do charity.
Look at me.
I think the most meaningful moment was
leaving on the last night.
Because, that day I had a long chat with
Tudou, Yongji and Gali.
I really listened
to the voice inside.
Then, we
are making a (public welfare) study tour plan.
I just want to let these kids
be able to go through
a small trip.
Then go sow their dreams.
They can see a bigger world.
Something for their future.
[Expanding horizons and sowing dreams]
Seeing more hope.
It will continue until
they reach 18 years old
and they
get into their desired university.
Like Tudou.
The day he truly becomes a soldier.
Maybe to me,
those will be a response to me.
That requires time.
Where to go for the second stop?
Take a break.
[*Sounds like Xiuxi in Chinese]
Xiuxi Village.
[Next stop, Xiuxi Village in Sichuan]
[Xiuxi Village, see you there!]
[Be Myself will come back soon]
[Be Myself continues now]
[Preview: "Be Myself": New Journey, New Friends]
Hello everyone, I am Ma Boqian.
My name is Ma Qirui.
I heard him say that you are online friends.
Yes, this would be
the first time we meet.
Hello!
I think the younger sister is quite cute.
If you say so,
I can suddenly feel
Ma Boqian's feelings now.
I laughed so hard.
This makes the top of my head appear very high.
Do you want to learn Qiang dialect?
How to say "horse"?
"Ru".
What about "old horse"?
She thinks I'm not normal.
She also thinks I'm noisy.
I look at you like this all day long.
It's really snowing outside.
The snow is so heavy.
So beautiful!
Look!
Look here and smile.
Three, two, one, go.
["Be Myself" Performed by Duan Aojuan]
Through the tiny dust
See the light pouring down
Footprints of dozens of centimeters
Can depict mountains and seas
Lift the fallen body with both hands
Learn to start running
To chase the distant future
With the posture of shining meteors
From the small window sill
Imagine beyond the blue sky
The flower to bloom we've been waiting for
ten thousand times
And time will record
Every stay and departure
Little you
Little me
Exist with little courage
Big dreams
Big world
Can be carried by a heart
No matter the confusion,
still seek a ray of light
No matter the despair,
still use the last ounce of strength
Be Myself
Because we look for
The small yet immense love