Coffee, Do Me a Favor
♫ With a pretty hairdo and eye-catching lipstick ♫
♫ I wear clothes that I saved for a special day to go out ♫
Episode 7
Prosecutor, please question the accused.
Why did you follow the victim all the way to her blind date and disturb their date?
Tha... that...
- That was because of the deadline.
- According to our investigation,
there was a meeting but there was no deadline.
I'll submit the related material as evidence.
Prosecutor, continue with your questioning.
At 9:30 pm,
at Miso park, why did you grab the victim's waist?
At that time, Go Woon was about to fall so I instinctively...
Go Woon, please tell the truth.
Your honor, the defendant is currently intimidating the victim.
I'm not intimidating her.
Denfense Counsel's Bench
I agree.
I'll ask my last question.
On the day of the incident, at 11:45 pm,
in front of a building in Itaewon
you approached the victim under the pretext of popcorn in the victim's hair.
Do you acknowledge that you kissed the victim?
That wasn't... I didn't forcefully do it.
Go Woon.
Your honor, the accused is still not showing one iota of remorse.
Therefore, prosecutor will
sentence twenty years of prison time to the defendant.
Twenty years!
This court sentences, the accused, Im Hyeon Woo,
to twenty years.
No. No. No!
Writer Im.
My hair is a bit strange, right?
- You're here.
- Sir, did you have a good weekend?
It was alright. Were you guys together during the weekend too?
Writer Im, what did you do this weekend?
My man's recipe
From episode 11,
should we have Jeong Won actively approach Go Woon?
Good. The rival has to live so that the love line can survive.
Let's make Jeong Won's role bigger between Go Woon and Joon Woo.
Oh Go Woon, you're doing well as expected.
Thank you.
When Joon Woo and Go Woon haven't yet developed a relationship,
does it make sense to grow second male lead character?
No.
Then from episode 12, instead of the theater, how about Joon Woo and Go Woon
meet somewhere else coincidentally and have them go on a date?
Good. Good.
At the end of episode 12, they got to get close enough to touch each other.
Having them get together again sounds good.
Oh Go Woon, you have a way to make people's hearts flutter.
Noona, why is Vice Team Leader acting this way?
I don't know either.
You need to write a love story which sounds like inevitable destiny.
There shouldn't be too many coincidences.
Continued coincidences become fate.
I firmly agree with Oh Go Woon's idea.
Fearsome.
Don't be swayed by popularity, and try to
focus a little more.
Yes.
Why did you do that to me yesterday?
I don't think you can leave like that.
Yes?
It is snowing from the sky?
It's a delicious snow.
♫ Like the white snowflakes that have fallen on a dark night ♫
♫ Your smile melts into my heart  ♫
♫ all day ♫
♫ At times we might ♫
♫ have difficult days ♫
♫ Our everlasting moments, and shared feelings ♫
♫ I promise you, they won't change ♫
Well,
she arrives suddenly and asks to be an assistant.
And then she disappears.
Then she returns and says she'll work really hard.
What is this really?
♫ The path we are walking on now is brightening new days ♫
♫ You are,  ♫
♫ you are ♫
♫ from the heavens ♫
Seriously, I never thought because of someone
that I would I keep thinking,
and keep floundering.
Seriously, because of someone...
Be like this...
Ah...
Hold on.
Everyone in this world knows my password.
You know too.
Dating doesn't become me, right?
As I expected.
If I offended you yesterday, I apologize. Because of the mood there, I made a big mistake.
Until I'm in my grave, I'll never ever make such a mistake again.
Oh Go Woon, I'm sorry.
Whoa. Unexpeted.
Yes. I completely understand what you're saying, Writer Im.
However, I'll help you with your drawings.
I don't need you to.
A mistake is a mistake and a promise is a promise.
I'm a person that always keeps my word.
I'll be helping in the spirit of humanitarianism.
Ah, humanitarianism.
Yes. If you really want to, then give me a proper drawing lesson.
Subtitles brought to you by the Coffee Please team @viki.com
Heartbeat: 139
Caffeine: 2%
Oh my...
Aish!
Do you know who I met when I went to the jimjilbang (Korean spa)?
He was my ideal type.
From the right, he looks like Jeong Hae In. And from the left, he looks like Park Seo Joon.
Hey! Focus on me. However, were you...
Were you with that beard man the whole entire time?
Why do you keep touching your lips?
No way! You kissed him at your first meeting?
You took a wrong guess!
What?! What did I get wrong?
Then, who was it?
Honestly... No, forget it.
However, so it was...
Never mind. Howeverㅡ
Wake up!
Geez, you've gone completely crazy over one kiss.
Hey. Why does this story only have a beginning, but no end?
You have to tell me the details. All of the details.
It was really good.
What's the point of knowing?
I thought my heart stopped.
Still, girl, you should have ended neatly.
Then, what should I have done?
If I would have remained, my regular appearance would have popped out.
Alright. Alright. You've done well.
I thought you would be living like a nun forever.
Then, is this the first day of dating with Writer Im?
Isn't that how people do?
Take a dump why don't you.
This is all because I've gotten prettier.
From now on, I must hang out with Writer Im as Oh Go Woon.
Thank you.
- Oh, this.
- The chocolate is on the house.
Oh, dear! Last night you with Writer Im...
Can't you pretend to not know about stuff like that?
If I know about it, why would I pretend not to?
Then, you should try being a god instead.
Since I can't control the coffee the way I want to,
it's starting to become harder and harder.
Working during the night will increase soon too.
That's why, in order to not get caught, you have to do better by being more careful.
Well, not everything in this world goes the way I want it to.
Please give me a heart latte.
Is it because today's the first day of you dating?
You're planning to appeal to him with a pure and lovable style.
Oh, seriously.
Oh? What is this? Why didn't I change?
Oh?! Ah..it's because my heartbeat is too high.
I need it to drop to 110 though.
I am calm.
I am calm. I am caㅡ
♫ After staying up late ♫
♫ looking at the dews on grass ♫
Hello, Vice Team Leader.
My hair is a bit unsightly, right?
I am sorry for my untidy appearance.
No. No. It looks moisturized so you look lovely.
What's this? She is scarier by behaving this way.
Oh Go Woon's soul food is?
Perhaps, soondae stew (blood sausage noodle stew)?
Oh, soondae stew... is good.
Then what about a musical you most adore?
Per chance, is it Phantom of the Opera?
Opera? It's a good play.
Ah, pa pa pa pa pa pa bam bam.
Then, your ideal type is?
Oh my god! You like a man who sings well and is warmhearted, right?
A warmhearted man has appeal.
However, why do you ask?
Writer Im, end the meeting within one hour. I have an appointment.
Let me make you some coffee, Writer Im.
That's why Writer Im was consistently quarrelsome from the morning.
I was so clueless that from the morning I was talking nonsense about our first day and whatnot.
I was beating the drum and celebrating (counting my chickens before they hatch).
Oh, Dong Goo. What's up?
Why can't I get in touch with you?
Did you forget about us already?
No way. I have been busy.
However, why does your voice sound similar to Go Woon's?
It may sound like it because of your mood.
Or you have some hearing problems.
When are you going to meet up with us? Writer Im is different from us.
Then, should we hang out at night?
I am not available in the early evening.
If you're okay with us meeting up at night.
I'm missing you.
How can I look at Writer Im's face?
I picked it according to your style.
Hurry up and put it on. Quickly.
You really like this, right?
I'm thankful, but what use is there for a tie?
No, there is no rule when to wear a tie.
You can just do it.
Okay. Let me do it for you.
I'll do it later.
You should see Jeong Won for a moment before you leave.
You need to work really hard. Okay?!
About your unpaid wages,
I spoke favorably to the president.
The economy is bad. It's not one or two factories that have shut down.
Still, there's no place like this place, right?
What audition are you planning on applying for with that?
I am playing a role for a factory manager who is taking good care of laborers from overseas, even though he has a temper sometimes.
Seriously. What can we do with you?
Hey. If you're that worried about me, you can just take responsibility for me.
Even yesterday, after she left, he was so concerned for her.
Oh. I heard that Oh Go Woon drew that for him.
I don't like the pen touch on the drawing.
Hyeon Woo, let's help Jeong Won and Oh Go Woon to get together.
Why should we help them get together?
I asked Oh Go Woon earlier and her taste completely fits Jeong Won.
She likes soondae stew and even Phantom of the Opera.
- On top of that, her ideal type is—
- I thought you said you have an appointment?
Your acting completely sucks.
To begin with, act naturally and eat first.
That's right, you should eat soondae stew.
I don't have feelings for Oh Go Woon.
Aigoo, are you embarrassed?
I'm not an elementaryschool student, okay?
Then are you a middle school student?
As long as this noona is involved, it'll take exactly two weeks for you to start dating Oh Go Woon.
Hey, why are you so into making us date?
Because I should be the only woman beside Im Hyeon Woo.
Hey Sticky, I found this for you.
You must have found it while thinking of me.
- Yeonnam-dong Seol Hyeon, have you eaten today?
- Yes. Mopo-gu Jeong Hae In, please don't skip a meal. Eat well.
- Man: I had a glass of milk.
- Woman: I wish I could drink it with you.
This is the first time being able to communicate with a girl so well.
I will ask her out after finishing this series.
How could I survive without Seol Hyeon?
I was suffering from a nightmare last night after three years.
That woman from the spa was stepping on my arm so hard in my dream.
Aigoo. She is really strange.
She wasn't strange.
Aigoo. Take a look at your dark circles.
You should have run away when you saw Writer, but you hung out with him.
So why was Writer Im there drinking alone?
No comment.
What a man. A man.
This is the record of our meeting.
Subtitles brought to you by the Coffee Please team @viki.com
Writer Im! We're going to head home now.
We just sent via email what we worked on.
You guys worked hard. I'll check it later.
Hyeon Woo! I'm going to go to my part-time job!
If you do it like this, is it easier to work?
Later, I'm going to also look over Dong Goo and Jeong Sook's drawings personally.
- Let's keep it a secret for now.
- Yes.
Try drawing this.
What's with that bandage?
Ah... This is like a promise I made to myself
that I won't let go of the pen until I'm satisfied with my drawings.
It's kind of like that.
That's amazing.
Seul Bi also had a bandage like that.
They say best friends have similar moods and habits.
Go Woon, instead of short touches, draw it over.
Not like that, but inside the line, round it out, til the end.
Let's stop it here for today.
Complete what you are drawing and show it to me tomorrow.
Dream's come true.
No, if you're going to be that awkward,
why did you offer to give me a lesson?
I don't understand that.
Even though I was drawing with ease, as soon as he watched me from behind,
I kept making mistakes.
Who are you talking about right now?
Who was I talking to? I was about to call a waitress.
Auntie, please give us one serving each for savory flavor and marinated flavor.
Auntie, instead, give us two more servings each.
I am so low in energy recently.
I need to eat whenever I am low in energy.
I agree.
Writer Im scolds me no matter I do.
I think I don't have talent for this.
I want to cry.
Here. Eat this eel ssam (veggie wrap) I made and cheer up.
Say, ah.
Hello.
Oh my.
Oh, flower boy.
Yesterday, why did you do that to me?
That thing on her hair, is it a butterfly or a moth?
Moth.
Honestly,
when Seul Bi said she would set me up with a blind date,
I said I didn't want to.
Because I don't like such a meeting set up by others.
Because she insisted, I agreed.
My destiny, please eat plenty.
Noona, did I do something to make you upset?
There's nothing like that.
Then why are you punishing me?
Oh my, Dong Goo.
Why haven't you emptied your glass?
Perhaps,
you want me to be your black rose (a woman who drinks for a man)?
Then, you have to grant me a wish.
Hey, I'll drink it.
If I drink all of this, from today, we're speaking informally to each other.
Oh, it's very sweet.
Me too, be my black rose.
Dong Gu, us meeting like this is fate. How about a love shot?
What do you mean love shot?
There's something urgent at home suddenly.
Let's go for the love shot.
- Love shot
- Hey, I'll give you a lot of love shot at home.
Sit down.
Why are you doing this to me?
Ah Reum, you're really drunk, let's—
- Noona, are you alright?
- Noonim.
I think I have to go home now.
Let's go the emergency room with me.
Our Dong Goo, you said you were low in energy.
Don't go anywhere and eat a lot of eel. Okay?
Ok, Seul Bi. You go home first. See you later.
Dong Goo, let's have another shot.
Dong Goo, how old are you?
I twisted my foot a little bit.
Trouble when I see him, trouble when I do see him.
Seul Bi.
Are you still being rejected?
As usual, as you know.
How about drawing? Are you still drawing?
I'm drawing, but...
It's just so so.
I guess it's not a question that I should ask.
I'll be going. Be well.
Writer Im.
Is Go Woon working out?
Ask her yourself.
I am not the type of a person to rot in this setting.
That's mis—
Perfect night snack is pig's feet.
If it's pigs feet, then lettuce wrap.
Then, pig's feet and lettuce wrap set.
If you're going to eat, order food only for one person.
There is no single serving for that. They only sell with small (2 serving), medium (3 serving) and large (4 serving) sizes.
Hyeon Woo, you're still taking meds?
Hey, don't you know stress causes all the sicknesses?
Don't take this, and follow me
and breathe like this.
That's right. One more time.
Moon Jeong Won, you're my stress.
Get out.
Hey, wait. I'm just showing you how to breathe.
Just one serving, let me eat it. I'll eat it quietly.
Do you think this is a restaurant?
You're working so late into the night.
Eating together like this is more enjoyable.
Lettuce wrap 580 plus pig's feet 460,
together it exceeds 1000 calories. Do you think I'm going to eat this?
Are you able to work eating this grass every day?
I also know how to dig into pig's feet.
Do you think I don't want it?
Then, eat it. What's the big deal with eating it once?
If I eat it once, I want to keep eating it.
And if I gain weight, I'm the one who'll suffer.
It's okay, you can gain some weight.
I liked it back when I could eat to my heart's content.
Do you remember during high school? The Kkabaegki (knot-shaped donut) House in front of the school.
You, me and Hyeon Woo went there every day.
There weren't that many ingredients for it, just flour, sugar and oil, that's all.
But it was delicious for some odd reason.
Now that we're talking about it, I really want to eat some.
Ye Na, I brought this instead of kkabaegki.
What is it?
My heart.
Bang!
Bang! Bang!
Ye Na, accept my heart.
Bang! Bang! Bang!
Why did you do that to me yesterday?
Please enough. Please.
I told you I'll be fine once I take medicine. I don't why you insist I come here.
- It's a gastric ulcer.
- Gastric ulcer?
- I knew it.
- If if becomes severe, you'll need to be admitted for treatment.
You need to watch out. Do you have severe gastrospasms?
Yes, he lives sucking on meds.
My condition got better, but...
Recently, is there something that's bothering you?
Like you're under severe stress?
Geez, what did I tell you?
What would have happened if you hadn't come today?
You must be happy
because you have a best friend like me.
You're way too excited.
How can I be excited when you're sick.
Let's go.
Get examined and then just get plenty of rest today. Don't think of anything else.
By the way, don't tell the assistants about me being sick.
I'll tell them I'm going to an interview, so you keep your mouth shut and forget about it.
You got it?
You know that I have tight lips.
Hurry up and go. You need to be examined.
Don't even tell Ye Na
since I have some reserve scripts (to send her).
Aigo, I won't say anything.
I'm Moon Jeong Won.
Is Writer Im at the workshop?
I can't get hold of him by phone.
Oh, he went to an interview today.
Interview?
Ah, I understand. Goodbye.
There was no mention of an interview, though.
It doesn't seem like Vice Team Leader is aware either.
I don't know.
Hey guys!
Hyeon Woo has a gastric ulcer.
What?
Moon Jeong Won, enough already!
I told you, you are my stress.
- You haven't eaten dinner yet, right?
- Yes.
Ah, no. Whether I eat dinner or not—
Then eat first.
- Excuse me.
- I will put these on the table.
- Side dishes can go into the refrigerator—
- What are you doing right now?
Writer Im has a gastric ulcer.
How can I not care about it?
Hyeon Woo has gastric ulcer.
Jeong Won.
You don't have a fever.
Why would I have a fever when it's a gastric ulcer?
All I have to do is rest a little bit, so you should leave.
It's not like you're uncomfortable with me, right?
I'm here to extend humanitarian aid
on behalf of all the assistants.
- It's alright.
- Don't feel uncomfortable with me.
You should just go in and rest.
Just the way you are right now.
That darn humanitarianism.
I made the mistake of saying the wrong thing and...
If you eat these, your stomach will get worse.
If I don't eat these, then my temper gets worse.
Seriously.
When your stomach is not well, you need to eat warm food.
Today, eat egg custard and porridge only.
I'll make it quickly, so wait a little bit.
You don't need to do this. I can handle it myself.
It's humanitarian aid, I told you.
I don't need that kind of aid.
Really!
That Jeong Won.
Oh geez.
- Hide.
- What?
Quickly. Quickly hide. You're good at hiding, right?
Why, all of sudden...
Oh, my.
Oh, it's hot.
It's heavy.
Oh, my legs.
We heard you're sick, so we came in a hurry.
We just managed to stop Mom and Dad from coming here from Australia.
Remember me.
Aish, Moon Jeong Won.
Who will take care of our brother?
How will you take care of me with a microphone?
Here, this is made of the special garlic from Yiseong.
It's the best thing for men.
This place exudes the lack of a woman's touch.
There's no hint of that.
What is this?
Ah... that. I was planning to make egg custard with that.
- You're...
- going to make...
- egg custard?
Yes...That is...
Oppa, you have a woman here!
Gee, a woman. Nonsense.
Omo, omo.
No...I said I don't.
Not here.
You!
Well, since we're all together,
why don't we go to the street restaurant? My treat.
Don't try to pull some trick.
Hey, hey.
There really is no one here.
That's right. Who would be here?
Nice to meet you.
So the two of you are...
Two of us are what?
It's nothing like that.
No, it's not like that.
So exactly what is "nothing"?
Go Woon is my assistant. Assistant.
I'm an assistant. Assistant.
Your assistant even makes you an egg custard. Oppa, you must be happy.
Oh, that is under the context of humanitarianism.
Of course, under the context of humanitarianism.
It really isn't that. Even if I'm in my grave, it's not.
Even if I'm reborn, it'll never ever be like that with Go Woon.
Geez, why to that extent...
Is that so?
How's this woman? With her dog, doesn't she look pure and innocent?
She is a teacher in Mock-dong.
- So what?
- You have to get married.
A man becomes a real adult when he has a family.
He has to date first.
When I see the male characters in your webtoon, it shows that you haven't dated.
I like a serious man.
Oh boy. What do you guys know about men?
You guys haven't been married.
Oh, so is that why you're arguing with your man every two days?
Why are you bringing that up here?
You don't have a girlfriend because you're relieving your stress with this.
I guess I don't have to inconvenience you guys anymore.
Starting from today, I'm going to live here.
Remember me.
Yes, please speak.
Yes.
She is too pretty for him.
Her eyebrows are too much of a mismatch.
That's why Writer Im keeps his distance from women.
Hello?
Come to the room right now.
Why are you calling me to—
Hurry. Hurry.
Let's date.
Just for a short period, let's say we're dating.
Ah. So,
Because of your older and younger sisters,
let's date momentarily.
Just until recently, the person who said he can never be with me...
Will you be alright?
I was too harsh before. I was out of mind back then.
I mean, you said you came here in the context of humanitarianism.
Just once, please?
Please? Just once.
- Alright.
- Really?
In exchange...
In exchange?
From here on,
let me work from home whenever we need to work overnight.
Until we're done with the scripts, it's easier when we're together in the office.
Whenever you want, send it over via "talk."
I'll answer in a heartbeat.
All right. Let's go out now.
- One more.
- What else?
Compliment Dong Goo and Jeon Sook.
The guys look really tired lately,
extending their efforts working. That's why.
But if you give them one word of compliment,
think about how much strength it'll give them.
The thing called compliment is not always a good thing.
It's the responsibility of the main writer to point out what mistakes they are making.
One-a-day. One compliment a day.
The compliment has to come out naturally.
I understand.
If you're saying you just can't, then, oh well.
Then I guess it's all null and void.
Let's do it.
Alright then.
We're dating.
We're dating. We are.
What?!
Did you fall for him at first sight?
This is so immature.
Yes.
Lie Detector
Alright.
This time it's Hyeon Woo's turn.
Now, now.
Hold on.
Did you two...
Do it...kiss?
No.
You did. You did.
Writer Im, is your hand alright?
I have to get going.
Oh, it's so late.
Why?
We still have ninety questions left.
Yeah, we have a lot to go.
Remember me.
Oh, please!
Let's go.
I'll escort you home since it's late and all.
It's okay. I was advised a taxi is at the gate.
Alright then.
Why aren't you going?
Well, you have to let go of my hand.
Her specialty is taking off.
This drives me crazy.
Go Woon, thank you for today.
Customer.
Yes.
Customer, we've arrived.
Customer. AH!
One martini over here.
Hold on.
Jeong Won, at this rate, you will be the master of the martini.
What the hell is that?
- Seriously, that guy!
- Oh no, Jeong Won.
Hold on a minute.
Jeong Won. Jeong Won.
You. What are you doing?
How dare you do such a thing to her!
Honey, you know this person?
I don't know him. I was doing that while looking at you, but
this guy just...
I'm sorry. Please enjoy.
Oh man, what did you do?
Do you know "Young Miss and the Gangsters"? I was just practicing it.
The sense of realism is important to an actor, you see.
Can you not do a musical?
I'm going to play with Im Hyeon Woo instead of you.
Wait. Wait. Hyeon Woo is busy today so he can't come.
Why is he so busy today?
But where is my martini?
Hold on.
I came home safely.
Please make sure you're the only one to eat the octopus porridge.
Octopus porridge?
At least you have a conscience. I see that you cleaned up before you left.
You know that we're very conscientious. How are you feeling?
I feel much better after sleeping.
I'm going to buy something good to eat for my assistant. She overextended herself.
Go Woon yesterday, she is a really good person.
She is cheerful and amiable. You're unworthy of her.
Okay. Stop there already.
Tea
Subtitles brought to you by the Coffee Please team @viki.com
♫  I'm dating lately  ♫
Coffee, Do Me a Favor
♫  I feel like I'm born again  ♫
♫  So pretty I can die. So cute I can die.  ♫
[Epilogue]
That, that, that one.
Give me the biggest one, please.
Are you going to cook a stew with it?
I'm going to make porridge with it.
My family's specialty is octopus porridge you see.
With my mom's octopus porridge, every sickness got cured at once.
Wow, what a filial daughter.
Thank you.
♫  It doesn't work out the way I planned  ♫
♫  I didn't quite think about it this way  ♫
♫  But I don't exactly hate it  ♫
♫ Hey, losers, I think it differently now ♫
♫  Hey losers. You wouldn't know even if I told you  ♫
♫  I really like it. I really do like it  ♫
♫  I don't how to explain it  ♫
♫  Hey losers. You see, the thing called life  ♫
♫  Seems livable  ♫
♫  It's because I like having you  ♫
Coffee, Do Me a Favor