Mano Kosei, the man frequently meeting Asaoka Yumi,
is a leader of the Otsuka group.
The Otsuka group?
He is a Yakuza?
They're rumored to be colluding with the entertainment industry.
So this doesn't seem to be just another love affair.
Asaoka Yumi became the Commercial Queen, three years ago.
Mano and Asaoka were seen together then, too.
A second-rate celebrity, Asaoka Yumi,
suddenly climbed to the top as the Commercial Queen.
And the yakuza was behind her success.
I see.
Your first scoop together sure is a big one.
- You two got what it takes.
- The Otsuka group...
I'm Onoe Satoshi, a journalist for the Weekly Dash.
- Asaoka's commercials...
- He's Kaburagi Motoharu, a photographer.
He's my partner, I guess.
Our first job as a team
was to investigate an affair involving Asaoka Yumi, the Commercial Queen
who's loved by all for being approachable.
Or so I thought.
However...
I might know this guy.
Who is he?
[Otsuka group management, Mano Kosei, leader's right-hand man]
Mano Kosei from the Otsuka group.
We suddenly found out the relationship between Asaoka and the Otsuka group,
which is why we are being praised in this meeting right now.
But I got really interested in my partner, Kaburagi.
For the article, we need to prove
that the Otsuka group is getting commercials for Asaoka.
And I'd like a single photo
that clearly shows their relationship.
- Okay.
- Got it.
Get on it, then.
♫ Good Morning, this is the twelfth alarm ♫
♫ A predicament is certainly a chance ♫
♫ I realized it, thank you, thank you ♫
♫ If you realized it, go sign, oh yeah ♫
♫ Loose but greedy, oh yeah ♫
♫ Hey, come here, my friends, my bae ♫
♫ I really won't let you get bored,
If you realized it, go sign, oh yeah ♫
♫ Loose but greedy, oh yeah ♫
♫ Being alone isn't for me ♫
[Candy Color Paradox]
[Shot 2]
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hey, who are we meeting in a place like this?
An informant.
An informant?
Hello.
Hi there.
You've never brought someone with you before, Kabu.
I'm Onoe.
I just moved teams and was paired up with Kaburagi-kun.
Is that so?
I'm Kaori. Nice to meet you.
Oh, take a seat.
Okay.
I've been keeping Kabu company since he was in college.
- Keeping company?
- Please don't give him the wrong idea.
I worked at this club.
Kaori-san is the owner here.
As you can tell, Kabu is handsome, and he knows how to be thoughtful.
The guests and our staff loved him.
Don't bring up the past.
Why not?
I'll tell you some heroic stories later on.
Yes, that'd be great.
Come on, Kaori-san.
I wanted Kabu to stay with us together.
But that sly old man stole you away, unfortunately.
Sly old man?
Your editor-in-chief.
But I still get to see Kabu, so I'm over it.
Now then, down to business.
Asaoka Yumi has been frequenting this place.
An outdoor cafe?
Yeah.
It has private rooms. Perfect for private chit-chat.
Let's take a look. Thank you.
One more thing.
That cafe...
is secretly being run by the Otsuka group.
We have to get that shot.
That's my job.
So... where's my payment?
It will be in cash.
I'll add some extra in as a thank you.
Thanks.
Please excuse us.
What're you doing? Get in.
I'll watch for Mano to come out at the Otsuka group's house.
You want to go to the yakuza alone?
It's fine. It's not that dangerous.
But you won't be able to run away. You're slow.
I researched that area in the current affairs department.
I know where to hide.
Yeah, but...
Just go to the outdoor cafe.
If you get there late, it's not my fault.
Fine.
I'll let you know if I see anything.
See you.
Hello? Mom?
It's me. Yumi.
No, it's not.
You don't recognize my voice?
It's me, your daughter.
Hey...
Yeah, it's me, Yumi.
What? School?
School's fun.
I made friends, too.
Are you having fun, too?
I'm glad.
Yes.
She thought Yumi was a child.
Asaoka Yumi's mother has dementia, huh?
[Matsubara Association | Otsuka Group]
I'll get that photo.
I need results.
Yeah, I just finished.
It's Mano.
I have to call Kaburagi.
[Onoe Satoshi]
Hello?
He's on the move!
Hey. Onoe.
- Hey, you. What is it?
- What?
Come with me.
What happened?
Damn it!
This is Onoe's...
Damn.
Are you kidding me?
[Matsubara Association | Otsuka Group]
I'm telling you, I'm not suspicious.
Yeah, you say that,
but why were you loitering around there?
I was on a stakeout.
I'm a journalist from Shinkansha.
Do you have a business card?
Well...
No, I just moved departments.
Can you come with me to the station?
Asking for confirmation.
I'm sorry. We're from the same company.
I'm Kaburagi, from Shinkansha's Weekly Dash.
Kaburagi-san from Weekly Dash?
So he's with you?
- We're co-workers.
- Yes, I'm Onoe.
Thanks for helping me.
He wouldn't believe I was a journalist at all.
Huh? That's mine.
Why do you have it?
What are you doing?
Someone reported me, and the police took me away.
I understand that, but why didn't you call me?
I mean, I didn't have my phone.
You could've found another way.
You can use a public phone or borrow the policeman's phone.
Do you even know what you're doing here?
You're doing a yakuza stakeout.
You thought the yakuza caught me?
I didn't know. That's why I looked for you.
You called and didn't even say anything.
You looked for me?
Is that why you found this for me?
I almost went to Tokyo Bay.
You thought they threw me into the Tokyo Bay?
That's over the top.
Sorry.
I won't forgive you if I lose my story over this.
Oh, right! They're meeting right now.
What?
Probably at that cafe.
Why're you even here?
Whose fault is this? Don't make me punch you.
I see.
You'd abandon a stakeout just to look for me?
I might have misjudged you.
I wasn't expecting you to be so kind.
That scared me.
I don't want to go home yet.
- Come on and go home.
- I don't want to.
- Hey!
- You've been drinking.
- You're already swaying.
- Drinking is fine.
What? Hey, you...
We are in public.
Well, it can't be helped.
You got that?
That was good.
"Kissing a Yakuza member on the street."
"The dark side of Asaoka Yumi, the Commercial Queen."
"It started three years ago."
"Asaoka required funds for her mother's nursing home"
"Thus, she approached an Otsuka member involved in entertainment."
"In exchange for being his lover,
he promised her high-paying gigs."
"The Commercial Queen Asaoka Yumi was born from dark, shady practices."
Hey, this is incredible!
This photo in particular is great!
You got a great shot here!
Thank you.
What's the matter? This is a huge scoop!
You don't look excited.
I pulled an all-nighter to write it.
Wow, I knew you guys were great.
I'm glad I paired you two up.
It's the birth of a great pair.
A great pair?
I was writing frantically while that guy slept like a log next to me.
What's with that reaction?
Well, it's rare.
Kabu really trusts your writing, huh?
Yeah.
Usually, he wants to do everything himself.
And where's Kabu?
I don't know. When I said I finished, he went off on his own.
Oh, maybe he's hiding somewhere near the building.
Go look for him.
He's having a smoke break while reflecting on his work.
Reflecting?
What are you doing?
Stretching exercises.
Yeah, as if.
I was looking at the sky then.
Then look up at the sky.
Is your mother doing well?
Yeah, she is.
I wonder if it was okay to write about Asaoka's mother.
Well, some people will sympathize with her when they read it.
That's better than getting a beating from everyone.
I see.
But once that article goes out,
Asaoka Yumi will probably retire.
I guess so.
But no matter what the reason,
she's the one who did something bad.
Yeah, that's our job.
You have to believe that if you want to continue this job.
You should...
change teams soon,
before you become numb like me.
If you're numb...
Why're you making that face?
What?
You're not numb to this.
You're seriously a nice guy.
I'm sorry!
Excuse me.
[Teppan Sakaba Okubo Base]
What's wrong with me?
Why did I hug him?
Kaburagi's seduced you, too.
No, it's not like that.
He cast his work aside
and looked for me because he was worried.
He's actually pretty nice.
So you say his expression changed, and he jumped in immediately to save you?
What's this? Are you bragging?
How is that bragging?
You think about him constantly after you get home, right?
And you get excited.
My heartbeat has been weird lately, that's all.
From what I've heard, there's only one answer.
You've... fallen for Kaburagi.
I-I've fallen for Kaburagi?
You looked for me?
Is that why you found this for me?
I wasn't expecting you to be so kind.
You know how to smile?
Of course I do.
But hey, you're amazing.
You should change teams soon,
before you become numb like me.
You're not numb to this.
You're seriously a nice guy.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you
♫ I look through the viewfinder at the feelings
that crossed my mind ♫
♫ This way nothing is captured in the photo,
but disappears into the past ♫
♫ The polaroid on the wall and this faded graffiti ♫
♫ Everything is torn off, the mistakes will be reset ♫
[Preview]
Congressman Sagawa? Tax evasion?
I'll come to save you if something happens.
I don't need you to save me.
Honestly, I need to tell you something.
You don't care about me at all.
That's not okay!
Kaburagi?
Shut up.
[This story is completely fiction.]