As for our news updates,
an encounter in Iloilo resulted in the
death of several members of rebel groups.
According to a report
from the military,
there was an intense
clash between soldiers
and a rebel group
yesterday morning
that lasted for several hours.
In the said encounter
three rebels were reported dead,
while three others were
injured and captured.
Operations by the military
forces are still ongoing.
To ensure the safety of
the communities in the area.
No soldiers have been
reported wounded.
However, the authorities are
closely monitoring the situation.
The local government continues
to remind the residents
to report any suspicious
activities in the area.
We are continuing to monitor
the events that will soon unfold.
Oh...
I know this person.
Hi, love.
Are you not tired of those?
No matter what,
I'll never get tired of this.
I'm so handsome,
and so lucky too.
So... how are the children?
Well...
We were sent home early today.
There was another encounter
with the military in the city.
I was just there.
Really?
I'm glad you're safe
and back home.
People in the NPA will
never stop fighting for
what they believe in.
Government officials
will continue
their efforts to stop them.
Make sure to always
be careful, okay?
- Yes.
- I don't want to be a young widow.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll always
be careful for you.
Come, take a rest.
Take a break.
Come on.
- You're already tired.
- Grades are due tomorrow.
Give that to me.
That's enough.
Hey, love.
I've got it covered for you.
Come on. Take a rest.
I'll make sure you pass.
A violent encounter
has once again resulted
in the loss of many lives,
including those of countrymen
who are rebels and soldiers,
- Roy?
- in the secluded village
- Are you there?
- of Hacienda Conchita
in the province of Iloilo.
The deceased military personnel
and rebels are still being identified.
I'm even more scared
hearing that news.
Until Ka Roman is alive,
our lives will
not be at peace.
Change your clothes first.
I cooked your favorite water spinach.
I want to eat a different
kind of water spinach.
You're so silly.
Why? Don't you want to?
Let's eat first.
Later.
I want to eat you first.
Oh?
Are you sure you're not
going to eat breakfast?
I'll eat at the
military camp.
There was a commotion in the area.
I also woke up late.
You tired me out last night.
You tired me out too.
Love.
Aren't you going to school?
You've already been
absent for days.
I’m really feeling lazy.
Maybe I'm pregnant.
Pregnant?
Love.
Oh you! You might
just be feeling sad here.
I'll just cook you favorite dish.
That's why I'm
gaining weight.
Alright, love.
I'll go ahead, okay?
How many times
should I tell you, love?
Every time you go,
don't say 'I'll go ahead.'
We're still young,
and we still have
many dreams,
plus we'll have many kids.
Yes, alright.
I'm leaving now.
Permission to leave, ma'am!
Okay!
Bye.
Roy?
Come here!
You fell asleep there again.
You know what?
If I were Roy,
I would be upset with you.
Would he really hold
a grudge against me?
I'm already sleeping beside him.
Oh?
What happened?
It's a long story.
Our house was set on fire,
but Roy saved me.
Then,
they took our
land after that.
And since then...
Roy and I decided to
live on the mountain.
You know,
I’m intrigued by you.
Whenever we
pass by this tree,
you stop.
What’s so special
about that tree?
That particular tree...
is the witness by my side
to Ka Roman killing
my husband.
Roman?
Isn't that just his alias?
Yes.
His real name is
Mark Santa Cruz, right?
Why?
That bastard Roman
still hasn't been
caught until now.
He murdered Lito
because of his loyal
service to the town.
All my husband wanted
was a peaceful life for our town.
I honestly don't know
what the NPAs
are fighting for.
I’ve left the movement.
That's why we left the mountain
because we want
to start a new life.
We no longer know
what we are fighting for.
A never-ending battle.
To be honest,
I’m still terrified of
gunshots until now.
I don't know what
to do anymore.
Don't worry.
I'm here.
I’ll always be
here for you.
No wonder I felt so at ease
when I first saw you.
Me too.
Maybe it's because
we are both widowed.
We both have
suffered a loss.
Happy Birthday to you!
Love?
Love!
Where are you?
I'm here, love.
Come, let's eat.
I cooked your favorite.
It looks delicious.
Thank you, love.
I love you so much.
I love you.
I miss you so much, Lito.
Thank you, love.
Breaking news,
fellow countrymen.
More than fifty rebels have
surrendered voluntarily today,
- February 17, 1980.
- Emma?
To rejoin society here
in the town of San Rafael,
- province of Iloilo.
- Emma!
As promised by the government,
- Emma?
- there are programs prepared for them.
- One reason for this is that
- Emma!
life in the mountains is said
- to be getting tougher.
- Emma?
Emma.
Just a second!
It's only Saturday, right?
I thought that
we would visit
our husbands on Monday.
Yes.
But I don't have
anything to do at home
so I decided
to come here.
I also
have something
to give you.
What is it?
A dress,
I bought it in town.
Oh my!
You didn't have to.
You shouldn't
have bothered.
Come, let's go inside first.
Just a minute.
This is really beautiful.
Even though I don't
usually wear dresses,
I'll wear this.
Come on, I cooked Adobong Kangkong.
Thank you again
for the dress.
This food... This is Roy's favorite.
Try it.
It's delicious.
Here.
Have some pork adobo.
It's delicious too.
Maybe...
that's why we
became friends
because
our husband's
favorite food is
adobo.
Adobong kangkong.
Pork Adobo.
Hey!
Ah! What are you doing?
You're going to give me
a heart attack!
Sorry.
Hey, I'm sorry.
Don’t do that again, okay?
It won't happen again.
Promise.
Do you want
to go to town?
We might get home late.
You know that
our village is far from town.
That’s why I decided
to bury Roy here.
That's why it's easier
for us to visit them, right?
You can sleep at my house.
I'm alone anyway.
Love?
How are you?
I asked your colleagues...
About that bastard
Ka Roman.
Whether he has
been caught or not.
They said he hasn’t
been caught yet.
Your husband might answer
if you keep talking.
You’re actually talking
to him, aren’t you?
Yes.
Especially when I'm at home.
Does he answer?
Yes.
I talk to him
in my mind.
Especially
when I'm next
to his portrait.
I feel like...
He is really here.
I thought I was
losing my mind.
Because
I did exactly what you're doing.
We're not going crazy.
We do this
because of
how deeply we love them.
And we don't
want to lose that.
That's why I always
try to look good.
Especially when I visit him.
Emma, wait.
Can we talk first?
Talk to me, please.
What did I do?
This is wrong.
What we did is wrong.
What do you mean?
I feel like...
What we did isn't right.
Not right?
I don't care what
others might say.
I'm a teacher.
I couldn't care less.
We did not mean
for this to happen.
It happened spontaneously.
A weak woman
is helped by a strong woman.
Perhaps this is our fate.
We both lost our spouses.
We both experienced grief
and here, we found each other
to be there for one another.
Love.
I'm going home now, okay?
I love you so much.
That's why
I fought for you
to be buried
here in our land.
Because I don't want you
to be far from me.
There's something
I need to tell you.
You know,
since
I married you,
I have dedicated
myself and all my love to you.
I tried to stop myself
from being who I truly am.
To be true to myself.
I am asking for
your forgiveness.
Roy,
Emma didn't visit you?
I haven't seen her for weeks now.
I hope
you can forgive me because
I created chaos in her life.
Emma!
Emma, what happened to you?
It's nothing.
It's just a fever.
Here,
have some hot soup.
To help reduce
your temperature
and you can have
your medicine as well.
Thank you, Sandra.
I should thank you
because you came with me.
Why?
What do you mean, why?
Why are you doing this?
Of course, who else
would help each other?
Well, it's us widows.
I don't know,
but ever since I kissed you.
I kept trying to
forget about it,
but I just can't.
Is that why
you don't visit your
husband anymore?
I still visit,
but on a different day.
Now I understand.
A sad report has been received
about the situation of the
rebellion in the mountains.
According to the authorities,
the conflict between the military
and armed groups
seems to be escalating.
The long-desired peace
still appears far
from being achieved.
Despite government efforts,
the area affected by the incident
is falling into chaos and fear.
It’s disheartening
to think that many
innocent individuals
remain victims.
Many of them have wives
and children who are grieving
the permanent loss of
their husbands and fathers
because of the
seemingly endless war.
As the fight and
misunderstanding continue,
the peace that has
long been hoped for
seems like an
unreachable dream.