Fukuyama-san.
You seem happier than usual today.
Want to know why?
No need, I can probably guess.
You should at least ask.
Actually, from today onwards...
Chihiro-san is going on a 10-day summer vacation.
Oh, really?
10 days! A whole 10 days!
Time to get back to work.
What are you doing here?
Please go back to your own seat.
Don't be so cold.
Welcome back, Kenta-san
I'm home, Chihiro-san.
I can see Chihiro-san as soon as I get home.
It's simply the best!
[A sizzling new life for newlyweds]
[Zero days dating, let's get married first and then fall in love]
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Just relax and take it easy.
Oh, there's a place...
in front of the station that
serves really delicious cheesecake.
Kenta-san?
Yes?
Here's your lunchbox.
Did you make this for me?
I tried my best.
Thank you.
Don't get your hopes up too high.
I'll rush back as soon as I get off work.
Then I'll head to work.
Um...
Did you forget something?
Huh?
Phone, wallet, lunchbox...
Be careful on your way.
I don't want to go to work.
Please properly go to work.
Okay.
Then I'll be going.
I'm leaving now.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Take care.
Good morning.
It's hot today.
[Fukuyama's very important lunch, don't touch it!]
What's this?
I said don't touch it!
Mifune.
This is...
a lunchbox made by my beloved wife!
That's right, your wife has been
living here recently, hasn't she?
This is the first lunchbox Chihiro-san
made for me with her own hands.
I wonder what kind of dishes she put in it.
Will there be sausages? Or an omelet roll?
Or maybe...
Looks like this guy can't focus on work today.
Alright.
It's perfect weather for doing laundry.
Finally, lunch break!
You're fast!
I'm starting to get nervous too.
Alright, Mifune-kun, I'm going to open it!
Okay.
Ready, Go!
[Thanks for your hard work.]
Lunchbox made by Chihiro-san, it's so dazzling.
How do I say this, it's really hearty.
I hate to eat it,
but I'm going to dig in!
This is so good.
This is...
It's eel!
It's a low-key version of an eel rice lunchbox.
It's so elegant and understated.
This is amazing! I feel so happy.
Getting emotional over eel
is such a typical Tokyoite reaction.
Chihiro-san is amazing!
Well then, everyone, thank you for your hard work today.
Thanks for all your hard work...
10 days, no, the next 9 days...
Please bear with him.
Sorry about that.
I'm back.
You're back!
You actually ran all the way back?
Chihiro-san.
The lunchbox is super delicious!
That's great!
Actually, I have a surprise
prepared after we finish eating.
Oh? What could it be?
I wonder if Chihiro is enjoying
her summer vacation right now.
Kenta is probably even more excited
than usual to spend the weekend.
You know, I've been thinking...
You and Kenta-kun are such good friends.
But in terms of personality types,
you're actually opposites.
And you work in different departments too, right?
I heard that a lot...
So how did you two become such
good friends in the first place?
I think it was about six months
after we both joined the company.
Really?
There's no way around it...
Got it.
Yamada...
He's on a business trip.
Sato...
He can't either.
That gentleman over there, enjoying his fried sausage.
Are you free today?
Want to go to a mixer?
A mixer?
So it's just a mixer to make up the numbers?
It was a total disaster that day.
He suddenly started preaching
about the correct way to grill meat.
And then explained the difference
between black and white pepper.
The conversation was so off-topic that
it made all the girls lose interest.
Even the girl I had my eye on left early.
I can imagine...
(Watch on www.kisskh.la to support Admin)
Talking about pink peppercorns
and how they're not actually pepper.
No one cares.
I guess Chihiro probably likes this side of Kenta too.
After all, Chihiro-san is a bit naive.
But, she's able to see the good in Kenta.
That shows she has good taste.
So that means you have good taste too.
Bartender, another draft beer for me.
And a plate of spicy octopus, please.
Coming right up.
What?
Nothing.
So sweet!
The sugar content is really high.
So the after-dinner surprise was watermelon?
I saw it at the supermarket near the station.
I couldn't resist buying it.
I was surprised you could carry it back on a bicycle.
It has always been my dream to buy an entire watermelon.
It was just me and my dad at home.
So we always only bought half or a quarter of one.
But now, it's just the two of us.
I think that with you...
we should be able to finish it all.
Then let's eat as much as we want!
Okay.
Watermelon is definitely a must-have for summer.
And there's something else...
Speaking of summer...
Look!
It's fireworks!
So beautiful.
I can't remember the last time I saw fireworks.
Even though we're grown up, fireworks are still beautiful.
When I was little, I was scared to hold fireworks myself.
So I would just stand and watch others play with them.
But my mother told me there
are fireworks that aren't scary.
She specifically got me a sparkler.
I bought a sparkler too.
It's so nostalgic.
These are still the prettiest.
Did this remind you of your mother?
No, it's not that...
I just feel so happy right now.
Ah, but Kenta-san...
What is it?
You were going to leave me and
transfer here yourself, weren't you?
That's...
And you haven't said you like me yet.
I'm sorry...
Chihiro-san,
I...
Like...
Looks like there's a fireworks display.
You're right.
They're so beautiful!
We spent this summer together, happily and fulfillingly.
This summer was truly happy and fulfilling, but...
I'm sorry, I made you weed during this rare vacation.
It's okay, this is my home too.
Besides, it's my first time weeding, I'm having fun!
The summer vacation is already halfway over.
But since we had our first kiss last week,
no progress has been made.
A single-family home is a lot of work to maintain.
I'm planning to slowly buy a cabinet
that can store barbecue equipment.
I also want to add a roof to the parking space.
Do you have anything you'd like to do in the garden?
Things I want to do in the garden...
Definitely to enjoy barbecue with a cold beer.
Let's hurry up and finish it then!
Okay.
All that weeding she's not used to must be wearing her out.
That's right,
time for that to make its entrance.
Let's get started.
Put the pork trotters in the mixing bowl.
Salt, sugar and pepper.
Jamaican pepper and nutmeg.
And finally add some ice cubes.
Chill it through the bowl with the ice.
Mix everything together thoroughly.
Make sure the meat temperature doesn't exceed 15 degrees.
So cold...
But, I have to endure it.
Then take out the lamb intestines that
were soaked in cold water for 15 minutes.
Carefully put the casing onto the piping nozzle.
Put all the mixed meat into the piping bag.
Now it's time to squeeze!
This takes some effort.
Next...
Boil in water at 70 to 75 degrees for 20 minutes.
Sorry, I accidentally fell asleep.
Chihiro-san, you woke up just in time.
I made a side dish perfect for pairing with ice-cold beer.
They look like lollipops from a picture book.
Enjoy these with ice-cold beer,
it's a pleasure only adults can appreciate.
Well then...
Let's eat!
The meat juice is so good!
Then...
This is what summer is all about.
So cute!
For that smile...
I'd do anything!
Adding some herbs or spices would probably be good too.
You're right.
Like lemon or basil...
That would be amazing.
But...
Is this really okay?
How about we start a home garden?
A home garden, great idea!
If we keep this up...
Our summer vacation will really
turn into a kid's drawing diary...
I guess...
It'll just become like any other weekend.
If only I knew how to handle things more maturely...
Don't you think this joke has gone too far?
I'm not joking.
I'm serious about building a relationship with you.
Chihiro-san has already had two beers.
As long as the bed is made.
She'll probably fall asleep in a second.
And she'll probably curl up like
a burrito again, just like before.
That's cute too.
That's not the point.
If we just let this opportunity pass...
Kenta-san.
Aren't you going to eat?
I am! I'm eating right now.
I want another one too.
Chihiro-san.
It's a rare summer vacation.
How about we go on a trip together?
A trip?