[English subtitles are available]
[Hard To Find]
[6]
This marriage
is between
her and me.
If you can't be responsible for her,
I can.
Liang Chan.
Xi Jiu.
Do you
really have to cancel this marriage
with me?
I used to
live in a daze.
I thought forgetting the past
could lead a new life.
But I never thought
there are things I can't forget.
I thought
we could...
I let you down.
I deserve
all the blame.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
As the Crown Prince of Shuoyun,
how could I be so shameless
to marry a married woman?
I regret
this marriage.
You
can leave now.
But according to Shuoyun's rules,
even the Crown Prince has to...
You're not one of the Shuoyun tribe.
Our marriage
is wrong at first.
It's not restricted by the rules.
Liang Chan.
Sorry.
She just fainted.
Take her for treatment now.
I'll leave her to you.
What's wrong with Young Madam?
Prepare some food.
Soup and rice porridge would be best.
Okay.
Your Highness.
Just apologize to His Majesty.
Why do you have to suffer here?
There are the tribe rules
and rules
must be followed.
I'm glad you don't have a fever.
You're finally awake.
What's wrong?
Water.
I want water.
Drink it.
Have some porridge.
If there's anything else you want to eat,
I'll have Qin Sang prepare it for you.
Why are you
doing this to me?
I just can't let you die
from thirst, hunger,
or choking, etc.
Got it.
What now?
What's wrong
with the porridge?
It smells bad.
Did you put something
strange in it to trick me?
It's not the porridge.
It's you.
Me?
Exposed outside for two days and nights.
Do you think
you can stay clean?
You can wash here.
The hot spring water here
is good for your injuries.
Wait.
What now?
Do you want me to wash it for you?
Even if I need help,
I'll ask Qin Sang.
I just wanted to ask
if you have soapnut
or hibiscus leaves?
I need to wash my hair too.
So troublesome.
Could there be hidden secrets
behind what happened back then?
What should I do
to help her regain her memory?
Feng Yuan.
What are you doing here?
What's wrong with you?
You got yourself lost while taking a bath.
I just stepped on a stone.
Why are you making a fuss?
It's dark here.
Don't be so nervous.
I won't do anything to you.
It's actually snowing here.
I haven't seen snow
in Shuoyun for three years.
It's normal.
This place is at a high altitude
in the mountains with low temperature,
so it naturally snows.
But what's
the stone you mentioned earlier?
It's this stone.
I was afraid Qinsang might hurt her foot
when bathing,
so I picked it up
from the water.
What...
What are you doing?
What's wrong with it?
I don't know.
It has been there
since I can remember.
Why did her arm
become like this?
What happened back then?
I'm done.
Please leave.
His heart blood can't work.
Your blood should do.
You must be luckier than him.
Come. Come here.
Don't move.
It won't take long.
I'm looking for
Shuoyun people
with Linchuan bloodline.
What have you
brought me?
Why don't you give it a try?
My lord.
As you ordered,
all I brought
are the Shuoyun people
with Linchuan bloodline.
But the intermarriage between Shuoyun and Linchuan
happened a hundred years ago.
Perhaps the Linchuan halidom
can only be activated
by true Linchuan people.
But I can't even find
a single bird in Linchuan,
let alone the people.
Where can I find
pure-blooded Linchuan people?
How can I activate
the heart of this Divine Tree?
When will I have
the same abilities
as Helian Xi?
My lord.
Since they're all looking for us,
why don't we play along?
I'll sneak in
and use the Princess
to sow discord between Shuoyun and Helian Xi,
[Wanted]
and lure Helian Xi
to this place.
Helian Xi.
That woman treated him badly back then,
but he still wants to protect her.
Why?
Perhaps
the Princess
can help us
get Helian Xi's blood.
Good idea.
Let's send a gift to
the Shuoyun Crown Prince.
Why would I use
pomegranate flowers from May as rouge?
If she had any grudges
with people in Shuoyun,
it should be from before.
But when Young Madam was in Linchuan,
she'd been loved by the people.
Besides, Linchuan has already...
I mean,
it's even less likely for her
to have enemies in Linchuan.
Then there is only one possibility left.
It's related to her previous identity.
Could it be
that incident three years ago?
That incident?
Young Master.
Please forgive me for this.
Over these days,
I can tell
that you also don't want to believe
that incident.
I'll keep investigating.
Since she has come to Nanzhi Manor,
take good care of her.
Got it.
Young Madam.
Wake up. Your hair is still wet.
Young Madam, wake up.
Young Master.
She's been busy all day
and is very tired.
Don't wake her up.
I'll do it.
Why don't you ask Qin Sang
to apply the ointment for you?
I can do it myself.
No need to trouble others.
Is there anything
in this world that you can't do?
At least now,
I still can't recover my memory on my own.
I can
handle this.
Your neck is injured too.
How could it be?
I'd better ask Qin Sang to help me.
Qin Sang.
Come in.
Young Madam.
You want to see me?
Qin Sang, help me apply the ointment.
Okay.
Young Madam.
I suddenly remembered
that I had an appointment with a friend
and I gotta go.
I can't apply the ointment for you.
I'm leaving.
Qin Sang.
I'll do it myself then.
Let me.
All right.
You can rest now.
Where is my hairpin?
Did I lose it at that time?
Is Shuoyun's pomegranate sweet?
Yes.
Young Madam likes it.
She should like it too.
Buy some more.
I'll bring it to her.
Young Master. Are you going to see her again?
Not only to see her,
I want to get back something
that might help Feng Yuan
regain her memory,
and also investigate the incident
from three years ago
to see if there are any loopholes.
I feel like something's wrong.
Understood.
Young Master.
I really hope
that Young Madam can recover her memory,
but if she remembers the past,
everything between you and her
will no longer exist.
No matter what happened three years ago,
everything now
is just an illusion.
It's something
not worth clinging to.
It's better to face it earlier.
Qin Sang.
After I go,
I'll leave Nanzhi Manor to you.
And don't tell
Feng Yuan about her yet.
You can rest assured.