[English subtitles are available]
[Hard To Find]
[22]
Stop!
Who is in the carriage?
His Majesty is leaving the palace.
How dare you stop him?
His Majesty？
Get out of the way!
Open the door.
The rabbit lantern
looks fierce
like your mother.
Don't speak ill of my mother.
Fine.
It's my fault.
I'll take you to buy
the most beautiful lantern
for your mother, okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
Where are you
taking my daughter?
He said he'd take me
to buy the most beautiful lantern.
Mom, come with us.
No.
You're an adult.
Don't spoil the kid's fun. Let's go.
Let's go.
You...
Look.
A man
is carrying a lantern for kids.
How weird.
Yeah.
Maybe
he bought it for his wife.
It's a waste
to buy so many lanterns.
I have to satisfy
a lady's needs.
Why did you two come out together?
This is my first time in Yongzhao.
The Lantern Festival is such a grand festival.
So I'm here to experience it.
Helian Xi.
Your daughter is a shopaholic.
What's wrong with you? Are you blind?
Don't make trouble.
His Majesty.
Where are you going?
I seemed to see His Majesty.
The King of Yongzhao?
Why is he
here
in civilian clothes?
The two are following him.
Xi Jiu,
send Shi Liu
back to the clinic with Shi Ying.
I'm afraid something will happen at the Lantern Fair tonight.
Okay.
His Majesty is missing.
Now, everyone is here.
Remember,
don't let anyone go.
Yes, my lord.
Your Majesty, step back.
How dare you block my way?
Did my father send you here?
Your Majesty.
Aunt.
He came back, as you said.
He's back?
This is not the time to talk about this.
Your Majesty, come back with us.
Qing,
you've grown up.
You have your own thoughts.
You have
associated with my enemy.
Feng Yin,
he is your only son.
Won't you let him go?
Son?
Feng Yuan,
your father
taught me a lesson.
There is no father-son relationship in the royal family.
You came at the right time.
I don't need to bother to find you.
Helian Xi.
Aunt, what is that?
The heart of the Linchuan Divine Tree.
I
won't let you trample on me
as before.
You talk too much.
Aunt.
Aunt, your hand!
Aunt!
Aunt, why did you
have the same injury?
What did you do to her?
She will
hurt when I get injured?
Come on, Helian Xi.
Aren't you going to kill me?
What are you waiting for?
You can't kill him.
You dare not.
Because...
I knew it.
I was wondering
why I was able to use
the Heart of Riyao suddenly?
Thanks to
my blood relationship with you.
Our blood relationship?
Turns out
at that time…
Come on, Helian Xi.
Kill me.
If I hurt, she will hurt.
If I die, she will die, too.
Come on, avenge Linchuan
with my worthless life.
Shut up!
Three years ago,
you killed a substitute.
Three years later,
you can't kill me.
If I were you,
I would have no face to return to Linchuan.
Xi,
kill him!
Xi, don't worry about me.
Kill him!
Aunt!
No!
You will die.
Aunt, no!
Kill him!
Aunt!
Feng Yin.
Xi Jiu, no!
Helian Xi,
why did you stop me?
If he dies, Yuan will also die.
What are you talking about?
Xi.
Helian Xi.
You dare not kill me.
I can finally kill you.
Take them away.
Xi.
Let's go.
No!
Aunt is going to…
Feng Yuan.
Aunt.
Yuan.
Do you want to kill yourself?
He doesn't dare kill you.
I dare.
You're afraid of death
but I'm not!
Yuan.
Go.
Let's go.
No one…
No one can kill me anymore.
[Zhizi Clinic]
Don't worry.
She will be fine.
Shi Ying, save her!
Yuan!
Send her to the room.
I'll get the styptic powder.
[Zhizi Clinic]
Your wound...
Don't care about me. Save her first.
How did she get hurt like this?
It's all my fault.
Yuan,
it will hurt after the medicine is put on.
Hang in there.
It's okay.
Yuan.
It'll be done soon.
Hang in there.
How is Feng Yuan?
Is Aunt okay?
Don't worry.
These are just superficial wounds,
not lethal ones.
I've stopped the bleeding and applied the medicine.
The wounds will heal slowly.
-That's good. -That's good.
I don't know why Your Majesty left the palace,
but if you don't mind,
please stay in the clinic tonight.
Thank you.
This way, please.
Don't worry.
Yuan is fine.
Thank you.
What's up?
What
did Yuan go through?
Can you tell me?
Is your wound hurting again?
It's hot.
Hang in there.
Don't touch it.
Do you want some water?
It turns out
there were so many things
between them.
They suffered so much.
Yes.
I think the word "suffer"
can't sum up what they've been through.
Shi Ying,
you can't hide
your love for a man when you gaze at him.
Do you
love Helian Xi?
When I met him,
I didn't think so much.
Miss,
it's going to rain.
Looks like
there won't be any patients.
Let's take the child
back to the inner court and rest.
Okay.
She has
never cried
when there's thunder and lightning.
I wonder
which one she is like, her mom or dad?
It's good to be bold.
She can be a doctor like me in the future.
But she's not your kid.
Do you want to take her as your own kid and raise her?
Got it.
I'll go pack up.
Let's go back to sleep.
Auntie Lan,
is it raining outside?
He...
Where is she?
Who are you looking for?
Feng Yuan.
Where is she?
I don't know where Yuan is.
Why are you looking for her?
Yuan.
Where did this child come from?
I fed her
once an hour today.
It's almost
the same as yesterday.
You
ate so much.
Little glutton.
[Autumn Festival. Colorful threads can drive out the evil spirits]
You are her father, right?
It's you.