[English subtitles are available]
[Hard To Find]
[16]
Feng Yin hasn't found out
about the key yet.
Anyway,
I
have changed the pattern of the key.
Even if Feng Yin gets it,
he can't enter Linchuan.
But what about the baby?
I can fool Feng Yin for a while,
but even if I can give birth to the baby,
it may not
leave the palace safely.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, why are you here?
Aunt, it's all my fault.
I put you under house arrest by my father.
I'm here to apologize to you.
Your Majesty,
you don't have to apologize to me.
This has nothing to do with you.
My mother passed away after giving birth to me.
In the palace,
you are the kindest person to me.
Hua'e comes.
She
is arrogant
and domineering in my father's favor.
Your Majesty, leave now.
If she sees you, we'll be in trouble.
Okay.
Hurry.
I told you
not to bother me.
What are you doing here again?
Your Highness,
you seem to be in a good mood
for painting.
The fetus
is less than eight months, right?
What a pity.
What do you mean?
Pitifully,
the baby will never have the chance to see its father
after it's born.
What do you mean?
Helian Xi
came to the palace to see you.
What?
Where is Xi?
The Young Master of Linchuan came from afar.
Of course, we will give him a feast
in the palace.
Where is General Wu Jiu?
Why hasn't Yuan shown up yet?
I wonder
how many pieces would he be cut into
after the banquet?
Anyway,
I will dig out his heart
and give it to you.
What are you doing?
Give birth.
I'll take you there then.
I hope you and your baby
can see him for the last time.
I'm a subordinate of General Wu Jiu.
General told me
Yongzhao is indebted to you.
So I come to toast you.
How is General Wu Jiu?
He...
He died in a battle.
What?
To General Wu Jiu.
Helian Xi, Young Master of Linchuan.
Who are you?
I forgot.
I know you very well
but you don't know who I am.
I am Feng Yin,
the elder brother of Feng Yuan.
Catch him alive.
You were born safely.
That's great.
I will let you
leave here safely.
Be good.
This is the Nightfly Powder given by your father.
It can make you fall asleep and look like you're dead.
If you look alive,
I will have no way.
Don't be afraid.
Trust me.
Your Majesty, can you do me a favor?
After my baby is born,
no matter it's alive or dead,
bring it to a clinic
and give the baby
to a girl named Shi Ying.
I'll help you
protect your child.
Xi,
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect that our marriage
will end up like this.
Feng Yin is cunning and vicious.
To protect you and our baby,
I should be more ruthless than him.
I think
our marriage
is the beginning of this tragedy.
Now, I only have one way
to protect you.
I hope you can
live on
with our baby.
May the Divine Tree bless us.
Your husband is so tolerant.
He didn't even moan.
Alright, Yuan.
Tell me.
How can I enter Linchuan?
Your Highness,
their baby died.
As you see,
if I don't stop it,
they will continue
to cut his flesh.
By then, your husband
can't even
leave the whole body.
Okay,
I can tell you
how to enter Linchuan.
Give him
to me.
Do you want his body?
My baby was born prematurely.
It died
at birth.
Helian Xi is doomed
anyway.
I can't live on either.
How about
letting us three
die together?
Give me the baby.
Give it to me!
Splash salt water.
Yuan,
run!
Yuan, run!
Sorry.
Yuan,
why?
He is my husband.
I'd like him to die directly.
I heard that you were happy
in Linchuan.
But you made a deal with me without any hesitation.
Don't you care about
the Linchuan people?
I'm the Princess of Yongzhao.
Their lives
have nothing to do with me.
Good.
Very good.
The key to Linchuan
is here.
So this is it.
We are indeed siblings.
You're even crazier than me
when acting unscrupulously.
What are you waiting for?
He's mine.
Untie him now!
All the mistakes
began in this palace.
All I can do
is to end
the crime of Yongzhao against Linchuan.
I have to
sacrifice my body
for a miracle.
[I had a nightmare that made me sad about our parting]
[Luckily, our story isn't over yet]
Xi!
It's been two days.
Why hasn't Feng Yuan woken up?
Don't worry, Young Master.
The doctor checked her again this morning.
He said Young Madam is fine,
but a little weak.
She hasn't woken up yet
might because she was frightened
by the hit.
Do Shuyun's imperial physicians
know how to treat patients?
She hasn't woken up for two days.
But doctors said it was due to her weakness after being hit?
If it doesn't work,
Qin Sang,
find some
folk doctors.
Yes.
Xi!