[Miss Ye in Wonderland]
[Episode 16]
[Party B Individual Ye Wange]
There's one more thing
I want to ask you.
Do you know the truth
about my mother's being put into prison?
I know
you've been investigating it for years.
Me too.
But I could only leave it unsettled.
But I'm sure
Shen Lingzhu is a pawn at most.
Someone else killed your mother.
And this person...
Boss, we've caught him.
Okay.
What did Boss say?
Leave no trace behind.
Why does he look so familiar?
Isn't he Feng Muchen?
Why did Mr. Feng pretend to be him?
Stop asking.
Just throw him out.
What is this place?
Where is this?
What's going on?
Why can't I get out?
Why am I back again?
[Mr. Jackson took out the contract and said, all the shares are yours now.]
[This is the last stroke. Take a look. Sign here if there's no problem.]
[Ye Wange took a look at the contract and signed her name. She was overjoyed.]
What?
[Ye Wange came closer and closer.]
[Pull Ye Wange up.]
[He tried to pull Ye Wange up, but she dodged quickly.]
[Ye Wange was pressing on Feng Muchen.]
[The classical style was outstanding.]
[Ye Wange took a look at the contract and signed her name. She was overjoyed.]
[Mr. Jackson stood up and said, I'm done with everything I need to do. See you.]
Am I
[Ye Wange took a look at the contract and signed her name. She was overjoyed.]
[Mr. Jackson stood up and said, I'm done with everything I need to do. See you.]
in the world of telencephalon?
How could it be?
[End of the chapter. Please look forward to the next chapter.]
If you're not feeling well, you must go offline immediately.
Otherwise, your consciousness may be sealed
in the space of consciousness in the world of telencephalon forever.
I modified the plot myself,
which caused rejection to the system.
That's why I'm trapped in the space of consciousness.
[Chapter 908] [High-end Business Talent Party]
Its color
and style
are based on our latest design concept.
Long time no see.
Where am I?
The scriptwriter is so stupid.
I wanted to go back to the Ye family to see my dad.
Why am I here all of a sudden?
The scriptwriter is so stupid.
How could she go on a blind date while I was away?
Ge.
Ye.
[Chen Ye handed Ye Wange a glass of wine, and talked to her about how Feng Muchen had been ignoring her these days.]
[Talked to her about how Feng Muchen had been ignoring her these days.]
[Trying to ask her to leave Feng Muchen.]
How dare you, Chen Ye.
Taking advantage of her while I'm away?
[Talked to her about how Feng Muchen had been ignoring her these days, trying to ask her to leave Feng Muchen.]
[Paste]
[Copy]
[Recall]
[Paste]
[Copy]
Copy, paste, delete.
Don't blame me for being harsh on you.
[Ask her to leave Feng Muchen.]
[Copy]
[Paste]
[Recall]
Delete. Delete.
What?
Could it be...
It can be reversed?
[Chen Ye handed her a glass of wine and said, you look so pretty today, Ge.]
Here.
Ge,
you look so pretty today.
[Ye Wange blushed and said...]
You are also very handsome today, Ye.
[Ye Wange is popular with young talents. A lot of people gathered around her.]
What was that nonsense I just said?
Miss Ye.
This is my card.
Nice to meet you.
Miss Ye, this is mine.
What's going on?
Who are these people?
Did the author update the plot again?
[Ye Wange is popular with young talents. A lot of people gathered around her.]
Looks like I have to be faster than the author.
You must have no idea
how I've been living my life
before I met Ge.
[Ye Wange is popular with young talents. A lot of people gathered around her.]
Check out my speed after being single for 20 years.
[Recall]
[Ye Wange is popular with young talents. A lot of people gathered around her.]
Delete. Delete.
[Recall]
[Ye Wange is popular with young talents. A lot of people gathered around her.]
Really, Sir?
Again?
[Ye Wange found the cakes in the dining area waving at her.]
[Copy]
[Paste]
[Recall]
Copy "found".
[Ye Wange]
[Cakes]
Chen Ye found the cakes.
Ge.
Ye.
[Cakes]
[Ye Wange noticed Lu Wanqing coming, so she walked towards her to say hello.]
[However, she slipped and almost fell. Luckily, Chen Ye took her in his arms in time.]
Taking her in his arms?
How inappropriate!
[Ye Wange noticed Lu Wanqing coming, so she walked towards her to say hello.]
[However, she slipped and almost fell. Luckily, Chen Ye took her in his arms in time.]
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Isn't she the mistress's daughter?
So you also know that her mother cheated,
got pregnant with someone else's child,
and was kicked out of the Ye family?
No wonder
she was so eager to seduce Mr. Chen.
Turns out
she's here to get a boyfriend
so that she can go back and take more advantage of that family.
Children will grow to be like their parents.
Lu Wanqing was definitely faking it.
What are you talking about?
The Ye family's affairs
are none of your business.
If you bully my sister,
it equals bullying me.
I won't let go of
any of you.
Making a nasty scene at my place.
Beware, you may lose your tongue.
Get lost!
Go on.
Keep drinking.
Don't mind what they said.
They just don't know you.
It's okay.
Thank you.
You don't need to thank me.
I didn't get to know you through others' words.
You want to chase after her?
Found it.
Ye Wange saw Feng Muchen's handsome silhouette.
Stood still.
Copy.
Paste.
[Ye Wange looked at Feng Muchen's handsome silhouette and stood still.]
[With Ye Wange's help, Chen Ye finally took the initiative to approach Lu Wanqing.]
The author wants Ge
to be the stimulus of the relationship between the hero and heroine?
What's going on?
Does this mean that if the content I edit
follows the author's thought,
the alarm won't ring?
My body index is normal.
I didn't expect
there's this other side of you, Miss Lu.
How about this?
I'll take you to a place.
Let's go.
How do you know this place?
Right.
You must have watched that video.
Am I a joke?
After all the ups and downs,
I lost everything.
I lost my mom.
So
you got separated from your family too?
What is this?
This is called a bird whistle.
This is for you.
It's you.
It's me.
This time,
we don't have to look for our parents anymore.
Because we have become adults.
I'll go with you
wherever you want to go.
Yun Yi.
Ge.
Ning Yuan.
Handsome.
You must be Feng Muchen.
Come with me.
Sorry.
The subscriber you dialed cannot be connected at the moment.
How dare you, Feng Muchen.
You didn't answer my calls,
reply to my messages,
and you didn't come back the whole night.
How dare you!
Mrs. Zhang,
have you seen Mr. Feng?
I've been busy this morning.
I didn't pay attention.
Okay, go ahead.
Thank you.
Okay.
Yun Yi.
Have you seen your boss?
No.
He said he had something to do, so he didn't let me follow him.
Something to do?
Don't worry, Miss Ye.
Boss is an adult.
He'll be fine.
I'm only worried because he's an adult.
Alright, Feng Muchen.
You must have done something bad behind my back.
Don't let me catch you.
If I catch you,
I'll skin you alive.
Good morning, Miss.
You...
Have you seen Feng Muchen?
No.
Have you seen Mr. Feng?
How could you not see him?
Didn't he tell you anything before he left?
He said he wouldn't let me follow him.
Look how anxious Miss is.
It's 8:00 a.m. now.
He didn't let me follow him. If I followed him...
Why are you drinking coffee here like nothing happened?
You don't even know where your boss is.
Could it be something happened to Feng Muchen?
I don't even want to talk about it.
If you keep doing this, I really think...
Shut up!
Who are you?
What is he doing?
Mr. Feng.
Beautiful girls?
We'll take you to a nice place.
Feng.
Mu.
Chen!
Stop spraying.
You've been spraying it all night.
The whole room smells like peach.
I won't run away, okay?
Your uncle ran away.
You should repay
the money he owes us.
Yes, you should pay us.
Even if I want to,
you need to give me my phone, right?
If I can't reach my uncle,
you can't get the money.
Your uncle also owes us something else
besides money.
Yeah.
Tell me, what should we do?
Kid, sometimes,
choices are more important than hard work.
Just spray it on me.
Scumbag.
Just wait and see.
Miss Ye.
Boss's video call.
Answer it.
Ge.
[Switch to voice call] [Hang up] [Switch the camera]
I'm with my uncle.
Nonsense!
There are two beautiful girls by your side.
Beautiful girls.
[Switch to voice call] [Hang up] [Switch the camera]
Niece-in-law.
Feng Fugui.
Who is Feng Fugui?
Come to Yuewan Karaoke with five million yuan.
[Switch to voice call] [Hang up] [Switch the camera]
If you dare to call the police...
-But... -He hung up.
Who is Feng Fugui?
He's our boss's prodigal uncle,
Feng Fugui.
He is indulged in eating, drinking, hooking up and gambling.
When Boss became the chairman,
he asked Boss to give him one million yuan every month.
Boss had no choice.
He had to agree.
He agreed?
One million.
Feng Muchen is such a pushover.
It must be because the Feng family is having a hard time,
and Boss is short on money.
That's why he found two beautiful girls
to kidnap Boss.
Oh no.
Feng Muchen must not know about this.
Let's go.
I don't want it.
I want it, okay?
Stop dawdling.
I want it too.
Feng Muchen.
You're having fun.
How about I join you?
You're finally here. Did you bring the money?
You are funny. Where could I get the money?
I'm here
to tell you that
I have no money.
If you want Feng Muchen,
I've brought this to add to the fun.
Don't listen to her nonsense.
My nephew is the president of Feng's Group.
Every girl likes him.
You can ask around if you don't believe me.
Feng Muchen is a deadbeat now.
Why should I care?
Let me tell you.
Our Miss won't take him over.
Don't say that.
Although Boss is a deadbeat,
he's been taking it for granted, right? Boss?
You are so good at summarizing.
There's a position open at Mars.
You should take it.
I will
continue to be a freeloader.
Look.
He admitted it himself.
But how does he deserve to be a freeloader?
Like uncle, like nephew.
The Feng family are all bad people.
Feng Fugui.
What are you looking at? Run!
Let's go.
Retreat!
Go beat them.
They have the money.
Go after them. Stop beating me.
[Theater parking lot  Entrance]
Stop running. I can't run anymore.
Where did you go
last night?
[Theater parking lot  Entrance]
Are you feeling uncomfortable because you ran too fast?
Do you want some water?
I'm fine.
I'll be fine after some rest.
[Theater parking lot  Entrance]
Feng Muchen.
Ning Yuan, hurry up.
Call an ambulance.
What's going on?
Feng Muchen, don't scare me.
Feng Muchen.
[Public Welfare Rescue Division]
We haven't got in yet.