[Miss Ye in Wonderland]
[Episode 8]
[Feng Muchen][Ye Wange]
Contract?
[No physical intimacy with each other.]
[Don't interfere with each other's life and privacy.]
I won't sign it.
[House-sharing Contract]
I can step back.
First move,
let him touch you.
He didn't even look?
What?
Calm down.
He's so calm?
Am I not attractive?
Don't be attracted. Don't be attracted.
What is he murmuring about?
I can't look. I can't look.
I have to go.
What does she want?
Hey.
My medicine...
dropped.
Please help me.
Yun Yi. Where are you?
Where are you?
Do it yourself.
Doesn't he like me?
My look...
[First move, physical intimacy]
He didn't like it?
You wanna know?
He can't leave.
Second move,
let him know your secrets.
Hi.
I'm in a mood.
I want to see you.
Who is she calling?
Remember love at first sight?
Remember butterflies in the stomach?
Isn't that enough to describe our feelings?
I want to
eat something,
hotpot, barbecue, donuts,
and ice cream.
And I kind of miss you.
See you tomorrow. Bye.
Fragrance Manor.
I'm going all out.
You can't drink.
This wine is quite hot.
Why are you drinking at home?
A way of relax.
Stop!
Let me ask you.
Why didn't you ask me who I was calling?
That's your privacy.
What does it have to do with me?
If you don't care about me,
Why should I?
I...
I'm your wife.
I don't care. You're lying.
You're double-faced.
The cowlick on your head
is quite cute.
When I think about giving you back to her,
I still...
A little...
[Calling]
I failed again.
Boss, remember Mr. Ye.
You need to discuss with him
about tonight's business meeting in advance.
Got it.
Boss, go ahead.
Since I can't do it,
I give you to Lu Wanqing.
That's it.
Feng's Group is pretty good
in this industry.
Unfortunately, the business hasn't been good these years.
I can't keep up with the market.
But now that Ge is married,
I will take care of her.
Please have a seat.
The closing of the Ye and Ye families will start a new cooperation mode,
and the resource integration.
We can definitely bring the industry to a new stage.
Mr. Ye, you really have a comprehensive grasp of things.
No, no.
We're getting old day by day.
The future is yours.
Mr. Chen is here. Don't just talk.
Have some fruits.
Thank you.
Last time I heard Mr. Chen
was looking for an assistant.
Have you found a suitable one?
Aunt Shen still remembers
my little thing.
It's just that this dark horse does not come often.
Well, what do you think of our girl?
Well,
I have a lot to do after graduation.
I'll cause trouble to Mr. Chen.
How can she be my assistant?
This is a waste of her talent.
Exactly.
You're too kind.
Hello, Mr. Feng. Miss.
Dad, Aunt Zhu, Wanqing
are all here.
Feng Muchen, talk to them,
especially Wanqing.
I need to go to the bathroom.
Didn't you follow me?
What do you want to do
in the bathroom?
If you don't let it go,
you have to accept it.
Muchen is here.
Here, sit down please.
Talk to your dad.
Mr. Chen is here too.
Here.
Hello.
Sit here.
Have a seat.
I'll go upstairs to see Ge.
Dad.
Did you quarrel with Ge?
No.
Let's not talk about
the business meeting.
No.
I'm comfortable.
I haven't been back to my place for a long time.
I miss it.
It feels so good to be home.
What is this?
Isn't this the brooch Grandpa gave me that day?
Why are you here?
Do you think I really want you
to work for Chen Ye?
Do you know your father likes him?
He likes him.
Why do you want me to help him?
How could it be?
Do you know how many people...
Alright, Mum.
Wait.
Is it inappropriate
for me to do this?
I need to read. Be with them.
Wait.
Can you learn from Ye Wange?
She's always fooling around.
She didn't delay anything.
Look at you.
Praise me?
No, who's silly?
Stop it.
I'm going back.
Wait.
I haven't finished yet.
I need you to get ready
for that summer camp in two days.
All the famous young men in the circle will go.
Besides, this time you can see elites,
Jackson, the tycoon in the industry.
Jackson will come here, too.
Wouldn't that be more possible?
The love scene between the male and female lead is too difficult.
Chen Ye appeared in the Ye's family today.
Ye Shuyuan also didn't want to discuss
the details of tonight's business dinner.
Plus...
Boss.
Ye's Group just issued a notice.
Mr. Ye ordered to stop the production line in Feng's Group.
Ye Shuyuan has suspended
the production line of Feng's Group.
The business banquet tonight should be wonderful.
I wonder what the old man is up to.
Now he has a problem
with his father-in-law.
I guess Feng Muchen can't sit still.
As long as there is a gap between them,
we win.
The location of this summer camp has been confirmed
It's organised by our Business School.
Anyone who collaborates with us
can participate.
I won't go.
I've been busy lately. I don't have time.
Okay, bye.
Wait.
Can I...
No.
Why?
Because you're a bad student.
How can I participate?
You have no choice in your life.
Why is he so cold?
My Lady, let's go inside.
You'll catch a cold if you sit like this.
Thank you, Ning Wan.
Sit with me for a while.
Okay.
What's so good about a rich lady?
My father and mother don't love me.
I have a sister,
but we're not close.
My marriage is profitable.
The point is
I have no money now.
Miss.
You still have me.
Yes.
I'm glad you're here. Let's go. Let's go.
Boss.
Why don't we take Miss Ye?
It has nothing to do with her.
Why?
I shouldn't be too close to her.
I almost forgot my purpose.
I hurt Feng family.
Boss, what do you mean?
You have love and career.
You're the winner.
You can't even dream about it.
What do you know?
The world suddenly became so quiet.
I can only hear my heartbeats.
I love her.
I'm ready.
Let's begin.
[Exhibition Post]
The brain system is still under testing.
If you don't feel well in the brain world,
you must go offline immediately.
Otherwise, his life will be in danger.
The one in front.
Can you drive?
You scared me.
Yun Yi.
What's wrong, boss?
Are you okay?
I'm coming in.
I want to get off.
Boss, where are you going?
It's raining, boss.
♫Your eyes are so mysterious♫
Ge.
I'm coming.
♫Your unobtrusive smile♫
♫Is your most affectionate hide♫
Ge.
Wait for me.
♫My heartbeat is eavesdropped by you♫
♫Your concern for me♫
♫Is an unexpected foreshadowing♫
♫In this banal plot♫
[Chapter 351 Renovation]
[He's coming.]
♫You must be in the ending♫
[Ye Wange was asleep on a rainy day.]
♫That I am chasing♫
♫The promise you keep♫
♫Shall also be inscribed♫
♫In the story about me♫
♫You descend♫
♫In my clear dream world♫
Don't kill me.
I'm not the Ye Yange you're looking for.
♫You travel through the parallel of time♫
[Ye Wange woke up.]
Don't come over.
♫Embrace you♫
♫Our destined meeting♫
♫Made me realize♫
♫That those once you guarded♫
I have a fever.
♫Are the reason♫
♫Why happiness is not let down♫
[Feng Muchen's shadow emerged from the darkness.]
Don't come over!
Don't come over.
Don't be afraid.
I'm coming.
♫Your eyes are so mysterious♫
♫Your unobtrusive smile♫
♫Is your most affectionate hide♫
♫My heartbeat is eavesdropped by you♫
♫Your concern for me♫
♫Is an unexpected foreshadowing♫
♫In this banal plot♫
♫You must be in the ending♫
♫That I am chasing♫
♫The promise you keep♫
♫Shall also be inscribed♫
♫In my story about me♫
♫You descend♫
♫In my clear dream world♫
♫You travel through the parallel of time♫
♫And walk with me♫
♫Firmly♫
♫Embrace you♫
♫Our destined meeting♫
♫Made me realize♫
♫That those once you guarded♫
♫Are the reason♫
♫Why happiness is not let down♫
Here, have this. It's sweet.
Have more.
♫My heartbeat is eavesdropped by you♫
♫Your concern for me♫
Why did you come back suddenly?
♫Is an unexpected foreshadowing♫
♫In this banal plot♫
You have a fever.
♫You must be in the ending♫
Stop talking.
Go sleep.
♫That I am chasing♫
♫The promise you keep♫
♫Shall also be inscribed♫
Don't worry.
♫In the story about me♫
I'll stay here.
♫You descend♫
♫In my clear dream world♫
♫You travel through the parallel of time♫
♫And walk with me♫
♫Firmly♫
♫Embrace you♫
♫Our destined meeting♫
♫Made me realize♫
♫That those once you guarded♫
♫Are the reason♫
♫Why happiness is not let down♫
Why is he sleeping here?
This guy
is easy to get along with.
Besides,
when I look at him, I find out that he is handsome.
You told me not to leave last night.
All these years,
I finally met someone
I can't let go of,
my man.
How could I leave?
Maybe you can't remember me now.
Ge, I believe.
One day you will remember me
and our past.
I will protect you
until that day.
What's wrong with your brain?
It’s my duty to protect you.
But I can't do it.
Your lady is fine now.
You have to punish yourself?
I wasn't there every time you're in danger.
It's my negligence.
What are you doing?
Speaking of negligence, I'm more.
I often forget my boss.
Should I throw water?
Are you crazy? It's all in the past.
I know.
What's the point of being late?
What are you waiting for? Go get changed.
Let's go.
In the novel,
hair gel is okay.
His hairstyle was still there.
His ring, his watch.
Too much.
Much better now.
Was he really staying all night by my bed?
Weird.
Feng Muchen is warm now.
He has turned good lately.
Did he see my bad habits?
Grinding, snoring,
or talking.
Why should I think about that?
Since last night,
I found out something strange,
me or him?
Of course. You.
The toothpaste is so small.
Your ex-boyfriend
didn't buy you toothpaste?
That's all you can do.
I've never had a boyfriend.
I guess she really forgot me.
Go ahead.
This toothpaste is good.
It won't be squeezed like before.
Keep it up.
Why do you suddenly talk like my mom?
Like your mom?
If you take me as your dad,
I'm willing.
You took advantage of me?
This is my room.
It's my room.
Of course I can use it.
Are you okay?
I didn't touch you. Don't extort me.
Do I have a heart disease?
How would I know?
Is my body still not used to it?
What are you murmuring about?
Go to see the doctor if you're sick.
What are you doing?
Not for now.
What happened?
The system has something wrong.