[Miss Ye in Wonderland]
[Episode 1]
It's not easy
to be the son-in-law of the Ye family, right?
Feng Muchen.
I'm the one who fell in love with you first,
but you ended up marrying my half-sister.
Humans surely are fortune's fool.
Wanna leave?
Let's see how you can escape
tonight.
I slept so well last night.
Me too.
I can't believe the plot development.
Nowadays, they only write feel-good novels.
They are not realistic at all.
If a man and a woman break up in real life,
the girl should be the one who's in tears.
After all, breakups should be decent.
That darn decency.
But the vicious female supporting role
has the same name as me.
I'm not capable of doing that kind of things.
Approaching the carpool pick-up location.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'll hand in the script within an hour.
Editor-in-chief, please calm down.
[Author of The Low-profile Miss Ye]
[Lu Wanqing]
[Personality: Tough on the outside, not so soft on the inside]
A stone-cold fox.
She's obviously a workaholic.
I'll stick to my novel then.
That's how Ye Wange turns from Feng Muchen's sister-in-law
into his fiancee.
Sister-in-law?
The author is so tacky.
I like it.
[GPS]
[Sister-in-law]
Excuse me.
Sorry for disturbing you.
In two weeks, Feng Muchen will hold a press conference
[Chapter Three  Marriage of Business between the Feng family and the Ye family]
to announce the strategic cooperation between the Ye family and the Feng family.
And they'll announce the marriage
of Feng Muchen and the female lead of the novel, the second daughter of the Ye family, Lu Wanqing.
Her condition is very urgent.
She's lost some of her memories due to severe head injury.
We have a new treatment.
The telencephalon treatment.
Perhaps in the world of telencephalon,
she can be healed and her memory can be brought back.
I hope she can recover
[Revival]
[Life-saver]
[Lu Wanqing]
[Ye Fengyan]
[Mr. Ye]
[Lu Wanqing]
[Disguise]
[Go for a walk]
[Feng Muchen]
[Tacit]
[Birthday party]
[Su Yinyin]
[Ye Wange]
[Feng Muchen]
through telencephalon treatment.
[Su Yinyin]
[Shen Lingzhu]
[The Ye family]
[Feng Muchen]
[Chapter 1354 Operation Proposal]
It hurts so much.
Where are my glasses?
When did the rain stop?
Where did all these come from?
My phone.
Miss Ye, please get off.
Something's wrong with the car?
Oh no.
I haven't got to the office yet.
I'll be late.
Put me down.
What are you doing?
I have to work.
You are going to be a mom.
How can you still walk in high heels?
Let me carry you.
Be a mom?
What the hell?
Why does he look so familiar?
Have I seen him before?
Have you seen enough?
Put me down.
Or I'll call the police.
What police?
Just hold me tight.
You pervert!
Put me down!
Bastard!
Uncle Ye, Aunt Zhu.
Put me down!
Put...
Be careful.
Lie down for a while.
Uncle Ye.
Aunt Zhu.
Who are they?
Are they kidnapping me?
I don't have much money.
I'll go home now.
Sorry for disturbing you.
What's going on? It's not right.
Are you done?
Honey,
you have to do right by Wanqing.
She's locked herself up in her room for a while.
Don't worry.
Muchen,
I've always trusted you the most.
Look at you.
You...
You and Ge...
I don't even know what to say.
Uncle Ye, Aunt Zhu.
Don't worry.
I've made it clear to Wanqing.
We can go on as we planned.
It's just the bride...
How do you know my name?
Who are you?
Honey, look at her.
What's wrong? Your IQ is gone due to pregnancy?
It's more like you are pregnant.
What's your name?
Tell her.
Call...
Call him father.
Father?
Shuyuan.
We should really teach her a lesson.
[Feng Muchen, why do you only find out about the truth now?]
[Ye Shuyuan]
[Ye Wange's biological father]
[Ye's live-in son-in-law  CEO of the Ye's Group]
[Ye Shuyuan]
Ye Shuyuan?
How dare you call my name?
Shen Lingzhu.
[Shen Lingzhu]
[Doesn't look like a good person]
[Ye Wange's step-mother, Lu Wanqing's biological mother]
Feng Muchen?
[Yun Yi: We've sent someone to keep an eye on her. She's been walking this way since she left the hospital.]
[Seems like she's going to make a scene at the press conference]
[Male lead of the novel  Feng Muchen]
[Boss of the Feng's Group]
[Fashion designer, top in the industry]
Wait a minute.
Let me think about it.
[Feng Muchen: OK. Let's play Miss Ye's game as she wishes.]
Bar.
Drugs.
[Yun Yi: We've sent someone to keep an eye on her. She's been walking this way since she left the hospital.]
[Seems like she's going to make a scene at the press conference]
Two weeks later,
Muchen held a press conference.
Photoshop it so that we look more like a couple.
That's for extra price.
Haven't I transferred the money to you?
Ask them to work hard.
OK.
Boss.
Those shares belong to Ye Wange,
not Lu Wanqing.
You mean, the disappeared shares of the Ye's Group
belong to Ye Wange, not Lu Wanqing?
Yes, Boss.
You almost married the wrong person.
Where is Ye Wange?
I sent someone to keep an eye on her.
She's been coming this way
after she got out of the hospital.
Looks like she's going to make a scene.
Change of plans.
[Press conference on the strategic cooperation between the Ye's Group and the Feng's Group]
I believe our strategic cooperation
will be a pioneer in the industry.
Mr. Feng is young and promising.
I'm very confident
about our cooperation.
And I'm more than satisfied
to trust my daughter with you.
Wanqing.
Come to the stage.
[Ye's Group]
[Press conference on the strategic cooperation between the Ye's Group and the Feng's Group]
I heard that Mr. Feng
is not only announcing the strategic cooperation with the Ye's Group,
but also some other good news.
Please be quiet.
As a member of the Feng's family,
I will definitely share any good news
with you as soon as possible.
Bullshit.
How dare you, Feng Muchen.
What are you looking at?
[Ye's Group]
What kind of occasion this is?
Why are you messing around?
Go back.
Dad, you won't help me.
Can't I fight for it myself?
Well...
[Examination report]
I have some good news to announce.
Mr. Feng
is going to be a father.
At this time,
you can't get too emotional.
It's not good for your health.
I'll take my responsibilities.
But don't mess around on this kind of occasion.
Everyone.
I will definitely share the good news like this
with you.
I'll announce it in a few days.
By then,
please witness it with me.
[Ye's Group]
That's how Ye Wange turns from Feng Muchen's sister-in-law
to his fiancee.
Oh no.
Am I in the world of the novel?
I'll go check on Wanqing.
Drugged?
Pregnant?
Take your time.
Oh no.
Listen to me. I'm Ye Wange.
I'm not the Ye Wange you think I am.
I don't know you.
I'm not the one who drugged you.
I'm not pregnant.
I don't want to marry you either.
Isn't all this
what you want?
Hold on.
I must be dreaming.
Why haven't I woken up?
Pinching alone won't work.
You have to slap your face.
Really?
Thank you.
You went too easy on yourself. It wouldn't work either.
Why haven't I woken up?
So you can't get out either.
I'm also good at acting, right?
Drama queen.
Open sesame!
[Don't come over.]
Bro,
I'm counting on you.
Ye Wange.
Whatever.
Time to work.
I'm still in the book?
Are these photos of me?
My head hurts.
Who are you?
I'm Ning Yuan.
Your personal assistant.
You are at your house, Miss.
The Ye family's villa in Haibei, Miss.
Miss, you seem to be hit badly.
You should eat something first.
This is like a calorie "bomb".
I'll have some soup first.
I'll put it here.
Miss,
please eat more of this pregnancy diet.
Your morning sickness is so serious.
Wait a minute, Miss.
I'll go get you some preserved plums.
Wait a minute.
Forget about the plums.
Go buy me a...
Come here.
Buy me...
A pregnancy test kit.
What kit?
Pregnancy test kit.
What's that again?
How can I get out of here?
I need to find a way out.
But Boss,
do you have to sacrifice so much
to marry the daughter of the Ye family?
Tell me why I need to do that.
Marrying Ye's daughter who has shares of the Ye's Group
can not only solve the urgent cash flow problem,
but also maintain the long-term brand cooperation
with the Ye's Group.
So that we can bring the faded old brand of the Feng's back to the front line.
Oh my god.
Boss.
You are such a great person.
I am more than willing to do that
for the Feng family.
But Boss,
are you really going to propose to Miss Ye
in three days?
Yun Yi.
Go with me to see my fiancee again.
Also,
what kind of men does she like?
She likes
muscular men.
My dear son.
When will you be here?
Ridiculous.
So ridiculous.
At such an early hour.
You are just letting people talk about
my daughter's pregnancy before marriage so freely?
Find someone
to delete the news.
Or all of you, get lost.
Here.
But how should I use
this thing?
Honey.
You must be tired lately.
I made this for you myself.
Try it.
I'm not tired.
Thank you, Honey.
Honey,
the marriage with the Feng family
is so unfair to Wanqing.
She is your biological daughter.
You don't understand.
Wanqing.
Although the Feng family is not doing well now,
they still have a solid foundation.
If the two families can be united through marriage,
it will be a good thing for us.
Did you hear that?
I didn't teach her that.
Our daughter is even better at business than you.
Thank you, Dad.
Wanqing.
Don't worry.
I have something to do in the company.
I have to go now.
Do you know why
Ye Wange's biological mother
was resented by your father
when she was alive?
Yet you still want to be a career woman?
Why do I have a daughter like you?
I'll say it again.
I respect your capability
to please men.
But I can't do that.
Ye Wange.
Relax.
How can I get pregnant
simply by time-traveling through a book?
I can't be so unlucky, can I?
God bless me.
I put it here just now.
It's here.
[I'm pregnant?]
[Pregnancy before marriage]
[Two bars]
No way.
My dear son.
Where is my son?
Where did he go?
Why is it here?
[Still not pregnant]
[No son]
[One bar]
I have to leave now.
If I don't leave now, I'll become a mother.
Are you done?
Hello.
Can you help me with this door?
You...
You're here too?
It's me.
I'm the one who carpooled with you that day.
Don't you remember?
I thought I was the only one who came in.
I didn't expect you to be here too.
Great.
It rained yesterday.
We carpooled.
You were typing on your computer in the front,
while I was reading novels in the back.
Don't you remember?
[The Low-profile Miss Ye]
This is the novel.
We're both in the plot now.
[Not available]
[The information is restricted. No reading is allowed.]
Sister.
What do you want to say?
Are you done?
Sister?
I know it's hard to accept,
but it's okay.
I've read a lot of stories like this.
It's only a matter of time for us to get out.
As long as we work together.
You don't believe me?
I do.
We are not
from the same world in the first place.
I know you don't believe me.
You can't leave.
Your gentle kiss.
Dangerous.
You have no idea?
Spicy gluten.
I bought it on Pindaodao.com.
Let's go hiking.
The Bad Kids.
Are you scared?
Since you carpooled with me,
you must work near my company.
Look at the address.
Does it look familiar to you?
[Malia Maternity Hospital]
Turns out you just want to show off to me that
you're pregnant with Feng Muchen's child.
Why did my delivery bag
turn into this?
[Malia Maternity Hospital]
Ye Wange.
Are you pregnant with a prince or a Son of Wisdom?
There's nothing to be proud about getting pregnant before marriage.
How much has Ye Family's stock dropped?
Take it seriously.
Shouldn't she be proud of
being pregnant with my baby?
Morning sickness?
Let me see the Feng family's baby.
Don't touch me.
What did you eat?
Childish.
I'm meeting with the investor tomorrow.
The client resources
and project plan you promised
must be presented to me by tomorrow.
No hurry.
I heard that the Ye's stock has dropped drastically today.
Compared to this,
isn't it more important
to solve the problem of the public opinion on Ye's marriage of business?
After all, what your investors are interested in
is your identity as the daughter of the Ye family.
Lu Wanqing.
She's the heroine of the novel, Lu Wanqing?
Ye Wange's half-sister?
Have I really mistaken her for someone else?
Then tell me,
what should I do?
What should you do?
Of course you should listen to my fiancée, Ge.
Ge,
shall we start planning
our marriage?
Help me.
I'm having some
severe pregnancy symptoms.
How about this?
You can take me out for some fresh air
and do something pleasant.
Where do you want to go?
I'll take you there.
My baby.
I finally found you.
I worked so hard to bring them back into the car.
It's the perfect timing.
Now is the time to travel back.
[Feng Muchen: Why do you only find out about the truth now?]
[Feng Muchen looks at the photos in the camera carefully.]
Why hasn't it changed?
Why is there no change at all?
Did I not act it out vividly enough?
[Century-old Street]
Stop.
The other side of this wall
is where I was born and raised.
As long as I can travel across this wall,
everything will go back to normal.
Wanqing.
Do you want to go back with me?
How can you live here alone
if I go back?
Feel free to go crazy yourself.
Why don't you get me?
I'll lose my job if I don't go back.
What job?
It's...
You won't understand.
It has nothing to do with you.
Of course it has something to do with me.
Why don't you two both hold my hands?
No.
I've had enough of you.
Feng Muchen.
Remember
what you promised me.
The wall is so hard.
If I couldn't make it across the wall,
my face will be marred, right?
Forget it.
I remember
you can travel across walls.