[Miss Ye in Wonderland]
[Episode 6]
Reeking of alcohol.
If I don't take a shower now,
I'll rot.
Come on in.
This is for you.
Anti-inflammatory and pain-relieving.
You can leave now.
I changed the water in the bathroom for you.
Go take a bath.
Tell me if you need anything.
Why is he suddenly so nice to me?
Did his conscience smite him?
I know when to yield and when not.
No matter how hard life is,
I'll still take my bath.
Flowers,
snacks,
and a bubble machine.
I didn't know
Feng Muchen is so meticulous.
Boss.
Miss Ye is taking a bath.
In my opinion,
girls should be pampered.
Pamper her?
No way.
Have you heard that
you may take pleasure in being harsh on your wife for a while,
but you'll have an incredibly hard time getting her back?
You want to go to Mars again?
No, Boss.
Master.
Be careful.
I'll take a look.
Mr. Ye, welcome.
Where are Ge and Muchen?
Miss Ye is washing up upstairs.
Boss is having lunch. He'll be here soon.
When I called him the day before yesterday,
he was not with Ge either.
Does he remember that
he has a wife?
Mr. Ye,
why are you here without notice?
the thing you told me before...
That's not important.
I'm here to see my granddaughter.
I'll get her.
Make Mr. Ye a cup of tea. Go.
Mr. Ye.
Would you like something to eat?
Grandpa.
Mr. Ye, Ge is here.
Move aside.
I miss you so much.
My darling.
Ge.
Why did you lose weight?
Lose weight?
Did he treat you badly?
No.
I'll take you to have hot pot next time.
Grandpa, have a seat.
You know me so well.
I love hot pot the best.
It's hard to have hot pot here.
Every day it's either light dishes
or western refreshments.
I'm craving for it.
Right?
Have some tea.
What is this?
Coke.
On the rocks.
Mr. Ye.
Ice cola is not healthy.
Have some hot tea.
Leave me alone.
That's right.
Life is too short. We need to enjoy it.
Go get it for him.
Yes.
Yun Yi.
Go buy it.
Thumbs-up for you.
How does he treat you?
Not bad.
Grandpa.
He even asked me for living expenses.
Mr. Ye.
Let me explain.
If you have any difficulties,
ask me for money.
Why did you ask my granddaughter?
Why would you do that?
You're right.
I'll correct my mistake right away.
Go mind your business.
OK.
Grandpa, you are the best.
Of course.
By the way,
pass me the bag.
This?
Here.
Hold this for me.
Let me show you something first.
Take a look.
Give it to me.
[Personal profile]
[Ye Fengyan]
Ye Fengyan.
My mother.
I just found out
your mother didn't die of illness in prison.
She was murdered.
Murdered?
[Luo Hao]
[Zhang Ping]
[Li Yunsheng]
What should we do then?
Look.
Find these two people as soon as possible.
[Li Yunsheng]
[Mr. Jackson]
Because they are the last ones
who your mother worked with before she died.
Also, don't tell anyone about this.
Take it.
Let me see.
[Zhang Ping]
[Li Yunsheng]
[Mr. Jackson]
Li Yunsheng.
Mr. Jackson.
There are only two names on it.
Nothing else.
Where can I find them, grandpa?
Grandpa.
Grandpa, wake up.
Grandpa, don't scare me.
What's wrong?
What happened?
Grandpa suddenly passed out.
Mr. Ye.
Grandpa, wake up.
I just closed my eyes to rest.
Why are you so nervous?
Just kidding.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
Mr. Ye, you're so humorous.
Goodbye, Grandpa.
Let me see you off.
Me too.
Mr. Ye.
Mr. Jackson.
Li Yunsheng.
They were the last ones my mother worked with.
They must know something.
But Grandpa didn't tell me where to find them.
What should I do?
Forget it. I'll make a call tomorrow.
I forgot to borrow money from Grandpa.
The dishes are ready.
Miss Ye.
There's no meat at all.
What do you know?
This is called environment-friendly.
You're back.
It's been a long day, right?
I've sent your grandpa home safely.
But it's not worth it for him to come here.
He didn't get to drink ice cola,
but could only listen to you
complaining about me.
That means I'm super cute.
Grandpa is satisfied as long as he sees me.
I've paid off
the debt on your card.
So nice.
Seems like your performance
has lived up to the green feast I specially made for you.
Try it.
It won't poison you.
Miss.
Ning Yuan, you're back at the right time.
Come and try my green feast.
Okay.
Make yourself at home.
Eat whatever you like.
How is it?
Delicious.
Great.
Eat more.
Help yourselves.
Let's eat together.
Boss, by the way, there's something
I forgot to tell you about. About the event...
Let's eat together.
You don't wanna eat?
Forget it.
They don't want to eat. Let's eat.
Let's order takeout.
No, it's delicious.
No need, Miss.
No, Miss.
It's really delicious.
It's just a little salty.
By the way,
the media has
found out the source of the candid photos.
Let me see.
Take a look.
She has been taken away for investigation.
She seems to be Lu Wanqing's friend.
I've searched the lake where you fell into the water.
There's no new clue.
Lu Wanqing and Chen Ye are the characters of the love line.
Evil step-mother
is a villain who is neither cute nor charming.
[Click to check the mission]
Grandpa is like a systematic character
who guides me through the plot.
This Little Chicken is me.
The intrigue line
should be me finding the clues of Mom's case
under Grandpa's guidance.
My love line...
Is to be a couple with Feng Muchen.
But why did Lu Wanqing
send someone to take photos to smear me?
I didn't steal Chen Ye from her.
Could it be that Chen Ye
is the key to cracking the intrigue line?
Hello.
Hello, Miss Ye.
Hello, Mr. Chen.
Chen Ye.
Miss Ye, here's the thing.
There's a dinner party of the trust industry tonight.
Mr. Li Yunsheng, a guru in trust business,
is the host.
Li Yunsheng?
Do you have time to go with me?
Chen Ye is really resourceful.
But if I agree to go with him,
I would be fighting with Lu Wanqing for Chen Ye.
Will the readers complain about me?
Miss Ye.
Miss Ye?
Thank you for your invitation.
But I'm really sorry.
I...
He's like a plaster
that I can't get rid of.
I was too abrupt.
By the way, Mr. Chen,
do you know...
I'll talk to you later. Bye.
I'm hanging up.
You're going with Chen Ye?
This is my business.
Does it have anything to do with you?
Okay.
Are you jealous?
No.
So you like such lively occasions too.
You have double standards.
If I go with you, it won't count as "showing up in public".
But if I go with someone else, it will be.
Boring.
Boss, if you don't wanna go, don't go.
You've always disliked
this kind of activity.
Mr. Ye.
Feng, thank you for sending me home yesterday.
As for tonight's dinner party,
go with Ge.
I'm worried about her going there alone.
Okay.
Boss.
Look.
This...
[Invitation letter]
Boss.
I think it's time to teach you how to court your wife.
Sometimes when being with a girl,
you can be faster and act more like a "bad boy".
How so?
You can only win her heart over if you are faster than others.
Girls always speak with a forked tongue.
I saw Miss Ye getting changed downstairs.
Guess why she isn't getting changed
in her own room?
Of course she wanted to let you see it.
While Miss Ye is choosing clothes,
you can attract her with your profession.
Teach her how to match the dress for the banquet
so that she will be impressed by you.
Come closer.
Yes.
Ning Yuan, what do you think of this dress?
Beautiful.
Compared to those dresses just now?
They're all beautiful.
Forget it.
It's useless to ask you.
Go back to your work.
I also think it's beautiful.
Boss, I'll get back to work too.
I'll give you some space.
The dresses you just tried on are no good.
You need to ask
a professional about the profession, right?
You're just a tailor.
What's to brag about?
Tailor?
I'm a fashion designer for haute couture.
Still a tailor, right?
The clothes I wear
are customized by famous designers.
What do you know?
You are just stupid and rich.
Muslin and lace need to be used cautiously.
The best material
is still silk and worsted texture.
The color should mainly be of low saturation.
High saturation can be used
to decorate locally.
This dress
is kind of approved by me,
a fashion designer for haute couture.
Go get ready.
I'll drive.
Who said I want to go with a tailor like you?
Bye.
She still doesn't understand
the difference between haute couture designers and tailors.
Stupid.
Thank you for picking me up, Mr. Chen.
Miss Ye, you're welcome.
Miss Ye, if I'm not mistaken,
this dress
is the designer's dress in the spring series
of Ye's fashion week this year.
Yes.
Since you know Ye's clothing so well,
have you worked with my mother?
You flatter me, Miss Ye.
Ye's is the top in the industry.
Unfortunately,
I haven't had a chance to work with your mother.
Be careful.
I have an appointment with the media.
Excuse me.
Friends from the media, this way please.
Indeed a business star.
Such massive turnout.
Wait.
He has my invitation letter.
Hello, Miss Ye.
Miss Su, we'll leave if there's nothing else.
Hello, Miss Su.
So distant.
It's only been six months since I went abroad.
You haven't forgotten about me, have you?
[1 Su Yinyin is the Su family's only daughter.]
[2 A tomboy]
[3 Ye Wange's best friend, Su Yinyin]
[Su Yinyin]
[Personality: Gallant]
[Nature: Cool girl on motorcycle]
Of course not.
It's just I haven't seen you for a long time.
I missed you so much.
But I'm glad you're back.
Finally, I have someone to talk to.
So the people who video-called you
is a fake person?
By the way, do you have the invitation letter to go in there?
[Invitation letter]
Indeed my bestie.
Let's go.
OK.
Please be quiet.
Welcome to the business dinner party
hosted by me, Li Yunsheng.
So he is Li Yunsheng.
To show my sincerity,
I'm specially presenting this painting by Picasso
that I recently collected here.
I hope you can enjoy
appreciating it.
Hello, where are you?
We're here too.
Come here.
Who is it?
I promise it's the person you're looking forward to meeting the most.
Miss Ye, what can I do for you?
Do you need my help?
Why is it you?
Who needs your help?
Uncle Li.
You're here, Wanqing.
I had afternoon tea with your mother yesterday
and mentioned you.
Wange is here too.
It's my honor
to have both of you here today.
He really knows my family well.
Uncle Li, you're welcome.
I heard that this painting is rarely shown in public.
And I heard there's some special connection between it
and Miss Ye Wange.
You two are highborn.
Ge, you are also a collector of this painting.
I'm sure you have a unique understanding.
Why don't you share it
so that we can learn more about it?
How's that?
I'm sorry, but I don't know much about this painting.
You really don't remember this painting?
This is a world-famous painting.
How could I not remember?
This is your mother's favorite painting
when she was alive.
You really don't remember?
It's just that I have too many paintings at home.
I may not remember this particular one.
Is Li Yunsheng related to my mom
because of this painting?
It suddenly occurred to me that
I forgot something.
Excuse me.
So, Shen Lingzhu sold my mom's painting
to Li Yunsheng?
Since Lu Wanqing could tell that I didn't know,
why did she tell me?
Is it out of justice?
The main character should have the sense of justice.
Good for you, Little Ye.
I'm leaving now.
See you at the bar later.
Doughnuts, I'm coming.
What a coincidence. You're hungry too.
I haven't got even with you yet.
Did you
make a fool of me on stage on purpose just now?
You're so ungrateful.
I finally decided to help you.
That painting is your mother's collection.
Your mother had to sell it to Li Yunsheng
because her business had some problems.
I wanted to avenge your mother on stage.
I didn't expect that you didn't know about this.
So I misunderstood you?
Take it as an apology.
Eat.
I forgive you.
Since I've provided you
with such important information,
and I did you such a big favor,
shouldn't you feed me till I'm full?
Hello, everyone.
Everyone, this is
a stable low-risk investment project.
Eat by yourself.
You can collect the principal anytime.
And it's mainly invested by the banks.
My investment concept is different from others.
I don't pursue high return rate.
I only promise you that
you'll get a fixed 10% interest every year.
10%?
High risk again.
It comes with high risks.
If you want to make big money fast,
you should invest in stocks.
It seems that the author
has a friend
who's the victim of P2P.
Can you give me a chance?
My project is not short of investment.
I don't know if everyone can invest.
It's hard for me to decide now.
How about this?
Wait for my reply, okay?
Playing hard to get.
Mr. Li, may I have your number?
Sure.
Listen to me.
I know many of you
know the risk of doing this,
and you know the meaning of this kind of deal
is to keep recruiting people to join you.
But I hope you can understand
as long as this kind of capital deals like passing the parcel
exist,
there will be victims.
Please think twice
before you do it.
Miss Ye.
I didn't expect
that you are already quite like your mom
at such a young age.
My respect.
Just so-so.