♪Flowers falling by the river again♪
♪Turning the clear waves red♪
♪Sparrows singing in celebration♪
♪Calm years pass by the silent bustling city♪
♪Sitting at home♪
♪No one knows love's outline like I do♪
♪If one day the river breeze blows again♪
♪I won't be a mere reflection in the mirror♪
♪Dreams can shatter; Memories remain♪
♪Rich fragrance aids; Light ink writes♪
♪In the deep red windows lies mundane dust♪
=Are You The One=
=Episode 21=
Zhen.
Lord Zhao.
He is someone worthy of lifelong commitment.
You should cherish this opportunity.
Don't act pretentiously in the future.
Don't defy your husband.
Is marrying him
the only way I can repay my family?
Everything I did and tried
before
was never appreciated.
In your eyes,
the only way out
for me
is to marry Lord Zhao, right?
Yes.
Only this way.
Zhen.
Where are you going?
Coming.
Coming, coming.
Miss He.
After these months,
you've lost lots of weight.
I left abruptly that day
and didn't leave a note.
Will you blame me?
I was wrong at first.
It's my fault for saying that
out of the bad mood.
Alright.
Let's call it even.
Never bring it up again.
Alright?
What kind of pattern is it?
It's so unique.
A golden lantern flower,
also called heartless grass.
Heartless?
While the leaves are still there,
the flower hasn't bloomed.
When the flower blooms,
the leaves have withered.
The flower and leaves never meet.
They are both indifferent
and heartless.
Madam,
why are you suddenly stitching this?
I find it interesting
in "Youyang Novels".
It says this flower
often blooms in the homes of villains.
Nanny Li, have you seen it?
I'm not a villain.
How could I have seen it?
What a sin.
Miss He?
Ms. Liu.
What's wrong with you today?
I...
I have a friend
whose brain was damaged
by a fever as a child.
She lost her memory.
She denied her real mom
but mistook the maid for her mother.
The maid took advantage of her ignorance
to gain benefits from the family.
I wanted to tell my friend the truth,
but everyone stopped me,
telling me not to meddle.
I feel distressed.
Miantang.
Do you understand how I feel?
How could it be?
Her real mother
is right there.
She won't let the maid harm her.
It's probably just to amuse your friend.
You're worrying too much.
The stitching is indeed too rough.
I'll just take it apart and redo it.
It has come to this.
Why are you still...
I'll take it apart
to escape
from the current situation
and start over.
I originally did it for fun.
But gradually,
it felt wrong.
Now,
I'll take it all apart
and sew a pattern that I like
and that is auspicious.
Miss He,
what do you think?
Good.
Don't stitch the grass.
Stitch what you like.
Aunt.
Drink this calming soup
and rest early.
Getting angry harms the spleen.
You still have to oversee the rites tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
It's also me who lacks the ability
to hold Xingzhou's heart.
This child
has always been determined.
Once he makes a decision,
even I, his mother,
cannot stop him.
Among all virtues,
filial piety comes first.
Common people lose their reputations
for not being filial.
And officials
lose their positions.
Let alone a lord.
So many eyes in the court
are watching Xingzhou.
You cannot ignore this
and give others excuses.
Do you mean...?
I have a plan to make amends.
But...
Tell me.
Aunt.
Tomorrow, when you go to Liuming Temple
to oversee the rites,
I'll accompany you.
At that time,
with the people and officials
of Zhenzhou present,
you can publicly recognize me
as your daughter-in-law.
Thus,
this marriage will be known to everyone.
Everything's set.
Xingzhou won't be able to back out.
(Zhenzhou)
The certificate.
Go.
- Go.
- Let's go.
The Consort Dowager's procession has set off.
It's in vain.
The madam has arranged for a carriage.
It should also be heading
towards Liuming Temple.
She does like lively scenes.
What if they run into each other?
Huang Gui.
My Lord.
Tighten the city's defenses to prevent bandits
from mixing in.
Rest assured.
Aside from the Taoist priests,
no one else came in.
Where's the roster?
It's quite tricky.
What's tricky?
The level of realism in the fake certificates
is quite sophisticated.
But they don't know
that Liuming Temple,
as a major Taoist institution,
altered the characters on the prayer scroll
to advise Emperor Wen of the previous dynasty.
(Liuming Temple)
"Liu" is shortened,
and "Ming" is slightly elongated.
It symbolizes less transience
and more clarity.
Emperor Wen was enlightened
and rewarded Liuming Temple.
This practice has been passed down since then.
I've been negligent.
Moru.
Prepare the regular clothes. Let's go.
Yes.
Has the madam arrived?
Not yet.
When did she set off?
She left early this morning.
Order the guards to protect
the Consort Dowager.
Yes.
Nanny Li.
Stop the carriage at the street entrance.
Aren't we going to Liuming Temple?
Didn't you say
Liuming Temple would be crowded today,
smoky,
with ruffians and thieves?
Yes.
Let's follow your suggestion
and not go today.
That's great.
When we reach the street market ahead,
Nanny, buy a bass for me.
I'll go to get some tonic medicine
for my husband.
Madam,
isn't it better if we stay together?
There are so many people today.
If anything happens,
it will be hard to explain to the master.
If we get to the fresh fish market late,
the remaining fish won't be fresh.
I'll wait for you at the pharmacy.
What could happen?
Just come find me as soon as you're done.
Alright, alright.
Sir,
check if you have these.
Sure.
Do you have fine antlers?
Yes.
It looks like business is booming today.
Please get all these
tonic prescriptions ready.
I won't delay your big sale.
You're right.
Please wait a moment.
We have everything you need.
Madam, I'll prepare
the medicine for you right away.
Please wait a moment.
- Sister.
Lu Zhong, Lu Yi.
Sister, Uncle Qiao has told us
everything.
How do you want
Lord Huaiyang to die?
If we hadn't changed the location today,
I would've killed him
in Liuming Temple.
The time isn't right.
We must be cautious.
Avoid the dangerous wall.
On the Shangsi Festival,
where were you that night
when I went missing?
That night,
Lu Yi and I discovered a group of ambushers.
We managed to drive them off.
We returned and found out
you were missing.
I tried to ask Mr. Ziyu,
but Sun Yun'er stopped me.
She told me you
had decided to leave and wouldn't return.
Ghosts are more reliable than her.
Later, Mount Yang became hers.
There was no place for us.
We had to go to Beizhou to find Uncle Qiao
and search for you.
If you want to avenge,
listen carefully to what I say.
Master.
Where is Madam?
Madam and Nanny Li left early this morning.
If I couldn't stand it,
I would speak out.
The medicine he sold
to Butcher Li's wife
was mostly common herbs,
except for one or two,
but he charged her double.
If he dares to cheat me,
I'll make sure Butcher Li knows about it.
Butcher Li
is a tough character,
a bully in the market.
If Madam truly wants
to tell him,
it's enough to make
the shopkeeper suffer.
What a sin.
Honey, why are you back?
Honey.
What happened?
The Lord asked me to take half a day off,
so I came back to check.
Yesterday, you mentioned Liuming Temple.
I thought you had gone there.
I was going to,
but Nanny Li kept saying
it was too crowded
and might lead to trouble.
I thought it made sense,
so I changed direction to the market.
On the battlefield,
you risked your life.
You must be exhausted.
You need to recuperate.
I bought a bass
that was just caught today.
It's very fresh.
How considerate of you.
Praying for the deceased soldiers
shows compassion.
Taking care of the living
is also important.
Dear, I'll speak frankly.
A villain has entered Zhenzhou.
Have you seen any
suspicious men?
Suspicious men?
Why would they come to me?
Did you see anyone
dressed as a Taoist priest?
Why would a Taoist priest not be
in the temple chanting
and wander around instead?
Dear.
This matter is very important.
Think carefully.
Honey.
Sounds like you're interrogating me.
I'm not interrogating you.
You returned in such a panic
only to check if I was being unruly.
Nonsense.
Just chatting.
When you lie,
you always avoid my eyes.
Dear.
It's really just chatting.
I was afraid of the villain,
so I came back to check on you.
What?
Honey,
are you afraid I'll be taken by them?
Don't worry.
Our family is now
under Lord Huaiyang's protection.
What villain would dare act?
That would be ignoring
Lord Huaiyang.
You're right, dear.
Master.
Lord Huaiyang sent word
that the rites had ended
and he had already left.
He wants you to visit him.
Then you should go quickly.
Don't keep the Lord waiting.
If we lose
the Lord's protection,
and villains come again,
you might really lose me.
Alright, dear.
I'll go now.
Mother.
Two villains disguised as Taoists
and broke into Zhenzhou today.
I went to investigate,
which delayed the blessing time.
I hope you'll forgive me.
Sit down.
Yes.
This is peony stamens.
Binglan
saw I looked unwell
and brought it to me.
Today,
I was alone in charge
at Liuming Temple.
With the sudden villain trouble,
my frail body
could hardly endure it.
Fortunately, Binglan helped me,
so I didn't
lose the family's face
in front of the people.
She helped me
and also helped you.
You must remember this favor.
Today,
I planned to recognize Binglan as your fiancee
and have you reconcile with her.
What do you think?
It seems you're still thinking
about that mistress.
Mother, I've said it before.
She is not a mistress.
I don't need to know who she is.
Binglan has already stepped back.
She said
if you truly favor
that Liu woman,
she will give her face
and support you properly.
What more do you want her to do?
You're a lord.
You knew villains in the temple,
yet you were absent from your mother
and the people.
You ran off to a place
of leisure on North Street.
Isn't that absurd?
I can
overlook all this.
But you must promise me today
to marry Binglan.
Mother.
For today's matter,
it is true that I was at fault.
There are other reasons behind this.
I will explain it to you later.
As for the engagement,
please forgive me.
I will only marry Liu Miantang.
What are you saying?
I, Cui Xingzhou,
will only marry Liu Miantang in this life.
You scoundrel!
Scoundrel!
Madam.
Honey.
I came to fetch your changed clothes.
Why are you injured?
It's nothing.
Let me apply medicine.
Does it hurt a lot?
Yes.
This person is rough.
But don't worry.
It wasn't the villain who hurt me.
The Lord
punished me.
How can the Lord treat his soldiers so harshly?
Perhaps he is in a bad mood.
I heard he fell out
with the Consort Dowager.
The Consort Dowager
matched him with a well-suited marriage,
but the Lord's heart
belongs to another woman.
It's chilly today.
A warm soak is good for your health.
Honey,
the villain you mentioned earlier.
Was he a remnant of Mount Yang?
Why do you suddenly ask about this?
I'm just curious.
After all,
I once fell into their hands.
I heard from the neighbors
that the leader of Mount Yang
had surrendered to the court.
So, they are
no longer Zhenzhou's enemies.
Mount Yang no longer causes chaos.
Those unwilling to surrender
have scattered.
Why do you keep mentioning Mount Yang?
Zhenzhou is not lacking.
It takes vigilance to stave off evil.
The Lord has won against them many times.
Many times?
How many times?
Honey,
who do you think
is stronger, Lord Huaiyang
or the Mount Yang leader?
It's hard to say
who is stronger between them.
On the Shangsi Festival,
at the ritual, the lighting
should've brought a truce.
But the Mount Yang leader
attacked Lord Huaiyang.
The leader attacked?
Yes.
The Lord didn't expect
that the leader, who always kept his promises,
would break his word
and attack him while the soldiers
were resting.
The Lord was furious
and tried every means to defeat him
and heavily harm Mount Yang,
but the leader then vanished.
The Lord tried to capture him,
wanting not only to defeat him
but also to ask him in person
why he broke the agreement.
Later,
Mount Yang surrendered,
and the Lord
completely lost the chance
to settle things with him.
Honey.
I want to go to Mount Yang.
Why?
I want to clear the demons in my heart.
Do you remember anything?
At the Shangsi night years ago,
I had not yet
married you.
My family was
on Ling Mountain outside Xizhou City,
viewing the scenery
and making wishes through sky lanterns.
The open terrain here
would make the sky lanterns
look very beautiful.
Indeed.
On Shangsi night,
sky lanterns
accompanied by the blooming mountain flowers
are quite magnificent.
Did Lord Huaiyang tell you this as well?
With the sky lanterns in the air,
if the villain attacked,
he would be easily spotted.
How could there be an ambush?
Lord Huaiyang is so smart.
Could he be lying to you?
Along the way,
we walked through a section
of collapsed mountain road.
Do you remember?
It used to be
the only way up the mountain.
On Shangsi night,
Lord Huaiyang
camped right there.
The soldiers were making wine,
temporarily letting down their guard.
That day,
they had agreed to a ceasefire.
But with the sky lanterns,
the soldiers waited
for a horde of fierce Mount Yang bandits
to break into their camp.
It seems
Lord Huaiyang wasn't lying.
In fact, he's not good at lying.
Miantang.
Since returning to Zhenzhou,
I've been uneasy.
I always feel like I'm going to lose you.
Haven't I always been by your side?
I know.
That's why I plan
to tell you everything.
Everything?
What do you mean?
Master!
What's wrong?
Master, Madam.
The army
says you need to return.
Tomorrow is the Little New Year.
Remember to go home.
I thought I could rest.
Work is important.
You have two letters.
One is from the capital.
The other is from Beizhou.
Anything else?
Your mother is ill.
They want you to return quickly.
Miss.
The hidden agents at Mount Yang
found Liu Miantang and Lord Huaiyang.
What was she doing at Mount Yang?
It seems she was just climbing the mountain.
But the agent found
that Liu Miantang left this behind.
Miss.
Is this a Mount Yang mark?
I don't quite understand it.
This mark isn't for you and me.
You wouldn't understand.
In five days,
at noon,
at Youyu Cave?
I'm going to Mount Yang.
The firewood is damp
and won't catch fire.
It's just a spring rain.
It went afar to avoid it
but still got soaked.
How useless.
Do you remember when you were young,
you and your cousin, Qingying,
used to argue?
Even at a young age,
you learned from the opera
to sever the ties,
but when she was
bullied on the road,
you were the first to step in.
Your grandfather used to say
you appear
tough on the outside,
but you're softer
than anyone inside.
I said
I came here to rid myself of the mental demons.
Your demons
are also mine.
Yes.
I once
wanted to reclaim everything from before
because it concerned us.
Honey,
we've weathered so many storms together.
Perhaps what we have now
is even better than the years we lost.
What I want to say
might surprise you.
If you intend to say
anything that breaks this happiness,
then I don't want to hear it.
A couple
always has secrets, doesn't it?
If you truly feel regret,
then keep deceiving me for a lifetime.
Don't hide half of it
and then falter, revealing it.
You would feel better,
but I, as a woman,
would have to bear
this burden.
Is that truly how you feel?
Yes.
So don't tell me.
I beg you.
Honey.
I haven't said thank you to you yet.
No matter what,
without you,
I might have been gone
from this world long ago.
From now on,
if Mount Yang is mentioned,
this is the only thing I will remember.
If you recall
everything later,
you can always
do what you think
is right.
Soft-hearted?
I admit.
I did
have a slimmer of hope.
I thought
perhaps he was also used
by Lord Huaiyang.
Maybe he had no choice.
Only in this way
could I justify
my soft-heartedness.
If you...
Anyway, he's going to marry you.
Marry me?
What he wants to marry is not me,
but the canary he has raised.
The woman who only
has eyes for him.
It's just his delusion.
The deeper his feelings,
the more ironic and ridiculous it seems.
I've played this self-deceiving role
enough.
So I won't be soft-hearted anymore.
Mother, you're awake.
Wake up for what?
I might as well sleep it off,
so everyone could get peace.
My Lord, Consort Dowager.
Time for the medicine.
My Lord.
You haven't slept all night.
You should rest early.
It's fine. Leave.
If you really can't let her go,
I can step back
and let her become a concubine.
Is she so good
that you'd throw away the reputation
of the entire family?
How many concubines did Father have?
Ten?
Twenty?
How many mistresses
are unknown to us?
What?
Are you using
your father as a shield?
He made a fuss.
Do you want to follow his example?
Mother,
the life here is rich and luxurious,
but it's full of scheming
and indifference.
I know you haven't had
an easy time these years.
I haven't, either.
I always thought
that if I restrained myself
and didn't indulge in love,
even if it's just to respect each other,
I wouldn't let
my wife and child suffer.
Mother.
For her,
I pretended to be an ordinary commoner
in a small household
struggling for a living,
burdened with countless trivial worries.
But she didn't seem to feel troubled.
She lived freely and unrestrained.
All she wished for us
was to be united as a couple
for a lifetime.
Only then did I realize
how terribly wrong I was.
Happiness and joy
must be earned with a true heart.
But I let her down
and overestimated myself.
Mother,
please forgive my unfiliality.
I don't want any more
mutual respect
or noble concubines.
With all the marital rites,
in this life,
she's the only one I want.
(Lu Wen left the capital, went west,
and didn't step into Zhenzhou.)
Not Lu Wen.
(Bai's Pharmacy)
Madam, why are you buying these medicines?
Wasn't my husband injured a few days ago?
It's all bruised.
It's nothing.
We still have plenty of fine
medicines from Physician Zhao.
These are remedies from Mrs. Yin.
You wouldn't know.
Madam.
What's wrong?
There's one more thing I need.
Master.
Where is Madam?
She went to the market with Nanny Li.
Should I go find her?
Knowing your return,
Madam will be pleased.
Hurry and go.
Yes.
Forgive me.
Please clarify this.
Madam, you're back.
Why are you standing here?
Where's my husband?
He didn't sleep all night,
so he took leave from the deputy.
He's resting now.
Then I'll go see him.
Honey.
Dear.
I thought
you were already asleep.
I did lie down,
but I couldn't fall asleep.
I might as well read a book.
What book are you reading?
A good strategist
would take the initiative.
Void and Actuality.
The Art of War?
Since you joined the army,
you've changed a lot.
You read military strategy
as if it were light reading.
I found it casually
and just skimmed through.
It's the Little New Year,
yet you had to take leave.
The army is really unreasonable.
Others
don't have the privilege I have
to return home at night
and have dinner with their wife.
Alright.
Are you going to keep lying down
or come with me to the kitchen?
I'm going to cook today.
I'm indeed a bit tired.
Sure.
I'll wake you up later.
Okay.
Dear,
is there crab roe rice?
What are you thinking?
At this time of year,
there's no crab roe.
True.
♪The boat drifts,
bringing back the sunset♪
♪When we reunite, we still joke
about the cause and effect♪
♪Who passed by, the crabapple
falls with a turn♪
♪Loving rightly but choosing wrong♪
♪With joys, sorrows, partings and reunions♪
♪Everyone travels far, seeing clouds and snow♪
♪Always hard to stay, yet easy to part♪
♪Crossing spring waters and autumn trials♪
♪A couple under the moonlight,
can stay together♪
♪Long hidden in the eyes,
flickering in and out♪
♪Let go of the flowers blooming
in the yard last night♪
♪Let go of the waves in the stream
in half a lifetime♪
♪Let those dust and chaos go on endlessly♪
♪In this lifetime, my wish is to the vast sky♪
♪There are many more♪
♪Everyone travels far, seeing clouds and snow♪
♪Always hard to stay, yet easy to part♪
♪Crossing spring waters and autumn trials♪
♪A couple under the moonlight,
can stay together♪
♪Time flows as we dream through four seasons♪
♪I wish to journey with you forever♪
♪Year after year♪
♪For many years to come♪