♫  No longer panicking on the night of the blackout  ♫
♫  You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me  ♫
♫  Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet  ♫
♫  Your breath brushes up against my cheek   ♫
♫  With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close  ♫
♫  Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner  ♫
♫  Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves  ♫
♫  Happiness and sadness  ♫
♫  Make up the moments of life  ♫
♫  Rainy days become very special because of you  ♫
♫  Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street  ♫
♫  No matter when and where, you always appear  ♫
♫  Holding me tightly and spinning in circles  ♫
♫  Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you  ♫
♫  Becoming some part of the memories  ♫
♫  Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another  ♫
♫  Warming up the whole world  ♫
So you two were together before?
Absolutely not!
We were purely classmates.
That's where it ends.
- Also, regarding the photo—
- I know about the photo.
It's obvious that that was a positioning trick.
I have such a smart brain. Of course, I can think of that.
So is being afraid of water also like this?
Being afraid of water was all thanks to my eldest brother.
As long as you're by my side, I'll be very at ease.
After Johnny's group of people changed jobs last time,
they left with the SA system that we were developing.
Fit is preparing to hit the market and they are about to release the SA system with improvements.
If they succeed in releasing it, then our technology will
be worthless in the market.
Most of Ling Fang's money was invested in Fangyu Construction.
Things like research and development cannot successfully be completed in such short periods of time.
Where did he get so many launch funds?
The major shareholders behind Fit are part of the company. I really don't understand.
Why must these major shareholders invest in Fit?
Looks like they're determined to follow Ling Fang.
Ling Fang must've promised those people that they would get high benefits in return,
and they made the preparations to divide New Way's dividends.
Come on. We're going to Fangyu Construction.
Okay.
Uncles, don't worry. I won't disappoint your hopes.
Then we'll all rely on you, Director Ling Fang.
You scared me to death!
W-Why did you stand behind me without making noise?
If you don't usually do any guilt-inducing things, what would you have to fear?
I'm happy today. I won't hold it against you.
This time, you really used a merciless move. The two-pronged approach.
Not only did you inflict a heavy blow on New Way, you also took the opportunity to rope in many major shareholders.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Using Ling Group's money to block off New Way's survival route
is really a good method.
What do you think will happen once Dad finds out?
Then tell him.
Haven't you always been a crybaby who only knew how to tattle anyway?
Let me put it this way. Even if he did find out, things will be fine.
It's a perfect chance for him to see how I, Ling Fang, can support some random
company and still easily replace your New Way that you put all of your efforts into.
Didn't you always say that only e-commerce
and technology can represent the future of the Ling Group?
I'll let you see what the future is really going to look like.
You're always so impatiently trying to defeat me.
- What exactly do you want to prove?
- To prove that I'm the only successor to Ling Group
while you're nothing.
Don't you fear that your excessive greed will land you in a self-made mess?
All of this was originally mine!
You just got a share of it toward the middle!
You have the face to say I'm the greedy one? Ridiculous.
What consequences?
What consequences? What consequences?
I think you are just calling the grapes sour because you have no way of getting to them.
Then I hope your wish comes true, Eldest Brother.
- Seriously, why doesn't this brat have any feelings of anxiety?
- Exactly.
He's making me quite unhappy.
Is everything prepared?
Don't let him get another chance.
He's a gecko who pokes into every nook and cranny.
Don't worry, everything has been prepared.
Let's go.
Nana, Jiejie, Beibei, and Xiao Chi, tell the people from your department to have a meeting with me.
- Okay.
This time, the invasion of hackers caused the company a severe loss and the leakage of multiple important documents.
The company is now making arrangements to recover them.
The amount recovered is... less than 35%.
In terms of abilities, we have two groups who have applied for resignation.
We need to arrange effective people immediately to get into those positions.
Are you trying to murder me?
I was... was practicing.
Practicing?
Why did you come?
Your delivery girl is here to send you shrimp.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Let's go.
Very fresh grilled shrimp
paired with the citrus oolong
is truly amazing.
Do you smell the deliciousness?
What is it?
Could it be that you've never eaten grilled shrimp before?
Give it a try. Give it a try and you'll know. It's really tasty. Come on.
I'll demonstrate for you.
Remove the head and the tail.
Give it a try. Fine, let me do it.
I don't think this shrimp is ready for someone to eat yet.
How is it? Is it tasty?
Put on the gloves. Here.
Is it tasty?
Your delivery girl has accomplished her mission today.
I won't disturb you from working. I'll get going first.
- Let me send you.
- No need, I can go back myself.
No. Wait for me here. Let me go wash my hands.
I'll come back soon. Wait for me.
Don't worry, I'm here.
I won't hog up your time, Overtime-Working Dog.
Hurry and finish so you can come and look for me.
Gu Xin'er, long time no see.
This is the rich daughter of the Gu family.
She gets on the Hot Search quite often.
Isn't she the one who has recently been in rumors with New Way's president?
Isn't that true, Xin'er?
What's going on with you and the second young master of the Ling family?
See, the two of you can be considered childhood sweethearts.
Why did he personally come out to deny this issue with you?
I heard you're getting married. Congrats.
Surely it isn't the Master Chen that we took back our investment from?
How could it be? I dumped him long ago.
My fiancé is Chairman Qin's son.
Turns out that it's the VIP golf managing Chairman Qin's son. Impressive.
Since you and Young Master Qin are getting married, I'll have to trouble you with persuading him.
It's been more than two years. Stop sending me flowers every single day.
I don't want our company's cleaning staff to do
useless cleaning every day.
You're spouting nonsense! It must've been you who seduced him!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Auntie, this fairy sister already said
it was your fiancé who kept pestering her wishfully.
Then, please go back and control your man properly.
Stop splashing others in public.
Make it clear, who's an auntie?
How did you know I was here?
Looks I need to post more cautiously in the future.
Then your fans won't be happy.
Thanks for today.
But at this time, the art exhibition should be closed already.
It's fine, there's always next time.
However, there seems to be a livehouse near here
just about to start operation.
Wait for me. I'm going to purchase the tickets right now!
How are things?
Don't worry. Everything has been prepared.
There are still three hours left before Fit's ceremony starts.
Is there any movement from New Way?
Nothing much.
Seems like my younger brother is trapped in a warm and cozy place and can't come out.
Director Ling, your diversion tactic was so wise.
Let me ask you. Is Ling Yue
going to be unable to save this hopeless situation?
He will be unable.
Am I handsome?
Handsome.
Let's go to Fit.
Hello?
Now?
- Boss.
- What is it? Speak.
Fit just received a legal notice.
What do you mean?
On the basis of stealing trade secrets, New Way just filed a lawsuit with the Disputes Department.
So suddenly?
Block off the news. Fit must join the market as normal.
What's that expression? Say it!
I'm afraid there's no way. It happened too suddenly.
The shareholders of the company seem to have already received the news.
They are selling Fit's stocks at a low price.
These impatient old men.
Just a lawyer's note made them unable to hold back.
It seems that the shareholders received an email last night.
It contained the turnover sales data of Fit.
They're saying we're giving everyone empty checks and
that the promised growth rate is very hard to achieve.
Immediately buy all those circulating shares back. Do you hear me?
Yes.
Enter!
President Ling.
I'm afraid you can't buy your shares back.
What do you mean?
Do you think Fangyu Construction can't afford it?
For now, let's not talk about whether you can afford it.
The more important thing is whether I'm willing to sell them to you.
What does it have to do with him?
It was you.
Let go! Let go!
Call security!
Are you afraid of a woman?
Look, Director Ling, even if security comes, they won't  be able to beat her.
This isn't that simple.
Why do I feel like I got tricked?
Did you plan it a long time ago?
Eldest Brother, did you think I didn't know you've been coveting New Way for a long time?
My car accident was also a part of your plan.
Stalling me so Fit could rise easily.
You would even have time to take away my team and steal New Way's core technology.
You've known for a long time?
You did it on purpose!
In order to mess me up, you even dared to give me your own company's core technology so easily. You're really cruel!
But you think you won?
Let's see how long your company can last without the core technology.
I am still Fit's biggest shareholder!
Do you think that by taking away my team,
taking away the SA system,
New Way would collapse?
Actually, I need to thank you.
I always thought New Way's personnel was redundant. It's all thanks to you
for helping me do some staff reduction.
I've always invested in new students inside and outside the country
to carry out fully automated technology research and development.
So far, it has been very effective and ready to enter the construction phase.
So that SA semi-automatic system
was nothing more than an illusion you created?
Originally, it wasn't.
It's just that you allowed me to advance my plans. That's it.
If it weren't for your premature greed,
maybe you wouldn't have lost so much today.
Also, if you keep being so greedy,
you will sooner or later be swallowed by your ambition.
Either way, you won.
You get to have all the cool talk.
Damn.
D-D-Director Ling, are you okay?
Hello. Chairman Liu.
No, it is definitely not like what the rumors say.
Our boss...
He isn't here. Yes. He coincidentally left the country a few days ago.
Yes, yes.
Boss, what do we do?
Right now, all the shareholders are looking for you.
What can we do?
Let me think about it.
I will not be seeing a single person who comes to see me in the next few days.
Okay.
Hello. Director Zhu.
By the way, President Ling, the Dispute Department needs new evidence.
No need.
I understand.
All these resumes didn't get any response, like rocks sinking into the ocean.
Being corporate livestock sure is hard.
Don't be anxious. I haven't found a job either.
If you really can't do it, just go back and be the president's wife.
Or inherit the president's family business. It's not bad either.
Look at you going again. It's not like you don't know.
Look over there.
Let me tell you.
That person has been taking selfies ever since we sat down.
Isn't he far too narcissistic?
With his looks, even if he opened skin smoothing and beauty filters,
- it still wouldn't be good enough to warrant this kind of picture-taking.
- Manager Zhao.
Someone you know?
Stop pretending.
I know you have been observing me for a long time.
Waiter, give me a glass of white water.
Are you looking for a job?
- Yes.
- Consider
- coming to my company.
- Your company?
Yes. I've resigned recently, and I'm preparing to start my own company.
I just met an author,
but I think his price offering was rather expensive,
so I'm still thinking it over.
Doesn't he just want to jump ship but can't find any jobs?
Your voice was a little too loud.
Great. Manager Zhao has great courage!
Just call me Zhao Lei.
Manager Zhao, why don't you consider our Anxin as your business partner?
Our Anxin is a super webcomic master.
Webcomic master?
No, she's speaking nonsense. I'm not any kind of webcomic master. I'm just a
rookie who likes to draw mangas. That's all.
What's your ID then?
The Northwest Watches Chang'an.
Excuse me, I couldn't hold it in the moment.
I'll do it myself!
Your lipstick doesn't seem to be very waterproof.
Apply Armani lipstick and l will smear it all over your face so you can see how you like it.
Don't, don't. I haven't had any intention of setting foot into the beauty circle lately.
The Northwest Watches Chang'an? I have always been your fan.
Really? You've seen my work?
Of course!
Not long ago, I had been following "Accidentally Picking Up a Prince,"
but not long after, it stopped uploading. I was sad about it for a long time.
Why aren't you updating it anymore?
Y-Y-You can join my workplace.
You only need to invest in the copyrights.
So this job is...
just the two of us?
Our office will expand very quickly.
How about including my good friend Youyou, too?
Her sketches are super smooth.
Really?
Brother, how is it?
Not bad. You have some talent.
But who is this?
Mike. He's just an idol.
Most of his drawings are done by Youyou.
I don't know him, but it's fine.
Then, Miss Youyou, are you willing to join our workplace?
I'll consider it.
Don't consider it.
You can't find a job anyway. Let's just do it together.
How do you know I can't find a job?
Would anyone who could find work be like you two?
Just chatting in a cafe in the middle of a workday?
How about it?
Fine. Count me in.
Then, what's our company called?
Galaxy Cool Man!
- All finished.
- Nice!
Isn't it still slightly crooked?
It's not crooked. The logo I designed is supposed to be a bit tilted like this.
- That's right, it's fine.
- Isn't it nice?
- Let's go take a look inside.
- Go, go.
- It's drawn quite well.
Look!  How is it?
- The new renovation cost quite a big sum of money.
- It's not bad.
The photos are rather nice.
I was diligent, okay?
Right, Anxin, that's your spot.
This is the CEO's spot, mine. Youyou, just sit there.
Why am I here?
- Because you're close to the door and can easily get the takeout.
- It's fine.
Right, we can put a sofa there and hang up a poster here.
- I think it's a bit empty here.
- Yes.
Who is here? Who is here?
Why are you here?
Boss, can you let me work here?
Don't block me.
This person is totally senseless. Come, help me to tidy up.
Don't stop me from looking! I'm getting some eye candy!
Yes, food and housing are included, but no salary.
When do I sign the contract?
Let's go get some food.
Why did you bring an umbrella?
It's going to rain today.
It's going to rain? How could there be rain when there's so much sun?
Don't you check the weather report?
The weather report is often inaccurate so I never look at it.
Then let's just say it's accurate today.
I planned ahead. Is there a reward for me?
They're looking.
Now it's okay.
♫  The first time I met you, I never would've believed there would come a day  ♫
- Let's go.
- Let's go!
♫  You are full of coldness. No way to get near  ♫
♫  Prepare for Plan B at any moment  ♫
Anxin, someone delivered warmth again.
Quick! Look at what it is.
Stop gossiping. Come help me calculate the costs.
A ball?
The weather is sunny today. The average temperature is 22°C.
The temperate at night is 18°C.
Please wear more clothes to prevent catching a cold.
Turns out it's a smart sphere.
It will be named Xiao Liu in the future, and you are Xiao Ba.
(T/N: Little Six and Little Eight respectively)
It's named Xiao Liu, so it's a perfect match.
My CP is supposed to be with you!
(T/N: Slang for Couple Pairing)
You know what "CP" means? Have you been studying behind my back?
I know much more than you think.
Nonsense. Do you still remember that you burned my microwave?
You're not down-to-earth at all.
Down-to-earth? Just wait.
It's 12:00 noon now. Time for lunch.
Eat your lunch on time so that you will have good health.
Why are you as talkative as Ling Yue?
What happens if I don't eat lunch? Can you see me?
Not eating on time can cause gastritis, stomach ulcers, and indigestion.
It will also reduce cerebral function and affect cerebral development.
- Moreover, it will also lead to a decline in intelligence—
- I'm going. Stop talking.
Eat!
Is no one going to help me change the water?
P-President Ling.
It's done.
What's going on?
Are the materials prepared?
Yes.
Can we get them back?
If this continues...
I will have nothing and no prospects in the future.
- It's a swift and violent collapse.
- That's right.
If this is the case, there won't be any future prospects.
All right, stop arguing.
Listen to me.
We are all aware of the situation now.
Dear shareholders, please express your personal views.
Chairman, we and Director Ling Fang
signed a clear contract.
He said that he only made that whatever company in order to develop the Ling Group's strength in the logistics industry.
Now, not only the promise was not fulfilled,
we have incurred losses too.
We are family. We don't want to take this to court, either.
Chairman, please preside over this difficult situation for us.
Then, what do you wish for him to do?
We just want our original shares back.
Since there's no money,
cash out Fangyu Construction's stocks
- to compensate everyone.
- Yes.
You're just trying to kill me, aren't you?
Shut up!
Such a huge problem happened,
and you want to wash your hands of this?
Do according to what they said.
Everyone, I have a better plan.
Fangyu Construction has now sustained severe damage.
Even if you cash out the stocks, it won't be able to make up for everyone's losses.
At most, it will only make everyone feel a bit better.
If everyone is willing, I can sell 5% of New Way's shares
to you at a lower price after dilution.
Take it as my eldest brother's apology.
I believe everyone knows that New Way is going to be listed in the market soon.
This 5% profit
will have unlimited promise in the future.
That's right. This is not a bad idea.
Given the current situation.
Fine.
It's a solution too.
Yes, it can make up for it.
Look!  The report is rather positive, Old Shen.
Fangyu is currently an empty shell.
Instead of beating it to death, why not choose one with a promising future?
It still requires us to spend money on its stocks.
It doesn't look like a worthwhile plan either.
Since that's what you think, you all should just take my brother's shares.
Taking into account our relationship with the chairman,
I don't want to hesitate any further. Let's just go with this.
Chairman, we will go now. We don't want to delay the handling of your family's matters.
Thank you all for taking the trouble to come out here.
Eldest Son.
I can't care how you harassed others with unreasonable demands in the past,
but your current approach has
already threatened the interests within the group.
Fortunately, my second son has reaped some profits for you.
Otherwise, even I wouldn't have been able to protect you.
Dad, I know my mistake.
You know your mistake? Where were you wrong?
I shouldn't have been arrogant and switched from real estate to e-commerce.
My mistake was not predicting the risks and difficulties across the industries.
Let me tell you what your mistake was.
Your biggest mistake was reckless advancement.
Did you think this was due to a lack of experience? It wasn't.
What you lack are vision and insight.
If one day, you really sit in the chairman's seat of this group,
how can you convince everyone in the company to
have faith in you that you can lead the company and move forward?
Dad, have some water first.
Cool down first. Eldest Brother already knows his mistake.
Use this period to rest properly.
Don't bother with the company for the time being.
- Dad!
- Let me tell you.
You should really be thankful to your younger brother this time.
Not only did he help you, but he also redeemed huge losses for the Ling family.
Do you know this or not?
What's wrong? Can't sit still?
You can't accept it?
Dad, the company still has matters to attend to.
I'm leaving.
Look at how your younger brother handles matters.
You should really learn from him.
Same for you, too.
- Me?
- How old are you this year?
You are twenty-two years old and already an adult.
Every day, you follow a woman around and chase her everywhere.
For what?
Do something promising, can't you?
Hold on.
Why are you raising your guard?
He just helped me. What could I do to him?
Speak. Why did you help me?
You clearly won back there.
As soon as I fall off the stage, everything in the Ling family will be yours,
but you insisted on pulling back at this moment.
I really cannot figure out what your reason for doing this could be.
Winning or losing is not important to me.
I have never thought of fighting with you.
So your motive for doing this was just that you wanted me to thank you?
I don't care how you think about it.
Eldest Brother.
Since this has already happened, just let it pass.
Don't overthink things.
I suddenly feel it's not very interesting anymore.
What isn't very interesting?
Your eldest brother, me, just experienced a roller coaster.
This is good, too. I'm suddenly relaxed.
Eldest Brother, where are you going?
Didn't Dad tell me to go on leave?
I'm obeying him.
Go back to the company first. I'm heading out.
Okay.
Xin'er.
Why are you here?
I knew you would be working in the area today,
so I wanted to invite you to elope. Are you interested?
Eloping doesn't sound like something adults would do.
I'm just joking.
I've come to ask about the date you've promised me.
Where do you want to go?
For a spring outing.
I know there's a huge themed music festival in the suburbs.
I think you'll definitely like it.
But I still have some work I haven't finished yet.
It's fine. I knew you would most likely reject me anyway.
Since you have to work overtime, eat more.
Replenish your energy and take good care of yourself.
Thank you.
So, do I have high awareness now?
But I really have work.
I know, you busy person! Go do your work.
Bye-bye.
Excuse me. Sorry for bothering you. Can I give this to you?
I just remembered... My company matters aren't that urgent.
Let's go out first.
Really? Then quickly, get in the car.
What's that?
I don't know either.
Can I have a sip?
Here.
What is it? It's so sweet. It doesn't taste good.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Awesome! Our comic has already exceeded 100,000 clicks.
Look, look, look. In the comments,
thousands of fans are begging for updates.
Anxin, why do I suddenly feel that this Xiao Ying looks quite like me?
I drew her based on you.
Wouldn't it be so wasteful to not make use of such a beautiful face?
I'm embarrassed.
You should be.
No way. Do girls give flattery so blindly?
Her pancake face can't come anywhere near a melon-seed shaped face!
(T/N: Melon-seed shaped face is one of the most sought-after face shapes in China)
Zhao Lei, why are you acting like it's your business again?
Sometimes, that mouth of yours was grown for no reason.
I think it's perfect.
You guys talk.
I wanted to scare you. What's up? Why are you spying on me?
Get in the car.
Is there an occasion?
Celebrating you guys getting over 100,000 clicks.
But I still have a lot to do.
You've been working for so many weeks in a row.
Do you not even have the right to give yourself a break?
I see other bosses torturing their employees,
but when it comes to you, why are you doing it to yourself?
Where do I have any employees to torture? The boss is me and the employee is me.
The cleaning lady is also me. Everything is me.
Who else can I torture but myself?
Then, where do you want to take me?
Camping. Didn't you say I'm not down-to-earth?
Camping?
You're quite good at understanding mistakes and correcting them.
Then... all right. I'm going back to get my drawing board.
My girlfriend is really a workaholic.
My goodness!
Isn't your long journey lacking a very cute, beautiful girl as your companion?
And this beautiful man here can reluctantly accompany you, too.
We...
No.
Anxin, we also need a break to prepare for the exceeding of one million clicks.
Right, let's pretend we're going together
to celebrate!
Let's go.
I won't be disturbing you, right?
Get ready.
♪  I encountered the girl in my heart on the street tonight  ♪
♪  My feet decided not to listen to my yells and went home with her  ♪
♪  She used her serene eyes, about to speak to me  ♪
♪  Slender, fluttering figure, turn around silently!  ♪
♪  She said, romantic lover, do you love me?  ♪
I told you so. You insisted on drinking those two huge bottles of water for beautification.
How could you not end up like this? You're about to explode.
By the way, Youyou. We are going camping today. Can we really see that galaxy of stars in the sky?
- Yes.
- Really?
I looked it up multiple times online.
It said there are many enthusiastic campers at the observatory point here. We will definitely see them.
Then since we can see it, we won't be disappointed.
Can we eat this?
What do you want to eat and drink?
- Are you thirsty?
- I want to eat this, but I'll get fat.
- You mean this?
- Xiao Sheng?
What a coincidence.
Second Brother. Sister-in-Law, you're also here.
What a coincidence. Where are you guys going?
- We're going camping. What about you?
- We...
We also happened to be finding a camping spot.
How about we go together?
Anxin, what a coincidence that you're here, too.
What a coincidence.
Right, we were planning on camping, too.
Since it's such a coincidence, why don't we go together?
Okay.
Then let's go together.
I'm ready!
Good.
I, Little Youyou, am so amazing.
This was my first time setting up a tent and it was so successful.
Help me take a picture.
Okay. Go ahead.
- Okay.
- Done? Let me take a look.
Am I cute?
Zhao Lei, I've never seen anyone as narcissistic as you.
You did today.
- Don't!
- You haven't taken the photo.
Stop messing around.
Is the reason why you're upset because I called everyone over to camp together?
I was thinking that rather than going to a music festival where we don't know anyone,
we would've been happier to come camping together with everyone.
It's not because of my second brother?
Anxin is here, too.
Look!  Everyone is here.
I won't be mad at you.
I just thought I finally had a chance to go on a date with you alone,
but who would've expected that everyone would be here.
This isn't considered us dating alone.
Really?
Then what you mean is... that there's a next time?
Why are you so cute?
Look!  Your hair is a mess.
What's wrong? Are you mad?
No.
Are you mad because my younger brother and Xin'er are both here?
Didn't Youyou and Zhao Lei also come?
Then, why do you look sulky and unhappy?
Are you on your period?
Anxin, the nail hasn't been nailed in.
You nail it then.
Besides, nothing will happen if a nail is missing.
It's so strong. What's wrong?
If you don't believe me, I'll lie in there for you. I'll sleep in there for you.
- I'll try it out for you. Nothing at all.
- Come out.
- It's not strong enough. Come out.
- It's very strong.
- Hurry.
If you want to play so badly, let's try it together.
I don't want to try it with you.
Didn't I say? It's not strong or safe.
It's safer than you at least.
My goodness.
Brother Yue, are you okay?
He's fine.
As long as you're fine, it's good. Be careful in the future.
He's so big and not made of paper. Of course, he's fine. Right, Ling Yue?
That's right. I'm fine.
He's fine.
Fan over here. It's dripping oil.
Smells good. He took them away so soon?
Xin'er, I just grilled these. Give them a try.
Xiao Sheng, let's go take a walk.
You're trying to go look for my second brother, right?
So, can I reject?
The meat is quite tender.
Smells good. Where's Anxin and Young President Ling?
Is there a need to say? They're obviously in their own two-person world.
Give it a try. I cooked them just for you.
Anxin, are you home?
I came looking for you.
Brother, don't worry. I'm having fun with my friends.
I see. Don't stay up too late. Stay safe.
Are we going down?
Be careful. Come on, slowly.
Why is there a tent here?
Didn't you say you wanted to stargaze?
I set up a tent here so we can stargaze together.
You even remembered this? So thoughtful.
It seems like we can't see stars tonight.
But it took me so long to find this place.
Then let's look at them next time, okay?
I'm sorry I couldn't let you see the stars.
What's there to be sorry about? Silly.
There are so many.
♫  Watching as the street lights flash on and off  ♫
♫  We can see how far away our future is just
by turning our heads back  ♫
♫  We've yet to part but longing has already begun  ♫
♫   Hugging you like owning the whole world  ♫
♫   Too beautiful that I fear time is limited  ♫
♫    Promises are too superficial,
not even as good as one one-thousandth of you   ♫
Do you like it?
♫  Let me love you  ♫
♫  Let me use my sincere heart  ♫
♫  and learn to use warmth to cover up   ♫
♫  the cold memories of the past  ♫
♫  Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met  ♫
♫  Memories are soaked in rain  ♫
♫  Fate works bizarrely  ♫
♫  The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response  ♫
♫  My heart suddenly beats abnormally  ♫
♫  Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you  ♫
♫  Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more  ♫
♫  Abandoning the token of happiness,
for it has always been you  ♫
♫  Our story has only just begun  ♫
♫  Yet the longing has never been able to stop  ♫
♫  Searching for the route to return to your side  ♫
♫  Our story has only just begun  ♫
♫  Using all of my most beautiful adjectives  ♫
♫  Is still not enough to describe your name  ♫
♫  Our story is exclusively ours  ♫
♫  Our palms hold onto the key to the future  ♫
♫  Using love to slowly open up a lifetime  ♫