♫  No longer panicking on the night of the blackout  ♫
♫  You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me  ♫
♫  Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet  ♫
♫  Your breath brushes up against my cheek  ♫
♫  With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close  ♫
♫  Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner  ♫
♫  Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves  ♫
♫  Happiness and sadness  ♫
♫  Make up the moments of life  ♫
♫  Rainy days become very special because of you  ♫
♫  Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street  ♫
♫  No matter when and where, you always appear  ♫
♫  Holding me tightly and spinning in circles  ♫
♫  Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you  ♫
♫  Becoming some part of the memories  ♫
♫  Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another  ♫
♫  Warming up the whole world  ♫
Recently, it's true that some bad things have happened at Ling Group.
Thank you all for your trust in me.
I will definitely take on the responsibility of the president
and lead Ling Group to the future!
I do not accept!
- It's Ling Yue!
- Yes, it's him.
- It's really Ling Yue!
- It's Second Brother!
Dad, Second Brother is alive!
Second Brother, you're finally back!
We missed you like crazy, didn't we?
Dad.
Your leg injury isn't severe, is it?
It's not. The doctor said some rest will heal it.
You just said you didn't accept, didn't you?
Right.
Everyone thinks it's good. Your disagreement is useless!
Aren't I right, Little Brother?
I have enough supporters present here.
Your disapproval is useless. You can't take me down.
Look at this little brother of mine. He broke his leg
and even his head! Hilarious!
Tell everyone why you don't accept it.
Because this kind of business deal is destined for loss.
Funds cannot be returned. Not only is it a failed plan,
it will eventually affect the development of the company's headquarters.
What nonsense are you talking about?
- You're just a—
- Let him finish talking!
Luocheng does look like fertile land at first glance.
It is located in the East Asian monsoon region.
At its southeast corner is a heavy metal industrial field that's been established for decades.
Normally, it indeed doesn't cause much of a disturbance,
but every winter,
the factory emits large amounts of hazardous gas.
And due to the wind, it drifts towards Luocheng.
If you purchase this land, I'm sure everyone is clear about
what the outcome will be.
If that's true, wouldn't the property rot in our hands?
- Yes.
- Yes, that's right.
Ling Fang, why is it that the environmental monitoring report
in your report says that
- there are no problems?
- Father.
Don't listen to his nonsense.
I've conducted an inspection across a radius of a dozen miles. There wasn't even a factory in sight.
You can't let him say whatever he wants, can you?
He has no evidence. He does e-commerce, what does he know?
What a coincidence. I just happen to have evidence.
Many years ago, when President Ling was looking for a location for the logistics warehouse, he considered Luocheng.
This report not only shows the environmental monitoring report for a radius of ten miles, it even shows a hundred-mile radius.
Dad, listen to my explanation!
Why would I listen to your nonsense explanation?
You're eager for success and desperate for an achievement.
You don't even have any sense of foresight when making decisions!
What right do you have to be the president of the group?
Sorry, shareholders.
We took up too much of your time.
Regarding the issue of Ling Fang
becoming Ling Group's president,
- I vote against.
-  What are you saying, Dad?
I disagree, too.
- Me too.
- As do I.
- I also am against it.
- I'm against.
- Against.
- I'm also against it.
- And me.
- Me too.
Okay. The votes stand.
Meeting adjourned.
Luckily, Ling Yue made it back in time. Otherwise, we wouldn't even be able to measure the losses.
That's right. Luckily we found out quickly that he handled it so improperly.
You did this on purpose.
You purposely chose this time to come back to purposely make me look bad.
- I did do this on purpose.
- Why do you always ruin everything of mine?
Enough!
Do you need me to find the best doctor to take a look at your leg?
It's fine. I won't need it.
Stop acting so peculiar!
Who knows what your true intentions are.
You're the one with the impure intentions, aren't you,  Eldest Brother?
I just happen to want to ask, why do you always want me to die?
This was found from someone else's dashcam.
How will you explain this?
- How?
- Father, this is fake!
Bring that vehicle owner to me if you have any capability!
Shut up!
I will give you an explanation regarding this issue.
What have you been doing during this time?
Why was there no news?
- I had some things to take care of.
- What kinds of things
could be more important than that of the company's?
Father, don't worry about this.
Isn't the most important thing that Second Brother came back safely?
Since he's back, let's let him continue to be the pres—
Shut up, you little brat!
Let the spot of the president
be empty for now.
Ling Yue, take this time
to rest up.
I will do as you say.
Ling Fang, you and that group of old things
are creating a small commotion behind my back.
Don't think I don't know.
That's why during this period of time, you'd best know your place.
Behave yourself.
Do you think you've won?
It doesn't matter that you messed up my business. We're both the vice presidents right now.
We sit on an equal footing. The winner cannot be determined yet.
Eldest Brother, you're not my match.
Who are you looking down upon?
I don't care who the successor is.
I just don't want to be controlled by you.
So you want to control me?
- Eldest Brother!
- You don't care about the position of president?
- Ridiculous! Come over here!
- Eldest Brother, we're one family!
There must be a misunderstanding. Calm down.
Calm down.
You brat.
Second Brother,
looks like you're determined to make me your scapegoat.
You obviously know whether or not I've unfairly accused you, Eldest Brother.
Let's see who's lying then.
Your leg is crippled, isn't it?
You really can't stand up anymore?
What? You don't trust me?
That girl is named Gu Anxin, right?
Don't look at me like that.
Why are you suddenly interested?
Don't think about doing anything to Anxin.
You care very much about her?
- It's none of your business!
- How is this none of my business? Did you forget?
Ever since we were young, I always made absolutely sure to steal everything you treasured most...
or ruin it.
- You wouldn't dare to.
- Why wouldn't I?
Unless you never meet her again,
I will definitely be able to find her.
Second Brother, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Ai Li, did you borrow my car last time because you knew that
my dashcam showed Eldest Brother and the others
manipulating Second Brother's car?
On the day of President Ling's accident, we didn't see Director Ling Fang in the parking lot monitor.
But it just so happened that your car was there too,
so I thought it might be a lead.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I didn't even know my car had such a thing.
That was my idea. It doesn't concern you.
I just didn't want to drag you into this.
Second Brother, we're all brothers.
Eldest Brother just lost himself for a moment.
He wouldn't want to do harm to you.
You don't have to worry.
I will handle it.
President Ling, is your leg okay?
I didn't think that bastard would go so far.
Then, should I send you to Miss Anxin's house?
We can't go back there. Knowing Ling Fang,
as soon as he grabs hold of a lead, he won't let it go so easily.
Since you've already been followed,
if we go back to Anxin's house, we won't be able to hide her.
I'm sorry. I failed my duty.
For the time being, protect Anxin well.
Don't let Ling Fang become aware until the matter is over.
Understood.
Excuse me. What is your friend's name?
Next time, invent a name before you come.
I have some issues on my end. Once I've dealt with them, I'll come and find you.
Xiao Ba?
Hello, is this Miss Gu Anxin?
Congratulations! You've won a prize.
The prize is to enjoy a set of undergarments worth ¥288!
Please provide your chest, waist, and hip measurements.
I don't like to wear undergarments.
However, my good friend Youyou likes them.
Send them to her. Her chest measurement is 36A.
Hey! I'm clearly a 36D.
Gu Anxin! You've ruined my good reputation.
I'm not in the mood to talk.
Let Xiao Ba come and cure you. Where is he?
Xiao Ba! Say something!
Don't hide on the side in silence. I know you're there.
He—
Xiao Ba!
I didn't hear anything.
♫  But I've already started to miss you  ♫
♫   Hugging you like owning the whole world  ♫
♫   Too beautiful that I fear time is limited  ♫
♫    Promises are too superficial   ♫
You're so big, but that's all wasted. You're afraid of cockroaches.
Why are you looking at me?
No reason.
How about I gift them to you?
In the future, I'll help you with physical tasks like opening cans.
Stop fooling around,  give it to me!
What do you want to do, leaning so close to me?
♫   Let the eyes of time be our witness   ♫
♫   for the words, "I do"  ♫
Fine.
Then it's a promise. Seal it.
Anxin? Are you still listening?
Is the connection bad?
He left.
President Ling, the meeting with Director Chen is at 10:00 a.m.
Got it. Go ahead and arrange it.
33 computers.
Anxin, you're still here?
You should hurry home. The company's new system doesn't allow overtime work.
I'll be done very soon.
You're taking the company bus, right? It's available before 10:00 p.m.
When did the company become so generous?
I don't know either. It's like there's a new person in charge.
- I'm going now. Bye.
- Bye.
Anxin!
How come you're here?
I came out for a walk.
You can't stand and you still want to go for a walk?
Let's go home.
♫   I've just gotten used to you giving me consolation first  ♫
♫  Those times we want to wipe away tears  ♫
♫  Those times we withdrew our hands  ♫
♫  No need for right and wrong in a relationship, how dull  ♫
♫  Gaze at me, don't avoid me  ♫
♫  Give me the last of yourself  ♫
♫  Let me try to touch your hard shell  ♫
♫  Hugging the fragility  ♫
♫  Hold me gently  ♫
♫  Give me the last of yourself  ♫
♫  Memories are like heavy rain.
Having never walked through it,  ♫
♫  how would you understand?  ♫
♫  Gaze at me, don't avoid me  ♫
♫  Give me the last of yourself  ♫
♫  Let me try to touch your hard shell  ♫
♫  Hugging the fragility  ♫
♫  Hold me gently  ♫
♫  Give me the last of yourself  ♫
♫  Memories are like heavy rain.
Having never walked through it,  ♫
I have already increased the security there according to your instructions.
♫  Hold me gently  ♫
♫  Give me the last of yourself  ♫
♫  Memories are like heavy rain. Having never walked through it, how would you understand?  ♫
President  Ling, I'm worried Miss Anxin will blame you.
At least she doesn't have to tread into these muddied waters.
Xin'er, look! Who's that?
I heard Ling Yue just escaped death
and is already burying himself in work. He's really going all out.
I heard his leg's crippled.
Let's not talk about this. Xin'er, how is your company coming along?
- How much is Uncle Gu deciding to invest?
- It's his own daughter!
She'll get however much she wants, right?
Angela, let me get off at that intersection there.
What's wrong?
I might have caught a cold and don't feel very well. I don't want to drink today.
It's so late now, and it's very unsafe.
Don't worry. My driver will come and pick me up immediately.
You two go ahead and have fun!
Then send me a message when you're home. Bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
I wonder whether I could have the honor of being this lovely fairy lady's driver?
What a coincidence!
It is and isn't a coincidence.
I was originally planning a "chance" encounter.
How about it? Are you getting in?
You're awake?
Why did you bring me here?
Whenever I feel down
or have something I can't come to terms with, I always come here to get some air.
Then, my mood improves. You can also try it.
Do I look like I'm in a bad mood?
Do you think you look like you're in a good mood?
How am I that ugly?
It's just that you're prettier when you smile.
Thank you.
It feels so nice.
You'll never go wrong listening to me.
You usually look like such an optimistic and carefree person. Do you also have worries?
I only appear carefree.
Think about it. I have two brothers who fight all day.
How carefree could I, a pond fish, be?
I heard... Ling Yue came back?
The internet must be frantically spreading the news about my second brother.
The media has yet to actually catch a real photo of him.
But everyone says he... says his leg—
They say my second brother's leg is crippled, don't they?
Don't listen to their nonsense. My second brother's leg is indeed injured,
but he's been recovering all this time. It will definitely get better.
Xin'er, don't worry.
Second Brother can always turn misfortune into good fortune. This time will be no different.
His injuries... are they serious?
Honestly, I'm not clear on it either.
Ever since Second Brother came back, he's locked himself inside the house.
He doesn't interact with anyone and devotes himself wholeheartedly into his work.
I think this matter really impacted him greatly.
He is so prideful, but now he's like this.
However, I believe he will definitely get better.
Because he is Ling Yue.
There is nothing that can knock him down.
Xin'er,
you still care about my Second Brother that much?
How can I forget so many years of feelings so easily?
All right, then I will place it in the To-Be-Received cabinet for you.
You're welcome.
Thank you for your call. If you have time, please rate my service.
- All right.
- Look!
So handsome!
Thank you.
Brother?
I'm sorry. I arrived late.
- What sort of charm does this Gu Anxin have?
- I know right...
The pond's so large, but why does she get to be the mermaid?
Perhaps that's just fate.
Today, we're all lemon fairies.
(T/N: It means that they feel "sour" and jealous)
Brother, why did you suddenly come back?
I should have come back earlier.
You've experienced so many things. Why didn't you tell me?
What things?
How long are you planning to keep the fact that you dropped out of school from me?
How did you know?
We've video-called so many times and sent so many emails.
You've always told me things are good, everything is good...
Look at you now. I can't help but worry about you.
I'm all right, Brother. I'm actually living very well right now. You don't have to worry.
Give me your hand.
Look into my eyes.
You think I don't understand you? You've been like this since childhood.
No matter what wrongs you suffered or difficulties you experienced,
you just like to suppress them all in your heart.
Your only fear was causing trouble for others by telling them.
I'm not just anyone. I'm your brother.
Your brother is back. From now on, you won't ever feel wronged.
You don't need to pretend to be strong in front of me
or pretend to be sensible, all right?
This ice cream has made my teeth hurt.
It's all right. Don't cry. Your brother is back.
From now on, I won't let anyone bully you.
Right, Brother,
I only asked for a half-hour off, so I might need to get back earlier.
Okay, I'll drop you off. We have time.
You insisted on eating ice cream. Now you're cold, aren't you?
No need, Brother! Your sister has a very strong body, and I'm not afraid at all!
What do you mean, "strong body"?
Look at you! You look like a small penguin.
If I had always been by your side, you wouldn't have suffered so much.
Look.
You've always been next to me, always been by my side.
I dreamed that a strange auntie was in my room.
Don't cry, I'm here.
- What is this?
- It's a nightmare-filtering bracelet.
As long as you wear it, it will eat all of your nightmares.
Thank you, Brother!
- All right. Let's go.
- Let's go.
Stop working here.
Work at the manga company that you brought up to me.
Haven't you always liked drawing?
Just like Auntie Jin.
If I can't draw well, then what do I do?
I'll support you.
But I eat a lot. When the time comes, you can't blame me for that.
You have lost so much weight.
You have to eat more from now on. The chubbier you get, the better, okay?
Brother, don't you know that if you eat too much, you will get eaten?
Ever since you were little, you've always been competitive.
I came here to tell you that I'm back.
Go.
Hello?
Mom.
I'm going back now.
What are you doing here?
Yesterday, he drank at my place.
I didn't feel comfortable getting someone to drive for him, so I sent him home.
When I have time, I want to properly meet that girl, Anxin.
What kind of woman
could crack this hard rock into shavings?
This is the female lead of the story?
She is quite pretty.
Who is the guy next to her?
He's pretty good-looking! A new lover?
Given his way of avoiding a problem by walking away from it,
I would've also found a new lover if I were her.
Which eye of yours was able to discern that he's good-looking?
He's quite radiant.
At least he's better than certain rocks.
Girls like this type.
Why aren't you going back?
Are you waiting for me to ask you to stay for dinner?
I will leave soon in order to avoid eating food you poison for me.
Go do some digging on that guy.
Okay, I will do it right now.
Manga convention recruitment?
"If you send your work to our inbox,
your work will have a chance to appear at our manga convention,
allowing more talent scouts discover you."
Sister Chang'an must go! Quickly, submit.
Exactly! Goddess Chang'an, you have to participate!
We will support you!
Let's go, Chang'an!
Can I really do it?
Does it still hurt here?
I'm asking you a question. Does your leg still hurt?
Can you please respect the doctor in front of you and tell me whether your leg still hurts?
"Sister Chang'an has to go"?
When did you become so effeminate?
And you call yourself Yuanyuan?
Why don't you call yourself Fangfang or Bianbian?
(T/N: "Yuan" means "round", "Fang" means "square", and "bian" means flat)
Give it back to me.
I don't even want to see it.
Who is Sister Chang'an?
President Ling's person.
Then it looks like...
there's a lot of interesting things going on.
Silly, don't you know to block it?
Sister, wipe yourself and don't get cold!
Thank you!
Sister, use this umbrella.
Then how do I give it back to you?
No need to! My bus is here, goodbye!
President Ling, the manga convention has already been arranged.
Let's go.
Later, when we see her piece,
- Do you understand what to say?
-Yes, I understand.
- I do, so rest assured.
Please.
Hello, teachers.
Sit.
Okay, thank you.
You see? It is raining.
- You are all wet, please wipe yourself.
- Thank you.
Drink some hot water so that you don't get sick.
- Okay.
- Drink more.
What is going on?
Gu Anxin. Right?
- Did you bring your work?
- I did.
I'm sorry, I forgot to bring it...
No worries, you can tell us
about your previous projects.
In the past, I have serialized
"The Big Wolf and Little Sheep."
Also...
- Then...
- That's good!
I have seen it in the past and it's so well-drawn!
It can be directly published.
- Really?
- Really!
Is it that good?
What nonsense are you saying?
Your acting is going a little overboard. Pull it back.
Anxin, you have been selected.
S-Selected?
Just like that?
No need to do a second or third interview?
No need.
It's an unconventional hiring.
Clean up your stuff. You can start working tomorrow.
Tomorrow? I'm not ready to begin tomorrow, sorry.
Then, if you have any requests,
don't worry. You can just tell us.
No! It's not a request.
To be honest, it's because I haven't quit my job,
and I still need to pass on past work,
so I can't come to work tomorrow.
That's fine.
I know this good news has come too suddenly. I understand it may be hard to accept.
After all, we are Brilliant Worldly Culture!
Right, right, right.
Well... make sure to consider it carefully after you get back.
Once you are done considering, you can contact me whenever.
- Let me introduce myself.
- Zhao Lei, right?
- Yes, Zhao Lei.
- Me too. My name is Wang Li.
- And me as well.
- My name is Chen Hong.
- Hello, Chen Hong.
Then, I'll leave now.
- All right.
- Sure.
- Do you need me to see you out?
- See her out.
- No need.
- Go ahead.
- Seeing you off is a must.
- I'll see you off.
- No need.
Take care. This way.
- Auntie.
- Son!
- Mom.
- My wishfulness for you finally brought you back!
Hurry and give me a hug.
Let mother see you.
Why have you gotten so much skinnier?
Is the food abroad not to your taste?
Not at all.
Come, quickly.
Try the food I prepared specifically for you.
Your favorite dishes.
Come on. Quickly, sit down.
In the few years I haven't been back,
- your cooking skills have really improved so quickly.
- Eat well.
You didn't order food to fool me, did you?
You always know how to sweet talk.
All you have left is your sweet talk.
Dad.
Your mother is always wishing to the moon and the stars for you to return.
The first thing you did after coming back was not visiting her. Do you think I don't know that?
You've spent the whole day with an outsider.
Dad, how could Anxin be counted as an outsider?
She isn't related to me.
How could she not count as an outsider?
Dad, look,
aren't I also not biologically yours?
Don't you still love me very much?
What sort of nonsense talk is that? How could that be the same?
Yuanchao, did you finish your phone meeting?
It gave me a headache.
Let me give you a massage.
You are just too tired.
Yuanchao, stop blaming our son.
He and Anxin grew up together.
- Naturally, their relationship is good.
- That's why I'm afraid he'll be used by her!
Dad! I always feel like there's something secretive going on.
Anxin has been so kind since childhood. How could she have ever hurt anyone?
Do you think you understand her well?
Look at her temperament!
She is made of the same mold as her mother.
No matter how terrible the deeds she does are, I still wouldn't be surprised!
That's enough, stop fighting. Our son just came back.
However you look at it, Anxin is a child of our Gu family.
You also promised Sister Jin Wan that you would take good care of her.
This child was indeed too headstrong in the past,
but I trust that she now knows she was wrong.
Right, Yuanchao.
Your birthday is in a few days. How about we welcome her over to get together?
You can organize it.
Leave it to me.
Son, eat more.
- Here.
- Thanks, Mom.
♫  Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met  ♫
♫  Memories are soaked in rain  ♫
♫  Fate works bizarrely  ♫
♫  The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response  ♫
♫  My heart suddenly beats abnormally  ♫
♫  Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you  ♫
♫  Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more  ♫
♫  Abandoning the token of happiness, for it has always been you  ♫
♫  Our story has only just begun  ♫
♫  Yet the longing has never been able to stop  ♫
♫  Searching for the route to return to your side  ♫
♫  Our story has only just begun  ♫
♫  Using all of my most beautiful adjectives  ♫
♫  Is still not enough to describe your name  ♫
♫  Our story is exclusively ours  ♫
♫  Our palms hold onto the key to the future  ♫
♫  Using love to slowly open up a lifetime  ♫