[Jixiang Unhappy]
[Episode 5]
Why are you following me
to the restroom?
Stay away from me.
You better give up.
I will never let you pass easily.
Go away.
Further away.
You go farther!
Even farther!
Don't look back!
Only fifteen minutes left.
No matter how far I go,
you won't be able to pass the exam.
Don't
look
back.
You perv, did you look back?
I need to use the restroom.
You need to go to the restroom again?
Hurry up.
Time's up.
The exam is over.
[Preliminary exam rankings,
top of the list: Jixiang]
Jixiang.
Come over here.
How dare you cheat?
I'm going to cancel your exam scores.
Now you realize it?
Too late.
Who cheated?
How can you accuse me like this?
Everyone can be my witness.
You were watching me the whole time,
even when I went to the restroom.
Right?
- That's right.
This is our private grudge.
How can we trivialize
something as serious as the exam?
If that's the case,
this sect isn't really worth it.
Let's just dissolve it.
Do you agree too?
Alright,
then I announce that Baichuan Sect
is hereby dissolved.
Who's that?
Who wants to dissolve the Baichuan Sect?
Master,
she was just joking.
Don't be angry.
It's you.
We shared this meal together today,
so consider us friends now.
If you ever need anything,
just let me know.
I've got your back.
Thanks.
I, Gui Sihai,
am the head of Baichuan Sect.
Answering questions
is not important for this exam.
What matters
is the ability to gather intelligence.
The spirit tribe is powerful,
hiding and lurking in the world.
If Baichuan Sect
wants to capture them one by one,
we must learn to gather information
without leaving a trace,
by any means necessary.
Miss Jixiang has done an excellent job,
so her being at the top of the list
is completely appropriate.
See?
The head of your sect
says that I've done a great job.
Don't get too complacent.
After the written exam,
there's still the martial arts exam.
I'll keep a close eye on you.
Then I must strive to come out on top
and enter the sect
with integrity and honor.
Ye Zhou,
you've played with my feelings,
abandoned me,
and repeatedly deceived me.
This time,
I won't let you get away again.
I never expected such behavior
from Martial Brother Zhou
of Baichuan Sect.
It's truly disgraceful
and brings shame upon the sect.
All the newcomers, listen,
this martial arts exam will involve
removing a spirit tribe stronghold.
Anjing.
Manyue.
Lead the official disciples
to take the lead.
Jiahao.
Yes.
Lead the newcomers
to coordinate with them.
The performance of the newcomers
during the operation
will contribute
to part of their assessment scores.
Master,
there's no precedent for this.
For the newcomers,
it's too dangerous.
If the newcomers don't understand
the danger of evil spirits,
how will they comprehend
the significance
of eradicating them
and safeguarding the human realm?
With greater power
comes greater responsibility.
If one finds it hard to bear
the heavy responsibility,
it's better
to withdraw early.
Yes.
Eradicating evil spirits.
Why does it sound so strange?
Jixiang,
do you have any questions?
No, I don't.
I will do my best.
Remember, safety comes first.
Have you discovered anything
while secretly keeping watch?
That Myriad Spirits Pearl
is somewhat special.
It's only a matter of time
before it matures.
Well done.
You did a great job.
Take a rest, you deserve it.