(Akari) If that's the case, then you can win, right?
24% of people in tax-exempt households
‎If everyone would vote for me
(Igarashi) If you appear, you will win.
(Mari (Festival)) Of course Ten Thousand
‎So stop calling me that!
‎-(Igarashi) Hahaha… ‎-(Akari) Excuse me.
(Door chime)
(Takaomi) Too bad, suddenly.
(Ryusei) Secretary-General, please call me.
I could come anytime and anywhere.
-(Ryusei) Please.-(Takaomi) Oh, thank you.
(Amemiya) It was fishy.
‎It has a theatrical feel to it.
‎No, well, but
Don't you all love stories like this?
The person at the top personally goes to the person at the bottom
It's like bowing your head
(Mari) Fuu
(Amamiya) Did we meet?
‎Huh?
‎Mr. Igarashi
(Mari) Ah...
‎Yes
Sorry for the late report. I was able to meet you.
‎Will you tell me after all? reason
‎Sorry
(Amemiya) No, not at all.
I'm glad I was able to help you. Please feel free to ask me anything...
No, my relationship with Mr. Amemiya ends here.
(Amemiya) Huh?
Thank you very much for everything so far
No, no, wait...wait a minute, eh? picture?
(Mari) From now on, Mr. Amemiya and I will have no relationship at all.
(Amamiya) Eh...choo
‎Excuse me
(Amamiya) Ah... that (no sound)
(Vibration sound of mobile phone)
(Staff) Nori salmon croquette bento‎Customers waiting for 3 items
‎-(Mari) Ah, yes‎-(Staff) Sorry to have kept you waiting.
(Mari) Thank you
‎♪～
‎～♪
(Akari) Story?
(Mari) Normal is impossible.
The secretary general personally visits young members of his own party.
‎Honestly I am
In recent election campaigns, trying to capture the hearts of voters through stories...
(Igarashi) No, let's not get into this.The story is a bonus.
‎The main thing is the unanimous recommendation of Tokyo Metropolitan Federation
‎Recommendation of the Civic Party
(Mari) Huh?
There must be someone who is good at it.
‎Awful play scenario
In this short period of time, the Tokyo Metropolitan Federation has been able to produce candidates.
Including Ryusei, there are at most 4 people.
‎Probably the other three people will have opposing opinions at the board meeting.
It was probably prepared in advance.
(Akari) Eh, how?
‎Thoroughly digging into the past
‎Knock it out until the dust comes out
‎Gently whisper to someone from Tokyo Ren.
(Shizukuishi) If this becomes public and I lose the election.
‎Involved in party tickets
‎100 years of inherited craftsmanship
It is the responsibility of Tokyo Metropolitan Federation to select candidates who can win.
I pin my hopes on the only remaining meteor and go to woo him...
‎We decline your request.
Again, he should have given instructions in advance.
‎When I receive a request from the Metropolitan Federation to run, I do it on the spot...
(Shizukuishi) Please refuse.
I cannot betray the Machida citizens and the secretary general who is my benefactor.
‎On top of that, if the secretary general wants it, it should be
Could you please come to
‎Nothing to do
(Igarashi) Toren bows to the boss
‎Then the boss issues conditions.
‎Unanimous vote of the Board of Governors: Get it.
‎Hiyama‎Kun no Minmin Party Recommendation
Also, please tell me about the recommendation of the Civic Party.
(Igarashi) Well, probably this is the scenario.
(Mari) It's a pain.
‎That's Nagatacho, ladies.
‎You too
If there is dust that is likely to come out when knocked down, please report it yourself.
‎I have to pay it now.
Will Rep. Hiyama announce his candidacy just before the announcement date?
‎You told me this before.
Who do voters vote for?
‎Make an impactful statement when you start considering...
(Igarashi) No, that's my way.
The meteor will probably be early next week
It will be announced as soon as the notification date is decided.
‎Set up your organization chart as soon as possible.
‎Escape
‎Ah...
(Igarashi) Yes, Shizu-chan's specialty
(Shizukuishi's sneeze)
(Sumita) Do you have hay fever?
(Shizukuishi) No
(Nodamura) Someone is spreading rumors.
Mature men will definitely say that.
(Email reception sound)
(Akari) I'm glad you fixed it.
‎Yes
-(Akari) Yes‎-(Mari) Thank you
‎(Akari) Oh
Ah, those words.
(Mari) Yes, this is a passage from Kenji Miyazawa's ``Outline of an Introduction to Peasant Art.''
(Akari) The picture is nice too.
‎Who drew it?
‎I don't know.
It's a postcard for my father, but it doesn't have the sender's name.
‎Even when I asked my father, he didn't tell me.
(Light) Yeah.
Shortly before my mother died, she said she would do it to you.
That's when I decided
‎Becoming my father's secretary
‎Because I wanted to be the governor of Tokyo
I had no intention of inheriting my father's foundation.
I was thinking of training somewhere else.
I wonder if my mother will be happy
‎She was actually very happy.
‎I see.
I wanted to make you more happy...
I wasn't a very cute child.
-(Akari) Yeah? -(Mari) Alone⸺
Go anywhere on your own and get lost
Also, kids never seem to eat lunch.
‎Eh, why?
‎I don't want people to think I'm a child
Actually, I really wanted to eat it.
‎That kind of girl is cute
Is that so?
Yeah, it's so cute
(Mari) Thank you
Who made that child?
These kids are also the same artist, right?
Are you famous?
‎No, junior high school girl
‎Eh!
‎Wow, amazing talent
I'm looking forward to the future
‎Cute
But it seems a little lonely
‎Mari-chan
‎Yes
It's me...
‎Me⸺
‎10 years ago…
‎(Akari) 10 years ago‎A little while ago Various things
‎I have no choice but to die.
It's okay, if you feel like talking.
Candidates are not required to disclose their past or career history.
If something about you is exposed and you are targeted
I will do my best to be your shield.
Can also be used as a spear
‎I will definitely protect it
‎Thank you
(Announcer) Due to the resignation of Tokyo Governor Yanagihara
Tokyo gubernatorial election schedule announced on May 28th
We have decided to vote on June 14th.
I, Ryusei Hiyama, am determined to run for Tokyo governor.
‎(Cheers) ‎(Ryusei) Thank you
The reason I wanted to convey this determination here is
‎I, Hiyama Ryusei Politician
‎No
I was able to meet Dr. Hoshino Takaomi, who opened up the path for me in life.
Because it is the place where it begins
(audience nods)
(Ryusei) I have a story
‎...Some people say that, but ‎It's completely non-fiction.
When I was 12 years old, my father's factory went bankrupt.
The father was clearly depressed.
When I woke up one day...
(Meteor) When I woke up the next day...
(Ryuusei's father) Let's die together
What?
‎Ugh...
(Ryusei) Die alone
(Ryusei) My father committed attempted murder
Mother may be arrested for abandoning her guardian
I didn't think that was cute.
It's not like I felt lonely.
If your parents become criminals, it will probably be a lot of trouble.
But then what should I do?
‎What should I do...
(Takaomi) I don't know what to do anymore.
A society where you can raise your voice and ask for help in times like these.
‎Politics that responds
I believe that this is the origin of our democratic party's politics.
(Ryusei) It's okay, I can go.
I feel completely sorry right now
(Takaomi) I seriously want to make it.
Please help me
(Ryusei) At that moment, my poor friend became a “story”
Mr. Hoshino supported my father's reintegration into society.
Please let me live in your home...
(Audience cheering)
‎Like family...
‎Sorry
You brought me this far with your deep love.
(Women's excited voices) You have brought me this far with your deep love.
(Women's excited voices)
(Women's excited voices) ‎And now
‎And now
‎Secretary-General Hoshino pushed me again‎
‎The philosophy that we continue to hold unchanged today
‎A society where people can cry out for help
‎Politics that responds to that
‎(Meteor) For us... ‎(Audience noise)
(Ryusei) I...
(claps and cheers)
‎You're doing your best
‎Thank you
(Mari) You've changed, haven't you, Dad?
After my mother died
(Ryusei) No, Mari-chan
‎My father hasn't changed.
‎I changed it.
‎The story that I carry
(Announcer) Ryusei Hiyama, a member of the House of Representatives,
‎I have already submitted a nomination request to the Democratic Party and the Citizens Party...
‎Yes Bingo
-(Mari) Huh! -(Light) Dangerous
‎Just press it a little and it will disappear.
I cut off the evil spirit of this stupid farce.
(Igarashi) Even a farce has great effects.
‎Last House of Representatives election⸺
The Tokyo electoral district has approximately 11.5 million voters.
‎Valid voter turnout is 50%
‎The Democratic party's vote share is
‎1.72 million votes, about 30%
The Citizens Party received 300,000 votes, or about 5%.
‎In other words...
Ryusei has already received 2.02 million votes.
‎Eh? Already?
‎That's the recommendation.
(Igarashi) Similar calculations
The expected number of votes for candidates of the Kyosei Party, the main opposition party, is
‎700,000 votes
‎What is our side?
(Igarashi) Currently...
- (Igarashi) 0 votes - (Mari) No, 3 votes
There are 3 votes here!
(Akari) Huh?
Can't I vote for me?
Of course
You may win by 3 votes, but you will never win by 3 votes.
‎I know that.
That's why I invited you, right?
If you can afford to emit unnecessary CO2 with unproductive words
‎Be aware of your position
How about showing off your talent to the fullest?
‎Remember‎This is how politicians get angry.
-(Akari) Yes‎-(Mari) You don't have to remember it.
‎I'll do my best even if you don't tell me
‎I have prepared two secret strategies.
(Mari) Secret plan?
‎First of all, Part 1
‎These 2.02 million votes
‎Divide
(2 people) Do you want to divide it?
Promote another candidate within the Democratic Party and compete with each other
But the recommendation from the party...
‎Usually 1 person‎Because the votes will be split.
‎Yes...
‎That's why I endorse him without an endorsement and bring about a divisive election.
‎Can you do it? That kind of thing
‎Recommendation is in principle unanimous by the Tokyo Metropolitan Government Board of Governors.
‎Ryusei is popular, but has many enemies.
There must have been some people in the metropolitan area who were aware that he had made it himself and had an antipathy towards it.
I can't come up with any other candidates.
Under pressure from the chief secretary
‎Cannot object publicly
‎What if that happens?
‎Leave before making a decision
‎Oh, so it's going to be unanimous?
‎Naru desu
‎1 person…
No, there should have been two people.
‎There is an anti-Meteor faction within the Tokyo Ren.
First find out who it is
‎How?
Set up with
‎What?
‎It will take some time.
In the meantime, I would like to ask the two of you for secret plan 2.
‎Name Operation Avengers
‎-(Igarashi) Akari-san‎-(Akari) Yes.
‎You have charm
‎Human power
But when it comes to politics, I'm an amateur.
Even after studying hard for 50 days
‎It is impossible to build up the strength to run the metropolitan government.
Voters aren't stupid either.
No patient entrusts their life to a doctor who works overnight.
‎-(Mari) But... ‎-(Igarashi) Because it's ⸺
‎Sell as a team
‎Team?
‎Includes Deputy Governor
(Mari) It is true that the Tokyo governor can appoint the vice governor.
‎Parliamentary approval...
‎It's necessary but
At the election stage, Tokyo gubernatorial candidates select vice governor candidates.
There's no rule that says you can't make it public.
Even in the presidential election, the vice president...
(Mari) No, please wait.
‎Do you mean to make it public? ‎Me and Mr. Igarashi's names
‎Of course
‎Hoshino Mari‎Daughter of the insulated secretary general and former secretary
No, my father... No, there was interference from the Democratic Party...
‎Take it
‎Obstruction is propaganda
‎I'm 100,000,000 times more thankful than being silently killed.
With a former snack shop mom full of humanity
‎Challenge the Tokyo gubernatorial election
‎Avenge of the losers who were cut off by the secretary-general of the Democratic Party
The story we carry in order to win in this election campaign
‎Hold your stomach, young lady
‎You need to be prepared to commit to life.
‎If you want to use this as a trump card
‎-(Mari) This... ‎-(Igarashi) It reached me too.
It is the darkness that brings the light.
‎I understand
‎2 more people
The number of deputy governors that the Tokyo governor can appoint is up to four.
While I'm dividing the votes
‎Two of us, third Avenger‎Please woo me.
‎Who...
‎He's the only one there, right?
(Hotaru) Hinata!
‎Water bottle
What about gym clothes? I got it
‎Yes please
Yes, I'm fine
‎Courage
‎Flower!
‎Bloom!
‎Yes, please come.
-(Yota) I'm coming.-(Hotaru) Yes.
Hey, this is a new product created by the very popular Maru-san.
‎(Maru-san)〈Of course〉
(Fireflies) Hey, Mom, how long will you keep it up?
(Hotaru's mother) That's fine.
‎Customer: It's popular, so hey?
‎Isn't it good that it's not particularly popular?
-(Hotaru's Mother) What about delivery? -(Hotaru) Huh?
‎Wow, it's already been this long‎Dad, are you ready?
(Hotaru's father) It's done.
Because there's a typhoon tonight
Tell me to be careful
Tell me to be careful‎〈Tonight's typhoon〉
‎
To the elderly‎〈Tonight's typhoon〉
Yes, I know‎〈Tonight's typhoon〉
‎I'm worried about the elderly, but I'm not an old person either.
(Children's voices of joy) (Fireflies) Yes, I'll open it. Ahaha...
‎Okay, the bread has arrived.
-(Children) Thank you‎-(Firefly) You're welcome.
(Firefly) These days, my favorite phrase is already...
‎I'll blow you away
(Fireflies) Oh, good morning.
(Fireflies) Who am I?
What did you want to blow away so much?
‎What could I have thrown away?
Maybe without being able to blow anything away
‎I woke up after being blown away.
Please, from now on, live a life that suits you.
(Hotaru) The world was too strong for me
‎-(Fireflies) Yes, please enjoy‎-(Customers) Thank you.
-(Hotaru) Thank you very much‎-(Customer) I'll come again.
‎Welcome
‎Girl...
It's been a long time
Kumoi Hotaru-san
‎It's a wonderful shop.
‎What happened?
‎Sorry
The emotion of those days has come back to me
Around this time, it was decided that the factory would be relocated.
‎Regular customers‎Most of them were from there.
I feel extremely anxious every day.
(Fireflies) Sorry for keeping you waiting.
(Mari) Ah, no, I'm sorry, all of a sudden.
‎Don't worry about it
Akari-san, please calm down.
-(Hotaru) Sorry for the mess. -(Mari) Sorry to bother you.
(Akari) Excuse me.
(Firefly) Please sit down.
‎-(Mari) Don't worry about that‎-(Akari) Don't worry about it
‎Ah, on-site sales...
(Fireflies) Shichijojima
‎There is no bakery ‎There are not many types of bread you can buy.
Well, there's no allergy-friendly bread either.
‎Differences in selection by region
That is also an issue for Tokyo.
Ah, Shichijojima is Tokyo.
(Hotaru) The ferry fee is expensive, so I only do it once every two months.
‎This is a wonderful initiative.
‎Soup kitchens to support disaster-stricken areas and people in need ‎Food distribution, etc.
You provided bread, right?
I heard about it from Mr. Igarashi.
(Hotaru) Gala-san...
‎Also active in hiring people with disabilities.
All of our staff are regular employees.
‎This is a wonderful initiative.
(Hotaru) It's not like that.
‎What they want to do What they can do
‎What we want you to do ‎What you can do for us
‎Because we matched, ‎I'm just working for you.
Well, I don't think it's a problem because it's a general employment.
‎Employment of people with disabilities There may be cases where employment is the best fit for both parties.
Type A and type B workplaces each have their own significance.
Well, people with disabilities are lumped together.
‎Regardless of the type of job, the legal employment rate remains the same, even if you keep increasing it.
In the end, that's it...
‎Sorry, I'm fluent by myself
No, I want to hear more.
‎-(Light) It's a learning experience‎-(Firefly) Stop it!
‎-(Hotaru) Sorry for being so bossy‎-(Mari/Akari) No, no...
(Sound of door opening) (Yota) I’m home.
(Fireflies) Hey, I'm back.
‎Yota Welcome back
‎Customer
‎Yota-san, I’m bothering you.‎This is Mari Hoshino.
Hello, this is Akari Tsukioka.
(Yota: in a whisper) Hello.
‎A modest child
‎Please
‎What grade are you in?
‎1st year student? It's shiny
(Hotaru) Yota Wash your hands and gargle
At the store, grandma has prepared a snack for you, so go ahead and eat it.
-(Akari) So cute‎-(Mari) Yes
‎-(Firefly) Please‎-(Mari) Thank you.
(Fireflies) What? Talk to me
Kumoi-san, I have a request for you today.
‎-(Hotaru) Impossible‎-(Akari/Mari) Huh?
‎I thought you were talking about the lieutenant governor. Stop joking.
-(Mari) I'm serious‎-(Hotaru) Even if it's impossible, I have a child.
But when you were mayor, Yota was still in nursery school, right?
It was a burden
To Youta, to his parents, to city officials
I always feel so guilty
I mean, when you go to elementary school
‎It will be easier to balance childcare and work⸺
There is a mysterious misunderstanding, but the opposite is also true.
Never heard of it? 1st grade wall
‎Uneducated
Elementary school starts later and leaves earlier than nursery school, right?
‎You won't be able to work shorter hours
‎There are more events, and ‎We have summer vacation.
‎The problem of waiting lists for school children remains high.
I'm lucky to live at home with my parents.
My parents are fine too, so I'm doing okay.
It's a tightrope walk
It ends when someone falls down
‎It's a truly important city...
No, this is a national issue, so please join us.
‎Without any physical or mental burden on anyone‎Without making any sacrifices
How to balance childcare and work with career...
(Fireflies) To find
Do you want me to make a sacrifice?
‎Sorry, I said it in a mean way.
But I've already given up
I sacrifice myself and my family for others.
‎Gara-san is free too.
Even though Hotaru said I would protect her, she quickly ran away by herself.
‎That's different
I didn't run away, I turned myself in.
‎To protect
Mr. Igarashi was seriously in love with Mr. Kumoi.
I'm running around trying to make you a candidate recommended by the Democratic Party.
Please lend your strength to Kumoi Hotaru
‎I know
It was my father who turned it over just before the notification date.
‎Become chairman of the supporter's association
A father was asked to make his son mayor.
‎Recommendations taken from you
‎Election support has also been discontinued.
I ordered the chairman's son to win.
‎I know that too
But Mr. Gala
Thank you for continuing to support me secretly behind the scenes.
‎I became the mayor
When his father found out, Mr. Igarashi was fired.
‎If I get involved any more
Mr. Kumoi may be removed from his position as mayor.
So Mr. Igarashi...
Although I was dragged down, in the end
‎I'm really sorry.
‎Sorry‎I said something mean again.
There's nothing for a young lady to apologize for.
‎I chose it.
(Mari) But...
‎It's okay
I'm happy now
‎Son and parents
Cherish the people and work within your reach
‎Well, what about your height?
Shichijojima is not the only remote island without a bakery.
Our staff are not the only people with disabilities who want regular employment.
‎Childcare and work: walls of first grade
Back when it was called the ``blow-up firefly''
I'll do all of that somehow.
Desperately trying to reach out to places I can't reach
The people and things you must cherish most
‎I was stepping on it
‎Be a kind child, Yota.
‎That's why I'm a little scared
‎Thunder, typhoon, earthquake, etc.
‎You cry when you're scared, right?
But at times like that, you have to go, right?
‎I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
‎Leave your crying son behind
‎Tell me what you need ‎I'll take care of it.
(Citizen) What can you do?
‎The mayor is just a decoration anyway.
(Firefly) When I rushed to the place, the response was poor. I was criticized for being a tax thief.
What am I doing? I hide and cry.
‎What's up with the fireflies?
‎Not at all
‎I wasn't good enough to be mayor.
I mean, it's not a good idea to blow it away.
It's violence, in this era of dialogue.
(Akari) But...
‎Ah, sorry‎I cut in too sharply.
I feel like saying something
But I was saved.
‎Blow away Firefly's blow away
‎Huh?
‎Isn't it?
‎When you really want to be blown away and ‎When you want to be blown away
‎When you want to be blown away?
‎Yes, look, even in that song
♪ I have to let something blow my back
‎♪ There are times when I don't even have the courage.
No, wait a minute, that's it.
‎Not “I have to get blown away”
‎“I have to be pushed hard” ‎Isn’t it?
-(Akari) Huh? Huh? -(Hotaru) Huh? Huh?
(Mari) Uneducated
(Fireflies) Ah... wait a minute.
‎Ah, right?
‎Daikoku (Oguro) ‎Maki‎
‎Look
(Akari) Ah!
‎Huh? Haha
Eh, I thought, “I have to get blown away.”
‎I was singing passionately at karaoke
‎Eh, the lyrics will come out, right?
No, I thought you remembered, so you dance, right?
‎Are you going to dance? what kind?
♪ I have to let something blow my back
Something like that hahaha...
‎You're blowing it away.
(laughter)
It's Akari, right?
‎Yes
(Fireflies) Are you ready?
‎Prepare to get hurt
(Akari) Eh...
(Fireflies) It hurts.
‎You'll be hurt, torn to shreds.
I wonder if people don't think of me as a human being.
‎In real life or online
‎It would be fine if it was just me.
‎Family, important people, things that are important to you, etc.
‎In a nasty way
My ex-husband had a criminal record. I didn't know either.
Mr. Kumoi...
‎Isn't it good? talk to me
‎Yes
(Hotaru) A little over a year after I became mayor.
I was suddenly summoned to be the secretary general of the Democratic Party.
(Shizukuishi) It will be published in "Weekly Bunkei" which will be released in 3 days.
If you resign, we will stop the article.
It's a threat, right? this
‎No, it's warmhearted.
‎Huh?
(Shizukuishi) It is true that there are people we would like to support as mayor.
‎-(Firefly) That's why... ‎-(Shizukuishi) That's why⸺
It would be better if this article was published and you were forced to resign.
‎It's good for us, but⸺
That could hurt you or your child.
Your parents' shops may also be affected.
The one who put you in a position that you don't deserve is
‎It is within our former family.
The Secretary-General is very sorry for this.
Here I would like to at least apologize for the inconvenience.
‎You are welcome to choose.
Resigned due to mental and physical illness
‎Stop article‎Can you take this home?
Will he be forced to resign due to injuries all over his body after the article was published?
It's true that I'm happy now
But I wonder if it's okay as is?
‎It's ok to get hurt so badly ‎It's ok to cry
‎One more time...
There are times when I wonder why, I want to scream.
‎One more time in that place
‎I want to fight in that place
But it's scary
‎Having hurt Youta and his parents
‎I won't let you get hurt
Youta, your parents, and Hotaru
‎Akari too
I will definitely protect you
‎It's impossible
‎I promise
(Akari) Me too...
I think it's impossible
‎Sorry
Even at that time...
‎I will definitely protect it
(Akari) I actually thought it was impossible.
‎Even if it was an article, I could stop it.
‎On the internet, it's instant...
‎A little while
‎What was done to me
Protected by freedom of expression
Even if you report it to management
‎There is no problem‎The AI ​​has decided for me.
‎I won't do such a lukewarm approach.
‎I will knock it down completely
I know how to do it
‎Why?
Because she's a politician's daughter
Born and raised as the daughter of a politician
For five years, I was fully involved in politics as a secretary.
‎So for me
‎Experiences that the two of you don't have
There are knowledge and skills gained from it.
So don't worry
No matter what method I use, I will always...
‎Ah...
(Akari) Wait a minute...
(Mari) I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
‎Sorry‎Sorry, Mari-chan
‎I'm sorry, I said it too strongly.
(Mari) No, that's not true.
‎Thank you
There were a lot of things that made me feel bad about being the daughter of a politician.
There is no such thing as a more normal election...
‎I wish I had a normal father
‎Secretary work too
‎I've been in pain for a long time
But now, for the first time, I thought it was good.
‎Me, born as the daughter of a politician
I was a secretary
‎Me now
Let's all work together to protect the two of you.
(Mari) Sorry to bother you.
You'd better go straight home. There's a typhoon coming.
‎Yes
See you again Yota-kun
‎Contact information for me and my office
‎If you feel like it
‎Sorry if it doesn't suit you.
No, it's okay
‎Excuse me
(Akari) Ah!
‎Sorry, I forgot to say it.
We just started talking about songs...
I thought
When I saw the news about Hotaru...
(Firefly) Why are you ignoring the voices of residents?
(Akari sighs) (Hotaru) Why are you ignoring the voices of the residents?
(Akari's sigh)
(Akari sighs) Are you going ahead with your plan?
Are you going ahead with your plan?
‎I'll blow you away
I will fight tooth and nail to protect the citizens.
(Akari) This person is trying to blow me away.
I wonder if it's "unreasonable"
It's unreasonable that our strength can't do anything about it
‎If such a person exists
Me too, let's try a little harder.
(Female) Typhoon No.3
It is expected to approach the Kanto region early tomorrow.
(Fireflies) Yeah, okay.
Well, let's go to sleep before the typhoon comes.
Are you going? mother
I've told you many times that I won't go.
‎Mom already
Even if a typhoon comes or an earthquake comes, I won't go anywhere
‎I'll always be by Youta's side~
(Sound of door opening and closing) (Sound of rain)
(Sumita) Please don't call me on a day like this.
(Igarashi) Oh, Sumi-chan, it’s been a while.
-(Sumita) It's been a while.-(Igarashi) What? A day like this
‎Typhoon, you might not be able to go home
(Igarashi) Well, that's fine. Let's drink until morning today.
(Sumita) Yes, yes.
(Igarashi) Is it Kahlua?
(Sumita) No, I'm restricting my sugar intake.
(Sound of the wind)
(Earphones: ♪ “Ah”)
‎Not enough at all
If you do not submit a formal request to logistics, can I go and pick it up?
(Firefly) This is how many signatures we have gathered!
Why are you ignoring the voices of residents and proceeding with the plan?
‎I'll blow you away
(Akari) This person is trying to blow me away.
I wonder if it's "unreasonable"
I will definitely protect you
‎What happened?
‎Mom, are you scared?
‎No.
‎Youta?
‎Youta
‎Youta!
(Yota) I'll blow you away! ‎I'll blow it away! I'll blow you away!
‎I'll blow it away! I'll blow you away!
‎I'll blow you away...
(Hotaru) Yota What are you doing? Let's go! I'll blow you away! I'll blow you away!
Let's go! I'll blow you away... I'll blow you away!
I'll blow you away... I'll blow you away!
(Fireflies) I'm going to catch a cold. I'm going to catch a cold.
‎Don't be afraid, Mom.
‎Huh?
‎I'm fine! courage!
‎Flower!
‎Bloom!
‎Please come
(Igarashi) Good morning
(Mari) It's not early.
I was worried, I didn't even answer the phone.
bad bad
But the harvest is perfect.
Please don't bring anything damn!
(Igarashi) If you know him and know yourself, there will be no more than 100 battles.
‎Research on rival horses is a must
‎-(Mari) Ugh... ‎-(Akari) Is that all there is to harvesting?
‎No way
I've heard about the anti-Meteor faction of the Metropolitan Federation.
‎How was it there? Are fireflies coming?
‎Um...
‎(Fireflies) came
I felt like it
Welcome back
I'm home
I'll blow you away
(Amemiya) I feel like...this is something that I shouldn't ignore.
(Announcement) The number you dialed is
I can't connect you
I hope I don't get lost.
yeah?
picture?
Wow, that's amazing.
(Subaru) Mari Hoshino
It seems that he has started running a public bathhouse.
Sorry, Subaru, please explain slowly.
oh sorry
Mari Hoshino is
To manage a public bath...
(Ryusei) Oh, I'm sorry, that's not true.
picture?
(Mari) Akari Tsukioka
Let's work together to make things brighter
(Toru) Prepare it.
-(Mari) So... -(Akari) Did you do it?
(Takaomi) I could see it all the time, inside your belly.
(Ryusei) Can I leave you a message?
(Mari) Please do it for me!
Huh!
(Amemiya) Mari-san, isn't she my god?
(Mari) Being dependent on someone is a nuisance.
(Igarashi) Me and Hotaru will split the votes.
(Mari) If things continue like this, the secretary-general's dog will win.
(Everyone) We'll win! Let's win!
-(Mari) We'll win! -(Akari and others) We'll win!
(Mari) I'll win!
(Akari and others) We'll win!