(Mari (Matsuri)) Ha ha...
(Mari) It's been like that since I was a child.
When you find something you are aiming for, go straight towards it.
(crow crow)
I wanted to see the crow's house
I wanted to touch the base of the rainbow
I feel like I can see the galaxy track
‎Run
‎Run, run
‎I got lost
For some reason, whenever I get lost,
Go to a dark and narrow place
(Mari's shortness of breath)
‎(Mari) Because⸺
I'm scared of bright, wide spaces
(Mari) Until the world is happy...
(Mari) The world was too wide for me
‎♪～
‎～♪
(Tap sound) (Video audio)
‎(Mari) Good morning
(Takaomi) I can't really say it.
(Momoka) Eh! ‎Mari-chan is cute today
‎Date?
‎Meeting with Tanohata Construction
(Takaomi) The target is the managing director, not the president.
‎I know
-(Momoka) Please‎-(Mari) Yes.
(Shutter sound)
-(Momoka) Hello‎-(Mari) Yes.
‎Itadakimasu
(Momoka) Wait
It arrived yesterday
‎Apple jam that has been waiting for reservations for 2 years!
Ah, Saturday's birthday party.
‎Ryuzaki‎The president?
‎Well, say no.
(Mari) Huh?
(Takaomi) Recently, he was hanging out with the Prime Minister and he was spreading bad reviews about me.
‎I don't have the time or money to spend on someone like that.
‎It's over with Ryuzaki-san.
Have you checked?
‎Is it true that there are negative reviews?
It might be a trap
Someone who wants to destroy the relationship between his father and President Ryuzaki.
‎Dad, you said that President Ryuzaki is a benefactor.
‎Jasmine
‎Understand
(Momoka) I will go on your behalf.
(Mari) Huh?
‎It's better than a surprise cancellation.
Thanks to you, I have plenty of money and time.
(Mari) But the venue is a tatami room...
(Momoka) Is that why?
‎Yes
‎This to someone's friend
(Mari) Thank you
‎(Peach flower) I'll have it
(Mari) Until the world is completely happy
individual happiness is impossible
What does it mean to live correctly and strongly?
Be aware of the galaxy within yourself
It is to go according to this
‎Correct and strong...
(Mari) That
‎Sorry
‎It is dangerous to block the Braille blocks ‎If you have a visually impaired person...
(Male) If they come, I'll move them away.
‎Excuse me, but
When I called out to you earlier, you didn't notice right away, right?
What is your field of vision when staring at your smartphone?
Research shows that it is 1/20th of normal levels.
‎Secretary-General Good morning
(Mari) 9:00 a.m. Board of Directors meeting 11:00 a.m. Regular press conference
‎11:30 Secretary General's Office Meeting
‎13:00 Plenary session
‎3 recs starting at 3:15 p.m.
‎Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare regarding pension reform
‎Ministry of Finance Asian Reconstruction Bank‎Regarding the next president
(Kuzuishi) Good morning, Secretary-General
(Mari) Today is one year since the Tokai heavy rain disaster.
‎Please add your comments at the press conference.
‎This is the manuscript
(knock)
(Shizukuishi) Excuse me. (Sound of door opening)
Here is a hypothetical question and answer about the prime minister's gaffe.
(lock sound)
(Shizukuishi) Something?
Nice color suit
‎Thank you
‎Your daughter is also very gorgeous today.
‎Because it's a meeting with Tanohata Construction at night.
‎I see
(Mari) Excuse me.
‎Please say no to the party‎President Ryuzaki's
‎If Momoka-san goes on your behalf...
(Takaomi) It's a nuisance, isn't it? Even if that happens...
‎I understand.
- (Shizukuishi) Young lady - (Mari) Yes.
(Shizukuishi) Possible questions and answers regarding the Prime Minister's gaffe. Can I have a paper copy?
I was able to make an appointment with Mr. Matsukura, Chairman of the Japan Respiratory Association.
I would like to hear your opinion, because I don't want it to turn into a bush snake.
‎I understand
(Nodamura) As expected, you have a wide face, Shizu-san.
The Secretary-General was a close friend of the Secretary-General when he was Minister of Health, Labor and Welfare.
‎Please
- (Shizukuishi) Thank you. - (Takizawa) Are you back?
- (Shizukuishi) At 10:30 - (Takizawa) Yes.
(Sumita) Takizawa-kun, there's something on his back
(Takizawa) Yes? ‎What?
(Sumita) Oh, that's shit.
It's bird poop
-(Takizawa) Huh! -(Sumita) Here, here, here.
(Nodamura) I got angry.
(Sumita) That's definitely what a middle-aged man would say.
(Takizawa) Wow, the worst
‎Please
‎Thank you
(Hiraizumi) Waited
(Takizawa) Huh?
(Hiraizumi) Don't wipe up bird droppings...
‎Pinch
(Takizawa) Oh...
‎Chief
I was told that the Tozai newspaper interview would start at 1pm.
‎It was a mistake at 14:00‎I'm sorry.
It's rare for a young lady to make a mistake at 2 p.m.
-(Mari) Yes‎-(Nodamura) Understood
(Sumita) Delicious tea
(Nodamura) Thank you
I'm going to the Diet Building
(All) Welcome. Hello.
(Elevator arrival sound)
(Mari) Thank you for your hard work.
‎Assumed questions and answers...
There seems to be no problem
‎Thank you
I'm going to go to the Diet Building for a moment.
‎Yes
(Mari) Ah!
(Shizukuishi) Something?
There's something attached
(Shizukuishi) Huh?
‎Ah...maybe lipstick
I have also been tagged on a train before.
-(Mari) Here it is‎-(Shizukuishi) Ah...
‎My makeup remover removes it.
‎Ah, there I am at the hall.
‎I'll drop it by the way.
It's okay. I'll make it in time for the press conference.
‎-(Shizukuishi) Miss... ‎-(Mari) Excuse me.
(Mari) Ha ha...
-(Mari) I'd like the duplicate key, please.-(Salesperson) Oh, yes.
‎Thank you for waiting
‎Thank you
(Ryusei) Due to the accelerated aging of the population,
Our country's insurance finances are in crisis.
Would you like to talk about the before instead of the after?
‎Before, not after...
(Sumita) Hiyama Ryusei is attacking again today.
‎It doesn't make sense though
It's (Mari)
‎Actually, we're dating.
‎No
‎You lived together, right?
‎When we were children‎We were like siblings.
‎Oh, on the contrary.
‎Ah! rooibos tea
(Sumita) Rooibos tea?
‎Currently, the secretary general told me to refrain from caffeine and prepare it before the lecture.
‎What should I do... ‎I have to create materials.
(Sumita) Ah, then I should go buy some...
‎Thank you!
‎Um...
Preferably here
‎-(Sumita) That's far... ‎-(Mari) Sorry.
(Sumita) On the contrary, I haven't been getting enough exercise lately.
(Mari) Ah, thank you...
(Sumita) Currently restricting carbohydrates due to metabolic syndrome
‎Then I'll go.
(Mari) Thank you
(unlocking sound)
‎Ah, welcome back
I forgot to change the water in the morning.
(Shizukuishi) Is that so?
(Mari) It was quick.
‎Return time is 15:00
‎Because it is an emergency situation
Governor Yanagihara appears to be resigning
‎Huh?
(Shizukuishi) Fact confirmation and if it is true
Candidates must be selected immediately
There will be an election within 50 days.
Please skip all the Secretary-General's schedule after 4:00 pm.
(Mari) Yes
(Shizukuishi) Come to think of it, young lady.
Where did you drop your lipstick?
You said it was at the Diet Building.
When I saw him running in the opposite direction, I saw Mr. Kamaishi from the general affairs office.
‎I went to buy jam.
‎Jam?
(Mari) Um... this
It's very popular right now and sells out quickly.
At that time, I wondered if I could buy it now.
‎During business hours‎I'm sorry.
(Vibration sound of mobile phone)
(Shizukuishi) Yes, this is Shizukuishi.
(phone ringtone)
(Acting Secretary-General) The official announcement will be made at the Tokyo Metropolitan Assembly plenary session next week.
The media...
(Shizukuishi) Probably tomorrow
(Deputy Secretary-General) Is the tide really high?... The approval rating has fallen completely.
(Deputy Secretary-General) I never thought I would be forced to eat poisonous steamed buns.
‎Mr. Yanagihara
‎Ha... I can't believe I'm actually going to eat it.
(Takaomi's laughter)
(Mari's crying)
(Ruri) Mari
‎(Ruri) Mari…
If you get lost, go to the bright side
(Mari) Are you a bright person?
Yes, the bright one
Don't go to dark places
‎What if I don't understand?
Which one is brighter?
‎Done
When you don't know which one is brighter...
‎Picky
‎Hehe
(footsteps)
(Ryusei) Battery dead?
‎Ah
‎(Ryusei) Ossu
(Mari) It's broken.
Even if I change the battery, it doesn't work anymore
‎Not (Ryusei), but Mari-chan
‎Huh?
‎My name is Mari-chan.
Are you the type of person who can't keep track of your battery level?
One day, it will suddenly become zero, so be careful.
‎You're saying things that will get you cut out.
(Ryusei) Huh?
-(Mari) It's become a buzz‎-(Ryuusei) Ah...
I'm sure it will look great
‎I lose to Momoka-san though
Look, the number of followers has increased again.
‎-(Mari) Flaming business method‎-(Ryusei) Huh?
(Mari) Purposely go to places that aren't barrier-free.
I'm sad that I couldn't get in
‎Strong
‎Ah, today's secretary general's press conference
It was Mari who made me mention the Tokai heavy rains, right? It's working.
It's easy, isn't it?
(Ryusei) Foot…
‎-(Mari) Oh, wait a minute‎-(Ryuusei) What...
It would be troublesome if someone saw me again and misunderstood.
‎It's okay
‎No one really comes here.
‎I only told Mari-chan.
‎My best slacking spot
‎Hmm...
‎Did you hear it? Governor's case
‎Yeah
It's a chance
‎Huh?
(Ryusei) I always say that.
Become Tokyo Governor and change national politics from the Tokyo model
(Mari) Don't tell anyone.
‎Especially now, never to your father.
‎I didn't say it. I didn't say it.
Why don't you say it?
There's no way I'd get a recommendation, right?
‎You can run for office even if you don't get it.
(Mari) There's no way I can win. I have no track record or popularity.
Well, the gubernatorial election is essentially a popular vote.
-(Mari) Then, what about Ryu-chan? -(Ryusei) Huh?
‎It's buzzing, and the name is selling well with the release of Gilba hostages.
‎Thanks to that, I have many enemies.
‎It's not easy in Nagatacho.
Well, that's what's interesting though
I have no intention of stepping down from national politics.
The constitution of the party must be changed from within.
If we don't change, Japan has no future.
Ryu-chan is strong, isn't he?
‎Really?
(Mari) Mom said so.
‎Strength is brightness
Mari-chan, you've been wearing it around your neck for a long time.
‎After receiving it from Ruri-san
From junior high school onwards, I put it on my bag.
‎Yes Amulet
‎Huh? Are you going to take it?
‎There's a meeting after this.
It's unseemly, so at least take it off when you go out in public.
‎To my father...
If you get lost, go to the bright side
(Ryusei) Huh?
‎It arrived yesterday
‎Not yet with my father...
‎I haven't shown it to anyone
‎Huh?
‎What is this?
‎Naranoki Medical University...
(Mari) The hospital where my mother was hospitalized
(Ryusei) From whom?
‎Do you know? this person
‎I have never met
But maybe my father has met him.
‎Huh?
‎5 years ago‎Shortly after I became my father's secretary
When Mr. Shizukuishi asked me to organize business cards and enter data...
‎This person's business card
‎But⸺
It was gone
(Ryusei) Huh?
I tried looking for it last night.
It disappeared from both paper files and data.
After my father became a member of parliament, the business cards he received were
I'm supposed to have kept everything.
Isn't your memory wrong?
‎I just saw it for a moment 5 years ago.
But it was my mother's hospital.
‎Later…
‎-(Mari) I can't read it as zaneri‎-(ryusei) zaneri?
‎The boy who appears in "Night on the Galaxy Express"
That's why I remembered
‎But
I checked it out
Mr. Shizukuishi's handwritten activity record
‎It's kind of strange, isn't it?
(Ryusei) Hmm, five years ago.
This was when the secretary general was the Minister of Health, Labor and Welfare.
‎Well, yes, not at all.
‎Don't let the bureaucrats pass
Go and listen to stories about the medical field directly
Ruri-san was hospitalized, so it might have something to do with that.
But it's Malivron.
‎A place to use for secret discussions that you definitely don't want to leak.
‎5 years ago, my father
‎Meet this person
‎8 days ago, this person passed away.
This arrived at the Secretary-General's office yesterday.
‎My business card and data have disappeared ‎That's...
‎Wait, wait, wait
‎I'm in a strange mode again.
Just ask the general secretary.
‎-(Mari) But... ‎-(Ryuusei) Huh?
‎You're going to crush it, right?
‎If this were true
‎Mari-chan
I don't think it was pushed down or something like that.
‎(Meteor) Of course
But I think there is a thing called pushing.
You've changed, haven't you, Dad?
After my mother died
‎Because I've seen it for the past five years
That's what my father said...
(Takaomi) Retirement allowance.
Let's assume it's a mental and physical illness.
‎I resigned due to mental and physical illness.
I mean, I've seen it
‎I have been complicit
‎Because
‎If
‎This person was chased by his father
In that case, I am also responsible...
There's no such thing as no
Because there is no
‎Understood
‎Let me keep it for a while
I have friends at Naranoki Medical University and the Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare.
I'll try to find out
‎Sorry for getting you involved.
It's better than running around alone and getting lost...
‎Thank you
(cell phone vibration sound)
‎Ah, Ryu-chan‎If you like, this...
‎Ah, sorry, hey...
‎This is Hiyama.
‎We apologize for the inconvenience.
‎No, no, what happened?
(Mari) Please
‎-(Mari) Managing Director too‎-(Senior Managing Director) Oh…
(Managing Director) When there's a girl like you, the drinking goes on.
(laughter)
Please don't drink too much
(Executives) Oh~ That's a nice drink.
‎Thank you
-(Managing Director) Would you like another drink? -(Mari) Ah, no, no, already...
(Female employee) Excuse me, but
Honestly, it's hard
‎Huh?
(Female employee) What we are fighting to change
‎What happens when you are defeated by someone on that side?
‎Eh...
(Female employee) It seems like she emphasizes and uses the fact that she is a woman.
(Mari and others) Thank you for your hard work.
(Managing Director) Huh?
‎It's okay, it's okay
(Mari) Ah...
‎That after-party venue...
‎Because there are good stores
Let's have a drink together, okay?
I'm listening
Is it finally time to run? ‎Next House of Representatives election
‎I'll help you, just like your father.
‎We are uncles
If you were as cute as me
‎I'm going to go crazy
It's easy
It's easy, isn't it?
have been complicit
-(Mari) Please stop.-(Managing Director) What? What...
Please stop! I'll report it.
(Mari) Ha ha...
(Sound of bag falling)
(Mari) Huh!
‎Hmm! Huh!
‎Ha... ha...
(Light) Did you drop something?
What is it? what kind?
Ah... that light bulb...
‎Light bulb?
‎Ah… yes, a toy.
It's a talisman
‎Understand
‎Ah, no, that's it...
(Light) It's something important, right?
It's okay, I'll find it
‎Thank you
‎Huh? I thought it was here.
‎Oh, it's going to get dirty.
(Mari) It's okay. I wore the clothes with a malicious feeling.
(Light) Yokoshima?
(Mari) Huh... Uncles seem to like it.
(Light) Ahahaha…
I love my aunt too
‎That's cute
‎It suits you
‎Me too...
‎It's so cute...
I bought it because I thought it would look good on me.
Yes, it's cute and suits you
(Vibration sound of mobile phone)
‎(Light) Yes, yes
‎Ah, sorry‎Wait a little longer
‎Yes, yes
‎Sorry
‎Um... It's okay now.
(Akari) Ah, it's totally fine. This is the phone call I just made.
No, I have to go home too.
(Akari) Oh, I see.
Sorry, I couldn't find it.
‎That's it...
‎Ah, if you don't mind, this is it.
(Akari) Okay, that's it.
‎Sorry
Food from strangers is scary, isn't it?
(Akari) No, no, that's it...
‎Wow...
‎He's such an amazing person.
No, not at all
Thank you for searching with me.
‎Thank you then.
Ah, around here, there's a place where you can get a taxi...
If you go down the main street, you'll see a lot of people running.
‎Well, go over there to the left.
Go to the next corner to the right.
‎Ah, I'll send it to you.
‎Ah, no, it's okay.
‎The bright one anyway
‎Toward the bright side
‎Hmm?
Sorry, thank you very much
‎Thank you
‎Foo
‎I'm home now
‎(Momoka) Welcome back
Sorry I couldn't answer the phone
‎Retirement allowance
(Mari) Huh?
‎I will tell everyone that I am mentally and physically unwell.
‎Don't go near my hometown or Nagatacho in the future.
I won't tell you to leave my house
‎A spoiled naive person ‎does not expect to be able to support himself immediately.
‎Just...
Wait a minute, that's a lie, isn't it...
‎This kind of thing?
‎I did something I shouldn't have done.
‎As a secretary and as a daughter
‎Is that what you mean?
‎Ha…
Is that why it's so easy to cut?
‎One-sidedly without even listening...
(Mobile phone ringtone)
(Takaomi) Ah, I'm leaving now.
(Mari) Did you kill her?
‎Do I cut it off and rub it away?
My daughter says she's crazy
(Takaomi) What are you so stupid about...
If so, let me know
‎April 19, 5 years ago
What did you talk about with this person at Malivron?
‎Why are my business cards missing? ‎Why did this letter come?
(Takaomi) Stupid
(Mari) It's not worth it!
‎People are dying.
Maybe it's the people your father discarded...
‎Why? ‎Why did it happen like that?
‎You taught me your mother's last words
Aren't you embarrassed? to mom
‎I have no friends
(Momoka) Huh?
‎What if your parents were found out to be politicians?
‎Will you be attracted to me or made fun of?
‎Will you be teased? ‎Will you have a strange interest in me?
There are restrictions on who you can play with, where you can go, and what you can buy.
‎Local ceremonial occasions on Saturdays and Sundays
‎Help with events Help with elections
‎So that you can win
‎My father wants me to win the next election too.
‎I sold a joke and told a lie.
‎Swallowing all sorts of things‎Me and my mom too
‎But it was good. Still
‎One day I will be like my father...
‎(Ying Chen) Jasmine!
‎Understand
(Momoka) Mari-chan?
(Takaomi) Thank you for the long wait.
It's hot, so be careful.
‎Yes, we still have it.‎Please refill it.
(Mari) Mother...
‎Mom Mom
‎-(Ruri) Mari... ‎-(Mari) Yeah.
‎Toward the bright side...
‎Correctly...
‎Strongly...
(Momoka) Are you leaving?
I forgot to mention that President Ryuzaki's party was...
‎Let's go
It's my ring
‎Ring?
‎This house too
‎To live with me
This house was built with my dad's money.
‎Ha... That's hilarious.
‎Stairs that stand out like this
‎I don't mean any harm.
‎Just not there
‎In the world of that person and everyone
‎We are
That's why I'm here
That's my fight
Is Mari okay?
‎Keep being beaten
Do you want to get out of the ring, let the hecklers fly away and die?
‎You're not that kind of balls, are you?
(Message notification sound)
(Vibration sound of mobile phone)
‎Mari-chan?
(Mari) Are you coming? Tokyo gubernatorial election
National Government: You said you had no intention of quitting, right?
‎Why? What did your father say?
‎What are the conditions for running? ‎Money? ground?
Is that why you betrayed me and gave me the letter?
‎I'll be in trouble if my father loses his footing.
‎It's okay to be in trouble.
It's not just me
‎You know, right? Even Mari-chan
‎Apologies to the Secretary-General
Don't forget about the letter
‎If it stays like this, Mari-chan
‎I can never return to politics.
‎What if?
‎Just in case
It is assumed that the secretary general had something to do with the dean's suicide.
‎What's the point of revealing that?
Dead people don't come back to life
‎Who will be saved?
The bereaved family...
‎(Ryusei) ‎You might just suffer more.
‎Truth does not equal salvation.
But who wrote that letter...
(Ryusei) If you want to expose it
‎Now is the time to do it easily.
‎Anyone can send messages to the world in an instant
‎I'll do it if I want to do it
You don't have to do it for me.
Maybe it was the current politics that drove him to suicide.
‎In that case, the secretary general is certainly...
Maybe it means we killed him.
But if you take responsibility for each one, there's no end to it.
‎What we can do
‎Changing politics
‎If I win
‎Nominate Mari-chan as deputy governor
‎From the Tokyo model‎You want to change Japan, right?
Let's change it together
‎Make it a country where no one is forced into anything anymore
‎The power and position to do that
‎You can't let go of the death of a citizen.
‎We are
‎Be on the side of influencing
‎The people who carry the country on their backs
‎Do not carry your burden on yourself
‎Not just that dean.
‎Many people die every day
But most of those deaths
‎Does not affect the country
‎Really?
‎Huh?
Does the death of one citizen really have no effect?
‎To the country...
‎For universal happiness in the world
‎I won't forget that letter
‎To forget
Which one is brighter?
Which one is correct and strong?
(tap sound)
(Sound of door opening)
‎Thank you
(Shopkeeper) Waiting for you.
(Sound of a white cane hitting)
‎Sorry!
‎(Male) No, you're welcome.
(Vibration sound of mobile phone)
(Laughter can be heard from inside the store)
(loud voice)
-(Atsushi) Mom Customer! -(Akari) Yes
‎Welcome
‎Ah, it’s here, it’s here! come in come in
‎Excuse me
(Kanbayashi) Eh, traveling?
-(Mari) Yes‎-(Akari) Eh, nice.
‎Where are you going?
‎Um, uh...
‎Galaxy…
‎See the galaxy
‎What? Is the galaxy the Milky Way?
- (Atsushi) Ah, then it's a mountain. - (Yama-san) Eh, why a mountain?
(Atsushi) You can't see the Milky Way unless you go to the mountains, right?
(Light) It seems that you can see it even in Tokyo.
‎-(Customers) No, no, I can't see‎-(Light) Really, really.
Close your eyes for about 10 minutes at a high place
When you open it like this and look at the sky
‎The stars look bright.
(exciting voice)
‎Sorry Sorry
‎This is it, right?
(Mari) Did you look for it and give it to me? After that
‎Just a little bit
‎Thank you
(Akari) It's okay, it's okay
‎Do you have some time?
‎Huh?
(Light) Please
(Mari) This...
This is the jam I got earlier.
‎This is delicious.
And now for the rest, this is our signature egg sandwich.
I went to buy these eggs a while ago.
I said I'm done with egg sandwiches today.
‎Acchan...
‎Ahaha this old man
‎You say selfishly that you really want to eat an egg sandwich.
(Atsushi) Mengo Mengo (Akari's laughter)
‎(Akari) Eat and eat
‎-(Mari) Itadakimasu‎-(Akari) Yes.
(Mari) What should I do...
‎What should I do?
‎Is this kind of influence‎ going to be given?
‎Who...
‎The country becomes the people
‎Country?
‎Policies of the Democratic Party...
‎Review of medical expense burden and ‎Revision of child welfare law
‎Governor Yanagihara's distribution of tax-free household gift certificates ‎Various benefits
Are you really contributing? ‎For everyone's happiness
‎Are you having any trouble?
‎Things that are missing or too much ‎Things you are worried about or things you can't keep up with
-(Atsushi) That's too much. -(Chiko-chan and others) Yeah.
(Chiko-chan) No, even if you say it's a stipend.
‎Taxes will just come back
(Mari-san) I don't have any children.
‎What about children? Sorry, not so much...
(Kanbayashi) Well, single freelancers...
‎There's almost no benefit.
(Atsushi) But when it comes to the country, we have no choice but to leave it to the great people.
We are doing our best to take care of ourselves.
‎I guess I don't really understand politics. Sorry.
It's like you can't reach it
I can't change even if I want to
It's not about politics
It's our story
‎Me and yours
‎Hands are within reach
‎It's no good if it doesn't reach you.
Have you ever tried to change something that you can't change?
Politicians are not great people.
‎Just a representative of our
Isn't it hard?
‎Everyone⸺
What a world full of myself...
‎It doesn't arrive
‎You made me feel like I couldn't change.
I'm really sorry for saying that being a citizen is easy.
‎Who?
‎I
‎But
Don't let go of your right to pursue happiness
Until the whole world is happy
‎Individual happiness is impossible!
‎Me...
Please don't leave me alone
Sorry, I hit eight.
‎Excuse me
(sound of door closing)
(Mari) Ha ha...
‎Sorry for a moment
(Mari's shortness of breath)
(Mari) Wow!
(Akari) Huh...
-(Akari) Wait!-(Mari) Huh?
-(Akari) Hey, wait‎-(Mari) Please let me go for a second.
(Akari) Don't let go! ‎I'll never let you go!
(Mari) Huh?
‎I decided! ‎Next time, I'll never let you go
‎Don't leave me alone
‎It's okay
‎I'll look for it
‎What I can do
‎It's no longer possible.
‎Searching and thinking
‎To say help me
It's already zero Charging
‎Sorry
‎Don't know what happened
But because I know, I
The feeling you get when you think you have no choice but to die
There was something I tried to change.
But it didn't work
All the important things are now gone
That's why I gave up
‎I have no choice but to accept it.
Even if you want to change, it's just hard
‎Sorry
You were talking about us.
‎I'll search for it
‎Because I think
‎What I can do
If I find you, I'll do anything.
So please
‎Don't die
‎I won't die
(Akari) Huh?
But now...
‎Ah... I want to see it
‎Galaxy?
‎You mentioned it earlier.
‎You can see it even in Tokyo
Go up high and close your eyes for 10 minutes.
‎Ah!
‎Ah... I see.
‎I see, ha…
But it's dangerous, right?
(Mari) I'm sorry.
‎Good...
‎Good!
‎Why?
‎Why is that so...
Because it has no effect.
Even if I die, in your life
‎That can't be true.
‎It's huge! It has a huge impact!
You said it earlier.
Until the world is completely happy
Personal happiness is impossible
Even you
It's part of the world
for me to be happy
I need you to be happy too
Toshiko-san
Ah... sorry
That store is borrowed.
My name is Tsukioka Akari
Akari?
(Akari) Huh?
Um... how did you know?
that I'm here
Ah... it was shining
(Mari) Was it shining?
Yeah that
(Mari) This doesn't shine.
It's broken...
but⸺
It was shining
(Ruri) Mari!
(Mari) It's been like that since I was a child.
‎What happened?
(Mari) When you find something to aim for
Straight towards it
‎Akari Tsukioka
‎Would you like to become the governor of Tokyo?
‎Governor?
Governor Yanagihara will resign soon
Would you like to run in the election that will be held within 50 days?
‎Huh?
The strongest rival is the candidate recommended by the largest ruling party, the Democratic Party.
But I
I'm in charge of the scandal that is destroying the Democratic Party.
‎If you are sure that you get the tails
I'll destroy it
‎Akari Tsukioka‎Please become the governor of Tokyo.
Please nominate me as lieutenant governor.
Ha, Deputy Governor...
‎World...
‎The world and you
‎For my happiness
Eh, why me?
There's one chance of winning.
(Reporter) Regarding the candidates for the Tokyo gubernatorial election
I would like to ask you
(Atsushi) What do you think about the next Tokyo governor?
(Atsushi) What do you think about the next Tokyo governor? (Yama-san) Looks like there will be a meteor shower on Hiyama.
(Yama-san) Looks like there will be a meteor shower on Hiyama.
(Mari) Strike with a deadly blow!
I don't want to miss you
It's you