[Ever-growing Radiance]
How is Leyu now?
Consort Su has always been intellegent
and skilled in martial arts.
She will surely turn danger into safety.
In the Changding Bridge case,
they failed to strip
the Su family of their military power.
Now they've seized on this matter
to try again
and stir things up.
It looks like they're targeting
the Su family,
but in reality,
they want to clip my wings.
Consort Su is in danger.
Your Majesty,
is this why you recalled Director Yin
to investigate the case?
Keep him alive!
Yin Cong,
I didn't expect to find you here.
This place borders the imperial tombs,
so I often come here for night hunting.
Wencheng,
I heard that near the imperial tomb
is a good place for night hunting.
With little vegetation
and frequent troop patrols,
few beasts are seen there.
Night hunting would be impossible there.
Why don't we go to the forest
outside the city?
[Luminosity Behind The Palace]
Stop.
What's this?
Take a look. There's nothing else.
You can go now.
Next one.
[Wanted]
Thank you, officer.
Open it and let me see.
[Wanted]
Alright. Next.
Thank you, officer.
You.
Remove your face covering.
I'm talking to you.
Take off your face covering.
After her!
Stop!
Move!
Don't run!
Stop!
-Hurry!
-Stop!
This way!
-Hurry!
-After her!
Search the place!
Let's go!
Over there!
Let's go search elsewhere.
Don't let her get away.
Find a way
to get this
to Consort Su's maid, Lady Song.
Be careful,
and tell her
to wait for the order
and appear at the critical moment.
I can only entrust this task to you.
You must succeed.
[Poetry Collection]
[Lu Yueying]
Lest we part, when rainbows fade away.
Where could we find a brighter day?
Do not refuse to get drunk.
Beneath the bright moon and lovely blooms,
treasure this night.
[Poetry Collection Lu Yueying]
[500 Taels]
[Wanted]
Anyone who provides a lead
will be rewarded
with 100 taels of silver.
[Wanted]
Isn't she from the Su family?
[The suspect, Su Leyu, female]
Isn't that Consort Xian?
Leyu, are you alright?
I nearly died.
Someone wants to kill you?
Luckily, you still remember
our secret signal from childhood.
Why were you with
officers from the Justice Bureau?
His Majesty recalled me to investigate
the Number Three Scholar case.
Really?
That's wonderful.
With you here,
the truth of this case
will surely come to light.
You didn't escape from prison yourself,
did you?
Of course not.
I discovered something suspicious
about that jailer.
He poisoned my food.
I took the chance to spit it out.
But I didn't expect
he would suddenly knock me out
and take me to the mass grave.
I was almost buried alive.
Now that the jailer is dead
and you've disappeared,
it looks like you escaped from the prison
and committed murder.
Indeed.
Now that I've disappeared,
they can freely slander me
and pin the crime on me.
In this way,
the Court of Judicial Review
has also fallen into a passive position.
The court couldn't agree
on who should handle the case.
That's why His Majesty recalled me.
I'm from the Qin family.
With me investigating,
Grand Preceptor Qin won't object,
and neither will Wang Zhan.
Yin Cong,
you had already escaped
from court politics,
but now because of me,
you're trapped in this political cage
again.
I'm sorry.
Leyu,
ever since the day the Qin family
sent me into the palace,
I was destined
never to escape court politics.
As a daughter of the Qin family,
you are both intelligent and brave,
and your loyalty is commendable.
Qin Cong,
you have rendered great service
by saving Prince Qi.
You risked your life
and showed extraordinary courage.
I grant you the imperial surname Yin
and bestow upon you the title
of Princess Zhaoyang.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
From the day the late empress
granted me this surname,
I was no longer a Qin.
It wasn't until I served the late empress
that my horizons were broadened,
and I realized that in court, one could
debate freely regardless of rank,
with rulers and ministers sitting together
and exchanging ideas openly.
I was fortunate
to have met you all back then.
I remember back on the city tower,
we once pledged
to build a prosperous Dacang together.
Now that you've returned,
we shall start with this case
to eliminate corruption
and uphold justice.
Did you find anything
in Lu Yueying's room?
Lu Yueying died
from a blow to the back of her head,
yet her body was hung from the beam
to make it look like suicide.
Lifting the body
and hanging it so high
requires height and strength,
so the perpetrator is likely male.
As for motive,
few men had grievances with Lu Yueying.
Liu Wenchong
and Wang Lin
both did.
We can start with them.
When I was investigating
at the Imperial Academy,
a student told me that
on the night Lu Yueying was killed,
he saw Liu Wenchong
sneaking out from the direction
of Lu Yueying's room.
Let's go find Liu Wenchong first.
Who are you?
[Justice Bureau]
The Justice Bureau
is investigating a case.
There are some things about Lu Yueying
we want to confirm with you.
I've already reported everything
to the Court of Judicial Review.
There's really nothing more to say.
On the night of the Qionglin Banquet,
did you go looking for Lu Yueying?
That night, I...
You'd better tell the truth,
or you'll get a taste
of what the Justice Bureau can do.
It's not that I don't want to say,
it's just that what happened that night
was too strange.
I don't know if anyone would believe me.
That night,
I was so angry
that I went to the Imperial Academy
to find Lu Yueying.
Say no more.
You can ask around—
I, Lu Yueying, have always relied
on my genuine knowledge.
Let go!
A fox demon?
Are you saying
you first saw Lu Yueying
arguing with someone,
and then saw a fox demon
in her room?
That fox demon
seemed injured and bleeding.
When it noticed I had discovered it,
it ran back into the room
and then disappeared.
Did you see
who she was arguing with?
It was too dark. I didn't see clearly.
But I heard Lu Yueying
call the person "Scholar."
That night,
all the officials of the Imperial Academy
were at the Qionglin Banquet.
Only the Dean, Lord Ming Qian,
had returned early.
[Imperial Academy]
Let us out!
Move!
We need to go out and file a complaint!
Let us out!
[Imperial Academy]
Students,
students,
please calm down.
This matter hasn't been settled yet.
You should all return to your studies.
That's what's most important now.
How can we focus on our studies like this?
Lord Ming,
because of Lu Yueying,
the court will hold a re-examination.
After all our hard study,
we finally earned our official ranks.
Won't all our efforts be in vain?
That's right!
-It'll be all in vain.
-Why should our results be canceled?
What if
we fail this time?
We need to file a complaint!
Yes, we must file a complaint!
Calm down!
Everyone, please calm down!
What are you doing?
Complaining here is one thing.
If you rush out of the Imperial Academy,
that would be causing trouble!
Whatever the reason,
you will be arrested and held accountable.
Students,
once this matter is settled,
I will inform you immediately.
For now, please go back.
Let's go.
Thank you, Director Yin.
Lord Ming,
may I talk to you privately?
Please.
Thank you again
for what happened today.
No need for thanks, Lord Ming.
And you are...
Lord Ming,
you must have recognized me, right?
Consort Xian.
Previously, you assisted His Majesty
in investigating the Changding Bridge case
and obtained evidence
of Xi Zimo's corruption.
You are truly a remarkable woman.
I deeply admire you.
This time,
we'd like to ask for your help
in solving the Number Three Scholar case.
What can I do
to help you?
Lord Ming,
on the night of the Qionglin Banquet,
before Lu Yueying died,
did you see her
in the Imperial Academy classroom?
I did not.
That night, after returning
from the Qionglin Banquet,
I stayed here working
and did not go to the classroom.
Lord Ming,
may we take a look around?
By all means.
[Having swept the fairy courtyard's jade-like mossy ground,
I see the languid breeze and brilliant moon through windows come around.]
Lord Ming,
these poems...
These poems are all my own work.
May I take one with me?
Of course.
Your Majesty,
are you worried about the imperial exams?
They're trying to use this incident
to force me to hold a re-examination,
undermine my authority
in the students' eyes,
and make more of them
turn to the noble families.
Any news from Leyu?
Your Majesty,
Consort Xian
is currently with Director Yin.
Would you like to summon her?
No need.
Have the secret guards keep watch.
Leyu shouldn't appear just yet.
Report to me immediately
if there's any news.
Yes.
[Justice Bureau]
Here are the exam papers
of all the students who passed this time.
This is Lu Yueying's paper.
[Lu Yueying, a candidate of the palace examination,
from Jinzhou, Jiangbei Province.]
One of the lines in her paper
is identical to a poem by Ming Qian,
word for word.
So,
you suspect Lord Ming Qian
was involved in cheating?
Lu Yueying's essay topic
[Third Place in the First Class]
matches Ming Qian's poem exactly.
Having swept the fairy courtyard's
jade-like mossy ground,
I see the languid breeze and brilliant moon
through windows come around.
It's very likely that
as Dean of the Imperial Academy,
Ming Qian revealed the exam lines
to Lu Yueying in advance.
Not knowing which question
His Majesty would select,
he might have told her all three key lines
from the possible questions.
[On ruling with reward and trust.]
[The founding Emperor
won Wu by ruling alone.]
[The last Emperor fell by ruling alone.]
[Same act, yet opposite results—why?]
The three examination questions
drafted for this year's imperial exams?
There may be something hidden behind this.
Leyu,
I know this is emotionally difficult
for you to accept,
but the evidence is right here.
But there are still doubts in this case.
For example,
why would Lord Ming Qian,
as an Imperial Academy official,
write the exam topics
in his own poem?
Could this poem
be forged?
But Lord Ming Qian just said
these poems are indeed his work.
This case still requires careful investigation.
Yin Cong,
we must not alert the suspects.
Very well.
[Taiji Palace]
Your Majesty,
it has been a while since the case of the Number Three Scholar
Lu Yueying's exam fraud.
If you don't hold a re-examination,
you will need to come to the Imperial Academy in seven days
along with the other passed candidates
to pay respects.
If anyone among them is involved in the fraud,
wouldn't that be a disgrace to Confucius
and bring shame to our Dacang?
This matter concerns our national dignity.
The Justice Bureau is investigating.
But Your Majesty,
I heard that
Director Yin has already identified
the person who assisted Lu Yueying in cheating.
Director Yin,
is that true?
Your Majesty,
I am currently investigating this case.
There are many suspicious points that need verification.
I...
Director Yin,
the Justice Bureau handles major cases.
You should indeed be cautious.
But the situation is urgent now
and concerns the state.
Progress is either there
or it isn't.
What does "still needs verification" mean?
Your Majesty,
I...
What?
Are the noble families
going to shield those guilty of cheating?
Lord Wang,
what reason would I have to shield anyone?
It's just that this case is full of suspicious points.
Full of suspicious points?
Director Yin, are you trying to delay things
to find excuses
for the suspect?
Lord Wang, please watch your words.
Current evidence points to
Lord Ming Qian being involved in the fraud case.
How is that possible?
That can't be.
How could it be Lord Ming?
Yes.
Lu Yueying's exam topic is identical
to Lord Ming Qian's poem.
Absurd!
How could my poem
appear on Lu Yueying's exam paper?
Lord Ming,
this case does indeed have doubts.
I am investigating.
But the poem found in your room
is exactly the same as the one
on Lu Yueying's exam paper.
Let me see it.
[Having swept the fairy
courtyard's jade-like mossy ground,]
[I see the languid breeze and brilliant
moon through windows come around.]
This...
Someone must be framing me!
Lord Ming,
this poem was obtained from you by Director Yin,
and your reaction just now
clearly proves
it is your handwriting.
Am I wrong?
This is not my writing.
Someone forged my handwriting
to frame me!
Your Majesty,
Ming Qian and Lu Yueying were originally teacher and student.
Lu Yueying, a woman,
only had the chance to take the imperial exams
because of Ming Qian's recommendation.
I believe Ming Qian
deliberately placed his student
in the position of Number Three Scholar.
You, Wang Zhan!
You are slandering me!
The handwriting is clearly yours.
Are you still trying to deny it?
If someone wants to condemn another,
they'll always find an excuse!
Lord Ming,
you are a scholar yourself.
The evidence is now conclusive.
How can you claim you're being falsely accused?
Are you trying to deny it
in front of His Majesty?
You...
Your Majesty,
I earnestly request that Ming Qian
and Lu Yueying's exam fraud case
be swiftly judged
to give the scholars of the world an explanation.
You...
Ming Qian.
Ming Qian must have a guilty conscience.
As the Dean of the Impartial Academy,
it's perfectly normal for him
to want to promote his student.
This is despicable.
-Yeah.
-That's despicable!
I never expected this.
Indeed.
I, Ming Qian, have always been honest and upright,
yet in the end,
my good reputation is ruined by a petty person.
Who is the petty person here?
The evidence is irrefutable.
Are you still trying to deny it?
Secret manipulations and cheating—
you are the petty one.
Your Majesty,
I
have failed the nation.
Please judge fairly.
If one day my name is cleared,
those scoundrels
will have nowhere to hide!
-Lord Ming!
Lord Ming!
Call the imperial physicians!
Lord Ming, wake up!
Lord Ming!
Servants! Call the imperial physicians!
Hurry!
Lord Ming!
Call the imperial physicians!
Lord Ming sacrificed himself for his principles.
I admire him greatly.
Wang Zhan!
Yin Cong!
Come in quickly.
Yin Cong,
what's wrong?
What happened?
Leyu,
I think I've made a mistake.
This morning at court,
Lord Ming Qian, trying to prove his innocence,
died by throwing himself against a pillar.
The court was in complete chaos,
and even His Majesty could not suppress it.
He used such a brutal way
to prove his innocence.
It's all my fault.
I'm the one who caused it.
I brought this upon him.
I never imagined they would use
Lord Ming Qian's poem to create such a scandal.
They used such a vicious method—
and you—
to drive Lord Ming to his death.
It's utterly despicable and outrageous.
Yin Cong, remember,
you must act
with even greater caution from now on.
You cannot be used by them again.
Yes.
Also,
from now on,
we probably cannot act together.
If you are implicated by me,
this case
may never be solved.
Don't worry.
I will see justice done
for the wrongful case against me,
Lady Lu's death,
and Lord Ming's grievance.