I have to say...
this scheme of yours
to pit enemies against each other
is brilliant.
This Ghost Soldiers Passing tactic
used the enemy's force to strike back.
If Su Leyu finds out about the truth,
she'll just help His Majesty
bring down the Xi family.
If she fails to uncover the truth,
it can still
weaken the Su family's power.
Either way,
you can remain in an unbeatable position.
This tactic
is brilliant.
Grand Preceptor, you're quite smart, too.
You're trying to
use the Xi family as a blade.
If the plan succeeds,
you can weaken His Majesty's power.
If it fails,
you can force Xi Zimo to commit suicide
and write a confession statement.
You can cut losses in time
and hide behind the scenes
with no harm to yourself at all.
Princess Zhaoyang,
we're quite alike.
Princess Zhaoyang doesn't
exist in Dacang anymore.
We're just black and white pieces
in this chess game.
I still prefer
calling you Princess.
After all, your surname is Yin.
[Luminosity Behind The Palace]
[Xianming Hall]
Princess Zhaoyang.
Tonight is Consort Xian's wedding night.
She can't receive guests now.
Wan.
Let her come in.
Yes.
This is a wedding gift for you.
I'm here to congratulate you
on your wedding.
May you and His Majesty
be like paired lovebirds
and love each other forever.
You're blaming me,
aren't you?
I have other plans.
That's why I've made this choice.
You're saying that you have other plans.
But in fact,
you've already chosen Yin Changyan.
Have you heard?
Yin Changyan has promoted Yue Menglin
to Minister of Revenue
to replace Xi Zimo.
He let Yue Menglin be the role model
and showed it to the whole country.
He used such cunning
and monarchical tactics.
But you didn't realize it?
You even helped him
eliminate his opponents?
Have you ever considered that
although Yang Yun was imprisoned,
we rescued her so easily
and we weren't hunted down afterwards?
The prison of the Court of Judicial Review
is not a place
where people can be rescued so easily.
I believe he was trying to buy time
for us
so that we could solve the case quickly.
So what?
He merely used you
to solve the case quickly
and establish his authority.
No matter what,
he saved my brother.
Yes.
General Su was exonerated,
and now you're going to be his consort.
The Su family's military power
is what he cares about the most.
Yin Cong, watch your tongue.
This country belongs to His Majesty,
and he can retrieve
this military power whenever he wants to.
You're still defending him now?
Back then, I asked you to leave with me.
But you said you would stay
for the sake of the country.
I think these were all just your excuses.
You just can't forget him.
It's not like that.
You witnessed
how he forced the empress
to abdicate and killed her.
But you still decided to
marry Yin Changyan
and be his consort.
How can you live up to
the late empress's expectations?
Are you worthy of
the golden age of Dacang you spoke of?
Yin Cong.
No matter how others misunderstand me,
it's fine.
But you can't misunderstand me.
I've never forgotten that night
at the Xuanji Pavilion.
I don't even dare to
forget the late empress's teachings.
Then why do you still want to marry him?
I once promised the late empress
that I would protect Dacang,
so I won't break my promise.
No matter what my status is,
I will do what I can for Dacang,
regardless of life or death.
His Majesty is here!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
You had an argument with Yin Cong?
Because you entered the palace
to be my consort?
Yin Cong only came here
to congratulate me.
She even brought a gift.
You ungrateful child!
Your Majesty, please forgive her.
I think you know
what Yin Cong's temperament is like.
She was just drunk
and muddle-headed,
acting impulsively
without thinking clearly.
I know she's angry,
and I can forgive her.
But with her temperament like this,
if she acts impulsively and causes trouble
again and again,
I will show no leniency.
I will
definitely remind her often.
Stand up.
In the past few days,
you've been busy with Wencheng's affairs
and have been mentally exhausted.
Today, it happens to
be the Mid-Autumn Festival.
Wencheng should be back at home now
after being exonerated.
You can go home to take a look, too.
Your Majesty.
What's wrong?
I...
just feel that
my brother's problem has just been solved,
and there are countless eyes in the court
watching Your Majesty and me.
If I leave the palace and go home now,
I'm afraid it'll cause gossip
and bring criticism upon Your Majesty.
It doesn't matter.
Consort Shu
has also asked for my permission
to go home and visit her family,
so you're not an exception.
I'd like to
thank Your Majesty for your kindness.
Leyu, one day if you marry me,
I'll personally make a crown
for your coronation.
How about making it with these camellias?
This Consort Xian is not that special.
On her wedding night,
she was left alone here like this.
Come and take a look!
Make way, please!
Sister!
Brother!
Brother.
You've suffered so much.
Thank you for running around outside
to help me.
I'm just glad you're back.
Come here.
Come on. Let's eat.
There are mooncakes,
chicken soup,
tofu and fish.
Hurry up. Eat while the food is hot.
Okay.
Leyu! Mr. Su!
Am I too late?
Yin Cong.
Sit down and eat with us.
Leyu.
I was drunk that day
and spoke without thinking.
I never meant to blame you.
Yin Cong.
How could there be any grudges between us?
But the wedding gift you gave me that day
showed your provocation.
Don't do such things again.
Have I caused trouble for you?
Sister.
What are you two
whispering about?
Nothing.
Sit down and eat with us.
Okay.
Come on. Sit down.
Come on. Drink my wine.
Okay.
Mr. Su.
This toast is to your exoneration
and your bright future ahead.
Leyu.
This toast is to you too
as my apology.
Cheers.
It still tastes the same as before.
Leyu.
As for the matter
of you entering the palace,
I'm not only confused
but also quite worried.
The Su family
is in a delicate position now.
His Majesty regards you
as the late empress's old officials
while the noble families regard you
as imperial members
and His Majesty's supporters.
Now the Su family
is truly in a dilemma.
Leyu.
With the Su family's current situation,
which side will you take?
The Su family is just the Su family.
We'll side with Dacang
and the people.
We will never align ourselves
with any particular side.
This is truly what Su Leyu is like.
Let's not talk about these things now.
Today, it's the Mid-Autumn Festival.
Let's only talk about the full moon
and reunion.
Come on.
Cheers.
-Cheers.
The full moon.
Reunion.
I remember how His Majesty always
used the excuse of loving our mooncakes
to spend the Mid-Autumn Festival with us.
But now...
[Ningzheng Hall]
Your Majesty.
Be careful, Your Majesty.
I remember
during the festivals in the past,
my mother would hang
wish-bearing wind chimes
all over the courtyard.
Their constant tinkling
reminded us to stay vigilant
even in times of peace.
Even with the music disturbing the ears,
we must cultivate inner peace.
Your Majesty,
hanging wish-bearing wind chimes
during the Mid-Autumn Festival
is also meant to pray for blessings.
Shall I ask someone to take them down?
No need.
I want to be alone for a while.
Yes.
Mother.
Today, it's the Mid-Autumn Festival.
The whole country is celebrating.
Why don't we...
Remember.
To walk the path we've chosen,
we're destined to endure loneliness.
Just like the sun,
the more brightly it shines,
the lonelier it seems.
A monarch
is just like a solitary peak
above an abyss.
Though he can watch
all the small mountains from the top,
there will be no one
standing beside him anymore.
If you feel lonely in the future,
come listen to
the sounds of these wind chimes.
[When the wind stops
and the chimes become silent,]
[you'll realize that all glory has faded]
[and you must walk alone till the end.]
Two yards are full of moonlight
while one yard is full of frost.
The wind chimes in the Buddha Hall
keep ringing all night.
Even when the moon is full,
it's still hard
to be reunited with my family.
Didn't I say
I wanted to be alone for a while?
Eunuch Xu has told me
you haven't
eaten any mooncakes tonight.
Didn't you go home for the family reunion?
Why are you back?
My brother said
you loved pastries
and sweet food the most.
He specially asked me
to bring some back here
so that you could taste them.
Wencheng always thinks
the sweeter it is, the more I like it.
He always brings me pastries
with preserved fruits filling.
But only you know
I actually prefer mashed potatoes filling.
Leyu.
[Leyu.]
[Do you know
after that night at the Xuanji Pavilion,]
[the bitterness in my heart]
[has been like a stone]
[pressing down on me so hard
that I can hardly breathe?]
It's better to shatter as jade
than survive as a tile.
In Your Majesty's heart,
there are also
some unspoken
difficulties?
Leyu.
Do you know
my difficulties?