(One morning with late frost)
(Sixth Sense Season 3)
(Episode Three)
(Jae Seok, Sang Yeob, and Jessi arrived early today.)
What's taking everyone so long?
We're early.
- What time is it now? - It's 8:16am.
Seoul city everyone?
- Gosh. That is... - MBC?
(Groaning, turning away)
- Goodness. - You never improve.
MBC is an improvement.
If he keeps it, it will be a good character.
A character that never improves. I mean it.
I stick to my own path.
Yes, that's the path for you.
Why did you start so early?
It's not even time yet.
- That's what I said. - Why are you so late?
Why are you so early?
Mi Joo. Hurry up already.
- Everyone's angry. - Jessi. Why are you so early?
- Oh, my gosh. - Mi Joo. Come on.
- Oh, my gosh. I get it. - Come on.
You're wearing matching.
- Right. You look cute. - You think so?
Yes. You always look cute.
She told me before she left.
"Jae Seok. Actually, you dress exactly the way I like."
(It's to Na Ra's liking.)
- Really? - Before she left last week.
The way he dressed last week.
Hello.
Hey. Don't be late!
- Mi Joo. - Mi Joo!
- What are you doing? - Where are you going?
She's carrying the mic. She didn't even put the mic on.
Mi Joo. You took it too far.
That's not it. My shoes...
You had enough time to do that upstairs.
No, I was right in front.
Turn the mic on.
We start at 8:30am. Why are you so early?
(You told me to hurry up.)
- Let me tell you exactly. - Why are you doing this?
- It's all your fault. - Why?
Why did you stand here with a mic on?
What else would I do in the car?
Jae Seok. But if you stand here,
- we can't help but get here. - You think we were starting?
I see.
(He acts like an old fossil boss.)
(Murmuring)
They're talking so much.
- What? - The guests are talking so much.
Who are the guests?
The writer said one of my favorite guys is here.
Yes.
(Na Ra's...)
(favorite?)
Is it Seok Jin?
- What? Why? - Mi Joo.
(The guy Na Ra liked)
(They showed opposite emotions last time.)
The guests who disappoint Mi Joo the most are...
Seok Jin and Sae Ho.
Don't say that.
(She hopes it's someone else.)
- Don't say that. - Seok Jin. Did you miss me?
(Seok Jin. Are you there?)
- He's not answering. - Gosh. It's true!
(A common reaction after finding the guest)
(Peekaboo)
He's desperate.
- Why do you hate me? - It's true!
- Why do you hate me? - "It's true".
- Seok Jin. - I hate this.
The guest isn't mysterious at all.
Hurry up and call him.
- Let me tell you. - Okay.
A lot of places...
- want Seok Jin these days. - Who?
I know that a lot of shows are calling him,
- but we didn't have to call him. - I know.
- He should've gone somewhere else. - That's what I mean.
Don't you have "Running Man" today?
- When? - Today.
That's Monday.
You should shoot "Running Man" today.
How can I shoot "Running Man" when Jae Seok's here?
(Oh, right.)
(Understood)
That's true.
Hey.
Those two behind me are handsome.
Oh, there are two more?
- Are they in there? - What?
- Are they in there? - Of course.
My.
My. Jae Lim.
- Hello. - EL.
(She played the birth deity in "Goblin".)
(She goes over Netflix...)
(and YouTube.)
(Actress EL)
(The man of an appealing deep voice)
(From "How to Be Thirty")
(He's the man who taught So Min...)
(the chemistry theory.)
(Actor Song Jae Lim)
Go inside.
Come to the center.
Jae Lim. You changed a lot.
- You're Jae Lim? - EL. Come here.
You didn't know?
Weren't you together?
(They spent 30 minutes together in the green room.)
We kept talking.
Then why didn't you know? What did you mean by that?
When we were talking inside,
this guy...
- "This guy"? She's EL. - I'm sorry.
- She... - "This guy"?
She's a junior. I can call her a guy.
Who's a junior? Why is she a junior?
- She's a junior. - She's not your direct junior.
She may not be my direct junior, but she starred in a movie with Ji Hyo.
Seok Jin. You know you're my junior.
This isn't the place to talk about that.
You debuted after I did.
You're a junior in the neighborhood.
(Sorry about that.)
You starred in "Yaksha"?
- Yes. - Yes.
Can you tell us what it's about?
What's the genre?
The title sounds like a thriller.
- No, it's an action movie. - Action.
Isn't it an action thriller?
- Seok Jin. - Jae Lim.
It's an action?
It's an action blockbuster.
A blockbuster?
We play agents of national intelligence service black team.
- That sounds cool. - National intelligence service?
(It talks about the intelligence war...)
(of national intelligence service agents.)
(EL and Jae Lim appear as Black NIS agents.)
Are you doing the action?
- Yes. - Yes, quite a lot.
- Did you? - Yes.
Can you teach me?
- Why? - So I can use it on Jae Seok.
(So I can use it on Jae Seok.)
- Me? - I will...
(Na Ra challenges Jae Seok.)
- Bring it on. - Same hand and leg.
I dare you.
- Come here. - Wait.
(Getting beaten up as usual)
(That's funny.)
(Stop it now.)
Seok Jin is having...
his first glory days.
"First".
- It's your 1st glory days. - It's my 2nd.
- It's first. - It's crazy.
I took only two days off in a month.
- Really? - Yes.
Lately, I've been thinking...
the bubble should deflate soon.
- Your bubble? - Yes.
There's a bit of bubble. It should deflate soon.
But you're not that popular.
People don't think...
it's a bubble.
I can't deny what he said.
I'm not extremely popular.
I just keep getting calls.
(Forever Seok Jin's glory days)
What's the topic today?
Today is topic.
Today?
Not is. Today's topic.
(What's the difference?)
(Here's today's topic.)
All right.
Can you move back?
Science of sleep for those who can't sleep?
(Science of sleep for those who can't sleep)
Science of sleep?
(Extraordinary)
(The areas Sixth Sense covered until now)
(Unknown, brilliant, enormous, delicious, surprising)
(Sleep)
(The sole solution...)
(for those who can't sleep)
(We'll bring you back your lost sleep.)
(It's an attempt no one has ever tried before.)
(Delude their sleep.)
(Against the greatest topic, )
(the members of Sixth Sense make a deduction with their instinct.)
(Find what's fake.)
(What's fake today?)
Science of sleep for those who can't sleep.
- Yes. - Good job.
A lot of people are having a hard time...
- sleeping. - Me.
- Right? - I couldn't sleep.
- How long did you sleep? - Maybe three hours?
That's a long time.
- Really? That's long? - You had enough sleep.
How long did you sleep?
- Maybe an hour? - An hour?
- How long did you sleep? - I slept a lot.
- Four and a half hours. - Four and a half hours.
- Same as Mi Joo. - Three hours?
(Glad)
- Three hours. - Three hours.
(It's the 3-hour club.)
- Seok Jin. - I slept for nine hours.
- What? 9 hours? - I slept for 9 hours.
- Nine hours? - You should've slept more.
(Seok Jin can have 9 hours of sleep even during his glory days.)
- His nose got bigger. - Yes.
Look at Seok Jin's nose.
It's still puffy.
It might be from his sleep...
or his wife might have stepped on his nose.
(The mystery of Seok Jin's big nose in the morning is solved.)
Let's check out...
Science of sleep for those who can't sleep.
What?
"You just fall asleep while listening to it?"
"A songwriter from Berklee who writes customized sleep music".
- Oh, customized? - Customized?
(Customized sleep music songwriter?)
(Various sounds help you fall asleep.)
(The sound of a brazier)
(The sound of waves)
(The sound of rain)
(And the sound of wind or classic music)
(Is it really effective?)
(So we prepared...)
(the one and only sleep music for you.)
(The customized sleep music...)
(composed by Berklee graduate)
(It's a studio.)
(This is...)
(They can't believe their eyes.)
(They can't believe their ears.)
(Scientifically and medically...)
(A collaboration of music and science for only one person)
(He even melts Jessi's heart.)
(Is the customized sleep music songwriter real or fake?)
Right.
I think this is fake.
"Berklee graduate".
They think we'd fall for that.
Berklee?
For Berklee College of Music,
they'd bring someone...
- Exactly. - who can play the piano.
- And give him a Berklee tag. - How would we know it's true?
And play some music...
and argue that will make you fall asleep.
This is the phrase...
- production crew likes. - Yes.
(The phrase sounds like a common TV show phrase.)
We wouldn't know...
until we get there though.
Can we sleep today?
(What?)
Oh, you can sleep.
If you fall asleep, you should.
If you fall asleep, we'll leave you behind.
- Okay. - You can't move to the next place.
- Come on. - If you fall asleep,
we're leaving you behind.
(You're watching Sixth Sense...)
(where casts get abandoned the moment they fall asleep.)
- Okay. Number 2. - Number 2.
"A restaurant where you can sleep".
- A restaurant that induces... What? - Induces sleep?
(A sleep restaurant that induces you to sleep)
A sleep restaurant?
(Sleep and restaurant?)
(Restaurant, bar)
(Cafeteria, food court)
(Why do we only eat in there? Why can't we have some sleep?)
(Hotel, resort)
(Motel, editing room)
(Sleep at home please.)
(Why can we only sleep? Why can't we eat in there?)
(Eat and sleep)
(There's a dream place where you can do both.)
(A meal that helps you sleep)
(The unique place only the sleep restaurant has)
(They even have this.)
(The sleeping area in the restaurant...)
(that surprised Sixth Sense)
(Of sleep, by sleep, for sleep)
(Sleep and eat at the same time)
(Is the sleep restaurant real or fake?)
Doesn't it sound fake?
The restaurant is all about a turnover rate.
- That's what I mean. - People shouldn't sleep in there.
- That makes sense. - Right?
- That makes sense. - Yes.
- That makes sense. - You're sharp.
If you sleep after eating,
- you don't feel good. - No.
- Right? - Number two is fake.
But people say...
- lettuce makes you sleepy. - Yes.
Maybe that is...
- what they serve. - Oh, my gosh. He's the spy.
- Why? - He's the spy.
Oh, we have a spy.
- I think... - There's a spy?
- Or... - There is.
- Seok Jin! - No way.
- Could Seok Jin be the spy? - He has no idea.
- I didn't know. - He doesn't know there's a spy.
Don't be ridiculous.
- You're the spy, right? - Are you the spy?
- Oh, my gosh. - He's the spy.
Why don't you know about spies?
He's blushing again.
- You're suspecting me? - We got him.
- You're suspecting me? - We got him already.
- You're suspecting me? - Do we even have a spy today?
But it's impossible...
- We got him. - for him to be a spy.
He used to be a director of "Running Man".
So I told him I wouldn't do it no matter what.
I told him that I'll enjoy my time here.
- Why are you acting up suddenly? - Acting up?
What do you mean I'm acting up?
I've been acting up since the opening.
You may not know,
but there are gestures that you do when you're given a role.
Like what?
(Reason for suspecting him: Body language)
- He's anxious. - But he does...
things like this.
He does that when he's flustered.
- When he's flustered. - That's because...
Everyone, please don't suspect me.
The actual spy is laughing at us.
(Is Seok Jin a clumsy spy like how everyone is suspecting?)
Anyway, forget about the spy.
We should take a look at this.
The most expensive bed in the world.
A handmade bed that costs 650,000 dollars.
They make only six of them a year.
(A bed costs 650,000 dollars?)
(650,000 dollars)
(The things you can buy with 650,000 dollars)
(An apartment)
(A supercar)
(A yacht)
(And another thing you can buy with 650,000 dollars)
(A bed?)
This doesn't make any sense.
(It does.)
(Another super rare item that Sixth Sense found)
(There's something special about this bed.)
(The ultimate handmade item)
(The masters make only 6 of them in a year.)
(A bed that costs 650,000 dollars)
(The mire of delusion where they can't believe what they see)
(Surprised)
(Lie on it and judge for yourself.)
(Would you like to lie down on it?)
(A handmade that costs 650,000 dollars)
(Is it real or fake?)
- Wait. Such a bed exists. - Come on.
- I'm sure it exists. - No, it doesn't.
- I think it exists. - It does exist.
- This is... - It doesn't exist.
- It costs 650,000 dollars. - But this is...
They make only six beds a year.
That means they only make 3.6 million dollars.
They make about 3.6 million dollars.
Isn't that too little...
- You don't think it's possible. - to run a company?
- Wouldn't it be hard... - You can't tell.
To figure out if it's real or fake?
That's what we're supposed to do.
- We'll figure it out. - We'll know once we see it.
- You see, EL. - EL.
I'm not sure if it's appropriate, but we're like card sharks.
We can figure it out right away.
- So did you figure it out? - We're like card sharks.
- Did you figure it out last week? - No, I didn't.
- What about the week before that? - I couldn't figure it out.
- Why are you calling yourself that? - I am a card shark.
You're not so good at figuring it out.
- You're not so good. - I mean, that's what we're called.
It doesn't mean card sharks win all the time.
That means you're not a card shark.
I am a card shark.
(Card Shark Yu, doesn't win that often)
Let's divide ourselves into teams.
EL and Na Ra will be the team leaders.
- Oh, really? - Yes.
(Today's team leaders: EL and Na Ra)
- Have you made up your mind? - Yes.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Na Ra wins.)
Na Ra gets to pick first.
(It's time for Na Ra to pick her first team member.)
(Look at me, Na Ra. I'm the guy you used to like.)
(Shall we show our good teamwork today?)
I pick Sang Yeob.
She loves Sang Yeob.
It feels like...
Na Ra will take Sang Yeob...
to the otherworld as well.
- You should start dating. - I'm on her side.
You even screamed when I came last time.
Yes, I did.
But I got tired of you soon.
She just said the same thing my wife says.
She said the same thing.
(People easily get bored of him.)
There are such days.
(Team EL, Team Na Ra)
- Did you put on your seat belt? - Yes.
- All right. - I think we'll do well.
Everyone.
- It'll be quiet in the car today. - That's right.
But we can't be quiet...
because we have to sleep at every place we go today.
She's being funny.
Seok Jin, how could you say that?
I should be funny! This is a variety show.
She is saying funny things.
Mi Joo is a promising variety show star.
You must help her grow.
(My boss is indeed amazing.)
Promising stars...
must be able to get back up even if we crush them.
(Upset)
- That's what weeds do. - That's what weeds do.
Is that so? I don't think I'm a guest here.
I think they hired me as So Min's replacement.
- You grasped their intention, - Of course.
But I'm sure the staff members were worried a lot.
(Laughing)
He's not as good as So Min.
- That's true. - So Min!
- So Min! - I miss So Min so much.
- EL. - Yes?
When will your movie premiere?
It hasn't premiered yet.
How long has it been?
How long has it been since you shot it?
- Two years. - I knew it.
It's been a while since we shot it.
I hear it's really hard...
- That's true. - to premiere a movie these days.
Then you two must be awkward too.
It's been long since you last met, right?
No, we met from time to time.
- Oh, really? - I see.
Because it's an action movie,
- we built a comradeship. - Right?
You grew affection through your bodies, right?
- That's right. - Pardon?
- You grew such affection, right? - Affection through bodies?
The sound of it...
- What? - Na Ra.
You're quite witty today.
- Na Ra. - What?
I can talk better in this seat.
Na Ra is the ace of this show.
Na Ra is good.
He's like our Messi.
I've improved a lot.
Above anything,
we're visiting the first place, right?
I'll observe the first place more carefully than other places.
(Jae Seok is most suspicious of the 1st spot.)
Wait. It means he went to Berklee, right?
- That's right. - If he went to Berklee,
then he should be able to speak in English.
- That's for sure. - In English?
- Since Jessi can speak English... - I should pick on him.
(Jessi is burning with the desire to reason.)
- This must be it. - Where?
- You can get off now. - Okay.
Let's move.
(What is customized sleep music?)
(Science of sleep for those who can't sleep, Vol. 1)
(You just fall asleep while listening to it?)
(A songwriter from Berklee who writes customized sleep music)
(Seogyo-dong, Mapo-gu)
Okay. Let's move.
We're starting our reasoning now.
Good luck.
Please get off.
(Grabbing hard)
- Get off now. - Why did you grab my head?
This is the place?
(An ordinary building you can easily see in Hongdae)
A recording studio?
The overall vibe of this place...
(The entrance is filled with billboards of musicians.)
There are many recording studios around this area.
The staff members...
- make things like these too, right? - That's right.
- Here... - They even make these things.
(It's a piece of cake for the staff to make signboards.)
I think they made this.
It looks so new, doesn't it?
(He's adding his reasoning.)
They stuck this with tape.
(It's almost falling off.)
- They made it too obvious. - Right? It's...
It's too obvious.
(A signboard stuck in a rush? Is this place fake?)
- They could be tricking us... - They made it so obvious.
With a signboard that looks fake.
- It's part of their trick? - That's right.
Right. Sometimes they make it look fake.
(Welcome to the mysterious world of Sixth Sense.)
Let's get going.
(As soon as they go down to the basement, )
(they can see the door to the recording studio.)
- It's real. - It's a recording studio.
What is this place again?
- The songwriter from Berklee. - From Berklee, right?
(Opening the door carefully)
Goodness, this place is...
(A recording studio...)
(unfolds before their eyes as soon as the door opens.)
(Various audio equipment that looks real)
(Is this place an actual recording studio?)
This is just...
(This looks too much like an actual recording studio.)
They didn't do anything to this space.
This is... This place is real.
You know I've been to a lot of recording studios.
This place is real.
But you can just rent the studio.
Right. Since they just need the songwriter.
Actually, you don't have to look around the place...
- It's an actual studio. - because they're running it.
We can't tell if it has...
anything to do with sleep music.
There's a keyboard.
Won't we just see him playing the piano?
We'll be able to tell if he went to Berklee...
once he plays it.
(Is that so?)
(Mi Joo quietly stands in front of the keyboard.)
- Do you know how to play the piano? - Of course.
It looks like it's been used.
- What song is this? - Can you sing along too?
(This is a breeze.)
- The dance major can't stand still. - No, I can't.
- Let's play it. - Which one?
Na Ra is...
clearly more beautiful than Mi Joo.
(He loves her snort.)
I thought the corners of her mouth...
(Replay)
- You're the worst-looking one here. - Na Ra looks so happy.
I could clearly see the difference.
I love you, Mi Joo.
I could clearly see the difference, seeing you two together.
So what?
(He loves it.)
She's good. That was a great response.
(Mi Joo can't stand being treated unfairly.)
Mi Joo is indeed amazing.
It's fun to tease Mi Joo.
- She's the best. - It's fun to tease her.
That's why those who are older than her like her.
Because it's fun to tease her.
(Na Ra and Mi Joo play "Chop Waltz" despite their talk.)
They're good.
(Mi Joo finishes playing it with fury.)
Na Ra is good.
- You're good. - Yes, I know how to play.
The son... Can you play the ballad for the son?
- "The son"? - I'm sorry,
but it's "Ballade Pour Adeline".
("Ballade Pour Adeline" composed by Paul de Senneville)
(Richard Clayderman)
(You recognize this song, right?)
It's not a ballad for the son.
- Nor for the daughter. - It's "Ballade Pour Adeline".
- Adeline... - "Adeline"?
Madeleine is a type of bread.
(He rubs his ears out of embarrassment.)
Do you know how to play that song?
("Ballade Pour Adeline" by the Queen of Okcheon)
(I'm this good.)
- She can play. - You can play.
Mi Joo.
They played this song in western restaurants last time.
Do you want pork cutlet? Rice or bread?
(A common vibe of Yeongdeungpo's western restaurant in the 90s)
Let's sit down.
(Enough with the piano, it's time to find out if this is real or fake.)
(Youthful yellow)
You wore like a chick today.
Yes, you're dressed nicely today.
Really?
- Chick! - I hope you don't do that.
(Cheeping)
He's so funny.
Why are you fighting with Mi Joo?
Mi Joo is even more fun to tease than So Min.
Actually, this place is...
To find out whether this is real or fake,
this place is a studio that is actually in use.
- This is too hard. - It's a bit hard today.
There's nothing to suspect.
I think we have to check the person.
Shall we invite him and see what kind of music he makes?
- I'm so curious. - So today...
Boss.
- "Boss." - Why're you looking for a boss?
He's a director.
- Teacher. - He's a director.
- Songwriter. - Sir.
Hey, teacher.
(Today's teacher walks out slowly.)
He is so handsome.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - I don't think I can sleep.
(The sleep music songwriter who makes everyone flutter enters.)
He is so handsome.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - I don't think I can sleep.
(The sleep music songwriter who makes everyone flutter enters.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Customized hypnotics for just one person)
(The pianist who composes customized sleep music)
(He makes you fall asleep in sleepless nights...)
(with sweet melodies.)
Hello. I'm a pianist...
and sleep music songwriter, Yoon Han.
I was introduced to neurology and psychology professors...
of university hospitals...
and am continuing with my research.
I compose the songs by designing based on...
the frequency and type of music,
tonality, tempo, rhythm, and such.
I got the Institutional Review Board's approval...
since last year,
and I'm prescribing sleep music...
to actual patients.
I was the first to come up...
with the concept of prescribing music.
CEOs of big companies, athletes,
anchors, and chefs.
Most of them find that it's easy to sleep and are amazed.
(Sleep music songwriter who designs comfortable sleep)
Sixth Sense. Am I real?
(Rather awkward)
(He's surprised by the entrance of a handsome songwriter...)
(that he stands up as if enchanted.)
Really?
Why did you stand up?
- Mi Joo. - Mi Joo, why did you stand up?
I don't think I can fall asleep.
- How can I sleep? - She doesn't think she can sleep.
- But... - I don't think I can sleep.
(Her gums are getting dry from smiling because of Mi Joo.)
- He's really handsome. - I saw him a lot on TV.
You're really good-looking.
But he's a songwriter. I'm sorry.
- I can't sleep. - Exactly.
I'm completely woken up.
(I'm completely woken up.)
- You're dressed really well. - Exactly.
He's real.
- Let me ask you first. - Okay.
What is sleep music?
It's the music we listen to to fall asleep.
On the Internet and YouTube,
- there is a lot of sleep music. - You're right.
The sound of rain.
(The sound of rain)
The sound of firewood burning.
(The sound of firewood burning)
The sound of waves.
(The sound of waves)
I listen to the sound of the beach.
The sound of waves.
But a lot of them have...
(The ASMR music known to the public has no effect?)
no scientific evidence that they help with sleep.
So I started to research about that...
scientifically and medically.
- Really? - It's been about three years.
I did clinical research with a university hospital...
and am writing a thesis now.
(The professionalism is unlike the previous ASMR.)
(Is he really a sleep music songwriter?)
Why are your shoulders so wide when you play the piano?
His shoulders are so wide.
(A random investigation, but it makes sense.)
- Did you swim? - I didn't.
(His shoulders don't look like that of a pianist.)
(Could he be an athlete instead?)
(Detective Jae Lim's radar activates.)
Does it run in the family?
(Does it run in the family?)
(The first investigation is rather strange.)
Did he add pads?
- Stay still. What pads? - You know, shoulder pads.
You can't make those shoulders even with shoulder pads.
You're right.
It must be good for you. Your bag doesn't slip down, right?
Mine slips down a lot.
That's why I wear mine diagonally.
Bags slip down a lot on shoulders like these.
Those with shoulders like us must wear it diagonally.
(Thinking about something)
I think I know him.
I saw him a lot on TV last time.
Aren't you a pianist?
- I'm Yoon Han, a pianist. - That's right!
(He reveals his identity. I'm Yoon Han, a pianist.)
That's right!
- Yoon Han. - Yes.
That's a stage name, right?
- My surname is Jeon. - Jeon Yoon Han.
- He's very famous. - Exactly.
Is he? Do you really know him?
He's really famous.
Sang Yeob's pretending to know him.
No, he's really famous.
Really? Then is this place real?
Yes. No. It's not about whether he's a songwriter or not.
- Exactly. - It's about whether he composes...
sleep music or not.
This is hard.
How does music induce sleep?
Sleep is most related to your brain.
(The science of sleeping)
(Sleeping is science.)
Music produces hertz or frequency.
(Every sound has its unique frequency.)
Between two dos, there are twelve notes.
When I measured the frequency, the la note.
Do, re, mi, fa, so, la
La
The la note has the most stable...
waveform.
When we played the la note...
to water, it produces the prettiest...
- wavelength. - The wavelength.
(It surprisingly recorded the most stable and prettiest wavelength.)
Seventy percent of the human body is made of water.
I came up with a hypothesis and found out...
that if I play the la note, it will produce the delta wave...
and produce serotonin and melatonin...
which helps with sleep.
I play it for people to induce sleep.
That's what I did.
(A systematic explanation about sleep music)
(Is he really a songwriter who is researching sleep music?)
How long is it per music?
It's about 20 minutes.
That long?
You don't play the song, thinking, "I will sleep."
You play the song for ten minutes...
- before you fall asleep. - You play it first.
Play it softly in the place that you sleep in.
After you do other stuff and check your phone,
you naturally fall asleep.
For insomnia, the first thing you should do...
is not to use a phone before sleeping.
- That's right. - Then why check your phone?
(A question as sharp as a nail)
Because there are a lot of people...
who use their phones before sleeping.
Good job, Song Jae Lim.
I forgot to mention this.
A human's average heart rate is...
between 60 and 100.
But when we sleep,
it decreases by about 20 percent...
and you get calm.
If 20 percent is decreased from 60, what is the rate?
(If the heart rate decreases 20 percent from 60...)
It's 40.
- It's 48. - It's 48.
- Hold on. It's not 40. - Why?
I think she deducted 20.
(Answer)
It's different from deducting 20 from 100. Got it?
Okay.
- That can happen. - It's okay, I was confused too.
You have to multiply.
- I have to multiply. - I was confused too.
If 20 percent is decreased from 100, what is it?
- It's 80. - Yes, it's 80.
About that.
I design the music between 48 and 80bpm.
He speaks as if he's real.
Exactly. He's so fluent.
(Then is he a real sleep music expert without a doubt?)
How did you start making the music?
(How did he start making sleep music?)
(Her eyes are twinkling from curiosity.)
Actually, my wife...
- You have a wife. - Are you married?
Are you married? Too bad, Mi Joo.
- I'm falling asleep. - She's going back.
I'm falling asleep.
Mi Joo is gone.
Does she fall in love and move on every week?
She resets every week.
It happens every week, I see.
I can fall asleep easily.
(He's sorry for no reason.)
Until just now, she was like, "How can we listen to it?"
I wondered where I can listen.
(Why did I act up just now?)
- My wife had very bad insomnia. - It was for your wife.
At first, she went to the hospital and took pills.
- We even changed the mattress. - And the pillows.
We tried a foot bath too.
But they weren't very effective.
- It was for your wife. - What a beautiful story.
I thought there might be something I can do for her with music.
Through studying and researching, I started composing sleep music.
(It's a rather dramatic story. Is this real?)
- But theoretically... - You're cool.
Studying about this...
sounds unfamiliar.
And you're really cool because for us,
- if our wives have insomnia, - Excuse me, I'm not done talking.
Okay.
Seok Jin, be quiet!
Seok Jin, seriously.
Let Jae Seok talk.
He's cool.
- He really is. - Because...
for us, if our wives say that they can't sleep,
we tell them to run in the afternoon.
- You're so mean. - Run in the afternoon.
We say that, but...
Thank you for getting married early.
- You must feel bad about it. - Not at all.
Wives like people like me.
I'm curious about this.
When your wife listened to the music that you composed,
did she sleep well?
- Did it get better? - She had a hard time...
for a year and a half.
I composed and played two songs for her.
(What happened?)
After five minutes, she fell asleep while snoring.
(Isn't your set up going too far?)
He's a bit...
- But there's no evidence. - Exactly.
That was too much.
(Yoon Han who composes sleep music as strong as sleeping gas)
Did your wife really sleep in five minutes?
- Yes, she fell asleep and snored... - In five minutes?
In five minutes.
- She snored? - Can you play the song...
that you composed for your wife?
(Expectant)
I don't remember.
- Sorry? - How can you forget?
This is strange.
You must've listened to it every day,
- but you can't remember? - Did you not even record it?
After that,
- I composed countless songs... - I see.
And clinically tested them.
(An unexpected ending to the dramatic story)
(The songwriter forgot the music he wrote himself.)
(Is he a fake who only has the set up but not the music?)
(Mi Joo was focused in the beginning.)
(She melted down.)
I'm sleepy.
- I'm already sleepy. - This is...
His voice...
- It's so gentle. - makes you fall asleep.
- Very gentle. - Exactly.
- I almost fell asleep. - It's really gentle, so...
Instead of the music, why don't you record your voice?
- I think it will work well. - I'm really sleepy.
- I'm sleepy. - You're falling asleep, right?
Is your shirt ink painting?
Ink painting...
It looks like ink is smudged.
Seok Jin, your talk today is messy.
Filter out as you like.
(To the staff members)
Are we going to listen to the song right away?
Hyun Ju and Jee Seok Sam.
It'll be hard to make me sleep.
Me? I can't sleep.
She really has insomnia.
- She really has insomnia. - I really have insomnia.
(How long did you sleep?)
(Jessi has very bad insomnia where she can only sleep...)
(for 1 to 3 hours.)
He's going to customize...
- the sleep music. - Let's check it out.
- Yes. - Shall we start?
Can they sleep in the midst of this?
- Are you writing it now? - Yes, firstly,
I have to evaluate...
- Jessi. - Then go ahead.
That's nice.
(She's slightly envious.)
- What is your job? - My job is an entrepreneur.
(First question: What is your job?)
What?
- What? - I don't understand.
- Why? - Say it again.
Entrepreneur.
I don't know what that means.
Why doesn't he know "entrepreneur"?
- What is that? - He lived overseas.
It means you do everything.
(Business founder, pioneer, or proactive and initiative)
I'll interpret it in Korean.
- An all-rounder entertainer. - An all-rounder entertainer.
- An all-rounder entertainer. - It's an all-rounder entertainer.
(He understands perfectly.)
You said you studied in Berkeley.
Yes, I studied for four years.
- Then shouldn't you know that? - Then you should know this.
(The composer is very flustered. Did he not study overseas?)
Describe your personality.
- Why? - What is your personality like?
- My personality? - Please...
- cooperate with him. - It's because she didn't sleep.
She's going nuts from not fighting.
(He says it nonchalantly.)
(She's going nuts now.)
- Stay still. - What's wrong with you?
- "She's going nuts." - Why did you call him here?
When she sees someone she doesn't like, she gets angry.
She can't pretend to like someone if she doesn't like the person.
- Seriously. - That's her personality.
- You're right. - I'm right.
- No. - She can't smile...
in front of someone that she doesn't like.
That's how she appears to be,
- but she's very soft on the inside. - She's soft.
- That's how she is. - She gets hurt easily.
She's hard outside but soft inside.
She's a paper tiger.
- That's right. - Yes.
(Name: Ho Hyun Ju. Occupation: All-rounder entertainer.)
(Sleeping time: 1 to 3 hours. Personality: Paper tiger.)
(Favorite music genre: Hip hop. Habit before sleeping: Phone)
- Are you going to play right away? - Yes, I'll compose it.
- You're composing it now? - You're composing on the spot?
Really?
(Engineer Ho Jin who will help with the work)
- Then I'll start. - Okay.
- Gosh. - Right now?
I'm excited.
(We're looking forward to it.)
- For the tempo... - She is...
like a paper tiger.
Let's go with three four.
(Sleep music for Jessi the paper tiger)
Play it.
I got scolded.
- I still can't do it. - Still...
(With la note as the benchmark, the warm melody plays languidly.)
- It's nice. - It's nice.
It's making me comfortable.
Are you already sleepy?
(Jae Seok is already sleepy.)
(Dear viewers, listen carefully.)
(The music wraps your body like warm water.)
(They listen to the repeated melody as if enchanted.)
I'll end it here.
(It's so nice.)
I want to listen to it more somehow.
- It makes me feel relaxed. - It really does.
It makes me feel relaxed.
(But Detective Song is not fooled.)
Does the music progress from here?
You only played the repeated melody.
The main point of sleep music is repeated pattern.
(The main point of sleep music is repetition!)
- That's right. - The music is not for enjoyment...
but for making you sleep.
When you play it,
the music serves to shape the ambiance of the room.
So you have to listen to it very softly.
- I see. - So that it's not prominent.
- The volume? - Yes.
- You just leave it playing. - He speaks so smoothly.
When he says that, he looks real.
He really looks like he's doing research.
(Thorough theory and impromptu composition...)
(that matches. Is this place real?)
- And you said you liked the sea. - Yes.
- If you add ASMR sound to this, - Listen to the beat.
It is more effective according to the research.
- I see. - This sound is...
Then can you add the sound of water to this?
I'll play a few samples, so select what you like.
I'll mix the sound into the music.
- He really is... - Let's start...
with the first sound.
- Really? - That's what happened.
That sound is...
This water is dumb.
- Really? This is not it? - It shouldn't be so loud.
(Eliminated because it's too loud.)
Then...
(Play the next sound quickly.)
The sound of waves.
- It's the sound of seagulls flying. - It sounds refreshing.
(The 2nd Water. mp3)
I don't like the birds.
(Eliminated because she doesn't like the sound of the birds)
See? She's picky.
It will be hard to make her fall asleep.
Please play the next sound.
(They quickly move on to the next track.)
(What about this water?)
(The 3rd Water. mp3)
- I like this. - It's too frivolous.
- That's right. - It's too frivolous.
- It sounds like someone's peeing. - It sounds too narrow-minded.
There's another one, right?
- So... - No.
There are only three for water.
We have these three prepared.
- This is something basic. - This is strange.
- They're not well-prepared. - This is strange.
Don't you have too few samples?
- There are too few. - You only have three.
We normally have a lot,
but we can't listen to all of them.
(There are way too few samples! Is this place fake?)
- Then the 3rd one. - The 3rd one.
- Okay. - The flowing water is the best.
(The sleep music only for Jessi with the third water added...)
(is revealed now.)
(REM Only for Jessi by Yoon Han)
(Autoplay next video)
(You're watching Sixth Sense which is unpredictable...)
(and bewilders your senses.)
- I'm sleepy. - You're sleepy, right?
- I'm sleepy. I think it suits me. - This music...
(I want to have this music.)
I think some of the viewers...
might listen to this song...
- And feel sleepy. - and feel sleepy.
(The impromptu sleep music made everyone feel languid.)
(Then is the sleep music songwriter real?)
We exceeded the rental time,
so for Seok Jin's music,
- we'll send it to you separately. - Okay.
(We'll send you the music separately next time.)
You guys are so mean.
You invited him as a guest after a long time.
- Seok Jin is a guest. - I mean...
I was looking forward to it!
You talked too much just now.
- That's not it. I was curious. - You talked too much.
Please send me one.
Actually, I asked the writers...
- about the guests. - Yes.
They told me that Actor Ha Seok Jin was coming.
Ha Seok Jin?
(This hurts.)
I see.
- Ha Seok Jin? - An actor?
You guys...
- They're so different. - What did you tell him?
They're so different.
- It turns out that I misheard it. - I see.
So I prepared...
classy music.
Are you saying I'm not classy?
- Okay, then... - You're insulting me...
in our first meeting.
Yes.
He's hurt.
(Sleep music for classy Jee Seok Jin)
(Hypnagogic Only for Jee Seok Jin by Yoon Han)
(Name: Jee Seok Jin. Age: 57. Sleeping time: More than 9 hours.)
(Style: Classic?)
(Listen to the rest on the internet.)
Thank you. Please clap for them.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(They clap for the songwriter and engineer who played good music.)
- I'm sleepy. - Go out that way.
I think this is effective.
- It looks like he studied about it. - Right?
And he doesn't waver in his speech.
- He's calm. - Exactly.
He didn't have many samples ready...
this is not his own studio.
He works here often,
but that doesn't mean all of his data is here.
For people with insomnia,
if you just do some research, this stuff is all on the internet.
- You're right. - Yes.
(The coexistence of his great skills and clumsiness. Is he real or fake?)
- We're going to play the game now. - Shall we?
Okay.
The game we will play here is "Watch Your Mouth for 3 Seconds".
- We have to watch our mouths. - Watch Your Mouth for 3 Seconds?
(Even the fan of the show doesn't know this new game.)
What is this?
- Please sit by your teams. - Shall we?
(This is a team game.)
You have to say three words that fit into the category that I say.
For example, if I say "Favorite Food" in three seconds,
you can say jjajangmyeon, jjamppong, and tangsuyuk.
- What's so hard about that? - That's easy.
The next part is important. Why should you watch your mouths?
(The category is "My Attractive Features".)
(The banned words are "Two syllables".)
(There's a special rule of having banned words.)
(Eyes, butt, nose)
(If you say the words in 3 seconds, you succeed.)
(The category is "Favorite Snack Food".)
(The banned words are "Two syllables".)
(If you say a word that is banned, you fail.)
(All 4 members must succeed to win.)
Suddenly?
(The banned words cause a stir.)
- That's hard. - We just need to focus.
We really need to focus.
Why are you doing this after making us feel tired?
Stop acting like you were always good at the games.
Yes, sir!
(I got caught.)
- He just hit you hard with facts. - Yes, sir.
Okay, decide on the order.
- Will you go this way? - Yes, we will.
Let's start with me because I don't understand.
I couldn't understand because it's so hectic.
That's mostly because of you.
(Jessi vs. Seok Jin, the outbreak of their 1st war)
He's so blunt.
I feel so calm, and then I hear your voice,
- and it puts me in a daze. - Oh, my gosh!
(Jessi explodes.)
- We're so different. - We're different.
- We can't get along. - We're so different.
This is natural in a way...
because Seok Jin and his wife are very different too.
(Inadvertently found out about someone else's problem)
He looks like he's going to cry.
That's true, but that's why it's so fun.
It's been so hard for us to agree on something for the past 20 years.
But it's so much fun.
(Naughty Yu enjoys this situation.)
- That sounds nice though. - Exactly. That's right.
- What he's saying is good. - Right.
Okay, let's go this way for now.
- Let's start! Ready, begin! - Sure.
"Your Favorite Animals", two-syllable words not allowed.
Tiger, lion.
(Fool)
(Happy about his failure)
- Lion. - Lion.
He's so bad at this.
I got nervous.
(Embarrassed)
- Give our team a chance. - I'll move over to this team.
- Okay. - It's our turn. Watch and learn.
- I bet... - Jae Seok, what do you mean?
You know I'm good at these three seconds games, right?
- You are? - I am.
I'm good at ad-libs.
Here, watch.
"Your Favorite Snacks", English is not allowed.
(English is not allowed?)
(That's so easy.)
Three, two, one.
Snack?
(That's a word that's not even used a lot lately.)
What the? It sounded so much like Korean.
You could have said Squid Peanut Ball or gwamegi!
He has gwamegi as a snack?
Worry about yourself.
(The two older brothers on the side are the problem.)
We should go. That team is so bad.
- How could you be so bad? - You guys aren't cut out for this.
We're starting.
(Jessi tries this time.)
"Your Favorite Singers", women are not allowed.
(Jessi, show us what you can do.)
- Three, two, one. - Rain, Yu Jae Seok,
Oh Na Ra!
- Oh Na Ra? - Oh Na Ra, wrong.
(Me?)
Why? What's wrong?
She's a woman! A woman! Come on!
Come on!
You can't say women, come on!
(Strongly articulated)
(Roars)
(I'm scared.)
(Feels so chaotic)
(Don't worry. Jessi doesn't hurt the guests.)
After you said that,
Seok Jin was looking forward to what she'd say.
(He was anticipating Jessi to say his name.)
(Jessi, I'm also a singer.)
(I'm right here.)
Hey, I'm a singer too.
Seok Jin isn't a singer, he's a folkie.
(It suits him.)
Do I sing Korean folk songs?
- Seok Jin is a folkie. - He's a musician.
- Okay? - He's a bad boy.
Okay, let's go. Say it in three seconds.
- Something you do before bed. - What?
"Three syllables" are not allowed.
(What do I do before bed?)
- Three, - Sing,
- two, one. - eat.
Hey, you could have just said...
- poop, what else? - Poop, fart,
- Fart, and kiss. - Kiss!
Why would you say something that you don't do?
(Why would you say something that you don't do?)
You don't do that before bed!
- I do! - He says stuff he doesn't do.
Poop, fart, and kiss.
- Kiss! - Gosh, seriously.
He acts like he's romantic. It drives me crazy!
I can't live without my wife.
He's lying!
(They're so funny.)
I don't want to do this!
- Why? What's wrong? - Why?
Everyone's so bad!
You didn't do a great job either.
(Were we ever good?)
Okay, we're starting from Hyun Ju.
"My Favorite Fruits", three syllables are not allowed.
- Three, two, - Grapefruit,
- one. - apples...
Time's up.
- No! Wait! - Three seconds.
Can't I even breathe?
- Excuse me. - Wait!
No, I mean.
- No, I needed to breathe. - Wait, but I thought...
- you were going to beat him up. - You really looked like you were.
If you do that,
- think of how shocked we will be. - No, wait.
- I mean... - Give her time to breathe.
I need to breathe!
She was about to hit Chul Min.
I'll go this time.
What will you do? Look at his face.
(What do you want?)
- He's the worst at this game. - He's the worst.
(It's a fact.)
- He's the worst at this. - He's doing worse than usual.
- I know, why is he so bad today? - He's doing so bad today.
I think he's doing it on purpose.
- I was just a little weird earlier. - Okay.
- Let's go. - I'll do it for real this time.
"My Favorite Furniture".
English is not allowed.
- Three, - This is so easy.
- Chair, window? - two, one.
Is it that hard?
- He's actually the spy. - Table, chair, you know?
Bed and pillow.
- But why do I keep... - Window?
Thinking of Ace Bed?
- Things like Simmons and Ace. - What's wrong with you?
The first thing that popped into my head as soon as he said furniture...
- was Simmons. - Do you know why?
- Simmons. - It's because you're the spy.
(Jae Seok is suspected as the spy every week.)
How is he suspected every week?
Now, if just one person gets a question right, the team will win.
- Let's go! - I'll do it.
- Let's go! - Hey.
(Now it's doable.)
- He said one person. I'll do it. - Seok Jin.
I just hope someone would get it right already.
You have to say 3 in 3 seconds.
The category is easy. It is "Countries".
Asian countries are not allowed.
(This is really easy.)
(Can Seok Jin do it?)
- Three, two... - Argentina, Portugal, Brazil.
(Success)
So you aren't the spy!
- They have a chance too. - We have a chance.
We have a chance too.
- The brain amongst us. - Who will it be? Who's the brain?
He graduated from a college of engineering. Our Sang Yeob.
"Favorite Singers".
Men are not allowed.
(We trust in you, our brain.)
- Lee Hyo Lee, Jeon Won Ju... - Two, one.
Uhm Jung Hwa.
Jeon Won Ju?
Hey, did you say Jeon Won Ju?
- How could you? - This is hilarious.
- Why did you say Jeon Won Ju? - Jeon Won Ju.
She's a celebrity that's good at investing.
A celebrity that's good at investing.
Yes, she's good at investing.
- Only this team can see the hint. - Yes!
I was pretty cool.
What's this?
(Opening up the hint after praising himself)
Someone wrote about this music in a blog post.
(I only heard it for a short while, )
(but the music helped me feel calm.)
(It really made me feel like I could fall asleep comfortably.)
- What is this? - But...
didn't he say he didn't have a website?
So this is a review?
Wait, but...
anyone can just say this.
(Is it a review of his song as a pianist or for the sleep music?)
(I'm not sure even after the hint.)
This is hard.
(A songwriter from Berklee who writes customized sleep music)
(1. He studied abroad but doesn't understand Jessi's English.)
(2. A composer who forgot about his own sleep music.)
(3. The studio has very few samples of ASMR.)
(Is this place real or fake?)
- I'll get going then. - Let's go!
We're going to eat now.
The atmosphere here is so great, Jae Seok.
There are a lot of girls,
- so the atmosphere is... - We're gorgeous.
I'm not sure about that.
We're bubbly too.
(She's good at cutting in.)
The sound of their laughter is also high-pitched.
(A 3rd octave G sharp)
(The high-pitched tone vibrates the cochlea.)
High-pitched tone. So cute.
Don't force us...
into believing what you say.
- Stop acting cute. - I wasn't.
It just looks like that because I am cute.
Absolutely not.
(Failed to hold his laughter)
You wavered a little.
No, I would never.
So he does think I'm cute.
My wife started looking cute after 20 years of marriage.
Stop lying, Seok Jin.
Why are you like that all of a sudden?
He's trying to be the romantic guy of Jamwon-dong.
(Startled)
This isn't the first time I've experienced this.
Myung Soo was like this a long time ago.
(At that age, everyone wants to be the "Romantic Guy".)
I want to give you all advice to meet a man like me.
A man like you is who I want to avoid the most.
(Laughing)
- Mi Joo. - Mi Joo!
- Mi Joo is just great. - I feel so delighted.
- Did you read my mind? - It was at the perfect timing.
This is why I love Mi Joo.
She's doing great these days.
It's a criticism, but if it's funny it's okay.
At Antenna, Mi Joo is basically...
- She's a princess there. - Of course.
Jae Seok is the princess.
- Hey! - What?
He's a princess.
It's true that I'm adored at Antenna.
Mi Joo got on Jae Seok's train.
(The engineer of Jae Seok Express)
You were the first one on it.
Seok Jin, you're at the very front of that train.
I know, right? He was the first one on.
I don't know if I should say this because you're older than me,
but you should come to my house this Chuseok.
(About to bow to a younger brother for the holidays)
- To bow? - Go to his house with a gift.
You need to come once.
(So funny)
When we were waiting in the green room,
he said everyone here is below him.
He told us to let him know if we have any complaints.
I told them that you all come to my house during the holidays and bow.
But we saw him turn into dust with our own eyes today.
(Dust Brother)
- My gosh, Jae Lim! - Yes?
- You're amazing! - You're back!
The return of his verbal skills.
Jae Lim, you need to appear on variety shows every once in a while.
He says stuff that will provoke you.
(Bring Song Jae Lim on more variety shows!)
From just looking at the board,
- the second place seemed fake. - Yes.
Does that make any sense that you sleep while eating?
It is pretty absurd because why would you sleep at a restaurant?
We're almost there.
(They've almost arrived at the destination.)
We're headed towards Yeouido, next to the 63 Building.
(The location of spot 2 is in Yeouido?)
Yeouido?
It's in here?
It must be this building.
(The combination of sleep and food. What is this place?)
(Science of sleep for those who can't sleep, Vol. 2)
(A restaurant you can sleep at exists?)
(A sleep restaurant that will help you fall asleep)
We're eating this time.
We're eating, so we need to find something this time.
Let's go eat!
- Hey, let's move! - Move it!
Is it time for Mi Joo to come out?
(Got it)
(Hair grabbed 2 times in a row)
Let's move!
Everyone, it's this way.
The location is believable.
(Next to the Han River)
(In the middle of Yeouido which has a lot of offices)
It's believable because there are a lot of offices around here.
That could be why the production crew made it here.
If it's Yeouido, it makes sense.
(It makes sense because the targeted customers are workers.)
There's nothing new that's stuck on there.
It's over here.
- Oh, it's here. - Wait.
This seems fake.
This is so obvious.
Sleep itself is restorative.
- Wait. - Wait, this place looks so fake.
- Something smells delicious. - Hey, this is...
(They enter.)
(When you're too tired to eat, )
(but also too hungry to fall asleep, )
(there's a restaurant that will help you satisfy both needs?)
(You eat in a pastel-toned area.)
(Where do you sleep?)
Oh, my gosh! There's even a massage chair.
No, it's cozy.
(The area to sleep is a private sleep capsule.)
Is this a place for people in the finance district...
to take a rest while working?
(The prices are cheap.)
(It's cheaper if you eat and sleep here.)
(A variety of services to ensure a good sleep)
(Sleep restaurant, is this place real?)
The interior design and the scent are so different.
This place smells so new.
(Something smells suspicious.)
(Does it smell new because the production crew just made it?)
It's a capsule. That's a capsule over there.
- No way. - You sleep in a capsule.
So you leave after eating and sleeping?
- But... - The sleeping room is...
- So the production crew... - This is amazing.
- made this? - They made all of this?
- That's almost impossible. - Right?
(The core of this restaurant, private sleep capsules)
(You get your own cozy bedroom.)
- Does it open? - Oh, my gosh!
- Oh, my gosh! - This is real.
- It's a big investment. - It's a capsule.
It's so nice.
This could really exist.
(It's hard to believe that this large-scale sleeping room is fake.)
It's so cozy here.
I could sleep well in here.
I think I could visit this place.
(If this is real, I love it.)
Really, I would come here.
There's even a ventilator.
(There's even a ventilation system because it might get stuffy.)
This is amazing.
Oh, my gosh.
(Pushing the buttons)
(You can change the lighting according to your taste.)
Hey, look at this. You can even change the colors.
This place is definitely real.
(It has a lighting and ventilation system.)
(It's so detailed. Is this place a real sleep restaurant?)
Oh, my. There's a comb here too.
(Should I fix how I look?)
This place is real.
I would come here.
(Mi Joo is upgrading her appearance.)
This place is great. I love it here.
(She feels elated.)
What?
Where did my shoes go?
(A bolt out of the blue. Me?)
(Roaring)
It's down there. You put them there.
- I put it there? - Yes.
(They never went anywhere.)
I thought Seok Jin moved it.
Mi Joo. I can't believe you.
(The actual culprit is Jae Lim.)
(He pushed the shoes in because they were in the way.)
This place is real.
- The menu... - "So other people can sleep..."
- I don't know about this place. - This is a little weird, Na Ra.
(Please be quiet so that other people can sleep.)
Because people are also eating,
but it doesn't make sense to make them be quiet.
So they should sleep after eating?
Then everyone has to be silent while eating?
(Talking during lunch is also a joy of life.)
(But they ask for silence? Is this place fake?)
(There's still a lot to see in this restaurant.)
- What's this area? - It's for massages.
There's a massage chair.
(The massage chair is pulling me.)
(If you want to use me, you have to pay.)
Should I check to see if it works?
(Jae Seok uses his card.)
(If it's real, the transaction will go through.)
(But if this place is fake, it might not work.)
(Will it work?)
- It worked. - It worked!
(Your payment has been completed.)
(It worked!)
It works. This place is real.
(Jae Seok has lost all suspicions of this place.)
It works.
- A dollar has left my account. - One dollar.
- This place is real! - Why?
He's the spy.
- No, I saw everything. - It works.
- It works. - It worked.
You're saying that just because this works?
- I paid for ten minutes. - The payment went through.
- Mobile payment works? - Yes.
What's hard about that?
Jae Seok, why don't you look at other stuff too?
(Why am I getting scolded for inferring?)
- So you think this place is real? - I do.
It's hard for the production crew to set all of this up.
Because of the massage chair?
(Did Jae Seok's dollar provide proof?)
(Payment for the massage chair is possible. Is this place real?)
- Let me just say one thing. - Sure.
- What's important is... - Will you just say one thing?
- No, I might say more. - Okay.
(Gets to witness their chemistry with her own eyes)
You're allowed to negotiate.
Judging by the district we're in,
it's believable that there is a sleep restaurant in the area.
Tired office workers can come...
- And take a quick nap? - Yes.
(It's great for office workers to come here during lunch.)
But the lighting is too bright...
to sleep here.
You sleep over there anyway.
The lighting is different in there.
No, but still, it's too bright here.
- No, but think about it, - "It's too bright!"
- you don't sleep... - "It's too bright!"
- right here while you eat. - You don't sleep here.
But the overall vibe should still be dark over here.
It's dark in there.
It's too bright here to go sleep in there after eating.
- I'm sorry for saying that. - It needs to be dark here...
so that by the time you're done eating, you're ready to sleep.
Why are you guys fighting?
Her voice is so hoarse.
I can't stand your voice.
(Jessi doesn't back down.)
Jae Seok, that's what I think too.
(Jae Lim is still adjusting.)
We're all about to fight each other. Where is the owner?
You can come this way.
- Hello. - Hello.
(The owner enters shyly.)
Hello, I am the owner of this sleep restaurant in the city.
My name is Song Eun.
Our restaurant provides food that is easy to digest...
and food that helps you go to sleep.
We also provide an area to sleep. This is a rest area within the city.
I was originally a teaching assistant at a university,
and whenever I wanted some rest during lunch,
I used the rest area at the school.
But I felt uncomfortable using the area...
because a lot of people used the area together.
In 2018, healing cafes started to trend,
so I visited one,
but the drawback of the cafe was that you weren't allowed to eat.
I thought it would be nice to have a place where you could...
eat and rest at the same time.
An opportunity arose, and I started managing this sleep restaurant.
The sleep capsule is what I invested in the most for this restaurant.
For the sleep capsule,
there is a machine inside that keeps the oxygen concentration...
above at least 21 percent.
It allows enough oxygen to be supplied to the brain...
to allow mental and physical comfort,
and it also helps you regain energy.
Sixth Sensers. Is this place real?
How long has it been since you started this restaurant?
I started in 2019, so it's been about three years.
- It's been a while. - Yes, it has.
There's something that a lot of us have been questioning.
Please understand because we need to raise doubts for this show.
Yes, of course.
The lighting is a bit too bright for a sleep restaurant.
(The bright interior and lights don't match with the restaurant.)
We received a relief fund due to COVID,
so before, the color was dark grey,
but in hopes of the virus coming to an end,
we repainted the place.
(Remodeled the whole place with the relief fund)
(Did it smell new because it was recently remodeled?)
(Or is it just a lie made up by the production crew?)
- So we used a bright color. - It's eco-friendly paint.
(Okay, but apart from that)
I feel like the colors will make...
men a little reluctant to come here on their own.
You're right, but a lot of our customers are women.
A lot of women come?
Our regular customers come from the banks around here.
(She knows her customers well. Is this sleeping restaurant real?)
If it costs 12 dollars for an hour, is it okay? Do you make a profit?
When we set the price... It's not 12 dollars.
- It's 10 dollars. - For 30 minutes...
(It's 10 dollars.)
- It's 10 dollars per hour. - Yes, 10 dollars.
I saw that it was 6 dollars for 30 minutes.
- Look before you speak. - It's just that...
(He was in the wrong.)
This place is quite detailed.
That's only for using that.
(Is this clear-cut owner real or fake?)
For me, personally, this place was the most suspicious,
judging by the panel earlier.
After I paid for that massage chair.
(He could be a massage chair promoter.)
- You mentioned that payment... - This place...
- around 20 times already. - But I think...
(Someone send him a massage chair, please.)
Can you explain the menu for us, please?
Our meal plan...
includes foods that are easy to digest...
and ingredients with nutrients that help promote sleep.
That's the basis of our menu.
(You're curious, right? We'll reveal it later.)
The most popular dishes are the spinach and mushroom risotto,
the clam pasta,
and the salmon and sea trumpet chazuke.
(Foods that promote sleep that have captivated workers in Yeouido)
(Is it real or fake?)
In that case, ma'am,
would we be able to sample those menu items?
- Yes. I'll prepare that for you. - Please do.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you!
It takes a while to make the food so we'll play a game first.
- All right. - Okay.
The games are hard, aren't they?
The game we'll play for this hint is "Don't Laugh Hide and Seek",
and will make use of the sleeping capsules.
- What? - Sorry?
(Right in this place where they must keep quiet)
(A game developed specifically for this location)
(This game is also played in teams.)
- There are six capsules. - Yes.
The hiding team could hide in numbers 1, 3, 4, and 6.
Or they could all hide in number 6.
The seeking team chooses three capsules.
They choose numbers 1, 3, and 6, say.
But...
the hiding team will go in with whistles on their lips.
(Whistles?)
(Seeking team's mission, make the hiding team laugh)
How do we make them laugh?
So the crew has...
compiled a list of hilarious stories...
and brought them.
(The hiding team will inadvertently blow the whistle if they laugh.)
You'll be awarded ten points for each person you find.
(Understanding completely)
- It sounds fun. - This is great.
What are you talking about?
- "What are you talking about?" - "What?"
- Can we have that? - Try it.
Yes, I think we need to show Jessi.
Pretend that you're hiding in one of those.
I'm hiding?
(Am I the one hiding?)
I will read...
some to try to make you laugh.
- But would we blow the whistles? - This sounds fun.
Would we laugh at what we hear from the outside?
- I don't laugh easily. - I'll read another one.
(What will happen?)
This one is short and sweet.
(Time to try not to laugh)
"I got a pet dog for the first time."
"I found all these strange bumps on the dog's body."
(This would lead to his capture.)
(Sacrificing her face not to laugh)
"My mom and I took her to the vet, crying."
"They said, 'They're nipples.'"
(Failing to defend)
This is how it works.
("They're nipples.")
(How could anyone not laugh?)
(He who rarely laughs has been defeated.)
This is how it works. Then...
- "So my mom and I just came home." - Hey! Wait.
Just a moment. You're the funny one.
Your face is funnier than the story.
You need to make the story funny. Read it in a funny way.
We need to read them well like that.
If you make them sound funny, they will surely laugh.
Oh, no. I think I'm going to laugh.
I'll read you another story.
"I was urinating in a cafe bathroom when I also passed wind."
"A child must have accompanied their mother into the next cubicle."
(Caught)
"I was busting, so as soon as I sat down,"
"I passed gas and then peed."
So she passed wind while she was urinating.
(Think sad thoughts.)
"The child in the next cubicle said to their mother,"
"'Mom, there's an elephant next door.'"
(Mom, there's an elephant next door.)
(Blowing)
(We're in trouble.)
We're going to get caught no matter what.
- Yes, 100 percent! - We'll get caught!
This is so hard!
- Hey! - Let's do another one.
- This is so much fun. - All right.
- One more time. - This one is funny too.
- Listen up. - Let's try this.
"Someone got on a full bus so had no choice but to stand."
"But they were tired, so they said to themselves,"
"'Gosh, I want to sit down.'"
"'I want to sit down.'"
They were mumbling this to themselves.
(Please, let me stop smiling.)
"The bus stopped abruptly."
"They whispered into the ear of a seated gentleman,"
"'I want to sit down.'"
(They whispered into the ear of a gentleman.)
(The sudden appearance of an unconventional character)
(She's not crying.)
This is how it is.
(The practice game attacker is proud.)
But you know, this is quite easy for me.
Because I don't understand some of them.
I didn't get this one.
I don't understand some of them.
Right. You don't understand them.
You're so...
This game is great for you then.
- Jessi. Use this to your favor. - It's not funny at all to me.
She's on our team!
This one wasn't funny to me.
I'll do just one more for you.
You can't take all the good ones now!
This is the last one.
Now...
"A while ago, I was parking my car with my girlfriend."
He asked her to spot them while he was reversing the car.
The girlfriend said, "You haven't hit it yet."
"There's still space."
"Not yet. You just hit it."
"You just hit it."
(She was proving live commentary for the fender bender.)
(Struggling to breathe)
(The reader is satisfied.)
There was a story like this about one of our senior comedians.
"Okay! Reverse back."
They were saying, "Okay."
There was a slam. "Stop."
- It happened. - It was a true story.
This one was funny.
Let's decide which team hides and which seeks.
We'll decide and then play the game.
- How should we decide? - These are funny.
We also have to choose...
which capsule and how many in each capsule.
- We have to decide that too. - Then we might...
end up leaving...
Hey. This one is short and incredibly funny.
- Stop it! - You can't read them all here!
- You can't read them all! - Stop reading them!
Why are you still reading them?
- Stop reading them. - We'll use it when we attack.
- Just listen to this last one. - Stop it.
- You're wasting them. - Listen to this.
- See here. - Hey!
We should listen with our eyes shut. That's how we'll know.
- Eyes shut, everyone. - This is a simulation.
- The last one. - I'd prefer to watch.
"I called my younger brother."
"He answered in a whisper,"
"'Hey. What's up?'"
(Hey. What's up?)
"So I responded with,"
"'Hey.'"
"And he said, 'No. I mean, I'm in a meeting.'"
(Destroyed)
"No. I mean, I'm in a meeting."
(Thunderously loud)
(He who rarely laughs has been defeated again.)
(Collapsing again)
(This kind of story would have a 100 percent catch rate.)
He wasn't saying, "Hey. What's up?"
- "I'm in a meeting." - "I'm in a meeting."
I can't do this.
- "In a meeting." - I can't!
(It's time for the actual game.)
Let's go. Let's do this.
- Let's go. - Jessi!
EL, we're the hiding team.
Let's hide separately.
- Let's all hide separately. - All separately?
(Mi Joo and Jessi plan to all be in different capsules.)
- Yes. But... - All separately.
Let's all go into the same one.
- No. If we do... - We can't!
- Everyone in one capsule. - No...
No! Because I won't laugh.
- It'll be fun. - It's not fun!
Do you know anything about this show?
It won't be fun!
I'm going into this one by myself.
It'll be fun and thrilling.
(No, thank you.)
Should we all stay together?
- All together? - Yes.
- All right. - Because...
- that would be more fun. - It's more fun that way.
Come in. We can't get caught though.
Seok Jin...
We'll all get caught out even if only one person laughs.
I think this was a bad idea.
Don't laugh!
I don't laugh easily.
(I'll show you how good I am at not laughing.)
I won't laugh. Don't you dare laugh!
- We're going in. - Can we come in?
Yes, you can come in.
(Na Ra's team enters.)
I wonder where everyone is.
(Checking out the state of the rooms)
All right, then.
(Silent)
Oh, no. I'm already laughing.
Don't think about Jae Seok's face.
Stop picturing his face.
(Laughing at hearing his name)
I'll start reading the story.
We already read too many of the good ones.
- Make it funny, Jae Seok. - I'll read it now.
(Trust me.)
(I won't laugh.)
I will read you a story now.
(The bag of laughs is finally opening.)
"I work in a hospital."
"The patient's name was Acorn Kim."
"Acorn Kim."
(He who rarely laughs might get caught within 2 seconds)
(You said you didn't laugh easily.)
"That was the first threat."
(Are they here?)
"I held back my laughter..."
"and said, 'Acorn Kim, the doctor will see you now."
"And it was a man in his 50s."
(Shaking)
"That was the second threat."
(He who rarely laughs is also under threat.)
"Standing next to the doctor in the examination room,"
"she seemed taken aback after reading his chart."
"Acorn, what has brought you to the hospital today?"
(Measuring decibels)
(Cutting it fine)
"That's what the doctor said."
"I bit my lip, left the room, and laughed out loud in the tea room."
(We made it.)
(Did they successfully defend the first story?)
(Mi Joo's delayed reaction whistle blowing)
- No one's laughing? - Wasn't that funny?
It must not be funny.
- They're holding back. - They're trying not to laugh.
There aren't any more strong stories.
(Narrowly evading death)
This is the next story.
(Moving on to the next story)
"My friend told me to meet her at 'Twosome'."
(Patting)
"But I thought she said 'Ttukseom'."
(Trying to make up for it)
(I'm here.)
(Like using an alarm to tell them his location)
(Which of the following did Jee Seok Jin not do?)
(Suppress his laughter in order for his team to win)
"I've been waiting alone at 'Ttukseom' for two hours."
(Averting her eyes)
(Mi Joo started laughing because of Seok Jin.)
(He who pretends to laugh rarely)
(Reprimanding)
- I know where they are. - They're not in these two.
They're here. Here and...
(There's definitely someone on this end.)
(EL's team is backed into a corner.)
- This one? - This one.
I don't think it's this one. It's a trap.
- In that case... - Yes?
- Na Ra. - Yes?
- Let's go with that one. - Okay.
(What is "that one?")
- Okay, I'll read it. - We'll read it for you.
- Get ready for it. - Okay.
Confuse them. Point it that way.
Bite down hard on your whistles. I'm starting.
(Which story is Na Ra so confident about?)
This is U Plus customer service.
(Audio file that won the Internet when it was released)
How can I help you?
(Attacking with an audio file?)
(Is that Yong Seok?)
(No, ma'am. This is LG U Plus.)
(- Sorry? - It's LG U Plus.)
(Is there a fire?)
Is there a fire?
(They're here.)
(What is this?)
(Is LG on fire?)
(Confessing)
Is LG on fire?
(We're in this one.)
It's LG U Plus.
We're an Internet provider.
(Mi Joo is laughing particularly gleefully today.)
(Jessi, hip hop queen, snorting)
(- Sorry? - It's a customer service center.)
(A trade center?)
(This is a customer service center, ma'am.)
(A bathhouse?)
(Chaos)
(Forgetting their mission and laughing out loud)
(We've caught them.)
(Jae Lim is having fun.)
(So LG is on fire?)
(Chuckling)
(We could keep repeating ourselves all day.)
(How strange.)
(So what should I do?)
(Final blow)
So what should I do?
(We're here.)
(Na Ra's team is already huddled in front of capsule number 3.)
She's so sweet.
- So adorable. - She's so cute.
Choose three numbers.
We're done for.
We're all caught.
Yes, we are.
- It's 3, 6, and 2. - Yes.
Open numbers 2, 3, and 6!
- Open! - Open!
- It's empty. - Number six is empty.
- What is this? - Are they all empty?
- Are they all in here? - Mi Joo!
- It's Mi Joo. - Mi Joo!
Hey, Mi Joo!
- They're all here. - Are you all in there?
(Dazed)
(Na Ra's team has caught all members.)
- We still found them. - It was so funny.
- What a relief. - This is so hard.
- Let's go. - How should we hide?
- Do we hide now? - Yes, we hide.
- We have to choose. - We must choose.
- Should we use one... - All in one?
- No... - That's too dangerous.
- How do we decide? - Right. If one person laughs...
- Let's diversify. - Okay.
Sounds good.
(Where has Na Ra's team hidden?)
We're coming in.
I wonder where you all are. Bite down on your whistles.
Let's split up and take different areas.
Jessi, EL, and I'll go here.
Let's keep our promise.
Please keep the whistle at your lips.
Quick. Read the first story.
This is the first story.
(Will they find them?)
(Will they hold back?)
"My mom's friend saw me for the 1st time in 10 years."
"She was searching for the appropriate words."
"And ended up saying this."
"So this is what happened to you."
(Whistling)
I can hear it so clearly here.
- Number six! - No, keep quiet!
(Who is responsible for the melody from number six?)
(Na Ra and Jae Lim tensed up to suppress their laughter.)
(Sang Yeob only just makes it.)
(Whistling)
(Responsible for the melody)
(Sang Yeob and Jae Seok both entered capsule number 6.)
(I blow my whistle at funny stories.)
Excuse me? Is anyone there?
(His noisy roommate is making him nervous.)
I can hear it so clearly here.
(I don't know who you are but I know you're there.)
I know. But there are other rooms.
- Another one? - Read just one more.
Okay. You read it.
- Me? - Read this one.
- This one? - Yes.
(Jessi's reading it? Tired from laughing too much)
I'm starting. Listen up.
She might be even funnier.
It's perfect for Jessi.
"A lady said to a man wearing an Adidas jersey..."
(What's with her pronunciation?)
(Closing her eyes)
(Blowing)
(Incredibly flustered at the unexpected diction)
(Song Jae Lim)
(Confessing)
- I'm certain about this one. - You're certain?
(Please don't take it the wrong way, it's the clothing item "jersey.")
Hey.
I'm not done reading.
Where is that coming from? Are they all full?
(What is going on? They are everywhere.)
We can hear it from everywhere.
This is not fair!
How is this fair?
You're cheating!
This is cheating.
(Meanwhile, Na Ra is left alone.)
(Na Ra, you can make it.)
(Intensely fighting herself)
Okay. Quiet down.
"A lady..."
"said to a man..."
"wearing an Adidas jersey,"
"Oh, my. Your jersey is so pretty."
(It's a tough one.)
"Your jersey is so pretty."
(No. Don't let it out.)
"And so..."
"the man responded,"
"'Can you see my nipples?'"
(A perfectly funny story)
(I don't even know anymore. I'm just going to laugh.)
(Reality check)
(What will happen to Na Ra, who endured?)
- Please choose three numbers. - There's someone there, right?
I'm certain about this one.
- This one. - This one.
I'm certain about this one too.
There's definitely someone here.
- One more. - Should we go with number two?
Sounds good.
Open numbers 1, 2, and 6!
This is so unfair!
- Why would you read it like that? - Is that allowed?
In 1, 2, 3!
(Meanwhile, at capsule number one, )
(Jae Lim was squirming.)
(Caught)
(Offender)
There are 2! I caught 2 people!
We have all four!
(EL's team also succeeds at capturing 4 people.)
(Both teams are tied so neither gets a hint.)
"Jersey."
I'm hungry.
- I'm so hungry now. - We're hungry.
Our Hyun Ju has a very close relationship...
with this manager of hers.
- She's loyal. - And they're getting married today.
- Jessi agreed to sing for them. - Really?
The venue just happens to be in this vicinity.
- I'll be right back. - Be back soon.
Ho Hyun Ju. Yes!
- See you soon. - Hey. What's up?
- What's up? - I like that.
What an honor to have Jessi perform at their wedding.
- See you soon! - Okay.
We'll serve your meal now.
- What is that? - Hello, ma'am.
(Right here, ma'am.)
- "Ma'am." - Hello.
Hello.
(The sleep-promoting meal is finally served.)
Thank you.
- Is this the risotto? - Yes.
Excuse me, what kind of tea is this?
It's tart cherry tea.
There's tea too.
Yes. It's tart cherry tea.
(Tart cherries have a strong tart taste.)
(Benefits of tart cherry tea)
(It contains melatonin which aids in...)
(improving symptoms of insomnia and improves the quality of sleep)
- This tea is great. - The tea is tasty. It's sour.
Tart cherry tea helps promote sleep.
- Is that so? - Yes.
(We understand the benefits, but does it suit the meal?)
(The taste is complementary.)
I'll pour this over for you for the ochazuke.
The rice is really well made today.
(Dish that's easy to digest, salmon ochazuke)
So it should be tasty.
(Salmon, fish with orange flesh)
(Salmon has Vitamin B6 which assists the production of melatonin)
We tried to use ingredients that promote sleep.
We assembled the menu using various ingredients...
that contain melatonin...
or contain a high percentage of components that promote...
the production of melatonin.
(Salmon roe is on the house.)
(Side dishes that are easy to digest)
(Does salmon ochazuke actually promote sleep or not?)
Before you mix it, try it wrapped in the sea trumpet.
- With the rice? - Yes.
(I'll try the salmon ochazuke to see if it actually promotes sleep.)
- I'll try some. - Try it.
Honestly, it's really delicious.
(Showing a sincere reaction through her forehead)
The ochazuke is really delicious.
(Exactly to her tastes)
(What does it taste like?)
(Nice)
It's not just any green tea.
It's slightly flavored.
- It's a broth. - Right?
It's tasty.
All the meals...
are very healthy.
It's not very strongly flavored, is it?
I didn't realize it would taste so good with the broth.
(It's such a relief that I found this out now.)
(A big scoop)
(Open up, food is on its way.)
This place seems credible.
The food itself...
(It's for real.)
This place must be real.
It's delicious. How much does this cost?
How much is it?
(They're curious about the price now.)
What does it say for salmon ochazuke?
Just a moment. Is it the salmon dish?
It's 120 dollars.
(Going broke for a meal)
(Salmon is coming out of my nose.)
Why?
I'd consider paying up to 15, no 18 dollars for this.
- Is it that good? - Yes.
- It's 13.9 dollars. - That's cheap.
If it's 13.9 dollars,
that's not considered cheap for an office worker's lunch.
- It's tasty. - I'd pay up to 18 dollars for it.
The side dishes are also all very good.
These side dishes...
There's shrimp in this one.
What is this? Is it a pancake?
(Shrimp is an expensive ingredient to use in a side dish.)
(Is salmon ochazuke really a dish made to promote sleep?)
Is it tasty because we're hungry?
- No, it's really tasty. - No, the food is good here.
What is this green thing?
- Avocado. - Is it avocado?
I'm not sure.
It's seaweed.
- It's crown daisy. - Spinach?
- Is it spinach? - It's delicious.
(Salmon ochazuke)
(Spinach mushroom risotto)
(Easy digesting dish number 2, spinach mushroom risotto)
(Spinach and mushroom)
(They keep your stomach healthy with a lot of fiber.)
It helps you sleep, and it's healthy.
It's low calories. It helps your diet.
That's what we prepared.
Amino acid has an element that helps you sleep.
We tried to make dishes...
with mushrooms, milk, spinach and celery...
which are the materials for melatonin.
(Does spinach mushroom risotto help people sleep?)
I think this place is real.
(They carefully try the mushroom risotto.)
This place is real.
It doesn't taste too strong.
- This? - Yes.
- It's not too salty. - Right.
It doesn't taste too strong. I can go to sleep right after this.
(Is she sleepy already?)
It tastes good.
What do you think of the risotto?
- It's tasty. - Is it?
It's just perfect. It's not too salty.
Right.
(He might fall asleep because he's full.)
- Do you like it? - Yes.
(Jae Seok likes it too.)
The owner is a good cook.
- This place is really good. - It's really good.
I would come back here.
It's not common for a restaurant to sell both Japanese and Italian.
We're having both Japanese and Italian.
This is Italian.
Maybe they just brought everything.
(Two different cuisines in one restaurant)
(Is it real or fake?)
Gosh.
(Jae Seok finished his food.)
Can we have banana soy milk latte?
(Pestering)
Have coffee.
This is the perfect time for BM.
- BM. - What's BM?
BSM. It's time for BSM.
Old people abbreviate words unnecessarily.
(Two middle-aged men abbreviate words unnecessarily.)
Gosh, that girl.
I want ILES.
Stop abbreviating.
What's that?
Iced latte with extra syrup.
ILES.
I hate that. ILES?
Look at EL's face.
I want ILES.
She closed her eyes.
This place is real.
- It's fake. - I think it's real.
- It's fake? - Yes, it's fake.
That was cute.
ILES?
That was pretty cute.
- She's cute. - She's pretty cute.
- She's the cutest here. - Isn't she cute?
I go crazy...
about those who were born in 1974.
(No thanks.)
My wife was born in 1974.
- Seok Jin... - She refused.
I like everyone who was born in 1974.
(No thanks.)
EL. What do you think? Is this place real or fake?
(Thinking)
It was confusing.
Once I start doubting, everything looks fake.
I think it's fake.
That says, "We'll wake you up if you snore."
Everything looks fake.
You're not listening to me.
(Please listen to what I say!)
The payment system gave it away.
He's into it.
You need the business license number to set up the payment system.
I paid it with my account.
(A dollar disappeared from Jae Seok's account.)
(Does the massage chair prove this place is real?)
I'd come for the food. But it doesn't match the place.
You think so? But the food doesn't match the place.
(Discord between the sleep capsule and luxurious dishes)
(Is it a fake sleep restaurant?)
(A restaurant where you can sleep)
(1. Inappropriate interior design and lights for a sleep restaurant)
(2. The restaurant demands silence.)
(3. A mix of Japanese and Italian cuisines)
(Is this place real or fake?)
(Science of sleep for those who can't sleep Part 3)
(Only 6 are produced in a year. 650,000 dollar handmade bed)
(The third spot is Cheongdam-dong.)
(It's a common 6 lane road.)
Did you all eat?
Is it here?
(The 650,000 dollar bed is in this building?)
The 650,000 dollar bed is here?
(It looks like an ordinary furniture store.)
(Moving to grab Mi Joo's hair)
- You have to take it off. - Take it off.
No. I should've stopped you.
(Jae Seok fails to grab Mi Joo's hair.)
- Okay. - Let's hurry up, Mi Joo.
- Okay. - Hey.
Is it here?
Is it really 650,000 dollars?
(They enter the building with doubts.)
Which floor?
Second floor. You can walk up there.
Second floor?
This place is real.
- This place is real. - This place is real.
Is that why it's confusing?
Does this place really have a 650,000 dollar bed or not?
The thing is, is it really 650,000 dollars?
(Is the 650,000 dollar bed real?)
It's the same store upstairs.
Oh, it's nice.
(What's it like inside the bed store?)
(All kinds of beds are in the same place.)
(Starting with a cute bed for a baby...)
(Peekaboo)
(To a wide modern bed)
I love the bed.
(Which bed costs 650,000 dollars?)
This bed is nice and big.
(Is the 650,000 dollar bed real?)
(Jessi enters.)
(Glancing)
- Oh, my gosh. I want a baby. - It's so cute.
When I have baby, I'm going to make her sleep in a bed like this.
(Jessi's more interested in the baby bed...)
(than the 650,000 dollar bed.)
When I have a baby...
(Aren't you going to look for the 650,000 dollar bed?)
(Let's make a deduction, Jessi.)
This is the 650,000 dollar bed.
- Is this it? - I can tell.
That costs 650,000 dollars?
This is it. It says it's 650,000 dollars.
No way. 650,000 dollars?
(The most expensive bed in the world)
(Strong foundation)
(On top of the luxurious pattern, )
(a comfortable looking mattress is placed.)
(Place a thick topper, and the perfect bed is ready.)
I know why. It's all handmade.
(Is the 650,000 dollar bed real or fake?)
This is it. It says it's 650,000 dollars.
This one?
Am I right? It's 1, 10, 100, 1,000, 10,000.
Hundred thousand.
Why does this cost 650,000 dollars?
This is why.
(This?)
If they used high-quality leather,
and if it's all handmade, it'd make sense.
(Is this really 650,000 dollars?)
Jae Lim. What's the horse mane bed...
you mentioned before?
(The horse mane bed?)
It's got horses drawn.
Is that the signature logo?
- This pattern. - Is this real?
Everything has that pattern.
I've seen the horse mane bed.
(Jae Lim mentioned the horse mane bed while they were moving.)
(He said it's an expensive bed.)
I read in the article about a bed made with a horse mane.
I heard it's very expensive because it's all handmade.
Is this it?
Is this the horse mane bed?
(Is the horse mane bed the 650,000 dollar bed?)
Jae Lim. How do you know that?
Are you the spy?
Look at the handle.
It's all leather.
- Wait. - What?
Inside this...
- Is it different? - Is it really the horse coat?
- Come on. - Isn't it?
Then it'd be too stiff to sleep.
Is this...
(Is the topper the secret of the high price?)
It's on TV.
- What is? - It's on TV.
- What? - This bed is on TV.
- The commercial? - Yes.
(Something's playing on TV.)
(A high-quality bed commercial)
They go through all that?
- It's possible. - Right.
(Is it a real commercial made by the bed company?)
(Or did the production crew put so much effort to make a fake one?)
Can I try lying down on here?
Yes.
(Lying down)
It's so nice.
Gosh! It's so nice.
- I'm falling asleep. - It's comfortable.
- I'm falling asleep. - It's nice.
This is so nice.
What's Mi Joo doing on there?
(Na Ra tries how comfy the 650,000 dollar bed is.)
It's so nice.
How can this be fake?
It's very nice.
That's just enough comfort and softness.
You all look like old ladies.
Stop lying there.
I get that it's nice,
- but it costs 650,000 dollars? - That costs 650,000 dollars?
I'd think about it if it's 6,000 dollars.
Or 6,500 dollars.
Or are the springs inside gold?
- What? - The springs?
- Maybe it's not the spring. - What is it?
- Maybe it's got some science. - Why is it so expensive?
It's the horse.
Who spends so much on the bed?
(It's nice, but it's not worth 650,000 dollars?)
Let me tell you.
(Jessi knows the secret of the price?)
There's a really expensive bed that cost one million dollars.
And Drake has it.
I know Drake.
(A famous hip-hop singer-songwriter from Canada)
(He's really famous.)
(Anyway...)
It was expensive...
because it was all handmade.
That's why it costs one million dollars.
(Drake's bed cost one million dollars.)
(Then could there be a 650,000 dollar bed?)
I want the staff...
to tell us about this bed.
- Let's bring in the director. - Yes.
Director?
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello. I'm Manager Soo Hyun.
I'm going to tell you about...
the 600,000 dollar bed today.
This company is known as Swedish royal family's bed.
At first, this family made the saddle.
It was 1st established in 1852.
At the time, the company that made saddles...
also made mattresses.
Over time,
as fewer people ride horses,
they improved their mattress technique...
and started producing...
comfortable and durable beds.
This bed was created after collaborating with...
the world-famous building designer, Ferris Rafauli.
Only six experienced masters...
can participate in the bed production.
It takes six months for production.
Only six beds are produced in a year.
Sixth Sensers. Is this place real?
Nice to meet you.
I'll be straightforward.
Can you tell me why this is 650,000 dollars?
Do they really produce only six in a year?
- Is it six in the whole world? - Correct.
We have a unique spring technique.
The masters place each spring...
by hand.
It's 100 percent handmade.
(650,000 dollars because it's all handmade?)
I get that only six beds are produced in a year...
- by masters. - That's amazing.
Is there anything unique about it?
This bed...
only consists of natural materials.
(I see.)
The signature material is the horsehair.
(I was right?)
He mentioned it before.
Yes. Wool, cotton...
and flax.
Wool is flexible.
It keeps you cool in summer...
and warm in winter.
The flax prevents...
static from the springs.
The horsehair has outstanding permeability.
It can absorb and release...
sweats produced while sleeping.
Really?
Since it only consists of natural materials,
it was set...
at a high price.
(That makes sense.)
I thought it was decorated with gold...
- or something. - Or has a diamond.
I thought that's why it costs 650,000 dollars. Isn't that it?
No.
When I saw the handles,
I thought you had a technique to fold it in half...
- and carry it. - That's a good idea.
I tried to open it.
- That's so old. - I thought it opens.
- With wheels. - This isn't a folder.
I thought it looked like a suitcase.
- I thought it comes out. - Me too.
So you can take it with you on your trip.
(They thought it was expensive because you can carry it around.)
- What's this? - What's that?
- What's that? - I have to show you.
- Show us. - That must be evidence.
It's one of the materials for the bed.
It's the horsehair I mentioned earlier.
- Goodness. - Oh, Bigfoot.
- That's cute. - That's cute.
That's so cute.
Here we go again.
- So cute. - Like Mr. Bob.
(Armpit attack)
(You looked cold.)
Jae Lim. You should be on variety shows.
Is this expensive too?
Do you know how much it costs? Stop playing with it.
- Is it expensive? - Correct.
- We had to collect it. - Don't touch it.
When you had it...
- That's expensive. - He wanted to try it.
It smells so nice.
- Let me smell it. - It smells really nice.
- It's expensive. - Let me try.
Try what?
- She said it's expensive. - Let me try.
It's expensive. Don't you dare touch it.
(Sang Yeob. Buy one yourself.)
If you sleep on this bed,
how does it affect your body?
Conditions follow for a good sleep.
Like I said, the natural materials...
can control the temperature and humidity on their own.
That's pretty interesting.
The horsehair absorbs sweats...
and keeps the bed dry.
So you wouldn't turn over in your sleep.
- This? - Yes.
- No way. - I'm not sure about it.
(They can't believe how absorbent horsehair is.)
(Can the materials alone dry the sweat?)
(Is that true?)
- What about a warranty? - What about a warranty?
The warranty covers...
the springs and the base.
We provide 25 years of warranty.
Twenty-five years?
- That's necessary. - Right. That should come with it.
That means people can use it for life.
The warranty is 25 years...
because we have confidence in our product quality.
That's how it's possible.
(Still, it's too expensive.)
But it's too expensive.
How do you wash it?
- You don't have to. - You don't have to wash it.
- No? - Do you wash your bed at home?
- This? - The natural materials...
can control the temperature and humidity.
It's breathable.
- It's too expensive. - So you don't have to.
But you have to wash it.
What if someone pees...
in sleep?
Normally...
you have the bed sheet.
So you only wash the bed sheet.
- Yes. That applies here too. - This too?
There's a bed sheet? This isn't the bed sheet?
But if you put the bed sheet,
you can't tell this is a nice bed.
- No. - Does it come...
- with a bed sheet? - Only you know it.
- I see. - Only you know it.
As long as I can sleep.
As long as your family knows.
You're the one who needs to know.
(A high price bed that doesn't need to be washed)
(Is it real?)
I have a question.
Does anyone buy it?
(Paying attention)
(Curious)
Yes.
Is it Jennie?
(Is it the bed from Jennie's social media?)
(It's the same brand, but it's not the same model.)
In Korea,
personal information is confidential.
I can't tell you...
- who bought it in Korea. - Right.
A famous hip hop singer abroad,
Drake bought it.
- You mentioned it earlier. - Jessi mentioned it.
He's the first purchaser in the world.
- I mentioned him. - You mentioned Drake.
As far as I'm concerned, it was one million dollars.
He probably customized it.
(If that's true, he probably customized it.)
(Jessi knew that Drake bought it.)
(Then is the expensive bed real?)
(Or is Jessi a spy...)
(who got information from the production crew?)
(Let me see.)
Drake didn't come here to buy it.
No.
(Is that what you were thinking the whole time?)
- This can't be... - Did you deliver it to him?
"I'm going to Cheongdam-dong to buy a bed."
(Stop it.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(The conversation with the manager ends.)
It's so strange...
because people sweat and drool...
in sleep.
Dust and mites.
It's strange...
that she said it doesn't need to be washed.
- Wash it on your own. - Even there's a cover...
(Was that her mistake?)
(Or is it really the power of natural materials?)
This place is too humble for a 650,000 dollar bed.
- Right. - Don't you think?
Who leaves 650,000 dollars here like this?
- Exactly. - You have a point.
Put a fence around it at least.
(The expensive bed is left unprotected.)
I want to ask EL.
Is this brand real?
- Yes. - Is it?
It appears...
- on "Emily in Paris". - Right.
- Goodness. - That's true.
(It's so difficult.)
- Here's the hint. - Give it to us.
- I want to see the hint. - Give it to us.
- Give it to us for once. - Give it to us.
- We never had a chance to see it. - Give it to us.
It's luxurious.
Drake's house?
It's the same bed.
(The same brand bed in Drake's house)
- It's same. - It's not.
- The color is different. - It's the different color.
Maybe they put marble on the bottom.
- She said this can be customized. - Yes.
Is it a replica?
(A fake bed created by production crew based on Drake's?)
But it kind of looks similar.
(The same bed as Drake with different customization?)
(650,000 dollar luxurious bed)
(1. The bed is left unprotected despite its price.)
(2. Natural materials that do not need to be washed)
(3. A different design from Drake's)
(Is this place real or fake?)
We're going to reveal the answer up here.
You have five minutes to discuss.
I'm not sure.
I think it's number 2, but number 3 was strange too.
She made us really confused.
(Confused by high difficulty level)
(There were suspicious moments.)
Don't you think?
I saw the menu...
in the counter.
It was just a piece of paper.
(It looked like it was just printed.)
- It should be laminated or thick. - It should be thick.
This is really hard.
If the production crew had to fabricate it,
number two is what they'd do.
(The interior design looked like it was done by the production crew.)
(The sleep restaurant's interior design bugs them.)
(Is this place real or fake?)
- This place is real. - Then is it number two?
- It's number 2. - Number 2.
- Number two? - Yes.
If we choose number two, does the bed become real?
Yes.
(Well...)
The brand is real, but I'm not sure about the price.
(The bed looks too ordinary for the price.)
Only six are produced in a year. Think about it.
It's for the show,
but they'd let us sit on it?
Exactly.
They wouldn't just let anyone sit on it.
(The bed is left unattended when it's rare.)
(The 600,000 dollar bed sounds suspicious.)
(Is this real or fake?)
This is so hard.
It's really hard today. I still can't decide.
It's Seok Jin.
Yes.
I'm telling you.
- Hey. - Let's talk without Seok Jin.
- Hey. - I don't think it's number two.
Since they're going for number 2, we should go for number 3.
See? He says we should go for number three.
He has no plan to win at all.
Trust my hunch.
(Seok Jin was suspicious of the manager.)
(How frustrating.)
(Seok Jin's acting so strange.)
(The manager here.)
(This place looks weird.)
(Seok Jin repeatedly said it's strange.)
(You look like a spy.)
(Speechless)
(Staring)
(Jae Seok noticed it.)
(His facial muscles can't hide it.)
- Seok Jin. - Hey.
(Why is he suddenly putting his hands in his pockets?)
(He hides his hands to hide awkwardness.)
(His hand doesn't know where to go.)
(Seok Jin appealed that he's the spy in the third spot.)
Seok Jin made the gestures he makes...
- when he's nervous. - Did he do that a lot?
- His face turned red. - That's right.
Seok Jin's acting weird.
It's about time for the guest to be a spy.
When I got the call, I said no.
Stop forcing us.
You have 30 seconds.
Oh, my gosh.
I don't know. I'm getting dizzy. Can someone hurry up and say it?
What's fake? And who's the spy?
Number two is fake. The spy is Seok Jin.
- You've made the decision. - You'll be happy.
What about you?
Shall we go for number three?
(Choose Spot 3 unlike Team EL?)
Since they chose number two.
Number three since they chose number two?
They chose number two. Let's go for number three.
Let's choose number three and pick the spy from there.
What's fake?
- Number three. - Who's the spy?
- Seok Jin. - Seok Jin.
It's Jae Seok.
(Oh, my gosh.)
(Twitching)
- Wait. It's Jae Seok. - Is it Jae Seok?
Why are you making that face again?
- I say it's Jae Seok. - You can't change it now.
- I got the wrong spy. - Wait a minute.
- It's Jae Seok. - No.
Jae Seok is the spy!
No.
(Driving it on Jae Seok again)
You have already made the decision.
You fools.
This team said number two was fake and the spy was Seok Jin.
This team said number three was fake and the spy was Seok Jin.
Let's go for it.
- The answer is shocking. - Let's go.
- Here it is. - Let's go.
(Mi Joo. You're not in a good condition today.)
(I couldn't sleep.)
(Wait. That's me.)
Because she was the spy?
(I'm stressed because I couldn't sleep.)
(The problem for one-third of people on earth)
(Insomnia)
(Is your night...)
(okay?)
(The project for those who cannot sleep at night)
(Science of sleep for those who suffer from sleepless nights)
I...
(Which is fake among the items that help you sleep?)
What's the answer?
(You just fall asleep while listening to it?)
(A songwriter from Berklee who writes customized sleep music)
The famous pianist.
We forgot about him.
He has multiple jobs. That's probably one of his jobs.
(A restaurant where you can sleep?)
(A sleep restaurant that induces you to sleep)
- Is that what you had? - Yes.
Number two.
(The most expensive bed in the world)
(The handmade bed that only 6 is produced in a year)
I guess the bed was real.
No, that can't be it.
(Which fake item bewildered you?)
Hurry up and show me!
(Getting bigger and more elaborate)
- They're making something again! - Hurry up!
What is it?
(Which team was not deluded by the spy and found what's fake?)
Please.
Number two.
It's fake. Please.
(Is the sleep restaurant Team EL chose fake?)
Number two.
(Is Team Na Ra's expensive bed fake?)
(To be continued)
(Which team will receive the lucky ball?)
- I'm surprised. - Where is it?
Number two.
(Is number 1 that no one suspected fake?)
(Which team will receive the lucky ball?)
- I'm surprised. - Where is it?
Number two.
(Is number 1 that no one suspected fake?)
(The sleep restaurant was fake.)
See? I knew it was number two.
(They got it.)
(It's a party.)
(Laughing)
- I said it was number 2. - You wanted to go for number 3.
(He doesn't know how to react.)
We changed it at the last minute.
It was number two.
- Why did we change it? - That's not the point.
You did your part.
You knew it was fake, didn't you?
(What's wrong with that guy?)
You shouldn't eat and sleep.
(Nothing is impossible to Sixth Sense.)
(In the concrete jungle)
(Yeouido the office town)
Right. I knew it was weird.
Inside that was...
What's that place?
(We found a good vacant office.)
Vacant office?
(My goodness!)
We didn't check the pipe.
Right. The kitchen was completely hidden.
(A perfect place for a restaurant)
(Until now, Sixth Sense made...)
(15 fake restaurants.)
- My goodness. - It was well-made.
(Let's show them what we've got.)
(Starting with the ceiling)
(We put up temporary walls according to the new ceiling.)
They put so much effort.
(Faster and faster)
(Put tiles on the floor.)
(Sleep restaurant is ready in no time.)
What?
I knew it was too easy.
- It looked like a cafe. - If it was a cafe, I'd get it.
It said silence on the wall.
(It became a real restaurant.)
(Sleep restaurant)
Unbelievable.
(What's left is the sleep.)
(Mission: Get the sleep capsules.)
(The long journey to find...)
(the sleep capsules began.)
You rented them?
(Let's rent them from the sleep cafe.)
- Can we borrow the sleep capsules? - That's crazy.
No?
I called you to see if I can borrow them.
How much does it cost?
(I see.)
(2nd attempted failed because it was too expensive.)
(We made 30 calls to borrow sleep capsules.)
Really?
(But we failed.)
(Let's visit the sleep cafe and ask the owner in person.)
(Would he lend them to us?)
You worked very hard.
(Are we failing it?)
- Did you buy them? - The production crew...
(The youngest writer's hands move fast.)
(Let's call the sleep capsule company.)
Can we borrow the sleep capsules?
- You'll lend them to us? Thank you. - They'll lend them.
That's really amazing.
(We finally met the sleep capsules.)
You rented them?
They were all rented?
Once they make up their minds, they make it happen.
(We hired the experts to install the sleep capsules.)
- No wonder the sleep capsules... - I know.
Were pretty nice inside.
(The experts installed them.)
(The sleep capsules were installed in no time.)
The sensors inside were real.
Impressive.
(The sleep restaurant is cleared.)
(The details to create a sleep restaurant)
(About this...)
- What's that? - Oh, the massage chair.
But I made the payment.
Jae Seok fell for that.
That's what made Jae Seok fall that.
Jae Seok kept talking about it.
(A massage chair room is completed.)
You could actually run it.
(Starting with the sentimental counter)
Oh, that.
(To minor details)
(A sleep restaurant is completed.)
That's unbelievable.
(The food looked pretty nice.)
That was...
When something is to my liking, I should suspect it.
(32 days before the science of sleep shoot)
We need food for the sleep restaurant.
What helps you sleep?
(The meeting becomes silent.)
What's going on?
(Zero knowledge)
Did some chef help them?
(For the perfect delusion, we researched it for 2 weeks.)
(We also studied books on nutrition.)
(We checked FDA, associations and papers...)
(to collect data on the food that helps you sleep.)
(Over 100 pages of recipes and related information)
(Exclaiming)
They go through so much.
- They're amazing. - It was really good.
The food was really good.
(Dozens of demonstrations)
Why does the production crew keep...
making it to meet Jae Seok's taste?
Maybe they have the same taste.
(We came up with the sleep food that did not exist before.)
(Successful)
It was really good.
I liked it.
The food was good.
- Well done, food team. - I was deceived by the food team.
(Then who was the owner?)
Hello.
I provide nice beds.
(Does she have something to do with sleep?)
(She's grabbing something.)
(There it is.)
What did she grab?
(It's hard to tell who she really is.)
What's that?
(What are you doing?)
- What's that? - What is that?
(Dragonflies?)
(What?)
I study entomology including dragonflies.
(Not the bed for humans, )
(but bed for dragonflies?)
Dragonflies?
A bed. A dragonfly.
(It's the same sound in Korean, but different meaning.)
A dragonfly.
I can't believe them.
(He's knocked out.)
My name is Kim Song Eun.
I've been working as a TA for nine years in SNU.
(Did you all fall for it?)
What's the food that helps you sleep?
- They have to eat and sleep. - She was very eloquent.
So I thought I should open it in a place with lots of workers.
Weekdays and weekends are different.
I could tell that she memorized it.
(She's good enough to deceive the production crew.)
You're very eloquent.
I have to say she was good.
Sixth Sense.
This place is fake.
(A restaurant where you can sleep?)
(The sleep restaurant is fake.)
- Who's the spy? - Today's spy is...
It's you!
- It's not me. - Oh, my gosh. Jae Seok.
- It's him. - Get ready.
- We should've changed it. - Get ready for it.
The spy failed his mission.
- One of them got the answer. - Okay.
The spy is...
(Nervous, fidgeting)
(The spy was confusing because he was so obvious.)
(Who's the spy?)
You did a terrible job, Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin was the spy as expected.)
- You were terrible. - You did a terrible job.
You were so terrible.
(It looked as if he was here to ruin the show.)
Seok Jin. You have been selected as the third spy.
It's not my first time. I can fool them easily.
Guys. Long time no see.
Don't expect to get the answer. See you then.
(Let's watch Seok Jin's new concept of spy.)
(When they started talking about the spy in the opening...)
There's a spy?
(He pretended like he didn't know.)
(Then he got angry for no reason.)
(Why is he suddenly acting out?)
(The spy ruined it from the start.)
(I am the spy.)
(He was told to stop them from getting the hint.)
(He got up resolutely.)
(He should've just stayed seated.)
(He gave the answer away.)
(The spy is happy after getting the hint.)
(I am the spy.)
(How do you wash this?)
(He gave them a chance to doubt her by mistake.)
(Everyone becomes suspicious.)
(Then he stepped out.)
(The ugly spy stops the suspicion by talking about the cover.)
(I am the spy.)
(We will never ask you to be the spy again.)
Let's start with Seok Jin. What did you think?
I never hated Jessi and Mi Joo so much like today.
They were fighting the whole time.
No matter how much I insisted, they kept saying no.
(Mi Joo and Jessi, I hate you.)
I did my best, but I didn't get it.
You still got the spy right.
Yet I still used up all my energy.
I got both right.
(Perfect ceremony)
- Good work. - Good work.
It was amazing.
(See you next week.)
The end.
(Sixth Sense is full of love.)
(The unwelcome guest, Cho Sae Ho returns.)
(Why him again?)
(Mi Joo's love life takes a break.)
(I had never been interested in you.)
(Nation's traitor, Choi Tae Joon)
(I am happy every day.)
(Advice from a senior married man)
(That's Jae Seok's opinion.)
(Today's topic)
(Put the cart before the horse.)
(An unexpected jackpot?)
(A restaurant with the sales of 50,000 dollars a month)
(The secret is not the food, but the workers?)
(An internet cafe that hit a jackpot with something unexpected)
(It's not a game. What is this?)
(Is this a short rib restaurant or what?)
(Why do people want it more than the short rib?)
(And)
(The backstabbing...)
(production crew's...)
(mega longterm project)
(It took them 60 days.)
(They moved 300km.)
(They cast a special guest...)
(to delude the doubtful members...)
(100 percent.)
(Sixth Sense 3)