Have you sobered up a little?
Yes.
Don't get bothered about what the empress said. She was speaking nonsense since she was drunk.
I think I should get back to my quarters.
♫ On that day ♫
♫ when the weather was so warm ♫
Tonight,
why don't you sleep here?
♫ Embraced in your arms, I rested ♫
How long are you going to keep me lonely?
- Your Majesty.
- I'm asking you until when you're going to keep your distance.
♫ That day we loved until we wept ♫
I want you.
♫ Can't I return to that day? ♫
♫ Even if I were to ache and it was our last moment ♫
♫ Embrace me in your arms ♫
♫ If I could become the dust flying in the wind ♫
♫ If I could become the raindrops on your window ♫
I will wait.
Until the day you take me into your arms first.
♫ No matter where it is, as long as you are there ♫
Even though you're with me,
I miss you so much.
♫ Until I wept ♫
Right now,
you should only be thinking about how to gain back your authority.
You're the one who made me this way.
So don't make me wait too long.
♫ at any time ♫
♫ You can return to me ♫
Go back to your quarters and get some rest.
♫ Because I will always remain there ♫
♫ Don't let the passing time ♫
♫ make you give up ♫
Is something on your mind?
I've started to become...
a little fearful.
You're so strong. What is making you fearful?
Your Majesty, what brings you here so late at night?
That wench Ki went into the emperor's quarters.
She's making a fool out of me even out here!
Tonight is the last time the two of them will be able to hurt your feelings.
Are you done preparing to kill that wench?
It's not just Lady Ki.
What are you talking about?
- You don't mean...
- Yes.
The two of them will die together.
- You didn't tell me you were going to kill the emperor, too.
- It's Father's orders.
The emperor and Lady Ki...
They will both die.
That's enough!
Those bastards are trying all kinds of things in order to win.
They must be planning on catching a large animal.
Cover it up so you can't see it.
Begin.
- Did you poison the arrows?
- Of course.
One arrow will cause death.
Let's finish up and go back.
Once they leave, we should destroy the trap they installed.
It's going to be daylight soon. How will we destroy them all?
Still, we can't let them cheat.
- We should do as much as we can.
- Those bastards...
they're really trying to capture all the animals. How many traps did they set?
There are 30 in total. Especially,
they're concentrated in this location, Cheonmaru, where the emperor's group has planned to hunt.
That will become his gravesite.
Make sure you place a man there who doesn't talk easily and is trustworthy.
Yes, Sir.
Don't take part in tomorrow's hunt.
What are you talking about?
I will watch that wench's demise with my eyes wide open.
Did you sleep well?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Today...
let's try to do well in the hunting competition.
You lost in the horseriding competition yesterday, too.
Your Majesty, you told me you won.
Golta, I said I... nearly won. When did I...
say I won?
Well, anyway, the real competition starts today.
Let's see who catches a bigger game.
Yes, I am confident, whatever it is.
- Your Majesty!
- My Lady!
What are you doing? Follow them!
They're coming!
The emperor and Lady Ki are on their way.
Everyone, to your places!
What?
What happened?
The rope must have been cut.
This dumb bastard!
There's no way that would happen.
Go check it!
Check the ropes!
Everyone spread out and check the traps!
Yes, Sir!
- It's this way.
- What are you talking about?
I saw it running away that way.
Then you go that way. I'll go this way.
Fine. Let's meet here once we catch something.
I will show you what a strong man I am.
There's boar's blood here.
It was hit by an arrow, so it couldn't have gone far.
Your Majesty!
Why are those imperial guards hiding there?
That's where the traps were set.
Traps?
Last night, those weasels put a lot of traps everywhere.
They seem to really want to win this hunt.
Something is strange, don't you think?
It's not normal for people to be near the traps.
That's true.
The animals won't go that way if people are there.
There will be a good spectacle.
I am going to catch a very impressive animal.
What they're trying to catch might not be animals.
Pardon? What do you mean? Why wouldn't they catch animals on a hunt?
Where were the traps set?
There are several over there and over by Cheonmaru.
Cheonmaru is...
where the emperor and Seung Nyang went hunting.
Pardon?
Then... what they're trying to catch is...
Eunuch Bang, go and tell Bayan about this. We're going to Cheonmaru.
- Yes, Sire.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Whoa.
More.
Just a little more.
Kill that wench!
Hurry up and get her!
Go and fetch more imperial guards.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Stop!
Get her!
It looks like we won't even catch a rabbit today.
Let's go back, Lady Oh.
Still, it's our pride on the line. How could we go back empty-handed?
Lady Oh! Look over there!
Stop!
What's going on?
We need to let His Majesty know!
I will kill each and every one of you.
Yang will be really surprised when she sees this.
I think you've won this time.
But... I think Lady Ki is coming back too late.
Your Majesty!
The imperial guards are trying to kill Lady Ki!
What? Where is she?
It's toward Cheonmaru.
I know you're out of arrows. Come out here!
I see this lowly wench knows how to fight.
I told you once. There's no one who's better at shooting than me at the palace!
Over there!
Are you trying to kill me?
There are no witnesses. Who would know if you die out here in this deserted hunting ground?
Then hurry up and shoot.
Why? You want to die quickly?
I can't let you. I will kill you slowly
and watch you die in pain so that I can remember it for a long time.
You probably didn't expect the cost of having received His Majesty's favor would be this cruel.
Even if I die, I have no regrets.
Do you know what His Majesty tells me every night as he holds me in his arms?
That I am the true empress of this country.
- What?
- He said Danashiri is not even a woman.
She's just a shell of a person who's like an ornament of the inner court.
Shut that mouth!
Being upset will cause the arrow to miss the mark.
You're laughable. And I feel sorry for you for being an empress who the emperor doesn't even glance at.
Silence I said!
Even if you kill me, nothing will change.
You will never feel the emperor's touch for the rest of your life; and even in death, you will be wandering the heavens thirsty for love.
I will rip you to death!
I'm the empress of this country.
Do you think you'll be safe if you kill me?
Hurry up and put down this dagger. If you do, I will have reason to let you—
You can't kill me.
There are no witnesses, so who would know if I killed you out here?
You started this fight.
I will end it for you right here.
P-Please spare me.
I'm sorry. Please let me live.
Please... Please don't kill me.
You killed the innocent Lady Park and those Goryeo servants so brutally!
Your life is precious; but yet, their lives were that insignificant?
I am sorry. P-Please forgive me.
Please. Please don't kill me. Please don't kill me, Lady Ki.
Silence!
Death is too light of a punishment for you.
I will let you live. Live on
and feel pain down to your bones that's worse than death.
I will make sure...
you end up that way.
- You're here, Father.
- What happened?
The emperor and Lady Ki are still in the hills.
We sent the imperial guards as back up, so it will be taken care of soon.
We're going hunting, too.
You mean, you're going to do it yourself?
We will need to bring the bodies if they're dead; and if not, we'll have to kill them!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, what's the matter?
Why are you coming now?
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
Lady Ki just headed down. Go and kill her!
You must be sure to get rid of her!
Yes, Your Majesty!
But... what happened that your face is...
There's no time to waste.
I need to see that wench die myself.
Your Majesty!
She's finally here.
Yang! Where are you Yang?
Your Majesty!
Yang!
Are you all right?
Sire!
Sire! Protect His Majesty!
My Lady.
Your Majesty.
I'm fine.
I'm glad you're safe, Yang.
Because of me...
We're killing them all.
If we fail, we won't be able to live.
We've already failed.
We need to kill them in order to succeed.
But, Commander...
Whoever doesn't take action now, once this is over,
will die by my sword!
Everyone follow me!
Hurry up and protect His Majesty!
Please get away from here with His Majesty.
Let's go!
It's the emperor! Kill him!
Get them!
We need to stop them.
There are too many of them.
It's too dangerous!
Your Majesty!
We have an order from Prime Minister. Please stand aside!
You will need to kill me if you want to go after them.
You're a traitor! Kill him!
♫ Carried on the wind, you are heard ♫
♫ Ceaselessly falling ♫
♫ Drip Drip Drip ♫
♫ In the sound of the rain for a long time after ♫
♫ Even if I wander and am lost, ♫
♫ it is you, it is you again. ♫
Come and get it!
Your Majesty, are you all right?
I can't see anything, and my body...
I have a chill.
Please look at me.
It's a poisoned arrow.
We need to remove the poison.
No.
If you're not careful,
you could be put in danger, too.
If we leave it alone, you will die.
It's dangerous.
You must stay awake. You must fight it.
Your Majesty.
It's Wang Yoo.
He betrayed us.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty. Your Majesty!
We must not let even one man chase after Seung Nyang.
Even if we die, we must stop them.
Understand?
This is your chance. Shoot now.
Hurry up, Your Majesty!
What's wrong with me? Why can't I kill him?
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, please come to your senses.
You must get up now.
Please wake up, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
- Your Majesty!
My Lady!
What happened?
He was shot with a poisoned arrow. Hurry up and help him!
Help His Majesty up!
Yes, Sir.
You're bleeding a lot. You have to get down and stop the bleeding.
Did you tell General Bayan?
He's on his way here with his men.
There's no time to waste. Please get on my back.
I can still walk.
Never mind me. I don't know if Seung Nyang is safe.
Your Majesty!
Seung Nyang's life isn't the problem right now, Your Majesty!
You must take care of yourself!
You could die like this!
Please kill us, Prime Minister!
Useless bastards. Making me unsheath my sword!
I have no excuses for failing you!
Father, look over there!
Go and surround them!
Yes, Sir!
Is the emperor not well?
Your Majesty, I will soon send you where you can be comfortable.
Father, it's Bayan!
How did he know?
Sir!
What happened to His Majesty?
He was shot with a poisoned arrow.
Please bring him here with you.
Bayan. I will take care of His Majesty.
I will do it, so send him this way.
Are you disobeying me?!
Stand aside, Bayan!
Until I have His Majesty, I will not, even if I die.
Prime Minister, did you plot treason?
Treason? What ludicrous statement!
His Majesty got caught in the trap set for the animals.
We saw it clearly.
How dare you lie?
Silence. How dare a eunuch speak flippantly?
If His Majesty dies in Prime Minister's arms,
the magistrates won't be able to help but suspect you.
Stand aside, Prime Minister.
Bayan, His Majesty is not well,
so you should take good care of him.
Please come this way.
I will help him.
Please lead the way, Uncle.
We can't let them go like this! We need to kill—
Father!
You want the whole world to know we committed treason?
Forgive me.
You will need to get rid of the evidence. Take care of the bodies of the fallen imperial guards.
Yes, Father.
Your Majesty, please wake up.
You must take the medicine, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty! Are you awake?
What happened?
You've been sleeping for a day and a half.
According to the physicians, you seem to have been affected by the poison.
- Poison.
- It's a relief that it was a small amount.
His Majesty. How is His Majesty?
He's still unconscious.
I need to go see him, so get ready.
Is your wound all right?
Don't worry.
Are you all right?
We're not that easily affected, Your Majesty.
Please do not worry.
What are you doing here?
Prime Minister asked to see me.
Prime Minister is suspected of treason.
You could be put in danger,
so you will need to be careful.
Didn't we say we were going to follow our own path?
Whether interest or worry,
please don't have
concern for me.
Don't associate yourself with Wang Yoo any more.
He seems to be close to El Temur.
Your Majesty!
Seung Nyang is watching. Don't give it away.
We will need to change the dressing at the guesthouse.
Your Majesty.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
He can't seem to drink the tonic.
What can we do?
I will do it.
You will?
He ended up like this while saving me.
I am going to make sure
I save His Majesty.
Try leaving it to Lady Ki.
If there are any changes, let me know.
Yes, Your Highness.
The magistrates?
I've called for them early on, so they should soon be here.
There are witnesses.
This time, Prime Minister won't be able to get out of this no matter who he is.
I will kill him myself for committing treason.
But if Prime Minister uses the soldiers to intimidate us again like last time...
We will prevent any threat by stationing our troops around the palace.
I'm worried about His Majesty.
He has to wake up soon.
Will you be all right alone?
I will be fine.
♫ That day when we loved until we wept ♫
♫ That day when we were happy, can't I return to that day? ♫
♫ Even if I were to ache and it was our last moment ♫
Your Majesty,
you must drink the tonic.
That's the only way you can live.
♫ If I could become the dust flying in the wind ♫
♫ If I could become the raindrops on your window ♫
♫ No matter where it is, as long as you are there ♫
♫ If I could go there ♫
♫ I would give up everything I have ♫
♫ That day when we loved until we wept ♫
♫ That day when we were happy, can't I return to that day? ♫
♫ Even if I were to ache and it was our last moment ♫
♫ Embrace me in your arms ♫
♫ I stand alone in the darkness ♫
♫ Like a lost child ♫
♫ My heart is frozen with fear ♫
♫ If we could return just once ♫
♫ You can come to me at any time ♫
♫ Because I will always remain there ♫
- The emperor is showing no signs of waking up?
- Yes, Father.
Seeing how they're even preventing me from entering his quarters, he must be in a critical state.
Why did you want to see me?
We need a witness who will help us.
Can you testify on our behalf?
Not Wang Yoo!
Why not?
That wench Ki is from Goryeo.
People protect their own. How can we trust Wang Yoo?
Right now isn't the time to worry about those things.
The magistrates will be here soon trying to uncover the truth.
We will need to draw up a contingency plan, so please help us.
I would like to hear your opinion first, Prime Minister.
What do you plan on doing about what happened?
I would like to get rid of all evidence of treason and safely ride out the storm.
If I can prevent it by
even losing one of my limbs, that will become my mission.
And if I have to shed blood by fighting, that will be the contingency plan.
If the magistrates band together and fight against you,
it will be hard to go with the contingency plan.
You are more afraid of the small knife at your throat than a large blade far away.
I have the Capital Defense Force.
We have put them on standby in case of the worst scenario.
I don't wish to go with the contingency plan either.
So please testify on our behalf.
You will have to change your plan to reveal his treason.
It will be hard to get rid of El Temur over this incident anyway.
You must do as El Temur wishes and save yourself.
Eunuch Bang, go and tell Officer Bayan
- El Temur's plans.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
Your wound must be painful, but you're dealing with it quite well.
Just one word from me
and your despicable mask will be taken off.
But why did you not tell him?
Don't be mistaken. I haven't yet...
I haven't yet opened my mouth, that's all.
Then please go tell him.
That I saved Lady Ki by killing the imperial guards.
Do you still have
affection for Lady Ki?
Is that why you're helping that wench while putting your life in danger?
It's not affection but duty.
Duty?
What duty do you have left toward that wench?
You don't know.
When I was shot with an arrow by General Danqishi
and was near death, how Lady Ki, who was my subordinate, saved me.
Now...
I have paid back all of my debt to her, so she has nothing to do with me.
Do you expect me to believe that?
Whether you believe me or not,
I am just expressing my belief.
So... do as you believe.
You will need to help my father.
If not, when Lady Ki dies,
you will die along with her.
Hello, General.
Because you didn't get the job done properly,
Father is in grave danger.
I am very regretful about that.
If something unexpected happens,
you will need to resolve it.
What do you expect us to do?
This treason was
carried out by you two all on your own.
- Pardon?
- You want us to
- take all the blame?
- That's
the only way we can live and you can live, too.
It's not something else but high treason of trying to kill the emperor!
You can avoid the punishment for treason. I will help you.
Still, there won't be a way to avoid execution.
Don't worry. I will
let you escape in secret.
I will follow your order, General.
So...
please keep your promise that
you will save us, no matter what.
I promise.
Brother, the magistrates have arrived!
El Temur has mobilized the Capital Defence Force?
That's what I heard from Wang Yoo.
Dammit.
I think it would be best to see how it plays out first.
Why did you try to kill the emperor and Lady Ki?
With what proof are you saying that?
Lady Ki and the guards saw you clearly!
I will ask Lady Ki.
Who tried to kill the emperor?
The imperial guards.
The imperial guards?
We saw it, too.
The imperial guards tried to kill Lady Ki.
So, among those who tried to kill His Majesty, was I there?
If not, did you see my sons?
There were only the imperial guards.
Therefore, I've arrested the conspirators who committed this treason.
Bring them in.
Tell us what happened.
Everything...
was my, Yeom Byeong Soo's, plan.
You definitely received orders from Prime Minister. If not,
how could the captain of the Imperial Guard plan to commit such treason?
The person I was after
was not His Majesty but Lady Ki.
His Majesty...
got hurt because he was in the way.
Empress Dowager, we cannot believe this man.
Why did you try to kill Lady Ki?
Lady Ki has a grudge against me because I dragged her here as a tribute.
She tried to take revenge against me after she became a concubine, so I decided to kill her first.
Shut that mouth.
How dare you lie here?
Empress Dowager, he committed high treason.
How can you believe his cunning words?
We must shut his mouth immediately and thoroughly search for the truth.
Your words are correct.
You will have to prove that your words are the truth.
Yeom Byeong Soo and Lady Ki were both Wang Yoo's subordinates.
Wang Yoo can confirm the truth.
Please speak. Are Yeom Byeong Soo's words the truth?
His words are the truth,
not a bit of falsehood.
Drag them away.
Your Majesty...
Your Majesty, are you coming to your senses?
Yang...
Yang... where is Yang?
This incident has not been solved.
So let us not cause a disturbance
with any more baseless conspiracy theories.
We are not finished.
Since the emperor has become injured, Lady Ki and the guards who were with him
should be held responsible.
Isn't this something we didn't expect?
Empress Dowager, please order the arrest of Lady Ki as well as her servants and guards.
Shouldn't we follow the imperial law with rigor?
If you can't,
I will do it myself.
Arrest Lady Ki as well as her servants and guards.
You must hold back.
♫ That day when we loved until we wept ♫
♫ That day when we were happy, can't I return to that day? ♫
♫ Even if I were to ache ♫
♫ and it was our last moment ♫