Your Majesty, did you drink wine again today?
Oh, my Chief Imperial Consort.
I'm not in the mood for your nagging.
Your Majesty.
But seeing my Chief Imperial Consort
makes my heart feel lighter.
Have you come, Your Majesty?
So it was him?
He may have lost, but he fought a force with 20,000 with only 3,000 men.
But he lost.
He is a brave warrior. It's my fault for not sending him reinforcements.
But this man...
made a huge mistake.
A mistake?
This guy...
This guy... made my wine taste bad.
How dare you ruin the emperor's mood?
Of course you deserve to die, don't you?
Isn't that true, Chief Imperial Consort?
Your Majesty!
Please... Please...
Please let me live.
El Temür's puppet.
Only a figurehead emperor.
Idiot moron.
How dare you mock your emperor?
Your Majesty?
You called me El Temür's puppet?
Your Majesty.
I will kill you all! I will kill you all and
and shut your disloyal mouths!
Your Majesty! You must not!
Out of my way.
Didn't you hear them mocking me?
Didn't they just mock me and call me El Temür's puppet?
They have disrespected me!
Your Majesty! Please come to your senses.
I told you to get out of my way.
Your Majesty!!
Prime Minister, even you...
Do you find me ridiculous, too?
You don't care about my imperial commands?
Do you think I can't kill you?
- Uncle.
- Don't interfere.
Your Majesty, if you will come to your senses by beheading me,
I am happy to give my life to you.
Out of my way.
And if I don't?
Out of my way, Bayan!
It's Yang.
Yang?
Yes, Your Majesty. It's Yang.
Yang...
Yang.
Are you hearing voices again?
Yang...
No.
- Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
What is wrong with me
these days?
Please order the soldiers at war to return home.
But if I stop now, I will be branded a failure for the rest of my life.
No one will think of you that way.
I no longer want to become a subject of mockery.
For no one.
Then please promise me one thing.
You must not drink anymore.
All right, I will do that.
I will never drink wine again.
Your Majesty,
are you unhappy with me for some reason?
Your gaze, as you look at me, is not the same as it was before.
If you are unsatisfied with something about me, please tell me.
I am asking, just in case...
are you hiding something from me...
Why did you stop speaking?
No, nothing at all.
Your Majesty.
You are the only one in the world who can support me.
Only you, Yang.
Only you.
My Yang.
After working on driving them apart for five years,
shouldn't the emperor have cast out the Chief Imperial Consort by now?
But how can we hear nothing about it?
And what is that, that you look so serious?
It's a report from our spies in Ilkhanate.
Goryeo is selling sulfur and saltpeter to Ilkhanate?
Wang Yoo is more than capable of such treachery.
When will you meet with Court Lady Yeon?
Tomorrow is the day she runs errands at the empress's private home.
When you see her tomorrow, tell her to also bring Court Lady Seo out, too.
Are you going to meet with Prince Maha, finally?
I will give this spy report to Empress Dowager.
Why to Empress Dowager instead of the emperor?
Empress Dowager is raising Maha, so shouldn't we lend her strength?
But will Empress Dowager step up for us?
I know that woman's ambition very well.
There is no way she will only remain in the background.
But shouldn't we notify the leader?
Send him a message.
I understand.
Il-il-bool-nyeom-seon.
Je-ak-gae-ja-gi.
What does that mean?
"If you go even one day without thinking of good,
all evil will happen naturally."
That is what Zhuangzi wrote.
Try reading some more, Imperial Prince.
Jong-shin-haeng-seon, Seon-yoo-bu-jok,
Il-il-haeng-ak, Ak-ja-yu-yeo.
"Even if you do good all your life, it is not enough good."
"And even if you do evil just one day, it is too much evil."
You are progressing so well in your studies.
When you are taught one thing, you learn ten.
Empress Dowager, I want to learn martial arts as well.
Imperial Prince, you can't do that.
Even if I become the emperor someday,
I will relieve my mother's grudge myself.
How can your words
sound so refreshing?
If he even just finds out that you are studying your letters,
His Majesty will be furious.
Please wait just a little longer.
Not every day will be cloudy.
Hurry and recite after me.
- "The colors of the sky and the earth."
- "The distance between sky and earth is long."
- "The sun sets in the west and the moon grows full, this is the order of things."
- "The sun sets ...
Are you sleepy already?
Yes.
Why do you doze off every time you read a book?
Mother, studying my letters is fun,
but I am sleepy.
How can you resemble your father so much?
Your Highness, it is time for the prince to visit with His Majesty.
I will return, Mother.
Looks like Prince Ayu is monopolizing His Majesty's love.
Ayu is happier to see Prince Maha, more than His Majesty.
I think he should keep his distance from Prince Maha now.
How are you, Imperial Father?
Come close to me, Prince Ayu.
Yes.
I heard you are learning the Thousand Character Classic recently. Try reciting them.
"Cheon" for sky, "Ji" for earth,
"Hyeon" for dark, "Hwang" for yellow,
"Jip" for roof, "Jip" for house,
and the next one...
Next one is... ?
This boy. Is that all you know so far?
Elder Brother is better than me at letters.
Maha is learning his letters?
Well... about that...
Emperor!
I taught him.
I told Prince Maha to learn his letters.
I told you to not learn your letters or martial arts.
- Did you forget what I told you?
- Emperor.
Why won't you answer me?
Why can't I?
I also commanded you to not ask the reason.
I want to know why I can't do what Ayu can do.
How insolent you are.
I won't receive visits from Maha for the time being.
So know that and leave now.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Highness, please come now.
Brother.
Please take Prince Ayu away as well.
Yes, Your Highness.
Emperor! How can you be so cold-hearted?
Do you really not know
why I am doing this?
Yes, El Temür did this to you, too.
He forbid you from learning your letters or martial arts.
So you are now doing exactly what El Temür did.
What El Temür did?
You're the one actually acting like him.
What nonsense are you saying?
Do you think I don't know why you have Maha in your clutches?
To make him the emperor
and rule this kingdom yourself, of course.
Just like how El Temür used me as his puppet.
Your words are excessive.
You participated in Danashiri's death as well.
So, what else could be the reason you are coddling Maha now?
He is your blood and the eldest son of this imperial family.
What other reason do I need?
- I no longer want to hear you, so please stop.
- Emperor!
Yes, that damned, 'Emperor! Emperor! Emperor!'
I am so sick of hearing it now, I have bile in my throat.
Tell Maha to become the world's biggest idiot, please.
You must make him that way.
That is how Maha can avoid death.
Imperial Prince? Did you cry?
I think I now understand what sorrow my mother suffered.
Has something happened inside?
I find you despicable and disgusting.
Your words are excessive.
You are now at an age where you can determine reason.
I don't know what you heard from Empress Dowager, but do not speak carelessly.
He is still young, but his gaze seems dangerous.
I think you should reveal his true origins now.
Look at that. I said I would separate those two, didn't I?
Their fighting will become ever more vicious.
Until one of the two dies.
Here.
- General Tanqishi?
- He's waiting inside. Go on in.
Yeon Hwa.
What are you doing? What if Court Lady Seo sees?
Did you like the gold ornament
I gave you last time?
Is there any woman who doesn't like gold?
Oh, you're so adorable. Oh my goodness.
Sir,
to see you alive like this...
How is the imperial prince?
He is full of sorrow. I pity him so much.
I cannot stand to see it with my eyes open.
Time has finally come.
Tell Maha that his uncle is alive.
Yes. Yes, Sir, I will.
And give this to Empress Dowager.
If she asks where you got it,
tell her that you got it from a merchant association leader coming from the west.
I understand. I will do that, Sir.
What do you think is the reason for our loss at battle?
There are many reasons, but gunpowder is the most important.
We never expected that Ilkhanate would have such a large amount of gunpowder...
Someone sold them the sulfur and saltpeter required and reaped enormous profits.
Is that the truth?
Who did that?
Give that to him.
Please read that.
Wang Yoo?
Yuan has been blocking Goryeo's overseas trade.
During that time, Wang Yoo has been selling sulfur and saltpeter.
The latest defeat by our forces has caused the people's resentment to rise to the sky.
So we will need someone who will take that resentment for us.
Dethrone Wang Yoo.
I need more concrete evidence.
I heard there is someone in Goryeo who can collaborate with us.
Minister of Political Affairs Kim Soon Jo can be trusted.
Send him a secret letter
and tell him to create a ledger documenting Wang Yoo's transactions with Ilkhanate.
You mean, a fake ledger?
But Wang Yoo definitely did this.
Since we have no evidence, we have no choice but to create it.
If we provide that ledger with our petition to have Wang Yoo dethroned,
it should be enough evidence.
I think His Majesty should find out about this through a petition.
Yes, Prime Minister.
Why didn't you tell him that Wang Yoo probably colluded with Chief Imperial Consort Ki?
Because that's not something I should only say. We need to catch them in the act.
Do you have a plan?
I, Kim Soon Jo, Minister of Political Affairs of Goryeo,
am writing to inform the Emperor of the Great Kingdom of Yuan.
Wang Yoo, King of Goryeo has been selling military supplies
such as sulfur, saltpeter, steel and tin to an enemy state of Yuan and reaped enormous profits.
Not only that, he used that money to build up his military
and plans to take Liaodong Peninsula currently under Yuan rule.
This is treason by which he betrayed the trust of a great kingdom.
So faithful Goryeo vassals are requesting his dethronement.
We ask His Imperial Majesty the Emperor to hear us.
Chief Imperial Consort, have you heard the news?
The Goryeo king committed treason against Yuan.
Tonight, a petition will be submitted to the emperor by vassals of Goryeo.
But how do you know about this?
He is someone who caused my mother to die.
So, of course, I am interested in him.
Prince, you can stop. Come along, now.
You did very well, Prince.
Will Chief Imperial Consort really try to intercept this petition?
If she colluded with Wang Yoo, she won't just stand by and watch.
She will do whatever she can to try and stop this.
Then can Chief Imperial Consort also be punished for treason?
We must make it so.
Yes, that will happen.
Is that the truth?
Yes, Prime Minister. The chief gatekeeper gave the petition to Eunuch Park Bul Hwa.
More than half of the Imperial Guards are on the Chief Imperial Consort's side.
It shouldn't be hard for them to intercept a document.
And Chief Imperial Consort intercepted the petition in order to inform Wang Yoo about it.
Begin monitoring her immediately. She will make her move tonight.
You be in charge. If Chief Imperial Consort meets with any of Wang Yoo's people,
you must capture all of them at once.
Yes, Uncle.
Jadan and Mujin,
follow me.
Yes, Sir.
As I expected, it is certain that Chief Imperial Consort helped Wang Yoo to commit treason.
If this is true, there is no way she can escape execution by beheading.
Execution by beheading won't be enough.
We should use this chance to find all the Goryeo people in this palace who were planted by Chief Imperial Consort
and slaughter them all.
This isn't the time to just sit idle.
We must let the emperor know what is going on.
Yes, Empress Dowager.
What is written on there?
Didn't he agree to sell sulfur and saltpeter to Yuan?
But this says that he sold them to the enemy state.
What was the King of Goryeo thinking?
This is different from the list I gave to Eunuch Bang.
So it's a fake ledger?
I think they are plotting something against us.
In any case, if the King of Goryeo is captured, you will be in danger as well.
Have you let Eunuch Bang know?
Yes, Your Highness. They are probably waiting for us now.
Prepare for us to travel incognito.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
It looks like she will really leave the palace.
You must follow them without getting discovered.
What? Chief Imperial Consort betrayed us?
That cannot be true.
You two must be mistaken.
Chief Imperial Consort took the petition and ledger we received from Goryeo.
And she will get rid of those and send a secret letter to Wang Yoo.
If that is not evidence of her betrayal, what is it?
Another of Wang Yoo's secret letters sent to Chief Imperial Consort.
This isn't something you should just pretend not to know about.
How about asking Chief Imperial Consort about it and find out the whole story—
Burn it up.
You won't even read them now?
I told you to burn it and make it disappear.
Your Majesty.
I know it's a trick by those trying to drive me apart from Chief Imperial Consort.
Please wake up already.
How long will you let Chief Imperial Consort play her tricks on you?
Your Majesty, if Chief Imperial Consort really colluded with Wang Yoo,
even if it hurts like cutting your heart out, you will have to behead her.
Please stop.
Stop.
It's for our kingdom's sake. Be strong, please.
I asked you to stop.
Your Majesty, Chief Imperial Consort has arrived.
Chief Imperial Consort? What brings you here so late at night?
This came from Goryeo.
The content was very urgent, so I brought them to you myself.
Head Eunuch.
Thanks to you, we avoided a crisis.
Don't be mistaken.
I was not helping Chief Imperial Consort.
I am only trying to save the Goryeo people in this palace.
What's wrong, Head Eunuch?
You should know better why I'm doing this.
If Chief Imperial Consort was doing something so dangerous, you should have stopped her.
What she is doing now is for the sake of the Goryeo people in Yuan.
Do you think you can fight and win against them, in this palace?
That is a mistake. You have no chance of winning.
I think Her Highness's actions are correct.
Shut up. I helped you this time,
but if something like this happens again,
then I will report it myself.
Head Eunuch, aren't you from Goryeo as well?
Not at all. When Goryeo abandoned me, I abandoned Goryeo.
Then, are you a Yuan person?
You're not a Goryeo person, and you are not a Yuan person. Then what are you?
I am nothing.
I don't belong here nor there. Someone without a county.
That is why my life is even more important to me.
A life that is not protected by any nation,
it is a pitiful life.
After you've spent half your life here like I did, you will see what I mean.
[Emperor of Yuan Dynasty]
Hurry and capture Wang Yoo right now.
If Wang Yoo refuses his dethronement, things can get complicated.
I think it will be better to send an envoy and request his return to Yuan.
I've just put the imperial seal on the order to dethrone Wang Yoo.
Someone like Wang Yoo dares to disobey my imperial command?
I know his nature well.
If I had my way, I would set all of Goryeo ablaze. But now isn't a good time.
Send Lord Jang.
Yes, Your Majesty, I will do that.
Are you monitoring Chief Imperial Consort well?
Not only Heungdoek Palace,
but also the merchant association supplying the palace, I've forbidden them all from entering.
Chief Imperial Consort has more people on her side than I thought.
She must not be allowed to contact them.
I understand.
I saw the petition and the ledger sent from Goryeo.
It could have been fabricated by vassals who are hostile to Wang Yoo.
We can find out the truth when Wang Yoo is dragged here.
You are doing things out of order.
How can you dethrone a nation's ruler without even verifying the truth?
It's possible that more people are involved with Wang Yoo's treason than we know.
Whether that's just a few, or if I have to kill every vassal in the Imperial Court,
I must root out those who betrayed me and this Great Kingdom.
I really hope that you are not suspected needlessly, Yang.
So please just stand by and watch.
Please find a way to let Eunuch Bang and Yeon Bisoo know what is going on.
It's dangerous right now.
If the King of Goryeo is dragged here, it won't end with his dethronement.
We have to prevent disaster, don't we?
Your Highness, you are in danger as well. You must be careful.
Imperial Prince, you will go to Goryeo?
I want to bring the one who caused my mother's death to Yuan myself.
That is very far away. How can you think of—
Please grant him permission, Your Highness.
We have to lure Wang Yoo here, somehow.
If Imperial Prince accompanies us, we may avoid suspicion.
Please grant me permission, Empress Dowager.
I am no longer a child.
If that's what you really want, you may go.
I will try speaking to His Majesty for you.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Once you bring Wang Yoo and cross our nation's border,
your maternal uncle will be there to greet you.
My maternal uncle?
Yes.
General Tanqishi is still alive.
That boy is Star, who Seung Nyang gave birth to?
No, no, I mean, that boy is Maha?
He looks so mature. How he has grown.
Even seeing him from away, he looks just like His Majesty.
I better go to Goryeo after all.
Things are so busy here. Why go to Goryeo?
Since Maha intends to meet His Majesty, I am too worried.
You two, please take care of things here.
If anything happens, contact me right away.
All right, then go on.
I have something to report to you.
The King of Goryeo—
He said he already knows.
That Leader of Hawk House.
I think he does really hold a high office in the palace.
It was the hand of a woman.
A woman with a high rank in the palace...
Isn't it Empress Dowager or the empress?
We have to first find out why they are helping us.
Only then can we make use of them towards my revenge.
In any case, if things go too well, Wang Yoo and that Ki bitch,
we may get rid of both at once.
Where are you going?
I was going to meet with you, Teacher.
Teacher, you said you would keep watch over
how the secret fund was used.
Last year and the year before, you spent it to feed the people starving from famine.
Not to mention, you also used it to bring a few government and military officials to your side.
So you did know about all of it.
Now my life depends on you, Teacher.
Did you do something I don't know about which benefits the enemy?
I absolutely did not.
The famine is bad this year. Please provide more grain for the people.
I hope you won't stand by and watch anymore.
So that I can do something properly for this kingdom, please help me, Teacher.
If it involves sparing Goryeo, I must refuse.
The money that is saving the people of Yuan is coming out of Goryeo.
El Temür's secret fund is already depleted.
Please help me, Teacher.
Did you enjoy the mountains and streams of Goryeo on your way here?
I never want to return here to my enemy's land.
Prince Maha? That young boy is on his way here?
Yes, Your Majesty. He is coming along with the envoys.
There is no reason for that boy to come here.
I am curious about that, too.
I, Kim Soon Jo, Minister of Political Affairs, greet Your Highness.
We greet Your Highness the Imperial Prince.
Why won't the King of Goryeo come to greet the Imperial Prince himself?
He is waiting inside the Great Hall, please come in.
Please put a chair here.
Your Highness the Imperial Prince, why a chair?
If the King of Goryeo won't come out, I will not move a step from here.
What?
He wants me to go and greet him?
He seems like he won't budge.
Then I better test his stubbornness.
Is he disrespecting the Imperial Prince because he is young?
How can he be so impudent?
Your Majesty, his stubbornness is extraordinary.
It will get dark soon.
Please go greet him.
He's become quite bold.
You've come a very long way.
Please come in.
"Hear this, King of Goryeo.
Although you've received the favor of the emperor and were restored to your throne,
you've ejected your loyal subjects who've maintained a good relationship with the Great Kingdom of Yuan.
And it wasn't enough to stop sending tributes of concubines, eunuchs, and goods,
you've made this your official policy.
It would be fitting for me to send my military to punish Goryeo.
But thinking about our past friendship, I am giving you a chance to respond to a royal summons.
So the King of Goryeo will come to see me
and apologize for your disloyalty and bow your head."
So you're telling me to go to Yeongyeong?
That is His Majesty's Imperial Command.
Your Majesty, how about visiting Yeongyeong before the hostility grows deeper?
I am an imperial prince of a great kingdom.
How can you look at me with such an impertinent gaze?
When you were young,
I held you in my arms often.
Do you remember that?
Why did he come here with the envoys?
His Highness—
I came to see my mother's mortal enemy's face.
Your mother's death is regrettable, but without even finding out the reason
and passing judgment. That is not a proper attitude.
Don't think about lecturing me.
I will go to Yuan tomorrow, so have him rest comfortably tonight.
You should fear the day I become the emperor.
I won't leave Goryeo alone, the land of my enemy.
Someone who cannot control his heart does not have the right to vengeance.
You have much to learn.
What he just said, what does it mean?
What does he mean, I should look near me?
Don't pay any attention, Your Highness.
He's still young. He cannot be reasonable.
Don't pay any attention, Your Majesty.
That boy's twisted character
feels regrettable to me, somehow.
Wang Yoo...
Wang Yoo!
Chief Yeon, are you sleeping? Yeon Bisoo?
Come in.
I heard news from the palace.
The emperor dethroned Our Majesty the King.
What does that mean?
The emperor already wrote the order of dethronement
and he is tricking Our Majesty the King to come here.
We must let His Majesty know.
He probably already crossed the border into Yuan.
What do we do?
Starting here, it's Yuan land.
We should stay here tonight.
That sounds good.
Seeing how he ordered you to come all the way to Yeongyeong,
the emperor's interrogation will be tough.
I've already prepared for that, so don't worry.
It's very late, you should sleep.
Is Maha already sleeping?
He's still very young, so he's probably tired from the trip.
He is a very bold child.
Why are you so concerned about him?
The more I look at him, the more I feel sad and sorry for him.
He has a grudge against you.
Don't give him too much affection, please.
It's been a while, Lord Jang.
Since Imperial Prince desires this so much, I will allow it, this one time.
I will go with him only as far as the capital, so don't worry.
Hurry and go on in.
Your Highness the Imperial Prince.
My uncle.
Yes, I am your maternal uncle.
Your mother...
was my sister.
Where have you been all this time?
I'm sorry.
It's because I failed her.
That is why I couldn't protect your mother.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
Uncle.
Maha...
Maha.
Wang Yoo has gone to sleep.
Your Highness the Imperial Prince, watch me.
See how your uncle takes revenge on Wang Yoo.
What is your business?
Tanqishi.
Put down your swords.
Your Majesty.
Imperial Prince, what do you think you are doing?
Read the edict for dethronement.
- Dethronement?
- Why is His Majesty being dethroned?
Wang Yoo, the King of Goryeo, sold military goods to Ilkhanate who was at war with Yuan
and caused Yuan's defeat, which is high treason.
He used that money to aim a sword at Yuan and planned an insurrection.
So for his crimes of aiding the enemy and for insurrection, I order his dethronement.
- Your Majesty.
- Your Majesty...
- These are not the truth.
- Shut your mouth!
From this moment, Wang Yoo is a traitor, so no manners will be observed.
- Your Majesty.
Walk faster! Walk faster!
- Walk faster!
- Your Majesty!
- Walk faster.
- Your Majesty...
Faster...
Wang Yoo, the road to Yeongyeong
will be worse for you than the road to hell.
- Your Majesty!
- Your Majesty! Please stop! Please stop!
- Your Majesty.
- Please stop!
You killed my father and my sister and brother.
I will kill you with my own hands. You and Lady Ki! Both of you!
Your Majesty!
- Your Majesty.
- Your Majesty...
Stop! Stop!
- Please come to your senses!
- Ugh! Wang Yoo!
Your Highness the Imperial Prince.
Please tell them to stop. You cannot do this.
You cannot do this to His Majesty, you will receive divine punishment.
Your Highness the Imperial Prince. Your Highness!
Your Highness the Imperial Prince!
They conspired against our kingdom!
Wang Yoo is the reason we lost the war!
Kill him!
Kill Wang Yoo's spy Chief Imperial Consort Ki, too!
They're all on the same team!
Kill Chief Imperial Consort Ki!
Kill them!
You must come to your senses.
Just endure it for a little while longer, Your Majesty.
Those bastards. How can they do that to His Majesty?
What must we do? What must we do? Shouldn't we try to rescue them?
♫ To the day I said I loved you with tears welling up ♫
♫ To the day we were happy ♫
♫ I can't return ♫
♫ Even if I'm ache and it were my last second ♫