He's welcoming you.
Classic Chinese hospitality.
Is this gold?
Of course.
This temple was originally built during
the Yongjia era of the Western Jin dynasty
and later renovated during the Tang,
Liao, and Jin dynasties.
I like it.
This is for you.
Only one?
All of them, of course.
Fools.
Go!
Filthy beggars.
Back to the palace!
I had convinced the consuls
of Britain, America,
Germany, France, Russia, Italy, Japan,
and Austria-Hungary
to cease further involvement
in the Boxer Rebellion.
Empress Dowager, rest assured.
Very well.
The rebels of the Revive China Society,
Sun Yat-sen and Zheng Shiliang,
having failed in the Guangzhou affair
are now hiding in America,
assembling firearms
for a larger rebellion.
Internal stability must come
before dealing with external threats.
I believe we must take
the initiative and capture
both Sun Yat-sen and Zheng Shiliang.
I have one person in mind for the job,
Fei Yanggu,
the Captain of the Imperial Guards.
He is well-versed
in both literature and combat.
He has a dignified bearing
and immaculate appearance.
He's a master at throwing daggers
and fluent in English.
He's waiting outside.
- Summon him.
- Summon him!
Your humble servant, Fei Yanggu,
bows before Your Majesty.
Travel to America
and bring back those traitors.
Eliminate those pests
and you will help ensure
the lasting prosperity of the Great Qing.
Yes, Your Majesty.
CHINATOWN FIGHTS AGAINST
THE ANTI-CHINESE EXCLUSION BILL
What is a genius?
A natural talent.
By five, I had mastered music,
chess, calligraphy, and painting,
read all the classics, and could easily
recite Tang and Song poetry.
At seven, I studied medicine,
the family trade.
By nine, I treated patients.
People called me a prodigy.
At 11, Lord Yung Wing sent me to America
as one of the first Chinese students
to help revive China
because of my remarkable talents.
So, Mr. Prodigy…
Genius.
Mr. Genius.
How exactly did my father die?
I have to think about it.
- The pills!
- The pills？
The victim died from heavy drinking
combined with a large dose
of chloral hydrate,
which caused respiratory failure.
Who's responsible for his meal?
- He is.
He's the murderer.
Isn't that a bit hasty？
What a luxury room.
There's an ice box.
You knew the victim's habits,
so you laced the ice with chloral hydrate.
Whiskey on rock,
a nail in the coffin.
There's still some melted ice water.
Let's test it.
Tie him up!
Money!
Easy-peasy.
It's me.
What are you babbling about,
you banana man?
I am Sherlock Holmes.
You?
Last name, Qin. Given name, Fu.
Courtesy name, Olmes.
Fu-Olmes sounds like Holmes.
- I thought it would be a white man.
- I am. Can't you tell?
Is he?
Whatever. Take his words then.
Mr. Detective, this way, please. Come on!
- So this is San Francisco!
- Yes.
What's the case?
"Jack the Ripper"?
Wasn't he in England?
How did he end up in America?
Shut up.
- Run!
- Who is Bai?
Run!
- Big commotion in San Francisco, isn't it?
- Haven't you read the papers lately?
- It's shocking news in America.
- I just got here.
Jack the Ripper vanished over
a decade ago! Since when is he Chinese?
Three days ago, two Chinese people
wandering behind the theater
found two bodies.
A white girl named Alice and an old
Native American man called Six-Hands.
The woman was cut open.
Her organs were removed.
The old man's throat was slit,
blood sprayed across the ground.
The next morning,
the San Francisco Times received a letter.
It was from Jack the Ripper.
There's only one line.
"Very delicious…
Are you ready, girls?"
"Very delicious"? What does that mean?
The worst part is,
Alice's father's a Republican senator.
- Grant.
- He's running for mayor.
The white community won't let this slide.
And Six-Hands is
the chief of the Navajo tribe.
The Natives will not let this go either.
It's getting more chaotic
out there lately.
Our people dare not leave Chinatown.
Even Chinatown might soon be in danger.
What should we do?
Who exactly is this Jack the Ripper?
Hip Sing Tong. Ring a bell?
Who does not know
the biggest Chinese gang in America?
Jack… Bai…
Are you saying it's Bai Xuanling,
the boss of HST?
It's his son, Bai Zhenbang.
How sick are gangsters nowadays?
As if gambling, drugs, pimping,
looting, and kidnapping weren't enough.
Are they into cannibalism now?
So embarrassing.
All right, enough about them.
- Let's talk about our case.
- We just did.
Did what?
We've told you everything.
Our boss will tell you the rest.
Father!
Father.
- Why did you burn him?
- He was starting to stink.
No, I don't believe Father is dead.
He's gone.
And…
stinks too.
I will avenge him!
Ghost.
Go ask Pearl. Go on.
Pearl,
who killed Father?
Go where the Easterners gather.
The first person you bumped into
will answer you.
Use the gift granted
by the Kachina
to find the justice you seek.
HIP SING TONG
Here in America,
Buddha, General Guan, and Jesus all work.
You…
must be Detective Fu, right?
Such a majestic young hero.
I am Bai Xuanling. You can call me Louis.
Master Bai,
nice to finally meet you.
I've heard so much about you.
Coming to America alone, empty-handed,
building an empire in 40 years,
helping all Chinese in America
through Hip Sing Tong.
You're truly our hero.
Every Chinese knows your name.
Brother, you're too kind.
You don't mind if
I call you "Brother," right?
Big Brother.
What you said wasn't entirely accurate.
I didn't come alone.
In the third year of Xianfeng, 1854,
I set off
with seven fellow villagers from Siyi.
We traveled from Guangzhou to Hong Kong,
then went on a ferry ride for three months
before we reached San Francisco,
the Gold Mountain.
Two of us died of illness on the way.
This is a photo taken
by a British journalist back then.
- Which one is you?
- I'm not in this picture.
I hung up these photos
as a constant reminder to myself.
So I'll never forget where I came from.
Later, I opened a restaurant,
then a laundry,
a pawnshop, and finally, a factory.
I kept going against all odds.
Even against the Americans, Italians,
and Irish.
I made it to where I am today.
Out of seven, I was the survivor.
My success was built on two things.
Versatility and righteousness.
Amitabha
and hallelujah.
I've learned a lot from your words.
If you don't mind,
please take me as your disciple.
From just a brother to a disciple?
You're being too much.
Not at all.
Once a teacher, always a father.
From now on, you're my godfather.
Godfather.
Hey! You!
All right!
Fine, godson.
I accept you.
Shall we talk about your godbrother then?
So,
why do they think
my brother is the killer?
Three nights ago, on August 10th,
at the Chinese Grand Theater,
it was Ching Ling Foo's premiere
in San Francisco.
Soon after the show began,
Zhenbang suddenly rose to leave.
Hey, Zhenbang. You're leaving?
What's so great about those tricks?
That's amazing.
Bravo!
Alice and Six-Hands were killed that night
in the alley behind the theater.
Someone called the police,
claiming that they saw
Zhenbang there at that time.
Where was he going?
After leaving the theater,
where did he go?
No one knows.
Until the morning of the 11th,
when the police arrested him at the port.
After Zhenbang was taken to the station,
he didn't say a word.
He has a record of harassment?
Alice's family servant reported
the harassment.
That's slander!
Grant even came
to confront the master about it.
Shameless!
And he studied anatomy?
It's just a hobby!
It's just a coincidence.
Godfather, I may be a detective,
but I'm still green.
I'm far from qualified to solve this case.
Perhaps you should find someone else,
lest it delay the investigation.
Detective Fu, you solved
countless crimes in England.
How could you be "green"?
I'm working on bailing Zhenbang out
so he can meet you in person.
His life is in your hands now.
Zhenbang
is my only son.
Godfather,
to tell you the truth,
I'm actually here on a secret mission.
Fei Yanggu, an imperial official
from the Qing, will arrive
at the dock this afternoon.
He's been ordered
to capture some dangerous fugitives.
It's the order from the Empress Dowager.
Grant, the Republican senator,
has formally proposed a bill,
citing his daughter's tragic death,
to ban all Chinatowns in California.
In four days, I'll represent
the Chinese Chamber of Commerce
in a debate at the Council Hall.
If this bill passes in San Francisco,
they'll immediately propose it
to the federal government.
Then, Chinese people all across America
will have no place to call home.
So, this case concerns
not only the fate of the Bai family,
but also all Chinese in America.
Master…
Lao Si, ask Mr. Weyman
to come to the silk factory.
Take good care of Detective Fu.
Let him rest in the third-floor guest room
and keep an eye on him.
Sir, do we need to keep
such a low profile for this mission?
Mission confidential.
Be cautious. Strike and go.
What are they talking about?
They're welcoming us to America.
Don't send me back!
What are you doing?
Protecting our Master.
Firearms are powerful.
Do not act recklessly.
What does that mean?
- Wai Pen?
- What's Wai Pen?
Wai Pen? I think it means foreigners.
I am Fei Yanggu,
of the Yellow Banner under the Great Qing.
- He's telling us to kneel?
- Insolent!
I, Fei Yanggu,
only kneel before the Emperor
and the Empress Dowager.
Who do you think you are?
The first person you bumped into
will answer you.
This way.
Trots.
Where's the bathroom?
Over there.
Jack the Ripper, Hip Sing Tong…
Are you kidding me?
I have a better chance
of fooling that imperial official.
What? Why build the toilet so high up?
Detective Fu,
is everything going smoothly?
Detective Fu…
You…
Just a weird habit.
I can't go unless I'm undressed.
Understood.
You…
Also a weird habit.
Foul smell makes me dizzy.
I see.
Help!
He's trying to escape!
Please don't, sir.
Really, sir. Let me go.
Sir!
Please. Stop it.
Sir. Please, sir.
You bumped into me.
Chinese? You're Chinese?
- Go.
- Where?
- Take me to the killer.
- What killer?
- The one that killed Father.
- Whose father?
- Pearl said you would…
- Who the hell is Pearl?
The Kachina will protect us.
- Enough with the crazy talk.
- Where are you going?
- To get dressed.
- Take me with you!
Stop it. People look down on that!
Stop them, then we'll go for the killer.
Eyes of the Hawk!
Ears of the Wolf!
Speed of the Puma.
Useless.
Hey.
Sir.
- Go.
- By myself, please.
Strength of the Bear!
Impressive.
- What are you doing?
- Right.
- The killer is here?
- How did you find me?
I'm the hunter and you're the prey.
Put this on.
Together, let's thank Mr. Weyman.
- Congratulations.
- Louis.
I know you took them in out of kindness,
but you can only protect them
for a while, not forever.
I'll do it as long as I can.
Do you need me to help accommodate them?
No need to bother you with these.
Hold off work here before the hearing.
Can't give them any ammunition.
Understood.
- Take this.
- That was sudden.
Zhenbang's bail money is way too high.
This piece of land is
my most valuable asset.
Keep it as a mortgage.
Again, I'm counting on you
to help my family through this.
I told you. I can lend you the money.
No.
I've owed you so much all these years.
My people have owed you too much.
All right then.
I'll keep this just for now.
I'll arrange Zhenbang's bail shortly.
Right now, our priority is
to clear Zhenbang's name
and find the real killer.
Thank you.
So, this is America.
Not as fancy as I thought.
Sir, watch out.
Sir, where's the pick-up guy?
He should be here.
It's a young Chinese man called Qin Fu.
- Qin Fu.
Remember, in the West,
the given name comes first
then the family name.
So, we should call him Fu Qin.
- Fu Qin.
- Who's Fu Qin?
Fu Qin.
Are you looking for…
Fu Qin?
I am Fu Jin, yes.
And you are…
My name is Fei.
- Mr. Fei.
- Address him as Master.
Master Fei.
What are you waiting for?
Help the master with his luggage.
- Let me.
- I'll take this.
Find us the best inn in town,
then a nice meal.
The food on the ship was terrible.
No worries.
All set.
Chinese help Chinese.
Exactly.
No scamming your own kind. Let's go.
One moment, sir.
I'll go bring the ride around.
Hold on.
What ride?
Our master's not used
to those newfangled cars.
I'm driving a carriage.
One moment, sir.
- Don't wander around.
- Wait here.
"Fu Jin" will be right back
to pick you up.
Sir.
Have we
been scammed?
Why aren't you eating?
I miss my father.
Your name is Gui?
Gui as in Ghost.
All right, Gui.
So Six-Hands, the victim, was your father?
But how could an old Native man
father a Shanxi son?
I'm from Hebei.
No matter where you're from,
let me say this again.
I'm really not a detective.
I can't help you find the killer.
- But Pearl said…
- Pearl or pig,
no still means no.
Does she know me better
than I know myself?
Whatever, I'm sticking with you.
What's your problem?
Wherever you go, I'll go.
I'm going to the bathroom. Want to join?
If you can find me again,
I'll follow your command.
Sir, should we keep waiting?
Maybe a little longer.
Go back. Leave.
Indeed, this barbaric land
is full of tricks.
We must keep our eyes open
and never be fooled again.
- Come on, quick.
- Spread out and search.
Hurry.
He's not getting away.
Find him!
You're awake.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Ghost.
- We're here.
- Where?
- Home.
- Home?
This is him.
Stare at my sister again
and I'll drink from your skull.
Tell him.
What did he say?
He said if you find the killer,
his sister will marry you.
And you'll drink the wine
of matrimony tonight.
Do your people do that too?
What did he say?
Don't you want to avenge Father?
All you know is revenge.
Look at that stupid face of his.
Pearl must have made a mistake.
What is he saying?
If his sister isn't enough,
you can have that piece of land too.
- Deal!
- He's fine with it.
When I was five,
I watched my parents die in front of me.
Magpies cheer
New Year's near
Father's off to earn
We hear
Father found me,
raised me,
and taught me everything.
He gave me a second life.
Magpies cheer
New Year's near
Father's off to earn
We hear
Gain he will, silver and gold
Silver and gold
To buy the land and build a home
So, you must help me find the killer.
With you as my partner,
I'm very confident.
If you try to escape again,
I'll castrate you.
It hurts my feelings that you'd say that.
In fact,
they've already found the killer.
Godfather.
I'm back.
Fu, my boy!
I thought you ran away.
Godfather, how could I?
Exactly. How could you?
I actually left to recruit him.
Six-Hands' son, Gui.
We'll solve the case together.
It's Ghost.
Gui.
Fu and Gui.
A perfect match made in heaven.
Come here.
Last night, three men wandered around
looking for "Fu Qin."
And this morning, they came to my door.
This is Fei Yanggu. Master Fei.
Master Fei. Nice finally meeting you.
I was tied up yesterday
and couldn't pick you up.
Never mind.
As soon as I arrived, I got scammed.
We had to sleep on the street.
I heard that Hip Sing Tong is
the largest Chinese society in the city,
so I came to pay my respects
to Master Bai.
Master Fei, you're too kind.
You mentioned you're here
to arrest some rebels.
Who are they exactly?
Sir, the young master is back.
As long as you are safe.
Come, let me introduce you.
I hired these two detectives for you.
Mr. Fu and Mr. Gui.
This is Master Fei Yanggu,
who just arrived in America.
This is my son, Bai Zhenbang.
And this is…
We studied together in England.
Zheng Shiliang.
Master Bai,
you just asked me
who I came here to arrest.
This must be destiny.
Arrest him!
Stop!
Be civilized.
Master Bai,
this man, Zheng Shiliang, is a fugitive
wanted by the Empress Dowager herself.
Your Empress is back in the Qing.
This is America.
I'm taking this man with me,
no matter what.
Master Fei,
at this moment, both of them
are guests of the Hip Sing Tong.
As long as I'm here,
your safety is guaranteed.
Once you leave this room,
whatever you do is none of my business.
But here and now,
no one is taking him away.
Master Bai made his point.
Zheng Shiliang,
count your blessings.
You won't be this lucky forever.
Sheathe your swords.
What a day!
Wen, Wu, serve Master Fei some more.
- Yes, sir.
- That won't be necessary.
We're leaving.
Fu, Gui.
Tell them exactly what you did
on the night of the 10th?
You boys have a good talk.
I'll be right back.
Hey.
Where did you go
after leaving the theater that night?
How can we help you if you don't tell us?
Say something.
Tell us.
Please.
Why don't you tell us?
What are you doing? Didn't we agree to
only take action when it's necessary?
What more is there to say?
He doesn't even dare to say where he went.
- He must be the killer.
- Be patient. Give him more time.
No. I'll avenge Father right now.
What's the motive?
Why would he kill your father?
Don't you want to know?
Was he into money or Native men?
Come on, speak up, man.
Young Master, tell them.
Young Master, tell them!
- Please.
- Tell us.
- Are you going to talk or not?
- Tell them.
- Tell me.
- Tell them!
- Speak up.
- Will you talk or not?
All right!
Shiliang.
Nothing is more important
than clearing your name right now.
Shiliang, don't.
Zhenbang, I have to say it.
It's killing me inside.
- Shiliang.
- Zhenbang.
You two!
Did you go on a date?
Guns.
Marston said you two stole his guns.
That's right.
On the night of the 10th,
Zhenbang and I, we…
went to steal guns from the Irish.
You got something else to do?
No.
This is Zheng Shiliang.
We went to medical school
in England together.
He's joined Dr. Sun's
Revive China Society.
Guns can be bought,
why steal them?
The revolution is imminent.
Desperate times call
for desperate measures.
They stole from us all the time anyway.
The Irish gathered these weapons
for their next raid on Chinatown.
So you had no time to kill Father.
Of course not.
My people can vouch for him.
No wonder you kept silent
at the police station.
Turns out you were stealing guns.
I knew my brother was innocent.
Godfather, we did good, didn't we?
Gui, put your knife away.
Then why were you at the port so early?
You weren't trying to escape.
He was simply scared
after stealing the guns.
So, he was going to lay low out of town.
Right?
Just believing you is not enough.
All Americans need to be persuaded.
For now, we need to find the killer first.
Yes. Let's go find him.
Godfather,
- I have another request.
- Tell me.
I've just acquired land
in Native territory and taken a wife,
but I still don't have
American citizenship.
Do you really want to stay for good?
I have a property and a family now.
All right, I'll help you.
Thank you, Godfather.
One's a fraud,
while the other's a savage.
And you ask them to solve the case?
At this point,
is there anyone else
who would take on your case?
Qin Fu is quite observant
and quick-thinking.
He's definitely a man of talent.
As for Gui, with his animal instincts,
and skills in combat and tracking,
is no average Joe either.
The two of them came along
at the right time just to save you.
Right now, both of you are
wanted criminals out there.
Stay put.
Stay. At least until it's safe.
The great Master Bai
can only protect me for a while?
If I fail the hearing,
which is in four days,
I won't just fail to protect you,
but Hip Sing Tong and Chinatown too.
I fear that all Chinese in America
won't be safe, either.
We were never safe here, to begin with.
We shouldn't place our hope here.
No more talk of revolution!
If it could truly change things,
we wouldn't have to cross the ocean
to make a living in a foreign land.
I've fought my whole life to earn respect,
hoping we'd no longer be bullied
by the whites.
That's the Chinatown you've protected
for decades.
It's still filled with brothels,
opium dens, and casinos.
Have our people led better lives here?
If our hope isn't back home or here,
then where is it?
Gentlemen.
Your hope
feels too far away for me.
My only hope now…
is for you to be okay.
Where to?
Yeah, where to?
You're asking me?
I got it. Follow me.
A doctor of Chinese medicine
does four things.
"Wàng," observe the patient.
"Wén," listen to the breathing.
"Wèn," ask about symptoms.
And "qiè," feel the pulse.
Crime investigation is not that different.
Let's start with…
"WÀNG," OBSERVE
What do you have here?
Footprints of my father.
How do you know?
He doesn't wear shoes.
Judging by the bloodstains,
someone cut your father's throat.
His name is Six-Hands.
Once, he chopped off six enemies' hands
and wore them around his neck.
Did your father not carry a knife
at that time?
Someone must've ambushed him from behind.
These footprints…
That's strange.
Two people died,
yet only my father's blood was found.
How do you know?
Can't you smell the difference
between a man's blood and a woman's?
Can you?
You don't even have common sense.
So, Alice didn't die here.
There are no women's footprints here.
Only a fat man's.
- How fat?
- Thrice your size.
Carriage.
You don't need to eat shit
to prove that, do you?
City horse.
What's special about the dung
of a city horse?
City horses are fed beans. Ours eat grass.
So it wasn't a fat man.
Someone left Alice here from a carriage.
And your father just happened to pass by.
The killer wasn't alone.
Our land was taken from us.
Father would come here at night
to trade furs.
Maybe…
he was finding a mother for you.
"WÉN," LISTEN
What are you doing?
- Guess this country needs an FBI.
- Isn't sniffing part of wén?
In Chinese medicine,
it means to listen, not to smell.
As in listening to the dead.
Examine the body, do an autopsy.
You know what autopsy means, right?
How do I explain it to a Native?
Autopsy means…
Fractured joint at the funny bone.
Bruise on the tushy bone. Rack scraped.
Back of the head cracked. Neck snapped.
This is the fatal wound.
Hang on, wait a second.
What are "funny bone,"
"tushy," and "rack"?
Is that Native slang?
It's authentic Chinese.
You mean Hebei dialect.
You banana man.
- How can you do an autopsy?
- Father taught me.
Animals first, then people.
Impressive.
Multiple external injuries
suggest severe violence before death.
She fought back too.
No, she scratched.
Why can't I see it?
Because it's not visible to human eyes.
Only the Hawk's.
So the killer must have
scratch marks on him.
Gui, impressive.
The stomach is empty.
But why would the killer
remove all her intestines?
The estimated time of death
is between 6 to 10 p.m. on August 10th,
the same time your father was killed.
So the guy killed Alice nearby,
moved her and disemboweled her.
What was the purpose?
There have been rumors
that Jack the Ripper was a doctor
because the victims' wounds were
as clean as surgical cuts.
This person struck without hesitation.
He must be a butcher or hunter,
if not a doctor.
Didn't I tell you not to sniff around?
Just now, I smelled
a strange scent right here.
Look.
Wood shavings.
Why are there wood shavings?
A stick. She was beaten to death with it.
I see you've got the nose of a pig too.
This isn't an ordinary murder.
It's a crime driven by deep hatred.
Time to ask the question, "Who?"
Whoever knew her the best.
"WÈN," ASK
Nothing valuable.
Since asking fails,
it's time to feel the pulse!
Feel the pulse? How?
It's too early for that.
We'll just do it later.
Let's go, before Grant comes home.
Once you're in, open the door for me.
Didn't we say "feel"?
Since when did it turn into "steal"?
Clearly, your Chinese is terrible.
It's better than yours, you banana man.
You savage. Ever heard of homophones?
Qiè can mean both feel and steal.
- So handy.
- Screw you.
FEEL
STEAL
Come on. Get your ass out here
and do it yourself.
Where's Alice's room?
How should I know?
Use your pig nose to find it.
Wherever it smells nicest.
Second floor.
What is it about this photo that
makes you so emotional? I don't get it.
- Can I take it?
- No.
- Why not?
- Don't even think about it.
- But you said qiè also means steal.
- It doesn't mean you can take things.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
I have something important
to ask Bai Zhenbang.
Young Master.
Master.
Young Master left with Mr. Zheng.
No idea where.
San Francisco isn't that big.
Just tell the boys
to bring them back safely.
Yes, sir.
If anything happens to Zhenbang,
we'll never be able to overturn the case.
Is there anything you can do?
Damn!
Is this real? Do you have psychic powers?
Last time, you used bamboo acupuncture
to block pain and boost strength,
and chewed coca leaves
to stimulate your nerves.
Chinese medicine can explain all that,
but not this.
Come with me.
The Chinese Grand Theater?
Is Bai Zhenbang still in the mood
for a magic show?
We'll ask around and find out.
Ask who?
Him.
- We're looking for Ching Ling Foo.
- Sorry. Mr. Ching is about to go on stage.
He won't be meeting fans.
Do we look like fans?
Yes, you do.
You can't go in.
Sorry, Mr. Ching.
I couldn't stop these crazy fans of yours.
I understand.
After all, I am the great Ching Ling Foo.
Have you heard the song
the Americans made for me?
And I will have a Ching Ling Foo
Going…
You're a good singer, but please stop.
- Where is he?
- Who?
- There are three cups.
- Have a drink.
And three chairs.
Sit and drink then.
So, what do you want? An autograph?
We are detectives
hired by Master Bai Xuanling.
Mr. Bai and Mr. Weyman
are my loyal fans and magic experts.
So, where would you like me to sign?
Chest?
We're here to see Bai Zhenbang.
He's not here.
I can make anyone appear out of thin air,
except Bai Zhenbang.
I just heard him. He's here.
- No, he's not.
- He's here.
My friend!
You must be delusional.
We're often deceived by our own senses.
Whatever you think you see or hear…
isn't necessarily real.
The same goes for your words.
In fact…
they're more likely to be fake.
Isn't that right, Mr. Magician?
I'm about to go on stage. Be my guest.
Bai Zhenbang, we're not here for you.
We are.
Who are you?
Get out of here now!
None of your business!
Zheng Shiliang.
No one can protect you today.
We'll protect him.
Stab yourself.
- Use the sticks and transform.
- I can't.
Why not? Use Strength of the Bear now!
I can only use it once every two days.
There are four of us
and only three of you.
Get them.
Even four against three isn't enough?
No.
- How about four against one then?
Which one of you
wants to die first?
Come out.
Smile, just smile. Wave.
Now, get your ass back in there.
What the hell? Shut the door.
One.
Two.
Three!
Sir.
Go get them!
Kill them!
- So, you're a real kung fu master?
- Of course.
Can't even win four against two.
What about four against one?
No.
My leg! My…
My leg…
My…
Smile. Everybody, smile.
Say "thank you."
And bow.
Bravo!
Bravo.
You hid the guns
in the theater, didn't you?
You went to see Ching Ling Foo
to talk about moving the guns.
This is why you came to us?
Actually, we came for something else.
You and Alice, the dead girl,
were you a couple?
Why do you ask?
Observe, listen, ask, and feel.
Crime investigation is a lot
like Chinese medicine.
You look for seemingly unrelated symptoms
to find the root cause.
That day,
Zheng Shiliang hesitated to speak.
All right!
You studied in England, and so had Alice.
Maybe you two knew each other back then.
Most importantly,
you were arrested at the port
on the morning
of August 11th.
You weren't trying to escape.
You were trying to elope with Alice,
weren't you?
Apparently, I've underestimated you.
Looks like I was right.
Honestly, even I'm surprised
by my own detective talent.
Turns out I'm perfect
for this job after all.
I first met her by the River Thames.
I was eighteen.
From that moment, I knew
she'd be where my life began
and where it would end.
I despised my father
and all his criminal deeds.
I planned to settle in England for good.
I returned to San Francisco
only for her.
That's when
we truly got to know each other.
The Chinese Exclusion Act stated
that Chinese men cannot marry white women.
We were in love,
but it was us against the world.
We could only meet in secret.
Revealing your relationship
could've cleared your name.
Why didn't you say anything?
Alice is already dead.
I don't want her name tarnished
after her death.
A true romantic.
But you can't be known as
the Chinese Jack the Ripper, can you?
You've finally got to the point.
This case is the biggest story
in America right now.
They want to make
the Chinese Exclusion Act permanent,
so they need a reason
to convince the public.
Brother, why don't you tell us
what happened that night?
On the afternoon of the 8th,
I got a letter from Alice,
delivered by her maid, Amanda.
We planned to steal
the guns from the Irish block
on the night of the 10th.
After delivering the guns to the theater,
I went home to pack
and made it to the port before 6 a.m.
But instead of Alice,
the police showed up.
I understand now.
Go find Amanda.
She knows everything about me and Alice.
And she should know
who the real killer is.
- Where are you going?
- The revolution's underway
and those guns are crucial.
From now on, either love or death
must make way for it.
Shiliang and I will move the guns first.
You were born and raised here in America,
and you've never even been to China.
Why do you care so much
about the revolution?
I've never been to China.
Never even braided my hair.
And still, they call me "pig-tail."
Alice and I truly love each other,
but we can't be seen together
in broad daylight.
The world is full of questions
I have no answer to.
After meeting Shiliang, I realized
the Chinese are always protected
by their own.
They knowingly pursue the impossible.
They are the true hope of China.
Maybe they hold the answers
I've been searching for.
You're doing something great.
I admire that.
Great or not,
we all have a purpose in life.
I truly hope you two
can clear Zhenbang's name.
We can help you tomorrow too.
But right now, Zhenbang's case is
just as important.
We appreciate your kindness.
Qin Fu, Gui,
please find the person who killed Alice.
Rest assured, Brother.
Just call me Zhenbang.
Please don't call me "Brother."
It creeps me out.
All right, Brother Zhenbang.
Who here can speak Chinese?
Anyone?
Get out, Chinaman.
As long as there's a translator.
I am from the Yellow Banner
of the Great Qing,
Captain of the Imperial Guards,
First Assistant and Deputy
of the Intelligence Department,
Head of the Secret Escort,
Recipient of the Yellow Jacket,
member of the Niohuru Clan,
Fei Yanggu.
Translate that.
So?
So,
we can work together
to catch the rebels.
You take the guns.
I take the people.
I know where you can find the guns.
Eh, wait. You… My…
CHINESE AND DOGS ARE NOT ALLOWED TO ENTER
CHINESE ARE ALLOWED TO ENTER
Which is faster?
A dagger or a gun?
At this distance,
I'm faster.
Sir, you really held yourself together
back there.
Much respect.
- Sir.
- Help me.
Don't let the Americans see.
I'm about to pee myself.
Zhenbang has something important
to do tomorrow.
I know. The guns.
We'd like to check out the crime scene.
Go ahead.
I'll call Mr. Weyman.
Right now, he's the only one
who can help us.
Lao Si.
Get Zhenbang a ferry ticket
for tomorrow night,
and make sure he stays away for a while.
Where to?
As far as possible.
Hong Kong.
She was like me.
- She was a detective?
- She's a doctor of Chinese medicine.
Let's keep observing.
OBSERVE AGAIN
No signs of struggle.
Fresh blood.
This time, the body wasn't moved.
The attack happened right here.
She was strangled first,
then disemboweled.
LISTEN AGAIN
- Strange.
- What?
This cut isn't as clean as the last one.
The internal organs were displaced, too.
So, it wasn't the same person?
Definitely not.
All right, let's ask again.
Lin Yue'e was a good child.
She came to America with me
when she was 15.
She never even argued with anyone.
Why would anyone do something so horrible?
She had no enemies.
Did she have any friends?
What do you mean?
You should know that Bai Zhenbang's case
affects the future of Chinatown.
And the fate of all Chinese in America.
If you know anything…
Now's the time to speak
before it's too late.
And more importantly…
Don't you want justice for your daughter?
Hey.
He's a better driver than you.
Zhenbang is on the move.
- Are we heading out now?
- Let's go.
A distraction.
These amateurs…
Such an amateur move.
Amateur…
It's empty…
Gui.
Gui, please don't die.
Gui!
Gui.
My name is Ghost.
Thank Kachina
and my father, too.
Save the young master!
Dao.
- Dao.
- Young Master.
Get out of here, Young Master.
- Dao.
- Leave him with us.
We'll take it from here.
The master booked you
a ferry ticket to leave tonight.
We're taking you to the dock.
Let's go.
Mr. Lao Si, I can't go with you.
There's something I must do.
No, we have to go to the dock now.
No, I must do this.
Take him to the dock.
- Young Master.
- Young Master!
If you won't let me go,
I'll kill myself right here.
Give me the ticket.
I'll leave after I'm done.
Zhenbang, don't do this.
Give me the ticket!
Mr. Lao Si.
Tell my father that
even though I don't agree
with many things he has done,
he's always been…
a hero to me.
That has never changed.
I'm truly grateful
for the name he gave me.
It taught me
what a man
should do with his life.
Boss, everything is loaded.
Let's go.
Tell me where your operation is
and name every rebel,
and I'll spare your life.
Okay,
but on one condition.
What is it? Tell me.
Your hairstyle doesn't really
suit your face.
Cut off your braid and I'll tell you.
How dare you?
What are you trying to do?
Stop!
We don't want to start
a diplomatic incident.
I'm not dead.
I faked it.
A wise man knows when to yield.
Where's Brother Zhenbang?
He said he had something
more important to do.
He'll join me afterward.
Join you? How are you getting out?
Gui, do you have any ideas?
There is one, but it's slow.
How slow?
They're coming for us
first thing in the morning.
Don't worry.
We'll live.
We're doomed.
- Completely doomed.
- Master Fei.
We're like peas in a pod.
Why must we harm each other?
I'm nothing like you.
Look at you three.
A rebel, a savage, a banana man.
You all deserve to die.
Do you want to live?
Let him talk if you do.
Shiliang, just confess.
As long as you're alive, there's hope.
Revolution requires patience.
Let it take its course.
Live as a hero,
die a martyr.
I'll beat the "martyr" out of you.
Bury them. Do it!
Where are your powers?
Use them!
Strength of the Bear!
The pigeon said we'll live.
You believe a pigeon?
Our lives are at stake here
and you believe a pigeon?
I believe in Kachina.
And I believe in the revolution!
Oh sure, I totally believe you!
Sir!
The Eight-Nation Alliance, led by Britain
and America has invaded Peking
and occupied the Forbidden City.
Concubine Zhen was killed.
The Empress Dowager and the Emperor…
have gone missing, their fate unknown.
They say they'll loot the Forbidden City.
Now they are talking about sleeping
with the emperor's wife.
THE EIGHT-NATION ALLIANCE CAPTURED PEKING
A dagger or a gun?
Brother!
We're late.
Just in time.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
Does he speak Hebei dialect too?
He's my eagle eye.
Save China.
Detective Fu.
We have news of the young master.
Do you need us to go with you?
You'll scare people.
Just give us the horses.
Brother-in-law, take care of your sister.
I'll come for her soon.
What did he say?
That he'll find the killer soon.
We made a good team.
I misjudged you.
His sister is waiting for you.
Don't forget the land.
I will not give up.
Don't touch me.
POST OFFICE
HUA XIN RESTAURANT
FUNERAL
This is the American
residency paper you wanted.
Master Bai knew all along
that you are not Mr. Holmes.
Your real name is Qin Fu.
Your grandfather was the imperial
physician to Emperor Daoguang.
Qin Benyu, the Divine Hands.
He retired to his home village
and treated common folk for a living.
In the third year of Xianfeng,
Qian Yuan, the Lord of Jin, took Henan
and slaughtered all 11 members
of your family.
Your father was the only survivor.
I think that's why you'd rather stay here
than go back.
You're not a student sent
by the Qing government either.
The age doesn't match.
Your older brother, Qin Lin, is.
You came to America years ago
to look for him,
who is the only family you have left.
Am I right?
Take this residency paper and go find him.
What does this mean?
No more investigation?
And you? You're giving up too?
This time tomorrow,
Lance will announce the case as closed
at City Hall Square.
What more can we do?
My parents died in an explosion
building railways for white people.
I was young. I had to let it go.
Later, the Native American tribe
that raised me was driven away,
forced to leave their ancestors' lands.
Father told me not to resist.
I had to let it go.
Now Father was killed,
and Zhenbang was falsely accused.
Are we supposed to let it go again?
Plus, with so many loose ends,
we all know Zhenbang can't be the killer.
Yet in the end, even we are
giving up the investigation.
Then history will forever remember
a Chinese Jack the Ripper.
You can choose to give up, to let it go.
But this time, I won't.
I will find the real killer.
What are you doing here?
We've come to say goodbye
to Young Master Bai.
Everyone here has received help
from the Bai family to some extent.
Whether it's you,
Master Bai, or the Young Master.
Six months ago, I had a difficult labor.
The American doctors had given up on me.
If it weren't for the Young Master,
my child and I wouldn't have survived.
My wife and I run a laundry shop
outside Chinatown.
We're bullied
by the Irish gang all the time.
My wife was pushed
to the brink of suicide.
It was Young Master Bai
who stood up for us.
We don't believe he is a murderer.
We don't believe it.
- Public will.
Isn't this the will of the public?
Gui is right.
We can't let Zhenbang die for nothing.
There are still 24 hours
before the case closes.
We still have a chance.
Gui, let's go.
Take me with you.
Aren't you supposed to be
on a ship tonight?
Yes. The magician is waiting for you.
I want to stay
and fight with you until the end.
You have something more important to do.
We've got it covered here. Don't worry.
Shiliang, the greater cause
needs you more.
If all our countrymen were like you two,
China would surely become
a great nation again.
I guess this is where we part ways then.
- Take care.
From now on,
you two shall be known
as Detective Chinatown.
Observe, listen, ask, feel? Which one now?
Time is against us.
Just improvise.
These past few days, we were so focused
on Bai Zhenbang and Alice
that we overlooked an important person.
That Black maid.
You said the wounds on Amanda's body
are the same as those on Dr. Lin's.
The person who cut Alice open
is not the one who did them.
But I don't understand.
Besides a need for attention,
why would the killer copy
Jack the Ripper's pattern?
What's even stranger is,
why are there two killers?
What's this herb-brewing pot doing here?
Black people believe
in Chinese medicine too?
Mulberry mistletoe.
Nourishes the liver and kidneys,
dispels rheumatism, strengthens bones,
and stabilizes the fetus.
Baikal skullcap.
Clears heat, purges toxins,
stops bleeding, and stabilizes the fetus.
Atractylodes.
Replenishes qi, strengthens the spleen,
dispels dampness, relieves sweating,
and stabilizes the fetus.
The medicine wasn't for her.
But why would the killer
remove all her intestines?
This is the fatal wound.
Wood shavings.
Why are there wood shavings?
We're close to solving Alice's case.
Who killed Father then?
We need to do qiè one more time.
Which one are we talking about?
None of us believe
Zhenbang was the murderer.
There must be a loophole in what they saw.
Me, it's me.
You didn't leave?
I did. Almost.
I thought you had a ferry to catch.
That can wait a day.
Zhenbang's case can't wait.
Mr. Ching said
this whole thing
might just be a misdirection.
I was recreating the scene
where Zhenbang got shot in my mind.
I think maybe it was all a trick.
I wonder if he is thinking
what we are thinking.
It was rather misty here in the afternoon.
The person everyone thought was Zhenbang
wasn't him at all,
just someone dressed like him.
When he saw Lance and the others coming,
he pretended to escape.
Grant fired a shot.
Where's that gunshot sound from?
That was my whistle.
Impressive.
- So…
- Grant…
Fired a blank shot.
The fake Zhenbang pretended to be shot,
fell in the water, then was switched out,
and the real Zhenbang's body
was floated to the surface.
So,
there must be a hiding space
at the bottom of this pool.
Gui, how good a swimmer…
So hasty.
- So?
- Someone could hide in there.
And I found this.
Looks familiar.
The Irish Union pin.
Our theory is plausible,
but we're still missing direct evidence.
Right now, only one person can help us.
I studied medicine to save lives,
out of benevolence.
Later, I realized that practicing medicine
can only save individuals,
but not the world.
That's why I joined
Dr. Sun Yat-sen's revolution.
Who knew
I'd be back on my old trade again.
I studied Chinese medicine because…
Enough chitchat, let's get started.
Still so hasty.
Bai Zhenbang,
if you're watching from above,
please show us some clues.
On the night of August 10th,
two victims were killed in Chinatown.
One was Mr. Grant's daughter, Alice,
and the other was
the Native American chief, Six-Hands.
After the autopsy,
we discovered that the killer
demonstrated expertise
in the use of a scalpel.
On August 15th,
another victim popped up in Chinatown,
the female Chinese doctor, Lin Yue'e,
who was also disemboweled,
but the cut on her body was uneven,
just like Amanda's,
found at the silk factory yesterday.
From this, we can conclude
that your so-called Jack the Ripper
is actually two people.
Mr. Thomas.
We just happened to find your union badge
at the bottom of the pool.
It has the initials
of Thomas Lawrence on it.
I wonder what you were doing
in the pool at the silk factory.
Taking a bath?
Here's our second witness, Piggy.
PUNISH THE MURDERER
Depending on distance,
bullet wounds on an animal or a human
could be very different.
By looking at Bai Zhenbang's wound,
we'll know who's lying.
There are clear burn marks
on Bai Zhenbang's body.
He was shot by this gun.
But he was shot from point-blank range,
and the time of death
wasn't yesterday morning,
but the night before.
- What did you find?
- Clenched teeth, facial muscle spasms,
stiff limbs, a twisted smile.
The livor mortis appears bright red
with a blackened nose and fingertips.
Cold energy invaded,
keeping the yin energy inside
and the yang energy out.
Could it be he was…
I have a knife.
I have a bottle of vinegar.
What do you need vinegar for?
His complexion appears pale gray.
He's frozen to death.
Zhenbang would've been proud
to see we combine Chinese learning
with Western methods.
In San Francisco, there aren't
many buildings with ice cellars.
Mr. Grant,
don't you have one in your home?
You fought in the Civil War,
serving as a military doctor.
As you all know,
Mr. Grant is running for mayor.
His new policies include making
the Chinese Exclusion Act permanent,
shutting down Chinatown,
and banning any business
or individual from hiring Chinese.
These policies have won him votes,
especially the support
of the Union led by Thomas.
But what you might not know is,
his daughter Alice's boyfriend
was a Chinese man.
And that man
was none other than Bai Zhenbang.
Now, let's talk about
what everyone is eager to know,
Jack the Ripper.
The one thing that
confused us the most before was
why the killer would impersonate him,
removing the victims' intestines.
Until we went to the home
of the second victim, Lin Yue'e.
Her clinic
was where Alice and Bai Zhenbang
would meet in secret.
Don't you want justice for your daughter?
She did tell me that
she was pretty close
to Young Master Bai and Miss Alice.
But one day,
they were seen
by Mr. Grant.
And the true reason Alice was killed
was because she was pregnant
with Bai Zhenbang's child.
After discovering her pregnancy,
Alice decided to elope with Bai Zhenbang
on the morning of the 11th.
But just as she was about to leave…
You…
pushed her down the stairs to her death.
These blood-stained wood shavings
were found in Alice's hair,
and they are a perfect match for the
broken railing in Mr. Grant's home.
This is the true cause of Alice's death.
Also,
we found some human tissue
under Alice's fingernails,
from when she fought against her killer.
Mr. Grant,
I'm guessing there's a scratch
on your left hand.
You used Jack the Ripper's name
to increase public attention on this case,
then you blamed the Chinese
which earned you quite a few votes.
More importantly, it covered up the fact
that Alice was pregnant.
And Bai Zhenbang,
until his death, never knew
that Alice…
was carrying his child.
You moved Alice's body to Chinatown,
where Six-Hands who was there
to trade furs, saw you.
So, he became the second victim.
To make sure no one finds out
what you did,
you had to silence the witnesses.
The first was Lin Yue'e,
the Chinese doctor
who knew about Alice's pregnancy.
And then, the person who knew everything,
the maid, Amanda.
Bai Zhenbang.
FUNERAL
Gui, tomorrow morning, go to Grant's house
and get something for me.
What?
I know who you are.
I knew from the moment I first saw you.
Go!
What is it about this photo
that makes you so emotional?
I don't get it.
My old friend.
I have a house full of guests.
Please forgive me for not inviting you in.
No need for formalities.
I came to say goodbye.
I'm really sorry about Zhenbang.
It was all part of your plan, wasn't it?
What?
Grant could never come up with
an idea using Jack the Ripper
to frame Zhenbang.
Nor would he know so much
about the silk factory
to create a misdirection
using its environment.
It must have been someone who knows
how to manipulate public opinion
and is an expert in magic tricks.
Mr. Bai and Mr. Weyman
are my loyal fans and magic experts.
I told Lance to hand you the key evidence
not to help you,
but because I realized
that if Grant, a Republican, wins,
his policies would prohibit any business
from hiring Chinese laborers.
So, he had to be removed
to secure a win for William,
the Democrat candidate.
At the same time, you had to deal
with the mortal enemy of capital,
the union.
Only by winning the union over
can you legally employ
Chinese laborers long-term.
Louis,
you're indeed worthy of being my friend.
In fact, that day, I was going
to talk him into changing
his campaign strategy.
There must be something else.
Your silk factory…
I need that land.
But for the livelihood
of your fellow Chinese,
you would never give it up.
Now all my assets have been confiscated.
And the land is already yours.
You gave me the deed willingly.
This world operates on two rules.
Power controls everything,
or money controls power.
We are the latter.
Understood.
Old friend,
see yourself out.
We have an old saying in Chinese,
"Times change,
fortune rises and falls."
What is on top today
may be at the bottom tomorrow.
We will meet again.
SILK FACTORY
Gui, you look just like your father.
If he could see what you've become,
he would smile from beyond.
Too bad fate wasn't that kind to him.
Don't let your emotions
cloud your judgment.
There's so much
we can learn from this place.
Study your opponent's strength
before going into battle.
Godfather, I understand it now.
Fallen leaves return to their roots.
Zhenbang and I
are going back home, to Canton.
He's never been there.
Take care.
- Take care, Godfather.
- Take care, Master Bai.
Kid, sing us a song.
Kid.
Sing us a song.
Magpies cheer
New Year's near
Father's off to earn
We hear
Gain he will, silver and gold
To buy the land and build a home
Now that my godfather has left,
I have two plans in mind,
so help me choose.
Go ahead.
One, we work as a team,
Detective Chinatown.
I choose the second one.
Go back and marry the princess.
Become a prince of your tribe.
I'll go with the first then.
- Gui.
- Ghost.
What's your last name?
I forgot to ask Master Bai earlier.
From now on, your last name will be Tang.
Why Tang?
So your children will know
where you came from,
and where this Chinatown came from.
So, I'll be Ghost Tang?
It's Gui Tang.
"Fu" means fortune and "Gui" means wealth.
We wish you super-duper rich!
King-of-the-world rich!
God of wealth rich!
Rich and lucky!
Happy New Year! I hope you get rich!
Mr. Ching.
What's this?
This?
It's called a camera.
For making movies.
What's a movie?
Movies are the best thing ever.
But I worry that this thing
might someday put magicians like myself
out of business.
Mr. Ching, I hope to see
your performance again soon.
At least I didn't lose the bet.
I will surely have the courage
to come back one day.
- Farewell.
Farewell.
- Farewell, Shiliang.
- Farewell.
Farewell.
What exactly is a revolution?
It's something
that will make China better.
If things were better there,
who would come here?
Mr. Ching,
thank you for waiting another day.
Look at this country.
Their magic lies in cars,
movies, skyscrapers,
railways, and steamboats,
while mine is just for show.
So, what I cannot achieve,
I hope all of you can.
Can a few hundred guns on this ship
really save China?
If hundreds aren't enough,
then I'll bring thousands.
And if those still aren't enough,
then I'll bring tens of thousands.
Despite endless trials and tribulations,
our nation still stands.
It's all because our people
gave their lives for greater causes.
I believe that one day,
we will become the most powerful country.
Yes.
And that will be
the greatest magic trick
the world has ever seen.