(This series is made
for entertainment purposes only.
Characters, behaviors, places,
agencies, occupations,
and events in the series are fictional.
It is not intended
to encourage any actions shown in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.)
♪ The sky... that looks so vast, ♪
♪ with the sea that I see as vast. ♪
♪ Just looking at the waves every day.
There's no way we'll meet. ♪
♪ Our hearts... that beat together. ♪
♪ But the world never listens. ♪
♪ It's just a parallel line waiting for a miracle. ♪
♪ Even though in reality... there are many rules.
That doesn't allow us to be together. ♪
♪ But love is about you and me.
It's not anyone's. ♪
♪ No need to tell the world that we love each other. ♪
(Love each other.)
♪ Don't tell anyone and make it complicated. ♪
(Complicated.)
♪ Let you be my world. ♪
(My world.)
♪ Let us live in a new world together. ♪
(A new world together.)
♪ No need to tell the world that we are a couple. ♪
(Couple.)
♪ Because it's not important. ♪
(What is important?)
♪ As long as we have the same feelings. ♪
♪ As long as you're with me, ♪
♪ as long as we love each other. ♪
(as long as we love each other.)
♪ No need to tell anyone. ♪
"Lover Merman"
(Episode 2)
(Previously)
My name's Phurit.
I'm Nawa.
This here is Phurit,
my close friend from Bangkok.
From now on,
Phurit will be working here with us.
Phu's a player,
he throws his charm around everywhere.
If you can avoid him, then avoid him.
I don't want my little brother to get hurt.
As for Phu,
if he ever found out the truth one day,
he wouldn't be able to handle it.
Do you need something?
Well, I'm supposed
to start my internship here tomorrow,
Also, there'll be a trainee starting tomorrow.
Go ahead. I don't like training interns.
I suggest you don't touch it.
What kind of fish scale is this?
If I told you it's a merman's scale,
would you believe me?
There's no way I can believe it.
On the night before the full moon,
every mermaid shows an
eight-pointed star mark on their body.
If anyone can bring me
a mermaid to see in person,
then I'll believe it.
Right, Maiaek.
Yes?
Can you close up the bar for me?
I'm going out to hang out
with some customers somewhere else.
Thanks a lot.
- Sure, no problem.
- Please clean the glass for me.
Alright.
Hey Nawa, heading back already?
I can drive you.
Can I sit and relax here a little longer?
Mm, alright. I'll wait on the shore.
Okay.
- See you later.
- Okay.
Let's go first.
A merman!
Mr. Phurit!
I shouldn't have drank that much.
Wow...
How did I even get back here?
I really shouldn't have drunk that much.
This hangover's killing me.
And I'm in such a hurry.
Hey!
It's just been a rough morning.
Should I call the insurance for you?
I don't think that should be
the first thing you say to me.
Look, I really am in a rush.
I don't want any trouble with you.
I don't care where you're rushing to.
And I don't want any trouble
with someone like you either.
Someone like me?
What's that supposed to mean?
Someone who makes a mistake
and doesn't even bother to apologize.
What kind of person do you think that is?
Is that so?
Well, one thing's for sure,
I'm not the kind of person
who throws shade first, unlike you.
Anyway, about the car just now,
I'm sorry.
I was driving carelessly.
My car just got a little scratch.
Forget it.
Oh, and another thing,
even if you called the insurance,
there's no way any agent would
drag themselves out here to see you.
Don't forget, this is an island,
not Bangkok.
People here don't live the kind of life you do.
Excuse me.
Are you Nawa?
Yeah. And you are?
My younger brother. His name's Ping.
Phana asked us to look after him.
He's here to work behind the bar.
Sure.
If you need any help, just let me know.
Yes, thank you.
Man, my little brother's so lucky,
getting the bar's number one bartender
to look after him.
Oh, Ping,
grab the bottles from the crate
and put them up on the bar for me.
Be right back, I'll go to the kitchen.
Got it.
Ping, are you a local here too?
Yes, but I went to study on the mainland.
I only come back once in a while.
Why? Do I not look like a local to you?
I'm sure we've never met,
but for some reason you feel familiar to me.
Hard to explain.
Right, I feel the same.
For the mixers that aren't soda,
put them in here.
Makes it easier to grab when serving customers.
And also, tell Timmy to bring
more whiskey up to the front bar.
Got it.
Nawa.
Yes?
Has Phana come in yet?
He should be here by now.
Are you hungover, Mr. Phurit?
Are you worried about me?
Anyone seeing you like this would think
the same thing I just said.
Then what do I have to do to
make you really worry about me?
And why should I worry about you?
Because I like you.
This is Ping.
Phana brought him in as a trainee.
This is Mr. Phurit, he's...
Are you Nawa's boyfriend?
- No.
- Yes.
Not yet. But soon.
He's Mr. Phurit,
Phana's friend
and also a co-owner of the bar.
Sorry about that, Mr. Phurit.
Starting your shift early, huh.
Don't start hitting me, man.
My head's already killing me.
Last night, the customers
drank way too hard with me.
Have a regular drink of the staffs here.
Nawa,
can you get a hot honey-lemon drink for Phurit?
Yes.
Phana,
last night, I think
I saw something
that looked like a merman.
Sorry, sir.
What are you babbling about?
Mermen? There's no such thing.
I didn't think so either.
But I swear
my eyes weren't playing tricks on me.
Where did you supposedly see this?
Last night,
after I separated with the customers,
I sat by the beach to sober up.
I couldn't see clearly,
but I'm sure of it, it was a merman.
A merman!
But the more I think about it,
the more it looked like…
Looked like what?
Like…
Oh, Mr. Phurit,
you're sober now?
Please don't fall asleep drunk like that again,
you'll get sick.
What do you mean by that, Lek?
Last night,
I happened to go meet a friend at the beach.
That's when I ran into Mr. Phurit,
he'd passed out drunk there.
Damn, Phu.
So you were just drunk
and dreaming you saw a merman.
Let me tell you something,
this isn't Bangkok
where you can get wasted
and then just hop into a cab home.
People on this island might not be dangerous,
but that doesn't mean
it's safe for a newcomer like you.
Right. Sorry.
I'll take better care of myself from now on.
Good.
And thanks for last night, Lek.
No problem.
That thing Phu said was it you, Nawa?
Uh… Phana, you knew?
The signs were obvious.
Yesterday I swam pretty far out
from the hidden beach.
I didn't think anyone would see.
It's fine.
But I don't want you being careless either.
These days, there aren't many people on the island
who know about mermen.
And the fewer that know, the better,
for your safety.
I'll be more careful from now on.
By the way,
you're going to see Den today, right?
I'm heading out anyway,
want me to give you a ride?
No, it's okay.
I'll just take my motorbike.
That way I can hurry back
and get things ready at the bar.
Alright then, I'll go ahead.
- Alright.
- Take good care of yourself.
I was just about to head into town for a bit.
Mind if I tag along?
I'm only going to the barbershop.
Nothing special.
That's fine.
I'll come to the barbershop with you.
Wouldn't it be easier if you
just drove your own car?
You're not very gentle, you know that?
Let me ask you straight.
All of your actions…
Are you hitting on me?
That's right. I'm hitting on you.
I'm sorry if I gave you
the wrong idea that day.
Honestly, I thought you were just a customer.
I only went along with it
the way a bartender usually does.
I never intended to make you think otherwise.
So what? I really like you.
And what exactly makes you like me?
Mmm... I don't know.
I just feel like if I let you slip away,
it would be the biggest regret of my life.
Then I'm too tired to keep talking to you.
What's wrong, Grandpa?
Don't tell me you're out of gas again.
Want me to give you a ride?
I mean, you're in a hurry, right?
You said you've got to get back to the bar.
Now that I'm managing the bar...
I'm strict, you know.
If you show up late...
Fine.
But let go of my arm.
Alright.
Lead the way.
Uh… Sorry,
I didn't mean to be rude.
I didn't even say anything to you yet.
Ah, right.
So, how was it? Your first day at work.
It was good.
Today Timmy and Nawa
taught me step by step.
Right now I'm just trying to
get used to the things around here.
That's good.
Just take it slow and learn.
If you're confused, just ask.
Yes, thank you.
Oh, perfect timing Timmy,
a Manhattan as usual,
then put it over there for me.
Got it.
Does Mr. Phana
usually drink at this hour?
Pfft, usually?
If he's drinking at this time,
it means he argued with Namhom.
Ms. Namhom?
Yeah, his girlfriend.
They fight all the time,
but he really loves her, man.
I see them argue every time,
like twice a week,
but they've never once broken up.
(Ferry Kohkhen)
(Boat ticket sales)
(Speedboat port)
This is your regular barbershop?
There aren't that many shops on the island.
Thanks for giving me a ride.
If you're done with your errands,
just call me anytime.
I'll go walk around the town and wait.
But I don't have your number.
Are you asking for my number right now?
Either way, I have to have yours,
and you need mine too.
Don't forget to save it.
Call me anytime,
don't be shy.
I won't bother you.
If you finish your business,
you can just head back first.
You don't have to wait for me.
How's this?
I trimmed the sides a little higher this time.
Looks good.
Do you like it like this?
Whoa, Den, I really like it.
- Took quite a bit off, huh?
- Um.
Oh hey, Nawa.
Hello, Den.
Hello.
Oh, Phraphai.
Didn't expect to run into you here.
You came for a haircut too?
Oh no,
I came to drop off some wine
that Den ordered from the mainland.
Here you go.
Thanks.
I actually ordered it for you too,
but forgot to bring it.
Didn't think you'd show up here.
I'll just swing by the shop later to pick it up.
Sure.
Whoa, new haircut.
You look way more handsome now.
Isn't that a bit much, Nawa?
A bit much?
What, no compliments for your barber?
I cut it for him
with my best effort, you know.
Oh, well that goes without saying, Den.
Right, have you two heard the rumors about
humans hunting mermen on our island?
Where did you hear that from, Den?
Last time I went to release the poison,
I overheard some mermen talking.
They said some mermen were missing.
Two or three of them
went missing last week.
Didn't you guys hear anything about this?
I'll need to check with my father
about this first.
Ha, as expected of the headman's son,
never lets anything slip by.
That's Phraphai for you,
he worries about every single mermen
on this island.
Not every mermaid, I'd say.
My father said he heard about it too,
and there's a high chance it's true.
But there's no evidence yet that humans
are specifically targeting mermen.
So, how seriously should I take this,
tell me, Phraphai.
Phraphai.
Does this mean we have
to go back to hiding like before?
Nawa.
No need.
My father's handling it.
And besides,
I won't let anyone hurt our people.
Den.
Here's the payment for my haircut.
Thanks.
I'll go grab your change.
Right. Nawa.
Do you need to head anywhere else?
I'll just go back to the shop.
How'd you get here?
Want me to give you a ride?
I need to stop by the shop
to pick up the wine anyway.
Oh, sure.
Let's go.
(I parked my car in front of the barbershop.
If Mr. Nawa done...)
Oh, Nawa!
Do you want to stop anywhere on the way?
I better just head back to the shop.
Okay.
Let's go.
Someone who makes a mistake
and doesn't even bother to apologize.
What kind of person do you think that is?
You two know each other?
(Full & a Half Kohkhen)
I'll go inside and get the wine.
Alright, I'll wait in the car then.
What a coincidence.
I didn't expect to see you again.
Same here.
Are you here for dinner?
No,
a close friend of mine works here.
By close friend… you mean Nawa?
You know Nawa too?
Of course. I own this place.
Really?
I thought Phana was the sole owner.
Then you'll need to update your understanding.
By the way, what exactly
are your relationship with Nawa?
Why do you ask?
Because this time,
it's not just a near miss.
I think I'm about to collide with you for real.
Phraphai!
Nawa.
Ah, Nawa.
We were just talking about you.
You two know each other?
Not exactly.
We just happened to run into each other.
This is Phurit,
Phana's friend
and also co-owner of this part of the shop.
And this is Phraphai,
my senior,
he owns the fishing fleet
across the whole island.
Oh…
You're the influential one around here.
Pleasure to meet you.
Nawa, you're exaggerating.
You'll just make Mr. Phurit thinks I'm smug.
I won't, Phraphai.
Because on this island,
the only one I care about is Nawa.
Well, if you know there's a collision coming,
I'd advise you to step back now.
Because no insurance will cover you.
What's this?
Getting to know each other?
Hello, Phana.
Hey, headman. Been busy lately?
Haven't seen you drop by.
I only just came ashore a few days ago.
Are you heading back now, Phraphai?
Actually, I've changed my mind.
I'll stay and have some wine here.
Oh, perfect.
I was just about to discuss
the new shipment with you.
It's my pleasure.
I'll be waiting inside then.
Let's go.
See you in a bit.
What the hell are you thinking?
Tell me.
Do you remember?
I told you this morning I had a problem
when I went into the shop.
This is the guy I'm having trouble with.
Hey, Phu, what problem?
What the hell did you get yourself into?
Hey!
Ping, grab me a refill, will you?
Maiaek.
Yes?
Can I ask you something?
Who's that guy sitting next to Phana?
Oh… That's Phraphai.
He's the son of the island's headman,
basically owns the entire fishing fleet here.
Super famous around here.
He's got good personality,
good looks, rich too,
and he's been close with
Phana since they were kids.
But, well, Khen island
is a small island after all.
So he's Nawa's friend?
To Nawa,
Phraphai's like a real older brother.
Older brother.
Yeah.
But it's not the same as Phana.
How do I put this…
Honestly,
they look more like a couple than siblings.
People even say Phraphai has feelings for Nawa.
Oh.
Thank you.
So Phraphai likes Nawa.
- Yeah.
- And what about Nawa? Does he like Phraphai back?
That's the big question.
It's a pity nobody knows
what Nawa really thinks.
I wish I knew, too.
Everyone at the bar sees them.
But Phu,
you've been asking a lot about Nawa.
You've got a crush?
Yeah, I like Nawa.
And I'm going to make him mine.
I'm rooting for you.
Go for it.
Thanks for giving me a ride.
Yes.
Nawa.
Yes?
Can we talk for a bit?
What is it?
What kind of person is Phurit?
Well… Playful, a bit cheeky.
Overall, I'd say he's a good guy.
Is he trying to court you?
Let me ask you straight.
All of your actions…
Are you hitting on me?
That's right. I'm hitting on you.
I think so, yeah.
At first, I thought he was just joking around,
but when I asked him directly,
he said he was serious.
And...
And you? What do you think of him?
I don't think anything of it.
Between me and Phurit, it's impossible anyway.
Besides,
Phana told me Phurit is quite the playboy.
I just hope that's really the case.
You don't need to worry, Phraphai.
If I don't give him any attention,
he'll eventually give up.
Nawa, I'll be honest with you.
Other than Phana,
I don't want you trusting any human at all.
Don't forget
the scars humans have left on us.
I know.
I won't trust anyone so easily.
Good. Now, go on, get some rest.
Alright. Drive safe, okay?
Is he trying to court you?
Well... I think so, yeah.
Don't forget
the scars humans have left on us.
I know.
I won't trust anyone so easily.
All of your actions…
Are you hitting on me?
That's right. I'm hitting on you.
I don't want to see you end up hurt.
Phu's a player,
he throws his charm around everywhere.
If you can avoid him, then avoid him.
Besides,
I don't want my little brother to get hurt.
As for Phu,
if he ever found out the truth one day,
he wouldn't be able to handle it.
What are you babbling about?
Mermen? There's no such thing.
I didn't think so either.
But I swear
my eyes weren't playing tricks on me.
Nawa, what's wrong, sweetheart? Hmm?
Mom.
I don't want to play with Phana anymore.
He said he's scared of me
because I'm a merman.
Why is he scared of me just like that?
I've never done anything to him,
never even teased him.
It's alright, my dear.
You don't like being judged
by someone who
doesn't truly know you, right?
Phana only said that
because he doesn't yet understand
who you really are.
Once he sees that
you're kind and gentle,
I'm sure he'll want to
play with you again.
So what should I do, Mom?
You have to open your heart,
don't shut yourself away.
Show others who you really are.
You know, humans and mermen
deep down, we're not so different.
We both feel, and we both have hearts.
And if our hearts can truly connect,
then even a love that seems impossible
can become possible.
Really?
Of course, sweetheart.
As long as you lead with your heart.
Hmm?
Was what you said true, Mom?
I can't see it yet.
About what Den mentioned earlier,
the rumor that people came here to hunt mermen
my father says it's true.
He's already dealt with those humans,
but still, we can't afford to let our guard down.
Be careful wherever you go.
I worry about you, Nawa.
I understand, Phraphai.
I'll be more careful from now on.
Last time I went to release the poison,
I overheard some mermen talking.
They said some mermen were missing.
Two or three of them
went missing last week.
Didn't you guys hear anything about this?
(Love each other.)
(Complicated.)
(My world.)
(A new world together.)
(Couple.)
(What is important?)
(Next Episode)
I've been courting you for almost a month now.
Why won't you soften up to me yet?
Are you about to give up already?
I brought you something.
A mermaid keychain.
I thought of you when I saw how cute it was.
You know that Phraprai
is courting your bro, right?
If there's anyone who deserves to be with Nawa,
it should be Phraprai.
He's the most suitable.
If it were on your neck, Nawa,
it would look so beautiful.
Nawa,
I have something to tell you.
Mr. Phana.
You're the first person
who's ever made me feel like this.
You know what?
I think
I like you even more than I can handle.
♪ The sky... that looks so vast, ♪
♪ with the sea that I see as vast. ♪
♪ Just looking at the waves every day.
There's no way we'll meet. ♪
♪ Our hearts... that beat together. ♪
♪ But the world never listens. ♪
♪ It's just a parallel line waiting for a miracle. ♪
♪ Even though in reality... there are many rules.
That doesn't allow us to be together. ♪
♪ But love is about you and me.
It's not anyone's. ♪
♪ No need to tell the world that we love each other. ♪
(Love each other.)
♪ Don't tell anyone and make it complicated. ♪
(Complicated.)
♪ Let you be my world. ♪
(My world.)
♪ Let us live in a new world together. ♪
(A new world together.)
♪ No need to tell the world that we are a couple. ♪
(Couple.)
♪ Because it's not important. ♪
(What is important?)
♪ As long as we have the same feelings. ♪
♪ As long as you're with me, ♪
♪ as long as we love each other. ♪
(as long as we love each other.)
♪ No need to tell anyone. ♪