(This series is made
for entertainment purposes only.
Characters, behaviors, places,
agencies, occupations,
and events in the series are fictional.
It is not intended
to encourage any actions shown in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.)
Have you ever heard the legend of Khen Island?
They said, besides humans,
there are other beings who
look no different from humans,
living together on Khen Island
in harmony with mankind
to the point where
they can't be distinguished.
When they are on land,
they are no different from ordinary people.
But whenever these beings
dive beneath the ocean,
their bodies transform.
We call them
merman.
♪ The sky... that looks so vast, ♪
♪ with the sea that I see as vast. ♪
♪ Just looking at the waves every day.
There's no way we'll meet. ♪
♪ Our hearts... that beat together. ♪
♪ But the world never listens. ♪
♪ It's just a parallel line waiting for a miracle. ♪
♪ Even though in reality... there are many rules.
That doesn't allow us to be together. ♪
♪ But love is about you and me.
It's not anyone's. ♪
♪ No need to tell the world that we love each other. ♪
(Love each other.)
♪ Don't tell anyone and make it complicated. ♪
(Complicated.)
♪ Let you be my world. ♪
(My world.)
♪ Let us live in a new world together. ♪
(A new world together.)
♪ No need to tell the world that we are a couple. ♪
(Couple.)
♪ Because it's not important. ♪
(What is important?)
♪ As long as we have the same feelings. ♪
♪ As long as you're with me, ♪
♪ as long as we love each other. ♪
(as long as we love each other.)
♪ No need to tell anyone. ♪
"Lover Merman" (Episode 1)
(Full & a Half Kohkhen)
I'm telling you, today.
Timmy's the dark horse for sure.
But I think Nawa's better.
Maybe. We'll have to wait
until we taste it.
Timmy'll win,
- my bro always makes delicious things.
- I think Nawa will win.
Let's wait and see. Just wait and see.
Damn, you always go all out, huh, Nawa?
Can't you go easy on me for once?
In that case,
let's get started with the judging.
I can't wait to taste it.
Alright then.
I'll start with Timmy's drink first.
Let's do this, bro.
How is it?
Whoa, today's really good.
It might win.
Whoa...
What's the matter?
That good, huh?
Whoa…
Oh!
If you guys are reacting like this...
Let me see.
This is the real deal, bro.
Just how good is it?
Sh*t… damn, Nawa…
this is amazing!
Can I just admit defeat already?
That's too much, man, too much.
Then I'll just go ahead and announce it,
today's winner is…
- Nawa!
- Nawa.
This is the real deal.
Gotta hand it to him.
That's damn good!
I think we can put this on the bar menu.
Customers would love it.
It'll totally work.
I'll try pitch it to Phana first.
Okay.
Oh, I totally forgot.
Maiek. We've gotta go pick up
the stuff at the shop.
We're already late, man.
Then what are we waiting for, bro?
Hurry up!
- Bro is gonna start nagging again.
- Cover the shop for me.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
- Look after the place for a sec.
- Bro will nag again.
Hey,
I'm going to clean up the kitchen for a bit.
What kind of drink would you like today?
Usually, what do people in love order?
That would be the list on
the first page of the menu.
You can choose whichever flavor you like
sour or sweet.
What about you? Which do you prefer?
I like sweet.
I like… sweet too.
This menu was inspired by my own experience.
The flavor represents love
that feels like a dream,
hidden behind a mist of uncertainty.
It might be a little hard to drink at first,
but once you get halfway through,
you'll find sweetness.
And that, right there,
is the reward for someone who
makes love more clear.
Please, give it a try.
I bet you must have a lot of people
hitting on you.
My name's Phurich.
I'm Nawa.
Wow! I can't believe
how fragrant and rich the flavor is,
everything blends perfectly.
It's really delicious.
Thank you very much.
Can I get one more shot of tequila, please?
For you, Mr. Nawa.
Hey, are you trying to hit on my staff or what?
Phana.
Hey, Phu.
How have you been?
I'm good. And you?
I'm good too.
Your place looks great, man.
Of course, it's my shop!
(Full & a Half Kohkhen)
This here is Phurich,
my close friend from Bangkok.
He's also my business partner.
Together we founded Full & a Half Bar.
From now on,
Phurich will be working here with us.
So everyone,
treat him as another owner of the place.
Hello.
I've heard Mr. Phana mention you many times,
but I didn't expect you to be this handsome.
Are you single?
Aham... keep it down.
I'm Aunt Son,
the chef here.
And this is my nephew,
- called "Somchai"
- Hey!
It's Mary, my name is Mary.
Right. Mary.
My assistant in the kitchen.
And I'm beautiful and single too.
Mr. Phurich, I'm Lek, a server here.
If you need anything,
you can always call me.
I'm Maiek, Phana's cousin.
Do you still remember me, Phu?
Of course I do. You little monkey,
you've grown up a lot.
Hey...
More like he grown into a bigger monkey.
What kind of monkey looks this cool?
And what about those two?
Those two...
That one's Timmy.
And the one you just tried to flirt
is Nawa.
He's our number one here,
the one who really draws the customers in.
Anyway, that's pretty much everyone.
Now let's all get back to work.
We're opening slow today.
Go go.
Okay.
Why are you standing there?
Get inside.
If you need anything, Mr. Phurich,
just let me know.
Go on, move.
Don't even think about it.
I'm giving you a red card,
you're out of the game.
No hitting on Nawa.
Why not?
Don't tell me you've got
your eye on Nawa too.
What about Namhom, your girlfriend?
Nawa's no different
from my real younger brother.
My family raised him since he was a kid.
Then that's perfect.
Your mom doesn't hate me or anything.
But I know you too well, Phu.
You've never truly loved anyone.
And I don't believe that you've changed.
So, go mess around with someone else.
My order is final, no negotiations.
That's that.
I'm off.
We've only got four kinds of wine left.
Three bottles each.
That's all of them?
Yeah, all set.
Okay.
Everything good?
All good.
Nawa and I listed everything out.
Thanks a lot, Timmy.
Okay.
I want to speak to Nawa for a bit.
Oh, right! I almost forgot.
The kid I mentioned
who's coming in for training,
he'll arrive tomorrow.
Can I bring him over around noon?
Yeah, that's fine.
Okay, thank you.
Phana, is something wrong?
I just wanted to ask,
earlier, what were you talking about with Phu?
What kind of drink would you like today?
Usually, what do people in love order?
That would be the list on
the first page of the menu.
You can choose whichever flavor you like
sour or sweet.
What about you? Which do you prefer?
I like sweet.
I like... sweet too.
It's nothing, really.
Mr. Phurich only ordered a drink.
He tried to hit on you too, didn't he?
Probably.
At first, I thought he was
just a regular customer,
so I just went with the flow.
But once I realized
he's your business partner,
I won't get involved with him.
That's a relief.
I don't want to see you end up hurt.
Phu's a player,
he throws his charm around everywhere.
If you can avoid him, then avoid him.
Besides,
I don't want my little brother to get hurt.
As for Phu,
if he ever found out the truth one day,
he wouldn't be able to handle it.
Yes.
Alright then. I'll head out first.
Alright.
Stop staring at my brother.
What the hell,
I can't even look?
If it were someone else, I wouldn't care.
But you? You're way too flashy.
You've got no right to
lecture me about this, Phana.
Don't compare yourself to me.
At least I talk to one person at a time,
date one person at a time.
When I do, I date them for a long time.
So what?
I don't see your love life
turning out any better than mine.
If someone isn't “the one,”
why force yourself to keep dating them?
Hey...
Did that hit a nerve?
You hit him straight in the heart.
You know what?
Since the bar opened,
Namhom hasn't even shown up here once.
I see him every day just drinking,
getting drunk, missing her.
Geez, he's so pitiful.
There, there.
You brat, are you so free that
- you need to listen to others talking?
- Just kidding.
- Just kidding. Just kidding.
- Maiek.
Yes?
Get me another drink.
Okay. Same as before, right?
Phana,
is there something you want to tell me?
I haven't seen Namhom in almost three months.
It's not like it's a huge deal.
We're both busy with our own lives.
She's in Bangkok,
I'm stuck here on Khen Island.
Not meeting each other for so long,
I feel like Namhom's changed.
You think Namhom has someone else?
I don't think so.
If she really did,
it would actually be easier.
I'd just break up with her, no hesitation.
Then what are you gonna do?
Have you tried sitting down
and really talking it out?
We have.
We've tried fixing things so many times,
but it always ends in a fight.
Even this afternoon, when she called,
it was the same old argument again.
It feels like we're not part
of each other's lives anymore.
All that's left is the
“relationship status” tying us together.
I can't even give you advice on this, man.
I've never been in a relationship like yours.
Hey,
don't stress out on my behalf.
I'm sure once we meet up again,
things will get better.
Hey. Cheers.
I hope it turns out the way you say.
Hey, hey.
Cut it out.
None of your business.
(Full & a Half Kohkhen)
(yesterday
Phana: I have something I want to talk about.)
The bar isn't open yet.
Right now, we only serve breakfast and coffee.
I'm not here to order drinks.
I came to see Timmy.
Timmy's not here.
Do you need something?
Well, I'm supposed
to start my internship here tomorrow,
but Timmy told me to meet
with the owner first.
I see.
Hey, Ping!
Timmy!
Sorry, I'm late. Had a rough night.
Phana,
this is my little bro I mentioned
the one coming to intern at the shop.
Yeah, I know.
He didn't annoy or tease you, right?
Annoy or tease me?
He looked like a lost kid
wandering into the shop just now.
Anyway, what do you want to do here?
I want to learn about the bar system.
And actually, the reason I came here
is also because I want to understand how
a restaurant-bar hybrid works.
Then I'll leave you with Nawa and Timmy
to train him on the bar side.
Got it.
And if I've got time,
I'll teach you how
the restaurant system works.
Oh. But when it's busy,
you'll probably have to help serve as well.
No problem.
Alright then, I'll leave him to you.
- Got it.
- I'll get back to work.
Come with me.
- Let me show you.
- Sure.
Hello.
What's up, Phana?
Yeah, I'm in front of your house now.
I brought the car for you.
Hey, my car's ready already?
Yep. You can come out and get it, sir.
Okay, I'll hurry down.
Phana.
What's up?
Here you go. Your car.
- I checked it thoroughly for you.
- Asshole.
Not a single scratch.
Thanks a lot, man.
So,
how's it going?
First night in a new place?
Not bad.
Switching from my condo
to a house feels pretty good.
That's good.
Sometimes a change of scenery is nice,
you might like it.
Phana.
Oh, what are you doing here?
Aunty Pha asked me to bring
the documents you forgot for Mr. Phurich.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Today, I was thinking
of driving around the city.
Want to be my guide?
I'm not free today.
He's taking the day off today.
For what?
You don't need to know everything.
He told me many days ago.
But if a staff who works at the bar
takes time off, shouldn't I know?
Then I'll take my leave now, Phana.
Drive safe.
- Yes, see you later.
- Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
You, seriously...
Right in front of me no less.
If you're just messing around,
go mess around with someone else,
not Nawa.
And if I'm not just messing around...
Does that mean I can hit on him?
For someone like you?
Better not even say that.
Anyway, since we're at it,
drive me to the bar.
Also, there'll be a trainee starting tomorrow.
Go ahead.
I don't like training interns.
You handle it.
Alright, then.
You keep an eye on the customers
and the shop side.
Let's go.
I suggest you
don't touch it.
Sorry for being rude.
I just I saw it and it looked beautiful,
so I...
That's exactly why.
It's beauty is what lures humans
who are full of desire,
making them obsessed time and time again.
How so?
Never mind.
Let's just say
it's my personal, valuable possession.
By the way, what kind of fish scale is this?
I've never seen anything like it before.
If I told you it's a merman's scale,
would you believe me?
There's no way I can believe it.
Good. It's better you don't.
The more people believe in these things,
misfortune tend to follow.
You're not a tourist, right?
No, I'm not.
You're not from this island either.
I just decided to move here,
and I opened a bar
with a friend as a business partner.
I'm thinking about starting a resort too,
and planning to stay here long-term.
Khen Island should only have
two kinds of people,
one, the original residents,
and two, tourists.
This island isn't suitable for new residents.
Why not?
Excuse me.
Yes, Phana?
Okay, I'll go now.
I'll take my leave.
Sorry again for being rude.
What's your name?
I'm Silp.
I'm Phurich.
My bar is on the main beach,
called Full & a Half.
If you ever want a drink,
you're welcome to come by.
Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
I'll take my leave now.
Nawa, I'm in front of the house now.
Okay, Phraphai.
I'll be out soon.
Mm, finish getting yourself ready first
before coming out.
Got it.
Alright.
Take your time getting ready.
I can wait.
Oh, and about your heart, I can wait too.
No matter how long it takes,
I'll wait for you, Nawa.
Met.
You want to hitch a ride with me
to release the poison, don't you?
I'm just teasing a little, don't pout.
Watch what you say.
I don't want him to find out about this.
Honestly,
I think everyone on the island
already knows how you feel about Nawa.
Only he still sees you as
just a really good older brother.
I'm serious,
don't you have any plan
to tell him your feelings?
You're adults now,
if you feel something, just say it.
Oh, hey, Met.
Are we going together today?
My car's having a little problem,
- so I'll hitch a ride with you two.
- Uh.
Nawa,
shall we head out?
Ready.
Let me see.
Looking all dreamy.
What is it?
Met's just rambling, Nawa.
Come on, let's go.
Okay.
Let's go.
If it's going to be like this,
maybe they could just go together,
I'll release the poison here.
Damn it, Phraphai, Nawa, wait for me!
The weather's great today.
After releasing the poison,
I want to swim a little more.
Sure.
Nawa, you're not in a rush, right?
No,
I want to swim a bit longer too.
I'll go down first. See you below.
Mm, see you, man.
- Hello.
- Make yourself comfortable.
- Yeah.
Hello.
If you need anything, just let me know.
Make yourself comfortable.
Maiek,
our bar gets pretty busy, huh?
Yeah.
Even though it's not high season,
customers keep coming in.
Why do you think that is?
The mermaid legend?
Whoa! You know about that too?
Every customer talks about it.
They say that on Khen Island,
mermaids live mixed in with humans,
looking and living just like humans.
So people can't tell the difference.
You know the details, huh.
On the night before the full moon,
every mermaid shows an
eight-pointed star mark on their body.
Before the full moon night?
Yes.
Yeah.
Do you believe it, Phu?
Everyone asks me the same thing.
And my answer?
If anyone can bring me
a mermaid to see in person,
then I'll believe it.
I understand.
Hello.
Right, Maiek.
Yes?
Can you close up the bar for me?
I'm going out to hang out
with some customers somewhere else.
Sure.
I'll handle it.
Thanks a lot.
- Sure, no problem.
- Please clean the glass for me.
Alright.
You don't even clear your own glass.
Hey Nawa,
heading back already?
I can drive you.
Can I sit and relax here a little longer?
Mm, alright. I'll wait on the shore.
Okay.
See you later.
Let's go first.
How long has it been since I was drunk like this?
A merman!
Mr. Phurich!
(Love each other.)
(Complicated.)
(My world.)
(A new world together.)
(Couple.)
(What is important?)
(Next Episode)
That guy over there... Who's he?
Honestly, they look more like a couple
than siblings.
I want to ask you directly...
What you're doing right now...
Are you trying to hit on me?
Yes. I am trying to hit on you.
Are you here for a meal?
No.
It's just that someone close to me works here.
Nawa, huh?
If you know you're about to crash,
I suggest you back off.
No insurance will cover you.
By the way, have you two heard about
humans coming to hunt mermaids on our island?
Den, where did you hear about this?
Nawa,
I don't want you to trust any humans at all.
Are you a local here too, Ping?
Why?
Don't I look like a local?
Last night I thought...
I saw something
that looked like a merman,
but when I thought about it carefully,
it looked like...
♪ The sky... that looks so vast, ♪
♪ with the sea that I see as vast. ♪
♪ Just looking at the waves every day.
There's no way we'll meet. ♪
♪ Our hearts... that beat together. ♪
♪ But the world never listens. ♪
♪ It's just a parallel line waiting for a miracle. ♪
♪ Even though in reality... there are many rules.
That doesn't allow us to be together. ♪
♪ But love is about you and me.
It's not anyone's. ♪
♪ No need to tell the world that we love each other. ♪
(Love each other.)
♪ Don't tell anyone and make it complicated. ♪
(Complicated.)
♪ Let you be my world. ♪
(My world.)
♪ Let us live in a new world together. ♪
(A new world together.)
♪ No need to tell the world that we are a couple. ♪
(Couple.)
♪ Because it's not important. ♪
(What is important?)
♪ As long as we have the same feelings. ♪
♪ As long as you're with me, ♪
♪ as long as we love each other. ♪
(as long as we love each other.)
♪ No need to tell anyone. ♪