=Side Story Of Fox Volant=
(Adapted from Jin Yong's novel)
=Episode 40=
Commander Hai.
We don't know
whether Official Fu is dead or alive.
You can't fire the cannon.
You don't know?
If he is still alive,
these traitors
will use him as a hostage
to exchange for their freedom.
Since he has yet to appear,
it means he's already dead.
We need to fight to the end
and fire the cannon at the island.
Leave no one alive
to avenge Official Fu
and build the Qing Empire's pride.
Commander Hai!
Tiejiao.
Looking at how impatient Hailan Bi is,
I think he is
trying to gain an achievement.
Yes, Tiejiao.
Even if Official Fu isn't dead,
he will be blasted to death
by the cannon.
Cannoneers, get to your positions!
We owe Official Fu a favour.
We must not let him get his way.
Follow me.
Listen to my instructions!
Commander Hai!
Do you have His Majesty's edict?
If you don't,
you can't simply fire the cannon.
Although His Majesty is decisive
and cannot be threatened,
His Majesty's love
towards Official Fu
is like a father towards his child.
His Majesty's intention
is hard to predict.
If he loses Official Fu
and gets angry at you,
wouldn't it be too late
to regret your actions?
Enough.
I met His Majesty.
He would never let the traitors escape.
Listen to me!
Commander Hai!
Prepare to fire!
His Majesty's edict!
Commander Hai, hurry.
(Keep the peace)
Come with me.
- No, I don't go with you.
I want to be with Uncle Hu.
Since they want to follow you,
I won't force them.
I will let them
choose the paths
they want to walk in the future.
This is the edict
written by His Majesty.
Keep it well.
No matter where you go,
it will help you escape death.
There's no need.
The people of the martial arts world
keep their promises,
act righteously
and cherish their reputations.
If His Majesty keeps his promise,
I won't be needing this paper.
It's Official Fu!
Hurry!
Let's go.
Your Honour.
Everyone, listen to my command!
Prepare to fire!
Stop!
Your Honour.
Official Hai.
Official Fu has a deal over there.
He can't break his promise.
We will be setting them free again.
Your Honour, we can't
let this opportunity go.
This is the best chance
to wipe out Red Flower Club.
Everyone, listen to my command!
How dare you!
His Majesty's edict is here!
Are you trying
to defy His Majesty's will?
I
dare not.
Pass on my command.
Retreat immediately.
Now that the tournament has ended,
everything is over.
What do you plan to do, Sister Yuan?
Everything has been decided.
I have to return to Tianshan
with Master.
You are leaving?
I thought
you will be coming with us.
Since I'm already a nun,
we are already strangers.
You can still secularise.
You went through tonsure
because Fu Kang'an...
Amitabha.
I am
already a follower of Buddhism.
Having secular thoughts
will be breaking the vow.
Although the time
we knew each other was short,
we were close.
We can't become sisters in this life.
I hope we can keep our relationship
in the next life.
I am already a nun
and have nothing with me.
I will give the Epiphyllum Dew Token
to you as a gift.
I hope it can protect you.
Don't reject it
and miss out on a good relationship.
Amitabha.
Destiny will always come to an end.
When it comes to an end,
a new destiny is born.
From now on,
it's like a year ago.
You know nothing about me
and I know nothing about you.
I wish
you well.
I hope so.
I wish Master Yuan Xing
with perfect virtue and merit.
♪What does the future hold?♪
♪Hopefully,
all wishes will be fulfilled♪
♪What brought us together?♪
Listen to me!
I'm not a pervert.
It's you?
I have yet to learn your name.
If we got beaten to death,
we can greet each other
in the underworld at least.
Do I know you?
Why do you care about what I do?
Don't get involved because of me.
Do you think that's heroic?
If I'm going to die today,
I will die protecting you.
I like to wear purple clothes.
Just call me Yuan Ziyi.
I can only see you
whenever I open my eyes.
You're just saying that.
♪Life is already full of debts♪
♪So let's not dwell on
the little time we have♪
Who said I have to marry someone?
If you don't marry someone,
are you going to be a nun?
Seriously.
With your looks,
even if you become a nun,
you will also be a pretty nun.
Since I got to know you,
we have experienced
many things together.
After I got injured,
you also cared for me meticulously.
It's something I've never felt before.
So, I'm really afraid
that you'll leave me one day.
You are being unreasonable!
That's right.
That's who I am.
You've seen my true colours now.
I know!
I was wrong yesterday night!
I shouldn't do that.
Come back, all right?
Do you still remember
the small wooden comb
I wanted to give you
at the Guanyin Temple?
Are you going to
accept it now?
Every meeting
is not permanent
and won't be long-lasting.
There are many fears in our lives.
Life is short like the morning dew.
Love creates worries.
Love creates fear.
Those who stay away from love
will have neither worry nor fear.
(Hu Yidao and Wife's Memorial Tablet,
Miao Renfeng's Memorial Tablet)
♪Let youth blow at your long hair♪
♪Let it lead you in your dreams♪
♪The city's history♪
♪Has recorded your smile unknowingly♪
♪The blue sky in my heart♪
♪Is a life's beginning♪
♪The night you don't sleep
when the spring rain falls♪
♪The days when you slept alone♪
♪Made the flowers
youthful and beautiful♪
♪Your beautiful face♪
♪The sky is filled with falling catkins♪
♪I imagine them as your smiling face♪
♪The seasonal changes
in the mundane world♪
♪Who determines the fate♪
♪The silence you in the freezing night♪
♪That elusive brilliance♪
♪Take a glance at me♪
♪Don't let me be alone♪
Lingsu.
I've been wanting to ask you a question.
How did you grow the
Seven Pistil Chaenomeles sinensis?
Why did Shi Wanchen fail to do that
for life?
Actually, I had no idea.
But after Master passed away,
(Late Master Wu Chen's Memorial Tablet)
when I was offering joss sticks
and wine to him,
I found a pot of
Seven Pistil Chaenomeles sinensis
under the table
that bloomed because wine dripped on it.
I see.
Every coincidence
is fate.
Lingsu.
Can you
use your master's recipe to make
Nine Times Vitality Restoring Pill
with this?
I thought
you can only find condensation grass
on Mount Yuquan in the capital.
It should be precious.
I didn't expect to find it
in Medicine King Valley.
Medicine King Valley
is such a nice place.
Of course.
Master chose this place
because of this reason.
It's quite nice
to live in Medicine King Valley
for life.
Fei, do you still
have something on your mind?
Are you talking about Shi Wanchen?
If he intends to hide,
finding him will be
like finding a needle in a haystack.
But an evil person like him
will be punished by the heavens
even if I don't kill him.
There's no need to worry.
How can a man change his ambition,
I will still accompany you
even if you're going a thousand li away
to hunt him down.
I can't let you disgrace
the name of the Hu Family.
Don't worry.
You don't need to worry about my health.
This time.
I will make
100 Nine Times Vitality Restoring Pills.
All right.
With that many pills,
you will live a long life.
If you want me to live a long life,
the most important thing is you
instead of the pills.
Me?
The best way
is not to let me worry about you.
That is how I can live a long life.
In that case,
I'm more amazing than the pills.
Chinese medicine always talks about
different herbs helping each other.
You are one of the herbs.
I heal the people of the world
while you heal me.
Of course, you are amazing.
But this medicine
looks a bit ugly.
I think
it's similar to you.
It might be ugly,
but it's a precious treasure
to me.
Brother Wang.
Brother Wang!
Don't touch him.
Fei.
Control your breathing.
Remember the three promises.
You just won't stop following us.
Lingsu.
You should bow down
and apologise immediately.
Otherwise, you will die a horrible death
if he gets angry.
That's right.
If you hand over
the Verse of King of Poison
and Seven Pistil Chaenomeles sinensis,
you will be able to save him.
With the
Seven Pistil Chaenomeles sinensis,
do you think I can't cure
the poison of heartbreak grass?
Girl.
Do you think
you will have time to save him
when the three of us
are fighting against you?
Let's make a deal.
I will give you
the Verse of King of Poison.
Get out of Medicine King Valley
and never disturb me again.
Take it out first.
It is on Master's memorial tablet.
Go and take it yourself.
Hold it!
No one knows how many types of poison
are on his memorial tablet.
You are wise.
You would have died
if you offended Master.
I want you to hand it over
with your own hands.
(The Verse of King of Poison)
Show some sincerity
if you want to make a deal.
First, prove that
this is the real
Verse of King of Poison.
I can recite the whole book.
It is etched in my brain.
Proving it will be easy.
How?
The Brigitte silkworm poison technique
you are good at
is recorded in Master's book.
Master wrote
that the poison is one of the three
types of poison of the Miaojiang people.
It is a colourless and odourless
powder that is hard to detect
when applied to any object.
However, the poison isn't strong
and can be cured
when it doesn't
come in contact with the body.
But when it comes in contact
with the body,
it will be fatal.
However, nothing is perfect.
When the powder
is applied to the human body,
a slight green colour will appear.
In the book, Master mentioned
it's not hard to apply the powder
to a human body
yet not show its colour.
Nonsense.
Even the Miaojiang people
who are the ancestors of using poison
have no such method.
Your master knew nothing
since he had never been
to Miaojiang.
Of course, he went to Miaojiang before.
He rescued me from Miaojiang.
Master's book does mention this.
Do you want to know about it?
Interesting.
Tell me what the method is.
I'm sure you won't believe me.
You just need to try it.
How do I try it?
Apply Brigitte silkworm poison powder
on someone.
I will mix it with medicine
and see if the green colour appears.
You.
Come here.
Master.
Don't be fooled by her.
Give me your hand.
I...
Master, I beg you.
You dare defy me?
I will kill you right now.
No.
Master.
I dare not disobey you.
But this girl is tricky.
I'm sure she is up to no good.
There's no need to be fooled.
You are really incredible.
You defied Master's orders
and still act the same
after following a new master.
Shut up!
Master.
Master!
Now, it's all up to you.
What method will you use
to hide the green colour
on his palm?
If you lie to me...
Senior Shi.
I'm sure you have Arsenic
and Peacock's Gallbladder with you.
Do you know that these two medicine
clashes and complements each other
when mixed with
Brigitte silkworm poison powder?
Mixing Peacock's Gallbladder,
Arsenic and Brigitte silkworm egg
will create a slow-working
colourless and odourless poison.
Indeed.
Lingsu!
I beg you.
Give me the antidote.
(Verse of King of Poison)
In Master's book, it is said
that when the Brigitte silkworm poison,
(Verse of King of Poison)
Peacock's Gallbladder
and Arsenic are mixed,
the poison will strike the heart
and it's incurable.
I'm in pain!
Save me!
I know
Master will have a way
of curing this poison when he left it.
Save me.
Your evil deeds
make even the Gods angry.
I'm punishing you for the sect.
Lingsu.
I was wrong.
Xiaotie is dead.
I only have
your Eldest Senior left in this world.
I beg you.
Since we are from the same sect,
please save Eldest Senior.
I'll kowtow to you.
I beg you.
You'll die if you move.
Master.
I've helped you retrieve
the Verse of King of Poison.
Master.
Put these three types of poison
on her palm
and see if she can cure herself.
This method is smart.
Fei!
Are you not going to listen to me?
You don't even keep your promises
in an urgent situation.
I was too impatient.
I didn't keep our promise.
But how can I see them hurting you
without doing anything?
Brigitte silkworm poison.
Heartbreak grass.
Arsenic.
All of them can be cured.
But when they are used together...
Lingsu.
Is this poison incurable?
Don't move.
Here.
You shouldn't be too sad.
Our deaths are fated.
However,
you will be alone from now on.
I can no longer accompany you.
Actually,
being with you
in Medicine King Valley
has been the happiest times
of my life.
Lingsu.
I...
I want to...
Fei.
I know.
You have been thinking about
the Epiphyllum.
But you don't know
how much I wanted
to become the Epiphyllum.
I finally understand now
what it means
to have the flower bloom
and wilt in a moment.
For that moment,
everything will be worth it.
Fei,
when I'm not around,
the Seven Pistil Chaenomeles sinensis
will accompany you in your place.
I just fed you
a paralysis medicine.
If I didn't do that,
you wouldn't allow me
to suck the poison out for you.
Don't feel sad for me.
Actually,
I was already poisoned.
Just like
the Seven Pistil Chaenomeles sinensis,
the thing you love the most
is also the most poisonous.
I don't regret it.
Since you helped me sincerely,
I can't let you waste your energy
for nothing.
I'll give you two flowers.
Why are you dressing like a bride?
Look at yourself.
You look like a groom too.
I, Cheng Lingsu.
I, Hu Fei.
Will become sworn siblings today.
From today onwards,
we share our blessings
and misfortune together.
Anyone who breaks the promise
will be punished.
♪Burning tears running down the cheeks♪
♪But this turned out to be a dream♪
Master said
those who are poisoned by this
can never be cured
because he knew
no physician
in this world
is willing to sacrifice their own life
to save a patient.
But you are
not a patient to me
but my...
Brother.
The candle
is made by the pistil of
Seven Pistil Chaenomeles sinensis.
Seven Pistil Chaenomeles sinensis
might be the king of poison
it can also counteract any poison
and remove
the two types of poison
inside your body.
♪The gentle breeze
raises a shroud of mist♪
♪If one wishes not to see♪
♪One will be dazed at night♪
♪Don't ask where we will return to♪
♪Still watching you chasing love♪
♪My heart flutters as well♪
Fei.
Remember the thing you promised me.
You've never listened to me.
This time.
You must listen to me.
When you wake up,
live your life well
for me.
We made a pinky swear.
You must not break your promise.
Actually,
you look nice with a beard.
I want to see
what you look like with a beard again.
Unfortunately,
I won't be able to see.
Ruolan, be careful.
Don't touch it with your hand.
Mother, I know.
Brother Hu.
The Seven Pistil Chaenomeles Sinensis
grows taller again.
Come.
Father.
Mother.
Uncle Miao.
(Golden Face Buddha,
Miao Renfeng's Grave)
Fei has come to visit you.
(Legend of Liaodong,
Hu Yidao and Wife's Grave)
(Golden Face Buddha,
Miao Renfeng's Grave)
(Legend of Liaodong,
Hu Yidao and Wife's Grave)
(Sworn Sister, Cheng Lingsu's Grave)
Lingsu.
I helped you wipe out the sect's evil people.
(Sworn Sister, Cheng Lingsu's Grave)
Mother.
Why was father
buried here?
Because here lies
your father's best friend.
They will accompany each other.
I'm sure they are
sparring and chatting
while drinking wine
in another place.
(Golden Face Buddha,
Miao Renfeng's Grave)
Brother Hu.
Do you miss Sister Cheng?
What is the flower
carved on this jade token?
Why do you always carry it?
An Epiphyllum is carved on it.
Have you heard about
the story of the
Epiphyllum blooming just for Veda?
Legend has it that
the Epiphyllum was the flower goddess.
It bloomed every day
and it was pretty
during all four seasons.
Until she fell in love
with a young man that always weeded for her.
When the Jade Emperor found out,
he was angry
and broke up their relationship.
He demoted the flower goddess
to a flower
that could only bloom once a year
to stop her from meeting her lover.
He also got the young man
to become a monk at Vulture Peak.
He was given the name Veda
so he could forget the past
and the flower goddess.
But the flower goddess
couldn't forget the young man.
She knew Veda would hike up the peak
to gather flower dew
during late spring every year.
So, she chose to bloom at that moment.
The flower goddess
gathered her beauty for a whole year
and chose to bloom at that moment
because she wanted
to make Veda remember some of his past.
The Epiphyllum is so pitiful.
I hope both of them
don't miss out on each other again.
(The end)
♪Life passes by♪
♪In the blink of an eye♪
♪My heart is tied up♪
♪By the unintentional worry♪
♪What does the future hold?♪
♪Hopefully, all wishes will be fulfilled♪
♪What brings us together?♪
♪Why are we going separate ways?♪
♪I can never express love
and hate in words♪
♪Going through all the winters in our lives♪
♪Disposing of the unfulfilled wishes♪
♪And keeping them all to myself♪
♪Love only lasts so briefly♪
♪Who do I waste my time for?♪
♪Life is already full of debts♪
♪So let's not dwell on the little time we have♪