=Side Story Of Fox Volant=
(Adapted from Jin Yong's novel)
=Episode 34=
Thank you for saving
both my sons, Venerable.
They were rescued
by my disciples.
They are obviously
the ones who abducted the two princes.
Your Honor. I heard it myself.
She even called her senior.
The All-knowing Nun.
I'm sure you dare not admit
the fact that she is your disciple.
Venerable, is that the case?
Official Fu.
It's indeed as they say.
She is my disciple, Sang Feihong indeed.
Venerable.
You planted someone
in Official Fu's residence
and you also have
someone else on the outside
to abduct Official Fu's sons.
What ulterior motive do you have?
Exactly.
They caused Yiming's death.
Your Honor, you must
help set things straight for me!
Feihong.
Explain it yourself.
We need to split up
after entering the capital.
You need to be careful
since you're alone outside.
If you get captured,
do you know what you should do?
Please instruct me, Master.
I came here
to the capital on Master's orders
to bring medicine for Old Madam.
I was supposed to return
to Tianshan
after I brought the medicine
but Master insisted me to stay.
She said Official Fu organised
a Sect Leaders' Gathering
to reorganise
the martial arts sects' status
in the martial arts world
which is a good thing
for the martial arts world.
But Official Fu's action
will affect some people's benefits.
The residence hasn't been safe recently.
Master thought
something fishy was going on
so she suspected the problem originated
from the Commander's Residence.
However, she needed
to protect Old Madam
and couldn't investigate it
so she sent me to investigate in secret
because I was a stranger here
and wouldn't attract attention.
When I was
investigating yesterday night,
I realised someone abducting
the two princes in the residence.
Senior was pursuing them
but a young man rushed out
from the Commander's Residence
to intercept Senior
so I went to help her.
After that, when I went
with Senior to pursue the culprits,
she told me
the people who got abducted
were Official Fu's sons.
You are lying!
All of you abducted little princes
so my son Yiming
went to chase after you!
Let her finish.
This is their conspiracy, Your Honor.
After that, Senior and I
finally caught up
to the people who abducted little princes
and fought with them.
They have prestigious statuses.
After we got them back,
Senior took them away.
I was not strong enough.
I lost to them
and got captured.
Master.
I have embarrassed you.
Your Honor.
They were the ones
who abducted the Princes.
They are trying to shift the blame away.
Yes!
They knew they were going to be exposed
so they blamed us.
Nonsense!
It was all of you who did it.
Besides,
why do I need to abduct
the little princes?
Why?
You...
You abducted them
to threaten Official Fu.
My master is responsible
for Old Madam's safety.
Isn't it better to threaten Official Fu
with Old Madam?
Why should we do this?
The Tianshan Sect and
Red Flower Club are working together.
You abducted little princes
to give Red Flower Club.
I don't know
why both of you need
to abduct the two princes.
My disciple, Sang Feihong,
also didn't know
what happened here.
But I found out
you have a deep relationship
with the fugitive, Hu Fei.
You spent a lot of money
to get him on your side
and invited him to a banquet.
You even gave him a residence.
A fugitive can enter the residence
as easily as entering an empty space.
I'm sure all of you are behind this.
In that case,
Hu Fei is definitely related
to Red Flower Club.
I remember now!
Two days ago,
I saw them reading a letter
when I was patrolling
the Sect Leaders' Courtyard at night.
They were discussing something
when they read the letter.
I remember vaguely
there was a red picture
on the envelope.
I didn't see clearly
because I was too far.
What are you talking about?
Zhou Tiejiao.
Yes!
Take someone and search Tang Pei's room.
Yes.
Your Honor.
You must not believe their words.
Even if you find the letter,
I'm sure they planted it there.
Why are you so nervous?
It's just a search in your room.
Does your room
really have something you can't show me?
Your Honor, no!
Definitely not!
Your Honor,
if you're going to search my room,
I must follow them.
This old nun has been
in the residence for many days.
What if she bribed everyone?
Also,
her room needs to be searched too.
Perhaps we can find something strange.
Sure.
Hailan Bi.
Go with them.
Yes, Your Honor.
Ziyi.
Go with them as well.
Let them search thoroughly.
Yes.
Suit yourself.
Official Tang.
What else can be searched
in the Nun's room?
Official Hai.
You still need to search it nonetheless.
Young Lady Yuan.
It's inconvenient
for us to search the Nun's room.
Sorry to trouble you.
Besides Master's clothing,
the Ruyi and jade beads
were given to her by Old Madam.
The western clock
was given by Official Fu.
There's nothing else.
You can search around.
Official Hai.
There's nothing else
in the Nun's room
apart from this bundle
that Young Lady Yuan opened.
Let's go.
Official Hai.
Take a look.
What can be hidden in my room?
That's right.
This is the drawing Official Fu gave me.
Why don't you take a look?
Chief Tang.
You shouldn't do this.
According to what you said,
the three of us
might be bribed by the Nun.
To avoid any arousing suspicions,
we can't
search your room.
Official Hai.
Sorry to trouble you.
We will be waiting outside.
Yes!
Chief Tang.
(Wangwu Sect, Wuliang Sword Sect)
What is this?
I don't know.
Great, Chief Tang.
The Sect Leaders' Gathering
has yet to start
and you are already working together
with all sect leaders in private.
You even arranged everything
from the result
until the cup everyone will hold.
I...
Official Hai.
The Jade Dragon Cup...
What?
Besides the Golden Dragon Cup
and the Silver Dragon Cup,
are you even trying to
manipulate the Jade Dragon Cup?
Official Hai, the Jade Dragon Cup...
You are really daring.
Have you manipulated something
that Official Fu can't even decide?
How much money did you receive?
Official Hai.
I also did it
because I thought about Official Fu.
It won't be nice
if they were to fight for real.
I want to make some money
but everyone involved
will get a cut as well.
Official Hai.
You know how loyal I am to Official Fu.
For so many years,
I...
I have no other intentions.
How is it possible for me
to get involved with Red Flower Club?
How dare you!
Since you made a decision
behind Commander's back,
you probably dare to do more than that.
Search thoroughly!
Yes!
Official Hai.
Chief Tang.
What is this?
An incense burner.
Is it used to burn paper?
Take it back and examine it thoroughly.
Yes.
All right. Let's go.
Official Tang.
You are already guilty of a crime
with this ledger alone.
Your Honor.
(To Miao Renfeng only)
(Miao's Entourage)
Tang Pei.
How do you explain yourself this time?
What was written on that letter?
Your Honor.
I'm wronged!
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Your Honor.
This nun must have planted this
to frame me.
Your Honor, I...
Chief Tang.
The evidence is here.
Are you still not going to admit it?
The two princes know.
Yes.
Your Honor.
The two princes
must know who abducted them.
They can prove my innocence.
Your Honor, it's already late.
Both princes were terrified.
I'm afraid...
Bring both of them here.
Tonight,
I want to find out the truth tonight.
Yes.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Your Honor.
Pingping. An'an.
Come here.
Tell me.
Is the person who abducted you
among these people?
Little prince.
Tell your father
who abducted you two.
Tell me. Who was it?
I will get revenge for you.
- It was him.
Your Honor, I'm wronged!
I'm wronged!
Your Honor.
My son, Yiming, got himself killed
to rescue both of them.
Who is it?
Who is trying to frame me?
Capture them!
No!
Feihong.
Kill him!
Feng Tiannan?
Who are you?
Hu Fei?
I said it.
Even if I go to the end of the earth,
I will still kill you.
Fourth Uncle Zhong!
Mrs. Zhong!
Er!
San!
And everyone
who was bullied by you in Foshan!
Chase him down!
Your Honor.
I can't believe
there are so many ways to make money
using the Sect Leaders' Gathering.
In terms of making money,
Tang Pei is
really smarter than anyone else.
Yes.
Even if I crack my brain,
I can't even come up with
half as many ideas as them.
Let's go.
Go and report to Official Fu.
Yes.
(Ministry of Justice Prison)
Everyone.
You must help me.
How would I
collude with Red Flower Club?
Official Tang.
All of us believe you.
But Official Fu...
Also, he is still
angry because of that incident.
All of you.
I'm wronged.
Since Red Flower Club knows about this,
they won't give up easily.
They will definitely cause trouble
at the Sect Leaders' Gathering.
Everyone.
If you make the necessary preparations,
you'll be able
to achieve something great.
Then,
I will be proven innocent
regarding my relationship
with Red Flower Club.
Official Tang.
Your analysis is reasonable.
Well,
we will try our best
to persuade Official Fu
not to handle your case immediately.
We'll leave everything until
the Sect Leaders' Gathering is over.
What do you think?
Thank you!
Once the Sect Leaders' Gathering is over,
the truth will finally come to light.
Official Tang, calm down.
Official Fu would have killed you
if he wanted you dead.
Since he locked you up,
there must still be a chance.
We will definitely help you.
Thank you!
That's enough, Official Tang.
Go inside.
Everyone, you must help me!
Tiejiao.
I think Tang Pei is right.
Red Flower Club
will definitely cause trouble
during the Sect Leaders' Gathering.
If we help him,
we will reap the rewards.
Yes, Tiejiao.
I heard Tang Pei
has many assets outside.
Both of you are too greedy.
Even if Tang Pei
is not related to Red Flower Club,
what about Hu Fei?
Since Hu Fei
has been exposed today,
Official Fu will surely investigate it.
Right now,
it seems the relationship
between Hu Fei and Red Flower Club
is confirmed.
But Tang Pei
is supposed to know everything.
Why did he still lie to us
and want us to win over Hu Fei?
He is setting us up.
Once the Sect Leaders' Gathering is over
and Tang Pei is proven innocent,
he will push the blame
of Hu Fei's incident to us.
Then, we'll
be in deep trouble.
With Official Fu's personality,
do you think
we can still live a good life?
Tiejiao, what should we do?
The culprits of winning over Hu Fei
are Tang Pei and Feng Tiannan.
When both of them are dead,
we can
tell the Commander
that we were lied to
and let them take
all the responsibilities.
This jerk
still dares to threaten us now?
He really doesn't know his place.
Prepare a feast for him.
No matter what,
we were still comrades in the past.
Understood.
Did you ask him?
What is Tang Pei's relationship
with Red Flower Club?
He wouldn't admit anything.
He shifted all the blame
to Feng Tiannan.
In the past few years,
Tang Pei has been good.
He might not be very loyal
but he fulfilled his responsibilities.
If he is really working
with Red Flower Club,
what is your opinion about that?
Official Hai.
Official Fu.
I'm not close to Tang Pei.
But after the search yesterday,
I think he is a greedy person.
He dared to do so many things
behind your back
for his own benefit.
I'm sure he dares to do something worse.
You are close to Tang Pei.
Even if you are not involved
in what he was doing behind my back,
you should also know about it.
I want you to be honest.
Forgive me, Your Honor.
We might be used by Tang Pei.
Tell me!
After Feng Tiannan arrived
at the capital,
Tang Pei wanted us to win over Hu Fei.
He told us Hu Fei
had a grudge against Feng Tiannan
and Feng Tiannan
wanted to become friends with him
so he asked us
to organise a banquet for Hu Fei
and gave him a residence.
Your Honor, we really don't know
Hu Fei is a member of Red Flower Club.
Please investigate thoroughly.
Official Fu, since Tang Pei
is involved with Red Flower Club,
he should be killed.
Stand.
I got some results from my investigation
regarding Hu Fei's involvement
with Red Flower Club.
The true culprits
are indeed Tang Pei and Feng Tiannan.
Since you mentioned it yourself,
I will believe
the fact that you were being lied to.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Thank you, Your Honor!
You...
Don't worry.
It's not time to kill you yet.
You poisoned me?
I don't have to poison you
if I want to kill you.
These jerks!
I came to find you
because of injustice
from many years ago.
Do you still remember Yuan Yingu?
13 years ago,
a pitiful woman
brought her daughter
out of Foshan
and begged along her way.
When she was almost dying of hunger,
she was saved by
the Blessing of Seven Provinces
who gave her porridge.
To repay you,
she went to work in your residence.
When she settled down
and thought
her life would be getting better,
she saw her old enemy
at your residence.
The bully of Foshan, Feng Tiannan.
That was when she found out
both of you have been colluding
to do many evil things.
Who would have thought
the respectable person
in the martial arts world,
Young Hero Tang,
who was also known as
the Blessing of Seven Provinces
had another secret identity?
You committed so many crimes
that it was hard to list them out.
Unfortunately,
you discovered Yuan Yingu
who was hiding outside the window.
You were afraid
that she might expose you
and hurt your reputation
in the martial arts world
so you killed my mother.
After my mother died,
you wouldn't even spare my life
when I was only seven years old.
You sold me to a human trader
and wanted me to become a prostitute.
You always appear in public looking kind
but you don't know
what goes around comes around.
If I knew this would happen,
I should have
killed you as well back then.
You ended up like this
because of all the evil things
you did in the past.
You...
Darn it!
Even Tang Pei
was bribed by Red Flower Club.
I was also shocked
when I found out about this.
Red Flower Club
is everywhere
around us.
Seems like the manipulated sect leader
and Jade Dragon Cup
should be given to one of our own.
Your Majesty, do you have
a sect leader in your mind?
Hailan Bi.
Yes.
You are from Liaodong.
I'll grant you the position of
sect leader of Heilong Sect of Liaodong.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty is wise.
With Official Hai,
I believe
the Sect Leaders' Gathering
will progress smoothly.
All of you may leave.
Yes.
We'll be leaving.
(Tianlong Sect)
Who is
this Manager Sai?
Why did he come here without notice?
Apparently, he was under Official Hai
from the Firearm Brigade.
He was appointed by the Commander
as the tournament's manager.
Your Honor, enjoy.
I'm sorry for being late
in welcoming Manager Sai's arrival.
Please forgive me, Your Honor.
Isn't this Chief Tian?
I came here to visit
because of Commander's orders.
One who does not know isn't guilty.
You are too polite, Chief Tian.
I wonder what orders
the Commander has for me.
I will do my best to cooperate with him.
I'm relieved
to hear that.
I came here to talk to Chief Tian
about the Jade Dragon Cup.
I'm sure you know about
Tang Pei's public execution
because of his rebellion.
Yes.
Tang Pei was supposed to be
the one who manipulated
the eight great sect leaders.
After what happened,
the Commander is fearful
of everyone's loyalty.
Hence,
he cancelled
the manipulated qualification
and changed it to fair competition
through martial arts sparring.
So,
Chief Tian's Jade Dragon Cup
has to be won with your abilities.
Of course.
As compensation,
Chief Tian can skip the preliminaries
and enter the finals directly
to fight for the Jade Dragon Cup.
I believe
Chief Tian's martial arts
are good enough to win
the Jade Dragon Cup.
Yes.
Official Zeng.
What do you think?
Official Sai is right.
Tianlong Sect's martial arts are strong
and Tianlong Sect has a 100-year-old history.
Your sect will surely perform
and surpass everyone else
during the tournament.
All right.
I've done the things
Commander ordered me.
I need to return to the capital
and prepare for the tournament
so I will be leaving.
Let's meet again
when Chief Tian is in the capital.
Farewell.
Farewell, Your Honor.
♪Life passes by♪
♪In the blink of an eye♪
♪My heart is tied up♪
♪By the unintentional worry♪
♪What does the future hold?♪
♪Hopefully, all wishes will be fulfilled♪
♪What brings us together?♪
♪Why are we going separate ways?♪
♪I can never express love
and hate in words♪
♪Going through all the winters in our lives♪
♪Disposing of the unfulfilled wishes♪
♪And keeping them all to myself♪
♪Love only lasts so briefly♪
♪Who do I waste my time for?♪
♪Life is already full of debts♪
♪So let's not dwell on the little time we have♪