[English subtitles are available]
As long as I can take over the Ning'an Palace,
I'm willing to pay any price.
[Ning'an Palace]
Cleanse the court of traitors and sycophants.
The cinnabar imperial brush decides life and death.
Everything
is like a dream.
I once wronged a lot of people.
Zhang Zhe, please help me.
I'll be a good person after this.
I'll marry the one I spoil.
There are things
you can't give me,
but he can.
I want to live.
Only you can help me.
Everyone in the world has the right to run away.
But I don't.
I want to do my best
to make up for the mistakes and regrets in the past.
Do you believe in the previous life, Mr. Zhang?
I'd rather believe what's right in front of me.
Welcome, Your Majesty.
Congratulations on returning to our homeland.
Ning, what are you afraid of?
But in the stars,
there is always an invisible hand,
putting everything back to where it was.
Now that you've taken your revenge.
In the end, who are you?
A bustling place, or a battle ground.
A life of absurdity, a story of mistakes and regrets.
[Story of Kunning Palace]
[Episode 6]
Not to mention being a consort,
even if you become the empress,
you won't be able to enjoy it.
My Lady.
Be careful with your words.
Ning,
your mother has always been so straightforward.
She's like this only because she cares about you.
You should know
what kind of a place the imperial palace is.
It's a place where you can be punished for anything.
So, no matter what you do,
be careful with your words and actions.
You should really
adjust your temper.
Don't fight about anything.
Without us around,
safety should come first.
I'm tired.
I'm going back to my room.
Okay, go get some rest.
Miss.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
You may leave now.
Call us if you need anything.
We'll be outside.
Wait.
Are you the girl that was outside Baiguo Temple that day?
I accidentally found out about
the first encounter between Jiang Xuehui and Shen Jie.
I pretended to be Jiang Xuehui
and took everything from her.
Still, I ended up like that.
Maybe Mother was right.
It's my personality
and my inappropriate greed
that led to the ending.
But this time,
I want to change it.
But why is everyone pushing me?
No matter how hard I try,
there is always an invisible hand,
putting everything
back to where it was.
What about Yan Lin and Zhang Zhe?
Will they end up like that again?
No.
It shouldn't be like that.
Jiang Xuening.
You can't give up.
There must be a way to make a new path.
There must be.
The Xue family has got their hands on the Yan family,
and I only got to know about it now.
Is this how you did your job?
Please punish us, Sir. Please.
What are you doing?
It's not all their fault.
There are so many people in Xingwu Guards.
Zhou's background is not prominent.
He used to be a stableman.
In the past,
we wouldn't have paid attention to him.
A stableman?
Yes.
He was just a stableman.
He's the one
who came from the countryside
with Second Young Lady from the Mansion of Vice Minister Jiang.
By the way,
didn't you two
[Four years ago]
come to the capital together back then?
You don't know Zhou?
He comes from a humble family and is good at fawning upon the rich and the powerful.
This kind of people are usually skilled.
I'm going to the Yan Mansion tomorrow
to meet him in person.
By the way,
didn't you ask Dao Qin
to check the situation in Jinling?
Guess what happened?
Cut the crap.
It's Deputy Gong Yi.
That old man.
Ever since you left,
he's been badmouthing you to His Highness a lot.
But somehow,
he got His Highness's order
and was coming to the capital.
It was him
who sent someone to assassinate you.
He was giving you a warning
to not forget who you are.
Who is he to tell me who I am?
Bring it on.
I want to see
if he can make it back alive.
There are no decent plants in my garden.
Sorry to bore you, Ning.
Why don't you plant some Nerium oleander?
It looks gorgeous, but it's actually very poisonous.
It fits the scene well.
Yes.
Ning.
Zhou is good at martial arts after all.
He's a rare matching opponent to me.
He could fight with you
because others dared not fight with you.
What did I tell you?
Qing Feng.
I asked him to get some wine.
Why is it taking him so long?
Right.
I'll go take a look.
Enjoy yourselves.
Enjoy.
If I remember it correctly,
I have reminded you last time
not to mess with Yan Lin, Mr. Zhou.
Are you determined to get involved in this mess?
Miss, you must have heard of this saying.
The tree may long for calmness, but the wind will not subside.
Even if I don't do it,
there must be Wang Yinzhi,
Zhao Yinzhi, or Li Yinzhi who would do it.
Miss.
I knew you were coming today,
so I stayed here last night.
I just wanted to see you.
Please enlighten me.
How should I solve
this doomed situation?
The Xue family
wants to forge the evidence
of the Yan family colluding with Lord Pingnan,
right?
His Majesty is quite intimidated by Lord Pingnan.
If the Xue family wants to overthrow the Yan family,
it must be some serious crime that can take the whole family down.
The Yan family has been loyal for generations.
They couldn't get what they want.
That's why I thought
they'd want to forge evidence.
You're so smart. I'm ashamed of my inferiority.
I've obeyed you
and stopped stealing
or looking for His Lordship's seal and handwriting anymore.
But Duke of Xue just wouldn't let me go.
I thought
I could fool him with some casual handwriting.
But who would expect that
I would find something huge?
What is it?
Are you sure you were not mistaken?
I work for the Xingwu Guards.
That…
I've seen Lord Pingnan's emblem too many times.
How could I be mistaken?
Miss,
this is a serious matter.
I should have reported it.
But if Duke of Xue knows about this,
the Yan family will be punished for sure.
I am also destined
to be killed since I've outlived my usefulness.
So, Miss,
please tell me
what I should do next.
I can't take your salute.
As you can see,
I want to help the Yan family.
But like you,
I'm also a nobody.
It's okay for nobodies to work together for profit.
Although I have nothing now,
it's easy for me
to kill you.
Do you believe it?
Yes.
If you tell the Yan family about this,
they can take my life thousands of times.
That's right.
You may not be able to enjoy
what the Xue family promised you.
Besides, what you saw was just fragments of the emblem.
You don't know what's written in the letter.
I believe
the Yan family has no intention to rebel.
There must be some other explanation.
Anyway,
don't let anyone know
about the burnt letter.
Yes.
It's mainly about Duke of Xue.
If they want to forge it,
they'll need Marquis of Yan's handwriting and seal.
The handwriting is easier to get.
It's easy to find on the memorials.
You can fool them with some copybook
and buy some time.
But it's not a long-term solution.
The one who started the trouble is the one who should solve it.
You are right about one thing.
Even if it's not you,
there will be someone else
who will tell Yan Lin
everything you found out.
It's time for him
to grow up.
Your Highness.
-Where is the wine? -Your Highness.
-Where's the wine? -We have a guest.
Sir.
I didn't know you'd come suddenly.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't matter.
There's no need to stand on ceremony in your residence.
It's already past mid autumn.
Why haven't the flowers of this tree bloomed yet?
This tree was planted by my aunt
before she got married.
Twenty years ago, my aunt passed away.
The leaves started withering.
Since then, its flowers have never bloomed again,
as if it were dead.
Are you here for my father, Sir?
Father went to the military camp.
He might be back late. How about taking a rain check?
Why do you
smell like charcoal?
Are you having a barbecue in the garden?
Excuse me.
It seems I came at the right time.
Speaking of which,
I haven't had game meat for years.
May I join you?
What's wrong with Xie Wei?
Why did he come to the Yan Mansion for no reason?
Now that he saw me with Zhou Yinzhi,
I don't know what trouble he'll cause.
My goodness, you're still eating?
Get him out of here.
We're not friends.
Why do we have to eat together?
Your Highness,
there's not much meat left.
How about I go to the kitchen and get some more for you?
I'll be back soon.
Why are you so irritable?
Our fearless Ning
is afraid of Mr. Xie?
I wonder what will happen in class in the future.
Eat your meat.
Ning,
is this how you treat Viscount Yan?
-It's okay. -Mr. Xie, don't get me wrong.
Yan Lin and I are best friends.
He likes hot food.
Right?
Come on.
Drink some wine.
Don't burn your tongue.
Ning.
Don't you know drinking is bad for health?
Since you're friends,
you should be beneficial to each other.
You don't even know that?
Yes.
You're right, Sir.
I'll drink.
It will only hurt my body, okay?
Ning.
I don't know what's wrong with her today.
She's so drunk.
Ning.
Why don't you stay here for one night?
I want to go home.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
I have something
to ask Mr. Jiang about.
I can send Miss Ning
back to the Jiang Mansion.
In that case,
I'll leave her to you, Sir. Thanks.
Let's go.
Are you done pretending?
Get up if you're done.
You are so insightful.
I feel ashamed.
You know Zhou Yinzhi well?
You're mistaken, Sir.
We don't know each other well.
Think carefully before you answer.
Have you forgotten, Sir?
He was with us
when we came to the capital.
We were separated when we got robbed halfway.
Later, we finally got out of the wilderness.
[Four years ago]
It was Zhou Yinzhi and the Jiang family
who found us.
So,
of course there's some friendship between us.
Just a little bit.
What he wants to do now
has nothing to do with me.
You know what he wants to do?
To help the Xue family take down the Yan family.
I have persuaded him today.
He won't do anything to the Yan family anymore.
I can let myself believe that
you have no intention to harm Yan Lin.
But the court disputes are not as simple as you think.
I don't care what your relationship with Zhou Yinzhi
or who the person behind him is,
but I hope you'll stay out of this.
Otherwise,
your survival is threatened
even without me trying to kill you.
I have to ask you as well, Sir.
What is your relationship with Yan Lin?
What do you mean?
You come from the Xie family in Jinling.
You have nothing to do with the Yan family.
In the capital,
you seem to have no connections with the Yan family,
but you took care of Yan Lin repeatedly.
And now that Zhou Yinzhi showed up,
you even investigated it yourself.
I dare to guess
the secret you want to hide is related to the Yan family.
What does it have to do with you?
Yan Lin is also my friend.
Just like you,
I don't want to see him in danger.
Jian Shu.
Sir.
Follow them.
Yes.
I'll ask someone to send you back.
You didn't see anything
that happened today.
Zhou.
Why are you still here?
Your Highness,
I have something to tell you.
What happened?
I, Zhou Yinzhi, am a despicable person
who's greedy for power and profit.
I approached Your Highness
because I was ordered by Xingwu Guards
to investigate the evidence
of Lord Pingnan's collusion with the Yan family.
I failed your trust.
Please punish me severely.
Zhou Yinzhi.
Why did you
choose to tell me at this time?
It's Miss Jiang.
Miss Jiang and I go way back.
She saw through me
when we met today.
She was worried about your safety,
so she asked me to tell you everything.
Ning.
It's Ning.
You've treated me so well, Your Highness.
I am really grateful to you.
So if the Yan family
is not involved with Lord Pingnan at all,
I won't make up a false testimony.
But recently,
when I investigated the Yan family in secret,
I found that His Lordship did have contact via letters
with the remnants of Lord Pingnan's rebels.
I wonder if you know that, Your Highness.
What did you say?
You came at the right time.
Try this wine.
It was just delivered from the north.
You had a fight with Xuening?
Father,
do you know
the Xingwu Guards are investigating
the remnants of Lord Pingnan's rebels in secret?
People are saying that
this case is related to the Yan family.
What should come
will come.
After 20 years,
I still can't forget it.
Those who did bad things
won't be able to forget either.
Do you remember your cousin Xue Dingfei?
You've told me stories about him since I was young, Father.
You said that Lord Pingnan
rebelled 20 years ago.
In order to protect His Majesty,
Cousin was killed by Lord Pingnan.
Father.
Is there some other reason for my cousin's death?
I don't know.
It's just I received a letter from Lord Pingnan.
It said that
Dingfei's not dead.
He's in his hands.
How is that possible?
Lord Pingnan is a rebel.
They have wild ambitions.
They said that to perturb you.
They were obviously trying to sow discord between the Yan Family and the Xue family
to perturb His Majesty, Father.
If His Majesty is discerning,
no one can perturb him.
Rumors are just rumors.
But
those who did bad things 20 years ago
were not the Yan family,
but the Xue family.
I've burned the letter from Lord Pingnan.
But
the letter in which I asked for his whereabouts
got in their hands.
The rumors in the capital
didn't come out of nowhere.
Why were you tricked into this, Father?
This is your cousin.
How could I not ask about him?
Back then,
before your aunt passed away,
she held my hand.
She was so sick that she couldn't speak.
She could only look at me with those eyes
[Xue Dingfei's mother, Yan Min]
and she kept crying.
Even when she swallowed her last breath,
she couldn't close her eyes.
In the great State of Qian,
how could they push a seven-year-old child out
to face the cruelest sword?
Is this
fair?
Some things
should be known by you now.
[Baiyun Hall]
Sir, it's all clear now.
He's inside.
Do we need more people?
No.
[Baiyun Hall]
You're here.
Should I call you Mr. Xie,
[Lord Pingnan's counsellor, Deputy Gong Yi]
or Dujun, the Hermit?
Mr. Gong Yi.
I haven't seen you in a while.
How is His Highness?
You still remember him?
I thought that
you've long forgotten about your identity
since you've been in the land of wealth and tenderness at the capital.
And you've forgotten what His Highness told you
when you insisted on coming to the capital four years ago.
Those are some heavy words.
What I've done in the capital these years
is all under His Highness' order.
I dare not forget my origin.
How could I be anything
that you said?
The general trend of the court
is in the hands of the Yan and Xue families.
To achieve great things,
His Highness must make them fight.
We arranged spies in the capital
so that we could use their investigation on the rebels
to punish the Yan family for rebelling.
Once the Yan family falls, there will be no leader in the troops.
It'll be the best time for us to take action.
There's no way you don't understand this.
Of course I understand.
I've been planning for years
and making friends with the officials
in the capital just for this.
Nonsense!
If that's the case,
why did you stop the Xingwu Guards from investigating the case?
Instead, you instigated His Majesty to hand this case over to the Ministry of Justice.
You are obviously disloyal.
If you hadn't taken action in the capital
and made the court suspicious,
I wouldn't have to do all this.
But
I'm here today
to ask you a question.
I want to ask you
about the truth of
the assassin of Cengxiao Restaurant.
I said
I would overthrow the rule of Shen Lang.
But if you insist on interfering,
I have no right to stop you, Mr. Gong Yi.
But
I have to tell you.
If you kill our comrades
in the name of His Highness,
I won't sit back and do nothing.
Sir,
the capital
is my territory.
You must be careful
doing things here.
Xie Wei.
Don't forget
your life was saved by His Highness.
If you want to please both sides,
you will only be doomed eternally.
Miss.
Qing Feng from the Yan Mansion is here.
He said
Viscount Yan is not doing well.
They said
you locked yourself in your room.
How much did you drink?
Sorry.
Did I scare you?
Why is it so hot?
I'll go get a doctor.
Ning.
Don't go.
♫Time flies and everything's like a dream♫
♫I traveled so far but still can't forget you♫
I'm sorry.
♫I spent half my life loving you but ended up being a joke♫
Why are you saying this?
I should be the one
to say sorry.
♫My heart is broken♫
You've treated me so well,
but I failed to do the same for you.
♫But I never regret loving you♫
No.
I was too stupid.
I thought
there was no hardship in this world
that I couldn't overcome.
I also thought
I should let the whole world know that I like you.
But I forgot that
things change.
No one knows what will happen tomorrow.
You didn't have to go to the palace to be a study partner,
but I sent you in.
Now everyone knows
we grew up together.
♫We were too young to know about pain♫
If the Yan family gets in trouble,
what should you,
♫We drank under the moon amidst flowers♫
such a delicate girl, do?
How should you face those rumors?
♫We saw flowers blooming yesterday♫
You didn't ask me
♫And thought they'd still be blooming tomorrow♫
when I knew the Yan family was in trouble,
or how I convinced Zhou Yinzhi.
♫When we were young♫
You didn't suspect that I deceived you and hid it from you,
♫We believed that as long as we could♫
or worry that I'd tell others and hurt you.
♫Hold those warm hands♫
All you thought about is saying sorry to me
♫We could be with our beloved one forever♫
and worrying about my future.
I trust you.
♫Time flies and everything's like a dream♫
From beginning to end,
always.
You're so stupid.
♫I traveled so far but still can't forget you♫
You're the dumbest person in the world.
Because you're Ning.
♫I spent half my life loving you but ended up being a joke♫
You are the person who treats me the best
besides my father.
But it was me who let you know all this.
♫My heart is broken♫
You should have been a carefree viscount.
♫But I never regret loving you♫
No one can live carefreely forever.
I should have grown up.
But it's too late.
No.
You still have me.
Yan Lin.
Let's get through this together.
You will still be the carefree viscount.
OK?
Don't cry.
We won't cry anymore.
OK?
My Lord.
You didn't sleep all night.
Why are you standing here in the wind now?
You may catch a cold.
My Lady.
Look at these fallen leaves.
They seem to rely on the trees,
but as soon as the wind and rain comes,
they'd fall and turn to dust.
Who cares about the life and death of a leaf?
Is something troubling you, My Lord?
No.
I'm just thinking about a bet.
So, have you decided which side to bet on?
No one in this world can be relied on forever.
I came from nothing to now.
What I learned is to bet on both sides.
It's okay if I'm betting on the disadvantaged side or
being used as a tool.
As long as I can win in the end.
Father!
[Long History]
Bad news!
Something happened on the Cao River.
Our silk ship flipped over.
Look at you, panicking like this.
How inappropriate.
Why did the ship
flip over all of a sudden?
On the surface, it was because it rained for days on Cao River,
and our people overloaded it with goods.
So it was an accident.
But in fact,
someone dug a hole under the ship.
So someone wanted the ship to flip over on purpose.
The position and route of our ships have always been a secret.
It's hard for outsiders to figure out.
I'm afraid it was done by an insider.
Find out
who's behind this.
Find him
and get rid of him.
I've sent people to investigate.
Water transport
was a business appointed by the government.
Over the past years, our family
has made acquaintance with a lot of court officials
with the money from water transport.
We also asked some of the
Xingwu Guards to work for us.
If this matter
is found to be related to the Xue family,
His Majesty will be furious.
Now is the crucial moment for the Xue family
to take down the Yan family.
So this matter
must be suppressed.
Father, don't worry.
Leave it to me.
Wait.
Tell Zhou Yinzhi to hurry up.
To take down the Yan family,
it has to be quick.
Yes.
Xie Ju'an.
How can you still have the mood to feed fish?
Deputy Gong Yi has come to our door.
What does it mean?
It means Jinling
has started to be dissatisfied with you.
If they really get irritated
and report…
And report your identity as a traitor,
your life
and my life
will both be over.
What's the use of being afraid?
Yes.
It's useless to be afraid.
But you don't have to irritate
that old man, Deputy Gong Yi, right?
What?
Are you afraid he won't do something to you?
We've been in the capital for four years.
All the spies and secret agents in the city are under our control.
Even if Deputy Gong Yi has the intention to do something,
there's no one he can use.
Besides,
Lord Pingnan still considers me useful.
He won't kill me.
Then what did he
come here for?
The Yan family.
He's anxious to make the court chaotic,
but he was intimidated by the strength of Yan's troops.
So,
he wants to use Duke of Xue to take down the Yan family.
Then why are you so calm?
You would always get anxious
once the Yan family was brought up.
If we can make Duke of Xue only concentrate on his own affairs,
even if Deputy Gong Yi wants to turn the world upside down,
he can't do anything to the Yan family.
[Knowledge and Courtesy]
-Sir. -Sir.
You were right.
What the Xue family wants to hide
is really about water transport.
A few days ago,
the Xue family was joined by the big silk merchants in the capital
to lower the price of raw silk.
When the silk price fell, they secretly bought the silk
then shipped it to Jiangnan to weave.
And then it was transported back to the capital to sell at a high price.
Unexpectedly,
the ship flipped over on the way back.
The business of the Xue family
has always been done anonymously.
That's why we've been investigating them for so long
but we couldn't find evidence of their crimes.
But this time, they worked with the silk merchants to lower the price
and the ship flipped over. It's quite big news.
Since there were more people involved,
there's more evidence.
You two,
go investigate the water transport and silk merchants separately.
As for
you...
As for me,
of course I'll go buy raw silk at a low price
since word hasn't been spread yet.
As the news spreads, the silk price will rise tremendously.
Then we can make a big profit out of it.
Miss.
How long haven't you slept?
I don't know about business.
Thanks to your kindness,
I could learn math and accounting.
I should study harder.
This is the new ledger I prepared for you.
I've marked it so that
it will be easier
and clearer for you.
However,
staying up late to read the ledger
is bad for your health.
You should know when to rest.
It's said that the ledger should be private,
but you showed it all to me.
Are you really not afraid that I might leak it out?
I do business
honestly and conscientiously.
Every penny
is earned legitimately.
I'm not afraid of showing it to people.
Besides,
I judge people
by their hearts.
I know
what kind of person you are.
Thank you, Mr. Xu.
But Miss,
the silk price still hasn't risen.
Aren't you afraid of losing money?
If I lose,
I'll save enough money
and return it to Boss in the future.
You are really loyal
to your boss.
Logically,
the money belongs to Boss.
And it's Boss who asked you to do it.
It should be Boss who's responsible
for the gain and the loss.
Why did you say you'd pay her back if you lose money?
Mr. Xu, you don't know.
She's my savior.
Although
I don't know why she helped me so much,
or why she always
looks at me with such sad eyes,
"receiving drips of water when in need, and I shall return the kindness with a spring".
Since she asked me to do business,
maybe
if I do business well
and make a lot of money for her in the future,
she will be happy.
Mr. Xu.
I didn't tell my family I'd come here today.
I can't stay for long.
I'll leave now.
I'll come another day.
Thank you.
As for my silk,
before the price rises,
don't sell it to anyone.
Thank you.
[Honesty Comes First in Business]
Are you Mr. Xu, Xu Wenyi?
You are?
My surname is Lyu.
My first name is Xian.
[Xie Mansion]
Get out of my way.
Ouch!
Ouch.
It hurts.
What's going on?
Seems like
you failed.
It's half successful.
I'm so unlucky today.
Tell me honestly.
When did the silk ship
flip over on Cao River?
And when did the news first reach the capital?
And who knows about it?
It happened yesterday.
The news has only been in the capital for four hours.
Other than the messenger,
only His Lordship,
you, me, Dao Qin,
and the Xue family at most, know about this.
Impossible.
Someone bought raw silk from Xu Wenyi the day before yesterday
and predicted that the raw silk price would rise.
I tried many times
but Xu Wenyi didn't say much.
But I heard from the guild that
it was a girl who traded with him.
Guess who she is.
She's the illegitimate daughter
from Mansion of Earl of You that no one knows about.
Her name is You Fangyin.
There's a boss
behind this girl.
Unfortunately,
I haven't found out who the boss is.
Jian Shu.
Ask Dao Qin to investigate
the illegitimate daughter from  You Mansion
and the person behind her.
Yes.
You said it was half successful.
What do you mean?
Xu Wenyi
only sold 400 taels of silk.
He kept the rest to himself.
He is smart.
He thought I must be sent by some important official,
so he wanted to get on good terms with me.
He sold the rest of the raw silk to me
at the market price last year.
Good.
The silk price is turbulent this year.
The silkworm raisers suffered a lot.
We are not here for money.
It's okay to make less.
You are generous.
I remember the Yan family's accident
happened at Yan Lin's coming-of-age ceremony.
Now I've ruined Zhou Yinzhi's move in advance
and warned the Yan family to take precautions.
I think things can be changed.
But the Xue family's grudge against the Yan Family wasn't formed in one day.
I need to make more plans
if I want to help the Yan family.
Sister Jiang.
Come on in.
A chef from Yuhang came to our mansion.
He's best at making pastry.
I heard that you grew up in Jiangnan,
so I'm here to share it with you.
Baoying is an expert at eating.
So,
I followed her here to have some.
Its reputation is well deserved.
Compared with those time-honored brands in the capital,
it's as good if not better.
You don't like it, Sister Jiang?
It's delicious.
It's just that
I don't like the sweet taste very much.
No offense.
I knew it.
Even the Empress Dowager likes
the pastry from Baoying's mansion.
Well.
Since you don't like it,
I'll take it.
I only have a small box of it.
Save some for me.
Jiang Xuening.
There's something I want to ask you.