[English subtitles are available]
As long as I can take over Ning'an Palace,
I'm willing to pay any price.
Cleanse the court of traitors and sycophants.
The cinnabar imperial brush determines one's life and death.
Everything
is like a dream.
I once was indebted to a lot of people.
Zhang Zhe, help me.
I'll be a good person after this.
I'll marry the one I spoiled.
There are things
you can't give me.
But he can.
To keep my life,
only you, Sir, can help me.
Everyone in the world is entitled to escape.
But I'm the only one who can't.
I want to do my best to make up for
my past regrets and wrongdoings.
Mr. Zhang, do you believe in predestination from the previous life?
I'd rather believe in what's in front of me.
Welcome, Your Highness.
Congratulations on returning to the capital of our homeland.
Ning'er, what are you afraid of?
But in the unfathomable,
there's always an invisible hand
that puts everything back to its original place.
You've taken revenge and paid your debts.
At the end of the day, who are you?
A bustling place, or a battleground.
A life of absurdity, a story of mistakes and regrets.
[Story of Kunning Palace]
[Episode 36]
Can't you at least play one note right?
I've been playing for hours.
I can't even feel my fingers,
let alone feel the strings.
You only practice when you're in the mood.
I'm afraid even if you keep learning until you're eighty,
you won't be able to play half as well as I do.
Alright.
That's all for today.
Come and sit beside me.
Does it still hurt?
It didn't hurt,
but after I heard you play,
it hurt so much that I doubted it would ever recover.
Now,
you know me inside and out.
You've seen me for who I am
without any disguise.
What do you think?
Are you still afraid of me?
All I know
is that the man in front of me is Xie Ju'an.
Everything else,
whether right or wrong, true or false,
is just water under the bridge.
The past is the past.
What matters is the future.
Do you really think so?
What are you
going to do next?
I heard what Lord Pingnan said before he died.
I'm afraid the capital is no longer safe.
I've reported to the court that Lord Pingnan has been killed.
His Majesty
will leave Yan's troops alone for now.
But we need a long-term solution.
We'll return to the capital sooner or later.
Actually, there's a question I've wanted to ask you.
Will you stage a coup?
Why do you care so much about that?
I'm just worried that you'll land Yan Lin in hot water
and I don't want Her Highness to be upset.
That's all?
What else could it be?
Where are you going?
I'm going to meet Xue Dingfei.
We'll visit someone together.
He liked mung bean cakes.
Bring him some for me.
[Towering Like Mountains, Vast Like the Ocean]
Xiao Bao.
I'm here to see you.
Your master said
[Memorial Tablet of Xiao Bao]
you liked mung bean cakes.
I've brought you some.
I kept saying that I'd teach you to drink,
but I never got to do that.
Look.
I've brought you two jars of good wine.
Don't drink too quickly,
or you'll easily get drunk.
Lord Pingnan has died.
You're a free man now.
What are you going to do next?
To be honest,
I never thought that one day, I could really…
I could really be free of Lord Pingnan's control.
I was just a beggar
like Xiao Bao.
But I was lucky to have been chosen as the substitute
and survived.
Speaking of which,
I should thank Xie Wei.
Back then,
we suffered a lot when we were kids.
Now that Lord Pingnan is dead,
I just want to live a carefree life
and idle away the rest of my life.
It sounds perfect for you.
But Xie Wei is not out of the woods yet.
A tough battle is awaiting him in the capital.
Whether he can survive it
remains to be seen.
Mr. Xie.
The wound has festered.
I need to scrape off the rotting flesh.
I'll get you the narcotic drug.
No need.
Using that drug too often
can cause mental confusion.
I can't let myself waste away anymore.
It's funny
that until recently,
I didn't have the will to live.
Now,
I'm actually afraid of death too.
I want to live longer.
If I die,
who will protect Ning'er?
Your Majesty.
The baby just kicked you.
You're about to give birth,
so don't walk around in your free time anymore.
You need to be careful.
Your Majesty, you're always with Consort Xian
and barely come to me.
I missed you.
Recently, the situation in the court is complicated.
There's trouble both at home and abroad.
Be good.
Our son is the most important.
Do you hear His Majesty?
You're the most important.
My Lady, you can't go in.
Noble Consort Qin
is discussing something with His Majesty now.
You'd better not go in.
Yesterday, His Majesty said he wanted to eat the desserts I made.
I made some and brought them here in a hurry.
Please tell His Majesty
that I'm here.
I…
My Lady, please wait a moment.
Your Majesty.
My Lady.
Consort Xian came with these desserts.
[Imperial Study]
Who?
Consort Xian?
Who does she think she is?
She's Duke Xue's daughter
but has no manners at all!
Your Majesty.
You can't let her interrupt us.
Okay.
Don't be angry. Don't be angry.
It's bad for the baby.
You're more important in my heart.
Tell her to leave. We don't want her here.
My Lady.
His Majesty said…
I heard it.
Thank you, Eunuch Zheng.
I'll take my leave.
My Lady, the desserts…
Do you think
there will still be room for you in the court
after Noble Consort Qin gives birth to an heir?
My Lord.
You guessed right.
She agreed to work on the inside
to help us.
First Young Lady can see what's at stake.
She needs someone to back her up in the court.
Working with us is a win-win.
She has no reason not to agree.
Zhang Zhe
will arrive in Yuzhou very soon.
If he can bring Xie Wei back…
Where is Zhou Yinzhi now?
I've sent for him.
He'll be here soon.
I'm Zhou Yinzhi.
Greetings, My Lord.
How is the investigation going?
My Lord,
I've conducted a thorough search in secret,
but Mr. Dingfei is nowhere to be found.
After making inquiries, I learned
that the last time he was seen,
he was in Cengxiao Restaurant.
That day,
some mysterious people from the south
went to Cengxiao Restaurant too.
No one knows why they were there.
So I suspect
that those people abducted Mr. Dingfei.
My Lord, don't worry.
I'll do my best
and bring him back for you.
No need.
Don't mention
this matter to anyone.
As for Xue Dingfei,
I've got other plans.
Yes.
There's one other thing I want to ask you about.
How much do you know
about Xie Wei?
My Lord, there must be some misunderstanding.
Xie Wei is just a casual acquaintance.
I don't work for him.
I've pledged my loyalty
to you.
So under no circumstances will I betray you.
My Lord, please don't doubt me.
Enough.
I didn't say you work for him.
You had dealings with Xie Wei in the past.
So more or less, you should
know something about him.
You know I need to deal with Xie Wei.
I don't keep useless men.
You know that too.
If you can't be of any help…
I remember now.
All the people Xie Wei cares about have left the capital,
except one person.
[Lyu Mansion]
Yes. There's one person left.
Although she seems ordinary,
she's on good terms with Jiang Xuening.
And Jiang Xuening is very close to Xie Wei.
My Lord,
I promise to get evidence against Xie Wei
out of that person.
Mr. Zhou.
What are you doing?
Madam Lyu.
I apologize for my rudeness.
Mr. Zhou.
You need a proper reason to arrest me.
What have I done wrong?
This is the way Xingwu Guards do things.
No matter what you want to say,
you can say it in the prison.
Take her away.
Wait.
-You have no reason to arrest me!
-Madam!
-Let go of me!
-Madam.
What do you want?
Are you leaving tomorrow?
If I hadn't got injured,
I'd have long left for Yuzhou.
By the way,
thank you for your help.
You seldom say thank you.
I'll just accept your gratitude.
After all, I'm not likely to hear you thank me again.
Have you made up your mind
to part ways with us?
The journey ahead of you is dangerous.
Why should I join you?
Let's say goodbye here.
It's good this way.
I once said
after everything is settled,
you can keep using
the name Xue Dingfei.
But I wonder
if you still want that name now.
Actually, I'm always aware
that the name Xue Dingfei
is a thorn in your side.
You must feel very bad
every time someone calls me that.
Is that the reason
why you don't like me?
When we were young,
it did annoy me.
No wonder you were mean to me those years.
I knew it.
There's no way I was that annoying.
But you were not very likable either.
Don't say it out loud.
It's hurtful.
Xie Wei.
We've been tied to each other for 20 years.
After all those ups and downs,
are we brothers now?
Being my brother
means being in danger.
Aren't you afraid?
I am.
When I was with you,
nothing good happened.
Maybe
I should stay away from you.
After being controlled for 20 years,
you're finally free now.
Let's have a toast with tea.
Here is to
your freedom
and carefree life.
To my freedom.
Father.
I'm glad you got back safely.
Let me see.
How's Ju'an's injury?
Has it almost healed?
Marquis Yan, don't worry.
I'm fine.
Xie Ju'an.
How could you?
How could you put your life at risk like that?
Weren't you afraid…
Of death?
I am now.
Xuening.
You've gone through a lot too.
I failed to protect you that day.
Marquis Yan, please don't say that.
I should thank you.
It was Yan's troops that saved me.
Lord Pingnan and his minions have been eliminated.
I've reported it to the court
and explained everything.
I believe His Majesty
will forgive us
for deploying the troops.
Report!
General.
His Majesty's special envoy, Mr. Zhang Zhe, is here.
What will be will be.
Let's find out
what the imperial edict says.
Mr. Zhang, you came all the way from the capital.
Sorry that I couldn't make time to receive you properly.
Please forgive me.
I'm just here
to convey His Majesty's message.
There's nothing to forgive, Junior Preceptor Xie.
Here is the imperial edict.
By the will of Heaven, His Majesty speaks,
"I'm pleased to know about the great victory at the border.
Marquis Yan and his son led Yan's troops to successfully suppress the rebellion.
On my behalf, Zhang Zhe shall give them commendation
and reward the soldiers.
Junior Preceptor Xie Wei devised brilliant strategies
and made great contributions too.
I'll reward him myself after he returns to the capital."
All hail His Majesty.
General Yan.
The imperial edict is just half the message His Majesty wants to convey.
I'll tell you the other half now.
His Majesty hopes that Junior Preceptor Xie
and Viscount Yan can escort the princess back to the capital
and present yourselves to him.
No matter what grievances you have,
you can tell His Majesty then.
Yan's troops
shall retreat to the border
and continue to defend the State of Qian.
His Majesty cares for every one of you.
Please don't let him down.
I don't mean
to defy His Majesty,
but my wound hasn't healed yet.
I can't set off for the capital immediately.
So, Mr. Zhang,
please stay in Yuzhou for a few days.
Mr. Zhang, you came all the way here
and must be tired.
Stay here for a few days and have a good rest.
It's inconvenient to stay at the camp.
So I've prepared a place in town
where you can stay.
Her Highness is already there.
Why don't you all go to town and have some rest first?
We can
discuss everything else later.
Okay.
Thank you, General Yan.
-Ning.
-Your Highness.
Ning.
Your Highness.
You scared me.
I'm fine, Your Highness.
I came back unscathed.
When you go out in the future, you must bring enough guards with you.
Don't go out alone.
Got it.
I'm Zhang Zhe from the Ministry of Justice. Greetings, Your Highness.
Mr. Zhang?
I'm here on His Majesty's order.
Besides rewarding the troops,
His Majesty also wants you
to return to the capital as soon as possible.
We've all traveled a long way.
Let's get some rest first.
We can get down to business later.
Yes.
There's no rush.
There are enough servants in the mansion.
Let them know if you need anything.
I'll have more soldiers guard this place.
You'll be safe here.
Come.
Let's go.
Ning, tell me everything
you've been through along the way.
It's gonna be a long story.
Then let's talk all night.
I have a lot to tell you after all that's happened.
You almost lost the battle at Guiyi Heights?
We rolled the dice like we did so many times before.
Fortunately,
fate was on our side this time.
Ning, promise me
to stay safe.
Okay. I promise you.
The imperial edict has arrived.
We may go back to the capital very soon.
Are you happy, Your Highness?
When Princess Leyang left the capital,
she had lost all faith in her family.
Now that the State of Yue is no longer a threat
and the northern territories are in the clear,
she's fulfilled her duty.
Now, I'm just Shen Zhiyi.
I've had enough of the royal family's hypocrisy.
If I could,
I'd rather never go back to that cage.
How about you, Ning?
What are you and Mr. Xie gonna do?
I won't comment on his feelings for you.
I'm just a little worried.
You're spontaneous by nature.
But Mr. Xie is the opposite.
He's scheming and manipulative.
Loving such a dangerous man
will be exhausting.
Have you thought it through?
If there had been an easy way,
he wouldn't have chosen a path
that was full of dangers and traps.
You don't know him, Your Highness.
All these years,
life has not been easy for him.
People respect and fear him,
but I feel sorry for him.
I don't know what the future will be like.
All I know is that I don't want him to be alone anymore.
You're in love.
Yes, I am.
Is there anything you can do about it, Your Highness?
If you ask me,
I wish
there were a magic potion that can make you fall out of love.
Once you drink it,
you'll forget everything about him.
When love is gone, so are your worries.
But how can I forget
someone like him?
Your Highness.
Sometimes I wonder
whether I'm wrong.
What do you mean?
A long time ago,
I chose the wrong path,
made many mistakes,
and got what I deserved.
Later, I got a chance to start all over,
so I tried my best to change things
and make up for my mistakes.
I've done a lot by now
and it seems I've corrected some mistakes,
but I'm a bit scared.
Scared of what?
All this time,
I've been trying to change things
in a way that I think is good.
But what I think is good
may be bad
for other people, right?
What if their lives
could've been better?
You think too much.
You're always thinking
and end up confused.
Ning, believe in yourself.
You need to believe that everything happens for a reason.
Believe in yourself
and always live in the moment.
Your Highness, you have great wisdom.
What do you think
the imperial edict means?
Are we really going back to the capital?
A war has been fought.
Even if His Majesty is willing to let it slide,
Xue Yuan won't agree.
Whether we go back to the capital or not,
the Xue family won't just stand aside.
Why don't we just lead the army back to the capital
and eliminate the Xue family
in the name of cleansing the court of sycophants?
The court has doubted our intentions.
If we lead the army back,
we're very likely to be accused of mutiny.
If that happens,
things will only be worse.
Unless we have no other choices,
we can't do that.
Mr. Xie.
Here is the new qin you asked for.
Why hasn't Ning'er come to learn the qin today?
Miss Jiang and the princess talked the whole night.
Maybe she's too tired today.
I'll ask her about it later.
Since you're going to meet Miss Jiang,
I'll take my leave.
Has it ever occurred to you
that Miss Jiang can't play the qin well
not because the previous qin is bad?
A new qin won't be of much help.
If I teach her patiently,
she'll be good at it one day.
If she isn't,
the problem must be with me.
Look.
He's so defensive of her.
What?
Do you have a problem?
No. Of course not.
I'll take my leave.
The store-bought qin
is not comparable to the ones I made myself.
But I'll make do with it.
When I have free time,
I'll make a qin for Ning'er myself.
Yes.
He came all alone.
It seemed that he anticipated everything and got a perfect plan,
but in fact, he was putting himself in danger and taking a chance.
He was only so crazy and daring
because of you.
Now,
you know me inside and out.
You've seen me for who I am
without any disguise.
What do you think?
Are you still afraid of me?
Ning, believe in yourself
and always live in the moment.
-After we parted that day…
Since we parted at Lord Linzi's mansion,
a long time has passed.
How have you been?
I've been good.
Don't worry about me.
♫The snow is very light♫
What I said that day…
I didn't understand it at first,
♫It doesn't stop even after filling all the cracks in the eaves♫
but later, I got what you meant.
Those words sounded harsh,
♫You left in a hurry, leaving traces in the snow♫
but you said them for my good.
Thank you, Miss Jiang.
♫They're about to be erased now♫
At that time, I was bothered by vicious rumors.
♫Disrupting my expectations♫
Thank you for finding out the truth for me
despite our differences.
♫We made a promise♫
You stood up for me in the court.
I haven't thanked you for it.
♫Yet we are only left with our memory♫
Now that we've met,
thank you, Mr. Zhang.
♫Flowers bloom in the street♫
♫Without you♫
Mr. Zhang, you once said
♫Watching the clouds wait anxiously for winter♫
you love watching the rain.
You must be in a good mood today.
♫Keep the memories slowly♫
There are different kinds of rain too.
♫I've forgotten about the four seasons without you by my side♫
When the rain pours down,
it carries too much impact
and makes people uncomfortable.
♫We made a promise, yet we are only left with our memory♫
This kind of rain is the best.
♫Snow covers the street once more♫
♫My heart freezes into a cocoon♫
It causes ripples on water surfaces
and makes every place it falls on glisten.
♫The seasons repeat ruthlessly♫
It's like a small twist in life.
You'll see its worth after you've been through it.
♫Stealing my heart slowly♫
♫I forgot I've never been sure when♫
♫I'll break the cocoon and become a butterfly♫
Have you asked her?
When will she come?
She went to see him.
I heard from Mr. Jiang that you moved back to the countryside.
I didn’t expect you
to be with Junior Preceptor Xie and Yan's troops.
No one in the capital knows that now.
But if you keep staying with the troops,
it won't be long before word gets back.
No one knows
what will happen to the Jiang family then.
You mean
the court may control the Jiang family
as a bargaining chip?
Now Marquis Yan and Xie Wei control the northwest of the State of Qian
and an army of tens of thousands is stationed in Yuzhou
which is only miles away from the capital.
Without any doubt,
the court feels threatened.
If this goes on,
when the court runs out of options,
I'm afraid the Jiang family will be their last resort.
Thank you for caring for the Jiang family, Mr. Zhang.
But I need clarification about one thing.
What's His Majesty's plan?
He claims that he wants to reward the soldiers,
but it sounds like an excuse to me.
Is he planning to trick them back to the capital
and then settle the score with them?
No one knows what His Majesty is thinking.
The Xue family is also a source of pressure.
But without Yan's troops,
peace wouldn't have been restored at the border.
If Xie Wei hadn't put his life at risk,
Lord Pingnan wouldn't have been killed.
Now that both invaders and rebels have been defeated,
if His Majesty turns his back on these heroes,
everyone who has pledged loyalty to him will be disappointed.
Xie Wei and the others did everything they did
for the State of Qian and His Majesty,
not for their own interests.
I know what you mean.
Xie Wei is determined to wipe out the Xue family.
I know that too.
But no matter what crime the Xue family has committed,
they should be judged by the Ministry of Justice according to the law.
What Xie Wei has done
is nothing short of raising an army of his own and standing against the court.
It's understandable that His Majesty is on guard.
You're not him.
If you'd been through what he's been through,
you wouldn't have said that.
Sorry.
You're just looking out for me.
I shouldn't have taken it out on you.
It's fine.
I just hope
Junior Preceptor Xie and the Yan family
can return to the capital to meet His Majesty
as soon as possible.
As long as they return to the capital,
the court will see
their loyalty and sincerity.
His Majesty won't make things hard for them.
It's getting late.
The rain is beautiful,
but it's cold out here.
Don't stay here for too long.
Go back and get some rest.
Miss Jiang.
I have one question for you.
If that day,
my mother hadn't had that accident,
would you still have let go?
Things have changed. So have we.
Since we've moved on,
there's no need to dwell on the past.
♫Wind blows gently♫
I once made lots of mistakes
because of my obsession.
♫The fallen flowers bloom in my heart♫
I'm indebted to you, Mr. Zhang.
I will
do my best to make it up to you.
But I can't help who I love.
♫Your whisper under the moonlight sounds beautiful♫
Have you
♫Getting closer gently♫
given your heart
to Junior Preceptor Xie?
♫The season stays in dreamland♫
Yes.
I love him.
♫The snow is very light♫
♫It doesn't stop even after filling all the cracks in the eaves♫
♫You left in a hurry, leaving traces in the snow♫
♫They're about to be erased now♫
♫Disrupting my expectations♫
Miss Jiang.
Mr. Xie wants to see you.
What happened?
Why didn't you come to learn the qin today?
Where did you go?
Why are you all wet?
I stayed up late last night
and didn't get up until the afternoon.
I wanted some fresh air
so I went to the garden.
Then it rained,
so I watched it for a while.
You watched the rain alone.
Didn't you feel bored?
Not really.
I have something to discuss with you.
His Majesty urges you and Yan Lin to return to the capital.
His intention is unclear.
You should think about it carefully.
As for me,
if I keep staying here,
the court will find it out sooner or later.
The Jiang family is still in the capital, so I think…
You want to leave?
I'm not very close to them,
but I don't want to cause them trouble.
Where do you want to go?
I can go back to the countryside,
just like I planned.
Do you want to leave because of the Jiang family
or because of him?
Why didn't you tell me honestly
that you went to see Zhang Zhe?
What are you keeping from me?
I just ran into him.
I didn't tell you
because I knew you'd overreact.
You just ran into him?
You ran into him
and then watched the rain with him for so long?
I don't know what's so great about the rain.
It's wet and cold.
You can't flick it off when it falls on you.
The coldness seeps into your body bit by bit.
You may catch a cold if you're not careful enough.
It's not fatal,
but it's a constant nuisance
that keeps making you uncomfortable.
Jiang Xuening.
What's so interesting about watching the rain?
Or were you actually trying
to rekindle a romance with him?
Xie Ju'an.
I'm not your pet.
Even if I made a plan to meet him,
I don't have to explain it to you.
But you've promised to build a future with me!
Jiang Xuening.
♫Close your eyes before dark♫
You know what kind of person I am.
♫I'll see you again♫
Since you've given me your word,
I won't let you go.
♫I finally realize that I can't go back♫
I won't give you a chance to go back on your word.
♫To that day♫
♫Only when my weak points are hit can I see♫
♫The fragments deep in my heart♫
♫How intimate we were, but we couldn't withstand change♫
Jiang Xuening.
You're mine.
♫Let me sink into the bottom of the sea sober♫
♫You've disappeared as you wished♫
♫I clearly guessed the probability of our love♫
♫But it's not you and me in the end♫
♫I really want to ask you♫
♫Why?♫
♫In the plots we missed♫
♫Was there any sincerity♫
Jiang Xuening.
♫From now on, will you and I measure♫
I want you.
♫The abyss-like distance between us♫
♫What's the meaning of the decisions I make♫
♫When my hands are tied♫
♫I really want to ask you♫
♫Why?♫
♫In the plots we missed♫
♫Was there any sincerity♫
♫From now on, will you and I measure♫
♫The abyss-like distance between us♫
♫What's the meaning of the decisions I make♫
♫When my hands are tied♫
♫I can't guess or comprehend♫
♫The mystery of fate♫
♫In the boundless world, in the future or the past♫
♫Have we even met?♫
♫From now on, will you and I measure♫
♫The abyss-like distance between us♫
♫The reflection of time will one day♫
♫Engulf you and me♫
Stop.
What are you here for?
I got news from the camp.
I came to talk with Xie Ju'an.
Leave.
What's wrong?
Miss Jiang is inside.
So what?
-She can join the conversation.
-Yeah.
Aren't you usually the smart one?
Why are you
so dense today?
Are they…
I can't miss it.
Let me…
Move aside. Let me take a peek.
-Go away!
-Just a peek.
-Move aside.
-Go away or I'll beat you up.
Let me take a peek.
Leave now!
Jiang Xuening.
You are mine.
I'm not.
Then I'm yours.
Let's get married.
[Quheng Residence]
Are you up, Miss?
Mr. Xie sent us to serve you.
Miss Jiang.
What's this?
Before Mr. Xie left, he said
you got caught in the rain yesterday
and was worried that you might catch a cold.
So he asked Physician Zhou
to prepare cold medicine for you.
Where is he?
He got news from the front line
and went to the camp before dawn.
He left before dawn?
How quick and quiet.
Tell me
when he comes back.
I have something to tell him.
The medicine.
Tell him to take it himself.
When Yan's troops went south,
enough soldiers were left to guard the border.
So the border is quite safe.
But the situation we're in
is full of uncertainty.
The Xue family hasn't been eliminated yet.
Letting Xie Ju'an and Viscount Yan go to the capital
and the troops retreat to the border in the meantime
is not appropriate.
His Majesty
must be aware of that.
However,
the troops are stationed in Yuzhou now.
For those in the capital,
we're posing a big threat.
We have no intention to rise up,
but His Majesty
has good reason to suspect us.
If Ju'an and Yan Lin
return to the capital,
I'm afraid they'll be detained.
Even if His Majesty
doesn't mean to harm them,
the Xue family
may take the chance to kill them.
It's too dangerous.
Why don't we split the troops into three groups?
The first group
will retreat to the border to reassure His Majesty.
The second group will stay with Father
in Yuzhou as our backup.
The third group
are soldiers borrowed from Tongzhou.
They should be transferred back to Tongzhou.
This way,
they can go back to the capital with us
in case something happens.
That may work.
Ju'an.
What do you think?
Brother.
Xie Ju'an.
I'm listening.
Go on.
Are you sure you're listening?
Did you not sleep well last night?
You didn't have to get up early this morning
to attend this meeting.
I could send Yan Lin to town
to discuss it with you.
It's fine.
I don't mind coming here.
Go on.
Miss Jiang.
It's so late.
Why don't you go to bed?
I don't know when Mr. Xie will be back either.
Usually, when he left for a meeting,
he'd come back before noon.
Is he avoiding me?
No, he isn't.
If I can't see him today,
I won't see him ever again.
But…
It's late.
The front line is not safe.
I'll have soldiers escort you back.
Be careful.
Ju'an has something on his mind today.
I don't think he's here for the meeting.
It's more like he's here to avoid someone.
I was young once.
Some things
are quite obvious to me.
Are Ju'an and Xuening
in that kind of relationship?
These years, I've watched you
grow close to Xuening.
I know your feelings for her.
Unfortunately,
so many things have happened.
Do you feel bad
about them being together?
They've been through things
that brought them together.
Brother didn't steal her from me.
It's just that she didn't choose me.
She has the freedom to do that.
She doesn't need a reason
or to explain it to anyone.
I just want her to be happy.
I wish the same for Brother.
All these years,
he's suffered a lot.
Now he's finally met someone
who understands him.
I feel happy for him.
So I have no bad feelings.
Mr. Xie.
Mr. Xie, you're finally back.
Miss Jiang has been waiting for you all day.
She said
if she can't see you today,
she won't see you ever again.
Hurry.
I see.
I've been worried
for them the whole day
and careful with everything I said.
Do you know
what's wrong with Mr. Xie today?
Maybe
he's scared?
Scared?
He
once had everything.
But something horrible happened
when he was a kid
and deprived him of everything.
He's been living
in the shadow of it ever since.
Although he looks
tough and strong,
deep down,
he's extremely insecure.
So,
he'd rather never have anything again.
But when he does,
he'll be terrified of losing it.