[English subtitles are available]
As long as I can live in Ning'an Palace,
I'm willing to pay any price.
[Ning'an Palace]
Cleanse the court of traitors and sycophants!
The cinnabar jade pen can decide the life and death of a person.
Everything
seems to be a dream.
I hurt a lot of people once.
Zhang Zhe, help me.
I promise to be a good person after this.
I spoiled her, so I'll marry her.
There are things
you can't give me,
but he can.
I want to live.
Only you can help me.
Everyone in the world can escape,
but I can't.
I want to do my best
to salvage the past regrets and mistakes.
Do you believe in past life destiny?
I prefer to believe what's in front of me.
Welcome, Your Highness.
Welcome home.
Ning, what are you afraid of?
But somehow,
there is always an invisible hand
that turns everything back to the original point.
You've had your revenge and paid your debt.
In the end, who are you?
This bustling world is a battlefield.
My life is absurd and my love is misplaced.
[Story of Kunning Palace]
[Episode 7]
[To Mr. Yao]
Your wish came true.
Zhang Zhe wants to break off the engagement.
Mr. Yao,
I feel very grateful
for your generous kindness.
You acknowledge my work
and trust me with your daughter's hand.
My gratitude is beyond words.
I'll never forget your kindness.
Unfortunately, things have changed.
I'm a reckless man
and too tactless for politics.
I annoyed His Majesty
and antagonized the sycophants in the court.
I'm in a precarious situation now
and my future ahead is unpredictable.
I may be expelled from the capital
and never reinstated.
I can't ruin your daughter's life,
so I wrote this letter
to ask for your permission
to cancel my engagement with your daughter.
Your daughter deserves a better man
and a happy marriage.
Zhang Zhe.
Best regards.
He wrote this letter himself?
You were right.
He's a man of integrity.
I missed such a good person
and almost made the unforgivable mistake of smearing his reputation.
Are you happy now?
I want to ask you something.
You told me the other day
that if I don't want to marry him,
I just need to wait patiently at home.
You knew that Zhang Zhe
would break off the engagement, right?
What's your relationship
with him?
You hoped to break off the engagement
and now you regret it.
Instead of venting your anger on me,
you should ask yourself
what it is that you want.
I don't know.
He wrote this letter to my father
to break off the engagement.
He knows that his career prospects are uncertain
and doesn't want me to suffer with him as his wife.
He's a noble and considerate man.
Any girl would want
to marry someone like him.
Be a bad woman.
Yao Xi is not suitable for him.
Don't care about what others think.
Go make Zhang Zhe yours.
Zhang Zhe.
Help me.
I'll be a good person after this.
Okay?
You didn't make that unforgivable mistake
and have already realized how wrong you were.
If you insist on marrying Zhang Zhe,
your father will be very happy.
You...
Do you really think so?
I had objections
not because I have a special relationship with him.
I just couldn't stand someone staining his name behind his back.
Mr. Zhang
is the best person in the world.
If you've made up your mind,
please treat him well.
I...
I misunderstood you.
I'll write a letter to my father now.
Thank you.
Zhang Zhe,
I've long lost the right
to be with you.
Your Highness, take a look.
What's this?
How did you know I like this, Shu?
We grew up together.
Of course I know.
After I went home,
I especially sent someone to look for it.
I'm glad you like it.
I hear Your Highness likes Mr. Gu Wi's paintings.
My family happens to have one.
Have a look, Your Highness.
I brought something too.
This comb is made of fine redwood.
I prepared a gold hairpin for Your Highness.
Look at what I brought.
You all prepared a gift for me.
Sorry that I didn't bring anything.
But I'll keep my eyes out
for better gifts for you guys.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Miss Jiang has been quiet.
Did you prepare something special?
I didn't prepare anything.
No way.
Her Highness treats you so well,
yet you didn't prepare a gift for her.
I'm terribly sorry.
Your Highness, please…
Say no more.
Ning.
I know.
I know everything.
What do you mean?
It doesn't matter that you didn't prepare a gift.
Yan Lin has told me
about your situation at home.
You look restless.
You must have had a hard time after going back.
You misunderstood.
I just...
I feel for you.
Anyway, you being my study partner
is the best gift I've ever received.
If you like any of these things,
just take it.
Don't worry.
With me here,
I won't let anyone mess with you.
So this is how it feels
to be the princess's favorite.
What's taking them so long?
It's so late.
I'll turn in if they don't come back.
I'm sleepy.
Sir,
we've got news about the water transport.
The shipwreck was not an accident.
It was intentional.
Who do you think benefited the most
from this incident?
Once the silk ship capsized, the silk price rose.
Those who have stores of silk benefited the most.
Xue Yuan has stores of silk too.
In your opinion,
is he happy that the ship capsized?
No.
It's a felony to interfere in water transport.
Besides, water transport is lucrative in the long term.
If he wants to benefit from it, he gets to lay low.
He knows better than
to kill the goose that lays the golden eggs.
The Xue family's ships have always been elusive.
How come…
The most possible explanation
is that it was an internal issue.
One of Xue Yuan's men was desperate to make money
and secretly made the ship capsize
to raise the silk price.
Xue Yuan should have known about it by now.
Tell Dao Qin
to find this person before Xue Yuan.
We need him to be our witness.
Don't kill me.
I won't do it again.
Please spare my life, Duke.
Please spare me!
They're back.
Sir.
How's it?
We caught him.
You guessed right.
It's one of Xue Yuan's silk merchants
who sabotaged the ship.
His business went wrong recently
and he desperately needed money to make ends meet.
That's why he went out on a limb.
Sure enough, Xue Yuan sent someone to kill him.
We caught the killers too.
After almost being killed
by Xue Yuan's henchmen,
that silk merchant switched sides
to seek our protection.
He told us everything
about the Xue family.
No wonder you told them to wait
until Xue Yuan took action.
In that way,
you could catch Xue Yuan's henchmen
and easily make the silk merchant cave in.
Xia Ju'an,
you're so calculating.
How about You Fangyin?
Have you found anything?
We looked into her,
but…
Don't pussyfoot around.
Just tell him.
Miss Fangyin is a poor girl
and doesn't go out often.
She doesn't know many people
and has no friends.
She has never dabbled in business before.
The only abnormal thing recently
is that at the banquet on the Double Ninth Festival,
she was bullied by a mean servant
and saved by someone.
Saved?
Who saved her?
A few days ago,
when I was secretly protecting you out of Youhuang Store,
I saw her talking to Miss Jiang.
And the person who saved her
was also Miss Jiang.
That was the day Jiang Xuening bought the qin
and before You Fangyin bought silk.
Xie Ju'an,
this Miss Jiang
is not simple.
What does Jiang Xuening have to do with the silk merchant?
As far as we know, nothing.
Secretly give the witness and evidence
to the Ministry of Justice.
The Ministry of Justice hasn't made any progress
on the Rebels Case.
It's time for them to make some achievements,
or they won't be able to keep the Xingwu Guards in check.
But this matter concerns the Xue family.
Will Chen Ying dare to investigate it?
He's a smart man, or he wouldn't have got to
where he is today.
He knows what to do.
Yes.
What about Jiang Xuening?
Greetings,
Your Highness.
You're my study partners now.
We'll meet a lot,
so save the courtesies.
Don't you think they're tiring?
Take your seats.
Ning.
Why are you sitting in the back?
I'm thick-headed
and have been struggling with my studies.
I'm afraid the teachers wouldn't want to see me in the front.
I don't want to annoy them
and get kicked out.
With me here,
no one dares to kick you out.
Come.
Shu.
Can you do me a favor?
Miss Jiang can take my seat,
so she can spend more time
with Your Highness.
Miss Xue, take my seat.
It's closer to Her Highness.
You can talk with her more conveniently.
You just want to sit in the back and eat snacks, right?
If your father finds out,
you'll be punished.
You Yue,
why don't you give your seat to Baoying?
Me?
Come.
Sit.
Alright.
We'll sit this way in the future.
Good morning, Mr. Xie.
Good morning.
You may sit.
This is the first lesson.
I suppose Your Highness and the study partners
are not familiar with the teachers
and didn't do the reading in advance.
So I talked with other teachers
and decided that we won't have classes today.
I'll tell you
what you're going to learn in the next half year.
Xie Wei hasn't changed a bit.
Mr. Xie.
I'm confused about something.
Go ahead.
My father told me
that men and women
play different roles in the world.
Men should contribute to society,
while women should take care of family.
This clear distinction should never be compromised.
Politics are what men should learn.
I mean no offense,
but I think an erudite man like you
shouldn't compile such a textbook
for us girls.
I'm afraid it's inappropriate.
I'm confused about something too.
Empress Dowager is from the Xue family.
During the rebellion of Lord Pingnan,
she took charge of the court
in a composed manner
and kept the situation under control.
Thanks to her, order was restored.
Tell me, Miss Xue.
If Empress Dowager had adhered to social conventions,
would she have made such achievements?
-But my father also said… -Miss Xue.
I know
the scholars in Hanlin Academy are close to your family.
But remember,
we're not at your house.
If you don't want to learn,
you can leave.
What's wrong with Xie Wei?
Why is he so harsh on Xue Shu?
Is it because of the Yan family again?
Miss Xuening,
do you have objections too?
No. Not at all.
Then do you have anything to say?
He's forcing me to take sides
and stand against the Xue family.
In my opinion,
the articles Mr. Xie selected
are all political classics
on how to rule a country with wisdom.
This is a great textbook
and you must have put great efforts into compiling it.
Her Highness was born in the royal family
and we're her study partners.
That makes us different from normal girls.
It's narrow-minded
and ridiculous
to say this textbook is inappropriate.
Miss Jiang,
you don't have to be so harsh.
I have no choice.
Xie Wei wants me to his hound,
so I have to bark.
I'm glad you said that,
Miss Xuening.
You behave very well today.
Shu,
Miss Jiang is not a bad person.
She's just a bit straightforward.
Don't take it to heart.
Straightforward?
I don't think so.
What do you mean?
I shouldn't say this,
but do you remember
that Miss Jiang guessed
the test questions right?
She's explained.
It's because she's familiar with Mr. Xie.
Mr. Xie is a lone wolf in the court.
Even if they're close,
he wouldn't have told her about the test questions.
Xi,
you've seen a lot in the palace.
Jiang Xuening is powerless,
but both Viscount Yan and Her Highness are so nice to her.
Don't you think
everything has been too easy for her?
Not only that,
Jiang Xuening knew a lot about your engagement with Zhang Zhe
and became your close friend within days.
Jiang Xuening
is not as simple as we thought.
One needs to be a master of calculation
to get what she has.
You must be careful around her.
Shu.
Your Highness.
I thought about it
and decided to have a word with you.
So I caught up with you.
Is it about what happened just now?
It must have been a hard day for you.
I should've been more thoughtful.
I just thought that we are cousins
and have lots of chances to see each other,
but Ning may never come back
to the palace after the classes are over.
That's why I...
You don't need to feel sorry.
I'm glad to do something that made you happy.
You're so kind, Shu.
I hope you could not be angry with Ning.
This way, Your Highness.
-Jie. -Your Highness.
Why are you here?
I just paid Mother a visit.
You just finished school?
Yes. Come with me.
Let me introduce you to my study partners.
No. We're in the court.
It's okay.
We can wait for a better occasion.
Come with me.
Jie.
This doesn't look like something men use.
Which girl gave it to you?
Stop kidding me.
Tell me.
If you like her
but are too shy to propose,
I can ask His Majesty to help you.
Stop guessing.
I need to go.
Jie.
Miss Xuening.
Wait a moment.
Anything I can do for you?
Yan Lin didn't come to class this morning.
I heard that he's ill.
How come he fell ill
all of a sudden?
Mr. Xie,
I'm not a physician.
How would I know?
You went to the Yan Mansion
and soon after you left,
the Yan family sent for a physician.
Have you been spying on me and the Yan family?
I wish I didn't have to.
Zhou Yinzhi
was sent by the Xue family to approach Yan Lin.
You visited his house
and talked with him alone for a long time the other day.
Given that the Xue family hasn't taken any moves yet,
it's very clear
that you stopped Zhou Yinzhi from taking action against the Yan family.
You finally believe me now.
That depends on
whether you can be honest with me.
Don't you have anything to say to me?
What do you mean?
You told You Fangyin to buy silk from Xu Wenyi.
Was it for the Yan family too?
You've found out about that too?
I just
wanted to help Fangyin make some money.
Her life is too hard.
What I want to know
is why you were so sure that the silk price
would rise.
The silk price in the capital plummeted
and then soared after the shipwreck.
Everyone knows about it.
How should I explain it to him?
If you're trying to make up a story,
make it convincing.
Is that so unusual?
My father is the Vice Minister for Revenue.
He deals with money every day.
I picked up a thing or two
and learned how business works.
I knew that the silk price wouldn't keep plummeting.
It already hit the bottom,
so once demand exceeded supply,
it would rise again.
Besides, Yan Lin mentioned
that the water conditions in the Cao River have been bad.
So I thought
if something happened that impeded the transportation of silk,
its price would definitely rise.
I just took a chance.
You took a chance?
Should I believe you?
Why is everything by design in your eyes?
Can't they just be coincidences?
Why are you
always so guarded？
What made you so mistrustful?
Is it related to the secret you mentioned?
Steering the conversation toward me
is not gonna work.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
Don't meddle in things
that you should stay out of.
He even knew about my attempt to make money.
I have a feeling
that the clairvoyant one is not me
but him.
[Xie Mansion]
Why do you only believe that everything was planned
but not believe it was a coincidence?
Is it because
you are used to being on your guard?
What on earth made you hold such a shield?
Is it related to the secret you mentioned?
Did she confess?
She said it was a coincidence.
And you believe it?
Of course.
What a coincidence.
Do you know
the silk price went up this morning?
So what?
You didn't ask her
to give me all the silk she has？
So that I can sell it
and make a lot of money.
Lyu Zhaoyin.
Is there nothing else you can do?
Have you found out Deputy Gong Yi's whereabouts
and what he is up to?
If you are that unoccupied,
why don't you do something serious?
No wonder you ranked second
in the entry-level, provincial, and national exams.
You ranked first, so what?
Why did you suddenly write my name?
Have you paid for it?
You, the Duke of Xue, are in charge of the Xingwu Guards
and befriended half of the officials.
Yet you are not satisfied.
How dare you interfere in the water transport
and collude with the merchants to affect the market price?
You even tried to do away with a witness.
You do whatever you want under my nose.
Uncle,
what exactly do you want?
Your Majesty.
I'm truly loyal to Your Majesty,
having no disloyalty at all.
I know nothing about this.
Please spare me some time.
I will get to the bottom of it.
When did I ever doubt your loyalty?
But, over the years,
the Yan family has maintained its military presence
and repeatedly refutes me in court.
I don't really have any trustworthy aides by my side.
If even you are found guilty by others,
who else can I trust?
Your Majesty.
I was wrong.
My subordinates made the decision on their own.
It wasn't my idea.
Please rest assured, Your Majesty.
I will find out the truth
and give you an explanation.
Forget it.
This time, I'll suspend you for half a month
to show the other officials.
But if it happens again,
I won't let you off easily.
I understand.
I'll take my leave first.
A few days ago,
I heard the Duke of Xue try to draw the Ministry of Rites over
to appoint my brother as the Crown Prince.
In this way,
he may hold his tongue for that.
[Wang Xinyi, Emperor's Eunuch Attendant]
Your Majesty is wise.
To suppress this matter,
we must give the Ministry of Justice some benefits
to shut their mouths.
Pass my order.
The Ministry of Justice has done a great job in the Raw Silk Case.
The whole department will be rewarded.
Also, I will not go through with the Rebels Case anymore.
Those involved will be reinstated.
Yes, Your Majesty.
That is the Ning'an Palace, where the Empress lives.
It's so magnificent.
Today, the Empress Dowager wants to see all the study partners.
Where we are is still far from Empress Dowager's Tai'an Hall.
We can't be too playful,
or we'll be late.
Shu is right.
Let's go, ladies.
Boy,
Her Majesty punished you with 24 hours of kneeling.
That means not even a moment less.
Not to mention fainting.
Even if you die,
[Zheng Bao, Eunuch]
you have to get through it.
Zheng Bao?
The imperial edicts, memorials, secret letters, and verbal edicts,
Your Majesty handed over everything to Zheng Bao.
How trustworthy is he?
I once saved his life in front of my sister-in-law's residence.
Since then,
Zheng Bao has been the most loyal person to me
in the palace.
It will never change whether he's alive or dead.
It will never change whether he's alive or dead?
I don't believe it.
He's really a faithful man who has never changed, whether alive or dead.
This must be the day Shen Jie recruited Zheng Bao.
If I can save him this time,
will he devote himself to me in the future?
Stop pretending.
You may slap yourself
to keep sober-minded with the pain.
Do you want me to slap you instead?
But Shen Jie was Lord Linzi back then.
He had the right to save him from punishment.
How am I going to do that?
Your Highness.
It's getting late.
Let's go quickly.
Ning.
Are you okay?
Why do you look so pale?
Your Highness.
Is this common
in the palace?
I want to go home.
Don't be afraid.
This little eunuch made a mistake.
He'll be fine after he's punished.
Let's go.
No.
Your Highness.
I'm wondering
whether I will be punished like this
if I make a mistake in the future.
He had to slap himself while being splashed with water and was asked to kneel for so long.
He'll die if he can't bear it anymore.
I don't think so.
Your Highness, you are unaware of it.
The monk in the temple said I have a weak Bazi.
If he dies,
he will definitely pester me as a ghost.
I'm so scared.
Greetings, Your Highness.
What did he do wrong
to be punished like this?
You treat him like this.
Is my sister-in-law trying to kill him?
Your Highness, you have no idea.
When this brat was cleaning the hall,
he broke...
I don't want to hear it.
He's already been punished
and also kneeling for so long.
What else do you want?
Listen to my words and let him off.
If the Empress asks later,
just say it's my idea.
Understand?
Yes, Your Highness.
Help him up quickly.
Ning.
Did you see that?
Since I said I would protect you,
I will keep my promise.
You won't be afraid then, right?
Thank you, Your Highness.
It's great to have you here.
Cool.
Let's go.
Mother, Sister-in-law.
I've brought the study partners here.
Greetings to the Empress Dowager
and the Empress.
Shu is here.
Get up quickly.
And come to me.
You, an ungrateful girl.
Only now did you want to visit me?
I told your father long ago
to let you stay in the palace.
But he said it was against the rules.
That's why Zhiyi
had no friends of the same age.
And she had to find a few study partners outside the palace.
It was so troublesome.
Look.
After all that had happened,
you still came to live in the palace.
This old witch
is still so annoying.
Why would she try to prove her dominance
to us, a few young ladies?
Mother.
They are still kneeling.
What?
Are they reluctant
to greet me?
We dare not.
I...
The Empress is indeed a people-pleaser.
Mother,
I have no such intention.
I know
what your intention is.
Forget it.
His Majesty is sick at the moment.
He needs someone by his side.
You can go back now.
I'll take my leave first.
Aunt, I'll get you some hot tea.
Good girl.
Zhiyi, come.
Mother.
You all may get up now.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Madam Xu.
What's wrong with Aunt today?
The Duke was punished by His Majesty.
Her Majesty is in a fit of anger.
You grew up raised by the Empress Dowager.
She can listen to you the most.
Why don't you persuade Her Majesty not to be angry?
I see.
Mother, you always scare people like this.
They are going to play with me
and study together in the future.
All of them are not bold enough.
If they get sick being scared of you,
who else will play with me?
I was just too glad
that I forgot to get them up.
How was that scary?
Are you Baoying?
I haven't seen you in a while.
You've grown a lot.
Thank you for your concern, Your Majesty.
I heard that
there's a study partner
named Jiang Xuening
that you like a lot.
Which one is her?
Step forward so I can see you.
I'm Jiang Xuening.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Too beautiful.
A bit frivolous.
Not elegant enough.
I was born like this.
Why do you care?
Your Majesty,
I had inexorable doom when I was little.
Therefore, my parents sent me to a farm
and I was raised in frugality.
That's why I'm unknowledgeable,
frivolous, and a bit rough around the edges.
Getting to see Your Majesty today,
I feel very nervous, with profound respect and humility.
I will strictly restrain myself
and be a good study partner for Her Highness in the future.
I won't dare to slack off.
Quite well-spoken, though.
All right.
I also heard that you are the apple of
Viscount Yan's eye.
No one in the Yan family likes me.
If I give you a hard time,
I wonder what they'll say behind my back.
You may leave.
Yes.
Aunt.
Have some tea.
Your Majesty,
Eunuch Liu from the Imperial Household Department is here.
Do you want to see him?
Let him in.
Yes.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
What brings you here, Eunuch Liu?
Your Majesty, you said a Ruyi jade was broken
the day before yesterday.
His Majesty learned about it today,
and he's concerned about Your Majesty.
He specially asked me
to find the Ruyi jade, Qinghai's tribute from last year,
and give it to you.
Guards!
Arrest this rebel
and send him to the Office of Punishment for interrogation!
-Yes. -Your Highness, please calm down.
I'm just here to deliver the jade by order of His Majesty.
-How does that make me a rebel? -Mother.
-Please calm down. -Your Majesty.
I'm innocent!
Your Majesty!
[300 Loyal Souls]
All of you, leave.
Yes.
[Imperial Household Department]
Listen up.
Search thoroughly.
Don't miss any spot.
Yes.
From the Imperial Household Department?
How can that be?
Exactly.
I also find it weird.
We do have our people in the Imperial Household Department,
but we never gave an order like this.
The case of 300 Loyal Souls
is a taboo of the imperial court.
Who could be so audacious
as to irritate the Empress Dowager?
And for what reason?
Deputy Gong Yi is still in the capital.
Because of the case of raw silk,
Xue Yuan was suspended by Shen Lang.
Now the capital is in peace,
of course he couldn't sit still.
Oh no.
He must have been using our people
to take actions in the palace.
If they keep on investigating,
they'll trace it to us, right?
Sir.
Bad news.
His Majesty wants to see you in the palace now.
[Imperial Study]
Mr. Xie, you are here.
Please go in.
His Majesty is waiting for you.
Your Majesty, you wanted to see me so late at night.
Is it something urgent?
Someone in the Imperial Household Department
gave this to the Empress Dowager in my name today.
Her Majesty had a sudden heart attack.
Now all the people in the Imperial Hospital are taking care of her.
There are Lord Pingnan's people in the Imperial Household Department.
How do you know it was Lord Pingnan, Official Xie?
The case of 300 Loyal Souls is a national grief for the State of Qian.
If it's not the rebels of Lord Pingnan,
I can't imagine
who else would do this.
You have a point, Official Xie.
But Lord Pingnan is in Jiangnan, far away from us.
How could he get his hands on the imperial palace?
On the contrary, this exactly proves that
they have already got their hands on the palace.
Recently,
there have been rebels causing trouble in the capital repeatedly.
But they've only been doing trivial deeds like assassination.
Now it seems
they were trying to distract us
and cover up their actions in the palace
with rebellious assassination.
No wonder
Xingwu Guards and the Ministry of Justice
couldn't find anything even though they've searched thoroughly.
Turns out it was just a cover-up.
I can't believe it.
That old man is so evil.
I can't rest assured unless he dies a hundred times.
Your Majesty.
Lord Pingnan did this
to stir up chaos in the capital
and shake the foundation of our state.
The case of Ruyi jade
must be investigated,
but not in public.
Otherwise,
the people will waver,
and we'll be falling into the rebels' trap.
You're right.
I know what to do.
I feel relieved to have an official like you.
Go back and rest.
Mr. Xie, you are here.
Please go in.
His Majesty is waiting for you.
Uncle, are you assured now?
I did worry too much.
But Eunuch Huang found out that
the decree that the Imperial Household Department received to gift the Empress Dowager
was forged by someone
in the name of Your Majesty.
This means it must have been
someone close to you, Your Majesty.
Also,
the time when that Ruyi jade was sent into the palace,
it was also when
Mr. Xie proposed to teach Her Highness.
This matter is very important.
So it's understandable that
Her Majesty and I are especially cautious.
That's why I wanted to test Mr. Xie.
I know
what Mother is thinking about.
But Official Xie is loyal to me.
I'm confident about that.
It's getting late.
Uncle, you are still suspended.
You may leave now.
I'll take my leave.
Nanny.
We've been waiting here for more than two hours.
Why can't we go back first?
Miss You.
Something big happened in the palace.
Her Highness is still here for the inquiry.
You need to wait longer.
Then why does Sister Xue get to stay in the hall,
while we have to kneel here?
What does
their inquiry have to do with me?
At this point,
just talk less.
Nanny.
Her Majesty kept us here
just in case, I suppose.
But the girls are weak.
If they catch a cold,
I'm afraid we won't know what to say when Her Majesty inquires about this.
Besides,
Her Majesty sent people to investigate this matter secretly.
I guess she doesn't want to make it public.
Why don't you let us wait aside?
OK?
All right, you can wait aside.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
It's okay.
Are you hurt?
Your Majesty, you are finally here.
Her Majesty is waiting for you inside.
Nanny Xu.
It's too cold at night.
Let them go back first.
Yes, Nanny Xu.
The study partners live in the palace anyway.
They can't leave anyway.
If anything comes up, just ask someone to summon them.
If they get sick,
Her Highness will be worried.
Since His Majesty and Miss Xue have said it,
you may leave now.
Remember,
don't tell anyone
about what happened here today.
Yes.