But that night,
something strange really did happen.
What strange thing?
The opera troupe has many rules for performances.
Before the show,
the townspeople
have to put the troupe's payment
into thirteen cloth bags.
Ten coins in each bag.
Thirteen bags,
making exactly
one hundred and thirty coins.
If they find that
the actors on stage aren't serious
or make a mistake,
they cut down one bag immediately.
But this rule
is practically nonexistent for the troupe.
Because the audience
is so captivated by the play,
who would bother touching the bags?
That night,
when the performance was nearly over,
I was patrolling around
as usual.
Bravo!
Chang Xian'er is here!
This La Li Tou is a fool,
but he can distinguish
right from wrong.
It was because he stole
the money bag in front of the stage
that Chang Xian'er blamed him.
Xue Lao,
where is La Li Tou now?
Changxian'er Temple.
Before Hongniang's incident,
didn't she come here with Zhang Sheng?
Xue Lao also said
La Li Tou has no fixed home,
but spends most of his time at Changxian'er Temple.
I wonder if he's there now.
Let's go.
Let's go in and take a look.
La Li Tou!
It seems he's not here.
W-What's going on?
Could there really be evil spirits here?
La Li Tou!
Why are you here?
Look at him.
He seems badly frightened.
La Li Tou,
what exactly did you see that night?
Chang Xian'er...
Chang Xian'er is here...
Stop asking.
He won't be able to tell us anything in this state.
Then what do we do?
Since he cannot
tell us himself,
then let's have him
take us to see it.
First, I'll hypnotize him
and send him back to the troupe.
Mystic Heaven, Spiritual Earth.
Mind and thought as one.
Yin and Yang, ten thousand forms.
All things flow and change.
Be not startled, be not afraid.
Be not afraid, be not startled.
Hour of the Pig, third quarter.
Mind returns to the void.
Make him believe he has returned to that day.
Let's see if there are any clues.
La Li Tou.
Chang Xian'er is here.
Chang Xian'er has come to catch me!
Chang Xian'er is here!
Speak what you know.
This Great Immortal will not blame you.
Or else I will eat you!
Sister Hong.
Sister Hong was crying.
Will La Li Tou be okay with you doing this?
Once the knot in his heart is untied,
he'll be fine after a few days of rest.
But he didn't say anything.
He did.
That night, Hongniang left halfway through,
and appeared backstage.
He must have seen something happen.
What's going on here?
Look.
The Lai Mansion today...
with all this fanfare.
What are they trying to do?
What's happening?
Listen to me, everyone.
Our Young Master Lai
has recently contracted an illness.
We are hiring experts to treat him.
If anyone can cure our Young Master,
the Lai Mansion will reward them heavily.
Young Master Lai is used to bullying men and women.
Now he's getting his retribution, isn't he?
Exactly.
Serves him right.
Don't you know some medicine?
Of course.
I studied the art of healing and saving lives.
Evil people get their just deserts.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Why make it so mysterious?
All secretive.
Can you really cure my son?
Is he actually possessed?
We'll know after we see him.
My Lai family...
fasts and prays to Buddha every day.
Although my son is spoiled and willful,
he has never done
anything wicked.
Why does Heaven treat
my Lai family like this?
That's not necessarily true.
In all things,
one cannot just look at the surface.
Perhaps
your son did something wicked
that you don't know about.
What exactly happened?
Please tell us, Madam.
A few days ago,
a Ghost Opera Troupe came to perform.
My son insisted on making a fuss
to go watch the opera.
Everyone knows
when watching the opera,
one cannot leave halfway.
But that day...
Bravo!
Good!
Wonderful!
It's really good!
Son!
Son, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Since then,
my son has been possessed.
Calling him, shouting at him...
he doesn't react.
We found doctors, physicians,
exorcists, Taoist priests...
none could cure him.
If you can cure him,
whatever conditions you raise,
I will agree to them all.
Let me see the Young Master first.
Take a look.
Son!
Stop banging!
You're bleeding!
Think of a way, quickly!
Save him!
Think of a way, quick!
Son!
It's not demonic possession.
It's poison.
How could this happen?
Nerve damage caused by a potent toxin.
After the brain damage,
he became delirious,
and his intellect regressed.
Is there any medicine to cure my son?
You can try
giving him some detoxifying medicine first
to see if it works.
Then...
the previous doctors,
why didn't they find the cause?
Perhaps because Lai Mansion
abuses its power too much.
Others fear that the slightest mistake
would invite retaliation.
See them out.
Let's go, you two.
My son.
It breaks my heart.
It really is strange.
Right after San Yatou died,
something happened to the Young Master.
That's right.
San Yatou was destined not to enter Lai Mansion.
You heard that, right?
I heard it.
He said San Yatou was going to enter Lai Mansion.
And...
Young Master Lai's trouble started after San Yatou died.
Let's go.
Let's go check Uncle Bao's house.