Welcome.
You are...
We're looking for a suitable umbrella.
Please.
Feel free to look around.
Zhang's Umbrella Shop...
...was passed down from your ancestors, right?
I, Zhang Sheng, have failed the Zhang ancestors.
Zhang's Umbrella Shop has declined in my hands.
As far as I know,
umbrella making involves seventy-two steps.
Such exquisite craftsmanship...
...you must pass it on well.
This red umbrella looks very different.
This umbrella is indeed different from the others.
It can ward off evil.
This umbrella was made using an ancient method.
Modern umbrellas...
...are made in seventy-two steps.
The ancient method of umbrella making...
...uses eighty-six steps.
The secret lies in those extra fourteen steps.
These fourteen steps are called Divine Shrouding.
An oil-paper umbrella after Divine Shrouding...
...can ward off evil,
avert disaster,
and expel ghosts.
Others say Hongniang was harmed by Chang Xian'er.
What do you think?
I...
Why did you kill Hongniang?
What are you saying?
You killed Hongniang.
She was brutally murdered.
Her resentment is deep.
Now she's a vengeful ghost coming for your life.
Is that not so?
It wasn't me.
I didn't do it.
You still dare to deny it?
You said you could see Hongniang's ghost.
If you didn't have a guilty conscience,
why use Divine Shrouding to hide?
I didn't kill Hongniang.
Hongniang wasn't killed by me.
Then what exactly did you do...
...for Hongniang's restless spirit to haunt you?
How could I harm Hongniang?
How could I bear to harm her?
It's her who won't let me go.
After she died,
whenever I went out,
I felt a chill all over my body.
Once, after staying out too long,
I went home and fell seriously ill.
While I was in a deep sleep,
I found Hongniang standing right in front of me.
As if she had something to say to me.
It must be because I failed to protect her.
She hates me.
I'm sorry.
It's raining.
Let me walk you back.
We're here.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Silly girl.
Running out when it's raining?
Go back inside.
Hongniang.
Zhang Sheng.
It's raining.
This is for you.
Hongniang.
Marry me.
Will you?
Silly girl!
If word of this gets out,
how will I show my face in public?
Huh?
How can you be so shameless?
You're going to be the death of me!
That night, Hongniang came to find me.
Hongniang was crying her heart out.
It turned out Li Laosan, to pay off gambling debts,
was going to sell Hongniang.
I was willing to pay to redeem Hongniang.
Hongniang suggested...
...that I take her far away.
Hongniang.
What's wrong?
Take me away.
I'll take you away.
Come.
Zhang Sheng.
Where are we?
Hongniang.
Don't be afraid.
We'll make do here for tonight.
We'll leave tomorrow.
Okay.
Hongniang!