Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ¢  The Turtle-Flipping Deity Team  ðŸ¢  @ Viki.com
''Mortal World Diary'' - Zhang Jie
♫   Loneliness on the Immortal Island of Penglai is advising people from the mortal world   ♫
♫   That true love is hard to find   ♫
♫   What will happen if you give up on love?   ♫
♫   True love can only be enlightened by chance   ♫
♫   Fate played tricks on me, causing my tears to fall   ♫
♫   The sorrow of separation, and the butterflies in my dreams    ♫
♫   I'll never regret my decision, even if I have to suffer in the Six Paths   ♫
♫   I'm helpless against earthly rules and divine laws    ♫
♫   I made countless attempts to create my own fate   ♫
♫   Like the tree's burden of making flowers bloom, I've wasted years of my life   ♫
♫   An air of melancholy surrounds me as the Bodhi leaves fall   ♫
I found it!
"Illuminate all darkness."
"Protect and shield those deceased."
"Turn those ghosts into earthly beings."
"Revert what's been done and bring back the spirit."
Are you okay?
Ziqi!
Xuan Xiang.
Ziqi.
Shouldn't I be dead?
Why am I here?
A millennium ago... it wasn't me who killed you in front of the array.
I know.
Even though that man looked like you...
I can recognize your eyes.
I knew it wasn't you.
I'm sorry.
I was late.
You suffered a lot.
Is the Divine-Devil War still going on?
How did you resurrect me?
Where is this place?
We're at the Night Forgetting River.
I used Paper and Ink to revive you.
The Divine-Devil War ended more than 900 years ago.
I'll tell you everything later.
I have been dead for nine centuries?
What was the outcome of the war, then?
Don't worry.
The Heavenly Realm won.
Even though I couldn't prevent the war...
From now on, we can live how we had wanted to live.
It doesn't matter if Tang Zhou is already in love with someone else.
Let bygones be bygones.
Living in the present is the most important.
Feelings come from the heart.
Once someone enters your heart, this feeling will be inevitable.
We might as well confront it.
Oh, Ziqi.
It's all thanks to these three that I could revive you.
I owe my life to you.
You're welcome.
Liu Weiyang's determination was what brought you back to life.
Despite the hardship you had to go through, you can now continue to live happily.
Congratulations to the both of you.
Congratulations, Sister Tao.
Can I call you that?
I'm Yan Dan.
Your love story is more touching than any novel that I have read.
Can I include your story in my journal?
If one day the story is performed on stage, it will be an amazing and popular one.
Of course! I'll keep two VIP seats for you two.
You must come and watch the performance.
Ziqi!
Although Ziqi regained her human form... her soul was trapped in Bone Mountain for too long.
She is overwhelmed by ghostly energy.
I will leave with her soon.
Don't stay here for too long, too.
Sister Tao has the same gray spots I had.
Perhaps before I lost my memory, I was also here.
As expected of a demon.
You can never stay still in one place.
Aren't you the same?
Why are you here at this hour?
You must be up to no good.
You're the one who is curious about this place.
What... are you unhappy now?
I also don't know.
I... When I see this place, I feel weird.
Almost uncontrollably.
While we were by the shore just now, I saw many passengers crossing the river with lanterns.
It looked familiar to me, too.
Me, too. It just looked so familiar.
I saw this place in the Illusion of Devils.
I was alone with my lantern.
I was crossing the river.
It was hot and cold at the same time.
The fire from the lantern kept burning me.
Do you think we can regain our memory... here?
It works!
I get it now.
It's no wonder all passengers carry it.
This is Death Fire.
Who would want to cling to their past... when they're being burned by it.
If it were me, I would forget everything within a day.
Coward.
I believe... that some people will not forget... even if they are being scorched.
Is that why you can't forget the person in your dream?
Maybe you should carry this lantern and walk in the river a bit.
You might be able to remember the person in your dream.
You might find out what you did to wrong her.
Do you want me to recall my past that badly?
Do you not have the courage, or are you not willing to face the past?
Is it possible... that you truly wronged a woman?
Yan Dan.
You have no memory, too.
If you don't care about your past...
why should I?
♫   I blame time for the mortal world's woe is on your shoulder   ♫
♫   Like the surging tides of stars, I continuously ask where the origin of love comes from   ♫
You're the future sect leader of the Lingxiao Sect.
I'm a headstrong lotus demon.
Why do you treat me this nicely?
♫   In my momentary childishness, I now understand that all living things wither away   ♫
The magical bangle on your wrist is also binding your heart.
When it was vibrating earlier, I want to know...
if it's because of me?
♫   The beauty is in the burning agarwood incense, there's still hope when the ashes settle   ♫
♫   Hear the beautiful prose with a fine beauty and a picturesque view, they pair well together   ♫
♫   Sew two hearts together and a stem sprouts forth   ♫
♫   Understand the wind, think about the rain, and do not awaken from the dream   ♫
Tang Zhou! What's going on?
Don't come near me. Go away!
- Oh no! Are you...
- Leave!
I'll lose control soon. Run!
Let me pass my energy to you!
She is my beloved one.
Unfortunately, our time together is short. It will come to an end soon.
May she forget her past and live a happy life.
You're back.
The Tortoise-Flipping Deity? It's you?
My title is Qingli Emperor Ying Yuan.
A refined, happy face, but harsh brows filled with sadness.
Embellished words lead to emptiness, while simple phrases have deeper meanings.
The younger sister is Yan Dan.
This is a Distance-Keeping Bracelet. I have placed a Distance-Keeping Lock on it.
When you're within 15 steps of me, you will be pushed away like just now.
Let me ask you. If one day, I fell in love
but I harmed no one and did nothing wrong, would you kill me?
I will kill you.
You're smart.
In a GO game, the best way to resolve a deadlock... is to withdraw.
Otherwise, both parties will be hurt.
Whether it was in Yanxu Heavenly Palace, or in the cottage by the Land Under the Horizon,
no matter the time, the location, or the nature of your feelings,
did you ever have me in your heart?
My heart is devoted to all beings. There is no room for anything else.
I have tasted every kind of pain.
A gouged heart, thunder strikes, shred to pieces as I jumped off the Bridge of Emptiness,
scorched by the Death Fire.
None of them is as painful as heartbreak.
I must forget him and never look back.
Ying Yuan.
♫   After bidding farewell, when Spring becomes Autumn, where can I find my heart in this world?   ♫
♫   Several lifetimes will not be enough for our parting   ♫
♫   As I watch lovers enjoying fireworks on the riverbanks, my love and longing for you makes my pain unbearable   ♫
Yan Dan. I had a lapse of judgment just now. Sorry.
- Don't...
- Don't come near me!
Don't come near me.
♫   When the lotus blossoms again, you and I will be together   ♫
You've come to me by yourselves.
Run!
Tang Zhou, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Sheng De.
Tang Zhou.
You're still alive.
I guess my time is not up yet.
But today, your time is up.
If this carries on, his celestial vest will shred to pieces.
I will get the emperor's divine power
Aren't you two inseparable?
Then why not die together?
Ying Deng. From the Heavenly Realm to the Mortal Realm, why can't you let it go?
You regained your memory.
Very well.
At least, you know why you will die!
Yan Dan.
His Majesty doesn't remember you at all.
Does your heart... ache?
Oh, wait.
You only have half a heart now.
You won't feel as much pain as I do.
You ruined yourself for someone who doesn't even love you.
Can you still not understand?
If I can't get it... then let us all burn into ashes.
Why does your spiritual power contain Flower Spirit Clan's spirit?
My power got a massive boost... all thanks to the entire Flower Spirit Clan.
Your clan mates had limited power, but they were numerous and the demonic essence was pure.
It's perfect for me to use!
Remember.
They died because of you.
When you live a day longer, the people around you suffer a day longer!
You're insane!
I've now regained my memory of the Heavenly Realm.
I can now fight you with my divine spell.
When you make one mistake...
it leads to another.
There is... no turning back!
You killed my entire clan, hurt His Majesty,
provoked Zhi Xi and me against each other, and put me on that Heavenly Gallows twice.
Today, you will pay the price!
Why?
I trained for a millennium... to become a fairy.
I could have had a happy life and a bright career.
But I turned love into hatred because of His Majesty.
Now, I'm neither a human nor a demon.
Do I deserve to disappear into thin air?
I gave my love to the wrong person.
Was that...
my mistake from the very beginning?
I lost half of my heart.
Jiang Chen lost her life.
You... deserve this.
Yan Dan, oh, Yan Dan. You sure are foolish.
Whether in the Heavenly Realm or the Mortal Realm, you fell in love with him again and again.
I've suppressed his leaking divine power for the moment.
However, his celestial vest is severely damaged and won't last long.
We will need the fourth Divine Tool to turn the tide.
But the Three Realms are so vast. Where should we start looking?
I can save him.
Even the Devil King failed to repair his vest.
What can you use to save him?
If I didn't make him come with me on the boat, he wouldn't be like this.
I caused this mess.
I'll deal with it.
Don't worry. My body is full of medicine.
There must be a way.
Besides, the future sect leader of the Lingxiao Sect will surely owe me this one.
We'll wait outside.
Let us know if—
Stop nagging me.
If you have the time, make me supper.
Once I'm done, we'll have it together.
Go.
Yan Dan. Call me if anything happens.
Why is it... that I remember you at the end
but you forgot about everything?
Whatever.
You already owe me a lot.
I guess you can continue to owe me.
Yan Dan.
What did you do to save me?
Nothing. It was just a few petals.
You're awake now. You should rest.
I should go.
What about Sheng De?
Were you hurt in the fight?
Paper and Ink is a very powerful Divine Tool.
I used it to get rid of Sheng De.
She's dead.
It turns out you're very powerful.
I truly underestimated you.
Yan Dan. What you said on the boat just now...
I no longer want the answer... to the questions I asked earlier on.
Yan Dan, you gave me your blood directly from your heart.
Are you crazy?
Do you know how risky that is?
What else can I do?
Should I watch you die in front of me?
You know you can't promise me anything, so why won't you leave me alone?
Why do you always appear in front of me?
Why do you have only half a heart?
Where is the other half?
This thing followed me from the Heavenly Realm to the Mortal Realm.
Because fate...
is unavoidable.
Advisor Lotus, I made you supper.
Eat it while it's warm.
It's fine, Yu Mo.
I'm very tired from saving Tang Zhou just now.
I want to sleep now.
I saw you when you came out just now.
You were as white as a sheet.
How did you save him?
If you feel unwell, just tell me.
I'll help you.
I'm fine.
I just plucked out several of my petals.
I'll be fine after a nap.
Once Tang Zhou has recovered, I'll boss him around.
He'd better return my spiritual power to me.
All right. I'll sleep now. You should get some rest, too.
Ziqi.
The gray spots on your face are gone.
It seems like the ghostly energy from Bone Mountain has dissipated.
However, your soul just returned to your body.
It's still unstable. You need several days to recuperate.
Come.
I made this medicinal soup for you.
Xuan Xiang.
Do you have the information I asked you to find for me?
During the Divine-Devil War, 34 divine clans were wiped out.
The Ming Goose Clan... was one of them.
Were my people buried in the Divine Cemetery Forest?
Did they have an honorable burial?
The Ming Goose Clan was ambushed.
No bodies were found.
I'm sorry.
After I was promoted,
my mentor, Star Deity Ji Du, Huan Qin,
gave this purple hairpin to me.
He said this hairpin was unbreakable,
like the trust the Heavenly Realm had in me,
and the sense of duty I had to the Heavenly Realm.
Even though I chose you...
I never betrayed the Divine Clan.
Of course not.
But my mistake helped Elder Shuo Hua.
My selfishness...
started the Divine-Devil War.
Xuan Xiang.
We won't be what we used to be anymore.
Ziqi.
We trumped life and death.
Why can't we start over?
No.
Life and death... aren't what is between us.
It's the thousands of lives of those deities who died for nothing.
Xuan Xiang.
Please let me go.
Ziqi.
If you want to leave, wait till your health has improved.
Okay?
I let go of my memory of him last time.
This time, I can do it, too.
I really didn't expect us to meet again.
How have you been all these years?
Not bad.
If so, why are you here again, then?
The Night Forgetting River is losing its effectiveness.
I crossed the river to forget my past.
Now...  it all came back to me.
I've been in the Night Forgetting River for over a million years.
Everyone here is just a passenger to me.
Except for you who have kept me company for 800 years.
I have long regarded you as my only friend.
I think...
you should know something.
♫   Close your eyes and feel the warmth of your palm   ♫
The agarwood incense burner wasn't destroyed.
How come it's in your hand?
♫  The tangled hair can't untangle your sadness   ♫
♫  Once again renewing a lifetime of love  ♫
♫  The same moonlight falls onto the same people but this time a new departure  ♫
♫  How can we let gray hair scatter our memory?  ♫
♫  Love will return to where it started, oh ~ please slow down  ♫
♫  Looking back the gaze from that moment, that instance of a flutter  ♫
Ying Yuan. It was you
who erased our memory.
That day, Emperor Ying Yuan did not destroy this cocoon.
He used a deceptive trick.
Then he came to help you cross the river.
During a battle, it fell into the river.
Butterfly of Lucid Dreaming is banned in the Heavenly Realm.
I'll not allow you to have it anymore.
♫  I searched near and far, but I couldn't find your eyes  ♫
A Butterfly of Lucid Dreaming.
Didn't they say...
one will spawn when you let go of your love?
If I already let go of him...
why does it still hurt this much?
All records say the Butterfly of Lucid Dreaming will only break out of its cocoon once it senses true love.
That's why it went extinct 10,000 years ago in the Nine Heavens after the Heavenly Rules were enforced.
Only when it detects no love and no sentiment...
will it break out of its cocoon.
Even if you crush it, it will still be reborn from resentment.
Ying Yuan, you have been lying to me.
You are indeed in love with me.
Yet you still chose this world over me.
Okay.
I'm living with all my memories, once again.
If you can let go of me...
I can also let go of you.
Even if I can't forget you...
I will cast away all my love.
Yan Dan, don't become too heartbroken.
Emperor Ying Yuan wasn't being cruel.
He had no choice.
From now on, I won't love him anymore.
I will only live for myself.
♫   Fate played tricks on me, causing my tears to fall   ♫
Thank you, Yi Zang.
♫   I'll never regret my decision, even if I have to suffer in the Six Paths   ♫
The agarwood ember flickered wearily, the dust of love scattered to the wind.
My heart was broken in my previous life and my sadness shall part with the wind.
Yan Dan regained her memory.
As she looked into her past, she did not want to be troubled by love again.
Fate has led them to meet again.
Did she gain what was lost or did she lose what was gained?
People say when the agarwood turns into ashes, there's no turning back.
However, some are willing to sacrifice themselves because the ember still flickers.
Due to his broken celestial vest, Tang Zhou's life is at risk.
Everyone travels once again in search of the last Divine Tool.
The return of Emperor Ying Yuan is coming soon.
He will uncover the secret about his bloodline and unveil the identity of the ambusher.
The mystery surrounding the Divine-Devil War will be uncovered.
The story does not end here.
May the agarwood rekindle once more for our reunion.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ¢  The Turtle-Flipping Deity Team  ðŸ¢  @ Viki.com
''Agarwood'' - Zhang Jie | Jane Zhang
♫   My most bewildering memory is the moonlight falling like frost on the ground full of fallen leaves   ♫
♫   For a single teardrop, I'm drowning myself in sorrow, obsessing with forgetting you   ♫
♫   If we'd have to walk till we separate, to where would you want to go?   ♫
♫   Turn around and become the delusion of my life  ♫
♫   The most beautiful destiny is hidden in the dark night, "love" is the word for everything   ♫
♫   My loneliness and longing for you leaves a mark like fragments of the moon   ♫
♫   I still have an image of you imprinted in my mind even after washing away the fine dust   ♫
♫   Life after life, this is the longing I missed the most  ♫
♫   You are the breeze of a fallen flower in the world of flowers adding to the mound of fallen flowers   ♫
♫   Will you shed tears over the truth of the mortal world?   ♫
♫   You're like the unattainable Autumn Moon in the vast sky, don't dare to shine bright yet not hesitate to shine  ♫
♫   In my dream, the one I loved is with me   ♫
♫   After bidding farewell, when Spring becomes Autumn, where can I find my heart in this world?   ♫
♫   Several lifetimes will not be enough for our parting   ♫
♫   As I watch lovers enjoying fireworks on the riverbanks, my love and longing for you makes my pain unbearable  ♫
♫   There will be a time when the world is beautiful   ♫
♫   When the lotus blossoms again, you and I will be together   ♫