Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ¢  The Turtle-Flipping Deity Team  ðŸ¢  @ Viki.com
Immortal Lord Yue Yao.
- Are you drunk again?
- Not at all.
Cheers.
Marshal Huo De.
Your Supreme Majesty, it's been a long time since I last drank with you.
- Come on, here's a toast to you.
- Marshal Huo De.
Wait!
The world is at peace.
The Three Realms are free from chaos.
My fellow immortals, a toast to His Supreme Majesty!
A toast to His Supreme Majesty!
Yan Dan.
Tortoise-Flipping Man.
♫   You always light up the long night like the stars and moon   ♫
♫   Your smile melts my cold heart   ♫
♫   No matter how the world changes, you're always by my side   ♫
♫   If time is the wilderness, you're a flower field planting memories   ♫
♫   I've never said I miss you and I wonder when I fell in love with you   ♫
♫   We're entangled like agarwood intertwined into flames   ♫
♫   It doesn’t extinguish and I've forgotten the cold wind and snow along the way   ♫
♫   I've experienced the ups and downs of the world alone   ♫
♫   Finally, I can rest in your heart   ♫
♫   We've been together for a lifetime and gone through all the trials   ♫
♫   We won't complain as time will turn our hardship into sweetness   ♫
♫   I won't ask how long forever is, but we'll smile and laugh together   ♫
♫   Let the past be the past   ♫
♫   We're entangled like agarwood intertwined into flames   ♫
♫   It doesn’t extinguish and I've forgotten the cold wind and snow along the way   ♫
♫   I've experienced the ups and downs of the world alone   ♫
♫   Finally, I can rest in your heart   ♫
♫   We've been together for a lifetime and gone through all the trials   ♫
♫   We won't complain as time will turn our hardship into sweetness   ♫
♫   I won't ask how long forever is, but we'll smile and laugh together   ♫
♫   Let the past be the past   ♫
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ¢  The Turtle-Flipping Deity Team  ðŸ¢  @ Viki.com