Do you know that Mink likes you?
I know.
But you don't look at Pie
the way you look at your brother's wife.
What are you trying to stir up with me?
Have you asked yourself
how you look at someone else's husband?
A smart person like you should see
that you don't fit in with Pun's family,
but you're pushing through.
Seriously, are you happy
with how things are now?
I've got an appointment with Dr. Bee.
We'll discuss the IVF process tomorrow.
Have you ever been pregnant
or had a miscarriage?
I've had a miscarriage.
Please don't tell Pun
about my miscarriage yet.
I'll find a chance
to talk to him about it myself.
Go home! I said I'm going home. Now!
How can you stay calm about this?
It's like this isn't a big deal.
Pun.
You're grown up now.
You should understand me.
Understand what, Dad?
Understand you've been lying to us
and that you have another family?
Or now that I'm grown up,
I should just accept everything you do,
even if it's wrong?
Let me be clear, I don't understand.
I don't know how long
you've been lying to us.
But today, you have to make a choice.
You have to end this!
Pun.
I'm not choosing anything.
You see, I just had a baby with her.
How can I just leave her?
And I can't leave your mom either.
Do you think your mom
would just accept that?
Wait, Dad.
Why are you being so selfish?
Does that woman know?
Does she know about Mom and me?
She knows. She knows everything.
She knows, and she accepts it?
And this is the kind of person you chose?
I'm starting to doubt
what kind of person you are.
The dad I respected.
The dad I trusted.
The one who doesn't drink, doesn't smoke,
doesn't curse.
The one who practiced meditation,
who loved nature.
What was all that, Dad?!
Were you lying to me?
Were you just putting on an act?
Can I still trust you?
Pun.
I'm sorry.
It's useless, Dad.
You don't need to apologize.
Even if you apologize,
you're not fixing what you've done wrong.
You're still choosing to be selfish.
So why even apologize to me?
I'm sorry for disappointing you.
I'm so disappointed in you!
I never thought
you could do something like this.
You've made me feel like a fool.
Like you've been deceiving me
since I was a kid.
I'm not trying to make excuses.
But I never cheated on your mom before.
I've never done anything like this.
When you're as old as me,
you'll understand.
What do you want me to understand?
Understand that people can change.
The patience in a relationship
has its limits.
What we used to tolerate,
eventually we don't want to anymore.
When you don't want to tolerate it,
you have to find a way out!
By cheating?
By finding someone who values us more!
You know what your mom is like.
Before we got married,
I knew I was inferior to her in every way.
But because I loved her, I tolerated it.
I tolerated her pushing me down,
controlling me.
Over time, I couldn't take it anymore.
Then why didn't you talk to Mom?
Why didn't you communicate with her?
You can't use this reason to cheat on her.
I tried to talk to her.
But she wouldn't listen.
She never tried to adjust.
She's the way she is.
We can't change who she is.
You don't need to explain
anything anymore.
Your reasons don't make sense.
Then I won't say anything more.
When you're ready,
we'll have a heart-to-heart talk,
man to man.
Man to man?
Is what you're doing really manly?
Go ahead.
Do whatever makes you feel at ease.
If you want to think
or do something, go for it.
I know I've made a mistake.
I won't say anything more about it.
But there's just one thing I ask.
Keep this between us.
Don't let your mom find out.
You're saying it so easily.
If you want to make it hard,
go ahead and tell your mom.
But remember, Pun.
The person who will be hurt the most
is your mom.
Some things in life,
we don't need to know about.
Especially things that make us unhappy.
It's up to you now,
how you want to handle this.
22:03
FRIDAY 18TH AUGUST
Why are you coming home so late?
Where have you been?
Work.
Pie.
I'm asking you nicely.
I'm concerned.
Why are you answering me so bluntly?
At least I'm blunt,
not disappearing all day like you did.
I called, you didn't answer or call back.
Why should I speak nicely to you?
Why should I be the one
to explain everything gently?
It's not fair.
Why are you starting something with me?
I came home tired.
We should've talked nicely.
Don't act unreasonable like this.
Pun, I have my reasons.
Reasons you never ask about or listen to.
Then you assume I have no reasons.
Pie.
Seriously, what's going on?
Are you upset about something
and taking it out on me?
I haven't done anything to you.
I just asked where you've been.
Why are you getting so upset with me?
This is how you are, Pun.
It's always my fault. You're never wrong.
I haven't done anything to you.
I'm asking out of concern.
What did I do wrong?
Okay!
You're never wrong, Pun.
You're always right.
It's all my fault.
I'm the one who's wrong.
I'm no good, nothing good about me.
Stop with the sarcasm!
Are you looking for a fight?
I'm not being sarcastic.
I'm telling the truth.
I've never been good
in anyone's eyes here.
Stop!
Don't bring other people into this.
Who do you mean by "anyone here"?
You can't talk about my mom like that.
Yeah, I can't say anything about anyone!
But everyone has the right
to criticize me.
They can insult, mock, belittle me,
and say whatever they want!
Go ahead, say whatever you want!
I don't feel anything, Pun!
Ma'am. Ma'am.
Mr. Pun and Ms. Pie
are having a huge argument.
It's so loud,
it's even heard outside the house.
What?
- Let's go see.
- Yes.
Pie, what's going on?
Why are you acting like this?
Why can't we talk about it nicely?
- Will throwing a tantrum solve anything?
- Throwing a tantrum?
I've never thrown a tantrum, Pun.
I'm just protecting myself.
Honestly, I should have done this
a long time ago.
But I didn't
because I tried to be patient.
I stayed patient because I thought
things would get better!
The patience in a relationship
has its limits.
What we used to tolerate,
eventually we don't want to anymore.
When you don't want to tolerate it,
you have to find a way out!
Don't talk to me like that!
Oh my goodness!
What's going on?
What did you do, Pie?
Why is Pun this angry?
Mom, I need to talk to Pie alone.
Talking won't help.
Your wife isn't good for anything.
She just causes you stress.
What you just said, is it really right?
You still have to ask?
Can't you see his face?
It's obvious he's not happy.
If I'm the one making you unhappy,
then we shouldn't stay together.
Pie!
- Where are you going?
- Pun!
- I won't let you go. Come back!
- Pun, don't!
- Stop! I won't let you go!
- Let her go.
- Pie!
- Just let her go.
Hold him tight. Hurry up.
Pun, listen to me.
Don't say anything right now.
If you're going to talk,
wait until you both cool down.
Trust me, okay?
Go get the staff and clean up the house.
- Quickly.
- Yes, ma'am.
Pie!
What happened? Did you and Pun argue?
Was it really that bad?
Are you really packing your things
to go stay with me?
- What happened, Pie?
- Mom.
I'm going to take a bath and sleep first.
I have to go out of town tomorrow.
I need to leave early.
Hey, Pie.
Tell me what happened with Pun first.
What did you argue about?
Pie.
Mom.
Please let me be.
Hello, Pun.
What's going on?
Why is Pie staying at my house?
We had an argument, Mom. It's my fault.
I'm stressed about Dad,
and I ended up taking it out on her.
Oh no!
Alright, I understand
that the situation with your dad is tough.
But don't forget,
Pie doesn't know anything about this.
Here's the plan. I'll talk to her for you.
Just calm down for now,
and you can talk tomorrow.
Wait, no!
She said she has to work
out of town tomorrow.
Let's talk another time, then.
Sure.
I'm sorry. Goodbye.
Pie, where are you?
Pie.
It's okay, sweetheart.
Don't cry, Pie.
Life in marriage is like this, you know.
There are arguments sometimes.
But you just have to talk,
adjust, and work things out.
And it will get better, okay?
It might not get better, Mom.
I've tried my best.
But it's just too much.
Well, it's okay.
If it's too much, take a break first.
When you've rested,
you can talk things through again,
and it will get better.
Pie.
Marriage isn't always smooth.
Once you work things out, talk it over,
everything will be okay.
Don't cry, sweetheart.
Hey, Pun!
How did you get here?
I had an argument with Pie.
About what?
It's something trivial.
I probably took out all my stress
from other things on her.
She ended up going back to her mom's.
I've never seen myself act like this.
I don't even know what happened.
It just exploded out of nowhere.
So how is Pie doing?
She's in shock, of course.
Did you blow up…
to the point of getting physical?
No, not like that.
I didn't hurt Pie physically.
But I still feel bad about it.
I know she has to work
out of town tomorrow.
Rok told me
it's just the two of them going.
I'm worried.
I want you to help me out.
But Pie already has Rok, right?
Rok doesn't really know much.
It's just the two women going.
I'm worried.
You know the area better than they do,
since you're local.
Please.
Take care of Pie for me.
Why don't you go yourself?
I have something important to do.
Please help me feel at ease.
04:30
SUNDAY 3RD SEPTEMBER
ONE MINUTE
Here it is. Is this the one?
Not this one.
I called for the bigger one.
Hey, Win! How did you get here?
Pun told me to come.
So surprised.
What's the surprise?
Pun told me you booked the ticket for me.
He said I should fly to Chiang Mai,
then drive to Mae Hong Son.
Oh right, I completely forgot about that.
Rok.
You're terrible at lying. Try again.
Well.
Hey, here it is. This is the one.
Let's go. Get in the car.
Hurry up, Pie.
Mom!
Rok, help me!
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
Rok.
I'm so sorry.
You missed work because of me.
It's fine, Mom.
It wasn't my main job anyway.
I was just accompanying Pie.
You're more important.
That's sweet.
- Take it easy, Mom.
- Okay.
Who's here?
I'll be right back, Mom.
Okay, go check.
Who's here? Rok!
Krarok, Dad's here!
Dad!
- Hey!
- Dad!
You're back!
Come on.
Dad!
You said you were coming next week.
What happened?
Oh, come on. I missed you guys.
Can't I come earlier?
Dad, tell me the truth.
The stinky beans are perfect.
I wanted your mom to enjoy them,
so I swapped shifts with a friend.
So, where's Mom?
You didn't read the message?
I didn't turn on the internet.
No wonder you didn't know.
- What do you mean?
- Mom fell. The doctor says she needs rest.
She's in a cast at home.
Why tell me now?
Oh, shoot!
Mom, does it hurt a lot?
Dad's here!
Since when did you start
calling yourself that?
He's been watching
too many YouTube videos.
Mom.
That's so sad.
Looks like no more fun for you now.
‪What a shame.
I was going to take you on a date.
Such a shame.
Hey, don't worry.
I'll get you an electric wheelchair.
Oh, no need. You're overdoing it.
I'll be fine soon.
As for the date, we can have it at home.
- Want a date with me?
- You're so full of yourself!
You're the one
who came to see me, remember?
If I can't come see my wife,
where else should I go?
That was harsh, but true.
- Oh, it hurts.
- Does it hurt?
- It hurts.
- Take it easy.
THA PHAE GATE
Hey, how's your mom doing?
She's okay.
Her leg still hurts,
but she's got someone to comfort her.
Her husband came.
They're sitting there, all lovey-dovey.
Even at their age, they're still so sweet.
It makes me jealous.
You can't be jealous of your dad, can you?
Hey, let them be sweet. Come join me here.
Let's go together. What do you think?
It's fine. I don't
want to waste your time.
Plus, I want to spend time with Dad.
I don't often see him from down south.
Rok!
Come help me peel the stinky beans!
Okay, I'll be right there, boss.
I've gotta go now.
Dad's calling me.
You be nice to Win, okay?
Don't argue and mess up the work.
I'll try.
Bye.
Let's go.
Why not hire a driver to take us?
It'd be easier.
Easier for getting car sick, you mean.
If I don't drive, I'll throw up.
I feel sorry for myself.
Feel sorry for those
waiting for you to throw up.
You throw up
more than a pregnant woman does.
You remember that?
Hurry up. I don't want to get there late.
CHIANG MAI BUS TERMINAL
Is Grandma Khamman not here?
Yes, she went up the mountain.
She goes back and forth.
She has two houses.
One here and one up on the mountain.
She went up there just the other day.
Did you two make an appointment with her?
Yes, I called to schedule it yesterday.
She probably forgot.
She gets confused sometimes,
so it's uncertain.
Yes.
Can we drive up to see Grandma
on the mountain?
Are you from the north?
Yes, my mom's from Chiang Rai.
We're from the same place then.
You know what?
I'll have my partner drive you.
It's difficult to drive up the mountain.
No need to go up yourself.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
You can take the money
for gas and travel expenses.
It's okay. No need.
Don't worry about money.
Don't talk about it.
- I'll have my partner take you.
- Thank you.
Honey! Honey!
Come here for a second.
Yes?
Can you drive them up to the mountain?
To Grandma Khamman's house.
Sure.
Sorry to bother you.
It's fine. No problem.
PUN
Excuse me a bit. I'll be right back.
I'm really sorry to bother you.
Yes, Pun?
How's it going, Win?
Have you found any information?
I've just arrived.
But Grandma moved up to the mountain.
I'll have the locals
take me up to see her.
And what about Pie?
Pie…
She's focused on her work, like usual.
Okay.
I'm feeling less worried now.
Thanks a lot, Win.
I'll call for an update later.
Take good care of Pie and Rok.
Yes, Pun.
Hey!
Stop the car. I'm gonna puke!
I can't stop here!
Hold it in for now!
Wait, hold on. Don't throw up yet.
Here.
Take whatever you need.
Take some pills.
Water.
I've got gum and mints too.
Help yourself.
Why do you have everything?
For people who don't have anything.
Why are you smiling?
You're even more prepared now.
I brought it for Rok, not for anyone else.
But seeing your condition, I had to share.
You don't have to take it.
I'll take it.
- Rok.
- Yes?
Leave some garlic skin on.
Your mom likes it that way.
Got it.
- Dad.
- What's up?
You work far from Mom.
Sometimes you don't meet for months.
Do you have a mistress?
Plenty.
Does our house have a ghost or something?
Come on, what for?
Why would I have one?
I don't go looking for trouble
or create problems for myself.
Why do you think that way?
My life's good right now.
I have a lovely wife,
a beautiful daughter,
a house, and enough money
to live comfortably.
When I'm tired from work,
I just call you and your mom,
and I feel better.
I finish work,
have dinner, and sleep well.
My life right now, it's perfect.
So, what's wrong with having a mistress?
It's wrong in every way.
Having a mistress means what?
Your wife finds out, you argue, break up,
and the kid feels bad.
You come home tired
and have to cover up the mistake you made.
What a mess.
Sure, it might be exciting at first.
With that kind of thing.
But the trouble follows you like a shadow.
I don't need that. Not worth it.
Dad, you're so cool.
Mom is so lucky to have you as a husband.
And I'm really lucky to have you as a dad.
You're my darling girl.
Dad, do you know?
Every one of my exes
has plenty of mistresses.
No one thinks like you do.
Don't worry about that, sweetheart.
With things like this,
if it's meant to be,
it will come naturally.
As for all those bad people in the past,
just cut ties and move on.
You're dressed a bit differently today.
Is this a new style?
Come on, tell me. What's going on?
Nothing right now.
But if things become clear,
I'll bring him to introduce to you
at your work site down south.
Bring him! I'm waiting for him!
Anyway, I'll go call him now.
You were this small.
And now look at you.
The love life of young people.
MR. SHOHEI
Sorry, the number that you've dialed
cannot be connected at this time.
Looks like you're out of range.
How's everything?
How many rounds did you two argue?
Anyway, take care of yourself.
I'm worried.
Why isn't he back yet?
Pun!
Hey.
How's your wife?
She's not coming back, right?
Mom.
Pie's just upset with me.
We haven't broken up yet.
Mom.
I just want you to be happy.
Be with a wife who's suitable,
who matches your status.
That's all I want.
Is Dad not back yet?
Not yet. Maybe he'll come back next week.
Who knows how far he's gotten
with his spiritual journey.
Let's eat. Come on.
Tian, serve the rice.
Come on. Time to eat.
I'll handle it myself.
All the dishes look delicious.
Look, we've got your favorite too.
This pig's trotter is really tasty.
Thanks, Pun.
Here.
- Mom.
- Yes?
Have you ever thought about…
what you'd do if Dad ever cheated on you?
Why are you asking?
Is your wife cheating on you?
No, Mom. It's not about Pie.
I'm just curious.
There's been news lately
about celebrities cheating.
So I was wondering,
if something like this happened,
what would you do?
I don't know. I've never thought about it.
Because your dad would never cheat on me.
Why are you so sure of that?
Pun.
Look at me.
Look at this house.
Look at our family.
Look at everything we have.
Where would your dad
find a woman better than me?
Nowhere.
But if he did, I'd be shocked.
I'd never think
someone we love could betray us.
And I'd be the most disappointed.
Loving someone means you'll get hurt more.
That's normal.
But I trust your dad.
He'd never betray me.
Now, let's eat.
MUNGMINK
Yes, Mink?
Has Pie moved back to her own place?
Did Mom call you to tell you about it?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
She told you about something unimportant.
No need to apologize.
I'm happy to listen.
Are you okay, Pun?
How are you doing?
That's a big sigh.
If you say you're okay,
I'd say you're lying.
My wife asked to go back to her mom's.
Who could be okay with that?
Well, let me say this again.
If you ever need to vent
or talk about anything,
I'm always here to listen.
Because in the past,
you've helped me feel better many times.
I'd like to return the favor.
I want to see you happy.
Thank you so much, Mink.
Good night.
Grandma Khamman
just went to bed a little while ago.
Let's talk tomorrow morning.
For now, let's rest.
I'll take you to another house.
Not far from here.
That house has a guest room.
- Follow me.
- Yes
Are you two married?
No, we're not.
We're coworkers.
Good thing I checked.
Almost had you two sharing a room.
Come on. Let's go.
Mom, I'm going too!
Stay here. I'll be right back.
Enjoy your meal!
- Thank you.
- Alright.
- Enjoy.
- Kaew, join us for the meal.
I've eaten already. Feel free.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
If I'm sitting here and you can't eat,
just let me know.
Quiet, just eat. No need to talk so much.
Pie, can we be friends?
No.
You don't even think about it?
Why are you smiling?
You're afraid of being friends with me,
so you deny it without even thinking.
I'm not afraid. Why would I be afraid?
That's for you to answer.
Why are you afraid
of being friends with me?
Why did you walk away?
See? You're afraid.
I'm not afraid.
Good, I don't want you to be afraid.
Pie.
We can be friends. Trust me.
We'll be good friends
and wish the best for each other.
Whenever you see me as a friend,
you can talk to me
about anything.
Uncle Dech sent you here?
Yes, Grandma.
Dech who?
Well, Grandma's getting older.
Some days she forgets things.
Try talking about Uncle Dech a lot.
That could help her recall.
Okay.
Grandma.
Do you remember Mrs. Sangdao?
She's Uncle Dech's mother.
Mr. Dechnarong.
You used to help her out.
I used to help her?
Yes.
I don't remember.
Grandma!
Grandma, where are you going?
I'm going to feed the pigs.
Feed the pigs?
Normally, at this time,
she'd go to feed the pigs.
So she would walk there.
It's like this.
Whether she remembers or not,
we just have to hope.
Follow her. Maybe she'll remember.
- Okay, Kaew. Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
Grandma!
Are you hungry?
Come on. Let's eat.
Eat up!
Grandma.
Uncle Dech said
that when you were younger,
you often helped his mom
pick out beautiful fabrics.
Is that right?
Come on. Eat a lot!
You can get big and strong.
This isn't going anywhere.
She's only talking to the pigs.
Yeah, right.
‪Yeah, like that.
Here's what I'll do.
I'll video call Uncle Dech
and have him talk to her.
Maybe that'll help.
I heard from Kaew
that there's some signal around here.
You stay and talk to her for now.
Grandma.
Pie is going to get Uncle Dech
to talk to you, okay?
Alright?
Yeah, just eat.
Okay?
Grandma.
Let me do it. You go rest.
Okay.
Be careful, Grandma.
Take it easy.
Alright, Grandma.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Make sure it eats a lot.
Okay.
Talk to it a little.
- Talk to who?
- Talk to the pig.
Talk to the pig?
Tell it to eat a lot.
Sure, let's do this.
Grandma, should I speak
in standard Thai or the Northern dialect?
Use the Northern dialect with it.
- With the pig, right?
- Yeah.
Talk to it so it understands.
Alright, pig!
Hey, eat up!
Grandma made this for you.
Come on, big boy.
- Eat a lot.
- Yeah.
- A pig has to be fat. Eat a lot!
- That's right.
- Feed the small one too.
- The small one too? Got it.
- Yes, that one.
You bit me?
Good job.
A pig has to be fat, or it's a waste.
Eat up, little one.
Here.
Yeah, eat more.
Just like that. Pigs have to be like this.
You chubby! Chubby pig.
There's no signal.
Thank you.
Sure.
Come on, eat!
Hurry up!
A pig has to eat a lot to get big.
That way, Grandma will be happy.
Yeah, just like that.
Big and fat, Grandma likes it.
Am I good at this?
Am I good at feeding pigs?
Yeah.
Good job.
It will get even bigger, Grandma.
Just wait and see.
Here.
You really do talk to the pigs,
just like Mr. Dech.
Mr. Dech likes to talk to dogs and cats.
Grandma.
Do you remember Uncle Dech now?
How could I forget?
I've known him since he was a kid.
Mr. Dech is a good talker,
just like this young man.
So, who are you to Mr. Dech?
Grandma, my name is Pie.
Uncle Dech asked me to interview you
about the fabrics.
I heard he already contacted you.
Do you remember?
How could I not remember?
I remember.
Mr. Dech is opening a fabric museum.
Yes, that's right.
Come on. I've got something to show you.
- Okay, sure.
- Alright.
- Please get up slowly.
- Okay.
- Take it easy.
- Yes.
- I've got it ready.
- Alright.
Grandma remembers now!
You finally smiled at me!
Grandma.
- Wait for me! I'll help.
- I shouldn't have said anything.
Well done, pig!
See you later!
Grandma, I'm coming.
Let's go!
This is the fabric logbook.
Mr. Dech's mother asked me
to keep track of everything
since I was young,
when I used to help buy fabrics.
It's all written down,
what kind of fabric it is,
where it's from, how it's woven.
This way, we won't forget when we sell it.
Wow, Grandma, this is really detailed!
Yes, I wrote it all down for selling.
But she never sold a single piece.
She kept them all.
So, which fabrics
is Mr. Dech going to showcase?
- Just a second.
- Okay.
I've prepared some pictures. Here you go.
- You can look through them, Grandma.
- Alright.
This is what we will showcase.
Actually, there are more.
You can look at this album first.
I'll go get the rest for you.
I'll go get it. You wait here.
‪-Right here.
‪-Yes.
- Are you alright?
- That must hurt a lot.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. It's okay.
I'll be right back.
Back to work. I'll be right back.
Oh my!
Seems like you're only good
at talking to pigs!
I think Pie has someone else.
People can have secrets,
even when you're always together.
If they want to hide something,
they'll find a way
to get away with it, surprisingly.
No matter where I stand,
I'll always be by your side.
No matter how much you change,
I'm the one who stays the same.
I'm not the perfect woman
who's never made a mistake.
I'm just a broken girl
who once got pregnant, Mom!
If she still hasn't told me
what's in her heart,
the secret she's hiding,
I'll find the truth myself.
Subtitle translation by:
Chomchanach Yanaharn