This way. Come on.
Where are we going?
Haven of Faith, Number 7
Plaque of Appreciation
Trigger
Top Producer
Oh Soryong
Producer Awards
Report on the Cha Seongwook
Disappearance Case
She pulled another all-nighter.
Trigger, Investigative journalism.
I've been robbed…
robbed of my son.
- Huh?
- They burned up my son.
Those Haven of Trust people did it.
His body is in ashes!
- Did you say Haven of Trust?
- Jeongnam!
How could they…
how could they do that to my baby?
We had no idea
those documents were forged either.
A forged birth certificate?
- Ma'am, please.
- Jeongnam!
- Hello?
- I need you to calm down…
- Ma'am. Ma'am!
- Give me back my son!
Excuse me, repeat that for me, ma'am,
if you could, please.
Wait, hello?
You're here early.
It… It's moving day, isn't it?
I was hoping to wrap up my edit
before shipping it to the director…
In This Beautiful World Of Ours
That idiot Jeongnam
drank himself to death,
the hell could I do?
Hold on a minute, pastor, come on.
Why don't you put the gun down
so we can talk this out?
Don't you take another step closer.
Do it and I'll shoot.
Hey, all of you! Cameras off!
Hey, hey, the cameras.
Put them down, guys.
Lower the cameras.
Turn them off and put them away.
Cameras are all gone.
That's how the man died.
It was his drinking…
…so we'll have them do an autopsy, huh?
While we're at it,
we could also check how the family--
I mean, the congregation's doing.
The guy's a nutcase.
Hello.
I wanted to introduce myself
with a present.
"Oh Soryong"? Who the hell are you?
I'm the team lead for Trigger.
Shame on you all!
Men answering to this godless jezebel.
Hey, I'm no ordinary jezebel.
Happened to hear
about last night's hasty cremation
and document forgery.
It was cremated? So there's no body?
What? Were you afraid
an autopsy would reveal traces
-of Halloween?
-You talking about drugs?
So you do know the zombie drug.
One shot of Halloween
destroys your veins
and causes skin necrosis,
which leaves us something like this.
Also, how does a right-handed man
inject himself over and over
just in his right arm?
Didn't you hear what the cops said?
He was drunk!
It was all the booze that killed him!
The blood-alcohol content
at time of death was below .038.
Most likely a by-product of decomposition
and can't serve as evidence of drinking.
Lady, you're not God.
How do you know what the kid did?
You think we need an autopsy to find out?
We're Trigger.
Here's a tox report
from Kim Jeongnam's blood sample
as taken at the scene,
and it says, "Lorazepam."
We've already confirmed that this sleep
medication is used here in Haven of Trust.
What's strange is all the other drugs
in his system as well.
Now how might someone
who never left the compound
shoot himself up with these new drugs?
So, pastor…
would you know?
He was born evil.
His spirit was unholy.
I'm the one who made--
-Why'd you kill my son?
-Whoa, whoa. Ma'am, hold on.
-Why?
-Hold on, ma'am, wait.
Did you forget dumping him here?
A little late to try and play
the "loving mother" act.
How dare you?
What? What? Tell me I'm wrong!
You know I'm right!
If you loved him so much,
you should've raised him yourself.
You sold him off because he was defective,
and you know it!
Whoa!
Jeongnam! Oh, my God, my son, Jeongnam!
Oh, my God,
my son, no!
You all have got some nerves
showing yourselves here.
Stop your whining.
You should be thanking me
for sending your son off to Heaven.
- Mister Lee!
- What's wrong? What is it?
Did you get shot?
I can't…
- breath.
- I'll call 911.
Call them fast! Lee Sangmok…
Whoa, sir!
- Officer, we have a man down.
- Breath, breath.
-Just try to breath.
-He's been shot!
We called a while ago. What took so long?
Trigger?
Get out of here.
No one's allowed on my property!
Hold it!
Why the fuck are you just standing there?
Why aren't you doing your damn jobs?
You should take this with you.
It's a gift, after all.
You sacrilegious little hussy!
Why don't you head inside?
I'll save you from a life of sin…
so you can never do this again.
That's it.
Woman, you got a death wish or something?
Whoa! No.
Whoa, hey! It's over, Ms. Oh.
-Just shoot.
-What?
It's a nice day out…
-so just shoot me.
-I'll really do it.
Do it. Go ahead!
-Hey, hey!
-Go ahead and shoot!
Go ahead and shoot! Do it!
-Ms. Oh!
-I am the son of God!
- Let go of her, you bastard!
- Shoot me!
- Pull the trigger!
- Let her go!
That producer at Trigger,
a known hunter of the corrupt.
The naked truth
about KNS's flagship show, Trigger
Is she really
the hero they say she is, or…
is she a two-faced villain?
Post
Views, Likes
Trigger Producer's Affair with a Colleague
Dr. Trigger
Another politician
from a "royal" background
has been elected
in this National Assembly Election.
Assemblyman-elect Cho Jinman…
…the son of Chairman Cho Taesu
of Hanju Group,
won his seat last week.
The election remained close
throughout the night,
with Assemblyman Cho ultimately--
Lee Sangmok, how's it going?
Looking good. You've got guts.
You can still finish the episode.
You can't be serious right now.
I'm injured. I can't work.
Hey.
They pointed a shotgun at us,
and then the cops say if we show up again,
we get a restraining order.
They're supposed to protect us,
-not the Haven of Trust.
-My point exactly.
Why even bother with these stories?
-This is a fucked up world…
-"Fu…"
Let's use "forked up", huh?
You should be proud of your work.
You exposed Pastor Kim, that's great.
Your sense of duty is inspiring.
After two weeks, I reached my limit.
I haven't been home at all.
I can't remember
the last time I changed my socks.
And I've failed.
I can get us in, I figured it out.
Great, do it yourself.
Yeah.
'Cause I'm resigning.
Yoon said that yesterday.
You taking turns with him or something?
Goddamnit,
don't you ever get sick of this?
With every story I do,
I get more fear and more hate
for this terrible world of ours.
How?
How do you stay so optimistic
through all this?
We're both in the same line of work,
how do you do it?
That's what pisses me off the most.
Is he injured that bad?
Uh…
Ms. Oh, can we step outside?
Seriously?
I mean, did you not hear about the post
on the Trigger forums?
I got to plan a business trip, got hauled
by my hair to fill out forms
for the cops, so, no, I did not.
Is it because he just had that kid?
Like postpartum depression or something?
Uh… that kid is like three years old.
It's a panic disorder. Look at this.
The servers crashed
right after this was posted
and once they came back up,
the post was gone.
It's fake news and it's hack.
We're too much of a big ugly family
for an affair.
This isn't a joke,
the tabloids are running wild.
So we let them run.
That's no reason for him to go off on me.
He's the one
supposedly cheating on his wife.
"It has to be Lee.
I've seen him hit on writers."
It's just a bunch of trolls
looking for attention.
I'm sorry, but how is an investigative
journalist falling for this?
What if it did happen?
Ah, hold on. Wait, wait, wait.
-You're not going to ask him, right?
-Of course.
We always fact check with the source.
-It's protocol.
-To hell with protocol.
-You know he's testy, come on.
-Stop being scared.
Have the guts to go in and get the facts
instead of talking behind the man's back.
He may be testy,
but his pride's what keeps him going.
An affair?
When he's ready to go back in the field,
shoot me a text.
Oh, my goodness. Everything's so shiny.
And they say they're in the red.
Creating an Honest World
KNS
Trigger: Firing the Bullet of Truth
Well, look who it is.
If it isn't dear Ms. Oh Soryong,
our country's own protector of justice.
Hey, Lee Sangmok!
How about that cheater who resigned, huh?
I heard the editing room was his spot.
Poor guy must've been stressed.
You should get your people into yoga.
You ride them too hard.
Ride them how? Are they bicycles?
You haven't changed a bit, have you, sir?
Still learning the meaning of respect,
I see.
You can get in trouble for that nowadays.
Why don't you speak for yourself.
You're a disobedient one.
-Ain't that right?
-Is it?
I heard about the singer
you got dirt on, some has-been.
He is not just a has-been.
It's Cha Seongwook.
And what dirt? I'm no muckraker.
Aren't you concerned? Or you fearless?
I learned a few things
from this amazing director in drama.
He happened to teach
this rookie producer fearlessness.
Oh…
They're replacing mister cheater
-with a real freak.
-Stop calling him a cheater!
Ah, should've gotten rid
of his ass long ago.
The benefit of being full-time, huh?
These pesky workplace laws…
they're pretty fucked up.
What do you think?
Man, I wish
I could do it in the edit bay.
This thing was on the whole time,
oh, my goodness. It's a habit.
I called you hours ago.
You go to the old office or something?
Getting my things.
So you haven't seen
your new office at all?
Why? Is it…
Mid Century Modern?
Have I not made myself clear
to stop working so much
and help your team out, huh?
Your team's a mess
with their leader always
neglecting them for an investigation.
Is this about the affair?
My God, are you serious?
You know how Lee Sangmok is.
He doesn't have the balls
to cheat on his wife.
What's the matter with people?
Who'd screw that guy?
-No one.
-Well, why else would they say it?
Unless someone here's been making
the beast with two backs on the clock.
What's wrong with consenting adults
getting a little action?
-What?
-You know I'm right!
What's wrong with sex if it's not illegal?
Or an affair?
We know you guys do
some shady things in here.
-Oh, jeez, don't start with that.
-Can you really blame the guy
with his so-called family judging him?
I'd probably quit too.
I'll say it again.
I don't believe these stupid rumors.
How do you believe something
with no proof, huh?
Good for you. That's great.
Here. Courtesy of the president's office.
Hmph. After slashing our budget… bananas.
It's a yellow card.
You'll be out
if you don't quit smearing the guy.
Mr. Condom?
He knows a lot about smearing things,
I'm sure.
That Dr. Trigger post…
Did KNS delete that?
Apparently,
the original poster removed it.
The IP was somewhere in Ghana.
What did I say?
It's just somebody fishing for a reaction.
Oh, um… I heard we're getting
some guy from soaps.
That scumbag Jang told me
you're getting a guy that's a total freak.
He seems to have it easy though.
It's easier being shameless.
Apparently, he applied
to Animal Paradise first.
He's a bit too old to be a rookie.
Han Do, Born in 1990
So he is.
But why the Animal Paradise job?
Well, I'll tell you why.
Humans are hopeless.
He said those exact words
-to the general manager's face?
-He probably won't work.
Way to go. Love that.
According to his résumé,
he won some film award or something.
"Post Mise-en-scène Film Festival,
Audience award"
Great credentials and still ends up
at Current Affairs,
must have pissed someone off pretty good,
or… he screwed up royally.
-Wouldn't you guess?
-Exactly.
We've got no manpower with Lee out.
There's not much of a choice
for a manager to make here.
He's the best you've got.
Well, I'd say it's a chief's job
to get a little leverage over the bosses.
Your chief stuff's pissing me off,
all right?
What about tomorrow's episode?
-What are you gonna do?
-I'm doing it, of course.
-Why even bother asking?
-Our director's resigned
and we got no hook.
If you air this episode
and we haven't got a kill shot
-then our ratings not only--
-I know, I know, our ratings drop
and then we've got lawsuits.
-It pisses me off more than you know.
-In the show's long history,
we've never canceled an episode. Ever.
-You know this.
-You know I've never backed down
from anything.
Oh, and uh…
our "hopeless humans" rookie,
he'll be dropping in to meet the team
before his official start.
Can you just, for once in you life,
not make him run for the door?
I'm as nice as they make 'em.
Delivery Request
Decline
Jo Mingeun, if you keep missing tutoring,
you'll end up like this man.
Smacking on candy, delivering stuff,
like he's proud of what he does.
You plant poop, that's what you'll get.
You never heard that one before?
Don't sling poop or you'll end up
-like your poopy mom. Here.
-Oh, my go…
Good luck pooping.
Don't be a poopy head.
And now, I'm pooping out of here.
That man's a lunatic!
That's it,
I'm posting this guy's picture online.
Whoa, hey, Mingeun, wait for me.
Let's walk together.
Sorry, guys.
Not sure there's room.
Can you hit five for me? Thanks.
Whoa, you're Oh Soryong, right?
I'm such a huge fan of your show.
- Real big fan.
- Oh, I appreciate it.
But, by the way,
that rumor going around…
that affair. Is it true?
Can you just hit five?
I got my hands full here.
Why is the basement "one half"?
They should have just picked a number.
I mean, commit, you know?
KNS
Current Affairs Department
A man can't enjoy a lollipop?
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Animal Paradise
Yup.
You guys are just better.
This is the Amazing Animal Paradise,
isn't it?
Yeah, it is, but this isn't
where you're assigned.
Excuse me.
What happened to our office?
Isn't this Current Affairs?
Ah, I guess nobody told you.
The president told us
to move in here this morning.
Wait, the president…
All right, look,
my name is Han Do
and if you would just check
with HR again…
- Soaps guy?
- Uh… Huh?
You're not here.
Trigger's this way.
-Is that right?
-Uh-huh.
But why am I…
You're with us.
And where'd my office move to?
Trigger
- This is too crazy.
- The dog! The dog! The dog!
Get the dog!
Oh, hi Ms. Oh!
Are you kidding me?
- You can't be serious.
- No, no, no, no, don't eat that.
We're neck-deep in work right now, okay?
I'm sending this dog up the elevator
with a pile of crap, you hear me?
I'm not kidding! I'll do it.
Whoa, wait! Hold on, oh, God.
-What on earth?
-The Animal Paradise guys
rescued 200 dogs.
Then one just happened
to have a litter of puppies,
which is why we've taken
this guy on temporarily.
But why us?
Giho and Ha are out working on a story,
our forums are blowing up,
and there's no sign of the new guy.
They're treating us like we're maids.
I almost broke my back
just lugging all this stuff down here.
Koo Hyeongtae, that good-for-nothing…
Wait, you can't go up there.
Not to the president.
Are you out of your mind?
I know, sweetie,
you're important or whatever
but he's the president.
I don't care if he's the president,
he should know!
We haven't done anything wrong here.
I'm going upstairs.
Oh, sweetie, you're getting a call.
- Hey.
- Hey, Ms. Oh.
It's an emergency, it's a red alert.
- Whoa, wait, wait, wait,
- Hey, look, it's Pastor Kim, right?
- Sports car?
- Huh? It is, yeah.
Get down, get down.
Ms. Oh,
Pastor Kim's on his way out right now,
but the real problem is
these tour buses that keep driving in.
Ooh! There's another one.
Oh, duck!
Ms. Oh, right now,
uh, a van and two tour buses
are going up the hill.
What if those people drop dead tonight?
- Then we close in!
- Huh?
We strike, it's time to go.
Today. Lee's out,
so we infiltrate
and get the footage that we need.
I'm going to Yongpyeong,
you stay right where you are.
Wait, whoa… listen.
I'm… I'm not able to do
anything dangerous today, I'm serious.
I still haven't totally healed
from that rib injury that I got.
Hello?
Seriously? Damn it.
What'd she say?
-She's on her way over now.
-Right now?
Call the others.
I got to get back to Yongpyeong.
Ah, but don't call anyone
who's out of town.
And get Seo for me.
We need everyone if we're gonna finish
this episode by tomorrow.
Go interview the M.E.
who did the autopsy on Kim Jeongnam.
We have to get that.
But what's the use without Sangmok?
Tell the world we're canceling an episode
for the first time
because the director ran away?
Why not?
We're already at rock bottom, aren't we?
I mean, what do you think you can do
without a director?
Well, I'm not alone. Got my rookie.
What? Come in.
He transferred from Soap Operas.
Your name?
Sorry, but I think you're mistaken.
I'm not the person--
-Oh, what are you doing?
-Formally onboarding you.
Effective immediately.
What kind of onboarding is--
It's a new fad
with Gen Z couples these days.
It's a gift.
Now, now, don't try to run away.
You're gonna help us out, okay?
Hmm? We need you.
I thought we'd do your welcome party
-outside in the sun.
-What--
Do you like extreme sports, by chance?
When the heck is she getting here?
He… hey, what are you doing? Come on.
- Man, sure must be nice.
- What do you mean?
Wow, that looks fun.
- Wait a minute.
- That place is a fortress.
How's she getting in?
Where is the producer anyway?
Uh… descending from the air.
Hey, stop that.
Giho, pull it together.
Whoa!
Ms. Hong. Ms. Hong!
Ms. Hong. Get this.
Where are the dogs?
Oh, I took them back, no issues.
Whatever, guess what I found out.
You know the rookie from earlier?
I got a friend on the Drama staff
and they just told me what happened.
Well, they didn't personally witness it
but her brother's supervisor's friend did.
And you will not believe the reason
that he got canned from Soap Operas.
All right, so, uh…
I heard Han Do got fired…
'cause he peed on Jang.
-What?
-Maybe it was more like
he blasted him with urine.
An eruption of urine?
There was pee though.
You fucking asshole!
Watch where you're aiming!
- Ah, dammit, crazy fuck!
- He then went,
"You crazy bastard,
you fucking disgusting piss guy."
And then he just walked away.
Guess everyone thinks they're a writer now
-with these stories.
-This happened, I'm telling you.
There's no way
that if someone actually peed on Jang,
he would have just cursed and walked away.
Oh, so you know Mr. Jang? Seriously?
- Not very well, but Oh does.
- Oh Soryong?
Wait, you're saying
that Ms. Oh knows that man?
Sweetie,
take it from another writer,
if you want to keep your job here,
you got to learn to keep your mouth shut.
So quit worrying about all that
and make sure you find out
how things are going on Giho's end.
Okay, but do you think--
Got it.
You're crazy!
We've both got legs!
Crazy bitch.
The hell was she talking about?
Don't worry, don't help or anything.
God, I'm exhausted.
911?
Uh, I was out paragliding,
and I seem to have…
landed in the wrong spot.
Oh, this place?
I don't know.
It looks like a facility of some kind
but I don't know the exact--
Right, please hurry.
Haven of Faith, Number 13
This…
All this…
Who did this?
The pastor's wife.
-The pastor's wife?
-Mm-hmm.
Where are the others?
Are they here?
Where's everyone else?
Timer
Hey, rookie.
Hurry.
You lost your mind?
It's very important you stay with this guy
and hide somewhere.
Give me 30 minutes.
If help isn't here by then,
you hurry,
get out and call the police, okay?
Listen to me,
our assistant director's outside, Giho.
Let go!
Whatever you do, make sure
that this guy makes it out safely, okay?
Ugh, why am I doing this?
Here.
Ugh, as a last resort.
Okay, I'll take it then.
-Oh…
-Where are you--
Take this too.
You're guarding him.
Don't forget.
Wait, hey!
You kidding me? Jesus!
Can you tell me how to get out?
The exit…
The exit.
- Ex…
- I'm trying to get out.
The door.
Door.
Ah, ah…
Over there?
The exit. Is it… is it that way?
Oh, damn it. Whatever.
I can't help this dude if I die anyway.
I'll go outside and I'm calling the cops,
stay right here.
-Huh?
-Freeze game.
You act like ice till…
I touch you. Start the game.
Ah… ah…
Ice game!
Ah…
Freeze game.
Those who follow the voice…
Healing Through Faith
Ugh, where exactly
did he say the exit was?
Oh, God, this is the wrong direction.
Oh!
It's not human.
You're looking at a beast right here.
A crazed, worthless lowlife.
You're worth less than our crypto rigs.
We were 30 million
in the red last month.
How dare you doze off, huh?
These machines, they mine for us
though we feed them nothing.
But all you do is eat,
giving nothing in return.
You see how you're a parasite?
You got to do better than that
to enter the kingdom of faith!
Amen!
By the power of faith shall you rise!
So she's the mastermind.
And now for the mother
who raised her child to be a parasite!
You, get up here.
-Go on, go on.
-You need to be punished.
Goodness! I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, okay? Get up!
Now then, hit her 100 times.
- Hurry up and hit her!
- Hit her!
Hit her!
I guess you won't fully understand
unless I give you a punishment injection.
Hurry up and hit her!
Want me to show you how?
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
-It's because all of you…
-Please!
…are such disgraces
that those media sons of bitches
always look down on us!
What the hell is that?
Oh Soryong from Trigger!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Get that bitch!
Get the outsider!
Stop chasing me!
Han! You hear me? Hey!
- Han Do!
- What the hell did you do?
Grab the traitor!
Hmph.
Ugh, what is going on?
Didn't she say half an hour?
Yeah, I thought so. What's going on?
Whoa, hold on.
Someone's coming.
-Huh?
-Someone's coming.
Whoa, here they come!
- What's going on?
- Open the gate!
They're right behind us!
Get off her! Ms. Oh!
-Hey, Ms. Oh!
-Take this, Giho!
Let go! Get off!
Hey! Get off of him!
Get off of him!
-Let him go!
-Help me!
Hey, Giho!
- Take this! You ready?
- Whoa! Ms. Oh, no!
Kang Giho!
Giho!
I can't get the gate open!
Ms. Oh!
-Ms. Oh!
-Hey!
Freaking idiot!
Oh, shoot.
Whoa! Hey, hey, Ms. Oh!
-Ms. Oh! Ms. Oh! I'm sorry!
-Shit!
Ms. Oh!
It's the police.
The police, the police!
There's a person inside!
- Over here!
- Hurry, hurry, hurry!
- They're inside.
- They got our team leader!
- Hurry, damn it!
Open the gate!
Yongpyeong Police Station
Detective, uh, is this really going to go
on my permanent record?
It's hard enough being freelance.
-Zombies, you say?
-Kidnapping, illegal guns, assault.
She gives an order
and a bunch of her followers,
these enormous men, go and drag off
this woman acting like a zombie
like she was some wild forest creature.
-Right. And then?
-And then…
God, you're not listening.
I saw everything.
They're growing flowers
in their Haven of Trust.
I promise
they're opium poppies, detective.
It's to make Halloween.
You know about this new drug.
Officer.
This communist criminal trespassed
on our private property which is illegal.
As you can see, she has a wild imagination
and makes up horrific stories
-about what she saw.
-That's enough, lady.
You're the one lying your face off!
All right, all right,
let's, uh…
Let's see it then.
The evidence you took.
-The flower. Right?
-Oh…
Um, detective, the thing is…
-there's this coworker of mine, and--
-Oh, my God. Jesus Christ!
Pastor, what on…
How dare you treat
the son of God like this!
Oh, my God! Look at all this blood. Oh!
Ma'am.
He was caught in a motel
with a church member
and jumped out of the window.
Hurry up
and get him some clothes. Come on.
Your fucking dick.
-Are you an animal?
-Honey, uh, it's not how it looks.
- Okay?
- How many times have I told you
- to go to a hotel and not a motel…
- All right, that's enough.
Hey, hey, take him someplace else.
-Ma'am, please do that at home!
-You need to settle down.
Ugh, come on,
pastor, put that on.
What are you guys doing, huh?
Why are you wasting time?
Go search their compound.
We can't raid their compound
just 'cause we feel like it.
We need a warrant.
I'll be completely honest here
since no one's recording,
but do you know
how many times I've brought those two in?
We can try to book them,
but in this area,
the higher-ups just wave their hand
and they get out.
They're in with the prosecutor.
With many actually.
We're the ones working our asses off
so it annoy us more than anyone, okay?
And it's so embarrassing,
you wouldn't believe.
I'm telling you, it sucks.
So just… cut us some slack.
That's why we're doing
an episode on this story.
All you need's public opinion.
It'll force them at least
to make a little effort.
Come on. I'm ready.
Let's do this. What do you say?
You're seriously killing me.
Listen, I don't mind staying behind.
So let my guys go.
They got work to do.
All right, go.
-Thank you.
-Set this on my desk.
Okay.
The thing is,
if you have that flower on you,
you need to take it out now.
But you said…
Criminal Complaint Against Oh Soryong
Oh.
What are you doing?
Evidence.
-Huh?
-What?
-Oh, it's for our story.
-You want us to investigate or…
Just call if you need more from me.
Hey, where are you going?
I need you to give me that flower.
-Give it to him first though.
-Oh, that?
Oh…
-Yup, that's gone.
-Gone where?
Hey!
Oh, no, we should go.
I'll see you later, Ms. Oh.
Man, he actually lost it.
Come in.
What brings you here at this hour?
Proof of Jang Hakui's
verbal and physical abuse,
soliciting bribes, and sexual favors.
I thought after Jang,
I wouldn't wind up at Current Affairs.
We agreed! I chose the animals.
That's what I chose,
and that was the job--
That was the job.
We agreed, didn't we?
But you sent me to Trigger? Oh, go…
Today I was almost killed
just being at work.
You must have met Ms. Oh then.
So you know her?
You know back in the day,
Soryong and Jang actually used to date.
That was a long time ago.
It's all in the past now.
Okay so, wait, why are you telling me
about this now?
Ever since I was a reporter,
I've always hated those who hide behind
the facade of a nice title,
yet inside, they have filthy hearts,
they hide their true intentions.
I'm not sure what the point of this is.
Who knows?
You'll never get back at Jang
if you're all on your own.
Especially not with where you are.
I'm sure you know that.
Think of Trigger
basically as your time in purgatory.
A stop on the way to revenge.
You know I'm right.
I got dashcam footage from this morning
of these people shooting at me.
I'm sure you're aware,
that's attempted murder.
For now, let's use that to…
I'll keep them here
for the 48 hours I'm allowed to by law.
Do your episode, all right?
But you should know that if this fails…
not only will I have to turn in my badge
but they're going to go prey on
even more innocent folks.
This time, you'll get your warrant.
Bet on it.
Praise the Lord,
praise be to Jesus.
Let us all praise Jesus. Hallelujah!
Ms. Hong.
-Did you clean it?
-I did.
Alcohol swab and everything?
Huh?
Uh, no. I, uh…
I didn't wanna ruin it,
so I wiped it with a dry rag.
Ah…
Oh, Chief, please stop!
Come on and sit down!
-All your pacing is putting us on edge.
-How do you expect me to stay put?
You know what Soryong's like.
I'm worried
that the chief at that police station
will call to complain to President Koo.
What then?
You all let me know if something happens.
Ms. Hong, Ms. Hong, Ms. Hong.
Since you're checking the footage,
you mind sending it to the shared folder?
Looks like someone
doesn't want their hands dirty.
I'm okay
with getting my hands dirty, but I…
- Thank you.
- I swear to God
she only carries around
that phone of hers for show.
- Jesus Christ.
- Yes, Professor.
- I've reviewed the footage.
- Oh, right, right.
As for the plants in the field
where Ms. Oh landed,
those were definitely opium poppy plants.
It's illegal to grow them
without a permit in Korea.
I don't know how they've managed
-such a large operation.
-Oh.
-I sent you an email, so check it.
-Ah, right, thank you professor, yup.
I can never get through
to them in one call.
Chief, about that Haven of Trust place…
Haven of Trust? Yeah, right.
More like Haven of Drugs.
Whoa! M… Ms. Oh, are you all right?
Huh? I mean, I was worried sick
that you might not make it out of there.
Yeah, right,
I'm sure you were just worried
it'd go on your permanent record.
- How'd you get out without me calling?
- I walked out.
Hey, what were you thinking?
You put our rookie in a lot of danger.
Yeah, really.
The interview? The autopsy?
Apparently, the doctor
went to Vietnam for a conference.
Huh? So then…
We're gonna be okay.
He's gonna get the interview
from Vietnam in the morning.
-Nice.
-Can we really air this on time though?
Today's already here.
Well, uh, we got our writer
and everyone else, so why not?
You gonna cut it yourself?
Do… do you even know
where the edit bay is?
Huh?
It's our rookie.
- Ah.
- Looking rough.
Given the hour…
Are you coming in
or on your way home?
You don't need to answer that.
Just go back where you came from.
I was specific on what you were to do.
I said protect that kid or the flower
no matter what you had to do.
We are all bound by our sense of duty.
The work we do here is special.
We need people who understand duty.
No one's just passing the time here.
Everyone here works as a team,
if that's not you, there's the door.
You're not a good fit.
Hey, uh, why's she saying this?
Uh, just watch, you'll see.
It's funny, your talk about duty…
after you handcuffed me
and kidnapped me
on our very first day together.
An intellectually challenged young adult
makes his way
into the Kim's compound facility.
Less than a year later,
this young man's body is discovered
rotting on top of a toilet
in a public bathroom.
Somehow the police conclude
accidental death.
However…
the data we obtained,
after working our rear ends off
says otherwise.
It indicated a large amount of drugs
in his system did him in.
And someone else did it.
In order to know what happened,
we need an autopsy,
impossible at this point thanks to
scumbag Kim cremating the remains.
Regular people might just
scroll past a story like this
or be quick to hit the dislike button.
It's the people
who do this work who risk our lives
to shed light on these wrongdoings.
There's no other way to put an end to it.
Other reasons? I don't have any.
It was an unjust death.
That's what it is.
Yeah, the pastor's the villain,
that part, of course, is obvious.
Though I don't know why risking our lives
is part of this kind of work
when there are
plenty of safer, less extreme ways
to get aerial surveillance
this being the 21st century.
Why? It's just so…
-outdated.
-What?
-"Outdated"?
-Outdated.
What?
What what?
Tell me what you would've done.
Tell me, rook.
You know what? Don't spoil it.
Kang Giho, set up a desk,
so the man can work.
I don't believe a smart rookie like you
could lose important evidence
just like that.
I don't buy it.
Wait, hey!
You were the backup.
But a crummy one.
For now, airing the episode
comes before anything,
so let's…
just… table this for now.
21st century.
Outdated.
Uh, so… this, uh…
This is, uh, the only spot we have left.
- Ch… Chief, why are you still here?
- Hey, you…
Yeah, you should probably
-clean, uh, clean this desk off.
-Oh, right.
Editing in progress
-Moka. We have another one?
-Yes. Yes.
- Let's check on Halloween purchases.
- Just a second.
Hey, Kang Giho! The interview footage.
-With the family of the deceased.
-Right, right! On it, on it!
-They didn't even read the email.
-Ugh, I'm not doing that.
- Done!
- You sent it?
- Yeah!
- Okay, okay.
Almost done.
How far along are we?
-Here.
-There. Stop.
Okay. And that's a wrap.
-You did good.
-Eh.
-Clean up, then conference room.
-Yeah.
"Around 400 believers,
some of those children,
sent by their own parents."
A 21st century approach might work…
Probably.
Hey, is everything ready on set?
Yup, just give me one second.
Ms. Oh.
-We're all set.
-All right. Let's begin.
Title, standby.
Title, cue.
Counselor's Office
It says here…
you've found yourself with Trigger.
But… didn't you enjoy working on dramas?
I thought your love of work
was what kept you going
despite your struggles.
February 18th, Sunday
March 1st, Friday
Refuses to communicate
We request that the authorities conduct
a formal investigation into the Kim's
and render harsh justice to prevent
the deaths of any more innocents
like Kim Jeongnam.
"Please reach out if you have
information on the Haven of Faith"
Oh Soryong with Trigger,
a voice for all the voiceless,
we are their last resort.
Trigger: Firing the Bullet of Truth
Good job, everyone.
Good job.
Good work, people.
- This is my favorite song.
- Nice work tonight.
But, uh, where'd Soryong run off to
right after we finished
airing the episode?
Hey, rookie, you can go home.
Not like you have much to do here.
What?
We've got a ton of work.
He gets to go home?
- What else do we have left?
- Chief, you always discriminate.
I've been here for three years!
I've never gotten to go home on time!
I'm close friends
with your department chief, you punk.
How dare you even try to arrest me.
A flagrant civil rights violation,
and I will most definitely call
the main office for that.
Who the hell are you people?
What are you doing putting your hands
on a pastor, you prick?
-Now, now, now, hold on, hold on.
-Let me go. Damn it.
We're placing you both under arrest
for the production and distribution
of banned substances.
- Can you prove that?
- Of course we can.
Behold a 21st century device
that takes to the skies
collecting evidence from places
that humans can't go.
Didn't I tell you… that I would save you?
"Forgive us our sins
and lead us not into temptation…
but deliver us from evil."
Apologize to her.
Take them in.
Let go of me! Damn it!
Detective! I swear
I didn't know about this, okay?
I'll make sure you regret this day!
I'm innocent!
I don't know anything about that.
You Trigger guys are all right.
That was beautiful timing.
Cha Seongwook Disappearance Case
Today's Tip-off: New post from Dr. Trigger
Unfortunately,
the person you all killed
was an innocent civilian.
That is to say that the cheating
mafia member is still alive and well.
This leaves me with no choice
but to reveal the footage
taken on the day in question.
Trigger Adulterer Couple's
Edit Bay Sex Tape
Public Broadcasting Service KNS
A Brand New Building
Going forward, make sure
that more innocents don't end up dead.
Take care.
Congratulations on
KNS' new building expansion and moving