W-Two Worlds
"W" is Korea's best webtoon series.
Can Chul find the killer?
The lead character, Kang Chul
finds out through Yeon-joo
that he's a cartoon character.
You're going to shoot me?
Shoot if you can.
Shoot me!
This must be a perfect ending
for someone looking for a murderer
and became a murderer himself.
Chul and Yeon-joo realise their
true feelings for each other
and try to live a happy second life.
Why are you bleeding?
This means
you'll also die if you get shot.
You are Yeon-joo, right?
You are the girl who married Chul.
The killer appears to Chul
and threatens to kill Yeon-joo.
Have I really become a cartoon character?
Because I married the protagonist?
Because of the killer
and Yeon-joo,
other characters in "W"
lose their reason for existence
and start to disappear.
This isn't the sequel I was hoping for.
Episode 9
Isn't this place...
Do you remember?
This is the place.
You were lying down around here.
I was so surprised because
I thought you were going to die.
I was lucky.
Promise me one thing.
When you leave this world again,
can you draw me something?
Draw you what?
A dream.
A dream?
Make everything
that happened two months ago when
we first met to this moment a dream.
Everything will be solved if we go back
to the time when we didn't meet.
If I don't know you,
I wouldn't look for you.
I wouldn't think about you either.
Then you wouldn't be
pulled into this world.
I wouldn't learn the truth from you.
I wouldn't shoot your father.
The killer wouldn't leave this world.
No one would be in danger.
And here's the most important thing.
You cannot die.
I won't see that with my own eyes.
Give this to your father.
It's too bad that we only
got to do four romantic things.
There were over 100 more
romantic things to do.
I want to hug you,
but I can't do that.
It will make me hesitate.
Are you going somewhere?
We're running out of time,
and this is the only certain way.
Yeon-joo,
please forget about me.
I am just a cartoon character.
Take care.
Who am I?
Where is Chul?
Why aren't you telling me who I am?
Who am I?
Tell me who I am.
You betrayed me.
Sir?
Is everything okay?
Sir.
Why didn't you keep your words?
You said you'd tell me who I am.
Sir, are you okay?
Who am I?
Tell me who I am.
Give me my face!
Sir?
Sir! Are you okay?
Sir!
Sir, are you okay?
I heard some noise.
After our parting,
the killer disappeared
from the real world.
We found two drowned bodies at the
south end of Han River Bridge.
They're both male in their 20s.
Three people lost their lives,
but there were no more victims.
I can't believe this.
Ms Gil, you should go back!
-You can't
-I don't know what you're saying!
How can Yeon-joo disappear
while in the car with you?
Ms Gil, it's dangerous here!
You can't go in!
-Geez, seriously!
-Ms Gil!
-Where is your car?
Ms Gil, no! Ms Gil!
Ms Gil! It's dangerous here!
Ms Gil!
Goodness.
Why won't she listen to me?
Ms Gil.
It's that car, right?
Ms Gil, please don't go.
It's dangerous!
Yeon-joo! Goodness!
Oh, what should I do?
Yeon-joo, wake up!
Yeon-joo! Wake up!
-Yeon-joo!
-Mum and Soo-bong are fine.
And the characters in the webtoon
didn't disappear.
They are all fine.
Four new episodes were posted overnight.
Yeon-joo almost got shot.
The killer suddenly appeared
and shot her.
Who is it?
It's me.
Who...
Why are you here?
I thought you went to
New Zealand yesterday.
I just came back right away.
May I come in?
Come in.
What happened?
Where is Yeon-joo?
She's in her room.
She's sick in bed.
Did Soo-bong tell you?
I found her passed out after
drawing something inside the car.
She's unbelievable.
I took her to the emergency room,
and we just came back.
I don't know what is going on.
She won't tell me what she was
drawing inside that car.
And Soo-bong keeps talking gibberish.
I don't understand
what he was so scared of.
By the way, why did you come back?
I thought you'd stay there
for a month at least.
Excuse me.
What foolishness is this?
Give this to your father.
Connected with USB drive
To Mr Oh Seong-moo
It's such a mess.
This isn't the sequel I was hoping for.
To Mr Oh Seong-moo.
I heard you're alive.
I'm also alive.
I'm glad that you're alive,
but I won't apologise.
I don't deserve to be forgiven,
but you don't have the right
to forgive me either.
What an arrogant boy.
I'm writing not to apologise,
but to make a suggestion.
We have something we must end together.
We're going to get some fresh air.
I'll accept the terrible fate
you've given to me,
so you should do what you need to do
instead of running away.
If it's for your daughter and not me,
you can do it this time.
End "W" with a happy ending.
Mum, go sleep in your room.
You're awake?
Are you all right?
Why are you sleeping there?
It's uncomfortable.
It's all right.
I don't want to move.
Your dad stopped by.
-When?
-Around 11 PM.
Gosh, he said he would stay
in New Zealand for one month,
but he came back.
I wonder what's going on.
We're looking at all surveillance
cameras within five kilometres.
We're looking into everything.
-Why can't we find it, then?
-I'm frustrated, too.
-Hello.
So Chul, how do you feel?
I still can't seem to focus.
They must've injected a lot of drug.
I think
the dream stayed in
his subconscious for a while
since I could still see
Chul a few more times.
Though only
for a very short period of time.
Kang Chul
I'll do a check-up now.
-You're not putting on surgical cap?
-Oh, that's right.
Hey, are you going to wear a ring
into the surgery?
Hey, you shouldn't do that
when you have surgery.
Wow, that looks really nice.
Did you steal it from someone?
Did you get married secretly
without your professor knowing?
How could she get married
when she has no boyfriend?
I knew it right away when I saw
how she was on a blind date.
She's one of those people
who will stay single forever.
I hear there are many single old
women who live with cats.
She's following their exact path.
-Strangely enough, I agree.
-Right?
-You'd better stay focused.
-I'm sorry.
The third time I saw him
was a week later.
In Chul's world,
that's after two months.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry I didn't see you.
Your ring looks pretty.
Hello? I'm in front of the entrance.
I see you.
-Why are you so late?
-I was stuck in traffic.
Are you okay?
-No.
-Why not?
I'm sick.
What did you do
these past two months, then?
Who is she?
I don't know. She keeps
looking at me. I don't know her.
She looks sad.
Maybe she's one of your past lovers.
Perhaps you'd hurt her
and dumped her in the past.
Stop it!
Let's go.
Just like how I drew it,
Chul forgot everything.
What are you doing out here?
Hey, what's wrong?
As he got better and busier,
Chul didn't even have dreams anymore.
He completely...
...forgot about me.
He was infinitely devastated.
Life is sometimes
He was lost in life.
Chul depended on the power
of love in order to live.
But that man is gone now.
He went back
to being the man the readers love.
It's Chul again. Gosh.
Why are they always together?
Our lead character returned
to a man who's always strong
and never discouraged.
First Report on "W"
It was too sudden,
so Seon-mi and Yoon-hee
can only come on Wednesday.
The two of us can do it.
But, Mr Oh...
Actually, I was on the way home.
I am going to give up drawing cartoons.
I am seriously scared.
Ever since you got shot,
I've never had a sound sleep.
I don't understand why
my life has to be at stake
just for drawing cartoons.
I went to churches
as well as Buddhist temples.
I even got myself some amulets.
But I still feel anxious.
I'm seriously scared to even come here.
I called you because
I want to end it right.
I will go shave now.
I plan to end "W" with a happy ending.
A happy ending?
Chul will find the killer
and take revenge on him.
We will get rid of the killer forever.
Otherwise, we don't know
what else will happen again.
Are we killing the killer?
He killed three people and
even tried to kill my daughter!
We can't just leave him be.
Even though he's a killer, I created him.
It's only right that I end him.
In order to get rid of the killer,
you have to create
the killer's identity first.
He can't be a ghostly being.
He has to be a human I can catch.
I am attaching a copy of
my reports on Project W.
Report on Project W
The reports include investigation
records of 353 suspects.
You have to create someone
that is not in the reports.
Only then will I accept it,
and only when I accept it,
this webtoon can end.
First Report on W
You have to read everything.
Don't skip anything.
And we have to eliminate
all overlapping set-ups
or Chul will have doubts.
When Chul becomes suspicious,
-the curse will begin again.
-Mr Oh,
we made it a perfect crime.
So how do we create the killer?
Whatever evidence we come up with,
there will always be a flaw.
So there will be flaws.
We can't help that.
So we must come up with a face that
Chul can believe despite the flaws.
A face that Chul can believe?
I already picked the face.
Only this person will be acceptable
to Chul as his family's killer.
Mr Kang, shall I prepare breakfast?
After 10 minutes.
I will go wash first.
Okay.
-Yes, sir.
-Where are you?
I'm still at the hotel.
-I finally got something.
-What?
There was a man who came
from the hotel rooftop.
He was caught on
a delivery truck's dashboard camera.
President Kang.
You said you couldn't find anything.
You found nothing in these two months.
I know, but we missed one tiny detail.
The truck delivering ingredients
to the hotel kitchen.
I called you because I wanted to add it
to today's shooting
if it's the evidence.
It has to be right.
Look at the face.
That guy.
Enlarge it a little.
More. A little more.
This is...
He looks similar to you.
That's right. It is me.
Then you will...
...be the killer?
He won't believe it if it's not me.
Let's stop this!
I'm the only suspect he saw.
He'll believe it if he sees my face.
Yes. I know him.
He stabbed me on the rooftop.
I thought I saw an illusion since
he wasn't caught on cameras.
How is he caught on this camera?
You said other surveillance cameras
didn't catch anything.
That doesn't matter now.
At least one camera caught him.
This is unbelievable.
Let's air it on the show today.
Getting reports would be faster.
-Call Producer Park.
-Yes, sir.
-Hey, Yeon-joo. Have you seen it?
-Pardon?
Have you seen "W"?
No, not yet.
The King has returned.
The Great Oh Seong-moo
has come back.
After that idiot Yeon-joo disappeared,
the story is going great.
Haven't you seen it yet?
I was really disappointed
as I watched "W" get ruined.
I couldn't say anything because
he was sick.
And frankly, the recent storyline was
absolute rubbish.
It was third-rate childish romance.
It didn't make any sense.
But now, Mr Oh has finally
come to his senses.
Everything was just a dream.
This is a fresh start.
Chul will catch the killer
and then marry to So-hee.
That's how it should be.
Gosh. It's only right.
Doesn't that sound nice?
That's right. Your father is
in good health, right?
Tell him not to strain himself.
And tell him that I'm looking
forward to his work very much. Okay?
-All right.
-Okay.
Chul's action! Chul loves So-hee,
Chul hates Yeon-joo.
Oh, wait.
Why does the killer look
exactly like Mr Oh?
-Pardon?
-He looks like Mr Oh.
Could it be Oh my goodness.
It's like Hitchcock's movie, right?
He's leaving his face on his work.
Gosh. "W" is driving me crazy.
The killer has the artist's face.
Gosh, "W".
It's the best!
"W"! Yes!
He's giving it a happy ending?
No. He said he will finish it
in four episodes.
What you saw is the first of them.
What kind of happy ending?
Well, now that Mr Oh has left a clue,
they'll catch him using the broadcast.
Please take a careful look at
this picture.
This is the prime suspect of
the assault on Mr Kang Chul
at the Seoul Plaza Hotel on May 25th.
He seems to be in
his late 50s to early 60s.
On the day of the attack,
he was wearing a grey hooded jacket,
a khaki T-shirt and navy trousers.
He wears glasses and has grey beard.
He seems to be around 175cm tall.
If you know anything about him
or his whereabouts,
please call us.
-Goodness.
-Does he live in our neighbourhood?
They finally found him.
He is Han Sang-hoon, 61 years old.
He was Chul's father's
shooting team teammate.
He felt he was being
overshadowed by Chul's father.
He's been seeing a psychiatrist
for a while for paranoia.
He's basically crazy.
Restricted
They found all kinds of evidence
in his residence.
Chul's blood, a knife with his
fingerprints, Chul's family photo
and even records of his crime.
I found it.
Interview Room One
Please keep it short.
Thank you.
I killed your family.
Your father was a rude and arrogant man.
The day before it happened,
I ran into him in a bar after five years.
That jerk was still acting cheeky.
That's why I killed him.
I went in to kill just your father,
but I ended up killing everyone.
I would've killed you as well
if you were there.
I thought I'd get caught soon after,
but the prosecutor insisted
you were the killer.
I don't know if he's stupid
or if he had a plot in mind.
Either way, it was good for me.
I never thought
you'd keep looking for me
for over 10 years.
I got sick of it.
That's why I stabbed you on the rooftop.
But you still lived.
Why didn't you die?
Maybe I should've shot you
like I shot your parents.
You jerk!
That's not the end.
We should kill and eliminate the killer
from the webtoon
to prevent future trouble.
Is Chul going to kill him in vengeance?
That's not a happy ending.
A villain must be killed
by another villain.
The murder case of Mr Kang's family
has been aired
many times for the past five years.
I'm sure everyone remembers.
After a long and tiring chase,
the truth finally came to light.
10 years and 2 months after the accident,
Suspect Han finally confessed his crime
on August 20th.
-He confessed. It's over now.
-No!
No. That's not right, sir.
Chul must've bribed him.
That's not true.
Look here, the game is over.
You lost to Chul.
Please resign.
Are you telling me to step down?
Don't drag everyone down with you.
You are on your own now.
Han Cheol-ho misses his chance
to be the next president
and loses his mind.
He wants me...
...to go down?
Hello.
It's me.
How are your boys doing these days?
He kills the killer
under the guise of suicide.
Wait.
Stop!
He even makes a fake will that says
Chul bribed him
to make a false confession.
He told me to do it.
He told me to make a fake will.
He asks me to do
things like that sometimes.
He didn't tell me to kill him,
but he definitely wanted him dead.
Who are you talking about?
Han Cheol-ho, the candidate
in the presidential election.
Chul changes the game here again.
Sir. Is that true?
The police will eradicate crimes.
He's here.
-What was your motive?
-Why did you kill him?
Is what the man said true?
-Wait.
-Please say something!
Han Cheol-ho arrested for murder.
The killer gets murdered
and Cheol-ho goes to the prison.
It's a clean triumph of good over evil.
What do you think?
Would people like it?
-They'll love it.
-I know, right?
If this goes well,
I would finally be able to sleep well.
This is how it's supposed to be
in the first place.
Nothing would've happened, then.
-Is that the end?
-What?
-What's the last scene?
-Chul's love story.
We thought Chul's love story
needs an ending, too.
How?
Will he...
...marry So-hee?
No, we aren't planning that.
To Chul
Chul, congratulations on fulfilling
your heartfelt wish.
You've worked hard for it.
I'm happy that my support
paid off in the end.
Your long-time friend, So-hee.
Why'd you write me a letter?
It's unlike you.
Where are you?
Okay.
So-hee!
We'll finish it with a hint that
things will go well between them.
Hello?
Yeon-joo, are you listening?
I see.
Please answer immediately.
I almost had a heart attack.
It feels so futile, Soo-bong.
No one remembers me there,
and no one in this world
knows what I went through.
I don't even have a photo.
How foolish of me
to not even take a photo.
Do you know...
...what I did yesterday?
Is the final episode
coming out in August?
Yeon-joo?
Stab
Let us reconcile.
Sorry for what I did a while ago.
Answer me.
Where do you live?
You'll regret asking.
Is this sweet?
I love it.
Gosh.
I heard you should read books like this.
I'm tying your shoelaces.
Did I do four sweet things now?
It isn't the time to do your tasks.
This isn't the time to do your tasks.
Have some watermelon.
What are you doing?
Geez, what are those?
They look messy.
You're too old for that.
Take them all off.
They look bad.
Put up photos of
your real boyfriend instead, will you?
Isn't it funny?
Let's talk later, Soo-bong.
Chul.
Are you doing well?
Are you happy these days?
I'm not.
For each day, I...
Yeon-joo.
-Are you going to sleep?
-Yes, for 10 minutes.
What about dinner?
I'm sleepy.
Okay, see you.
Code Black, Code Black emergency.
Injured people from a shooting
will arrive soon.
There are too many injured people.
Doctors of all department
who aren't on duty
must come to the emergency room now.
Code Black, Code Black emergency.
-What's going on?
-Injured people will arrive soon.
There are too many injured victims.
Doctors of all department
who aren't on duty
Hankuk Sungjin Hospital
Was there a shooting?
Didn't you see the news? There was
a shooting at a broadcasting station.
At a broadcasting station?
We have emergency patients.
-Move out of the way.
-Please move.
-Go straight.
-Hello?
So-hee!
He got shot in the torso.
What's this?
Why am I here again?
It hasn't been confirmed yet,
but eight people died
and more than 15 people were injured.
I'll announce it again.
There was a shooting assault
inside W's recording studio
around 6 PM today.
The culprit hasn't been identified.
And despite containing the area,
the culprit managed to flee the scene.
The victims were staff members of W.
There were about 23 people
at the crime scene,
yet the culprit shot everyone in
the studio in less than five minutes.
Currently,
eight people were confirmed dead.
The 15 people who were injured
are being transferred
to Hankuk Sungjin Hospital.
-What's going on?
-Among them, seven are...
-This isn't how it supposed to be.
-We predict more fatality to be found.
Here's the list of people
who were confirmed to be dead.
The main host of the programme...
What's the current situation?
Who are on the list?
I'm a doctor!
It's an emergency.
Please hurry up.
Out of the way!
Please take a look at her.
She got shot in the leg and
is in great pain. Please do something.
It hurts.
Dr Oh Yeon-joo?
Dr Oh.
Can't you hear me?
Please do something!
Are you deaf?
Please wait.
How is she?
She needs surgery,
but she's not bleeding much.
She will be fine.
I'm sorry I yelled a while ago.
What about you?
Are you hurt?
I'm not hurt.
I saw in the news...
Oh, that's a false report.
I remember you.
You dropped that ring before, didn't you?
Why do you keep looking at me like that?
It's because I don't know why I am here.
Mr Kang!
How is Mr Son?
He's in surgery.
Can I talk to you?
Let's go.
I'm here, Mr Oh.
Mr Oh?
Let's eat some pork trotter, sir.
Mr Oh, I bought some pork trotter.
Is he sleeping?
Sir?
Is that you, Soo-bong?
It's me, Soo-bong.
Soo-bong.
Soo-bong
My face disappeared.
Soo-bong.
Oh, gosh.
Save me, Soo-bong.
He took my face.
Where did my face go?
Soo-bong.
Soo-bong?
Sit down.
Please take a close look at this picture.
This is the prime suspect of
the assault on Mr Kang Chul
at the Seoul Plaza Hotel on May 25th.
On the day of the attack,
he was wearing a grey hooded jacket,
a khaki T-shirt and navy trousers.
He wears glasses and has grey beard.
He seems to be around 175
centimetres tall.
If you know anything about him
or his whereabouts
-What happened?
What happened?
-Did he collapse?
What's wrong with him?
What's going on?
We're not sure.
Please wait.
-What happened?
-What?
See what's wrong with him!
What's going on here?
Gosh!
Who are you?
Request for assistance.
Chul.
Are you there?
Can you hear me?
I had to come because you
were looking for me so desperately.
I wanted to show you my face.
You suffered a lot because I didn't
appear for 10 years, didn't you?
It was painful for me, too.
I wanted to appear in front of you,
but I had no means to.
This is me.
How's my face?
I love it so much.
I'll see you often.
This is breaking news.
The face of the shooting
suspect has been released.
The man is presumed to be in his 60s
and his identity is still unknown.
The police are openly searching for him.
Around 6 PM today, he opened fire
randomly to the people in W studio.
Please save me!
W-Two Worlds
The killer must pay for this.
We have to find out who
raised the notorious killer.
Who are you? Why are you here?
Why am I still here?
Yeon-joo, you've been
bothering me since last time.
Why do you keep looking at me like that?
What kind of happy ending is this?
Why did we break up
if this is how it'd be?
I know everything.
Do you want to know
what will happen from now on?
We will kill each other.
I want to know the truth.
Are you doubting me right now?