Can you wash Nick's bottom?
Wash his bottom?
Ah!
You were going to strengthen the
relationship between our families.
How did Nai find out?
- About what?
- About me and Tin.
What clip are you talking about?
The one where she tried
to silence the kidnapper.
- Was that you?
- Madame.
Are you two
thinking of disowning me?
I'd like to know as well
if you two will survive
without me.
I'm right here.
And I will do whatever it takes
to prevent anything horrible
from happening to you,
okay?
Are you two
thinking of disowning me?
No, Mom.
We just want to be in control
of our own lives.
We want you to stop
meaning well toward us
because your good intentions
always cause us problems.
- Here you go.
- It's cooked now.
It's ready to eat.
- It's delicious.
- Dip in the sauce.
- How is it?
- How is it, Uncle?
The sauce is really tasty.
I agree.
I love the sauce.
- Me too.
- I made it.
Wow.
- It's delicious.
- How tasty.
- It's tasty.
- Guys.
Excuse me.
Sorry to interrupt
your Moo Krata time.
I'd like someone
to give a speech
to congratulate
Ms. Nade and Grandpa's success.
Yes.
Mr. Nai, say something.
Nade and I only got to eat delicious
food as kids because of you two.
Dang.
Without you, we wouldn't have
had a good ride to school.
That's right.
It's getting emotional.
Show us some tears.
Your turn.
Ms. Nade, we should be
the ones thanking you
for tying the knot with Trai.
- Auntie.
- Mind your words.
I'm not done.
If Trai upsets you in any way,
come to me.
I'll take care of him.
We'll teach him a lesson for you.
I'll probably have killed him myself
before you get to him, Auntie Erb.
Calm down.
- Please don't kill him.
- I think we have said enough.
Let's just eat.
Don't try to get out of it.
What did you say?
I said, let's just eat.
Gosh.
The sauce is delicious.
- I agree.
- It's not even hot yet.
- Trai loves meat.
- It's fine.
You can feed Mr. Nai instead.
Eat it.
- Mr. Nai, it's good. I've tried it.
- This won't do.
- Can I try a small bite?
- Nai.
Let me try it first.
I'd like to know as well
if you two will survive
without me.
Nai.
I need to answer Thom's call.
Ms. Pa and Mr. Nai,
I should put Nick down for a nap.
He seems sleepy. Bye.
Bye.
- He can't eat it.
- I'll be right back.
Do you want some?
Grandpa, Nick can't eat that.
I'll eat it for him then.
All right.
Please forward the contract
to me so I can go over it first.
Are you done with work?
Come and join our Moo Krata party.
Thom, I have to go.
Madame?
Let's talk.
- Oh my gosh.
Let's go.
Pawinee.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to do that.
It's all right.
Pa.
Come here.
Madame.
How dare you
try to hurt Pa on our turf?
No, Dad. It was an accident.
What are you talking about?
What are you doing here?
I came to check on you two.
Since you look happy here,
I will have your houses demolished.
Do whatever you want with it.
We are not going back there anyway.
Nade.
If that's what you want to do,
go ahead.
But if you ask me,
I don't want you to do it.
That place is my home.
I was planning
to live there with Nick and Pa
after the wedding.
Wait.
There's not going to be a wedding.
Dad.
Break up with him now.
Don't lead him on.
Do it.
Are you breaking up with me?
Yes, she is.
My daughter isn't stupid enough to
be that witch's daughter-in-law.
She hired hit men
to kill my daughter.
Nit.
Madame said she didn't do it.
I don't believe her.
I don't believe her either.
She would do anything
to get what she wanted.
Ms. Nade.
What about you, Nai?
Do you think I did it?
You don't believe me either, do you?
Nai.
It really wasn't Madame.
- Hey, don't side with her.
- What?
I'm not siding with her.
It really wasn't her doing.
Tell everyone that it wasn't you.
Set them straight.
It was me.
I did it because I hate you.
I don't want you
as my daughter-in-law.
Come here, Pa. Come.
I told you.
It was her doing.
What a shame, Nai.
You didn't believe me.
Go away. Get out of here.
Don't come back again,
you heartless monster.
Is this the bad thing
that you were afraid
would happen to me?
I have to do everything
now that everyone is gone.
There's no one to complain to.
Gosh.
There's no one for me to tease.
It sucks.
Let me go.
Did you find anyone else?
No, Boss.
These two are the only people here.
Good. Search the place.
Take any valuables you find.
Yes, Boss.
I heard everyone
turned their back on you.
I didn't believe it at first.
What do you want?
I came to collect the payment
you promised me.
Did you take the sachet
I put over there?
You mean this?
You can take any valuables
in the house.
Just give me back the sachet.
The item inside
must be extremely valuable then.
It's worthless to you.
Give it to me.
Don't move.
Show me where the valuables are.
Go.
Give it to me.
Don't move.
I have the right to kill you.
You're trespassing.
Give me back my stuff.
Give it back.
- Boss!
No way.
Take this.
You think you are so tough?
Boss, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Grab the valuables.
Check the safe.
(Tin sent you a photo)
What have you done to Madame?
Nothing, I haven't touched her yet.
But if you don't bring me
20 million baht in cash,
I will hurt her badly
to make up
for both of your betrayals.
How do I know that the photo
you sent me isn't photoshopped?
Hey.
Greet your frenemy.
Remove the cloth.
Singkorn.
Madame, what have they done to you?
Get him the cash.
Give him whatever he wants.
Just don't tell my children.
Why not?
I don't want them involved
in this mess.
Did you hear her?
Prepare the cash for me.
I'll inform you
of the meeting place later.
If you tell the police about this,
be prepared to collect
your best friend's lifeless body.
Hey.
Take this too.
Let's go.
Take her back to the warehouse.
We will kill her
once we get the money.
Let's go.
Ouch.
(Mom's House)
If you don't want it to scar,
you must apply ointment daily.
Do it for me then.
Welcome to the voicemail...
Ms. Nade.
Ms. Nade,
are you done in the bathroom?
- Yes.
- I'll take a shower then.
- Go ahead.
- Thank you.
(Home)
Hello.
Ms. Nade!
Tin broke into the house
and robbed us.
He took Madame with him.
He said he was going to kill her.
What?
What do you want me to do?
Should I call the police?
What do I want you to do?
Go live about it on the internet.
It should get my mother
some sympathy from netizens.
What are you talking about?
Do you think I don't know
that my mother ordered you
to call me
and lie about her being kidnapped
so we would feel sorry for her?
Please tell my mother
that she can't fool me anymore.
I have to go.
Ms. Nade.
What's the matter, Nade?
Mom's seeking attention.
She ordered Pit to call me
and say Tin has kidnapped her.
Our mother would never let anything
like that happen to her.
Just ignore her.
You don't think it's a lie, do you?
No.
My mother would find a different way
to seek attention.
Joy.
Can we borrow your car?
We're going to Madam Nuan's house.
Sure.
Can you drive?
Yes.
- Thank you, Joy.
- Thank you.
Where are you going?
I'm going to Madame Nuan's house
to check on her.
Do you think
what Nadedao told you is true?
That Madame has been kidnapped?
I agree with Nadedao.
I'm sure Madame Nuan is lying.
I don't know if it's true or not
but I have to check on her.
She's my mother after all.
Here.
I don't know what's going on,
but take this with you.
Only use it when it's necessary.
Here.
Thank you.
Take care of my daughter.
I will.
- Pa.
- I'll be back soon.
- Call me.
- I will.
- Let's go.
- Take care of yourself.
Hello, it's me, Pa.
Ms. Pa...
Tin took Madame with him.
He said he was taking her
to his warehouse.
But I don't think where that is.
Hey, get her.
Hey, stop.
Stop!
I know where it is.
(Singkorn)
Yes, Singkorn.
Madame has been kidnapped by Tin.
He told me to prepare cash for him.
Nai.
Madame asked me not to tell you,
but I had to.
I'm on my way to rescue her.
Please prepare the cash
and call the police.
I'll keep you updated.
Thank you very much.
Sure.
Hello, Boss.
Nueng is switching cars.
Yes, I know.
Boss.
I'll go buy a first aid kit for you.
- Come back quickly.
- I will.
Dang.
You stole a lot of stuff.
Hey.
Charn?
You took forever to call me back.
I need your help.
It's urgent.
It's this place, Nai.
Mom.
See you.
Stay calm.
Boss!
What's going on?
Boy, go see what's going on.
Yes, Boss.
Top!
Top, what happened?
Hey!
Top...
Who are you?
Let me go.
Boy, what's happening?
- Madame!
- Mom!
Die!
Darn it!
Mom.
Madame.
I'm fine, Nai. I'm fine.
Nai, go after Tin.
I'll stay with her.
- Please take care of her.
- I will.
Madame, hang in there.
Madame.
Hang in there, Madame.
Let's get out of here.
Madame.
What is it, Madame?
What is it?
They are pictures of Nai and Nade
when their father
had recently passed away.
Now that I look back,
the toughest time in my life
was also the most heartwarming time
because my children
were there for me.
And I knew...
that they didn't need
anyone else
but me.
Now,
I have everything
I could ever ask for...
but I don't have anyone left.
My children don't need me anymore.
No.
It's not true, Madame.
Nai and Nade...
will always need you.
You have to keep it.
If I die today,
I know I'll die in peace.
Pawinee.
If anything happens to me,
please take care
of Nai and Nade for me, Pawinee.
No.
Madame.
You will be all right.
Hang in there.
Madame.
All right, Madame? All right?
Let's go.
Don't bother crawling away.
Hang in there, Madame.
Pawinee.
I'm leaving Nai
and Nade in your care.
Take care of them.
Madame.
Madame, hang in there.
We will be at the hospital soon.
Hang in there.
Madame.
I'd like you to be prepared
because I'm going to convince
everyone to leave you soon
so you can finally understand
that your money
can hire them for work,
but you can't hire their heart
to love you like they always do.
Nade? Nai?
You are awake.
I'll go get a nurse.
(One Week Later)
You're ready to leave.
Madame.
Tin's been arrested.
He won't see the light of day
for a very long time.
Madame, I forgot
to give you this.
Mom.
Madame.
I'm fine, Nai. I'm fine.
Nai, go after Tin.
I'll stay with her.
- Please take care of her.
- I will.
- Welcome home, Madame.
Thank you, Pit and Tang.
What is Nade...
You should go upstairs and rest.
Madame.
Hello.
I went to visit you at the hospital,
but the doctor had already
discharged you.
How are you feeling?
I'm better now.
Thank you for visiting me.
When did you come back, Lita?
A few days ago.
I...
went there and begged her
to come back.
My life got lonely
without her.
If you don't want me
to run away again,
be mindful of your hurtful words.
I know.
Lita.
I know
how unpleasant your father can be.
But please talk things out
whenever you disagree on something.
Don't stop loving him no matter what
because
he loves you with all of his heart.
I know.
That's why I can never
stay mad at him for long.
If you are not in a rush,
stay for lunch.
It's lonely eating by myself.
My father and I came
to have lunch with you anyway.
However, you should get some rest
first. I'll walk you to your room.
Let's go.
This way.
Wait a moment, Mr. Singkorn.
Have you heard?
About what?
So you haven't heard.
Is there anything I should know?
You'll find out soon. After you.
Surprise!
- Surprise!
Yes!
Welcome home, Mom!
Mom.
I thought no one cared
about me anymore.
I was hospitalized for days.
Why didn't anyone visit me?
We visited you every day
when you were sleeping.
- Tom.
- Yes.
Why didn't you tell me?
It wouldn't have been a surprise
if I had told you.
How mean.
- All of you are mean.
- I know.
Don't blame them.
It was my plan.
I wanted you to know
how it would feel
if you had no one left.
Madame.
Thank you very much
for protecting me.
Thanks to you,
I didn't get hurt at all.
If it hadn't been for you,
Pa could have gotten hurt.
Thank you.
And I'm sorry
for not believing you
when you said
you never meant Pa harm.
Let's start anew, Mom.
Your father and grandma
are back on good terms now, Nick.
- Yes.
Nick...
Everyone, please ask the freelancers
who were working on the Health Plus
project to resume their work.
Ple,
once Singkorn compensates us
for putting the project on hold,
- please give everyone their share.
- Yes.
Okay.
(Nai)
Please excuse me.
Yes.
Yes, Nai.
Lita is at my house right now.
Did you say Lita?
Lita is there?
Wait. Seriously speaking,
which Lita are you referring to?
How many Litas do you know?
Well, I know
a few people named Lita.
This Lita is the person
you have been looking for.
Nai, be honest with me.
I don't want to be
disappointed later again.
Are you talking about Lita,
Singkorn's daughter?
Everyone, let's take a photo.
I should get out of the frame.
- It's fine, Dao. Stay in the photo.
- Okay.
Ready, one, two...
Lita, can you hold Nick?
It's okay.
- Hold him.
- Go ahead.
Come here.
- Turn this way.
- Nick.
- Okay.
- Look here.
One, two...
Okay.
Please send me the photos.
Sure.
Lita!
I'm sorry I'm late.
No, you arrived at the perfect time.
- Lend me your bike.
- Okay.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't worry about it.
Take the helmet, Thom.
- Aon, how do I start the engine?
- Yes?
Press the right button
while you grab onto the left brake.
Okay.
- Hold the brake, press the button.
- Okay.
- There you go.
- Okay, see you later.
Ride safely.
He's probably going to see Lita.
- Get back to work.
- Fine.
Our boss is in love.
Thom.
I like you.
Were you talking to Lita?
Yes.
Lita, I'm sorry I didn't answer you
when you asked me
how I felt about you.
The person who has a crush on you
is me.
Do you think it's possible
or impossible
between us?
I wasn't sure
how I felt about you.
But now,
I'm sure
that I like you.
I have a question for you.
Will you...
be my girlfriend?
I think...
I should go.
I'm starting to feel
like a third wheel.
- Take all the time you need.
- Thanks.
Goodbye.
Well...
I'm really sorry.
I couldn't help it.
I just miss you so much.
I really do.
So...
you haven't answered my question.
Will you...
be
my girlfriend?
There's your answer.
Mom.
- Sit down.
- Sit.
Nade and I would like
to apologize to you.
We are sorry for misjudging you.
Come here.
I'm sorry
for making you feel uncomfortable.
Back then, I was worried
that you two wouldn't survive
in this world.
But now I know
that both of you
are much stronger than I thought.
Especially Nade.
Who would have thought that she
would be able to make a living?
I can do it
because I'm your daughter.
You always taught me
to never let go of something
until it's mine.
Thank you for teaching me, Mom.
By the way, please be patient
with Trai.
Trai and I are working hard
to save money
for the dowry when he asks you
for my hand in marriage.
No need.
Save the money for your future.
All I want
is for Trai to be a good person
who loves you sincerely.
This necklace...
It's the necklace you gave Srikanda.
I was wrong about her back then.
I thought she was with you
for your money.
I'm sorry, Nai.
It's okay, Mom.
Do you believe now
that Da and her family
are good people?
Now,
I realize
that there's no better family
than Srikanda's family.
We are lucky
they didn't lose their patience
and leave us.
Keep this necklace.
Nick can give it
to the woman he loves.
Yes, Mom.
Mom.
I need your opinion on something.
It's actually about Pa.
What is it?
Everyone, come here.
Mr. Nai's about
to propose to Ms. Pa.
Keep it down.
Let me see.
Let's go to the other side.
The other side.
I'm coming too.
I actually
bought this ring for Pa
a long time ago.
I've been waiting
for the right time.
Do you think it's time
I give her the ring?
If you ask me,
there's no better time than this.
I've passed the first obstacle.
Here comes the second obstacle.
Nai.
Let me do my job as your mother.
Panit.
I'm sorry I mistreated you
and your daughters.
But
I'm a better person now.
Will you give me a chance
to be Pawinee's mother-in-law?
Oh my gosh.
You're asking for her hand yourself.
How can I turn you down?
All right then.
I'll let my daughter marry your son.
- Yes!
Pa.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
- Kiss her.
This sucks.
Let's watch them kiss at night.
You are such a pervert.
Everyone, let's take a photo.
Yes.
I'll take the photo for you.
Do you want to carry Nick?
Give him to me.
Here you go.
Wait.
- Trai.
- Oh?
What about me?
Go sit.
Sit down.
(Wait!)
(It’s Not Over Yet)
(Six Years Later)
Madame.
You said you weren't interested
in their business deal.
Explain this meeting then.
You are betraying me again,
Singkorn.
According to section 15 of
the contract you had Mother sign
when you hired her
as your consultant,
if you meet a person referred
by Mother behind her back,
she has the right to demand
any compensation from you.
This time,
I want 15 million baht.
What?
Sign it whenever you are ready.
Otherwise, you can meet us in court.
As her personal lawyer,
I will teach you
an unforgettable lesson.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I will donate
some of the money
to the anti-corruption foundation
and save some
to celebrate the arrival
of my grandchild.
Walk slowly.
You are walking too fast
for a pregnant lady.
Take it slow.
- Hello.
What happened?
Don't be alarmed. It's nothing new.
See you when the baby arrives, Lita.
See you.
Did you betray her again?
When are you going to learn?
Never.
Ever since Pawinee
became her assistant,
everyone's been afraid
of Madame Nuan.
But not me.
Just you wait.
I'll beat those two one day.
Don't stress out, honey.
Calm down.
Madame, Mr. Lee's secretary
sent you a message.
He wants to see you right now.
Tell him I'm busy.
I've got something more important
than his project to tend to.
We should go.
We can't be even a second late
to this event.
- Hello.
- Hello, Madame.
Did everything go well?
Yes.
My daughter-in-law
is an amazing lawyer after all.
Why are you just arriving now?
He took forever to pick a gift
for his grandson.
Seriously.
To be honest,
I was a little worried.
I wasn't sure
whether my beloved grandson
would be able to take
this giant present home.
Guess what's inside.
Here I come.
Here they go again.
Let's go inside.
He's probably waiting for us.
Let's go.
My goodness, Panit.
- What?
- Let me go in first.
Where's Auntie Orn?
She will probably be late.
Okay, great job.
Nick!
Yes! Grandpa and Grandma are here!
- Hello.
I've got a present for you.
Me too.
I'll go get the cake then.
- Tom, you can put that down.
- Yes?
Thank you.
Come to me.
- Come to Grandma.
- Come to Grandpa.
- Let's hug. Give me a kiss.
- Come to me.
Come to me first.
- Come on.
- Come.
- Come to me.
Come on.
Yes.
Dad said there's a baby
inside your belly.
Nick!
Nick, I told you to keep it a secret
until we got home.
Uh-oh.
- Pa.
- What?
Are you pregnant?
Yes, I'm three months pregnant.
That's great.
You should come and live with me.
I'll find someone to look after you.
No, she's my daughter.
She has to live with me.
It's my job to take care
of my daughter and grandchild.
She's my daughter-in-law.
And Nai is my son.
I gave birth to him.
Pawinee is my daughter-in-law.
It's not the same.
How?
How is it the same?
She's my daughter.
It's my grandbaby too.
- But she's my daughter.
- That's enough.
Pa can live with Nai.
Nai and Nick can take care of Pa.
Isn't that right, my beloved nephew?
Yes, my beautiful aunt.
- How is it the same?
- Dad.
- It's time for the cake.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
Let's go.
- She's my daughter.
- It's my grandbaby.
She's my daughter.
- Nick.
Come.
Whose cake is this?
Look.
Do you like it?
- Happy birthday to you.
You annoyed everyone.
What a rotten mouth.
- But my face is beautiful.
- Is that so?
What's your problem?
Why are you such a violent person?
- It's your fault.
- What?
- Happy birthday, happy birthday.
- Happy birthday to you.
Wow.
Great job.
You...
Dad, why are Grandpa
and Grandma always fighting?
Because they love you very much.
You are not tired of them
fighting, are you?
No, I'm a "strong" boy.
Who taught you to say that?
I did.
Strong people
have a lot of strength.
And we are
- a strong family.
- A strong family.
Wow.
Kiss your dad back.
(The end)