(Hwang Jung Eum)
(Lee Yu Bi)
(Lee Joon)
(Yoon Jong Hun)
(Shin Eun Kyung, Jo Yoon Hee)
(Yoon Tae Young, Jo Jae Yun)
(Um Ki Joon)
(The Escape of the Seven)
(All people, organizations, locations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(All child actors were shot under supervision.)
(Episode 4)
We have a guest!
Hey!
- Welcome! - Hey!
There he goes!
Sir!
- Who's coming? - Hey!
Look who it is.
He's a national star.
Goodness. It's an honour to meet you.
Did you think I'd say that?
You crazy pervert.
Where did you hide your daughter after you killed her?
Just tell us.
How was it?
Was it good?
Did you enjoy it?
You jerk!
Hey, hold it.
Look at him.
Should I get warmed up today?
One.
Two.
Three.
How noisy.
What? You loser.
How dare you talk?
Why are you doing this to me?
I was wrong.
Please let me go.
I'll do whatever you ask.
Please...
Geum La Hui...
Why did you meet her?
What kind of deal did you make with her? Tell me.
Did that wench blame me for everything?
Darn it.
I'll tell you!
I'll tell you everything!
I found out...
that Bobble was her daughter, and I blackmailed her.
I said if she didn't give me money,
I would post it online...
and tell everyone.
You should be ashamed of yourself!
I'm so sorry!
But...
she's even worse.
She asked me...
to stop Bobble from doing a live stream.
If I couldn't,
she said I could kill her!
You evil jerk!
What?
She said you could kill her?
Yes. I swear I'm telling the truth.
I have the entire call recorded on my phone.
I'll give you a million dollars.
In return, stop that girl.
If you want, I could give you 500,000 dollars more.
Do whatever you can to stop her!
Kill if you must.
How...
It's her own daughter!
Is that why you killed her?
No! I didn't kill her!
I didn't kill her!
I was just going to scare her, but she ran away!
But I swear, I didn't kill her.
Please let me go.
Why did you start Scarlet Letter?
What kind of grudge do you have?
That wasn't something I wanted to do either.
I just did it because someone told me to.
Who made you do it?
Was that Geum La Hui too?
Well...
Even if you don't talk,
there are other ways to find out!
- Kill him! - Sir!
Stop!
I'll talk!
Who is it?
Who made you do it?
Who?
Who did Joo Yong Ju get caught by? Darn it.
Darn it!
Hey, you idiot! Don't you know how to drive?
What are they up to?
Hey!
You're terrible at driving!
Yang Jin Mo!
Get in the car!
What are you doing? Hurry up and drive!
Hurry!
Darn it!
Get on the sidewalk!
What are you doing? Get him!
I'm sorry, Mr. Bang. We lost him.
Do whatever you can...
to make sure to bring Yang Jin Mo...
in front of me.
Kill him...
and bring his head if you have to.
I'll hire some more people.
Geum La Hui...
What does she have in her name?
She has the townhouse in Dogok-dong...
and the building in Seongsu-dong worth 30 million dollars,
both of which you bought her.
Why is that hers?
The house and the 30 million dollars...
were both given to my granddaughter!
Go to the courts...
and have all of that seized right away...
and make her give all of that back!
Yes, sir.
A murder without a body!
Who's the culprit?
- Lee Hwi So! - Lee Hwi So!
Let's punish Lee Hwi So, the scum of the earth!
- Jingle - Jingle
- Baduk's bell is jingling - Baduk's bell is jingling
(Lee Hui So deserves the death penalty.)
- Bobble's bell is jingling - Bobble's bell is jingling
There's her mom!
- Where are you going? - Don't do this. Move.
Please, let me go!
What are you saying?
You're not going anywhere.
- Let go! - What are you doing?
Do you have nothing else to do?
You're here all day banging on your drums.
Are you having a party?
This is the home of a victim who lost her daughter!
The victim!
Are you on her side because she lives downstairs?
You're supporting a criminal.
Do you want me to post your face on the Internet?
Take my photo!
Do you think I'm scared? Do it!
- Really? - Take her photo.
- Hey! - He's a criminal!
- Take my photo! - Hey!
- Do it! - Enough!
Honey, come on out. You have a guest.
Hello, sir.
I was going to call you...
because I was worried about my honey's health.
You came just in time.
I asked him...
to come today for you.
Me?
It's a geriatric pregnancy and your first,
so I should take special care of you.
Take her pulse.
Yes, sir.
Gosh, honey.
I'm an OB-GYN.
I'll take good care of myself.
Please check Mr. Bang.
I'm worried he might collapse.
Let him check you!
How is she?
I have a weak pulse,
so you can't feel it. Right?
Congratulations!
Your baby is very healthy.
Based on her pulse, I believe that it's a son.
"A son?"
A son? Me?
Yes.
- Dr. Park. - Yes, sir?
You can go now.
Yes, sir.
See? The baby is healthy.
I've been taking extra good care of myself.
Aren't you happy that it's a boy?
We got some good news,
so why don't you and I go to Jeju Island...
You!
Honey, why...
What if something happens to the baby?
How long were you planning to lie to me...
about your fake pregnancy?
It's been four days since Bang went missing.
The people are distraught...
as there are still no updates on her whereabouts.
The police have announced...
that due to the possibility that Bang could've gone down the river,
they will expand their search area to the Han River basin.
Up until now, there has been no trace...
of Bang's cell phone or personal items,
so they cannot confirm if she is still alive.
- As a result, - Where on earth are you hiding?
there are more questions than answers.
Are you dead or alive, Bang Da Mi?
They have asked to refrain...
from spreading false rumours.
We're in trouble, Ms. Geum.
Taeyang Investment Industry Development...
is taking back their 20-million-dollar investment.
What? What's the reason?
I don't know. They just gave us a notice.
If we lose this investment,
we have to stop production of the drama.
And this...
We received a letter from the court.
The creditor, Bang Chil Sung, has requested a seizure...
on Geumbit Building which is registered under your name.
A seizure...
I'm sorry!
Please forgive me.
I wanted to have your child so badly...
that I unintentionally lied to you.
I must've lost my mind for a second.
Your pregnancy...
means nothing to me.
Why did you lie about Da Mi?
That wasn't a lie.
A girl named Bang Da Mi really came to my hospital...
Shut your mouth!
Look. Da Mi...
(No trace of pregnancy in her uterus)
never had a child!
Why?
Was it because of money?
To pay back your ex-husband's debts?
- Sir... - Prepare yourself.
I'm going to make sure...
your medical license gets revoked!
I'm going to take back my building!
If you had honestly told me you needed money,
I would've given it to you.
Because my feelings for you...
were true.
Bang Chil Sung.
You would've given me money?
Who do you think you're trying to fool?
If I had mentioned money to you,
you would've taken my hospital out of your building.
You would've thrown a huge fit to make sure...
I could never step foot in this house again.
It's not like you can take...
all of that money with you when you die,
but all you care about is money. You frugal little Scrooge!
Cha Ju Ran!
It's been five years!
The only favour you gave me...
was the 100 dollars you took off my rent...
and then you bragged about it!
You would've given me money?
No way!
If you had hated me so much,
you should've left sooner!
Why should I?
I want the money that I worked for.
Pay me for being your personal physician...
and for sleeping with you for five years.
How dare you throw a tantrum?
Don't you feel bad for that girl?
Even if she were dead,
was it my fault?
You're the first person who abandoned Da Mi.
If you had really thought of Da Mi as your granddaughter,
you should've believed her when she said it wasn't her.
Even when the world was cursing and pointing fingers at her,
you should've protected her!
Da Mi died because of you!
It's because of you, a man who's so worried...
that something bad would happen to his money!
Understand?
Get out.
Get out!
Hey! Drag this woman out of here!
Why should I? This is my house.
Hey! Let go of me.
I said let go of me! You...
Have you lost your minds?
I refuse to leave!
What did I do wrong?
Let go of me!
Let go!
Hey!
Why would that old man suddenly...
Did he figure it out?
(Chairman Bang)
Hello.
The money that I gave you...
was used to kill my granddaughter.
I swear on the deity...
that the rest of my money...
will be used...
to kill you, Geum La Hui.
(Geum La Hui)
What?
You're going to tell him I'm not pregnant?
That's not the problem.
Chairman Bang has started...
his revenge for Bang Da Mi.
What are we going to do?
If they take back their investment,
all the actors who haven't signed on will leave.
Are you serious?
Once something is mine,
it stays mine even if it's broken and turned to dust.
It's not over until I say it's over!
(Seoul Detention Center)
Honey!
Da Mi... Did they find her?
Not yet.
Don't worry. She'll come back safely.
She's never disappointed us before.
I'm sure she's alive.
I'll find her.
Of course, my daughter.
Have some of the memories come back from that night?
Only bits and pieces.
It's probably because of the drugs.
They said they found drugs in your system.
I've never taken drugs!
I know. I trust you.
They said they found the same drug on our veranda.
Who did it?
Who came to the house?
No matter how much I think about it,
there's only one person.
Captain Nam Chul Woo from Deokseon Police Station.
Captain Nam?
He came into the house looking for the escapee.
My goodness...
It's nice and cold.
Okay, then.
He must've drugged my drink.
Why? Why would he do this to me?
Your time is up. Come out.
Hold on.
Honey. Da Mi's grandfather said he'd help us!
So you can't give up. Understand?
Is there anything else you remember?
Honey!
(Teen reported missing from Seoul Culture Forest...)
(My husband is not that kind of person!)
(Please find my missing daughter, Da Mi!)
(Medical Certificate)
(Patient Name: Bang Da Mi)
(No trace of pregnancy in patient's uterus)
(Could not find lochia in the patient's uterus.)
(No trace of pregnancy.)
That's it for today. Class president?
Attention. Bow.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Gosh. - Why is my body so sore?
Who are you?
Hello. I'm Da Mi's mom.
Hello, ma'am.
Is she the criminal's wife?
How brazen of her.
I came because I had something to ask you.
What happened the last day Da Mi went to school?
Who was the student who fought with Da Mi?
I need to meet them.
I cannot tell you that.
It was just Da Mi's accusation.
That student was very hurt as well.
As their homeroom teacher, I must protect the victim.
Da Mi is your student too.
Da Mi is no longer a student of Myeongju Girls' High School.
She was expelled before she died.
Da Mi is not dead yet.
Don't speak so carelessly.
Everyone. Please tell me.
Why did that student do that to Da Mi?
Tell me what you know. Please.
You cannot do this.
I need to proceed to class.
Class president. Call the security guard.
Yes, ma'am.
Anything is okay,
so please tell me something. I beg of you.
- Ma'am. Please calm down and leave. - Do you not know anything?
Please!
The school has decided to cover up...
the fight between Mone and Da Mi.
If anyone posts videos...
or comments online,
the school will track the IP address and punish the student accordingly.
So keep your mouths shut.
Answer!
Tell me who it was.
I need to know!
Please!
Why won't anyone tell me anything?
Please tell me!
Did you see that?
How insane.
The girl who had the baby...
was Han Mone.
Han Mone?
You can look her up online. She's an actress.
Da Mi accused Mone...
of planning all of this to frame her.
I believe Da Mi.
Han Mone was the one who had a baby!
I've kept my mouth shut for this long...
to protect Mone's secret.
But I can no longer keep silent...
while my dad is being accused.
Everyone.
- Everyone. - Stop the broadcast and come out!
- Everyone. - Why is your teacher hiding this?
She's the one who lied about seeing Da Mi have a baby.
All of our classmates also turned their backs on Da Mi.
But I...
think they are so despicable.
I'm Bang Da Mi from Class 2-7.
That night,
someone did have a baby in the art room.
(I report Han Mone's secret.)
That fake witch.
You can come down now, Han Mone.
I'll make sure everyone knows what kind of person you are.
(Send)
(Your mail has been sent!)
Please don't lose...
to Han Mone.
(Honest and virtuous)
(Myeongju students)
Han Mone.
Do something.
Please stop the old man...
with that smart head of yours you used to threaten me.
You made this whole mess!
If you hadn't sold me out to Scarlet Letter,
none of this would've happened.
My company is about to go down!
It's the same for me.
If I lose my medical license,
I won't be able to make a living.
- Who is this? - Hello.
I'm from the realtor's office.
I was told you put the house up for sale.
I never did that.
Do you know how tough that man can be?
We could never...
beat him in a fight.
Are you suggesting we just sit and wait to die?
We have nothing to lose now.
That old man...
hasn't revised his will yet, right?
The hospital building...
is mine for now.
He said I would get...
his entire inheritance once the baby was born.
What are you thinking?
The same thing as you.
It can't be...
Did you find Joo Yong Ju?
He still hasn't been found.
But...
you were right.
I got Bobble's family relation certificate.
Her grandfather...
is a very wealthy man.
Bang Hyun Woo.
Bang Chil...
Chairman Bang Chil Sung...
of Taeyang Investment Industry Development?
Darn it! What is this?
No!
We poked a beehive.
He's a super cash-rich man only known by a few people.
He can smell money from a mile away...
and always invests first in land about to be developed.
What will happen to Yong Ju, then?
You fool! Is he important right now?
My life is at risk here!
Then what should we do now?
Gather as many boys as possible.
Before that old man attacks us,
we'll attack first.
- Goodbye. - Goodbye.
- Thank you, everyone. - Here.
- I think it will be a hit. - Me too.
Hello. I'm Han Mone.
You're much more beautiful in person.
Mr. Ha Do Kwon.
You know I'm playing Ma Doo Kyung, your homeroom teacher, right?
I look forward to working with you.
It's an honour to meet you in person.
It's an honour for me. Take a seat.
Yes, sir.
You arrived last.
I'm sorry.
Director. I think this drama will be a hit.
We have a fresh, new face.
I think we might get on an online streaming platform.
We should. It'll be a hit.
Okay. I think everyone is here now.
Let's start the reading.
I will be your director. My name is Kwak...
- I need to see her. - Please be quiet.
- I need to. - You cannot do that.
- I need to ask her something. - Please, ma'am.
Who is that?
I'm...
Da Mi's mom.
Who is Da Mi?
Why did you want to see me?
How could you frame the friend that helped you?
Did you think you could keep your secret forever if Da Mi disappeared?
The secret that you were the one who had the baby at school!
- What? - Baby?
Excuse me.
Is this about Bobble, right?
There was a rumour that she was in the same school as Han Mone.
So Bobble wasn't the one who had the baby...
Han Mone. Was it you?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm not close to Da Mi at all.
I've never even talked to her.
Lies.
I know you and Da Mi...
had a fight on the day Da Mi disappeared.
You planned it from the beginning, didn't you?
Did you plan to use Da Mi as your scapegoat?
How could you do that to a friend?
How can you call yourself human?
How could you?
I think you need to stop her, Director Kwak.
Ma'am!
Outsiders are not allowed in here.
If you don't stop, we'll have to call the police.
Why are you just standing there?
Let's talk outside, ma'am.
- Please. - Let go!
You don't deserve to be an actress.
Now that I know the truth, I'm going to show the world...
what you did to Da Mi. You wait and see.
I apologize for causing a scene.
What is this, seriously?
- Wait. - Unbelievable.
Where is she going?
Han Mone.
Is this true?
This rumour isn't new, is it?
This is...
a big issue for our drama.
Well...
The thing is...
Let's cancel...
today's reading.
It seems we might need a new actress.
Go home, everyone.
I can't believe this.
Da Mi was an outcast since the day she came to my school.
She was jealous of me from the start.
She made it all up!
Mr. Ha. It's not true at all.
She's just taking it out on me.
Will you please believe me?
Hands off!
You brazen thing.
I hated you from the start.
You're filthy.
Mr. Ha.
Sir. I found the girl who framed Da Mi.
Han Mone.
She's an actress.
Do you know who her agent is?
It's Geum La Hui.
Geum La Hui?
From now on,
you can leave it to me.
This won't do.
Call the journalists.
Tell them that I, Bang Chil Sung, am Bang Da Mi's grandfather!
Prepare a press conference immediately.
Yes, sir.
Seven Star Convention Hall.
Do whatever it takes...
to stop Bang Chil Sung from talking to the press.
- Yes, boss! - Yes, boss!
Old man.
You picked the fight with me.
You brought it upon yourself.
(Han Mone)
What is it?
I told you we should keep our distance for the time being.
Da Mi's mom came to the script reading.
Her adoptive mom.
- What? - She knows everything.
That I had a baby...
and framed Da Mi for it. Everything!
What do you want me to do about it?
Do you know you got mud on me too?
Don't call me.
Call your agent Geum La Hui!
How can she help me when she knows nothing?
K. Talk to K for me.
He could help.
I said he left for the States!
I can't reach him!
The bigger problem is Da Mi's grandfather.
What about him?
Didn't you know her grandfather's loaded?
You went after someone you shouldn't have, you halfwit!
(Calling: K)
The person is unable to answer the phone.
Please try again.
No. I can't go down like this.
I must find a way out.
Enjoy your meal, boss!
- Enjoy your meal. - Enjoy your meal.
What's the matter with you? Stuff your face.
Leave him alone.
He's not hungry yet.
Inmate 1888.
Your lawyer's here.
How the heck did he get a lawyer?
I'm Kim Soon Pyung from Hanwool Law Firm.
I didn't hire a lawyer.
Take a seat first.
Okay.
Do you know Chairman Bang Chil Sung?
He sent me...
to help you.
But as of right now,
the proof and motive of murder is so clear,
even the best lawyer in the world...
can't prove you're not guilty.
I really didn't do anything at all.
I know that you feel wronged.
Are you aware Chairman Bang will hold a press conference?
No.
Your wife didn't tell you, then.
He's planning a press conference today at 6pm to prove...
your and Da Mi's innocence.
I need to ask you some questions.
Captain Nam Chul Woo from the Deokseon Police Station.
Is there any animosity between you two?
Not at all.
He drugged me.
He has to be involved in what happened to Da Mi.
So that's what happened.
He was promoted to Police Chief yesterday.
It's not even the promotion season,
and of all his classmates,
he was the first to make Chief.
Don't you find that odd?
I need to see him.
I have something to say.
The press conference is at 6pm.
We must prove before then that Captain Nam was involved.
There's no time.
Only one person can save you, Mr. Lee.
Who's that?
It's you.
Is it true?
I want to speak with you alone.
(Agreement to Break Exclusive Contract)
Let's not waste our breath.
There's more than enough cause to break the contract.
Sign it.
Give me a chance to explain myself.
I don't care about the facts.
What's clear is that...
I can't work with an actor involved in this scandal.
Our management deal is over as of today.
I can't break the deal.
Do you think you're making sense?
You're in your teens, and you had a baby.
The whole world is talking about it.
Didn't you know your past, present, and future would come out?
I don't know how this all came to be,
but I bet the stupid girl fell for your shameless act.
Who are you worried about?
The person you should care about is the actress you signed on.
You piece of trash.
Don't you have a sliver of a conscience?
I had a bad feeling about you when you lied about your age.
That your family's rich...
and your mom runs a business in the US.
They're all lies, aren't they?
I can't believe I fell for your dirty lies.
Be grateful I won't sue you for breach of contract.
Why should I pay you?
When I'm going to be your lifeline?
What?
It's true. I'm the one who gave birth.
You're telling the truth now?
You acted so dignified that I almost fell for it.
But...
don't you want to know whose baby it was?
Not at all.
Sign the agreement and get lost.
It's not too late for me to tell you first.
I'll tell you...
who the baby's dad is.
I'll give you two hours.
Today, an inmate will be released on bail.
I'll arrange it so you get released instead.
You'd better be on time.
Is that possible?
Chairman Bang made it possible.
Use this.
Captain Nam is on a break and will be at home.
I wish you...
great success.
Are you kidding me?
You expect me to believe that?
I'm not begging.
I'm giving you a chance to use me.
If you still worry about the risk...
(Hengbok Bank)
I'll return the two million dollars you gave when you signed me.
My answer...
is no.
Regardless of whose kid you had,
I won't get involved.
You 7, me 3, no down-payment.
You 8, me 2.
You 9, me 1.
I promise.
Once this drama's done,
I'll nab every commercial out there.
Wouldn't that be worth the gamble?
In return,
I need you to take care of this.
Hello?
Where are you?
Mr. Bang is going to hold a press conference.
He gathered every journalist out there.
What should we do?
- He's here! - Here he is.
Why would a mourning family want to talk to the press?
Who's mourning?
Da Mi...
isn't dead.
Will you reveal something at the press conference?
I'll reveal the truth about...
her adoptive father Lee Hwi So.
- Why would you explain now? - Anything else, sir?
You can hear the details at the press conference.
He's leaving.
- Gosh. - Darn it.
Who's that?
Who are you?
Did you feed me this?
Darn you.
What for?
Who hired you?
Hey, Lee Hwi So.
You're done for.
You're in a swamp you can never get out of,
you moron.
Get a grip and tell the truth!
What scumbag planned all this?
Who was it?
My Da Mi. Where is she?
I wouldn't know.
I just did as I was told.
Who told you to do this?
Give up.
You'll never find her.
Tell me.
Tell me, you punk!
Die.
Sir.
It's Lee Hwi So.
Lee Hwi...
How did you manage to call me?
At Captain Nam Chul Woo's home,
I found a bag of drugs.
Show it as evidence.
I'll come to where the press conference will be held.
Where are you now?
At Captain Nam's place.
How come you're there and not behind bars?
You pulled some strings.
The lawyer you sent me...
got me two hours.
What lawyer are you talking about?
I never sent you a lawyer.
Kim Soon Pyung.
You didn't send him?
Get out of there right now.
Go back to lock-up.
No, wait.
I'll come to you.
Yes.
Okay. I'll see you there.
Bye.
What a mess.
- Go to Deokseon Park quickly. - Yes, sir.
Untie him!
Are you all right?
Lee Hwi So threatened me with a carved toothbrush...
and took my phone.
He took my phone.
We have an emergency. Code Zero.
Inmate 1888 broke out.
Come with me!
(Deokseon, the safest city that is loved and respected)
He's near Deokseon Park.
Let's go.
- Let's go. - Hurry.
(Do not smoke in Deokseon Park.)
(Deokseon Park Suspension Bridge)
Lee Hwi So!
Is that you?
It's you?
When did you get on my tail?
Cancel the press conference!
We'll find you a place to waste away in comfort.
That's best for everyone.
Don't even dream of it!
You dare...
attack my granddaughter?
Do you think we killed her or something?
What's clear...
is that it wasn't Lee Hwi So!
If you'd been this great a grandpa from the start,
Da Mi,
that girl...
wouldn't have ended up that way.
I'll pay for whatever it is I did.
But you, Geum La Hui!
I swear on my life...
that I will kill you!
Cha Ju Ran!
You too!
Do you even have the strength to?
You're an old man who's nothing without his money.
So,
what gave you the guts to come here alone?
How dare you?
Let go!
Get off me, you witches!
How dare you do this to me?
Let go!
Goodbye, honey.
- There he is. - Catch him.
Go away. Stand back.
- Catch him. Come here. - Stand back.
Stand back.
Hey, stand back.
- Hey. - Freeze.
Ten minutes. Just give me ten minutes.
Please. Just ten minutes. No.
- Let go. - No.
No.
No. Let go of me.
Please.
Get inside.
Breaking news.
Bang Da Mi's grandfather, Mr. Bang Chil Sung,
fell from the suspension bridge at Deokseon Park.
The press conference has been cancelled.
The police are...
I'm free now.
He announced that he would reveal the truth about Lee Hwi So.
(Mr. Bang's mysterious fall. The accident is being investigated.)
I'm Deputy Chief Prosecutor, Uhm Ji Man.
Yesterday, around 6pm,
Mr. Bang Chil Sung fell below Deokseong Park's suspension bridge.
He died a little while ago.
What is his cause of death?
Did the fall kill him?
It was plain homicide.
Around 4:10pm, October 2, the suspect, Lee Hwi So,
had the intent to stop Bang Chil Sung's press conference.
So he assaulted his lawyer, whom he was in a meeting with,
and escaped from Seoul Detention Center.
We assume that Lee lured Bang to Deokseon Park...
and murdered him.
When he was arrested,
Lee Hwi So was in possession of a large amount of drugs.
We confirmed it was the same kind that he took...
at the time of Bang Da Mi's disappearance.
We, the police,
promise that we will do our best to make sure we take...
stern legal actions against the serial killer, Lee Hwi So.
I was supposed to meet Mr. Bang,
but that did not happen.
Why were you going to meet with Mr. Bang?
To give him evidence.
I found drugs in Captain Nam's house.
Captain Nam even admitted that...
someone instructed him to do so.
You met me?
You saw me yesterday. You were high on drugs.
You're the one who was high on drugs.
Yesterday, I was investigating Bang Da Mi's last whereabouts.
I went to the Youth Digital Crime Victims Support Center.
You can check with their director.
Yes.
Captain Nam came by yesterday,
and he took my statement as a witness.
I confirmed that Da Mi...
came to the center on the day she disappeared...
and that I drove her safely to Seoul Culture Forest.
Please call Lawyer Kim Soon Pyung.
He let me out in the place of someone...
who was being released on bail.
What kind of power...
would a public defender have to do such a thing?
I came to defend him out of the goodness of my heart.
But then...
I'm flabbergasted.
He beat me up like crazy...
and tied me to a chair before he escaped.
A public defender?
(We mourn the passing of Chairman Bang Chil Sung.)
(May he rest in peace.)
- Ms. Cha. - Gosh.
(We mourn the passing of Chairman Bang Chil Sung.)
Through a press conference, Mr. Bang intended to...
fully expose the wrongdoings of...
her granddaughter's adoptive father, Lee Hwi So.
But he passed away in vain.
I can't believe it.
Deprive the serial killer, Lee Hwi So, of his human rights...
and sentence him to the death penalty.
I dare implore the president.
Please bring back the death penalty.
- I have a question. - I have a question.
Mr. Bang's inheritance is hundreds of millions of dollars.
Since he does not have any children, will his spouse...
by common-law marriage inherit everything?
I don't really know much...
about Mr. Bang's inheritance.
- I have a question. - I have a question.
- Then how exactly... - Well then,
- Lee Hwi So... - I'm not really feeling well, so...
- Did he know about it already? - Please answer.
- I have a question. - Is there anything you want to say?
- Please answer. - I have a question.
- Ma'am. - Please tell us.
- Answer my question, please. - Please.
- What are you going to do now? - Answer us.
- What do you know? - What about the inheritance?
Are you okay with both of you being here?
Yes. Please proceed.
Then I will execute his will.
(Last Will and Testament)
To Cha Ju Ran, Bang Chil Sung...
bequeaths the Seongbuk-dong house and ten million dollars in cash.
- Ten million dollars? - Wait.
Maybe there's a zero missing.
If he's giving me a mere ten million dollars,
who's getting his hundreds of millions of dollars?
He has dozens of buildings in Gangnam.
Currently, there are no buildings in Chairman Bang's name.
What kind of nonsense is this?
You two fabricated the will, didn't you?
How dare you pull one on me?
Give me the rest.
How does it make sense that he only gave me ten million dollars?
Do you want me to take you to court?
- Hey, you... - Let go of me so I can talk.
Chairman Bang recently...
disposed of all his buildings and land.
The building your women's hospital is in, which he gave you,
was the last one he owned.
Then are you saying he cashed everything in?
What? It doesn't make sense.
Where are all the money,
possessions, and antiques that were in here?
Where is everything?
He duped us.
He played us over until the very end.
Can't you tell from the way he sold his buildings in advance?
There's no way.
How would he have known he'd die for him to hide it all in advance?
Maybe he opened a bank account in Switzerland.
Still, this wasn't bad.
Thanks to Lee Hwi So being framed for Mr. Bang's murder,
we were able to protect what we have.
Why is that important right now?
All I got was a house and ten million dollars.
And I have to split it with you. Once I pay the tax,
I'll be left with nothing.
Isn't this a happier ending than ending up behind bars?
We prevented the worst from happening, anyhow.
It's strange, though.
How did Lee Hwi So end up being framed for the murder?
It's as if an invisible hand was helping us.
Everything went in our favour.
If Lee Hwi So hadn't escaped just in time,
would we have been safe?
The old man dying from sepsis on the operation table...
were the deities helping us out.
One thing's for sure. We're luckier than Bang Chil Sung.
From now on, remove Mr. Bang's name from your head.
Don't open your mouth until he's in his grave.
You took the words out of my mouth.
Let's cut ties with each other from here on out.
You keep taking the words out of my mouth.
But,
where did all of the old man's...
fortune go?
He was so stubborn about his way of living,
but he didn't get to spend his money properly before.
(Three weeks later)
(Court)
(My husband is not that kind of person!)
(Please find my missing daughter, Da Mi!)
Look at this, everyone. What is this?
Do you know what I went through because of you?
Hey.
Do Hyuk.
Hey, congratulations.
A year and six months in prison, and a three-year probation.
Stay low key, even in the passing wind.
Here.
Eat.
Thank you.
So, what about your mom and little brother?
I didn't tell them I was going to be on trial.
I'll just see them at home.
What are you? In elementary school?
Hey, don't be like that. Let's go have a drink.
I know a place that has pretty girls.
You did a great job. Get in.
(Please find my missing daughter, Da Mi!)
Do Hyuk, don't look at that.
People like her...
think they have the worst lives in the world.
(My husband is not that kind of person!)
(Please find my missing daughter, Da Mi!)
Mr. Yang.
We're outside Bang Da Mi's house. What do you want us to do?
Should we keep Min Do Hyuk's family alive?
Get rid of both.
We should trample on him,
so he doesn't act up ever again.
Why is he pretending to be righteous when he's just a gangster?
He doesn't have anything to do with Bang Da Mi.
Stupid jerk.
Min Do Hyuk's mom...
has no luck at all.
She just happened to be Bobble's upstairs neighbour.
Chairman Bang, or whatever that old man's name is, is dead too.
The whole universe is in our favour, Mr. Yang.
Right. Wrap it up.
Hey, he's an important guest. Treat him accordingly.
Bring us your most expensive bottle.
What took you so long?
Raise your glasses.
You did a great job, Do Hyuk.
Let's celebrate.
Cheers!
She won't wake up easily.
We spiked her water with sleeping pills in advance.
Yes, sir.
- Gosh. - It's so cool.
(Tteokbokki 2 dollars Sundae 3.50 dollars)
Take care of yourself.
Goodbye.
Take care.
- Hello. - Yes, hello.
I'll have two portions of tteokbokki and two portions of sundae,
but I'd appreciate it if you give me as much fish cake as you can...
and cover them in sauce.
My mom loves fish cake.
So we call her the Fish Cake Monster.
I think my little brother is getting good grades because he eats this.
He plans on becoming a judge.
No, really. He actually does.
Your mom must be so proud...
that she probably feels full even without eating tteokbokki.
There must be a fire somewhere.
Loving you is hard.
What?
Stay back.
It's dangerous. You can't go inside.
Mom...
My mom and little brother are inside.
They're inside. I have to go.
It's dangerous.
Let go of me!
Mom!
Mom.
Mom...
Mom!
I heard Bobble's adoptive mother set the fire to commit suicide.
Why did they happen to be her upstairs neighbour?
The woman sprayed gasoline in front of their door...
so they couldn't even run away. They died, trapped inside.
The younger son was such a dutiful son...
that they found him dead while holding her mom's hand tightly.
Jae Hyuk.
I feel so sorry for them.
This is all Do Hyuk's fault.
He got caught up in bad things,
and his mom and little brother died because of him.
Jae Hyuk.
Don't forgive me.
Bring her back.
Bring my mom back.
Why did you do it?
Why did you kill my mom and brother?
Mom...
(A check for 100,000 dollars)
(Condolence money)
(The Escape of the Seven)
My goal is now the global market.
It's so nice to see you all here on Jeju Island!
Mone. I love you, my daughter.
It's today, right? The day Bang Da Mi disappeared.
Ran Women's Hospital. I used to be the director there.
You've never had a baby.
I'll leave my money to you.
- Da Mi, I'll find you soon. - Bobble.
Nobody here is free...
from this death.
Here. The cursed girl.
Enjoy it to the fullest.
I'll give you a taste of the abyss soon.