(Hwang Jung Eum)
(Lee Yu Bi)
(Lee Joon)
(Yoon Jong Hun)
(Shin Eun Kyung, Jo Yoon Hee)
(Yoon Tae Young, Jo Jae Yun)
(Um Ki Joon)
(The Escape of the Seven)
(All people, organizations, locations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(All child actors were shot under supervision.)
(Episode 5)
(In Session)
What the defendant, Lee Hwi So, did to his adoptive daughter...
would be considered sexual grooming.
Though his adoptive daughter's body was not found,
based on circumstances we view this as murder.
Furthermore, his crime of brutally murdering her grandfather,
who was looking for the truth, has been confirmed.
Regarding his inhumane acts and his planned murder,
he will inevitably be charged under the law.
The defendant, Lee Hwi So,
is sentenced to death.
I'm innocent!
I didn't kill them!
Justice is alive!
- Justice is alive! - I will file an appeal!
I can't go like this!
I didn't kill them!
I'm innocent!
I swear I am!
(Inhumane Lee Hwi So, Death Penalty!)
(Eternal damnation is too good for you!)
Escape taking place.
All CRT officers report to the east exit.
Darn it!
That crazy lunatic is at it again!
Can you just let us get some sleep?
Why would you do this every night?
Gosh, that jerk!
He tries to escape regularly.
I ought to knock him upside his head.
The boss is sleeping! Be quiet!
Darn it.
Sir, I'll punish them properly tomorrow.
That's enough.
Inmate 1888, 3 days in solitary.
Da Mi.
Honey.
I'll...
I'll go look for you soon.
- What do you want? - Come with us!
Don't touch me!
Let go!
Come on.
Get away from me!
Don't come near me!
Get him!
- Get him! - Let go!
Let go!
- Let go! - Be quiet!
- Darn it. - Hey!
- Darn it! - Darn it!
Let go.
Hey, Death Row.
If you want to die so badly, die right here.
Stop bothering other people.
There are lots of tools here.
Darn it!
- Hey! - Let go!
Which one should we choose?
Let go of him.
Die.
I said, die.
Why?
Are you scared?
If you aren't that bold, why run away every night?
You can't do it, right?
Then I'll kill you.
Here.
Die, you punk!
Why would I die?
I don't know if my daughter's dead or alive.
I'm...
I'm going to get out of here alive!
Get over here, you punk!
Let go!
Let go of me!
Hurry! Come with me!
Hurry!
Sir, over here!
- What are you doing? - Over here!
What is this?
Hey!
- Pick him up! - You jerks!
What are you doing? Get out.
(Emergency Medical Center)
He's a burn victim.
- Hurry! - Yes, sir.
Make way.
- He's an urgent patient. - Move him to the room.
Sir!
Gosh. Hurry!
Darn it. This is crazy.
Can you speak?
(Shining Mone, First Episode)
Bravo!
The first episode got 15 percent viewership ratings.
This is a huge hit.
Most of the comments say they watched it for you.
It's all thanks to you.
If it weren't for you, I wouldn't be here.
Cheers!
I'll never forget.
You'll only get busier.
We have a recording session for the drama soundtrack,
and we have a ton of commercials and interviews lined up.
Didn't I promise you...
that I'd make sure you get every commercial in the world.
One more thing.
You have never had a child.
Look at me in the eyes and promise.
Yes, ma'am.
I've never had a child.
Give me a hug right now
If you feel the same way as I do
Accept my feelings
If you hurt like I do
All I have is you
- She's no longer in this world. - If I cry
- Guilt will only be baggage. - Like I'm crying right now
Focus, Geum La Hui.
Right now, Mone is your everything.
You must make her the best actress.
That I miss you
Inmate 1888.
For the time being,
we're separating you from other inmates.
Is it okay for him to leave the hospital?
He still has bandages on.
The hot soup went into his mouth,
so even his vocal cords got burned.
- He lost his voice? - Of course. How can he speak?
He killed two people.
He's getting what he deserves.
Come with me!
Hurry!
(Emergency Medical Center)
(Geosan Hospital)
Look here.
Get...
me out of here!
Scalpel.
Gauze.
(Mortuary)
(Emergency Medical Center)
(Name: Kim Eun Tae, DOB: April 19, 1954)
(Geosan Hospital)
Sir, it's me.
What about that man?
Did he get out safely?
Yes. He'll need to receive more treatment for his burns.
Mr. Hwang will take good care of him.
Do you think Lee Hwi So figured it out?
I didn't say anything.
I...
don't have any right to get revenge for Da Mi.
He has to do it.
I will give all the money I have...
to you,
Kang Ki Tak.
So have his back.
You're not well,
so I'm not sure if you'll be able to endure things here.
My body is already broken and useless.
I...
want to repay...
all my debts to Lee Hwi So...
like this before I die.
(5 Years Later)
In 2023, Korea...
is going crazy over TIKITAKA, the messaging app.
With the advancement of secret chatrooms,
analysis shows they have targeted...
the exact needs of privacy-conscious people today.
Their advertisements with top star Han Mone...
as their model are gaining a lot of popularity as well.
(You know about tonight's party, right?)
Hey, TIKI. Prepare for a party.
With TIKITAKA, it's totally new.
With the fast and easy TIKI Pay,
complicated payments are made easy.
If you want your privacy,
trust TIKITAKA.
(Confirm Security)
With its innovative secret chatrooms,
it's 100 percent safe.
All of our moments, TIKITAKA.
A trip to Jeju Island sponsored by TIKITAKA...
and joined by Mone.
Let me announce the lucky winners!
Join me, Mone, on a trip to Jeju Island!
(Lucky 33)
(Shall we go?)
(Gimpo International Airport)
(Jeju Island)
(I love Mone, True Mone Fan Award)
Hello, everyone!
Hi!
It's so nice to see you all here on Jeju Island!
Shall we have some fun today?
Let's go!
Oh, my!
We will now start the Mone Quiz!
Okay. Here's the first question.
Who is the person that Mone respects most in the world?
I got it! Beyoncé!
- Wrong! - I got it!
Ms. Geum La Hui.
- Wrong. - What?
Of course, I really love Ms. Geum,
but the person I respect most in the world is my mom.
- Correct! - You're a great daughter!
- You're a great daughter! - You're a great daughter!
My mom is in the US for business,
so I try to call her often.
Oddly enough, when I hear my mom's voice,
I never make mistakes.
- Han Mone! - Han Mone!
Mone!
(All of our moments, TIKITAKA)
- You're so pretty! - Yes!
You're so pretty!
Is everyone...
here now?
I'm being released today after serving my sentence.
This will be the last time I'll see you like this.
Has all that time...
already passed?
Do you remember what today is?
I remember it exactly.
How could I forget?
Remembering this day...
is what has been keeping me alive.
There's something I didn't tell you.
To be honest, Lee Hwi So knows your plan.
I have no doubt that he will do a good job.
He knows how I feel...
more than anyone else.
It's me, Matthew.
(True Corrections, Bright Future)
It's me, Kang Ki Tak. It's been a while.
How is the elder doing?
He's still holding on,
but for nearly five years,
he's been staying in solitary without outside communication.
It's not something that can be endured by anyone weak-minded.
I'm indebted to him.
Look over here.
- Things are looking good. - Thank you.
Be sure to receive treatment in prison.
(Happy Corrections, Happy Citizens)
- Open the doors. - Yes, sir.
Why? Why would he do that because of me?
After breaking his spine from the fall,
he had surgery to put in 50 pins, and he overcame that.
For the past six months,
he received physical therapy daily to get better.
With the sole purpose of becoming you, Hwi So.
Don't forget how you're feeling.
You're up against strong people.
You need to gain power,
and you must succeed.
I'm giving you ten million dollars.
(Hanjin Bank)
(Lee Hwi So)
It's 20 percent interest a year.
You have two years to repay it.
Be sure to repay everything, including interest, in that time.
I have something...
to tell Lee Hwi So.
Go ahead, sir.
Tell him I'm thankful...
he took in and raised...
my granddaughter.
I ask him to forgive me,
a greedy old man obsessed with money.
Please take good care of Mr. Bang.
I wish you good luck.
Don't worry.
I'm ready...
to become a monster.
Part one of our party with Mone has come to an end.
We will take a short break...
and see you again at Mone's fan signing event.
- Cheers! - Cheers!
(TIKITAKA and Jeju, Jeju trip with Mone)
(The selected participants are so lucky. You're so pretty!)
(I wish I could be Mone for a day. Mone is so pretty.)
(Why did you lose so much weight? Today is the day Bobble died!)
(Today is the day Bobble died!)
You still haven't found Matthew?
Are you sure he's coming here?
Let's meet now. I'll come to you.
Oh, my.
I heard TIKITAKA was the sponsor.
Is Matthew coming?
What kind of person is he?
I'm so curious.
I heard he was very ugly.
Have you seen him in person?
You should at least say hi.
You don't have to ignore me.
Why did you come here?
You can't be Mone's fan.
What's the reason you keep following me around?
Why would you say that? I'm hurt.
I was chosen fair and square out of 100,000 people.
I totally love Mone.
She's so beautiful,
good at singing and acting,
and is a good person.
Get to the point.
I don't have time to have small talk with you.
I started a new business recently.
It's a top-notch program only for VIPS.
I want Mone to be the model.
Mone doesn't do advertisements...
for just any product.
That's why...
I'm asking you.
I'll turn down the offer.
I hope...
your business is successful.
You shouldn't...
reject me so rudely. Don't you think?
Let go of my hand.
It was around this time, right?
When your daughter died.
If you want to rise up higher,
you'll need to keep me quiet first.
I'm not the Geum La Hui from before.
If you provoke me,
you'll die.
I'm not asking for much.
Just get me a meeting with Mone.
My number is still the same.
Okay, Ms. Geum?
Who is the person that was chosen to be chairman?
I'm not sure. It's being done very secretly.
Gosh.
Why would they not choose us?
Cherry Entertainment and LH Media...
are the top entertainment and production companies.
There's no one better than us.
It is a very attractive position.
Chairman of TIKITAKA Studio.
They'll get a billion dollars in investments.
On top of that, they'll get full control of the company.
It's obvious the position will be very lucrative.
Of course, everyone would want it.
Everyone in this field must be going for it.
As long as Matthew shows up at the Jeju Island event,
we'll have a chance.
I must...
get that position.
Same for me.
Whoever gets it, don't break the promise...
to help each other out.
I'm going for the global market now.
To make the best content without worrying about capital,
I need the support of a big company like TIKITAKA.
You can be hopeful.
I hired a very useful guy.
Who?
He's a fixer who is famous in Gangnam.
I promised 200,000 dollars for his service,
so I'm sure he'll do anything to get Matthew here.
He'll do anything for money.
Hey, Do Hyuk. Come in.
I confirmed Matthew Lee arrived at Jeju Airport an hour ago.
- Look here. - What?
How can you guarantee this person is Matthew?
Nobody has seen him in person.
You sent two invitations to Matthew, right?
The first one was in a red envelope.
The second was in a gold envelope.
How did you...
I have a connection with Matthew's driver.
Anyway, the important thing...
is that Matthew Lee has come to Jeju Island.
I'll pay you an additional 100,000 dollars.
Find Chairman Lee and bring him here.
I'll trust you, Do Hyuk.
Trust me.
I just need to make an opportunity for you to meet Chairman Lee, right?
Mone.
Han Mone.
It's me.
Ko Myung Ji from Myeongju Girls' High School.
Ms. Ko!
Is that really you?
It's so nice to see you.
Mone!
I've been following you on the news every day.
I knew you would become a huge star.
Congratulations.
I was Mone's homeroom teacher in high school.
- Oh, my. - Oh, my.
She was such a good student.
You're right. She was so smart and pretty...
that the boys from the schools nearby...
waited in line at the school gate every day to see her.
I entered without telling you so I could surprise you,
and I somehow got chosen.
I thought maybe you had chosen me yourself.
Me?
Did I tell you I got married?
My husband is a professor at Stanford University.
I thought of moving to the US for the kids,
but my daughter's dream is to become an actress.
Do you want to see her picture?
They're twins.
They're so cute, right?
They're so cute.
They look just like you.
Right?
Do you know what they call my daughter at acting school?
Little Mone.
Look at this.
What do you think?
- I'm confident! - She looks just like you, right?
Yes.
I really want to do this.
Right.
On that note,
you're starting a new drama, right?
Could you help my daughter out?
I heard you made all of the casting decisions...
for dramas lately.
I'm sorry.
I don't take those kinds of requests.
- Oh, my. - She's so pretty.
Next. Please come forward, number ten.
- It's me! - Over here!
Han Mone.
You can't act that way.
It's today, right?
The day...
Bang Da Mi disappeared.
I brought you a present.
I was going to include this in my exhibit.
I hope you like it.
This is crazy!
Mone.
Mone. Han Mone.
Han Mone.
Yong Ju. Where are you right now?
I think I'm a bit lost.
Bobble.
Stop drinking so much, you punk.
I don't want you to mess up.
I'll have some water.
Well, if it isn't Mr. Yang?
You didn't quit drinking?
You wanted to come here to drink?
Of course, I came here to see Princess Mone in person.
Isn't she cute?
Where were you? Why are you here?
No, it was a dream.
What's the matter with you?
Why are you freaking out?
Oh, gosh. I have the chills.
I almost wet myself with shock!
Not so loud. Did you see a ghost or something?
Yes, I did.
Bobble's ghost.
What's even more chilling...
is that today is her death anniversary.
Why would you mention that and jinx us all?
I must be careful. It's my samjae, three years of misfortune.
A fortune-teller told me...
to be careful around bodies of water.
Enough!
Quit the nonsense and watch what you say.
No, wait, Mr. Yang.
I must ask...
because I'm so darn curious.
Why on earth did you harass Bobble so much?
Was it...
because of Mone?
Are you insane?
You're drunk witless already?
Mone doesn't even work for me.
It's true, she doesn't.
But now she's tight with Geum La Hui,
whom you can't stand,
and even Mone, who is picky about who she works with,
will only work with the guys you signed.
I find that so strange.
Darn you.
If you talk like that again,
I'll break your other leg.
It was about Mone.
(Ridon, Zolpiden, Linax)
Ms. Geum.
What are all these?
You said you'd quit.
Did you lie?
You know I hyperventilate.
Didn't I say you couldn't even drink water...
without my permission?
I monitor what you eat, wear, whom you meet,
and even the number of times you use the toilet!
I'm not just your agent but your guardian and mom!
I know that.
That face.
You forgot already?
I sent your troublemaker family abroad,
and I made you the highest-paid actor in the country!
I'm always grateful for that.
I apologize. I'll quit taking pills.
I'm doing this for you.
You can't mess up again like you did five years ago.
I am you, and you are me.
Okay?
Okay.
Someone outside would like to see you.
Smile a bit and then say no.
Miss Mone, it's lovely to see you.
I'm a huge fan.
Thank you.
You're busy, so I'll get right to the point.
I'd like you to model for my company.
It'll suit your image perfectly,
making it a win-win.
I can pay you more than your market price.
Gosh.
I'm so grateful for the offer.
But my agency and I decided not to take on new commercials.
I'm so busy with my new album.
I'll keep this in mind, though.
Don't be like that. Why don't you take another look?
Here's the contract.
can wire the full down payment today.
I have to get changed.
Ran Women's Hospital.
Do you remember?
Yes, Bang Da Mi.
Can I have the abortion today?
I was the hospital director.
I'll stop here, seeing it's a great day.
For part two,
you'll all get to party with Mone.
Change into a nice swimsuit...
and come over to the outdoor pool.
See you soon!
Thank you.
Hey, Mone!
Gosh. Did I scare you?
You're pretty even when you're scared.
I have to go. The party starts soon.
Wait.
Let's talk.
Gosh.
Did I do something bad?
Come on. I'm not a scary person.
I just want to talk to you.
Hey.
Oh, you don't know who I am.
Will this help?
To bring justice to the entertainment industry,
Scarlet Letter has come!
Justice!
You were Scarlet Letter?
Did you figure that out now?
Hey.
What's your deal with Yang Jin Mo?
Don't come closer.
Don't worry.
Your secret's safe with me.
Get up, pervert.
You're not yet cured of that bad habit?
Yong Ju, you should've broken a wrist instead of an ankle.
I'll do it for you.
We still have a score to settle.
Aren't you the original traitor?
You got me to turn against our boss!
Get lost.
Darn you.
I thank you all from the bottom of my heart...
for attending the party with Mone.
I'm Geum La Hui, CEO of LH Media, her agency.
This event...
was sponsored by TIKITAKA...
and arranged only for Mone's greatest fans.
There is no hotel staff,
and there are no...
security cameras.
What about food and drinks?
It would be weird to not have that.
- Yes! - Yes!
Eat and drink all you want and have a good time!
- Okay! - Okay!
My dear daughter Mone.
I love you so much.
- How sweet! - That's nice.
To our love, Mone.
- Cheers! - Cheers!
- Han Mone! - Han Mone!
Yes. I'll forget it all and enjoy myself.
I love you all!
- We love you! - We love you!
- You're amazing! - I love you, Mone!
It's Matthew Lee.
I'll come to your hotel tomorrow.
Enjoy yourself tonight.
Thank you for giving me the opportunity.
I'll see you tomorrow.
(I'll see you tomorrow.)
Luka, screen on.
Out of the 33 guests invited to the event,
twenty-nine of them are core members of Scarlet Letter.
Enjoy it to the fullest.
I'll give you a taste of the abyss soon.
Joo Yong Ju.
I'm starting with you.
I heard from Matthew Lee.
We're meeting tomorrow.
What did I tell you?
Great!
Oh, dear.
It smashed.
What are you doing? That's dangerous.
What's he up to?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Darn it.
Hey, Dumpling.
Yong Ju, you had too much to drink.
- Don't... - What do you want?
Hey!
You're fools, all of you.
Don't you dare glare at me!
You scumbag.
You'd all...
faint if I were to tell you who I was!
Who is he?
Do you know what day it is today?
You don't, do you?
Today is...
the anniversary of Bobble's death.
What does that have to do with us?
We're just here to party.
- Yes! - That's right!
You're drunk! Go somewhere and sober up!
Mister!
Quit acting like you're special because you're ruining the mood!
- Yes! - He's right!
Get out of here!
Mister!
Who is he?
- Hey! - What's that?
I am...
one half of Scarlet Letter called Joo!
You lot...
praised and worshipped me!
I'm Scarlet Letter's leader!
- What? - Darn it.
- You losers. - "Scarlet Letter?"
Look at your shocked faces.
Now do you get it?
Hey. Han Mone.
Watch how you treat me.
I can...
topple you from your pedestal in a second.
We didn't finish our conversation earlier.
Let's go.
Come here!
Come with me.
Come!
Let go!
Let her go.
Let go of me!
Come here!
Are you okay?
Get him!
Dunk him!
Who do you think you are?
We got him.
Well done.
Stop!
Stop it!
He's dead.
What?
Flip him over.
Yong Ju.
He's dead?
Darn it!
What's up with him?
Poor Yong Ju.
He's dead.
There!
What a moron.
A man's dead.
Shouldn't we call the police?
We can't!
Should we all go to prison?
Why me?
Wait.
He's the one who dunked him first!
- Yes! All I did was watch! - Right.
I don't have the strength to kill anyone.
That goes for me too!
I didn't do anything either!
Who pushed him?
You did.
You dunked him first!
What nonsense is this?
We all dunked him together!
Not me.
Silence!
Nobody here is free...
from this death.
This could ruin Mone's life.
Why should I care about her life...
when I could end up in prison?
You don't expect that from us, do you?
Is that all an agency CEO can come up with?
We all saw...
who pushed him into the pool, didn't we?
I need time to think about...
what will be best for us all.
What's there to think about?
Toss him into the sea.
I'm up for that.
We can say he went for a walk and lost his footing.
What if he surfaces?
Won't the autopsy show how he died?
His lungs will be filled with water from the pool.
What should we do, then?
What else?
Bury him somewhere on an island.
There's a deserted one 20 minutes away by boat.
Let's bury him there.
You want to commit murder and dispose of the body?
It was self-defence!
How so?
He harassed Mone.
I know the guy well.
He has no family to look for him.
There won't be a problem.
You're right.
There are no hotel staff,
and the cameras are out too.
No one but us saw what happened.
Can't we...
just get rid of him?
A show of hands.
Should we call the police...
or deal with the body?
Let's move fast. There's no time.
If someone were to come, we'd really be done for.
Who wants to call the police?
Then...
who wants to bury him?
Hold on tight.
One, two, three.
What is wrong with you?
Darn it.
Hurry up.
- Oh, dear. - Gosh.
What do you think you're doing?
You, in the back, come and help.
Pick him up. Over here.
Get him in there.
That's it.
Leave that.
One, two.
We're done.
Luka.
Begin.
Activating plan.
Why do I feel so invigorated?
I'm hungry and thirsty. Aren't you?
Is there anything to eat?
Let's look.
I'm hungry.
So am I.
Shall we?
- A toast! - Cheers!
Wasn't that so much fun?
It was the greatest day of my life.
Once we get this done,
we'll return to the hotel and party again.
As if nothing happened.
A toast.
Cheers!
Look at that.
Isn't that an aurora?
- What's that? - It's an aurora!
- It's beautiful. - How pretty.
Gosh. Come here.
- Goodness. - Ouch.
- Gosh. - Look at that.
This is paradise.
It's beautiful.
Look at the fruit hanging from the trees.
- Gosh. - Look at all the fruit!
- It's so nice. - What?
It's a unicorn.
There's a unicorn.
Come over here.
A unicorn?
It's a unicorn.
- What? - Come on.
- Goodness. - Come look.
- Jin Mo. - Jin Mo.
It's a unicorn.
I think something good will happen to us.
This feels like a dream.
- It's so pretty. - Right.
- Gosh. - Come here.
There, there.
Fly, unicorn.
- Fly, unicorn. - Fly, unicorn.
- It's flying. - Gosh, it's flying.
- It's flying. - It's flying.
Be happy.
What's going on with the boat?
We have a problem.
- We have a problem. - What? What is it?
It's being washed away by the sea.
- What? - No.
How can a boat that big get washed away like that?
I'm not sure. Maybe it wasn't anchored properly.
I can't remember. I was too drunk on the aurora. What do we do?
Are you kidding? What are you going to do?
- What are you going to do? - What do we do now?
Calm down. We should call for help immediately.
No. It's a secret that we came here.
Should we be trapped here forever, then?
Wait, I took a selfie with Mone at the dock earlier.
I'm so exhausted I could die.
You did great.
Yes, that's it.
(Boreumdeul Dock, Inquiries welcome)
I found it.
- Yes! - We're saved!
Give me the number. I'll make the call.
Hello?
I'm Han Mone, the actress.
Yes. Oh, we're...
on an island 20 minutes away from the dock.
Well... There's an aurora and pretty flowers too.
Yes, that's right.
Could you send us a yacht here?
Help is on the way.
- Thank goodness! - What a relief.
Who said you could call for help?
How are you going to stop him from talking?
Why are you all so careless?
We should have come up with a plan...
before calling for help.
Move.
Why do you keep picking fights over every little thing?
- Oh, my. - Goodness.
You jerk. Do you know who I am?
Who are you?
- Hey. - Gosh.
- Stop. - Don't.
- Hey. - Stop this.
- Calm down. - Hey.
Stop it.
I'll pay him to keep his mouth shut.
He won't talk if I give him 100,000 dollars.
Gosh, this guy is generous.
Hey. Over there.
There's a cave over there.
We can bury the body in that cave.
Isn't it the perfect hiding spot?
- Yes. - Nice.
We're so lucky.
Be careful.
- Watch out. - Hey.
Wait for me.
Hey.
Watch your step.
- Where are we going? - Gosh.
Over there looks nice.
Bring the body over here.
- Careful. - Here.
- Lift him up. - Be careful!
All right. One, two, three.
- Darn it. - Gosh.
Put rocks on top of him, one by one.
- What? - What?
Rocks?
You people, we came all the way here...
Can't we just leave it here?
Rocks? What is he talking about?
What are you doing?
Everyone has to do it. No exception.
We're all on the same boat.
Let's just do it.
- All right. - Okay.
- Come on. - Let's do it.
Quickly.
Put rocks on top of the body.
- Here. - Here you go.
- Pass me a rock. - Place the rock there.
- Gosh. - Here.
- Here you go. - Gosh.
By the way,
I heard from a hotel staff earlier,
and apparently,
there's a scary legend about this island.
An old Japanese treasure ship...
drifted onto this island,
and everyone was slaughtered...
by a monster that protected the island.
Their eyes were torn out,
and their limbs were bent.
That's ridiculous.
All we have to do is bury the body.
We seem to be done here.
So let's get back to the hotel...
and enjoy the rest of the party. What do you say?
- Yes. - Sounds great.
- Yes. - Yes.
Okay, great.
- What? - What was that?
What?
- Bats! - Gosh.
- Come on. - What is that?
No, go away!
Help me.
- What? - Gosh.
Please help me.
Darn it.
Hey, you jerk!
Move!
- Darn it. - Gosh.
It's so heavy!
Hold on.
Keep holding.
Everyone, let's save Mone first.
Mone, get out.
Really?
- Hurry up. - Quickly.
Thank you, everyone.
My dear fans, I'll never forget about your love for me.
Good luck, everyone.
I'll repay you with good acting.
I'm going.
- What? - Gosh.
I'm almost 60 years old.
I'm a doctor.
Mone needs me.
You can't just leave!
Sorry, Jin Mo.
What are we going to do?
On a count of three, we'll get out at the same time.
Okay.
One!
Two!
We made it.
Everyone, get some rest. I think we're safe here.
Relax for now.
What happened?
Why did the cliff collapse all of a sudden?
And where did those bats come from?
You're the one who suggested to come here.
You're responsible!
Darn it.
What are we going to do now?
We're all going to die now just to bury the body.
Nobody's going to die, you jerk.
We should just call 911.
We can ask for a rescue helicopter.
The man who died at the hotel died of a heart attack.
We didn't kill him.
No.
Five more people are already dead.
They might pin everything on us.
What?
Why isn't my phone working?
What's going on?
- What? - Gosh.
- There's no signal, is there? - I've got no signal.
- Goodness. - Darn it.
I was right.
This island is cursed.
Those people earlier...
They died with broken necks and limbs.
This...
is Bobble's curse.
Bobble's curse.
Hey!
Why did we do such a thing at the hotel?
We drank away as if we were possessed by something.
We moved a body as if it was nothing.
We must all be insane.
Everyone, please.
We should only be thinking about...
how we're going to get out of here.
Unless you want all of us to die together.
Right.
The rescue ship must be here by now.
Let's go to the dock.
Find a way to get to the sea. Quickly.
Move.
- Hurry up. - Let's go.
- What's that? - Come on.
What's...
What's going on with the trees?
There's something down there.
What is that?
Wild boars!
- Oh, my gosh. - Run!
No.
Get away!
Stay back.
Serves you right.
Take that.
What?
You big fat pig.
You can't touch me!
Goodness.
Stay back!
Get out of my way!
Don't go.
Don't leave me.
You jerk!
Help me!
Help me, please.
I'm exhausted.
What are you doing?
Aren't you going to share?
Be quiet.
- Give me some. - Be quiet.
What are you doing over there?
Hey, be quiet.
Come here.
Guys, there's water here. Line up.
- Water? - Line up behind me.
- Darn it, that jerk. - Water...
- Water... - There's water.
- Water. - Water.
- Line up. - Stand in line.
Get in line.
Is there enough?
It's just one bottle.
Hey.
- Stand in line. - Don't do it.
Keep order. Gosh.
- Don't drink too much. - Drink just a little.
- Hey. - What are you doing?
- Hey, stop. - Hey.
- Hey. - Let go.
Darn it.
- Gosh. - Really?
What do you think you're doing?
Are you insane?
There wasn't enough for us to drink more than a droplet each.
Why did you drink all of it by yourself?
Throw it all up!
What are we going to do now?
What's going on now?
Why? What happened?
Is she dead?
Look at her face.
- What is that? - It's a monster.
Who's there?
Maybe it's the monster that protects the island.
Be it a person or a monster, it better not show up.
I'll kill it if it does.
I think it's headed this way.
- What? - It's coming.
It's coming this way.
The body.
Hey.
- What? - Gosh.
(The Escape of the Seven)
Are you saying only seven people can make it out of here alive?
I killed him.
All we did was protect ourselves.
If we hadn't killed him, we would have been killed.
We have to work together and overcome this.
You're all connected to Bang Da Mi, right?
Mone, didn't you go to school with her?
Bang Da Mi's curse?
This one is a huge scoop.
Who could have left that threatening message?
Can't you see our silence is why they're tearing her apart?
Thank you for cooperating with the investigation.
Ms. Geum? I'm Matthew Lee.