(Names, characters, places, and incidents)
(are all fictitious for entertainment purposes.)
(We don't condone any acts portrayed in this production.)
You watch your man all day long.
Are you afraid that he might get away?
I'm afraid he might only come back when it's convenient for him like you.
There's another person who has entered the tiger's nest.
I learned that the maid
you hired wasn't normal.
Deal with this father and daughter.
If you can't do it,
I'll have to do it myself.
You'll learn how the betrayal of love tastes one day.
Keep this evidence. I'll expose him before the media.
I'll make him lose his business in Thailand.
Go tell your family. I'm going all-in for this match.
Do you think you can win against me with something like that?
I'm satisfied enough to teach you a lesson in front of the media.
(Even if I made a time machine)
(to travel back in time to see her,)
(even if I had 10 more chances,)
(it's all meaningless)
(if we can't learn how to admit)
(our mistakes the first time.)
Why did you go to his room?
I was just investigating to see what he'll attack us with.
You couldn't do anything to him
and you also got exposed. Should I say you deserve it?
At least, I find out he wants to build a boutique hotel opposite our hotel.
He's talking with the land's owner.
What have you been doing then?
You knew he'd overtake us. Why didn't you stop him?
I'm trying.
I'm trying to get close to the owner.
You'll fall for his trick again.
You've never caught onto him.
So, can our condo project be done in time?
Kaokla has already gone to that house.
The owner seems to be interested in Kaokla.
But I don't know what conditions they have discussed.
Good.
If we can't get that land, he can't get that land either.
Should we use this?
Ten years ago, that land was almost expropriated for an art gallery.
If we dig up this project again
to expropriate that land,
Kaokla has no way to win.
Good.
We have to get back at him.
I hope no one will allow him to ambush us again.
I'm not a modest man. I'll tell you that.
I won't be satisfied with just you.
What have I ever done to you?
Why are you so grudgeful towards me?
I asked myself this question too.
What have I ever done to your family?
For everything you've done to me,
I'll give it back to you.
It'll get worse
if you haven't learned your lesson.
You're lucky that you could turn it around just in time.
They used a dirty trick against me.
I only did the same back to them.
They'll counterattack us by taking that historic house.
We have to close the deal for our boutique hotel as quickly as possible.
That place will be our first hotel.
It'll become a hot topic.
I want you to see that place with your eyes.
I don't think it's suitable to make it a hotel.
You should come with me.
I'll take you to see what I want to do with it.
But if you disagree, I'm always ready to change my mind.
If you're this confident,
I want to know what your dream is.
If Mr. Sin changes his plan to build an art gallery,
Prompt's condo project will be abandoned.
Mr. Prompt isn't good at doing big projects.
I want Prompt to prove himself.
The art gallery project
is just politics.
He wants to win against Kaokla.
We wouldn't get any benefits.
You can take this project back to manage it yourself.
You can also gradually teach Prompt.
If you only wait for his order like this,
when can our relationship
be revealed?
The result will come out this evening.
They said this award is a curse.
Whoever receives this award will be single or have to divorce.
Then, I can break that curse for you.
If you really do get the reward,
I'll let you become the head of the family.
Don't you think that it'll be Lita instead?
Lita?
If she knows that she has to be single,
I don't know whether she would still want it.
Congratulations on the Woman of the Year award.
Woman of the Year? Me?
Yes. It's you.
Are you lying?
Hello.
We would like to interview you to give it out to the media.
We'll go prepare for it first.
Sure.
It does hurt.
Your dream must have come true now.
What dream?
It's the first time you have won against Saikhim.
You'll be even better
if you become the director of the new art gallery.
What's this?
The application letter for the new director of the art gallery
that needs a new director.
The award today
will open up your way
to become the new director of the art gallery gracefully.
I bought this award to upgrade you
even though this award should be given to Saikhim.
See?
I'm so generous.
You should be grateful.
Bought the award?
What do you mean?
Kaokla wants to build a hotel opposite my hotel.
I want to borrow your hand to get rid of him
by opening up this new art gallery before him.
You had gotten rid of him from Saikhim once before.
What's wrong with getting rid of him again for this award?
Is this the Stupid Woman of the Year award?
You thought that when you bought it, didn't you?
If you don't want it, don't accept it then.
Let Saikhim go.
How could you think like this?
Or do you want Kaokla to come back to expose
that you swapped the letter and caused them to break up?
If you promise me that
you would keep everything a secret
and keep that man out of Saikhim's life,
I promise that
I'll send you to study in England with Saikhim.
The one who's trying to blackmail me
isn't Kaokla.
It's you instead.
I'm also not Saikhim
who would just let you ruin my life with your stupidity!
If you don't take advantage of this chance,
your life won't be able to improve again.
This award will be going to Saikhim when I disobey you.
I don't want it.
I don't care if I can't get it.
For the Woman of the Year award for this year,
we only choose the woman who's renowned for...
Aren't you going in?
Are you afraid that you'll be disappointed if it's not you?
Have some sportsmanship. You can't accept that someone is better than you?
Woman of the Year award recipient for this year is
Ms. Lita Thongma, a new designer
whose work has become well-known internationally.
Congratulations.
Where are you going?
Go accept the award.
It should be Khim's award.
You should go first.
Go accept the award.
Please. It's your time to take the award. Please come quickly.
This way, please.
Ms. Lita is here. Please give her a round of applause.
Congratulations, Ms. Lita.
Congratulations.
Now, we'll take some photos. Please give her another round of applause.
She has accepted the award.
Good.
Deal with the application later.
Yes.
Lita, Lita.
What's wrong? What happened?
This award is like a symbol of my shame,
that I'm not good enough.
Hey.
Who would think that?
It's not an award.
It's a punishment for both of us.
Punishment?
We didn't do anything wrong.
It's about...
It's about the land that you can't give to your dad.
You didn't manage to do it for him,
so I got this punishment.
- Lita, accept it for now. - No. I don't want it.
- But Mr. Sin told you to accept... - I said I didn't want it!
Tell him to go to hell!
Lita, please come this way.
Hey, give this to her.
That award is supposed to be yours.
But suddenly, a sponsor gave a big donation to steal it from you.
That sponsor dared to host the award ceremony
to keep and protect the award.
How did you know?
Everyone knows it.
What did you do to your dad?
He didn't care about you like before.
Although we're rivals, you're a talented woman.
I don't mind it.
I actually want to cooperate with you.
Do you know that I want to build a hotel opposite yours?
If you continue staying here and feel uncomfortable,
you can work with me.
Don't let a man
treat you as his puppet.
Where is my dad?
He just went out.
(Construction Model for the Art Gallery)
It's about the land that you can't give to your dad.
You didn't manage to do it for him,
so I got this punishment.
(I want to build a hotel opposite yours.)
If you continue staying here and feel uncomfortable,
you can work with me.
Kla.
Suddenly, there's an art gallery project.
They said they want to expropriate that historic house.
This can't be a coincidence.
Your father-in-law
was the one who dug this up.
They want to stop us so badly.
What will you do?
Let me consult with Kloy first.
Kloy, where are you? Why haven't you come yet?
(I don't think I can come now.)
Is something wrong?
(I'll call you when my errand is done.)
Khem, what's going on?
Why didn't Kloy come here?
I'll go take a look.
Carl.
My mom said she would arrive this evening.
Why did you invite her to come here?
I want to reveal my relationship to my family.
I want everyone to be together.
I don't know whether your mom would like me.
I'm not her favorite son.
She isn't that possessive of me.
There's nothing to be worried about.
You can relax.
Wow. It's so pretty.
How did you find this place?
I found it when I stayed at the opposite hotel.
This place is cool and pleasant.
When there's a flower on you, you're even more beautiful.
Clare, this is Asia, my stepmother.
- Hello, Ma'am. - Hello.
We finally met each other.
Please go inside first.
- Hello? - I want to ask you something about the house.
I've prepared this meal to treat you, Ms. Asia.
Have you tried them?
No.
But I'm not a picky eater or anything.
Carl is the same.
He isn't a picky eater.
He's not picky, that's why sometimes
he eats some bad stuff. As for his taste,
I can't teach him to change it.
Mom.
You're here.
I'm sorry for being late.
Do you frequently come back to visit your family in Thailand?
I haven't really got to come back here.
I don't have any home here, so I don't know why I should come back.
Don't you have any relatives left?
No.
I invited everyone here because I want to do a food tour here.
Since you're a great cook,
I want to take tourists here to try your dishes
with a warm atmosphere like this.
Thank you.
Please do it. All of the dishes here are delicious.
Thanks.
This house is pretty because of its liveliness.
I want everyone to come here to feel a warm atmosphere,
just like when we visit our relatives.
She's now collecting her recipes to produce a Thai traditional recipe book.
I want to invite you to produce the manuscript with us.
Sure.
Excuse me, but there are more guests.
More guests?
They're probably my guests.
I have to apologize that I invited my guests here without telling you.
When I heard that there'll be a special meal today,
I really wanted to invite them.
- Please wait a moment. - I'll welcome them.
Ms. Khim, please come inside. Everyone is waiting.
How did you get here?
Your stepmother invited me.
Don't you have any manners?
Why did you come when the owner didn't invite you?
I told you
that your stepmother has invited me.
I was the one who invited her.
Don't be rude to my guest.
Please.
She's Ms. Saikhim,
the owner of the opposite hotel.
Oh, hello.
You're around here, I see.
- Please have a seat. - Let's have dinner, Ms. Khim.
This is my mom.
Mom, this is Khim, my role model.
Nice to meet you.
She's Ms. Rarin, she came from America. She just arrived today.
Rarin?
Ms. Khim, please take your seat right here.
When I was a child, I was a picky eater.
My mom had to pack up food from our home for me to eat at school.
I could only eat my mom's chicken stew.
Do you know what's the only Thai food my mom has ever cooked for me?
It's American fried rice that American children wouldn't know.
Isn't that right, Mom?
That's good.
I don't have a mom.
I don't know what a mom's dish tastes like.
When I was sick
and missed dishes from my home,
the dishes from my home for me...
There wasn't anything like that. I didn't even know what it was.
What are you trying to do?
Why did you bring Saikhim here today?
You dated Claire
because she has the same mother as Saikhim, right?
You know that,
so you tried to make them meet each other.
Haven't you done everything for today?
The day that Saikhim finds out that her mom has another child.
This is a chance for your revenge. Why are you still hesitating?
Even if it is, you have no right to get involved.
You said you didn't care.
Then, what have you planned all this for?
You wanted to be bad, so you should crush them now. Crush them to death.
Stop being flippant.
Wow. That looks difficult. Why does it have to be decorated so much?
Girl,
old ladies back then,
they had to know how to peel fruits, decorate with leaves,
and how to knead and make sweets.
When they can do all that,
that's when they could call themselves a lady.
Actually, it's not difficult. I'll show it to you.
- Please try it. - You should try it.
Thank you.
- Here. First. - Teach them.
We have to build up the base.
- Can you do it? - Yes?
- Here. - Oh.
- Thank you. You're so great, Mom. - It's not difficult.
- When you're done... - Ouch.
Oh, no.
You're bleeding.
It's fine.
I can take care of it.
Oh, my.
It might be a deep cut.
Does it hurt?
It still hurt less than
knowing that you're still alive.
Everyone said you were dead, Mom.
Why...
Your dad forbade us from meeting each other.
He claimed I was already dead.
He asked me to get out of your life since that day.
You're still alive
and you also have another child.
That's the only thing I can think of.
Claire isn't my real daughter.
She's my new husband's daughter.
I have to raise her.
I feel a lot better now.
Aside from raising your daughter,
you also raised another man's daughter.
You were a child, Khim.
You wouldn't understand back then.
So, you have to act like you don't know me today, right?
Okay. I understand now.
I can't even call you my mom.
So, think of it as
we've never met each other.
Because
I don't exist in your eyes anyway.
Everyone who was dead is alive again.
You came back to mock me, right?
This is the same method your dad has used to get rid of people around you.
You can't say that everyone has left you.
You killed everyone without any remorse.
Do you want me to feel sad?
If that's so,
you've succeeded.
I'm hurt. Are you satisfied now?
You're hurt because you saw that we're better off without you.
I'm hurt because I still remember your old self.
The old you who would never hurt me.
Where did you hide him?
I want that one back.
How much do you hate me for you to do this to me?
I want to see you not being able to love anyone again.
A selfish woman like you doesn't deserve love.
Ask yourself.
What did you do to your child when you were a mother?
What?
You can't love anyone because you only love yourself.
That's why you have no one left.
Even your dad who you think is possessive of you,
is he sincere with you?
He's the one who took your mom away from you
for only one reason. She's not worthy.
You can see it today
that you are the one who isn't worthy of us.
That's it.
That's the thing you want me to remember.
Hey.
Are you leaving like this?
Where is Ms. Khim?
She went back.
Did Carl go to send her off?
No. He's on a call.
That's why he took so long.
You should go wait inside.
Yes.
Khim.
Ms. Khim.
Ms. Khim, why do you look like this?
What have you done?
Ms. Khim.
Ms. Khim, what's going on?
You care so much for her. Running after her like that.
Are you satisfied now?
Don't take it out on me.
You were the one who prepared everything for today.
She's probably confronting her dad right now.
It's all as you planned.
Are you threatening me?
You're so soft-hearted.
That's why your life is stuck here.
The one who you should rebel against
are those people, not me.
Don't try to go against me.
Do you want something in here?
Dad, do you know whom I met?
I met my mom.
I met everyone who was dead.
Because actually,
they aren't dead.
Can you explain what the heck is going on?
I've done something that Saikhim's dad couldn't accept.
He said I didn't deserve to be a mother.
He pressured me
to not be near Saikhim.
Look at these photos.
Look.
A woman who agreed to take this perverted photoshoot.
Does she deserve to be a mother?
She's attracted to a photographer
so much that she took this nude photograph.
And these photos were leaked.
Where could I hide my face?
How would my daughter live?
She couldn't face anyone.
She committed suicide.
She was the one who left me and you first.
I was young back then.
So, I solved the problem foolishly.
I tried to overdose myself in return
after Sin wouldn't forgive me.
(I only blamed myself)
(and forgot about Khim.)
(I just wanted to run away from the problem.)
(He made me feel like I'm so disgusting,)
(that I couldn't be a mother.)
(Until I learned that)
(while he thought I was a bad influence,)
(he began to find a new mother for Saikhim.)
(He asked someone else to replace me.)
(When I realized that,)
(that my scandal was leaked,)
(it might be done intentionally by someone)
(to become the third wheel in our family.)
When I offered her to die from your life,
she readily agreed to it
even when you're a child.
She didn't care about you at all.
An unloving woman like that,
why would I keep her?
If you have decided to leave,
don't come back to your daughter again.
(She wanted to be with someone else.)
(She wanted a new life.)
(I gave her an ultimatum)
(to not face you ever again. She still did.)
(Unbelievable.)
(She's so selfish.)
I walked away
to make Saikhim believe her mom has been gone since then.
(To make Sin be able to face everyone else again.)
That's why I can't go back to Khim again.
And Khim was still young.
(She didn't even know what sadness is.)
Since
she only knows one side of the truth,
I don't know
why I should destroy a child's world
when we can live our lives without problems.
Why did you hide this from me for this long?
You still lie about this important matter to me.
Would there be anything that I can trust from you, Dad?
What did Rarin tell you?
Why did she come back?
Mom has another child.
Her daughter is Kaokla's girlfriend.
Kaokla again.
He caused us to be paranoid about each other.
Why aren't you blaming him?
He only stabbed me with the truth.
Even if it's painful, it's still the truth.
I suspect that his death and my mom's death
are just your excuse.
You use me as an excuse to eliminate people whom you don't like.
What are you saying?
Kaokla told me
that we're the ones who killed him.
Why was Kla in prison?
Can you explain it to me?
Did you get brainwashed again?
I...
The one who isn't worthy,
you wouldn't keep them.
Now, I'm not worthy to be your daughter.
You use money to buy the award for Lita,
to use Lita to put me down.
Lita saw you as her rival.
She hasn't thought of you as her friend.
She has done everything to win against you. You know what?
If she could steal your boyfriend, she would.
And so what? If I lose against Lita,
are you going to be embarrassed?
That's why you would kill me with this.
Mr. Sin might have lied to you
because he doesn't want you to hate your own mother.
A lie
came from a good intention sometimes.
You're pretending to console me,
but actually, you're laughing in your heart.
Ms. Khim.
He really has good intentions towards you.
Trust me.
Even you didn't tell me the truth, Oun.
I really feel bad for Saikhim.
Everyone around her
is all insincere towards her.
Khim, what's going on?
What happened?
Can I stay here?
Is something wrong?
You didn't answer my call.
(I want to see you not being able to love anyone again.)
(A selfish woman like you doesn't deserve love.)
(Ask yourself.)
(What did you do to your child when you were a mother?)
A woman who agreed to take this perverted photoshoot.
Does she deserve to be a mother?
She's so attracted to a photographer that she took this nude photograph.
She was the one who left me and you first.
Should we visit your mother?
Try to listen to her side of the story.
Don't make a conclusion right now.
People have both good and bad sides.
It doesn't mean that she can't be a parent.
Your dad forbade us from meeting each other.
He claimed I was already dead.
He asked me to get out of your life since that day.
Aside from raising your daughter,
you also raised another man's daughter.
You were a child, Khim.
You wouldn't understand back then.
(You can't love anyone because you only love yourself.)
(That's why you have no one left.)
Do you want me to feel sad?
If that's so,
you've succeeded.
I'm hurt. Are you satisfied now?
(You're hurt because you saw that we're better off without you.)
(I'm hurt because I still remember your old self.)
(The old you who would never hurt me.)
Where did you hide him?
I want that one back.
(Hong Hean Yoo Sa Bai)
I don't know whether he's dead or sleeping.
He must be tired. It's a long drive from there.
What about you?
You should think of him.
Dad.
Can't you see?
Do you think I can't choose?
If you don't like him,
don't hold him back.
Since when did I hold him back?
It's you
who ruins his self-confidence. You said he's dirty
to not make him hit on other girls, right?
You're sly.
I feel bad for Khem.
He's naive.
Kloy, please stop the car.
I'm sorry that I didn't look after you.
Watch out.
Kloy.
Kla said
you would drive to your home.
If you're this nice,
did you do something wrong?
I'm being generous.
You should thank me.
You shouldn't be sarcastic.
Is this your redemption?
- I hope you'll do this all the time. - Yes.
Please come this way.
(Can you feel something else aside from guilt?)
(She doesn't want only your sympathy.)
Since I was born,
this is already halfway through my life. I haven't done much.
For the rest of my life, I can give it to you.
Living for someone else
might be better for me.
It's already disgusting enough.
Who would endure it for the rest of their lives?
Who told him to be naive? I can't help it.
And where is the document about transferring the land?
I forgot about it. Let me go get it.
I've prepared it.
Here. This is for the land.
I found this one after I went through my stuff. It's been seven years.
I have no clue if it still has legal consequences.
(Marriage Certificate)
Dad.
What's this?
Since that day,
everyone thought Kla was dead.
But he changed his name and surname.
I don't know that it'll be dragged this long.
Is this going to be a problem?
Call your lawyer right now. Quick.
Sure.
Yes. I'm taking someone to make a complaint against the expropriation.
Can you please check the document I've sent you
to see if it still has legal consequences?
This is important. I want you to look at it now.
(Yes.)
Khem.
Khem. Wake up.
Pack your stuff and come down right now.
Okay.
You're leaving right now?
- Yes. - What did he say?
I'll go to hear it from him in Bangkok.
This is a life-or-death matter.
I have to go back to handle it for Kla.
About your land transfer, I'll handle it later.
Okay. Sure.
What's going on?
Don't waste more time.
- Where are we going? - Dad, goodbye.
- Let's go. - Khem.
- Take care of my daughter. - Yes. Where are we going?
Here.
I'll tell you one thing.
I suspect that
they want to transfer the land around here
because they want to make an art gallery.
I might not be able to die here.
I might have to stay in a nursing home for the elderly.
They're only threatening you.
Actually, this project was canceled once.
I'm trying to threaten them back.
Don't give up just yet.
They might lose to themselves.
Someone file a complaint
saying that you would use the art gallery to benefit our hotel.
They also know that we want to appoint our people as the director.
How is this possible?
We haven't announced anything. How could they know?
Lita might betray us.
I think this is from Kaokla. He wants to frame us for corruption.
With this stupid adviser,
it might get you in jail.
Your marriage certificate with still Khim exists.
The lawyer said it still has legal consequences.
You have to divorce her, Kla.
There might be a problem for the business.
If you don't divorce, Khim can't marry her boyfriend.
Good.
We have an advantage.
You don't look bothered.
Did you already know about this marriage certificate?
I'm waiting to see when Saikhim will notice it.
Kla, don't you think when your girlfriend knows this,
what would happen?
Khim, are you feeling better?
I'm alright now.
Thaen, are you free?
I think I'll resign from the bank soon.
I'm in talk with a new place.
Will your family's bank
let you resign, Thaen?
If I want to grow up,
I have to leave that place.
If not, I'll be controlled by my dad forever.
That's the news about my dad.
This is related to your hotel.
He intentionally attacked my dad.
Who?
Are you here for your package?
Yes.
It's you, right?
You sent someone to claim that there's corruption.
Your dad intends to expropriate the land to keep it to himself.
He deserves it as he used his unlawful authority.
If we give this house to you,
will you stop your grudge against me?
I didn't want to have a grudge against you.
Then, drop this complaint.
If you want to get back at me,
don't drag anyone else involved.
You can take this house if you want it so much.
But stop bothering us.
It would be great if it's that easy.
Even if I get this plot of land,
we might have to share its ownership.
We haven't divorced.
We're the same person according to law.
Impossible.
Karma sometimes comes back in the shape of marriage.
Then, let's divorce.
I would love to.
But I have to be sure that you wouldn't suck my money from me.
Who would want your money?
You want this land even though it isn't mine.
How could I trust a trickster like you?
What do you want?
Transfer your share of the hotel
if you want to divorce and get married.
I'll divorce if you have a better offer.
Dream on.
Then, I guess your groom-to-be will wait for nothing.
He can't marry you in this life.
Let's hope he can marry you in his next life.
When did you come here?
We need to talk.
What did you talk about with Saikhim?
You two have known each other before.
Yes.
What about the marriage you were talking about?
We used to date for a short while.
Date? Or did you two marry?
Does Claire know about this?
It's long in the past. I didn't tell Claire.
I've been with Claire longer than I'd been with her.
I didn't have any feelings for her anymore.
Let me tell you something.
Normally, time can heal love,
anger, grudge, regret, and sadness.
It'll make them become just a memory.
Like when I forgot my disappointment for Saikhim's dad.
But from what I've seen,
I think you're trying to fight against its nature.
You're afraid it'll disappear from your heart.
Do you still dare
to say that Saikhim doesn't mean anything to you?
If it's not for this coincidence that's bringing everyone together,
I would never let my daughter
be stuck in this complex relationship.
For both of my daughters.
Legally, if we can prove that the husband and wife
haven't lived together for more than three years,
it can be considered that the marriage is over.
It can be used to sue for divorce.
If I don't sue,
is there any easier way to end this matter?
You can agree to divorce.
But both sides must consent to it.
What about our properties?
That's the problem. I don't know whether you can come to an agreement.
This divorce contract indicates that
you won't claim any right in your marriage.
Consider all properties that were gained during the marriage
are personal properties of both sides.
You can offer this contract to him first.
If he doesn't have any problem with any of the conditions,
you might not have to file for divorce.
I heard you went to consult with the lawyer.
This means you had registered your marriage with Saikhim.
You might lose everything because of her.
Our business is also owned by Nate.
I won't let anyone else
take the inheritance from my son again.
Before you get into the stock market,
you have to end this problem.
Yes.
I won't risk our company.
When your dad secretly dated your mom, he also said that.
A man is usually indecisive.
That's why the problem has become this big today.
You're fortunate that you didn't have a child. If not, she might...
I know that you thought of me as a parasite.
You couldn't accept me.
This is the model of our boutique hotel
that the designer sent to me.
If you don't handle your divorce immediately,
I'll take your project back.
Don't let your old wife
use this opportunity to steal it from us.
I assure you that I can handle it.
If you can let a single piece of paper bind you down,
you're just good for nothing.
How was it? What did you get?
Not yet. But she might try to take everything back.
Everything is going in her way.
You have to divorce her now.
So, she won't have any excuse to take your company.
If I have to listen to everything she says,
I'll become a soulless man.
I wasn't born to be ordered around by anyone.
I'll never let anyone replace you.
Someone's luck
isn't something you can improve.
That means you can't marry Thaen yet.
Not only that,
but I also can't let Thaen know about this.
I have to get a divorce before Thaen suspects anything.
And does your dad know about this?
I can't let him know either.
The only one who knows about this other than us is Oun.
But Oun wouldn't suspect anything.
There is no reason for him to not divorce you.
He also wants his own benefits.
I have to take the divorce documents to convince him
before he uses my past to blackmail me.
Seriously.
I'm scared of his mind.
If he could kill me to make him single again,
he would do it.
He wouldn't dare to do that much.
He hates me so much that he can do everything.
He used to love you so much.
How could he hate you that much?
Did my dad drag you to get you involved in the art gallery?
It's lucky that he got exposed.
I might get criticized that I'm one of your dad's people.
I'm sorry about this.
He has dragged you into this problem.
He's paying for his karma.
He can't take the land
and he is also being investigated.
I think he'll lose his position as a minister.
Did you tell anyone
that I put in your name for the art gallery's director position?
The evidence is here.
Take it back if you're scared.
Then, who leaked this?
Kaokla could use this to file a complaint.
If you're afraid I'm a spy,
you shouldn't use me in the first place.
Forget about this.
If anyone asks you,
you must tell them that you don't know anything.
Of course. You've never used your authority
wrongfully before.
Good.
Don't betray me later.
Don't threaten me with Saikhim's letters again.
If not,
I might change my mind
to change my side and tell Kaokla
that you faked the letter and used me
to destroy his love.
If he knows,
he might try to get back at you
even more than this.
I could never
teach you manners.
You sent me to study, not to fix my personality.
It's difficult to change someone's personality.
Keep an eye on Lita.
- See if she contacts Kaokla. - Yes.
We filed a complaint about the corruption of the gallery.
We need to learn if you're conspiring with them,
or if you're being used.
He can't even protect himself.
Do you think he can protect you?
I feel like she's disobeying me.
I'm a regular at this boxing gym.
But I haven't had much time lately.
I saw that you're stressed about your work and your family.
I want you to vent your stress here.
What you want to let out today,
vent it on me.
I'll be the sandbag for your emotion.
Is it too tight?
No.
I will leave this disciple in your care.
Yes.
Does she need a warm-up?
Ms. Khim.
She is my mom.
What a coincidence. Are you training for boxing here?
I brought her here.
Carl is here to find a volunteer to teach boxing to foreigners
in exchange for teaching languages here.
I want to try it for once.
Hello.
I'm Thaenthai, Khim's boyfriend.
This is good.
Now, I have a friend to learn with me.
I don't think she wants a friend.
Her face looks like she wants an opponent.
She looks like she wants to punch someone.
Khim has told me about you.
We're getting married in five or six months.
If you don't mind,
can I invite you to attend our wedding?
But,
Khim's dad might not welcome me.
But I'm happy for you.
Khim probably wants
to create a perfect family
that she has never had before.
Khim might have shocked at first.
But deep in her heart, I think Khim is happy
to know that you're alive.
I think we should make today as worthwhile as possible.
- On your right, Khim. - Left, Claire.
Good job, Claire.
Good job.
I think I want to take a break.
You can receive her punch.
Don't be scared.
Fight fire with fire.
Let's have a duel.
- Khim. - Carl.
- Stop. - Are you alright?
Weak.
What's wrong with you?
You always like to pick a fight.
Khim.
Khim, do you know what you've done?
She's just a sore loser.
Khim.
Let's go. You should take some rest.
Let's go.
Khim.
You can't surprise him like that.
He sent his girlfriend to beat me up first.
Didn't you see?
Okay, Khim. I think you should rest for now.
If not, you'll get more upset.
Let's go.
Thaen.
I'm not scared of a coward like him.
He's only good with his words.
Khim.
Do you realize that every time you see him,
you always get upset?
Didn't you see him?
- He... - Khim.
You have to learn to differentiate.
Okay. If you want to vent your anger,
I think you should vent it out on that sandbag.
Let's go.
Yes. Of course.
Yes. I found it.
Yes.
That's right.
Please wait a second.
This is an important document.
Why don't you let him read it?
Don't flatter yourself.
A lot of things are more important than you.
Tell him to read it.
So, we can set a date for our divorce.
Let him read it.
I want the answer by today.
I've sent the evidence to the lawyer.
His only charge will be the unlawful appointment of the director.
This is a huge blow for him.
But I have something better.
The condition for your divorce that your wife offered.
Look at it.
She said she won't ask for any property.
You want to divorce without asking for money.
Your family is all the same.
A kiss after a kick.
I'm being fair. I don't want anything from you.
I only want to divorce.
I almost feel touched by you.
If you didn't catch me by surprise earlier,
I might accept your divorce.
Are you trying to goad me?
You're mad like your dad.
Why wouldn't you show this in front of your man?
What do you want? Tell me.
The farm is around here.
If those two don't want to go,
I can send you home when we're going back.
Khim.
I invited her to come to the coconut farm with us.
Doesn't she want to stay with her family?
I want to go with you.
Let me come with you.
Show-off.
Be careful.
Thaen.
Wait over there.
I'll take you here.
Trust me if you want to entrust your life to me.
We'll survive then.
Watch out.
I want you to get to know your mom.
The chance for you to stay with her
isn't easy to get.
She might feel awkward
and she might not want me to know.
But I want her to know that
I'm ready to take care of you instead of her.
She can relax then
if she wants to entrust your life to me.
She doesn't care about me that much.
Khim.
You're the one who doesn't care about her.
No.
Don't make that face.
Come here.
You should smile.
They look lovey-dovey.
Thaen.
They're a show-off.
What?
I said the sunlight is strong.
I'm getting tired.
Come here. Please endure it for a bit more.
Please do what my mom wants for now.
- Does it hurt? - Ouch.
- Try this coconut juice. - Thank you.
Can I ask you what you love about Ms. Khim?
What are you asking? They're all embarrassed now.
True love is when we fall in love with the same person over and over.
I feel like that with Khim.
What a cute couple.
Look. She has drunk all of the drink, but she still keeps drinking it.
I felt like she didn't pretend to keep her appearance when I first met her.
She looks real to me.
Whenever I think of that,
it made me smile.
No Disney's princess
would drink like that in front of a strange man.
Don't drink like this again. It isn't good.
I think Mr. Carl must feel the same way.
I don't think like that.
I don't like a gluttonous woman.
I wasn't talking about that.
- I was talking... - I have no clue. I have a bad memory.
Where did you throw it?
Khim.
I know that you have everything.
But if you're frustrated and can't share something with anyone,
I want you to think of me.
Although I'm not the most important person in your life,
I'm ready to hear your problem, no matter how tough it is.
I'm ready to help you.
Don't let your dad destroy your feelings.
If a man gets disappointed once,
he won't ask for love from anyone.
He'll make everyone else feel hurt
to protect himself to not getting disappointed again.
A man like that,
he'll force us to feel guilty about everything
until we feel like we're not good enough.
I don't know what happened between you and him.
But I think it's good
that you're trying to keep your distance from him.
Do you know about our relationship?
Carl...
Carl is similar to your dad.
I know with a glance that he's hard to stay with. He likes to act tough.
He wasn't like this back then.
Mr. Sin wasn't like this either.
But it's because of me.
Boys, you must be tired now.
Go take a shower and let's have dinner.
Yes.
Khim, I'm sorry
if...
I've ever made you feel bad with your dad.
He might become like this because I've disappointed him.
Thaen.
I brought your clothes.
Where do you want me to put them?
Hey. Let me go. Are you crazy?
Did you want to flirt with your man?
I'm sorry.
You're mistaken.
What are you doing? Hey.
Don't. No.
We're even
for what you did to me in the morning.
You overdid it.
I'm all bruised.
Can you see them?
The wound...
They're all yours.
You're still asking me.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry.
Is Carl inside?
You can relax and take a shower.
I can wash myself outside.
There's no secret in this world.
Letting everyone know isn't that bad.
What did you say?
It's empty now.
You can go use it.
You might see something inside.
Khim.
What have you done?
The weather is too hot, so I just took a shower.
Why didn't you change first?
Thaen, do you have any clothes left for me to change into?
Let's go find one.
- Yes. - Let's go.
Then, I think we should eat them now.
Yes.
How is it? Do you like it?
- It's delicious. - This is a feast. There's also a feast for my eyes.
Pervert.
I was looking at the scenery. You dirty mind.
Degenerate.
Everything you said isn't nice to hear.
You should try this.
Don't be upset anymore.
What a gluttonous woman.
- What's wrong? - It's spicy.
Are you alright?
Is that so?
I'll bring water for you.
- Yes. - You can drink this coconut milk curry.
Drink it for now.
Can that relieve the spiciness?
Where did you learn it?
Coconut milk curry.
You can use that to relieve it. Spicy chemicals will dissolve in fat.
Coconut milk can decrease the spiciness
and the burning in your mouth.
Let your wife take it.
Well...
Well, well, this is bad.
I think everyone knows that coconut milk can relieve spiciness.
I also heard about that.
We can find it if we search this on Google.
It really does help.
See?
For my daughter,
I don't think 200 million baht is too much.
Although Dad doesn't like it, I'll marry you.
I'll give you the last chance to prove yourself.
Destroy Saikhim's wedding.
This is your wife's stuff, right?
You're already married.
I caught his lie.
He also said he wouldn't divorce.
I'll divorce.
I can't stand living in this world with this man.
Your life was almost ruined because of him.
You should get some marriage properties as compensation at least.
The new divorce contract
asking for marriage properties.
She really wants to stoop so low.
Go call her to see me.
We have to end it by today.
It's only for a night
and you can stay with your man for the rest of your life. It's worth it.