(Names, characters, places, and incidents)
(are all fictitious for entertainment purposes.)
(We don't condone any acts portrayed in this production.)
They said you're dead.
I'm afraid I'm tenacious.
Why did you come here?
To watch my enemy die.
What is Prompt doing?
He asked his people to investigate Kaokla.
Don't go in. It might be his plan.
He made us suspect something.
When we break in, he'll put a charge against us.
So, you're a thief.
We had to teach you a lesson so you won't come here again.
I'll investigate why he wants to buy that house.
I'm good at below-the-belt stuff.
Should I let you stay here for a night as a test?
Please stay over tonight.
There'll be people who lose more than us.
I've never wanted to do any sin
until I want to curse you to death today!
(Technology exists to help make our lives convenient,)
(but it could never help our love become easier)
(We could see each other easily.)
(Love each other easily.)
(But it's harder to feel connected.)
You haven't gone back?
Can I go in with you?
Is he really clean? He's just plain dirty.
Khim.
Is something wrong?
I want to go back for now.
Khim, what...
I'll add aroma for you.
(Look at what I've found.)
(It looks like Kaokla and Thaenthai are doing business together.)
Thaen?
It's impossible.
Hey.
He's quick to fall asleep.
(Khim, you're almost married. You should try acting like a wife for once.)
(If he's this nice to you, he might be hiding something from you.)
(You should try)
(to see whether he's hiding anything from you.)
(If you can't find it, don't marry him.)
Did you know that Thaenthai invested in Kaokla's business?
Thaen hasn't talked about work that much.
Doesn't he know that you are fighting with Kla?
I can't bother Thaen's work with my personal problem.
When we asked him to invest in a hotel with us,
he wasn't interested.
I think Thaenthai doesn't respect us anymore.
He probably doesn't want us to know, so he's been hiding it.
It's like he's taking Khim for granted.
He doesn't care about you.
We can't blame him one-sidedly.
Khim is also hiding something from him.
You shouldn't tell that you're Kaokla's ex-lover.
Would my daughter meet any sincere man?
Every man seems to always trick you.
Kla.
So, do you want me to accept the bank's offer?
Okay.
Let's see whether we can make them paranoid of each other.
If they don't only care about benefits,
this won't do anything to them.
Impossible.
That family wants to catch me. Last time,
they invited me to go on a cruise.
He's getting married soon.
They still made that kind of move.
A woman like Saikhim doesn't deserve good love.
She might not have a chance to get married.
Khim.
What are you doing here?
I want to see you, Thaen.
You should call me when you want to see me.
I almost went out.
I just passed by here to run errands.
Thaen, are you going out for work?
Isn't today a holiday?
I have some meetings today.
Is it that urgent?
Do you want to stay in my room?
I'll rush back after I'm done with work.
It's alright.
You should go to work.
Khim.
I'll call you after my work is done.
Don't worry.
Your work is the most important thing.
I can't compare my girlfriend with my work.
I have to for a meeting with Carl's company.
It's my dad's project, Khim.
We don't know whether we will cooperate.
I haven't told you
because I see that you're having a problem with him.
I don't want to make you uncomfortable.
Why are you telling me this?
I don't want you to learn this from someone else.
I don't want you to be paranoid
or feel uncomfortable with words from those who hate us.
Thank you, Thaen.
There's only you left who is sincere with me.
I heard you met with Kidakarn. How was it?
They must be shocked that you're still alive.
I don't know. I don't care about them.
You came back here to get back at them, didn't you?
It's a coincidence.
I've never cared about them.
Then, you must be serious with your love this time.
It can make you forget Saikhim.
Saikhim has never meant anything to me after that day.
Didn't you have to go to the police station?
Didn't you want to get involved with her again?
Don't worry about my old flame.
If you don't like it, who would dare to go against you?
What if I say I don't like Claire?
Would you dare to break up with her?
Why would that be difficult?
There's nothing I can't do for you.
I hope it's true.
I'm tired
of hypocrites.
Claire is a really cute girl.
I'll introduce her to you sometimes.
You must love her so much
if you said that.
You could say I'm smitten with her.
Can you feel my love?
What about the historic house?
How's the progress?
I met the owner.
And what?
Is it suitable to be our first boutique hotel?
It's beautiful, but I think it can be even better than that.
It's not as worth as making it a hotel
to compete with our rival.
A new hotel on the opposite side of Kidakarn's hotel.
Aside from getting money, we can make them feel humiliated.
I haven't thought about this
as the owner didn't want to sell it yet.
I asked you to work, not to just talk.
Don't you realize that you're doing a business?
I'm starting to wonder if you're worried about Saikhim.
No.
I've never cared about them
and have never thought to lower myself to them.
Then, it must be because
you only focus on doing your app.
That's why you didn't want to do what I asked you to do.
Do you still respect me?
I might have to teach you a lot of lessons
like the first day of your job.
I had to teach you how to tie a tie.
Don't you think it's a waste
to not get what your dad has left for you?
Don't you want to accept your dad's legacy?
You're born to be his son.
Don't make him lose his dignity.
Khem.
What are you wearing?
A leash.
Someone tried to put it on me.
- What are you doing? - Lady asked me to get rid of your dad's stuff.
Right.
There's something interesting.
There is a document that she intentionally destroyed.
I tried to put it together, but I couldn't read it.
So, I checked your dad's computer.
And I was right. I found this document.
Take these boxes.
I have to use a decipher program
to learn that this is your dad's will.
She said there wasn't any will.
There is.
And there is your mom's name.
(Your dad intended to give you his inheritance,)
(but Lady intentionally didn't use this will)
(as she's afraid you would get your share.)
(Are you sure?)
(She adopted you as her son)
(to block you from her husband's inheritance.)
(She intentionally took your inheritance)
(for herself and her real son.)
(A kiss after a kick.)
(There wouldn't be any woman who can control my life.)
I took all of them.
I volunteered to get rid of them.
If that will is real,
this woman is more dangerous.
Thaen has admitted
that he's partnering up with Kaokla.
He told you and you believed him?
The woman that you saw
is Kaokla's sister. Thaen wouldn't think anything of her.
What I'm worried about is that Thaen might get tricked by them.
Even if he doesn't like her face, he might like her money.
We all like money.
You said it like you don't know Thaen well.
So, you would let him off?
Hey.
You don't have to act kind just because you're afraid he wouldn't love you.
The worse a woman is, the more love a man will have. Understand?
If I'm bad and only attract those kinds of men,
I don't want it.
He would never stop bothering.
If I get to build a new condo, I'll ask you to design the penthouse.
Which condo?
Oh, Saikhim hasn't told you?
We're building a condo opposite our hotel.
I want you to help decorate it
to be our house together.
You still can't be cured of your delusion.
If you want me to be cured,
someone has to help me fulfill it.
Seriously. Where did you get this kind of confidence?
You'll see.
In the end, you can't run away from me.
We're compatible because we know each other well.
I couldn't believe that you could stand this kind of man.
What? Do I look like I could stand him?
Even if he's the only man left, I wouldn't want him.
That's a relief then.
Don't fall for him.
Prompt is inside.
We should go somewhere else.
He's ready to insult you.
Let's go.
Even if you can trick Khim today,
it doesn't mean you can trick her forever.
You should mind your problem first.
Hey.
That two-faced guy. You don't realize that you've gotten Kaokla's leftover.
Are you still serving her? Look at him.
(Dad, I received your vegetables.)
Do you want me to do photosynthesis by myself or what?
You sent me too much.
(I sent them to strengthen you.)
Consider it your seventh anniversary
of your reborn.
(You got a new life.)
You have to love your life.
Kla!
You can't die!
Don't give up!
You can't die, Kla!
I have to use a decipher program to learn that this is your dad's will.
She intentionally took your inheritance
for herself and her real son.
(I don't want you to be careless.)
You had a chance to wake up.
I know that.
(You have to be grateful to your stepmother.)
(She revived you back.)
(If it wasn't for her,)
you wouldn't have today.
Is she still kind to you?
Don't worry.
I won't forget what she did.
I'll pay back twice for everything she's done.
(Opening the door.)
Hello?
I've checked the computer.
Lady called me to tell us to hurry up with the boutique hotel.
She said she would find an architect to renovate that house.
Boutique hotel?
She sent an example of the design she liked.
It's on the computer.
I'll get it for you.
(Opening the door.)
Hello.
I'm the one who called for a maid.
Can you clean my room when I'm not around?
Yes.
(Probably around three or four hours.)
I'll be back in the evening.
Please look after my room and tidy up my clothes.
I'll send you my room number and details.
Sure.
(Eighth floor B88/3)
The owner is an old noble, so you have to visit them yourself.
I don't want them to feel like we're there to buy his house.
I want them to feel like we're visiting our relatives.
I don't want to rush them.
Kla.
They might need money and want to sell the house.
If we're that direct with them,
they'll think we're throwing money at them.
We won't do it like those greedy Kidakarn.
We won't be like those who only want money.
What a bad mouth.
I got to talk about a project with your sister.
Kloyjai is new with investment. Please advise her if you can.
No problem.
I believe that you two are compatible.
Yes.
(Welcome.)
This is Indian gooseberry.
It's a traditional fruit that can cure some diseases.
- I want to give you this. - Thank you.
Thank you for giving it to me.
My dad has a farm in the countryside.
He made me only eat healthy food.
I see. There's also that basket.
How could we eat all of them?
That opposite hotel
just gave us that.
They sent their people to us.
They want to buy this land of mine
to build a condominium.
Come on.
- Let's go. - Come inside.
Come.
To build a condominium?
Yes. But let me tell you this.
I don't think I will sell it to them
because I think I want to die in this place.
Don't say that.
Okay. Since you two are here,
- I think, Chor. - Yes.
You go and make Indian gooseberry chili paste.
Let them try it, alright?
- Yes. - Isn't that good?
Have you ever tried it before?
My mouth is watering now.
Good. Then, wait for a moment.
- Go make it for them. Quick. - Yes.
Not his real name.
His birthday?
His ID numbers?
It's the last chance now.
Is he trying to avoid my face? If he's still inside...
He isn't here.
Then, it's easy for me to seduce him.
Don't notify him.
Why am I so unlucky?
Someone tried to open my computer.
Your computer is in your room.
Who got inside?
Hello.
Are you in my room?
I arrived and ran into your girlfriend.
- My girlfriend? - Yes.
A small woman. She looks rich and pretty.
She's also wearing a revealing outfit.
She's not my girlfriend.
It's fine. I'll deal with it myself.
Hello? What's wrong?
What are you doing in my room?
You told me that I could come here when I'm hungry.
Aren't you going to keep your word?
When did I tell you that?
Why did you touch my computer?
No. I just touched it when I placed some of my stuff.
Stop using dirty tricks to get my information.
Is Kidakarn too stupid to fight fairly?
(Mark my words. Your condo can't go anywhere.)
Get out of my room and return the keycard.
(If you're still bothering me,)
I'll remove your friend's room from the system
as it lacks security.
Fine.
They haven't learned.
They still dared to get into your room.
We're fighting against a cornered dog.
It's more aggressive than I thought.
We have an advantage from here.
It's done.
Come here. Bring it to them.
- Place it on the table. - Can I have a seat?
Sure. Please have a seat.
Have a seat.
This is it.
Indian gooseberry chili paste.
It looks tasty.
Eat a lot of them.
When you're finished, please tell me
whether this recipe is good. If it's good,
I'll record it.
Here you are.
What's this?
This is my recipe book.
You can say it's my family's recipe.
Can I look at it?
Sure.
You can look at it. They're all my recipes.
If you want to make a recipe book,
- I'll help you. - Really?
We just have to gradually type them out.
Then, we'll check it later to see if we miss anything.
Thank you so much.
But you two,
do you really have time to do it for me?
I'll gladly do it if I get to eat your delicious food from your recipe.
Okay. Then, please do that.
Eat all of them.
- So, you'll have the strength to... - That's okay now.
- Sure. - Thank you.
You watch your man all day long. Are you afraid that he might get away?
I'm afraid he might only come back when it's convenient for him like you.
All of your family knows it then.
Having clean food does nothing
if your behavior is still like this.
What kind of a clean woman likes to break into my room?
Don't use be contradictory.
You're using your body to investigate a rival. You're so good, aren't you?
When you come and go out of my room like this,
I'm afraid you'll go into the wrong room someday.
What I already spat out,
I don't want to waste my mouth with it again.
Kla.
Who did you call?
Who did I call?
I'm Carl.
(Carl)
What do you want again?
What...
Is there something wrong?
I want to thank you.
I have something else to ask of you.
(I have to work in Shanghai all week long.)
Do you normally cook for yourself?
What would you like?
I have a lot of organic vegetables in my boxes and my fridge.
You can take them if you don't mind.
(They're from my dad's farm.)
(It's a waste to throw them away.)
I'll give them to you.
In exchange, you have to take care of my mushrooms when I'm away.
Of course.
Thank you.
Since you've cleaned my room, I can relax now.
You'll get to relax later.
How can I bring this reserve battery with me?
When I'm tired, I get more strength when I think of you.
I don't know how I'll get a life force.
I want you to stay beside me to charge me up.
Then,
I'll charge you up with my energy.
What?
I just came back. The energy isn't enough.
I'm still tired.
What should I do?
Can I reserve my battery energy?
(I'll leave them to you.)
(Enjoy your meal.)
Mr. Carl isn't living alone.
There's a woman with him.
It's Saikhim. What was she doing over there?
Keep your eye on them.
I have to know what their relationship is.
Okay.
Today, we'll talk about cloud systems for accommodation booking.
Customers can look up the details, price...
(No new notification)
I gave my vote to you.
You'll get the crown this year.
For Woman of the Year's award,
you'll surely get it.
Look at who I'm competing against.
Look.
We're competing against each other.
How could I win against Khim?
Gosh.
Then, just forget it.
I don't want this award anymore.
Because at least if it's about your boyfriend,
I think you can win against Khim in that aspect.
Khim's dad is possessive of her.
It's difficult for her to have one.
Mom, Khim is getting married soon.
What? Getting married?
It's her second marriage. Meanwhile,
you don't even have a boyfriend.
But don't give up just yet.
The matter of husbands isn't certain.
Your soulmate
is in front of our door.
- Look at him. - Don't tell me
you found someone for me again?
I told you to not force anyone on me.
I didn't call this one for you.
My customer saw that you're a nominee for the Woman of the Year award.
She said this man is suitable for you.
So, I invited him to our salon as my customer.
What's this, Mom?
Welcome him yourself.
I'm tired of your test. Goodbye.
Bye.
This daughter of mine.
He's so handsome.
Is this Lita's house?
I'm tired of it. Why does she need to bother?
If I have to date a normal man, it's better not to date one.
What's with Mom?
Lita.
A guest is here to see you.
Come down here. Quick.
I'll go back.
I shouldn't have come here.
Why did he call me so much?
I'm sorry that I didn't call you for the appointment before.
Am I bothering you?
No.
You can call me like your mother. Don't mind it.
You're...
I'm Thaenthai.
Your name is also handsome.
What is your job?
I'm working at a bank.
Oh.
Here.
(Theanthai Tulanont)
That's why you look dignified.
Please come here. Since you're already here.
Come here.
Have a seat.
Please lay down.
Lay down.
We're going to improve your look.
When Lita comes down,
I'll make Lita scream when she sees you.
Take off your glasses.
Since you work at a bank,
you probably can transfer some money.
- What did you say? - You must be ready to pay up.
- Can I borrow 1,000 baht? - Huh?
Well, I would like you
to give some votes to Lita for Woman of the Year award.
Lita is afraid she will lose to her close friend who's in the final round.
I have to ask people in my province to vote for her.
- Excuse me. - Yes.
Where are you?
Hello?
- Hello? - Hello?
- Hello? - Where are you going?
Mom?
You.
Why didn't you tell me you were coming? You let her touch you.
You almost got a new mother-in-law.
Did you answer my call then?
Why did you come here?
- It's about my dad and Khim. - What did you say?
It's about my dad and Khim.
I can't hear you. Say it again.
That your dad wants a richer daughter-in-law than Saikhim?
Who would dare?
Don't tell Khim about this.
If your dad doesn't go to ask for Saikhim's hand,
Khim will learn of it soon one day.
My dad didn't hate the idea. He only has a bias.
If Khim feels bad about my family,
she will hesitate about our wedding.
Do you have hush money?
I'll vote for you with 10,000 baht.
You want it right? Woman of the Year's award.
Please help me with my charade.
Help me stop my mom from finding men. If you can chase off a man today,
I assure you that
I won't tell anyone about your dad.
Hello.
I have an appointment.
You can't see him.
Can you see now?
It's that guy.
- Okay. - Good.
I heard you just moved here.
Yes. I moved to be a school principal.
Really? Then, you probably love children.
Here. Let's take couple photos.
- One, two, three. - Ready?
Please smile.
One, two, three.
Turn your head here.
Come closer. Touch my cheek.
Please look straight.
- Is it short enough? - That's enough.
Mr. Principal, I was wondering
if you have gone to the market.
Who will cook for you if you live by yourself?
Well...
I'm hungry now.
What should we order this evening?
Oh, my. If you're hungry, you can come to have a meal with us.
I'm having a headache. It's so hot today.
Can you massage me?
Massage me. Strongly.
Wow. It's so good. It's comfortable.
It's done, Mr. Principal.
It's done.
I'll excuse myself now.
Thank you.
Hey! My goodness.
Why don't you continue that upstairs?
Not only you can transfer the money,
but you can transfer her heart too.
Transfer my heart?
Mr. Principal, don't forget to take your change.
Don't forget what you've promised me.
Hey.
It's normal to fall in love with a man as perfect as that.
Mom.
What are you saying?
Your eyes sparkled when you were with him.
Do you think I didn't notice?
A rich man like him wouldn't leave Saikhim.
Well, it's just an act to teach you a lesson, Mom.
Do you think I would be serious with him?
(You only want what you don't have.)
(That's why you didn't feel happy with what you have.)
(When you're jealous,)
(it's a sign that you believe that)
(you're not as good as Saikhim.)
(A smart)
(and impressive woman)
(must have more self-confidence.)
(My daughter is good enough to steal someone else's belongings.)
If no one loves us, we have to love ourselves.
I love Khim, Mom.
But I couldn't help but compare myself to her.
She can get everything easily in her life.
When I think of that, it's more upsetting
when Khim made me feel like
I'm a villain.
No one's life is easy.
Khim also has her own problems.
(This world sends a good man to Saikhim)
(to compensate for her dad's distorted love.)
(Saikhim has no one she can love,)
(so she has to behave nicely to make her dad proud of her.)
(As for you, no matter how ridiculous you are,)
(I've never blamed you once.)
(Having someone who loves you)
(without having to ask for it is extremely fortunate.)
(This is one thing)
(that Khim is less fortunate than you.)
You have more love than her. You should share some with her.
If you don't want to be the villainess of the year,
stop being jealous of Saikhim.
Let your friend have good love.
Speaking of which, actually,
a silent man like him,
if you have to stay with him,
it's boring. He looked too serious.
For my daughter,
she deserves someone spicy.
Our family is the home of spicy girls.
- Mr. Sin. - What?
I found the loophole in Kaokla's Arsa app.
Someone used his app to do illegal activities.
- How? - Tourists begin to find local guides
which makes it difficult to control illegal guides.
As for the car drivers,
people start to use their personal cars for public transportation,
the same like the app that was regulated earlier.
Ban him.
To make him stop his business.
I've released an article exposing this.
There should be an anti-trend coming soon.
We need to make him move back to his home.
Kla, look.
Our app is banned, claiming it causes teenagers to gain money illegally.
Find out who released this news.
Check if there's a mastermind.
I have to call you back earlier because of this.
There's a TV station that wants to interview you.
Are you ready to refute the claim?
I'll go to the interview.
It might silence them.
Kla, wait.
You have to see Lady first. She wants to see you now.
I have told you.
Your app has a weakness.
That's why you got attacked by them.
They just don't dare to fight fairly.
They need to use a dirty trick.
Can you still say that Kidakarn isn't our competitor?
You said you wouldn't involve your grudge with your work. It's impossible.
You're too careless.
I admit
that I underestimated them, so I got ambushed by them.
Wait.
There's another person who has entered the tiger's nest.
The other day,
I asked the messenger to send you documents while you're away.
I learned that the maid that you hired wasn't normal.
Deal with this father and daughter.
If you can't do it,
I'll have to do it myself.
Contact anyone who wants to phone in with me.
There's a tourist in the hotel requesting a masseuse around here.
Good. Send our people upstairs.
Ann.
I've accepted the request.
- Go up now. - Yes.
It's time for the masseuse.
Can he handle it?
If we can prove there's prostitution within the app,
this app will be closed down.
I can guarantee that
our app has an identity verification.
Everyone who uses our app can check it.
Our app focuses on helping and sharing kindness.
We don't have illegal activities or child labor.
They still haven't come out by now.
This isn't just a normal massage.
We can use this as evidence to say
that someone's using his app for prostitution.
That volunteering activities are just an advertisement.
You'll go on a news show tomorrow.
We can use this clip to expose him.
But this woman is only an actress from us.
We still have our prey in the spotlight.
This means his app has no protection.
Kaokla is deceiving everyone.
He dares to be a saint.
Tomorrow, he'll be a sinful man.
Who is actually deceiving the people?
If we get caught, Uncle Sin will have to take responsibility.
Whose side are you on?
(I can guarantee that)
(our app has an identity verification.)
He's upgraded himself.
He isn't as bad as when he came to trick Khim.
Your stupid plan, Prompt,
can't do anything to a sly man.
If you can do it with him,
he's not that smart.
Keep this evidence.
I'll expose him before the media.
I'll make him lose his business in Thailand.
Are you here to see Thaen?
What about you?
Don't tell me that you're here to see Kaokla?
And so what?
Are you jealous?
Be careful.
Don't let him brainwash you.
Why are you here?
Go away if you want to kiss me after a kick.
Khim, how did you get here?
Let's get inside.
Yes.
I'm here to warn you.
Prompt will release another scandal of your company.
- Why are you telling me this? - To assure you I'm on your side.
If you can betray your family,
do you think I would trust you?
You can trust me when you're in ruin later if you don't mind.
But let me tell you. The evidence this time
will make you lose your balance.
If you're scared, you can talk with Prompt about the hush money.
If you give up on the land opposite the hotel,
Uncle Sin might change his mind and won't expose you.
- Khem. - I've checked it for you.
A tourist used our app from Elite Hotel.
(I checked his volunteer profile.)
It's a new profile.
(It might be an impersonation)
(to accept a request in our app.)
I think something will happen.
Impersonation?
We got done by them.
I've warned you.
I have a problem to settle.
Go tell your family.
I'm going all-in for this match.
Khim.
I found the auspicious time for our wedding.
The monks gave me the auspicious time.
In six months. Or at the end of the year.
I forgot my stuff in my car.
I want to go and get it.
Sure.
Can I get the CCTV footage that I requested?
Here you are.
(I've watered them.)
The weather is nice.
Yes.
Khim, can you decide on our wedding date?
If you still can't decide, we should order something for our dinner.
Yes.
Wait here for me.
Are you that happy?
- What's wrong? - You're acting oblivious.
What's wrong with you?
You must be angry that your true nature got exposed.
I don't care about that.
I know that I'm not that great of a person.
I'm not good at pretending. I can't put on a mask like you.
I can only be half as bad as you.
You made a blunder.
- Why did you take it out on me? - Yes.
I made a blunder because I was careless.
You're a wicked woman
with various schemes.
If I'm wicked,
you must be a douchebag.
Khim, what's wrong?
Show your true nature. Stop acting already.
What did you say?
Have you seen her true nature?
How bad is she when she's behind your back?
With her bad mouth
and her black heart.
You're so great, aren't you?
See?
Your dark side will come out one day.
You're only good at doing something behind people's backs.
Mr. Carl.
Do you know what?
She's good at using your sympathy to kill you.
What are you saying?
You'll see.
I'll expose your lies and deception.
You'll know how horrible she is behind your back.
Why are you quiet?
Why aren't you saying anything?
I won't feel anything if you curse me in your heart.
You'll learn how the betrayal of love tastes one day.
What's going on, Khim?
Why did you suddenly fight?
He picked a fight with me first.
Why was he that rude to you? What happened between you two?
It's just because of business.
Because I expose his business.
That's why he's that angry.
(A tourist used our app from Elite Hotel.)
(I checked his volunteer profile.)
(It's a new profile.)
(It might be an impersonation)
(to accept a request in our app.)
(Ms. Kasalong Saengchai)
She's good at using your sympathy to kill you.
What are you saying?
You'll see.
I'll expose your lies and deception.
You'll know how horrible she is behind your back.
Why are you quiet? Why aren't you saying anything?
I won't feel anything if you curse me in your heart.
You'll learn how the betrayal of love tastes one day.
(Are you asleep? I want to ask something from you.)
(I'll move out of this condo, but I don't have time to move my stuff.)
(I would like to bother you for the last time.)
(I would like you to oversee the workers.)
(If it doesn't bother you, I would like to ask for your favor again.)
(No problem. I'll help you.)
(Thank you.)
Mr. Songsin went to give an interview for a TV show
regarding our app.
Find out the TV station and what show it is.
Tell them that I'd like to appear on it.
This is going to be fun.
Ms. Khim.
Kaokla said he would like to appear on a show with Mr. Sin this evening.
I think this has become far from what we expected.
I don't think Dad can catch onto him.
It's fortunate that you let me appear on the show.
That's good.
I think it'll benefit our citizens.
I want to see how you would answer us
and how you would fix this problem.
If there's a problem with my system, I can fix it.
But if it's a problem from an attitude,
I think we have to change it.
I hope it'll make some people open their minds.
So, they would come out of a cave.
You're still arrogant.
You might get knocked out.
Just you wait. Someone might lose their own face.
Are you ready? Five, four, three, two, one.
Good afternoon. Welcome to Perd Pom Khao today.
We'll talk about the news
that is the talk of the town.
It's about the famous app
which are being questioned
whether it's good to be used in Thailand
in terms of morals and ethics.
Please go that way.
(Today, our show has welcomed Mr. Songsin Kidakarn,)
a minister from the Ministry of Tourism and Sports,
who is worried about the ethics of this app.
(And we also have the owner of this app, "Arsa".
(Mr. Carl Raman. Greetings to both of you.)
- (Hello.) - (Let's get to the point.)
There was one certain video
from an app user. They called a masseuse to massage them in a hotel.
(But the video in question,)
it doesn't look like it's your normal massage.
Please take a look at this footage.
(This is the footage in question.)
From this footage, most people would feel that
it looks like a certain act of prostitution.
If that's true, there's been an illegal usage of the app. Isn't that right?
Well, we just saw it together.
Honestly, I'm worried.
If some people use this app to hide their illegal activities,
the app doesn't have any measure to stop it,
or discourage it or anything.
(From the outside, it looks like an app that lets people help each other.)
(But when it can't be regulated,)
(we can't say for sure whether the activity is legal or not.)
If the app is being used to exchange accommodations,
and we can't check or regulate it,
would that hotel have enough standard
as what tourists expected? If not, it can be damaging.
You're now in the hotel business too.
Yes. That's another topic. That's just my business.
I'm looking at the big picture of our country.
To make us be trusted again by tourists
who want to travel in our country after COVID,
it's not an easy process.
(If we run into this situation, it might badly impact our country.)
(That's the opinion of Mr. Minister.)
Mr. Carl, how would you explain
to the minister, society, and the audience?
I admit that
some people have used fake accounts in our app.
But I can say that it's a minority.
We want volunteers to share their kindness
to use their time to create extra income.
If we find an offender,
we can revoke their Arsa's membership.
I want everyone to see the benefit of this app
that matches the lifestyle in this city.
(How? I'll be the representative of our audiences.)
Please give an example of how your app works.
Of course.
I want to move house today, but I have to come to this show.
(I only need someone who can help me move my stuff.)
Here.
This is the volunteer who came to help me move today.
We'll see
if this person is actually the person who registered with my app.
There are a lot of details here. There is a face,
name and surname, and phone number.
I'll let everyone see this.
This is what the Arsa app looks like.
(I want everyone to see with their own eyes)
(that there are still good people who can still help us.)
(We can check to see if this person is an actual member.)
(If this member isn't Ms. Kasalong Saengchai as it's indicated,)
my company would reconsider our system.
(So, Mr. Carl, you're saying that)
(you have the system for checking)
which can be trusted that no one can impersonate anyone else
to do any illegal activities with your app.
This depends on the discretion of the users.
It's like your usual dating apps.
If both sides consent to it,
we can't say that all of them are lying.
You still insist that you created this app to help each other, right?
Yes. I think several people can benefit from this app.
(For example, an elder without relatives.)
(They can call someone to run a small errand that they can't do.)
(Someone can teach a kid how to do his homework.)
There are still handicapped people.
I would like to offer my opinion since it's missing our point.
The benefit that you imagine might exist, but what we're worried about
(is that if our country can't regulate the app,)
there might be criminals in there. That's what I'm worried about.
What he said has some interesting points.
If people would like to offer their time to someone else,
I think this app will make our life better
as no one will get left behind.
He's talking about the app, while I'm talking about tourism and sports.
I'm talking about the purpose of this app.
(Please calm down.)
(This is getting hot now.)
(But we'll go for a break,)
We'll come back in the next part. Don't miss it.
Because this volunteer will visit Mr. Carl at our studio.
But for now, we'll take a breather.
I'm sorry. The truck is almost here.
Okay.
When the moving truck arrives, cut into the live show again.
And I'll bring one camera to wait downstairs.
You're changing the topic.
I'll never let you blame me one-sidedly.
Watch your mouth.
He's a minister, not your friend.
(We're back. And now,)
(the volunteer is ready.)
(We'll get to see if this volunteer)
is the same with the member profile
in this app. Excuse me.
- Please. - We have to check it.
If he's this confident, this could be an act.
You'll see if it's an act.
Please calm down.
We'll get to see it with our own eyes soon.
We'll watch it with our audiences. Once again,
if it's the same person,
the volunteer must be a maid named
Ms. Kasalong Saengchai, 45 years old.
As indicated on her profile, her hometown is Chiang Rai.
We'll see
whether she's the same person. Let's take a look.
We're now going to see the live footage downstairs.
She's here.
Why did you come here?
To take you to see my boss.
Did you betray me?
Why did you disguise yourself first?
Hurry up. People all over the country are waiting.
Why does she have to hide her own face like this?
From the look of it, it might not be the same person.
Actually, our app can use phone numbers to check the identity.
You can try to call her.
Okay. I would like to contact her now.
We'll see if she'll answer the call.
The phone signal must have reached her.
We'll see her face now.
Does this mean this is an impersonation of identity to misuse the app?
We have to ask her who she is and why she impersonates herself.
If she has bad intentions, I'm prepared to take action against her.
It's unbelievable. We're hitting a jackpot.
Do you feel like she's similar to someone you know, Mr. Minister?
I think she looks similar.
I think she is your daughter.
She might want to try our app by using another person's account.
With her profile, I couldn't call her a con artist.
What do you think about this?
Stop the show right now.
Stop the show. I told you to stop.
Wow. Great job.
Get out of the car. Please respect the reporters.
Don't you have any manners?
Quick.
Stop recording.
Stop it.
Why are you recording it?
Didn't you want to expose the truth? Why are you scared?
They're using a dirty trick to make us a scapegoat.
You can't record this.
- Record them. - No.
You can't record it.
(Let's look at the situation downstairs.)
(In front of our studio. Here she is.)
- I told you to stop. - Record them.
You deceived us, so you have to pay for it.
- Stop. Get out. - Record them.
- (I told you to stop.) - (I'm sorry.)
With the chaos, we should come back to our studio.
The situation right now is unbelievable.
But our time is almost over.
We'll have to ask our minister
to say something in the end.
It depends on the app's maker.
You have to ask yourself who you want to destroy with today's incident.
I already told my purpose for making this app.
But the bad purpose of the impersonator is the cause of today's incident.
I think we have proved
whether it's the app's fault or the impersonator's fault.
So for today,
our topic has become even more interesting.
I believe there'll be the next part. It's such a shame
that our time is over. Thank you to both of our guests.
And...
We'll say goodbye to you for today. Until next time. Goodbye.
What? What have you done?
Your daughter disguised herself to get into my room.
You didn't know that she came to seduce me, right?
She probably can't give up on me yet.
She wants to relive the past with me.
Restrain yourself, alright?
Please be mindful of my father-in-law.
Your face is probably cracking by now.
Dad, don't believe him.
You overdid it.
You deceived me. I was tricked by him.
You stuck your nose in the problem first.
You used a dirty scheme against me first.
You brought a masseuse to me. Just be glad I didn't expose you for that.
Enough!
Do you think you can win against me with something like that?
I'm satisfied enough to teach you a lesson in front of the media.
I'll rip your mask off.
I'll expose to everyone
that you aren't that great.
Sure.
We can say that I was your former son-in-law.
You chased me away like a dog.
You might be the dog this time.
My daughter.
Are you satisfied now?
We have to talk.
You overdid it.
You know the truth. Why didn't you say it?
You tricked me into visiting you.
You have used me.
In the end, you did it to humiliate me.
Are you satisfied? How much do you want to ruin my life?
I'm not a modest man.
I'll tell you that
I won't be satisfied with just you.
What have I ever done to you?
Why are you so grudgeful towards me?
I also asked myself this question.
What have I ever done to your family?
I asked myself all year.
If you just start to question it,
it's not enough.
If you hate me, take it out on me. Why is it related to my dad?
The one who arrested me was your dad.
How does it feel when you're framed?
For what you've done to me, I'll give it back to you.
It'll get worse
if you haven't learned your lesson.
If you want to get back at me,
don't drag anyone else involved.
What have I ever done to you to make you so grudgeful of me?
If you don't use this chance,
your life won't be able to improve again.
Tell him to go to hell!
If you stay here and feel uncomfortable,
you can work with me.
Mom, this is Ms. Khim, my role model.
Everyone said you're dead, Mom.
What have you planned all this for?
You already wanted to be bad. You should crush them now.
Crush them to death.
Everyone who was dead is alive again.
Do you want me to feel sad?
If that's so, you've succeeded.
I'm hurt. Are you satisfied now?