THE GOOD BAD MOTHER
EPISODE 13
GWANGMYEONGHO
Mr. Cho!
Mr. Cho, it's me.
Mr. Cho.
Have you been well?
Mr. Cho, it's me, Choi Kang-ho.
Mr. Cho, what's wrong?
Are you all right?
THE GOOD BAD MOTHER
Suicide?
Ms. Hwang committed suicide?
Strictly speaking,
it was suicide.
It should be here by now.
Is that the one?
That must be the boat Kang-ho mentioned.
We're here. Please get ready.
You need to hide. Now!
Darn it!
You need to hide! Hurry!
Who are you?
Darn it, you…
After that day,
I called you many times,
but you couldn't be reached.
So I went to the Prosecutors' Office,
and I heard you got into a car accident
and fell into a vegetative state.
I had a feeling
those same men were responsible.
I didn't dare report it to the police.
I was helping her stow away illegally,
and if they found out I was alive,
they would've tried to kill me again.
That's why I sold off my business
and began to live in hiding.
I'm sorry for earlier.
When I saw you standing there,
looking rather healthy and normal,
I got scared.
I can't believe anybody anymore,
not even you,
who were like my son.
FLOOR INFORMATION
"Wards, dermatology…"
It can't be the neonatal unit.
It's just as we expected.
They completely denied
that there's a patient here by her name.
What?
Perhaps we were wrong.
Maybe she's not here.
We should look around some more.
Okay.
What are you doing?
-What is it?
-Come here.
-I saw a suspicious man.
What's with you?
Darn it.
You're the most suspicious one here.
Hurry up and hide.
-I'm serious.
-Okay, just hide.
Get in. It's okay.
-So this is the first floor.
-Going up.
What's with you?
The doors are closing.
-Found it.
-What?
What are you talking about?
Goodness, Sis.
I found the OB-GYN department.
-It's on the eighth floor.
-Yes, right.
The eighth floor.
My gosh.
I wonder how big your baby is now.
-Goodness.
-I know, right?
I wonder how big my baby is.
Auntie needs to be here for you.
Goodness.
-We're here.
-Yes, we are.
-My niece.
-Gosh, we're here.
Mi-joo, are you okay?
-Do you want to die?
-Maybe later.
-Let's go.
-What's wrong with you?
This way. Hide.
What?
LEADING THE FUTURE
OF THE KOREAN MEDICAL INDUSTRY
Bingo.
That must be where Oh Ha-young is.
What? Oh Ha-young?
How do you know?
-Do you see that guy wearing a cap?
-Yes.
If he's there,
it means she's there too.
Who is he?
On the day I met Oh Ha-young…
Yes?
…he tried to kill me.
I saw his tattoo.
Let's go down.
I recognized him back there,
-but you stepped on me so hard.
-Sorry about that.
-Wait.
-What?
Those who are in love
don't say sorry to each other.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Sam-sik, my friend.
I'm so truly sorry.
Damn it.
-Follow me.
-I'm sorry.
-Hurry.
-Why?
Why are we here?
-What?
-Why?
It's locked?
Why? It's not like anyone's going to
steal from the laundry room.
We are here to steal something though.
What?
-Yes, you're right.
-That's right.
Hide.
-We seem even more suspicious.
-No.
-Wait.
-What?
All right.
-I think I can do this.
-All clear.
I got it.
My gosh, Sam-sik!
Welcome.
My babies. I'm coming.
What brings you here?
We came to check a few things.
Is Mr. Choi Kang-ho inside?
He just fell asleep.
This is urgent.
Wait, sir.
Sir.
You can talk to me.
You know his condition.
He's not in the state to remember things
to answer your questions.
The visit to the police station
was very disturbing for him.
He's been having screaming fits.
-Detective Cho.
-Yes, sir.
Wait, sir.
Sir!
Please.
Did Mr. Choi
run away?
If he didn't, please let go.
-Mr. Choi.
-Sir.
We're the police. May we have a word?
You need to stop!
Why do you keep coming
to harass my son who's unwell?
If his condition worsens
because of the shock,
will you take responsibility?
Wait.
Do you even have a warrant?
Then you can't just
barge into my house and do this!
It's Intrusion upon Habitation.
Goodness.
Excuse me.
I've warned you.
Don't ever come back without a warrant.
If you do…
I don't care if you're detectives.
I won't stand back.
-Let's go.
-Yes, let's go.
You can come out now.
I almost suffocated.
I've been worried
you might suddenly end up losing your job.
I'm relieved to hear
that you're going back.
Thank you for all your hard work.
This isn't much,
but use it for your flight back home.
It's your severance pay.
Ms. Jin, you're wonderful.
Thanks to you,
I learned a lot about farming
and got addicted to makgeolli too.
Although Korean
is still freaking hard to learn.
Right, Ms. Jin.
I just learned a new word.
What was it?
In…
Intrusion upon Habitation.
I love it to death
When you intrude into my heart
This is a huge hit.
It's blowing up right now.
What on earth is happening?
Tell me about it.
How did you come up with these lyrics?
"Intrusion into My Heart"?
You must be a genius.
We're going to the top
the Billboard charts with this song.
Kang-ho!
Thank you, Kang-ho!
Congratulations, Mr. Son.
A crime-free village commendation
for Jou-ri.
I hear you're the first village
in our area to receive it.
I mean, seriously.
I knew it
when I first heard the name Jou-ri.
Mr. Son, you must feel jolly.
Come on. This is…
I'm sorry.
…all because they picked
the great village head.
I never bothered to say it,
but do you have any idea
how much stress I've endured?
They wouldn't even pave the road
because there weren't
enough people in the village.
Because of it,
we couldn't get early morning deliveries.
And because of that,
people wouldn't move into our village.
-It was a--
-Goodness.
That's good.
I'm finally getting some recognition.
That stings.
-What is this, acupuncture? Be careful.
-That's an acupuncture point. You're fine.
Hey, honey.
How does the suit look?
Is the color all right?
Honey, come and look at me.
What on earth are you up to?
I want to make a suit for our baby too,
since Daddy's receiving a huge award.
She treats her dog
better than her husband.
I'm also an animal expert,
so I'll make a nifty suit for your dog.
You're an animal expert?
Well, just birds.
I used to run a fried chicken restaurant.
It went under.
That's my phone.
But I can't move, can I?
-Please be careful.
-My phone…
-Can you answer it?
-Sure.
Be careful. You'll get paralyzed.
You've never seen a village like this.
Is this Jou-ri or heaven?
This is the phone of the village head
of Jou-ri, a crime-free village.
Where?
The police?
What?
A mur…
Murder case?
Oh, my.
You didn't have to.
This is really good…
More for you, doggy.
Gross. He can't have what a human touched.
Sir.
We came to check a few things with you.
You know Mr. Choi Kang-ho, right?
Yes, of course, I know him well.
He's like a son to me.
This is Mr. Choi
during his police investigation
at our station.
And this is him
when he was at the hospital
with his mother, Ms. Jin Young-soon.
I checked with the hospital
and heard he met the doctor himself
as his mother's guardian
to discuss her condition.
And these documents
were also filled out by him.
What do you think?
There's too much of a difference
to say these are the same person, right?
In your opinion,
which man is the true Mr. Choi?
The one at the police station,
or the hospital?
Police station?
Or hospital?
Come on.
You must be able to tell
if he's like a son to you.
Goodness, a son?
I never said that.
The sun.
He's like the sun.
He's always around his mother,
refusing to leave her side.
So we all said,
"He's like the sun that's always there."
Hey, Sung-ae. Are you there?
-You're here.
-Hello.
Where's our minivan?
Where's Sam-sik? Have you seen him?
No.
Sam-sik pulled a Sam-sik again.
Hey, don't pile on like that.
Have you had dinner?
-If not, you should eat.
-What?
My gosh, what's all this?
Skate, braised short ribs,
sweet and sour pork,
and stir-fried glass noodles too?
Is it a special day?
It's nothing like that.
I just made them
because the kids enjoy them.
Eat up.
Don't worry about the kids.
Just play your hand.
-Yes.
-It's my turn?
-Let's see.
Then…
This one.
Goodness me.
How many times do I have to tell you
that these are different suits?
This one is all black
but this one is mixed with red dots.
Good grief.
In that case,
-what should I play?
-Come on!
Goodness gracious.
You can't show me your entire hand!
Wait.
You only got three cards.
I went first, so you should have four.
-Really?
-What?
-Goodness. What?
-Where did it go?
-We're done with this round.
-Wait.
-Did you pick up an extra card?
-We're done?
-Wait.
-I almost lost big. What a relief!
I was so close to winning the game,
-but you ruined it!
-Put it down.
-I had it in my hand.
-Put that down.
This is awful.
Goodness, are you two in this together?
Darn it!
Don't worry.
We'll play all night
and you can win all this from me.
All night?
You never play Go-Stop.
What's gotten into you?
Tell me about it.
You've been acting odd since last night.
Not only did you sing and dance,
you even had a drink.
When someone acts out of the ordinary,
it means they'll die soon.
Sung-ae!
You startled me.
Why are you yelling?
Please!
You need to stop blurting out words
without thinking.
Come on. Don't be like that.
What the hell did I do?
I was just making a joke
to have a laugh.
To have a laugh?
Is life and death funny to you?
Is it?
There are things
you should and shouldn't say.
How dare you
say something like that to her?
"How dare you"?
Darn it.
That's how you've thought of me all along?
So you're saying
a mother of a thief like me
shouldn't dare to speak that way
to a mother of a prosecutor?
Tell me!
Is that what you're saying?
-You must be drunk. Stop it.
-Don't! I'm not drunk!
What do you know anyway?
A mother like you with a smart son
has no idea what it's like!
Kang-ho got all the attention
for being smart and getting good grades.
And now he's getting all the attention
because he's become an idiot.
Hey, do you even know
how much derision I suffered
because people compared your son to mine?
Have you gone insane?
What's wrong with you?
-Come here! Let's go home.
-Darn it. Let go!
I'll walk out on my own!
-Let's go! Cut it out!
-Let go of me!
-I don't care if he's a prosecutor.
-That's enough!
-You can't do this to me.
-Stop it!
-Darn it.
-That's enough!
Good grief!
-I can't deal with this!
-Where are you going?
Good grief!
Goodness.
No, it's all right.
Goodness, it's all right. Don't cry.
My babies, don't cry.
Why are you acting so childish?
-Goodness me.
-Sung-ae.
I need to talk to you.
Hear me out!
Forget it, you brat.
You're out of my life for good,
so just have fun
humoring Young-soon all the time
-and have a great life!
-Enough.
Goodbye.
Young-soon
is dying.
She has stage four stomach cancer.
No surgery or medicine
can make her better.
That brat must've gone crazy.
What kind of nonsense is that?
I honestly wish I was just insane.
I really want this to be nonsense.
How can this…
How can… What will she…
Jin Young-soon!
Come out!
Sung-ae.
You.
How could you do this to me?
How could you do this to me
to the very end?
You turned me into this crazy woman.
You can't go anywhere.
Stop this nonsense!
I won't accept this.
There is no terminal illness
in this day and age.
There's no illness that's incurable!
So,
go get yourself treated right now!
You can't go anywhere.
You need to stay by my side
and fight with me for the rest of my life.
You brat.
Go get treated now.
Go get treated, you brat.
Good grief!
I hate you.
You damned brat.
You need to live to see Sam-sik succeed.
You must live to envy me
and be mean to me out of jealousy.
You must live
to throw a fit at me, you brat.
Sung-ae,
I always envied you.
You have a wonderful husband
by your side that loves you
and a son who's healthy and amiable.
I was always jealous.
Goodness, what are we going to do?
You poor brat.
What do we do with you?
You poor thing…
-Thank you.
-I had a good trip thanks to you.
And this.
This is fresh abalone.
Please have it with your mother.
Goodness, abalone?
They're her favorite. Thank you.
I'll see you soon.
Okay, sir.
Let me know whenever you need my help.
I will.
-Investigation Officer.
-Yes?
This phone belonged to Park Cheol-su.
He was the defendant in the Woobyeok
construction site case two years ago.
Can you run a digital forensic on this?
But he abandoned the appeal,
and the case has been closed.
I know.
But there's new evidence,
so we must uncover the truth, even now.
Anything that would
help take down Woobyeok Group would do,
so please take a look.
Are you really
going to take down Woobyeok?
Well…
The higher-ups colluded
to destroy all the evidence,
-so it won't be easy.
-It's not that.
To be honest,
I'm not sure if you're
Woobyeok's enemy or ally.
Mr. Park Cheol-su's wife visited me
and told me about this phone.
She made a scene saying
you destroyed the only evidence
and then got dragged out.
The same goes for Yoon Jae-min's case.
Last time, your mother came
and got into a huge fight
with Jung Jong-gu's mother
who was protesting.
That day
was the first time
I felt like quitting my job.
Your mother
yelled at her saying that her son
wouldn't have done something so terrible,
but I couldn't side with her.
I've stood by your side
and assisted you for the longest time.
But to be honest,
I'm not sure what you're really like.
Thank you
for not quitting your job.
Sorry?
I finally have a chance to show you
what I'm really like.
I can't guarantee…
that I'll succeed.
But for the longest time,
you've worked tirelessly to support me,
so I'll make sure
you won't regret your efforts.
Can you really
keep that promise?
Then I'll do it.
We have to do that to Choi Kang-ho?
I always wondered
why Oh Tae-soo
was so desperate to kill Kang-ho.
And it turns out, it wasn't Kang-ho
who killed Hwang Soo-hyun.
I knew it.
Kang-ho isn't the type of guy
to let go once he's onto something.
However,
Oh Tae-soo got wind of it
and acted first.
He killed
Hwang Soo-hyun and the baby,
then framed Choi Kang-ho as the father
and the prime suspect in the murder.
So,
what if the baby's body is found
or Choi Kang-ho regains his memories?
What will happen then?
Now, before any of that happens,
we'd have to get rid of him, right?
How long do we have to stay like this?
Why isn't that punk leaving?
This won't do.
The hospital will close
before that punk leaves.
-Let's begin.
-Sam-sik.
Wait.
Why don't you do it instead?
This is killing me.
-Mi-joo.
-Yes?
What do you think Oh Ha-young will do
when she sees me?
This may be killing you
but I'll really be dead if she catches me.
Okay, give me a second.
Look at me. Wear this and the mask.
Gosh, you look so smart.
You look very clever.
You can do this. You got it, Mi-joo!
No, I can't!
I really can't do this. Sam-sik, please.
I don't have a choice then.
-I must help you.
-How?
-Mi-joo.
-Yes?
What is it?
I'm here to see the patient.
A doctor was just here.
The doctor who just came by called.
The patient has
a severely unstable state of mind,
so she requires counseling.
I'll go back if she doesn't need me.
Wait.
"Joo Gwang-cheol"?
Such a masculine name, right?
My parents gave me this name
hoping to have a son next.
Aren't we all sick and tired
of this preference for boys?
The counseling will take some time.
Ms. Oh Ha-young?
Get out.
May I have a word with you?
Get out of here.
Yes, exactly.
Let's get out of here together.
You know Choi Kang-ho, right?
If you scream now,
you'll never get out of this room.
Do you remember
what you asked of me a while ago?
I'll find the evidence.
So until then,
you must stay alive in here.
Find out the license plate number
of the car
and recover the dashcam footage
no matter what.
I have that footage.
You should cut your nails once you're out.
I got this only a month ago.
Who are you?
Why are you doing this?
What about you?
Why did you do that to Kang-ho?
What did I do?
Aren't you the least bit sorry?
He was once
someone you loved, wasn't he?
He betrayed me first.
He betrayed me before he betrayed you.
But I didn't try to kill him.
Let's get out.
You must confess everything.
No!
Why not?
Because of your dad?
He's capable of killing his own child.
He already did.
He killed your sibling, a newborn baby.
And what about you?
Look what he's done to you.
Do you think this is living?
He put you up to killing a man
and locked you up in here
as a mental patient.
Even beasts wouldn't do that to their own.
And now,
he wants to be a president of a country?
No, I can't condone it.
If you don't do it, I'll stop him.
Then he'll kill you too.
I'm sure.
He's a man who would destroy
anything that gets in his way.
Just recently,
he tried to kill Kang-ho again.
As if killing his father wasn't enough,
this time, he locked him up
with his mother in the farm
and set it on fire.
This is
your last chance at redemption.
At this rate,
Kang-ho may really die.
If you ignore it,
you'll become an accomplice again.
But of course,
you won't go to jail.
Because…
the moment something happens to Kang-ho,
you'll die at my hands.
Let's say I do get out of here.
Then what?
Report my dad to the police?
His influence runs deep.
That includes the police
and the prosecution.
Everywhere,
but one.
Choi Kang-ho.
It's been over an hour.
-Move aside!
-What?
She's in hypovolemic shock!
Hype what?
Hypovolemic shock!
It's an emergency!
-Wait! Just one call!
-It's an emergency!
Sam-sik!
-Mi-joo!
-Sam-sik! Come on!
-Sam-sik, let's go!
-Let's go.
-Are you okay?
-It's an emergency!
Get them!
-Goodness.
-They're coming!
Wait!
Come on.
No!
My goodness!
Sam-sik, hurry!
Wait, you're that…
Damn it.
Wait for me!
-Hurry!
-Come on!
Close the doors!
-Close the doors!
-Go away!
Take the stairs.
Run!
Mi-joo!
Kang-ho, catch!
How could you do something so dangerous?
You're in for it now!
-Goodness.
-Go!
-Get in.
-Okay. Oh Ha-young too!
-Get in the back!
-Hurry!
Wait, I'm not insured with this car.
-Are we good?
-Go!
Hurry!
Are you all insane?
-Mi-joo, you.
-No.
We were perfect. Everyone was great.
It was excellent.
Our plan was more perfect than General
MacArthur's Incheon Landing Operation.
They may not have seen our faces,
but they probably got the plate number.
Come on. Who am I?
I'm Bang Sam-sik.
I disguised it beforehand.
Even ghosts wouldn't know who we are.
SAM-SIK'S MILL
What now? Even ghosts wouldn't know?
-Let go of me.
-That's enough, Mi-joo.
What's wrong?
Is something going on?
It'll be too dangerous
to return to the village.
Let's find a different place.
Can't we just report this to the police?
-No.
We abducted her.
Who are we going to report?
We didn't abduct anyone.
We rescued her.
Who would believe that?
Would you?
Man, what's with my life?
I'm a thief,
a blackmailer, and now an abductor?
Darn it.
What did I get myself into
while trying to help a friend?
Wait.
Friend?
Who's my friend?
Come to think of it, this is absurd.
Why in the world
am I helping you, Kang-ho?
I begged you to help me,
but you didn't even flinch
and locked me up in prison.
You're nitpicking over that now?
-It's okay.
-I didn't have an opportunity before.
He's only just regained his senses!
All right.
First off,
Ha-young participated in the escape,
so this isn't abduction.
The security cameras would've caught it,
so they can't report us.
But we also can't report them.
We can't let anybody find out
until we're thoroughly prepared.
Okay, Mi-joo?
A place where nobody can find us.
Man, I do know this very secretive place.
Where are we?
A place that isn't open to just anybody.
However, it's also a place
that's hard to leave.
If we go inside, I can't guarantee
that we'll make it out alive.
DO NOT ENTER
-He's coming out!
-What?
Hey! Goodness.
Good grief.
-What?
-What are they doing?
Why are they so scary?
Kang-ho, listen carefully.
I'm risking my life bringing you here.
Because we're friends.
Hey, where are you going?
You crazy punk! Where are you going?
Mom, mom, come here
And look at this
Look at this.
You've been ignoring my calls.
I never imagined you would
Show up on your own
So?
Did you bring what you promised?
It's not ready yet.
Instead,
I brought my best friend.
Your friend?
CHOI KANG-HO
SUPREME PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
Prosecutor Choi Kang-ho from Seoul
Central District Prosecutors' Office.
-Please sit.
-Sir, this way.
May my officers sit too?
Of course. Come this way.
-Please.
-Sure.
You've illegally purchased,
renovated, and sailed a ship,
and even operated a gambling house.
Also, you failed to pay your employees,
blackmailed, confined,
resorted to violence,
and made
an illegal organ trading contract.
It seems that your business
should be discussed with me, a prosecutor.
But apparently, you have business
with my dear friend, Sam-sik.
No, sir. I have no idea
what you're saying.
Sam-sik, do I have
any business with you?
You wanted 100 million won from me.
Gosh.
Did you really take it that way?
There must be a misunderstanding.
Sam-sik and I were very close
since our schooldays.
We weren't.
Sam-sik and I attended the same school.
Not that school.
Prosecutor Choi,
you already know what I mean.
I closed the gambling house ages ago,
and look at my staff.
They don't look like they'd blackmail,
confine, or hurt anyone.
Come on, smile.
Aren't they cute?
Something like that
has never happened around here.
I see.
But I heard this hotel
was a private gambling den
open for members only.
Goodness, that's absurd.
This is simply my home.
My house of joy. Home sweet home.
In that case,
may my officers stay here for a few days
and investigate?
Sorry?
Of course.
Of course, this is just my home.
You can just live here.
If anything happens to my officers
or to my dear friend Sam-sik…
It'll be my fault, obviously.
I'll make sure they don't get hurt.
Goodness.
Look at that mess.
Once they burn all those shady ledgers,
they'll be wetting their beds tonight.
What's that?
What?
Fireworks?
My gosh, that's pretty.
-Did you prepare this?
-How did you know?
My gosh.
Aren't you cold?
I am. It's a bit chilly by the sea.
I told you to stay inside.
Why did you come out?
I figured the two of them
needed some time alone.
How pretty.
I know it wasn't an easy decision.
Thank you.
I'm not doing this for you. It's for me.
My life will be a living hell
if I don't do this.
And I'm the cause of that hell.
You were innocent,
but I dragged you into this.
I hurt you deeply.
I'm sorry.
Did you…
ever love me?
I was in love
with someone else.
I thought so.
You always seemed to yearn for someone.
I hated that
and it made me jealous.
That must be why I fell
for my dad's lie when he said
Hwang Soo-hyun was your woman.
The person you love…
is Lee Mi-joo, right?
Yes.
It's Lee Mi-joo.
What's taking you so long
to pick up your jacket?
I'm sure they're after us.
So don't leave the hotel, okay?
Where are you going?
I found Ha-young thanks to you two.
I need to find evidence on Song Woo-byeok.
Song Woo-byeok?
How are you going to find that?
I thought the evidence you had
were all destroyed.
There's one last evidence left.
Don't worry. I'll be back soon.
It's not dangerous, is it?
I'm going there
to make sure there's no further danger.
My dear friend, Bang Sam-sik.
Please keep them safe.
I'll be back.
Okay.
Hey, Mi-joo!
I told you, didn't I?
That if you saved my life once again,
I'd let you marry me.
You saved me from choking on candy
and from the motorcycle accident.
Do you know
the last thing you did to save me?
Our children.
You weren't by our side,
but I was always with you.
So make sure you come back.
Come back and live with us
for the rest of your life, okay?
Thanks, Mi-joo.
I'll make sure I do that.
I'll be back.
Hey.
A little lower and my lips are right here.
Was it too far down?
Was it too far for you to reach down?
Was it?
Goodness.
You always came over with a stomachache,
but it never dawned on me
that you had to see a doctor.
I shouldn't be the village head.
How is that your fault?
You told me to see a doctor
time and time again,
but I never listened.
You had to suffer all alone.
We spent our time in this village
like a family.
Why didn't you tell me?
How could you let me hear this
from a detective
who's a complete stranger?
Detective?
Yes.
Some detectives came in the afternoon
and asked me about Kang-ho,
regarding a murder case.
No, it wasn't Kang-ho.
Goodness, of course, it wasn't.
Young-soon.
I know it's hard for you,
but I need to know what's going on
to help you.
So tell me everything.
What on earth is happening to Kang-ho?
Please stop crying.
You'll break Young-soon's heart even more.
Goodness.
Sung-ae, please stop crying.
By the way, why do you have
those spoons on your eyes?
I can't open my eyes from crying so much.
Why is everyone crying?
Everyone is crying,
so it's making me cry too.
Goodness.
Not you kids as well.
Don't cry.
Goodness, don't cry, my babies.
Your mom.
Let's call your mom.
Mi-joo, it's me.
Can you pick up the kids
from Kang-ho's place on your way home?
Mom, I was actually going to call you.
I won't be home tonight.
I actually won't be home for a few days.
What do you mean?
Where are you? Why can't you come home?
Well, my friend's father passed,
so I'm at a wake.
Mi-joo, the food is here. Come.
Wait.
That voice.
Isn't that Sam-sik?
Are you with him?
Yes, she's a mutual acquaintance.
Your jjajangmyeon is getting soggy. Come.
-Jjajangmyeon?
-Hurry.
So you eat jjajangmyeon at a wake?
You brat. Where are you?
Mom, the thing is…
What are you doing with Sam-sik
that you can't come home?
Have you
moved on from Kang-ho
to Sam-sik, of all people?
It's nothing like that.
Anyway, I can't tell you now.
What do you mean?
Why can't you tell me?
Wait.
Mi-joo.
Something is going on, right?
I heard Sam-sik took his parents' minivan.
Are you in trouble right now?
Tell me if that's the case.
I'll call the police right away.
No, Mom. Don't.
-Not the police.
-Not the police?
Goodness, so something
is going on with you.
Sam-sik, that punk. That son of a gun!
Mom, please. Calm down.
How can I calm down right now?
How? I'm hanging up.
-I have to call the police--
-Mom, please!
The thing is,
it's not about me.
It's Kang-ho.
What? Who?
Kang-ho?
Yes.
So I have to help him for a few days.
But he's in the hospital.
Are you staying out
to look after him?
I will explain everything later.
You brat!
You cursed brat.
You're still out of your senses.
I know
you tried to run into the farm
to save Kang-ho when it was on fire.
You gave everything you had
to support him through everything,
yet he abandoned you.
So why are you still hung up on him
and looking after him?
Why do you keep acting like an idiot?
Because I take after you.
What?
You lived like that.
Dad always put you through so much,
but you only loved him and waited for him.
You know better than anyone
how painful that is.
That's why you're angry at me. Right?
But Mom,
you can also understand me
better than anyone right now.
You know I'll never get over Kang-ho,
that I'll never leave him,
and that in the end,
I'll go back to him.
You know, right?
You're…
my mom,
so you know that.
Thank you.
I've always wanted to tell you that.
You never abandoned Dad…
even though you went through so much.
That you let me…
have a dad.
I also want to be a mother like you
to Ye-jin and Seo-jin.
So help me do that, Mom.
You awful brat.
Why the hell do you want to
live your life like me?
Fine, you brat!
It's your darned life,
so do whatever the hell you want.
But don't you dare
come back to me crying with regret, okay?
Mom.
I'm hanging up!
I can't believe her.
How could she use that against me?
It's all…
your fault, Lee Choon-gil!
If Mi-joo becomes unhappy,
I'll seriously kill you.
Wait.
You're already dead.
Who is it?
Who's there?
Young-soon.
My gosh, Young-soon.
Goodness, poor Young-soon.
It sounds like Choi Kang-ho
is with Lee Mi-joo and Bang Sam-sik.
What now?
Over there.
Get that license plate.
-Three, eight--
-Three, eight, three, five.
It followed us from Seoul.
Who?
Us? Why?
Let's find out.
Go slowly so they don't notice.
Okay.
FAIRY BREWERY, FAIRY REAL ESTATE,
FAIRY FORTUNE TELLING
Find them.
I see a few familiar faces.
Chairman Song must've sent you here.
Why?
Did he tell you to get rid of us
after we kill Kang-ho?
Of course.
We do know a little too much about
Chairman Song.
What?
I'm only an assistant,
so I don't know that much.
But you did learn
how to dig and bury things
while cultivating that lettuce field.
Which one should I bury first?
-Nice!
-What are you doing? Get in!
Okay!
-Let go!
-You punks!
-My goodness!
-Hey!
-Who are you thieves?
-You're all dead!
And we know one more thing!
What Mr. Yang trusts more than his deity
is an anti-theft system.
-Come quickly!
-Faster!
These thieves.
-Round them up!
-You punks!
-Goodness.
-My goodness.
Gosh, this could've gone badly.
-How dare you break in?
-Get them away!
-Take them!
-Round them up!
-Darn you.
-Hurry up.
-Hey, Kang-ho.
-Is everything all right?
I have way too many bodyguards
for anything to happen.
They're like the Avengers.
What about you?
Is everything going well?
This is only the beginning.
I'M TRAVELING THROUGH A STAR CALLED SEA
Presidential candidate Oh Tae-Soo
of the Jeilmirae Party
visited an aquarium in Ilsung-dong, Seoul,
to commemorate
the second Marine Life Month today,
and began his campaign
for the welfare of the people.
Hello, I'm Oh Tae-soo.
Hello, children.
-Hello!
Were you looking at the fish?
-Yes!
"Daddy Fish isn't lonely."
"Because his babies are asleep
in little circular eggs."
"'Daddy will dance for you every day
until you hatch from your eggs.'"
"And then…"
"Crack."
Remember what I told you earlier.
-"Crack, crack, crack."
-You will, right?
Well done.
"His babies finally began to hatch."
"'Hello, my babies.
It's great to see you.'"
"The babies began to kiss Daddy Fish."
"'I love you.'"
"The happy Daddy Fish
danced his last dance and slowly let out
his last breath."
Song Min-ho.
President Oh Tae-soo, let's go!
-Go!
-Thank you.
Goodness, don't say that.
I'm not the president yet.
But now that I've heard your support,
I'm starting to get ambitious.
-You'll make it!
-You will!
Thank you for your support.
The children's book you read
was very touching!
Yes, I was also moved by the story.
I'll be a politician
who's just like a stickleback,
showing love to our people
and making sacrifices
for the sake of our citizens!
Thank you. Thank you for your support.
Please shake my son's hand.
Gosh, you're so adorable.
Goodness, I don't have a son myself,
so I'm jealous.
-What's his name?
-Tae-yul.
Tae-yul, thank you for coming today.
It's great to meet you.
Thank you. Nice to meet you too.
Thank you.
Goodness.
-That's all for today.
-That'll be all.
THE GOOD BAD MOTHER
Oh Ha-young.
She's with me right now.
I only have one goal.
It's to catch Chairman Song.
By the way, why are you here alone?
It'll be difficult
to obtain an arrest warrant
for Chairman Song's past crimes.
Honey, are you watching from above?
Keep me here for a little longer.
This was the very first ring
your father-in-law got me.
I'm truly blessed
for being able to live this precious life.
Our son will carry out the judgment
that we failed to do.
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon