♪Memories pile up, never fading away♪
♪I call it a sickness—I can't let go♪
♪Missing you cuts deep,
shaping your shadow♪
♪All my pain comes
from not wanting to part♪
♪I was caught in the middle♪
♪It's hard to survive♪
♪Love faded in you, but grew in me♪
♪And wore me down inside♪
♪I'm the desert, craving the open sea♪
♪I'll show you the humor in tragedy♪
♪Will you ever remember me?♪
♪The wind flows on, clear like a river♪
♪But me? I'm just stuck being me♪
♪Chasing you, and wandering♪
♪Rain falls, slipping away like wishes♪
♪But my heart stays solid, won't sway♪
♪Love's a flower, doomed to fade♪
=Love Beyond The Curse=
=Episode 1=
(The Yongye people
are blessed with eternal life.)
(But maybe this is fate's punishment.)
(Because their loved ones
would drift away)
(from them.)
(To end this endless existence,)
(they have to plant a Noctrose)
(with their hearts.)
(When the flower blooms,)
(they'll be free.)
(Yan Maidens of the Yan Clan
live only briefly.)
(To extend this fleeting life,)
(they must love a Yongye Clan member.)
(If it's true love,)
(it can break the curse of early death.)
Too bad,
I only have three months to live.
(The Noctrose is reacting oddly.)
(Yan Maiden.)
It hurts.
Who are you?
You're awake.
Are you from Yongye Clan?
The scent of Yan Maiden's blood
attracts Yongye Clan members.
Looks like I guessed right.
You are a Yongye Clan member.
Aren't you scared of me?
No, I'm not.
You should already know
what it means to know who I am.
Your blood is incredibly valuable
to the Yongye Clan.
In my eyes,
you're nothing
but a rare delicacy.
Yet now you want me to save you.
Please save me.
If you don't help me now,
I've got three months left at most.
If I die now,
it's no different than dying later.
How can I save you?
Yan Maidens have always been florists.
Our lives are short, like flowers.
We'll wither when our time comes.
None of us lives past twenty-five.
It starts on a full moon night,
with burning pain and a heavy heart.
Then, we'll be deprived
of all senses and die.
Unless...
Unless I marry a Yongye Clan member,
I could keep living.
Marriage?
Marriage is serious.
Aren't you ashamed?
Yan Clan values walking marriage.
Isn't that just natural for us?
Ridiculous.
It's true.
There was once a Yan Maiden
who married a Yongye member.
She lived until she was eighty.
I'm begging you.
I don't want to die. Please help me.
What's so bad about dying?
You Yongye people live forever.
How could you know our struggles?
I just want to survive.
I want to live like a normal person.
This so-called eternal life
isn't always a blessing.
Life and death are fate. Don't force it.
I've searched everywhere to find you,
even made a boat my home.
It took so much to reach you,
but you...
You should be glad
I haven't hurt you yet.
If you help me...
If you just help me,
I'd serve as your comfort food forever.
Can you walk?
If you can, then leave now.
For centuries,
the Noctrose stayed a bud.
It never changed at all.
But when Yan Maiden showed up,
the bud opened a little.
Why did that happen?
Looks like the one destined
to bloom the Noctrose
has come.
Do you mean
the flower opens when she's here?
Or do you mean...
You need to
find the answer yourself.
Where's the flower?
Where is it?
Go look for it!
Hurry up!
What are you doing?
Why did you ruin my flowers?
Hey, what are you doing?
You took money from the Meng family.
We agreed on a one-month delivery.
It's way past that now!
Wanting Lotus isn't easy to grow.
Look, can't we just talk this out?
Why are you wrecking my flowers?
Stop with the excuses.
If I don't deliver on time,
you're the one who'll pay.
(I can feel it. It's that woman.)
Guys,
throw the flowers into the river.
Smash everything!
Got it.
I'm begging you.
- Please stop.
- Get lost.
Stop?
You can forget about this business.
I'll deliver it
as soon as the seeds are ready.
Okay, I...
♪Memories pile up, never fading away♪
♪I call it a sickness—I can't let go♪
♪Missing you cuts deep,
shaping your shadow♪
♪All my pain comes
from not wanting to part♪
♪I was caught in the middle♪
♪It's hard to survive♪
♪Love faded in you, but grew in me♪
♪And wore me down inside♪
♪I'm the desert, craving the open sea♪
♪I'll show you the humor in tragedy♪
♪Will you ever remember me?♪
♪A divine once blessed us with love♪
♪But that blessing faded in a flash♪
♪The moon stays bright, never falling♪
♪But it's no longer mine♪
♪Longing finds a heartbeat as I fall♪
♪When our eyes meet, the world softens♪
♪I cling to the past like a wanderer♪
♪Still guarding the gate
to old memories♪
♪Eternal promise♪
♪How do I heal after losing you?♪
♪How could I let go of all this pain?♪
♪The more I hold back,
the closer you feel♪
♪The more it hurts,
the more I break♪
♪Every snowflake feels like your kiss♪
♪Let time pause,
let fireflies fill the sky♪
♪In your arms,
I lose focus—tears fall♪
♪And everything else just fades away♪
♪You belong only to me♪
♪Even if we're apart, or worlds away♪
♪None of that could ever matter♪