[LEE SUNG KYOUNG]
[LEE SEUNG GI]
[DAESUNG]
[STAYC YOON]
[HUI]
[CHOI YOUNGJUN]
[KWON EUNBI]
[HANHAE]
[ERIC]
[LIGHT NOW! RIGHT NOW!]
[Starlight Boys]
[New mission reveal
K-POP Generation Battle]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: It's a K-POP Generation Battle.
LUO JUN WEI："Chk Chk Boom"!
SUN YING HAO："Sheesh"!
HONG SUNG MIN："Sorry, Sorry"!
HUANG JIA LIANG：All the songs are amazing!
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：It's a battle between teams.
[10 teams and 5 rounds
A Team Battle mode]
LEE JUN HYUK：Actually, I'm not afraid of anyone.
We should get along even after the battle.
HAN TAE I：You don't look that strong.
[The atmosphere is getting hot
even before the actual performance has begun]
That's so cool.
[To make the [Polaris] member stand out more, the formations have to change]
[A new feature
The powerful privilege that only the Polaris has]
HIKARI：I want to (be the) Polaris.
[Polaris that everyone wants to be]
Polaris? Yeah.
Same here.
[On the other hand, another team that is fighting for the Polaris position]
Who are you to decide?
Because...
Who are you to decide that?
[Strong tensions surrounding the refusal
to give up the Polaris position]
[What's going on in other practice rooms?]
[Stumbling]
[LEE DA EUL can't keep up with the dance steps]
DA EUL is going to die.
[The atmosphere suddenly stiffens]
DA EUL is dying. Are you okay?
LEE DA EUL：Wait. What should I do?
LEE DA EUL：It's more...
[Trainee LEE DA EUL who is met with a crisis]
[K-POP Generation Battle
finally begins]
[Who is the winner of the K-POP Generation Battle?]
I really want to win.
Hello, Guardians from around the world!
[Starlight Boys]
I'm the Guardian Representative, LEE SUNG KYOUNG.
The boys’ shining journey towards a global debut has just begun.
Now, I will explain
how the global ‘Light up’ voting for “Starlight Boys” works.
While watching “Starlight Boys” on the iQIYI app,
you can access the voting page
by clicking the ‘Light up’ button or scanning the QR code,
where you will get to ‘Light up’ the boys who stand out the most to you.
Each time, you can ‘Light up’ up to 9 boys,
and each boy can only be chosen once.
Free users get 3 ‘Light up’ votes per day,
while Standard VIP members get 5 ‘Light up’ votes per day,
and Premium VIP members get 7 ‘Light up’ votes per day.
If you purchase the VIP Gift Card,
you can "Light Up" for an additional 25 times for each purchase.
The first round of global ‘Light up’ voting starts at 9 PM on October 26 (KST)
and ends at 12 PM on November 16 (KST).
The ‘Light’ you send will decide the final 9-member global idol group.
Start voting to ‘Light up’ your brightest Starlight Boys!
LIGHT NOW, RIGHT NOW!
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：iQIYI Global Idol Audition,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG："Starlight Boys."
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：We will be selecting the Polaris for the Signal Song "Good Luck"
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：starting from now.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The trainees who received All Star in the Signal Song Mission,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：who are now also the nine Polaris candidates,
[Through the Signal Song Mission,
the 9 final All Star trainees were selected]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：will perform the Signal Song here again.
[A new mission
for the Polaris position]
YOO GWAN WOO：I must get the Polaris position this time.
SHAO ZI HENG：I must stand in the position of the Polaris.
MIN JAE：I have to do my best.
MIN JAE：That's what a professional idol should do.
[The first performance of "Starlight Boys"]
[How does one become
the Polaris of the Signal Song "Good Luck"?]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The evaluation will start from the final chorus
[Mandatory lesson for idols:
Ending Pose]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：and end with the ending pose.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Through the evaluation of the ending performance,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：I, the Guardian Representative,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：and the Guiders will make our choice
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：of one trainee
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：to be the Polaris of the Signal Song.
[Signal Song Polaris]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Who will be the Signal Song's Polaris?
[Among the 9 All-Stars,
who will be the Polaris?]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The Polaris selection starts now.
♫Good Luck Good Luck♫
♫Want you to be on my side♫
[It's...]
♫Want you to have my back♫
[It's... coming]
♫Good Luck Good Luck♫
♫Want you to be my luck♫
-Good.
-Well done.
YOON: That's it.
[Cute]
[Oh my, look at him]
He's very relaxed.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：I think it's the best so far.
[YOUNGJUN's pick]
[(Wink)]
LEE SEUNG GI：I like him.
[SEUNG GI's Pick]
[My colleagues' fan service...]
[Is so interesting, hahaha]
[Awkward]
[Come on in,
it's your first time doing the ending fairy, right?]
DAESUNG：It's their first time doing the ending fairy, that's why.
I can't do it.
[Embarrassed] [Shy]
Why am I so embarrassed?
[It's not easy to be an ending fairy...]
[Who will be Polaris for the Signal Song?]
[The Guider meeting starts]
DAESUNG：Who do you think was good?
LEE SEUNG GI：We can’t just focus on the ending pose.
LEE SEUNG GI：But like who is the most powerful one at one glance.
DAESUNG：To see who can get attention?
When I think of it from an idol's perspective, I feel like it should be SHAO ZI HENG.
From the perspective of dancing skills, it's HONG SUNG MIN.
I think he's better than him.
But if it's him, the center will be too attention grabbing.
LEE JUN HYUK：If you went up, you'd be the Polaris.
LEE JUN HYUK：You.
YANG DONG HWA：If I went on there,
YANG DONG HWA：I would've ended it.
LEE JUN HYUK：Right.
[But I'll do it too ^^]
[(Glare)]
LEE JUN HYUK：Don't do it? Okay.
HAN GYUL：JUN HYUK, I'm going to get angry.
[JUN HYUK,
I will end you]
-LEE JUN HYUK：You said you'd get angry?
-HAN GYUL：Yes.
[JUN HYUK shall not be the ending fairy then]
LEE JUN HYUK：So scary.
HUANG JIA LIANG：Me too.
HE XI LONG: This move is too…
There is no trash can here.
[Smack]
[(Director, please take a look)]
[Permanent specimen]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The meeting to select the Polaris is over.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The Polaris chosen today
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：will represent the 56 boys
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：on the brightest spot on the Signal Song stage.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Who will be the Polaris?
[Who will shine the brightest among the 9?]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG："Starlight Boys"
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Signal Song "Good Luck's" Polaris...
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Please unveil it.
[It will be unveiled now!]
[The Signal Song Polaris
is trainee SHAO ZI HENG]
LEE SEUNG GI：SUNG MIN is good.
LEE SEUNG GI：But while he still has a lot to improve,
-LEE SEUNG GI：He's very fresh. To be honest, I think he's fresh.
-Yes.
LEE SEUNG GI：To be honest, when I saw him standing there,
LEE SEUNG GI：I thought he’s the center.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：Yes, that’s right.
LEE SEUNG GI：We can’t just focus on the ending pose.
LEE SEUNG GI：But who has the strongest aura.
SHAO ZI HENG: Thank you.
SHAO ZI HENG：I need to work harder.
SHAO ZI HENG：This is the beginning of my life.
[How will Polaris SHAO ZI HENG's
performance be?]
[Good Luck (Be my luck)
Starlight Boys]
♫I've never felt this way before♫
♫Even if I'm a bit clumsy♫
♫When you watch me♫
♫I yearn to become a different me♫
♫Since you stumbled into my life♫
♫Shine brighter and brighter (Starlight)♫
♫Oh, follow the ray of light♫
♫Like a gift that fell into your lap♫
♫Will you come along with me?♫
♫Right now, call out my name♫
♫Set my heart on fire♫
♫The long-awaited moment♫
♫Louder, call out louder♫
♫My final lucky puzzle piece♫
♫Is you♫
♫Good Luck Good Luck
Want you to call my name♫
Want you to be on my side♫
♫Good Luck Good Luck
Want you to have my back♫
Want you to be my luck♫
♫From afar, I believe♫
♫You can spot me♫
♫A bright and brilliant tomorrow awaits us♫
♫(Are you ready for this?)♫
♫Even if I may get lost sometimes♫
♫As long as we're hand in hand (Starlight)♫
♫Oh, I'll be braver than ever♫
♫With our throbbing hearts♫
♫Will you come along with me?♫
♫Right now, call out my name♫
♫Set my heart on fire♫
♫The long-awaited moment♫
♫Louder, call out louder♫
♫My final lucky puzzle piece♫
♫Is you♫
♫Would you be my luck♫
♫Our encounter♫
♫Isn't a coincidence; it's fate♫
♫Now, like a fleeting dream initiating our new page♫
♫Shine together with me♫
♫Good Luck♫
♫Charge forward without hesitation♫
♫Be my luck♫
♫Hold my hand tight♫
♫I won't let you go (won't let you go)♫
♫Be my luck♫
♫What I need the most now♫
♫Is you♫
♫Good Luck Good Luck
Want you to call my name♫
Want you to be on my side♫
♫Good Luck Good Luck
Want you to have my back♫
Want you to be my luck♫
[2024.09
The second day after the Signal Song Mission]
[Trainees gather in the lecture room one after another]
I'm suddenly nervous.
LEE JUN HYUK：Seems like we are going to pick our teams.
KIM SEON JAE：What's this?
DO HA：A sports meet?
KE MING KAI：What are we going to do?
MICHAEL WU：I'm scared.
[Startled]
[MC LEE SUNG KYOUNG's sudden entrance]
[Thankful]
Trainees：Hello!
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Hello, I'm the Guardian Representative, LEE SUNG KYOUNG.
[Nice to meet you, MC]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：It feels different to see you here.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Have you been doing well?
Trainees：Yes.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：You now have stickers on you.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：All Rounder, Dance, Rap, and Vocal.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：There are various kinds.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：How did you decide these positions?
MIN JAE：We just chose whatever we want.
-LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Did you choose it yourselves?
-Trainees: Yes.
[A few hours ago...]
-Hello
-Hello.
Hello.
DUAN XING XING：What is this?
HONG SUNG MIN：Vocal, Dance, All Rounder, Rap, Vocal, and Visual.
[The suspicious stickers placed in front of the trainees]
LEE JUN HYUK：Are they preparing for a battle?
[After careful consideration]
All.
SHAO ZI HENG：Because I want to do everything.
[All Rounder]
KAWK GUN：People say we have to aim high.
[All Rounder, let's go]
[Everyone chooses the position they want]
[Vocal]
YANG YAN：I want to show people I can perform.
YANG YAN：Not just because of my looks.
HAN GYUL：What is this?
[Visual]
ZHANG JING HE：Because I think I’m quite good looking.
XIN CHE：Of course it's this one.
[What does the position sticker actually mean?]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Right here,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：are the 56 trainees who have survived
[After the Signal Song Mission,
there are now 56 trainees who survived]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：the Signal Song Mission.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：With that, from now on,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：I will be announcing the Second Mission.
[Extremely nervous]
LUO JUN WEI：So nervous.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The theme of this mission is...
[Second Mission theme
K-POP Generation Battle]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：K-POP Generation Battle...
[(What is that?)]
Battle?
Generation battle?
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：This mission is
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：to present K-POP songs that have been
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：loved by the general public across various generations
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：as a perfect performance on the stage.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：And with this mission,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：the first Live Audience Voting will start.
[Starting with this mission
is the start of the first Live Audience Voting]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Through this mission,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：you will be split into 10 teams.
-Trainees: 10?
10?
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：It will be a team versus team battle.
[10 teams 5 rounds
Team Battle]
[Each team will be evaluated
and made up of trainees of various Levels]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The Levels will be mixed up, and all of you will be evaluated together.
[Team vs. Team
All members of the team that wins will receive a reward]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The team members of the team that receives more votes between the two
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：will receive individual votes as a benefit which is extremely important for survival.
[All members of the winning team will receive:
5,000 individual votes as a benefit]
PARK YEON WOOK：We must win then.
PARK YEON WOOK：We must win the team battle.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：So,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：the members and the choosing of the song for this performance
[Team member and song selection
are closely linked to this mission]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：will be very important, right?
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：So, starting from now,
[From now on]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：your Level will disappear.
[From now on, all Levels are removed!]
[Happy] [Sad] [Sad] [Happy]
[One Stars & Zero Stars
are almost all celebrating]
HAN TAE I：Okay, okay, okay.
KIM SEONG JU：We’re equal now.
ZHANG JI JUN：No more Zero Star.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Now,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：we will start with the team member selection.
[K-POP Generation Battle
team member selection starts]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：First, let's welcome Polaris trainee to the front.
[Pick me] [Pick me]
-Me.
Expression. I love you.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Right now, your center, the Polaris,
[Current Polaris SHAO ZI HENG]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：is SHAO ZI HENG.
[Polaris’s benefit]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The Polaris trainee
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：can choose their members first.
[Polaris’s benefit: to select their members first]
[Envious]
This benefit.
DUAN XING XING：This is awesome.
WANG KUN：That's awesome.
HAN TAE I：No, no. What if SHAO ZI HENG takes everyone away.
SHAO ZI HENG：I was in a good mood. Because I could choose first.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Okay, it's time to decide.
[Who will SHAO ZI HENG choose?]
SHAO ZI HENG：HONG SUNG MIN.
[SHAO ZI HENG team
HONG SUNG MIN]
SHAO ZI HENG：HAN GYUL.
[SHAO ZI HENG team
HONG SUNG MIN, HAN GYUL]
SHAO ZI HENG：ZAI.
[SHAO ZI HENG team
HONG SUNG MIN, HAN GYUL, ZAI]
SHAO ZI HENG：DONG HWA. DONG HWA.
[SHAO ZI HENG team
HONG SUNG MIN, HAN GYUL, ZAI, YANG DONG HWA]
HONG SUNG MIN, HAN GYUL, ZAI, YANG DONG HWA, LINGQI]
SHAO ZI HENG：LINGQI.
PARK YEON WOOK：He took all of them away.
SHENG QI：That's really invincible.
KAWK GUN：It’s the Avengers.
HUANG JIA LIANG：They're already really strong.
HUANG JIA LIANG：I don't want to fight against that. We can't win that.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Okay. The first team has been formed.
[Forming a 6-man team
SHAO ZI HENG team]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The next trainee to choose is...
KAWK GUN：YOO GWAN WOO.
[Isn't the second place YOO GWAN WOO?]
CHEN XUAN YOU：YOO GWAN WOO.
KE MING KAI：It should be YOO GWAN WOO.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Through drawing lots.
-Really?
-It will be chosen through that.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Through drawing lots.
-KAWK GUN: Really?
-Really?
LEE JUN HYUK：Drawing lots?
HUANG JIA LIANG：Drawing lots?
[The dream of building his own team disappeared right in front of his eyes]
WANG KUN：D-Drawing lots.
[(No way)]
KAWK GUN：Awesome!
SUN YING HAO：Really?
SUN YING HAO：I was stumped.
SUN YING HAO：I feel like I've never encountered such a rule.
YOO GWAN WOO：After SHAO ZI HENG chose, it wasn't my turn to choose my team members...
YOO GWAN WOO：It’s a pity.
DUAN XING XING：Why draw lots?
PENTOR：That's crazy.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：In this box
[Lot drawing box with the 56 trainees' names]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：is the name of the trainees.
KAWK GUN：She's going to draw the ball?
-YOSHI：Drawing lots.
-SYO：Drawing lots.
SUN JIA YANG：It's very good. I think it’s fair.
SUN JIA YANG：It's fair for everyone.
JUNG HAE SUNG：Really, please.
KIM SEON JAE：Please!
JUNG HAE SUNG：It's okay if I don't win anything,
[Betting with his life for the team member selection]
JUNG HAE SUNG：I just hope this will work out well.
LUO JUN WEI：I hope I can get the luck of being the leader.
[Tossing and turning]
MIN JAE：Please, MIN JAE. Please, MIN JAE.
PARK SI WOO：Please.
[With just a single ball, the crowd's attention is being captured]
It's me. It's me.
IVAN：Oh my god.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Trainee HAN JEONG WOO.
[The second person to choose their team members
HAN JEONG WOO]
KAWK GUN：This could happen?
[Passing first with the 9/55 probability]
HAN JEONG WOO!
JEONG WOO!
[Envious]
HAN JEONG WOO：I choose trainee CHOI JUN HO.
PARK YEON WOOK："Crazy Form's" fate continues.
HAN JEONG WOO：Trainee LEE DA EUL.
Trainee LEE DA EUL.
LEE DA EUL：I’m grateful, but at the same time, I was surprised.
LEE DA EUL：Why did he call me over?
CHOI YOUNGJUN：The last one to pass...
CHOI YOUNGJUN：LEE DA EUL!
[The last person to pass the Signal Song Mission, LEE DA EUL]
CHOI YOUNGJUN：Congratulations. You really improved a lot.
LEE DA EUL：Since you gave me this position, I’ll do my best.
LEE DA EUL：Thank you.
LEE DA EUL：I know my skills.
LEE DA EUL：I’m worried.
HONG SUNG MIN：I was surprised.
[HAN JEONG WOO team
CHOI JUN HO, LEE DA EUL]
HAN JEONG WOO：Trainee CHEN XUAN YOU.
[HAN JEONG WOO team
CHOI JUN HO, LEE DA EUL, CHEN XUAN YOU]
Bro!
HAN JEONG WOO：I choose trainee LEE JUN HYUK.
[HAN JEONG WOO team
CHOI JUN HO, LEE DA EUL, CHEN XUAN YOU,LEE JUN HYUK]
CHOI JUN HO, LEE DA EUL, CHEN XUAN YOU,LEE JUN HYUK, MIN JAE]
I choose trainee MIN JAE.
Trainee MIN JAE joins too.
-Yo, what's up?
HAN TAE I：The All Stars are almost all gone.
[After the formation of just two teams,
most of All Stars and Two Stars are gone]
[9 -> 5] [16 -> 11]
ZHANG JI JUN：Who is the next lucky boy?
[Me]
LUO JUN WEI：Good luck come to me.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：It's trainee BIAN SHI YU.
[The third trainee to pick his team
BIAN SHI YU]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：It's trainee BIAN SHI YU.
ZHANG JI JUN：BIAN SHI YU.
[Confused]
[Congratulations, friend]
ZHANG JI JUN：BIAN SHI YU. BIAN SHI YU.
[The first person to choose their members from Zero Star Level]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Please come forward.
ZHANG JI JUN：BIAN SHI YU. BIAN SHI YU.
PENTOR：Amazing.
-Is he going to pick them up?
-LEE SUNG KYOUNG：What's going on?
WANG KUN：He's coming.
DUAN XING XING：He's coming.
PENTOR：He's coming.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Trainee YOO GWAN WOO.
[BIAN SHI YU team
CONGB, YOO GWAN WOO]
CONGB, YOO GWAN WOO, DUAN XING XING]
DUAN XING XING. DUAN XING XING is mine.
Trainees: JIA LIANG.
[BIAN SHI YU team
CONGB, YOO GWAN WOO, DUAN XING XING, HUANG JIA LIANG]
KAWK GUN：The three members of Team Answer got together again.
PARK SI WOO：They got together like a family.
YANG YAN：I really think
YANG YAN：we'll be the last ones they pick.
-ZHANG JI JUN：In the end,
-Yes.
ZHANG JI JUN：although the Zero Star class was canceled, its members
-ZHANG JI JUN：will still be on the same team.
-KE MING KAI：will still be on the same team.
ZHANG JI JUN：Because no one will pick us.
YANG YAN：Five Zero Stars on the same team?
KE MING KAI：There's still a level system in our hearts.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：It's SYO.
[4th trainee to decide their team members, SYO]
[1st member of SYO's team, KAWK GUN]
[Wait and see]
Okay.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The battle has begun.
[Ridiculous]
[Bold and confident]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Looks like they'll be an aggressive team.
[Aggressive] [SYO forms a team of six]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Next one.
[5th trainee to decide their team members, CAI CHENG YUAN]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：It's CAI CHENG YUAN.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Okay. Congratulations.
[CAI CHENG YUAN forms a team of six]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Team 5, please come on stage.
[6th trainee to decide their team members, HIJIRI]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：It's HIJIRI.
Oh my God!
Oh my Holy God!
HIJIRI：GUN WOO.
[HIJIRI forms a team of six]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：HE XI LONG.
[7th trainee to decide their team members, HE XI LONG]
HE XI LONG.
YOO JUN：XI LONG. XI LONG.
PARK SI WOO：Oh, thank you.
[HE XI LONG forms a team of five]
PARK SI WOO：Nice!
[8th trainee to decide their team members, IVAN]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：IVAN.
Let's go!
[IVAN forms a team of five]
KE MING KAI：IVAN!
HAN TAE I：What should we do?
HAN TAE I：We'll be left for last.
HAN TAE I：In a sense,
HAN TAE I：we rated each other at the default levels.
HAN TAE I：This has made things harder.
[Gradually, there are only Zero Stars left]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Okay. Have you made up your mind?
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：It's PARK YEON WOOK.
[9th trainee to decide their team members, PARK YEON WOOK]
PARK YEON WOOK：The last member we're going to choose is...
[All the trainees left are Zero Stars]
PARK YEON WOOK：KIM SEONG JU.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Okay, KIM SEONG JU is your last member.
JAE MIN：Are you okay?
PONG：Guys, it's okay. It's okay.
PONG：We have four dancers.
HAN TAE I：I got frustrated in the end. I didn't know what to do.
[K-POP Generation Teams]
[Starlight Boys]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Behind the curtain,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：there are 10 songs waiting for you.
[There are 10 songs hidden on the noticeboard]
SHAO ZI HENG：10 songs?
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The 2nd Mission
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：is going to decide your fates.
MIN JAE：Let us see them now, please.
HUANG JIA LIANG：I'm so nervous.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Now, I'm going to reveal...
MIN JAE：Open the curtain.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：the 10 songs for you to perform.
[Chaotic]
[K-POP Generation Battle]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Released
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：from 2000 to 2024,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：they are the songs
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：loved by K-POP fans across generations.
HUANG JIA LIANG："Boom Boom Bass." "Sheesh."
HUANG JIA LIANG："How You Like That."
SUN YING HAO："How You Like That"!
[Wow, there's actually that song!]
LUO JUN WEI：There's "Chk Chk Boom."
SUN YING HAO："Sheesh"!
KAWK GUN："Sheesh"! "Sheesh"!
HONG SUNG MIN："Sorry Sorry"!
HONG SUNG MIN："ATEEZ"! "ATEEZ"!
HUANG JIA LIANG：Wait. Every song is great!
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Is there any song you want?
HAN GYUL：It's hard to decide.
HUANG JIA LIANG：I want them all. I want them all.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：To pick the song you want, you need to do group sit-ups.
[Within 90 seconds]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：All members do sit-ups arm-in-arm within 90 seconds.
[Four people do sit-ups arm-in-arm]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The team that does the most sit-ups
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：gets first pick.
[To get the chance to choose their song]
XU SHI HUAN：Come on. Come on.
[Very confident]
GUN WOO：100 sit-ups. Let's go.
[Let's do 100 sit-ups]
-HE XI LONG：Let's do 101 sit-ups.
-YOSHI：Okay.
[Everyone's enthusiastic]
-HE XI LONG：Produce 101.
-YOSHI：Let's do 200.
HAN GYUL：We can definitely win this competition.
PENTOR：This is the sport we are most confident in.
PENTOR：We can definitely do more than 70 sit-ups.
HONG SUNG MIN：I'm confident
HONG SUNG MIN：that I'm the worst at it.
HONG SUNG MIN：I can do no more than 10 sit-ups.
LEE DA EUL：Who's going to do it?
HONG SUNG MIN：I don't think I can.
HONG SUNG MIN：I'm too bad at it.
HAN GYUL：Let us show you our skill.
HAN GYUL：We'll show you our skill.
LEE DA EUL：Let's cheer for them.
HONG SUNG MIN：I'm the worst here.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Let's start the battle.
[SYO's team goes first]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Please come forward.
YANG YAN：Fighting!
YOO JUN：SYO. YANG YAN.
YOO JUN：Watch carefully.
YOO JUN：Sorry.
[It's too cheesy for me]
YOO JUN：I'll do my best.
YOO JUN：I love you.
YANG YAN：I love you.
[It's true they just formed a team]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Ready...
[How well will SYO's team do with the power of love(?)]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Go.
[START]
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven.
[Bravo! Bravo!]
Eight, nine.
MICHAEL WU：Keep going.
10, 11.
[Let's go!]
MICHAEL WU：Let's go!
MICHAEL WU：12. Let's go!
MICHAEL WU：13. Let's go!
[What is that?]
Let's go.
MICHAEL WU：16. Let's go!
MICHAEL WU：Keep going! 17. Let's go!
[He keeps shouting "Let's go" till the end]
MICHAEL WU：18. Let's go!
MICHAEL WU：Let's go!
[Under MICHAEL WU's command, even his finger is pointing up]
Let's go!
[Everyone starts to shout "Let's go"]
MICHAEL WU：Let's go!
KAWK GUN：My bones hurt. Don't press my bones.
KAWK GUN：YOO JUN kept poking me in the ribs with his elbow.
KAWK GUN：But I endured it. Why?
KAWK GUN：Because I had to get the song I wanted.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Time's up. Thank you.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：You did 48 sit-ups.
YANG YAN：I love you!
SUN YING HAO：Come on! Come on!
[Next is BIAN SHI YU's team]
SUN YING HAO：I'm taller.
SUN YING HAO：I'm taller here. It's different.
[No one asks him, but he explains with a guilty look]
LEE DA EUL：Okay.
HUANG JIA LIANG：I have nothing to say.
HUANG JIA LIANG：Let's just get started.
[Roaring]
DUAN XING XING：Let's win!
[Come on, my teammates!]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Get ready.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Go.
[START]
One, two, three, four.
Four, five, six.
[Being charming in a calm manner]
[I can't believe he can do this. Haha]
DUAN XING XING：I'm still the 20-year-old me.
[DUAN XING XING, the oldest one, 27 years old]
DUAN XING XING：I'm still so...
SUN YING HAO：Fighting! Fighting!
59, 60, 61.
[He alone is very calm]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Time's up. Thank you.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：You did 62 sit-ups.
[They're the current No. 1 after doing 62 sit-ups]
-SUN YING HAO：Well done!
-YOO GWAN WOO：Bravo!
[Our team is the best]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The four members of the third team, please come forward.
[The third team is IVAN's team]
[More nervous than the participants]
SUN JIA YANG：Oh my God!
SUN JIA YANG：Well, I can do it.
[Break before doing sit-ups]
SUN JIA YANG：I can do 20 to 30 sit-ups. It's not bad.
SUN JIA YANG：I'm not that bad at it.
KINGSTON WONG：You can do only 20 to 30 sit-ups in one minute and a half?
[Embarrassed]
[IVAN's team]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Five, four, three.
SUN JIA YANG：Come on! Come on!
[IVAN's team] [Come on! Come on!]
[IVAN's team]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Two, one. Time's up.
[IVAN's team] [56 sit-ups]
JUNG HAE SUNG：We must do it!
[PARK YEON WOOK's Team]
JUNG HAE SUNG：Go! How many have we done?
[PARK YEON WOOK's team] [54 sit-ups]
I don't know. Let's keep going.
[HAN JEONG WOO's team]
LEE JUN HYUK：Well, we'll just do 70 sit-ups,
LEE JUN HYUK：although I'm not sure if it'll be easy.
Eight, nine.
[HAN JEONG WOO's team] [What will be their result?]
[HAN JEONG WOO's team]
HAN JEONG WOO：Why isn't this over?
[HAN JEONG WOO's team] [Why isn't this over?]
[HAN JEONG WOO's team]
MIN JAE：The song! We must get the song we want!]
[HAN JEONG WOO's team] [We must get the song we want!]
[HAN JEONG WOO's team]
MIN JAE：We must get the song we want! Keep going!
MIN JAE：Keep going! We must get the song we want!
[HAN JEONG WOO's team] [They complete 57 sit-ups energetically]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Time's up.
[HIJIRI's team]
GUN WOO：Let's just do it like we're working out.
One, two, three.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Five, four, three, two, one. Time's up.
[HIJIRI's team] [45 sit-ups]
[HIJIRI's team]
[CAI CHENG YUAN's team currently ranks 8th with 41 sit-ups]
[HE XI LONG's team currently ranks 3rd with 60 sit-ups]
YOSHI：Fighting!
[Current Rankings]
[Next is SHAO ZI HENG's team]
SHAO ZI HENG：Because we are a team of men, we will win.
[Team of men]
[We will win!]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Okay, team of men.
KAWK GUN：I think this team will do very well.
LINGQI：We will win because we have HAN GYUL.
[Because we have HAN GYUL]
HAN GYUL：Because I'm good at doing sit-ups.
HAN GYUL：One must have a sporting talent.
[One must have a sporting talent]
SHAO ZI HENG：We can do 100. We can do it.
HONG SUNG MIN：Polaris, come on.
LINGQI：Fighting!
HONG SUNG MIN：Fighting!
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Go.
One, two, three.
Fighting!
-LINGQIi：Fighting! Fighting!
-HONG SUNG MIN：Fighting!
LINGQI：Fighting! Fighting!
SHAO ZI HENG：Let's stop holding each other's arms.
[He pulls his arm back]
HONG SUNG MIN：He can't do this.
HONG SUNG MIN：Didn't they say they were good at it?
YANG DONG HWA：You have to put your arm through mine.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：No, you have to get up at the same time.
[Doing it alone]
Let's go.
It's not like this.
[He keeps trying to pull back his arm]
Let's go.
[Happy] [Sad]
HONG SUNG MIN：Oh no.
[Oh no]
-LINGQI：Oh no.
-HONG SUNG MIN：Oh no.
LINGQI：Something bad happened.
LINGQI：I regret it.
LINGQI：I should have joined the competition.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Three, two, one.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Time's up. Thank you.
[Time's up for SHAO ZI HENG's team]
SHAO ZI HENG：Well, I couldn't get up
SHAO ZI HENG：with his arm through mine.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：You did 35 sit-ups.
[3]
[35]
CONGB：35.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：You did 35 sit-ups.
[They rank last with 35 sit-ups]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The last team.
MIN JAE：I think PONG is good at it.
[The last team is PHOOM's team]
HAN JEONG WOO：I think this team is quite strong, too.
LEE JUN HYUK：Seems so.
MIN JAE：TAE I, you can become a hero by doing this.
HAN TAE I：I was an athlete for seven to eight years.
[Former professional rugby player]
HAN TAE I：Doing sit-ups was the most common thing for me.
HAN TAE I：So, I must win.
[Getting competitive]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Start.
[START]
One, two, three, four.
Five, six.
XU SHI HUAN：They're doing one every second.
Seven, eight.
SHENG QI：Amazing.
[We're No. 1. Don't overtake us]
HAN TAE I：If we lost,
HAN TAE I：I'd be hopeless.
HAN TAE I：I was like a lion that had been starving for three years
[Look of a beast]
HAN TAE I：and barely survived.
HAN TAE I：I found my prey and rushed towards it.
[Going all out]
-KAWK GUN：What's going on? They're amazing.
-What's going on?
-LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Only five seconds to go. Five, four,
-HAN TAE I：Come on! Come on!
[Final sprint]
three, two, one. Time's up.
I'm impressed.
[Wow, I have to say they did a good job]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：They did 66 sit-ups.
[PHOOM's team complete 66 sit-ups]
HAN TAE I：We survived.
HAN TAE I：I think we can choose a song that suits our team's style.
[Final Rankings]
[Envious]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The No. 1 team, please pick your song first.
[K-POP Generation Battle] [Which song will they choose?]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Before choosing,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：have a meeting to discuss which song to perform.
[Current No. 7, SYO's team]
MICHAEL WU："Sheesh" is more popular.
YOO JUN：Is "Sheesh" our No. 1 choice?
[SYO's team]
SYO："Sheesh" is our first pick.
"Sheesh."
[Is SYO's team going to pick "Sheesh"?]
-YANG YAN：I'm okay. PENTAGON.
-YOO JUN：PENTAGON.
YOO JUN：But I think...
[SYO's team]
YOO JUN：Being cheerful and energetic
YOO JUN：are our strong points. If we choose "Shine,"
YOO JUN：I can picture us performing it.
[Current No. 3, HE XI LONG's team]
PARK SI WOO：Of "Sheesh"
PARK SI WOO：and "How You Like That,"
PARK SI WOO：I prefer the latter.
[HE XI LONG's team]
YOSHI：If we choose "How You Like That,"
YOSHI：we'll definitely win.
PARK SI WOO：We need to choose a famous song to get more votes.
HE XI LONG：The atmosphere when we perform is more important.
PARK SI WOO：Anyway, this is a performance.
PARK SI WOO：The audience will watch it and decide whether we'll be eliminated.
PARK SI WOO：I want to choose a famous K-POP group's song.
JUNG HAE SUNG：But we need to play it safe.
[Current No. 6, PARK YEON WOOK's team]
PARK YEON WOOK：I think the overall effect is more important.
[PARK YEON WOOK's team]
KIM SEONG JU：Let's choose one that matches our image.
JUNG HAE SUNG：But I think
JUNG HAE SUNG：if we perform badly, it'll be meaningless.
[If we perform badly, it'll be meaningless]
That's right.
[Current No. 5, IVAN's team]
ZHANG JI JUN：The happy style doesn't suit us.
IVAN：It's not happy. It's cool.
XU SHI HUAN：Is it famous?
[Current No. 9, CAI CHENG YUAN's team]
EDEN：It's very famous in South Korea.
-LUO JUN WEI：BTS's song is too hard. We can't do it.
-SHENG QI：Yes.
GUN WOO：Let's choose one from "BUTTER," "Again & Again,"
[Current No. 8, HIJIRI's team]
GUN WOO：and "Glitch Mode."
[The meetings are over]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Have you finished your meetings?
Yes.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：So, the No. 1 team.
[Which song will PHOOM's team choose?]
HAN TAE I：Because we are the last team formed,
HAN TAE I：we focus on the song that suits us best.
HAN TAE I：We want a song that can create a good atmosphere.
LEE DA EUL：I think it's "Boom Boom Bass."
-HONG SUNG MIN：Is it "Shine"?
-LEE DA EUL：It could be "Shine."
YOO JUN："Sorry Sorry"?
PHOOM：We decided to choose
PHOOM："Sorry Sorry".
[PHOOM's team chose "Sorry Sorry"]
[They didn't choose our song, great]
LINGQI：The song I wanted to sing the most is gone.
[It got chosen immediately]
YANG DONG HWA：It got chosen immediately.
[At the song selection meeting not long ago]
YANG DONG HWA："Sorry Sorry" is like a national rule.
YANG DONG HWA：So we must sing "Sorry Sorry".
YANG DONG HWA：Besides, our team is the only one that can deliver "Sorry Sorry".
YANG DONG HWA：Actually, although "Sorry Sorry"
YANG DONG HWA：was our first choice...
YANG DONG HWA：It really was our first choice.
YANG DONG HWA：It indeed was.
LINGQI：Ah, that was really...
[LINGQI has turned to the dark side]
LINGQI：I have a headache.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG："Sorry Sorry" is sold out.
["Sorry Sorry" sold out]
LUO JUN WEI：This song is very popular.
XU SHI HUAN：It suits their team pretty well, I think.
SHAO ZI HENG：Please put it here.
SHAO ZI HENG：Here. Here.
[Still obsessed]
PHOOM：I'm confident, because...
PHOOM：Because I'll try my best.
[Next, it's the turn of the second-place team, BIAN SHI YU's team, to choose]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：BIAN SHI YU's team.
BIAN SHI YU：The result of our discussion is...
[Don't choose our team's song...]
YOSHI：I really want to choose BLACKPINK's song.
BIAN SHI YU："Boom Boom Bass".
[BIAN SHI YU's team chose "Boom Boom Bass"]
[Ah... No...]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG："Boom Boom Bass" by RIIZE is sold out.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The next is HE XI LONG's team.
[Which song will the third-place team, HE XI LONG's team, choose?]
HE XI LONG：The song our team want to choose this time is...
[They chose "How You Like That" by BLACKPINK]
HE XI LONG："How You Like That".
[I love this song so much~]
PARK SI WOO：♫How you like that♫
PARK SI WOO：Actually, choosing girl groups' songs is either the best or the worst.
PARK SI WOO：If we do it well, I think we can create a wonderful stage performance.
PARK SI WOO：That's why we chose this song.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The fourth is HAN JEONG WOO's team.
[HAN JEONG WOO's team chose "Guerilla"]
HAN JEONG WOO：We choose "Guerilla".
-MIN JAE：Make a move!
-LEE JUN HYUK：Guerilla!
HAN JEONG WOO：We choose "Guerilla".
YANG YAN：I think one of the songs that I was scared of
YANG YAN：is "Guerilla". ATEEZ's "Guerilla".
YANG YAN：Because there's a lot of dancing.
YANG YAN：No, no, no.
YANG YAN：I don't like it. No, no, no.
[We can win. We're not scared of anyone.]
LEE JUN HYUK：We can win. We're not scared of anyone.
[At the song selection meeting just now]
HAN JEONG WOO：No.1 "Guerilla", No.2 "Chk Chk Boom".
MIN JAE：DA EUL, tell us which song you'd like to sing.
LEE DA EUL：I'll listen to you.
LEE DA EUL：What I wanted to sing is "Shine".
LEE DA EUL：(As for "Guerilla",) I'm worried if we can deliver it.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Now, it's the fifth team's turn.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：IVAN's team.
[IVAN's team chose "Sheesh"]
IVAN："Sheesh".
[PARK YEON WOOK's team chose "Shine"]
PARK YEON WOOK：We choose "Shine" by PENTAGON.
[Getting nervous because there are fewer and fewer songs left]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：It's SYO's team's turn.
[SYO's team chose "Chk Chk Boom"]
SYO："Chk Chk Boom" by Stray Kids.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：There are three songs left.
[Three songs left]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Okay, now it's HIJIRI's team's turn.
[Which song will the eighth team, HIJIRI's team, choose?]
HIJIRI："Glitch Mode" by NCT DREAM.
[NCT DREAM]
["Glitch Mode" by NCT DREAM]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Now there are two songs and two teams left.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：CAI CHENG YUAN.
[Now it's the ninth team, CAI CHENG YUAN's team's turn to choose.]
CAI CHENG YUAN：This song is... It's really hard.
HAN GYUL：Some people think we should avoid the happy songs.
HAN GYUL：I hope "Again ＆ Again" will be left until the end.
CAI CHENG YUAN：It's really hard.
CAI CHENG YUAN："BUTTER" by BTS.
[Nice!]
HAN GYUL：That's a relief.
XU SHI HUAN：I think our team suits this song well.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：So, which song will the last team,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：SHAO ZI HENG's team, choose? I’m so curious.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Is the song you wanted to choose in the first place still there?
-SHAO ZI HENG：Yes, it is.
-LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Oh, it's still here?
[Thick-skinned]
SHAO ZI HENG：We were quite worried, because we really wanted to sing this song.
[Great! ZI HENG!]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：So the song SHAO ZI HENG wants to sing is...
SHAO ZI HENG："Again ＆ Again" by 2PM.
[2PM's "Again ＆ Again"]
-Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
-HONG SUNG MIN："Again ＆ Again"!
-HAN GYUL：Let's go!
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Now, everyone,
-LEE SUNG KYOUNG：it's time to decide which team you'll battle against.
-The battle list.
[K-POP Generation Battle Matchup]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：You'll need to decide your opponent.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：You'll pick the team you'll battle against
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：in order of team ranking.
[PHOOM's team is the first]
MIN JAE：TAE I, what do you think?
[Recommending(?) Let him choose]
MIN JAE：TAE I.
HAN TAE I：The reason why we chose this song
HAN TAE I：was to show the rebellion of the weakest team.
HAN TAE I：We want to show you.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The name of your opponent's song is?
WANG KUN：Pick us.
LUO JUN WEI：I think the best result is for us to battle against their team.
[What will PHOOM's team, Team "Sorry Sorry", choose?]
HAN TAE I："Again ＆ Again" by 2PM.
[PHOOM's team, Team "Sorry Sorry", chose SHAO ZI HENG's team, Team "Again & Again"]
[Chaos]
KRIS：My god!
[Everyone's in chaos]
[You're a real man!!!]
LEE JUN HYUK：You're a real man! You're a real man!
[I'm a man]
PENTOR：Unbelievable.
EDEN：Wow, so cool.
[RESPECT]
[The weakest team, the real rebellion]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Wow, they chose Polaris's team.
HAN TAE I：Since they were the first one to be called,
HAN TAE I：you may think they are strong.
HAN TAE I：But it seems to us they're not that strong.
[Feels good watching others fight]
HAN TAE I：We will try our best to defeat them.
SHAO ZI HENG：Fighting.
BIAN SHI YU：The team we're going to challenge is...
[BIAN SHI YU's team, Team "Boom Boom Bass"]
[BIAN SHI YU's team, Team "Boom Boom Bass" chose IVAN's team, Team "Sheesh"]
BIAN SHI YU："Sheesh".
LEE SUNG KYOUNG："Sheesh".
LEE SUNG KYOUNG："Sheesh", so it's IVAN's team, right?
[Then challenge accepted...]
[What a relief]
IVAN：I hope we can defeat you.
DUAN XING XING：Oh, no. We're sending you home.
DUAN XING XING：So I feel a bit sorry for them.
[What will HE XI LONG's team, Team "How You Like That", choose?]
PARK SI WOO：The team we choose is
PARK SI WOO：the weakest team
PARK SI WOO：among all the teams here.
[The weakest team]
PARK SI WOO：The weakest team among all the teams here.
HE XI LONG：YEON WOOK's Team "Shine".
[The weakest team(?) They chose PARK YEON WOOK's team, Team "Shine"]
[HAN JEONG WOO's team, Team "Guerrilla" chose SYO's team, Team "Chk Chk Boom"]
HAN JEONG WOO：We choose Team "Chk Chk Boom".
[come on~ come on~]
LEE JUN HYUK：Come on. Come on.
YOO JUN：Thank you for choosing us.
YOO JUN：We will face it calmly.
[The two teams left automatically become opponents]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Are you satisfied with your opponent?
[Yes!!!]
KIM SEON JAE：Yes!
KIM SEON JAE：Actually, I don't really know what kind of people my opponents are.
KIM SEON JAE：But I believe I don't know that
KIM SEON JAE：for a reason, right?
[There must be a reason, right?]
[Interesting for no reason]
SHENG QI：Things got heated. So I think
SHENG QI：if you don't know our names now,
SHENG QI：you'll remember them well this time.
[Teams and songs have been chosen! Which team is the first to start preparing for the mission?]
LEE JUN HYUK：Bye-bye.
[Yesterday's teammates are today's enemies!]
-HAN JEONG WOO： Hello
-MIN JAE：Yahoo.
[Guerilla!]
Guerilla!
-ATEEZ's "Guerilla"!
-Let's go!
[Full of confidence Team "Guerilla"]
[Full of confidence Team "Guerilla" vs Full of confidence too Team "Chk Chk Boom"]
BOOM! BOOM! BOOM!
[BOOM!]
[BOOM! BOOM!]
[As they enter the room]
[Mental battle] [Furnace]
[calm down! x2]
CHEN XUAN YOU：Calm down. Calm down.
[At that moment]
["BUTTER" vs "Glitch Mode" Practice Room]
XIN CHE：We meet again.
[Naughty]
LUO JUN WEI：Here you are, XIN CHE.
[Be the Polaris]
XIN CHE：What is this?
XU SHI HUAN：You can't just tear this off.
XIN CHE：What are you doing?
♫Sheesh Sheesh♫
["Boom Boom Bass" vs "Sheesh" Practice Room]
Hello, "Sheesh".
-Hello.
[Provoking]
[(Guys, watch carefully)]
[SUN YING HAO：You're on the wrong team~]
ZHANG JI JUN：Alright, alright.
-SUN JIA YANG：Come on. Come on.
-ZHANG JI JUN：Come on. Come on.
[Come on~]
SUN YING HAO：Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
[Team "Sheesh" kidnapped SUN YING HAO from Team "Boom Boom Bass"]
SUN YING HAO：Bye.
[(Held hostage by Team "Sheesh")]
[After the exchange (?) of members!]
[Entering practice mode!!!]
["Guerilla" vs "Chk Chk Boom" Practice Room]
[Practice Room Dividing Line]
HAN JEONG WOO：This is an amazing song by ATEEZ.
HAN JEONG WOO：We have no reason to fail,
[Because we are all strong!]
HAN JEONG WOO：because we are all strong.
[Of course! We're all well-prepared.]
LEE JUN HYUK：We're all well-prepared.
[Right~ Are you ready, DA EUL?]
HAN JEONG WOO：Are you ready, DA EUL?
LEE DA EUL：Yes.
CHEN XUAN YOU：I think we will win.
[Of course!]
[Why so noisy?!]
CHEN XUAN YOU：Because all their talk cost more energy,
[Noisy]
[Noisy] [Noisy]
CHEN XUAN YOU：but we have more energy for our song.
[I'm so hungry!!!]
SYO：I'm hungry!
[Chatty Team "Chk Chk Boom"]
-I'm so hungry.
[TMT]
Me too. Me too.
[I'm so hungry (weeping)]
MICHAEL WU：I'm so hungry.
[In contrast, Team "Guerilla" is focusing on the song(?)]
HAN JEONG WOO：I think this song
HAN JEONG WOO：should be full of power.
[Power]
MIN JAE：Also, the content of song. I feel like we're the army that won this war.
MIN JAE：That's why we need to be charismatic.
[Be charismatic like soldiers!]
HAN JEONG WOO：Soldiers.
[Like soldiers, okay?]
HAN JEONG WOO：Like soldiers. Yeah.
[That's my specialty^^]
[I'm going to crush them all^^]
MIN JAE：There's a dance move like throwing a grenade.
HAN JEONG WOO：They're really soldiers.
[Fire in the hole]
[A grenade for you!]
CHEN XUAN YOU：Chk Chk Boom.
[(Staring!)]
[(Clenching his teeth)]
[One hour ago, when they were choosing their opponent]
MIN JAE：Actually, until last week,
MIN JAE：I wore the same clothes as YOO JUN and performed on the same stage.
MIN JAE：But why are the colors of our clothes different now?
[(One Star) (All Star)]
[I'll prove it on the stage]
MIN JAE：I'll prove it on the stage.
[Wait and see]
YOSHI：He's so imposing. So imposing.
[The climax of the mental battle]
YOO JUN：The probability of us defeating Team "Guerilla" is
YOO JUN：30% now.
[It'll rise by 1% every day!]
YOO JUN：But it will rise by 1% every day.
YOO JUN：The team that looks like it'll lose always wins (in the end).
[The team that looks like it'll lose always wins in the end. It's a national rule!]
[I'm confident. We'll definitely win!]
HIKARI：I'm confident (that we'll win).
LEE JUN HYUK：There's nothing to be afraid of.
[Bring it on]
LEE JUN HYUK：We will win.
[In this tense battle, who will be the final winner?]
["BUTTER" vs "Glitch Mode" Practice Room]
SHENG QI：I think the most important thing now is
SHENG QI：to choose the part each of us fits best.
LUO JUN WEI+XU SHI HUAN+EDEN：Yes. Right.
CAI CHENG YUAN：I'll go first then.
XU SHI HUAN：No, let EDEN go first. In order of age.
[EDEN is the eldest]
-You go first, big brother.
-EDEN.
CAI CHENG YUAN：The eldest goes first.
[Very respectful of elders]
PENTOR：You go first, eldest brother.
Okay.
-XU SHI HUAN: 1998?
-1998.
[Born in 1998]
XU SHI HUAN：We were born in 1998, 1999, and 2000 respectively. And you?
[(Born in 1998) (Born in 1999)]
[(Born in 1998) (Born in 1999) (Born in 2000)]
[(Born in 2001)]
CAI CHENG YUAN：I was born in 2001.
SHENG QI：2001. Come here.
[The youngest should sit at the far end!]
[This is an oriental country of etiquette, seats are arranged according to age]
EDEN：There's a year age difference between each of us.
CAI CHENG YUAN：What's our slogan again?
[(Born in 2002) (Born in 2003) The youngest one sits at the far end^^]
XU SHI HUAN：The age difference between each of us is only one year, right?
SHENG QI, CAI CHENG YUAN, LUO JUN WEI：Yes.
[1998 1999 2000 2001 2002 2003]
1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002, 2003.
[Hehe><I'm the youngest]
SHENG QI：I'm the youngest.
PENTOR：Perfect.
EDEN：Exactly.
CAI CHENG YUAN：I feel very happy.
CAI CHENG YUAN：When I'm with my teammates,
CAI CHENG YUAN：I feel happy every moment.
PENTOR：It feels like flowers blooming.
PENTOR：With my lovely friends, our performance will definitely be great.
XU SHI HUAN：We are destined to be teammates.
-SHENG QI：Exactly. You're right.
-CAI CHENG YUAN：Indeed.
It's not a coincidence. It's destiny.
[The atmosphere is harmonious]
[What about Team "Glitch Mode" on the other side?]
Oh my god. Okay.
WANG KUN：From Vocal to Vocal 5.
[Start dividing the parts!]
WANG KUN：That is to say, among all of us...
WANG KUN：Polaris is the best among the six of us.
WANG KUN：The best one will be Polaris.
WANG KUN：Main Vocal should sing more
WANG KUN：than other Vocals.
[Main Vocal's part] [Not only does the Main Vocal have to sing his part well,]
[but also the freestyle part]
KIM SEON JAE：Who wants to be Polaris?
[Hands up]
GUN WOO：Oh, HIJIRI.
KIM SEON JAE：Who wants to be Polaris?
HIJIRI：I want one more part.
HIJIRI：Can't a person be Main Vocal and Polaris at the same time?
GUN WOO：Can you deliver all those parts well?
[Can you deliver all those parts well?]
HIJIRI：Yes. I can.
[Took up 43%. Among 127 seconds of the song, HIJIRI wants 55 seconds]
GUN WOO：To be honest, I'm quite worried.
GUN WOO：HIJIRI's basic skills aren't good enough, right?
[Will Team "Glitch Mode" be able to divide the parts well?]
["Shine" vs "How You Like That" Practice Room]
PARK SI WOO：Hello. Hello.
[Team "How You Like That" looking bright]
YOSHI：Hello.
PARK SI WOO：Thank you for choosing me.
YOSHI+PARK SI WOO：Thank you.
[Vocal+Dance=Perfect]
[Exchange of gratitude]
PARK SI WOO：Thank you for choosing me.
[Question: Are there no communication barriers?]
PARK SI WOO：Not at all.
PARK SI WOO：HE XI LONG also speaks some Korean.
[Speaks Korean]
PARK SI WOO：YOSHI speaks Chinese, Japanese and Korean.
[Japanese, Chinese, Korean, he speaks three languages]
[So reliable]
PARK SI WOO：Let's practice hard starting tomorrow.
[Since SI WOO speaks Korean]
[YOSHI and I will start practicing the dance part first... (Translating)]
PARK SI WOO：YOSHI and I will start practicing the dance part first.
PARK SI WOO：He'll be in charge of Visual.
HE XI LONG：Slow down. I can't understand.
[Changing translator]
HE XI LONG：You translate.
YOSHI：My Chinese is too...
[(LOL) Changing translator]
HE XI LONG：I think it's okay. It's pretty good.
YOSHI：I'm worried you won't understand.
KE MING KAI：It's okay.
YOSHI：Well...
KE MING KAI：We've never communicated with each other before, so maybe
KE MING KAI：I felt like they recognized me.
PARK SI WOO：Let's practice hard starting tomorrow.
PARK SI WOO：Understand?
PARK SI WOO：We must win.
PARK SI WOO：Fighting!
-Fighting!
Three, two, one. Fighting!
[Fighting!!!]
[What about Team "Shine" on the other side?]
PARK YEON WOOK：What should we do?
JUNG HAE SUNG：I didn't expect the pitch to be so high.
[Started to blame the original composer of "Shine", the Guider, HUI]
PARK YEON WOOK：HUI set the pitch so high.
[What does that mean...?]
JUNG HAE SUNG：Is this right?
JUNG HAE SUNG：♫Listen to my♫
JUNG HAE SUNG：♫Listen to my heart♫
[Glassy-eyed]
JUNG HAE SUNG：It's too high.
KIM SEONG JU：Does anyone want to take the rap part?
NAM SON：Me.
[Hands up]
NAM SON：I want the rap part.
[What are they talking about?]
ZHANG JING HE：The only thing I'm not satisfied about is
ZHANG JING HE：that since
ZHANG JING HE：I'm the only Chinese in this team...
PARK YEON WOOK：I think the important thing is that...
[ZHANG JING HE can't participate in the meeting due to the language barrier]
PARK YEON WOOK：Only those who can hit that pitch can take this part.
[BUT! The Korean-only meeting...]
JUNG HAE SUNG：Except for this part, we can sing
JUNG HAE SUNG：all the Main Vocal parts.
PARK YEON WOOK：I think so.
KIM SEONG JU：But this part has the highest pitch.
PARK YEON WOOK：Yeah.
ZHANG JING HE：I don't know what to do.
[How will ZHANG JING HE, who can't communicate with his teammates, solve this problem?]
["Sorry Sorry" vs "Again& Again" Practice Room]
[Wow~~~]
SHAO ZI HENG：This part is cool.
[Appreciating the dance part]
[Even eyebrows are admiring it]
HAN GYUL：That's it. Right.
SHAO ZI HENG：Wow, this dance move is really cool.
HONG SUNG MIN：It's really cool.
[(One look One copy)]
HONG SUNG MIN：We'll definitely look cool if we can do the dance well.
[Speaking of the team that can do 'One look One copy']
HAN GYUL：So cool.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Just choose the trainees you want to choose.
[(When choosing teammates)]
SHAO ZI HENG：I've made up my mind.
[The leader is Polaris SHAO ZI HENG]
SHAO ZI HENG：HONG SUNG MIN.
[(Vocal) HONG SUNG MIN]
SHAO ZI HENG：HAN GYUL.
[(Visual) HAN GYUL]
SHAO ZI HENG：ZAI.
[(Dance) ZAI]
ZAI.
SHAO ZI HENG：DONG HWA.
[(All ROUNDER) YANG DONG HWA]
SHAO ZI HENG：And LINGQI.
[(Vocal) LINGQI]
IVAN：They can both sing and dance.
BIAN SHI YU：He only chose the good ones.
SUN YING HAO：They are like an average Ace team, you know?
LUO JUN WEI：This team is too strong.
XU SHI HUAN：As long as we don't have to compete with them, actually.
HAN GYUL：I have something to say.
HAN GYUL：I don't know if the other team can hear me,
HAN GYUL：but we'll wipe the floor with you.
[We'll wipe the floor with you]
HAN GYUL：We'll wipe the floor with you.
LINGQI：We will win.
LINGQI：Let's defeat Team "Sorry Sorry".
[What about Team "Sorry Sorry" on the other side?]
[Compared to the other team, Team "Sorry Sorry" is rather silent]
HAN TAE I：Since our team is made up of those who remained till the last,
HAN TAE I：the atmosphere of the whole team is a bit depressing.
[(All alone)]
[(Sigh)]
[Just watching the video repeatedly]
HAN TAE I：It's so hard.
[Start having a headache]
[(Sigh)]
HAN TAE I：What should we do?
HAN TAE I：What kind of stage performance
HAN TAE I：will the team composed of the weakest trainees deliver?
HAN TAE I：I'm pretty worried.
[What will happen to Team "Sorry Sorry"?]
[Team "Sheesh" and Team "Boom Boom Bass" are completely separated]
HUANG JIA LIANG：I think you're crazy.
[All of a sudden...?]
HUANG JIA LIANG：You gathered these three.
[Two Star, All Star, All Star]
HUANG JIA LIANG：How hard you must work, bro.
HUANG JIA LIANG：Dude!
BIAN SHI YU：I thought about it.
[Panicking]
[What should we do...]
BIAN SHI YU：I know. Really. Actually,
BIAN SHI YU：I'm doing this because I want to learn from you.
BIAN SHI YU：Because I think whether it's individual strength
BIAN SHI YU：or teamwork,
[Focused] [Listening]
BIAN SHI YU：there's a lot I can learn from you.
BIAN SHI YU：I've always admired my seniors,
BIAN SHI YU：like DUAN XING XING,
BIAN SHI YU：SUN YING HAO, and YOO GWAN WOO
BIAN SHI YU：very much.
[During the Level Test]
BIAN SHI YU：Because since the Level Test,
BIAN SHI YU：I had a deep impression of them.
[Wow]
DAESUNG：All three of you,
DAESUNG：All Star position.
[All team members got All Star positions]
Thank you!
BIAN SHI YU：So I really want to work with them once.
[Respect. We successfully hired three of them!]
HUANG JIA LIANG：But I'm telling you,
HUANG JIA LIANG：what I'm most afraid of is being overwhelmed by the energy of the three of them.
HUANG JIA LIANG：So we have to work hard.
BIAN SHI YU：We will definitely show...
[Right?]
DUAN XING XING：However,
DUAN XING XING：I have a question.
[What's... wrong?]
DUAN XING XING：Have you prepared the tuition fee?
[Lost ten years of life]
[No free lessons!]
YOO GWAN WOO：You can trade it with bread
YOO GWAN WOO：or cookies.
[Accept bread and cookies]
DUAN XING XING：Just kidding.
[Clamorous]
[In the harmonious atmosphere, they heard the opposing team singing]
SUN YING HAO：Can I go see them singing "Sheesh" now?
HUANG JIA LIANG：Go ahead.
[Go ahead, YING HAO!]
SUN YING HAO：I want to see them singing "Sheesh".
[Infiltrated successfully]
KINGSTON WONG：Why are you here?
[Got caught. Run with all his might]
YOO GWAN WOO：Not good, right?
SUN YING HAO：I suddenly feel like our "Boom Boom Bass" is a great choice.
Suddenly! Suddenly!
"Boom Boom Bass" is a great choice.
[Not happy]
[Not happy No. 2]
[The atmosphere got cold quickly]
RIN：Actually, because the members of Team "Boom Boom Bass" are really formidable,
RIN：although I'd like to say we can win,
RIN：to be honest, I think it's going to be tough.
IVAN：How can we overcome this?
IVAN：We can only give it our all.
[What will be the fate of the crisis-stricken Team "Sheesh"?]
[Practice is the only way to survive]
[D-5]
I hope we can show what we have prepared.
[D-4]
[D-3]
[D-2]
We want to be cooler on stage.
[D-1]
[D-Day]
[Studio]
[The audience cheering for the Starlight Boys]
YOO GWAN WOO, fighting!
SUN JIA YANG, come on!
LEE DA EUL, fighting!
ZAI, fighting!
BAE173, fighting!
I’m always rooting for you.
Love you.
[The entry officially starts 30 minutes before the competition begins]
[The audience has entered]
HAN GYUL：It's about to start.
LINGQI：Finally.
Finally.
HAN GYUL：It's about to start.
HAN TAE I：I’m so nervous.
[Starlight Boys finally starts]
[Wow, it's LEE SUNG KYOUNG!]
[Nice to meet you]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：iQIYI International Idol Audition, Starlight Boys.
[iQIYI International Idol Audition, Starlight Boys]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Hello, I'm the Guardian Representative, LEE SUNG KYOUNG.
[Guardian Representative, MC, LEE SUNG KYOUNG]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Nice to meet you.
[So beautiful!]
[The Guider Corps is with us today]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The Starlight Boys, who began their heart-pounding journey
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：with dreams of debuting as international idols, are here today.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Today is a special day for the trainees
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：because it's their first time performing on stage in front of the Guardians.
[The first time performing on stage in front of the Guardians]
[Fighting]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Which trainee are you here to cheer for today?
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Who is it?
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Your support is already very passionate.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：It should give the trainees a lot of strength.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Today's trainees
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：are divided into ten teams.
[56 people, 10 teams, 5 rounds, 1 vs 1 per match.]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Each round will have two teams,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：and there will be five rounds of group competitions in total.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：In each round,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：every Guardian will vote twice.
[The first vote. The second vote][Everyone has two voting opportunities for each round]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：First, the individual vote.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：During each performance,
[First: Individual Vote]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：the Guardians can vote for the trainee they like.
[First vote: During each performance, you can vote for the individuals from each team. You can vote for multiple trainees. If there is no trainee you'd like to vote for, you don't have to vote]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：If there is more than one trainee you want to support,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：you can press the numbers of all the trainees you wish to vote for.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：On the contrary, if there is no trainee you'd like to support,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：you don't have to vote.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Next, there will be a team vote.
[Second: Team Vote]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：After both the First Strike Team and the Counterattack Team
[Second vote: After each round, you can vote for the team you think performed better. No repeat voting is allowed. There are no abstentions]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：finish their performances,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：you can vote for the team you think performed better.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The five teams that win each round,
[Rewards eligibility: 1. All members of the winning team in each round; 2. The individual who ranks first in the individual vote]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：as well as the trainee with the highest overall vote count,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：will receive rewards,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：which will be reflected in the First Ranking Announcement Ceremony.
[The rewards will be reflected in the First Ranking Announcement Ceremony]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Now, Starlight Boys'
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：K-POP Generation Battle begins.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：LIGHT NOW, RIGHT NOW!
[LIGHT NOW, RIGHT NOW!]
[Starlight Boys]
[Star Lounge for the performers]
[Hello, everyone]
YOON: Hello, everyone.
[With the gift prepared for the trainees]
YOON: Thank you. This is a small gift from me.
YOON: It's called KOPIKO.
YOON: It really gives you energy, just like drinking coffee.
YOON: I often have it myself.
[Energy Charging TIME]
[The rich taste of coffee]
LINGQI：Delicious
HAN JEONG WOO：Delicious.
LINGQI：Delicious.
YOON: Starlight Boys must eat this.
LINGQI：Trainees who always stay up all night need it.
Thank you.
YOON: Fighting! Fighting!
[Fighting!]
-YOON：Fighting!
-We will eat it.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：iQIYI International Idol Audition, Starlight Boys.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Let me introduce the songs for the first round of the K-POP Generation Battle.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：First, the performance of the First Strike Team
[The First Strike Team of the First Round]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：is "Chk Chk Boom" of Stray Kids.
[Walking towards the stage with everyone's support]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Then, the performance of the Counterattack Team
[The second attack team in Round 1]
LEE JUN HYUK：We will face off against Team "Chk Chk Boom." I'm so nervous.
CHOI JUN HO：So nervous.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：is "Guerrilla" of ATEEZ.
[The Fourth Generation Battle: Chk Chk Boom vs Guerrilla]
-Fighting.
-MIN JAE: Make a move!
LEE JUN HYUK：Make a love!
HONG SUNG MIN：Do your best.
LEE JUN HYUK：Let's go, Guerilla.
[They look like heroes ready to sacrifice themselves]
LEE SEUNG GI：These two teams are really good.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：Today’s legend.
YANG DONG HWA: I’m looking forward to it.
HAN TAE I：I think they are the best two teams.
CAI CHENG YUAN：The members of their team
[Team Chk Chk Boom]
CAI CHENG YUAN：are all All Rounders.
YANG DONG HWA: I think they are exceptionally talented teams when it comes to performances.
[Team Guerilla]
YANG DONG HWA: So, I'm really looking forward to their performance.
KAWK GUN：I only have one thought: we must win.
[Team Chok Chok Boom]
KAWK GUN：It was chosen by Team "Guerrilla".
KAWK GUN：They always provoke Team "Chk Chk Boom".
[They always provoke Team Chk Chk Boom]
[When deciding the opponent]
LEE JUN HYUK：Honestly, I'm not that scared.
[Not that scared]
HAN JEONG WOO：After the battle is over, make sure to say hello to them.
[After the battle is over, make sure to say hello to them]
MIN JAE：Last week, YOO JUN and I did the same performance
MIN JAE：wearing the same clothes.
MIN JAE：Why has the color of the clothes changed now?
[You're a One Star. I'm an All Star]
MIN JAE：I’ll prove it with my performance.
KAWK GUN：Let's give it a try.
KAWK GUN：Let's show our performance
LEE JUN HYUK：Team "Chk Chk Boom" and we practiced together,
LEE JUN HYUK：so we roughly know their capabilities.
LEE JUN HYUK：We have 1004% confidence in our victory.
[1004% Confidence to Win]
MICHAEL WU：We will win.
HIKARI：Honestly, compared to other teams, we practice a whole lot more.
MIN JAE：In fact, the result
MIN JAE：matters more than practice.
MIN JAE：We will show you the result.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Now let’s welcome the First Strike Team.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Team "Chk Chk Boom", please come to the stage.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Please say hello to the Guardians first.
YOO JUN：Let's say hello. Two, three.
-Chk Chk Boom. -Chk Chk Boom.
-We are Six Pack. -We are Six Pack.
-Six Pack. -Six Pack.
-Hello, we’re Six Pack. -Hello, we’re Six Pack.
YOO JUN：Hello, I’m YOO JUN.
HAN GYUL：So handsome.
YANG YAN：Hello, I’m YANG YAN from Singapore.
YANG YAN!
Yeah!
LEE SEUNG GI：HIKARI is indeed handsome.
HIKARI：Hello, everyone. I'm Curry (KARI).
HONG SUNG MIN：HIKARI!
LINGQI：HIKARI, so handsome!
HIKARI：Hello, I’m HIKARI.
HIKARI：Nice to meet you.
HIKARI：Hello, I'm HIKARI. Nice to meet you.
MICHAEL WU：Hello, everyone. I’m MICHAEL WU from Canada.
KAWK GUN：Hello, I’m KAWK GUN.
SYO：Hello, I’m SYO.
SYO：Nice to meet you.
LEE SEUNG GI：During the practice, in Team "Chk Chk Boom",
LEE SEUNG GI：HIKARI and MICHAEL WU did so great.
-LEE SEUNG GI: Right? -KWON EUNBI：Agreed.
KWON EUNBI：They are literally eye-catching.
[On the Team Selection Day]
[Team "Chk Chk Boom" in the Part-assignment Meeting]
Shall we decide?
HIKARI：Can we choose Polaris ourselves?
KAWK GUN：Yes, we can.
We can choose Polaris ourselves.
[So that's it]
HIKARI：I've always wanted to be Polaris.
HIKARI：I wanna do this in the prelude.
HIKARI：I wanna be Polaris.
[The Visual Impact that HIKARI Wants]
HIKARI：I got a Visual sticker too.
HIKARI：I wish I could do it.
HIKARI：I want Polaris.
[I want Polaris]
MICHAEL WU：Polaris?
[I want]
HIKARI：I want Polaris.
[I want Polaris]
MICHAEL WU：Polaris?
MICHAEL WU：Same here.
[Me too. I want Polaris]
[Unexpected Rival]
[Unexpected rival, MICHAEL WU]
HIKARI：I really want Polaris.
OK.
You two, right?
I think so.
Yeah.
MICHAEL WU：He told me, when we were competing for the position,
MICHAEL WU：that he really, really wanted it.
MICHAEL WU：But I also really, really wanted it.
MICHAEL WU：(For the) first stage, ZAI took Center.
MICHAEL WU：And then, I feel like, this time, more like, can show dance, yeah.
[MICHAEL WU was not the Center in the Level Test]
[He's determined to get the center position this time]
MICHAEL WU：Well, it was like... Before, I'm (was) like, "Oh, okay..."
[What now?]
HIKARI：Polaris can’t be divided, right?
HIKARI：No.
[Sobbing…]
[Battle for Polaris in Team "Chk Chk Boom"]
[Contestant No.1: MICHAEL WU]
MICHAEL WU：I'm confident I can pull this off.
YANG YAN：MICHAEL WU is a really good dancer.
[MICHAEL WU stole the show even though he was not in the Center position]
PONG：He appeared charming and sexy even with a little dance.
LUO JUN WEI：Is he really an idol?
LUO JUN WEI：Not a professional dancer?
LUO JUN WEI：This is my thought.
LEE SEUNG GI：Isn't that the expression we often see on idols?
LEE SEUNG GI：That vibe of having lived in North America.
DAESUNG：Exactly.
[Contestant No.2: HIKARI]
HIKARI：I have confidence.
KAWK GUN：HIKARI's got great visual appeal.
KAWK GUN：That's a must in a group.
[Hee-hee]
MICHAEL WU：I can go first.
[Start from MICHAEL WU, trying the Polaris part]
♫Vamos, I know that you want it Boom♫
♫Lobos, we cannot stop hunting Boom♫
♫Ratatata I'mma make it♫
♫Boom Boom Chk Chk Boom♫
[Native speaker's pronunciation, Powerful "Chk Chk Boom"]
YOO JUN：OK.
[It's HIKARI's turn]
♫Vamos, I know that you want it Boom♫
♫Lobos, we cannot stop hunting Boom♫
♫Ratatata I'mma make it♫
♫Boom Boom Chk Chk Boom♫
[Steady Tone, Sexy Ver. "Chk Chk Boom"]
[Good Job]
YOO JUN：OK, OK.
SYO：It’s hard to decide.
YOO JUN： MICHAEL's got energy. HIKARI is sexy.
[Sexy vs Energy: Two Trainees with Different Charms]
[But there is only one Polaris position. Self-Evaluation voting kicks off]
YANG YAN：We'll choose.
SYO：Don't say the name. Just point.
[HIKARI vs MICHAEL WU]
YANG YAN：I think, for HIKARI, his Polaris for "Chk Chk Boom" is more sexy and cool.
YANG YAN：And for MICHAEL, it's a bit more power (powerful) and strong.
YANG YAN：And I think for Chk Chk Boom, we need a power (powerful) and strong Polaris.
[Power and Energy
MICHAEL WU's Supporter]
YANG YAN：MICHAEL suits better for "Chk Chk Boom".
[Sexy & Cool HIKARI's Supporter]
YOO JUN：I think HIKARI's a better fit.
YOO JUN：First of all, HIKARI is good at expressions
YOO JUN：with abundant stage experience.
YOO JUN：He’s relaxed and cool.
YOO JUN：I think he can do it well.
YOO JUN：One, two, three.
[3 Votes for MICHAEL WU, 2 Votes for HIKARI]
HIKARI：OK.
YOO JUN：OK.
[Pout]
HIKARI：In fact, I'm only interested in the Polaris part.
MICHAEL WU：It's very satisfying.
MICHAEL WU：Even if HIKARI is still holding on to that hope of being Polaris,
MICHAEL WU：I think I will show him that I deserve this position.
[That Night]
MICHAEL WU：Like HIKARI, he's more...
MICHAEL WU：HIKARI's my teammate.
MICHAEL WU：He competed with me for the center position,
MICHAEL WU：and he really wanted it.
IVAN：Are you saying they are ambitious?
[That's right.]
MICHAEL WU：Yeah, very ambitious.
HIKARI：I really wanna be Polaris.
YOO JUN：Really wanna be Polaris?
HIKARI：We only have 12 seconds for a two-minute song.
[Vocal 2]
HIKARI：There's nothing to show.
YOO JUN：Go talk to them.
[In the dead of night, HIKARI is lost in thought]
[Interim Check Day]
Welcome.
LEE SEUNG GI：So your team's Polaris is...
LEE SEUNG GI：MICHAEL WU.
[It's me, haha]
LEE SEUNG GI：So MICHAEL WU is Polaris.
LEE SEUNG GI：But I heard that HIKARI still hasn't given up hope of being Polaris.
LEE SEUNG GI：Is that so?
HIKARI：Yes, that's right.
[Yes, that's right]
[Interesting]
HUI：You're really something.
LEE SEUNG GI：MICHAEL WU, you feel that too?
MICHAEL WU：I think so.
[I think so]
LEE SEUNG GI：That relaxed tone!
LEE SEUNG GI：Even if one doesn't understand this language...
HANHAE：I think so.
[Relaxed]
CHOI YOUNGJUN：Looks like our opinions matter today.
LEE SEUNG GI：Should we let them dance?
[Urgent Suggestion from the Guiders]
CHOI YOUNGJUN：You wanna dance together, HIKARI?
HIKARI：OK.
MICHAEL WU：OK.
[Interesting Show]
HIKARI：I'm confident in being Polaris.
MICHAEL WU：I won't let him grab my Polarist position.
[Stumbling]
[HIKARI made a mistake in the dance]
[What a pity]
[MICHAEL WU's more energetic than usual]
♫Boom Boom Chk Chk Boom♫
[Energy 2,000%, all out]
LEE SEUNG GI：Okay, let's evaluate.
[Among the two trainees with opposite charms, who will be Polaris of "Chk Chk Boom"?]
[HIKARI danced very well]
CHOI YOUNGJUN：HIKARI danced very well.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：Very good.
LEE SEUNG GI：But this can't beat MICHAEL WU.
[But this can't beat MICHAEL WU]
LEE SEUNG GI：That's it.
[Energetic MICHAEL WU is confirmed as Polaris of "Chk Chk Boom"]
Wow...
HUI：But I wanna say something.
HUI：MICHAEL WU is also good at dancing. All good...
[All good?]
HUI：But for the idol-like charm...
[Agree 22: Idol-like Charm...]
CHOI YOUNGJUN：Yes.
HUI：It would be great if you could improve it a little.
HANHAE：I have the same feeling.
[Poining out the lack of idol-like charm]
LEE SEUNG GI：Learn the dance energy from MICHAEL WU.
LEE SEUNG GI：But in terms of expressions, MICHAEL WU should learn from HIKARI.
[Suggest the Integration of MICHAEL WU's energy and HIKARI's expressions]
MICHAEL WU：OK.
HIKARI：Personally, I’m quite sad I didn’t become Polaris.
HIKARI：But as a member with enough stage experience,
HIKARI：I'd like to do my best and help MICHAEL WU
HIKARI：with expressions if I can,
HIKARI：so as to put on a wonderful show.
HIKARI：What are you writing?
[Study of Idol Facial Expression]
MICHAEL WU：Idol facial expression.
MICHAEL WU：Do not show effort.
[Study of Idol Facial Expression: Do not show effort]
MICHAEL WU：No (expression like this).
[No Expression Like This]
HIKARI：It's okay.
HIKARI：Save your energy for expressions in the most important parts.
[HIKARI finds out what he can do and offers help]
HIKARI：Your pronunciation is so long.
MICHAEL WU：So long?
HIKARI：Make it short.
MICHAEL WU：Shorter?
MICHAEL WU：HIKARI is like an older brother to me.
MICHAEL WU：He has really helped in terms of
MICHAEL WU：taking the load off for me.
MICHAEL WU：Sometimes for dance, it's literally only me.
MICHAEL WU：And then HIKARI stepped out, helping me with that.
[For the team, in their respective positions, HIKARI and MICHAEL WU did their best]
HIKARI：Because it's a team mission about teamwork.
HIKARI：I want to put on a good show.
HIKARI：Fighting.
All: 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. Six Pack.
Fighting!
HUI：Fighting! Go for it!
HONG SUNG MIN：Let's go!
HONG SUNG MIN：I’m looking forward to it.
HIKARI：Because we literally practiced harder than any other team.
MICHAEL WU：I’m confident that we will win.
[With their efforts]
[How will their performance turn out?]
["Chk Chk Boom", Original: Stray Kids]
♫Boom Boom Chk Chk Boom♫
♫I hit the black dot right at the center♫
♫And even my swift plan♫
♫On a perfect scene without a blind spot♫
♫I dance according to my plan, keep going♫
♫Sick of this life, it's regular ♫
♫I overate victory, so full♫
♫To go for a stroll I wear the belt around my waist♫
♫We go to the universe, all the rest kneel, I'm strong♫
♫Yeah yeah yeah yeah ♫
♫There's nothing I can't do, I do it ♫
♫Just pull out my trigger I got that♫
CHOI YOUNGJUN：That's sick!
♫I'mma pop pop pop take a shot yeah ♫
♫Shoot down my goals one by one, I snipe them♫
♫Filling up my truck yeah you want that ride (Boom)♫
HAN GYUL：Cool.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：He didn’t really do anything, yet everyone's so hyped.
♫Filling up my truck yeah you want that ride (Boom)♫
♫Hit you like a truck I'mma make you fly♫
♫Boom♫
♫Vamos, I know that you want it♫
♫Lobos, we cannot stop hunting♫
♫Boom♫
♫Ratatata I'mma make it♫
♫Boom Boom Chk Chk Boom♫
♫Boom♫
♫Vamos, I know that you want it♫
♫Chaos, we so catastrophic♫
♫Boom♫
♫Ratatata I'mma make it Boom♫
♫Boom Chk Chk Boom♫
♫Destroying the cliché is more of a cliché itself♫
♫Maintain all the opinions about me♫
♫Nothing's changed, I'm not a changed man♫
♫My next move is still only applied to the next level♫
♫To the goal step by step, I took a step closer♫
♫I'm the owner of my goal♫
♫Lucky to have me as an owner♫
♫I make it right zeroing in clear♫
♫Breaking the silence, my trigger, fire (fire)♫
♫Raise the target higher to the end over there♫
♫My amigo♫
DUAN XING XING：It's coming...
[Blowing everyone away]
DUAN XING XING：MICHAEL WU!
♫Boom Boom Chk Chk Boom♫
♫Dig in deeper♫
♫My bullet goes tang, tang, tang♫
♫This is La Vida Loca♫
♫This is good shot, shot, shot♫
♫Dig in deeper♫
♫My bullet goes tang, tang, tang♫
♫This is La Vida Loca♫
LEE JUN HYUK：We need to be nervous.
♫Boom Boom Chk Chk Boom♫
KWON EUNBI：They did so well! They did so well!
LEE SEUNG GI：Why are they so good?
CHOI YOUNGJUN：They're crazily good, right?
CHOI YOUNGJUN：They're crazily good, right? I told you they'd be great.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：I told you they'd be great.
KWON EUNBI：They're so good.
HAN TAE I：That was so good. They did well.
HAN GYUL：It was fierce from the beginning.
HONG SUNG MIN：They set the standards high from the beginning.
Okay.
MIN JAE：They smashed it.
CHEN XUAN YOU：We have work very hard.
MIN JAE：Be nervous. We have to be nervous.
LEE JUN HYUK：My mind hasn't changed,
LEE JUN HYUK：I still think the probability of us winning is 1004%.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Team Chk Chk Boom's first round of individual voting
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：is about to end.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：I’ll call the trainees' names one last time.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：No. 1, Trainee YOO JUN.
YOO JUN：Please vote for No.1.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：No. 2, Trainee YANG YAN.
YANG YAN：Please vote for No. 2.
YANG YAN：No.2.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：No. 3, Trainee HIKARI.
HIKARI：I love you.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：No. 4, Trainee MICHAEL WU.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：No. 5, Trainee KAWK GUN.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：No. 6, Trainee SYO.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Now the five-second voting countdown begins.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The first round of individual voting has ended.
[Team Chk Chk Boom's first round of individual voting has ended
YOO JUN：Two, three.
Thank you.
HANHAE：Good job!
YOON: Really, that was great.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：The entire team did a good job,
[It's hard to beat the next team]
CHOI YOUNGJUN：But it's hard to beat them.
HUI：They are the best, really.
KWON EUNBI：Really?
HUI：They're really cool.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：I think they're the best out of all performances today.
[Out of all performances today,]
[Out of all performances today, they probably rank first]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Trainees from the Counterattack Team, "ATEEZ Guerrilla".
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：please come to the stage.
[With 1004% excitement, Team Guerrilla will take the stage]
LEE JUN HYUK：We'll greet everyone now. Two, three.
Make a love. Hello, everyone.
We are Break the Stage.
[Cu-]
[Cute]
-So cute. -Is it a cute performance?
YANG DONG HWA: Are they making the song cute?
MIN JAE：Hello, everyone. I am MIN JAE,
MIN JAE：here to ambush everyone's hearts today like a Guerrilla.
MIN JAE：Nice to meet you.
CHOI JUN HO：Hello, I'm Choi Junho.
CHOI JUN HO：Nice to meet you.
CHEN XUAN YOU：Hello, I'm Chen Xuanyu.
What's up?
LEE JUN HYUK：Hello, everyone. I'm Team Guerilla's Polaris,
LEE JUN HYUK：also the "Jun-chan" hero who always stays by your side.
LEE JUN HYUK：Nice to meet you.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：Business trip hero?
YOON: "Jun-chan" hero
HANHAE：Business trip hero?
CHOI YOUNGJUN：I heard it wrong.
HAN JEONG WOO：Hello, everyone. I’m Team Guerrilla's
HAN JEONG WOO：sexy representative, HAN JEONG WOO.
LEE DA EUL：Hello, I’m LEE DA EUL.
HUI：LEE DA EUL has gotten more charismatic.
KWON EUNBI：He's grown up.
HUI：Yes, he has.
LEE DA EUL：Hello, I'm LEE DA EUL.
[Fidgeting]
LEE DA EUL：Nice to meet  you.
LEE DA EUL：Thank you.
HUI：He became a child again.
-HONG SUNG MIN：So cute. -SUN YING HAO：DA EUL.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：I heard that the Counterattack Team has also prepared a strong performance.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Trainee LEE DA EUL.
LEE DA EUL：Yes.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：During the preparation of this stage,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：did you have any memorable moments?
LEE DA EUL：Well,
LEE DA EUL：I thought for a long time about whether I’m suitable for this stage.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The fourth team, Team HAN JEONG WOO.
[During the song selection]
HAN JEONG WOO：The song we chose is...
LEE DA EUL：The song I want to avoid the most
LEE DA EUL：is Guerrilla.
LEE DA EUL：It’s said to be very difficult.
[Guerrilla has a high level of difficulty in terms of dance and vocals]
LEE DA EUL：It’s very high-pitched.
LEE DA EUL：It’s also a powerful song.
LEE DA EUL：I hope it’s not this song.
HAN JEONG WOO：The song we chose is
[However]
HAN JEONG WOO：Guerrilla.
[However, the chosen song is Guerrilla]
-MIN JAE：Make a move. -LEE JUN HYUK：Guerrilla.
LEE DA EUL：I'm worried whether I can master the whole song.
[Mental breakdown]
[During part delegation]
MIN JAE：We are left with Positions One, Two, Three and Four.
[Team Guerrilla]
HAN JEONG WOO：Is there any part you want to sing?
HAN JEONG WOO：But I think you two
HAN JEONG WOO：should be in charge the Main Vocal and Vocal 1.
MIN JAE：Actually, I really want Vocal 1.
MIN JAE：Because I think this part can be showcased with the choreography.
CHOI JUN HO：Then I'll take the Main Vocal role.
[While the parts are divided smoothly,]
-HAN JEONG WOO：Are you find with Vocal 2? -CHEN XUAN YOU: Yup, okay.
Then I'll take Vocal 4.
-Vocal 4. -Yes.
[LEE DA EUL has not spoken]
MIN JAE：DA EUL, do you have a part that you want to sing?
[What's wrong?]
LEE JUN HYUK：I'm still a little worried about DA EUL.
MIN JAE：DA EUL is always lacking confidence.
MIN JAE：I'm worried that he might lose confidence again this time.
[During the Level Test,]
♫I’ll take a step back♫
♫And just be a friend, you know♫
[his performance did not meet the expectations]
♫I can wait♫
♫Tell me you think you like me too♫
CHOI YOUNGJUN：I don't think you've improved.
[and received a low grade in the Level Test]
CHOI YOUNGJUN：So I'm a little disappointed.
[Signal Song Mission]
CHOI YOUNGJUN：The last contestant to pass is.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：LEE DA EUL.
[LEE DA EUL was the last to qualify and barely survived]
[Team Guerrilla started practicing with concerns]
HAN JEONG WOO：Okay.
LEE JUN HYUK：Okay?
[O..Okay..?]
HAN JEONG WOO：Okay.
HAN JEONG WOO：I'll mark it again.
[Continuous practice]
[While everyone is managing the choreography well even when it is intense,]
[Stumbling]
[he is struggling to keep up with the choreography]
YOO JUN：Is DA EUL still alive?
YOO JUN：DA EUL looks exhausted. Are you okay?
LEE DA EUL：Yes.
LEE DA EUL：♫Expressions are losing the light♫
LEE DA EUL：♫Laughter is controlled♫
LEE DA EUL：Without me,
LEE DA EUL：they would have definitely done better.
LEE DA EUL：Because I’m not good enough.
LEE DA EUL：and I’m among a group of good people,
LEE DA EUL：it’s hard to keep up.
LEE DA EUL：So I can’t improve my self-esteem,
LEE DA EUL：both self-esteem and confidence.
[The next morning]
[LEE DA EUL's Dormitory]
[CHOI JUN HO and HAN JEONG WOO who are still in their sweet dreams]
[LEE DA EUL isn't here?]
[Where did he go so early in the morning?]
[DA EUL is the first to come to work]
LEE DA EUL：♫Dance, break that wall♫
[LEE DA EUL is the earliest to arrive for practice]
[Last night at the Heart-to-Heart Room]
LEE DA EUL：I feel that
LEE DA EUL：I kept letting everyone
LEE DA EUL：see my disappointing side.
LEE DA EUL：I feel guilty.
LEE DA EUL：So I want to use this time
LEE DA EUL：to practice harder and harder
LEE DA EUL：and go for it.
[LEE DA EUL starts practicing again after calming his mind]
LEE DA EUL：♫Dance, break that wall♫
[Singing]
LEE DA EUL：♫Break that wall, With our feel♫
[Singing again]
LEE DA EUL：♫Dance, break that wall♫
[Singing again and again]
LEE DA EUL：♫With our feel♫
[Working hard]
LEE DA EUL：Although I'm worried too,
LEE DA EUL：I’ll try my best to work hard
LEE DA EUL：in the remaining time.
LEE DA EUL：Because I think it’s a huge challenge for me.
LEE DA EUL：and I really have to work very hard,
LEE DA EUL：taking this as my last chance to try my best.
[Because this might be my last chance,]
[LEE DA EUL tries his best for her teammates.]
LEE DA EUL：Before this performance,
LEE DA EUL：I’ll be well prepared
LEE DA EUL：and performance a glamorous stage with my teammates.
LEE JUN HYUK：You suit this performance, DA EUL.
LEE JUN HYUK：It suits you very well.
HAN JEONG WOO：Let's cheer before we begin.
Make a Move.
HUI：Please.
LEE JUN HYUK：I’m not nervous.
LEE JUN HYUK：I just think it's time I should showcase myself.
CHOI JUN HO：As the name of this song,
CHOI JUN HO：I'm carrying the mindset of going to war.
LEE DA EUL：I really want to win.
[Guerrilla / (Original Singer: ATEEZ)]
Let's go!
♫I got it back♫
♫Turn the board over, this game♫
♫One chance right now at this time♫
♫I got it back♫
♫Turn the board over, this game♫
♫One chance right now at this time♫
♫Like that, short and intense escape♫
♫No next, just follow me easily♫
What's going on?
♫Boring, boring, sick, and tired, again♫
♫Stretch out now, look at the New World♫
♫New world♫
♫Boring, boring, sick, and tired again♫
♫So bored now, so long♫
♫Mm, disappearing emotions♫
♫Mm, expressions are losing the light♫
♫Mm, laughter is controlled♫
♫Only numbness left, no-oh♫
[WOW]
What's going on?
What happened to DA EUL?
DA EUL is so suitable.
He's a man now.
♫Mm, laughter is controlled♫
♫Only numbness left, no-oh♫
♫Can't bear it, no more lies♫
♫It's the time♫
♫Shoot the flashing light♫
♫Make a move♫
♫Dance, break that wall, with our feel♫
♫Spread it out, Guerrilla♫
♫This is how we shout♫
♫Shout♫
♫Loudly, keep it loud♫
♫Loud♫
♫Until everyone opens their eyes♫
♫Dance, break that wall, with our feel♫
♫Spread it out, Guerrilla♫
♫This is how we fight♫
♫Now we're gonna ride♫
He suits this song so well.
♫This is how we fight♫
♫Now we're gonna ride♫
♫Wake up the world, we are, oh♫
♫Dance, break that wall, with our feel♫
♫Change the world, we are the Guerrillas♫
♫Living with the eyes of emotions closed♫
That's crazy.
♫Doesn't it mean anything to you♫
♫Can't bear it, no more lies♫
♫It's the time, shoot the flashing light♫
♫Make a move♫
♫Dance, break that wall, with our feel♫
♫Change the world, we are the Guerrillas♫
♫The Guerrillas♫
♫Break the wall♫
♫The Guerrillas (Break the wall)♫
♫-Huh -The Guerrillas (Break the wall)♫
♫Change the world, we are the Guerrillas♫
♫Dance, break that wall, with our feel♫
CHOI YOUNGJUN：They dance like this and could still sing live so well.
LEE SEUNG GI：I know right.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：That's unbelievable.
[Go away]
[Ah! My eyes!]
HOU JIA EN：So cute.
KAWK GUN：They smashed it.
KAWK GUN：Team Guerrilla did a good job
KAWK GUN：but because the Guardians need to vote on the spot,
KAWK GUN：the result is not definite,
KAWK GUN：we might win.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Team Guerrilla's first round of individual voting
LEE SUNG KYOUNG： will end soon.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：No. 1, Trainee MIN JAE.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：No. 2, Trainee CHOI JUN HO.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：No. 3, Trainee CHEN XUAN YOU.
CHEN XUAN YOU：There's no time to explain. Vote for me.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：No. 4, Trainee LEE JUN HYUK.
LEE JUN HYUK：I’m No. 4.
LEE JUN HYUK：Please vote for No. 4.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：No. 5, Trainee HAN JEONG WOO.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：No. 6, Trainee LEE DA EUL.
LEE DA EUL：Thank you.
[Will they capture the hearts of the Guardians?]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：5-second countdown till the voting ends.
[Team Guerrilla's first round of individual voting has ended
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The first round of individual voting has ended.
The First Strike Team, please come to the stage.
["Chk Chk Boom" vs "Guerrilla" have gathered on the stage]
CHOI YOUNGJUN：They all did so great.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：I’m so proud.
LEE SEUNG GI：Both teams are good.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：What do you think of this round of performance, Guider CHOI YOUNGJUN?
CHOI YOUNGJUN：I want to tell the trainees,
CHOI YOUNGJUN：the stage makes me feel sorry
[A stage]
CHOI YOUNGJUN：for the things I've said to you in the past.
[A stage that makes me feel sorry]
CHOI YOUNGJUN：You all did so well
CHOI YOUNGJUN：and even incorporated the feedback from yesterday
CHOI YOUNGJUN：and presented the performance perfectly.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：I'm proud of that.
[Feeling proud]
CHOI YOUNGJUN：You were able to show the accumulated result
CHOI YOUNGJUN：of your hard work to so many people.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：Your dopamine levels have probably exploded.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：Please keep going with this emotion.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：Well done, I’m very proud.
Thank you very much.
YANG DONG HWA: That's a high compliment.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Next, let’s proceed with the group voting.
["Chk Chk Boom" VS "Guerilla". Which team will receive more votes?]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Guardians can vote for the team you think is better.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Vote for only one team, and vote only once.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The team with contrasting charm and aura on stage,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Team Chk Chk Boom.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The team showcasing strong and intense power,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Team Guerrilla.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：5-second countdown till the voting ends.
HONG SUNG MIN：Who will win?
HONG SUNG MIN：Both teams did well.
HUI：I really don't know.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：Both teams have different charms.
[Unpredictable]
HUI：I thought the Team Guerrilla would be stronger,
HUI：but this team did so well.
KWON EUNBI：I think they cooperated well.
[The Guardians are also troubled]
["Chk Chk Boom" VS "Guerilla",  the voting for the 4th generation battle has ended]
KAWK GUN：100 percent, 1,000 percent,
[Team Chk Chk Boom]
KAWK GUN：we'll win.
LEE JUN HYUK：I’m confident.
MIN JAE：I think we'll win.
What's going on?
What’s going on?
HIKARI：What is this?
[The result of the live voting will be revealed now.]
No, no, no.
[[The result of the live voting will be revealed now. Only the votes of Polaris and the trainee with the lowest score will be revealed.]
KAWK GUN：The lowest score.
YOO JUN：The lowest score.
KAWK GUN：Only Polaris and the lowest score.
[The Result Announcement Zone where victory can be predicted]
KAWK GUN：Wow, this is so cruel.
[Do you trust me?]
LEE JUN HYUK：Trust me.
[Starting with Team Guerrilla's Polaris]
[LEE JUN HYUK, 87 points]
[Oh!]
CHEN XUAN YOU：87 points!
[Oh! 87 points!]
[How abput Team Chk Chk Boom's Polaris MICHAEL WU?]
MICHAEL WU：Wow, scary.
[MICHAEL WU, 47 points]
HIKARI：I didn't expect this.
[40 points difference, A huge gap between 47 and 87 points]
MICHAEL WU：I thought "Oh, we might lose?"
[What will be the lowest score?]
LEE DA EUL：I think it must be me.
SYO：I thought I might be
SYO：the last place.
[HAN JEONG WOO, 12 points. SYO, 20 points]
HAN JEONG WOO：I have mixed feelings, but
HAN JEONG WOO：JUN HYUK's score is also out.
HAN JEONG WOO：So, it’s a happy thing.
HAN JEONG WOO：We might still win the team battle.
[Team Chk Chk Boom feels defeated on the other hand]
YOO JUN：Is it considered revealed?
HIKARI：It’s out.
SYO：As expected,
SYO：the impression I left was not strong enough.
HIKARI：There's a 30 or 40 points difference.
HIKARI：I even thought about whether we could still win.
[Now, only the result is left unannounced!]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：I will now announce the winning teams
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：of the K-POP Generation Battle
CHOI JUN HO：Here?
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Teams Chk Chk Boom and Guerrilla,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：please come to the stage.
[The two teams are back on stage for the result announcement]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：So, which team,
[Which team have the Guardians sided?]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：among Teams Chk Chk Boom and Guerrilla
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：have the Guardians sided?
LEE JUN HYUK：I’m really nervous and scared.
LEE JUN HYUK：I'm even more nervous than during the Level Test.
LEE JUN HYUK：I was that desperate.
YOO JUN：Come on, I really want to win.
YOO JUN：I can’t predict.
YOO JUN：This is an unpredictable result.
[Please]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Please reveal it now.
[Please reveal it now!]
[K-POP Generation Battle Mission]
[The first round
Team Chk Chk Boom VS
Team Chk Chk Boom VS Team Guerrilla]
[Which team will win the first round?]
[The result will be revealed later]
[Next, the songs for the next round]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Let me introduce the songs for the next round.
[Billboard Singles Chart]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：It's a song that took 1st place on the Billboard Singles Chart for 7 weeks in a row.
[1st place on the Billboard Singles Chart for 7 weeks in a row]
[7 weeks in a row?]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：It's Butter by BTS.
[The First Strike Team's song selection that can melt fans' hearts like "Butter"!]
EDEN：Fighting, fighting,
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Then it's the Counterattack Team's stage.
[What song did the the Counterattack Team choose?]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：This song ranked 1st on the album sales charts in 28 countries.
[Ranked 1st on the album sales charts in 28 countries]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：NCT DREAM's
[Ah~]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Glitch Mode.
[2 ROUND
Butter vs Glitch Mode]
[A battle between the shining boys]
[Plus,
The performance hasn't started yet and the fans are already cheering]
He's so cool!
LEE SUNG KYOUNG： "BUTTER" team trainees, please come up to the stage first.
[First Strike Team]
["BUTTER" team enters]
-EDEN：2, 3. 1 by,
-PENTOR：1 by,
[1 by]
-XU SHI HUAN：1 by,
-CAI CHENG YUAN：1 by,
[1 by]
-LUO JUN WEI：1 by,
-SHENG QI：1.
[One]
All： Hello, everyone.
EDEN：We are a team composed of
[Each of the members]
[Only one year apart]
EDEN：members only one year apart,
All： "BUTTER" team.
[We're going to melt your hearts]
["BUTTER" team]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Trainee EDEN, how was your teamwork
[How was your teamwork during your practice?]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：during your practice?
EDEN：Speaking of teamwork,
EDEN：among the ten teams,
[Among all the teams]
EDEN：I think we must be number one.
[No.1 among all the teams!]
[D-7]
[2nd Mission practice]
[Laughter that spread throughout the corridor]
[On one side, continuous laughter]
[Feelings MAX]
[Same space]
[Same space different feelings]
[Chu]
[A huge reaction]
[A huge reaction to every small joke]
[Ah!]
[Who is this team filled with happy virus?]
All：Hello, we are,
[We're One by one (a.k.a "BUTTER" team)!]
All： One by one (a.k.a "BUTTER" team)
XU SHI HUAN：Nice to meet you.
EDEN：This is it. Let’s go for it.
PENTOR：I really like it.
PENTOR：Everyone in this team is very cute.
PENTOR：They have a lot of positive energy and look positively at the world.
PENTOR：There's always laughter around.
♫Know that I got that heat♫
[Turn off the happy mode now]
[Turn off the happy mode now and start practicing]
Seven, eight.
Yep.
EDEN：What's wrong?
[Wow, handsome~]
LUO JUN WEI：Why are you so handsome?
XU SHI HUAN：Our Visual.
[Visual Check]
[The handsome face I see every day]
[Hahahahahahahahahaha]
[Their laughter never stops]
[Let's show a heart]
LUO JUN WEI：We have to show a heart too.
[Here is your heart]
No!
[Cute]
XU SHI HUAN：So cool.
SHENG QI：So handsome.
PENTOR：So handsome.
[What kind of visual is this?]
SHENG QI：He can't control his smile, Oh my God.
[So happy about it?]
XU SHI HUAN：It's harder to control than an AK.
[Yeah!]
Yeah!
[The best teamwork]
Go back.
[Noisy] [Ho!]
OK OK
[What with their atmosphere?]
Very good
OK OK
[Naughty when playing around]
[Naughty when playing around, but as soon as they start practicing, they are professionals]
[They cooperate well]
[Snooping]
WANG KUN：You guys are so fast.
WANG KUN：So fast.
XU SHI HUAN：Yeah.
[No way]
OK.
PENTOR：We brought up the energy and helped each other,
PENTOR：so everyone was encouraging each other during the practice.
PENTOR：Everyone was just helping each other.
[But]
PENTOR：But it wasn't this good at the beginning.
[But it wasn't this good at the beginning]
[The second day after the opponents were confirmed]
["BUTTER" team that gathered in the corner of the practice room]
[Zero laughter]
[A complete 180 from what we saw earlier!]
EDEN：We're the ones that were left
EDEN：until the last moment to be chosen.
[They were left until the last to be chosen during the time to choose their opponents]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The last one battle team has been formed.
KIM SEON JAE：I don’t actually know who are the people on the other team.
KIM SEON JAE：There must be a reason
[There must be a reason why I don’t know any of them]
KIM SEON JAE：why I don’t know any of them.
[Are they trainees without a presence?]
LEE JUN HYUK："BUTTER" team…
LEE JUN HYUK：Who are the members of "BUTTER" team?
WANG KUN：What’s his name?
WANG KUN：I don’t know.
KIM SEON JAE：The team next to us…
KIM SEON JAE：Actually, I don't remember who the members are.
[Humiliation of insignificance]
EDEN：It doesn't feel good.
EDEN：It's like they didn't choose us because they had no interest in us.
PENTOR：I was a little frustrated when I heard him say that.
[Know!]
♫Know Know Know that I got that heat♫
[Know that!]
[Someone moaning and groaning here]
♫ Know Know Know Know Know ♫
[Even trying while grabbing his hair]
[Even trying while grabbing his hair but he still can't hit the high notes]
[Team practice time]
♫Know that I got that heat♫
♫Let me show you 'cause talk is cheap♫
♫Get it, let it roll♫
[Can't hit the high notes]
[The members are struggling at the high notes]
XU SHI HUAN：We're in trouble.
EDEN：Why? Is it too high?
XU SHI HUAN：I mean the song.
EDEN：Why?
XU SHI HUAN：It's too high.
[The more I try, the harder it is to sing]
EDEN：It's really high.
Let's go!
♫Side step, right, left to my beat♫
[Interim Check for the second mission]
LEE SEUNG GI：It's not actually bad,
LEE SEUNG GI：but it's not good either.
[Ambiguous skills that are neither good nor bad]
LEE SEUNG GI：There's nothing to scold you about,
LEE SEUNG GI：there's nothing to comment on.
[Average skills that are neither good nor bad, just like tasteless butter]
LEE SEUNG GI：Just a performance that had no impact.
CHOI YOUNGJUN：It's just boring and bland.
[In the end]
[None of them showed any charm of the song!]
CHOI YOUNGJUN：That is the problem.
[Tasteless "Butter" Team received the worst evaluation]
EDEN：Is there any problems?
[What problems do we have?]
SHENG QI：Now it's so average.
SHENG QI：Average.
[The worst situation now is that their skills are just average]
SHENG QI：We just need something for us to move up.
[It’s time to confirm the strength and style of the team]
SHENG QI：Something that can just give us a boost.
PENTOR：I think everyone has a challenge.
[I think everyone has a challenge]
PENTOR：I think we have to change a little bit of ourselves
[We have to change ourselves]
PENTOR：Give us some time
PENTOR：to practice together, and see if
PENTOR：we can find a way to make it burst.
PENTOR：Then let's discuss again.
[PENTOR encourages the tired team members]
PENTOR：The problem doesn't fall on a specific person.
PENTOR：I think we just need to practice.
PENTOR：I wanted to give everyone strength.
SHENG QI：Let's practice our singing first, OK?
[Team practice starts to be able to show a change!]
♫Let's go♫
♫Side step, right, left to my beat♫
♫High like the moon, rock with me, baby♫
[PENTOR is leading with the high notes]
EDEN：Just repeat and repeat.
[Right after, they move on to practice dancing]
XU SHI HUAN：OK.
-OK.
-OK OK.
OK OK.
♫To my beat♫
[More frequent practice than before]
♫High like the moon, rock with me, baby♫
[The boring average butter is no more!]
[D-7]
[D-6]
[D-5]
[D-4]
[D-3]
[D-2]
[D-1]
PENTOR：I think hard work will never betray us.
[Please watch on to see if we've gotten better]
PENTOR：Please watch on and see.
[Did they manage to find the taste of their butter?]
KWON EUNBI：Fighting!
HUI：Fighting!
[A spoonful of support]
HUANG JIA LIANG：Come on.
-HUANG JIA LIANG：Let us enjoy "Butter".
-"Butter."
Let's go let's go!
-Let's go!
[Fighting]
CHEN XUAN YOU：Fighting!
PENTOR：We will try our best,
PENTOR：so that you can remember our names.
[Will they be able to show a "BUTTER" performance that belongs to them?]
["BUTTER" Original Singer-BTS]
♫Smooth like butter♫
♫Like a criminal undercover♫
♫Gon' pop like trouble♫
♫Breakin' into your heart like that (Ooh)♫
♫Cool shade stunner♫
♫Yeah, I owe it all to my mother♫
♫Hot like summer♫
♫Yeah, I'm making you sweat like that♫
♫Break it down♫
♫Ooh when I look in the mirror♫
CHOI YOUNGJUN: I can't hear you.
♫I'll melt your heart into two♫
♫I got that superstar glow, so♫
♫Do the boogie, like♫
♫A side step, right-left, to my beat♫
KWON EUNBI: Steady.
♫High like the moon, rock with me, baby♫
♫Know that I got that heat♫
♫Let me show you 'cause talk is cheap♫
♫Side step, right, left to my beat♫
♫Get it, let it roll♫
♫Ice on my wrist♫
♫I'm the nice guy♫
♫Got the right body and the right mind♫
♫Rolling up the party, got the right vibe♫
♫Smooth like (butter), hate us (love us)♫
♫Hate us (Love us)♫
♫Fresh boy pull up and we lay low♫
♫All the playas get movin' when the bass low♫
♫Got ARMY right behind us when we say so♫
♫Everybody♫
♫Let's go♫
♫Side step, right, left to my beat♫
♫High like the moon, rock with me, baby♫
♫Know that I got that heat♫
♫Let me show you 'cause talk is cheap♫
♫Side step, right, left to my beat♫
♫Get it, let it roll♫
♫High like the moon, rock with me, baby♫
♫Know that I got that heat♫
♫Let me show you 'cause talk is cheap♫
♫Side step, right, left to my beat♫
♫Get it, let it roll♫
♫Smooth like butter♫
♫Cool shade stunner♫
♫And you know we don't stop♫
♫Hot like summer♫
♫Ain't no bummer♫
♫You'll be like, oh, my God♫
♫We gon' make you rock, and you say (yeah)♫
♫We gon' make you bounce, and you say (yeah)♫
♫Hotter sweeter♫
♫Cooler butter♫
♫Get it, let it roll♫
[One by One Taste the BUTTER]
LEE JUN HYUK: Wow, there's confetti.
LEE SEUNG GI: This is not like other basic
idol songs.
[The song heavily relies on individual skills]
LEE SEUNG GI: Because everybody needs to
showcase their talents.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: The first individual voting for Team BUTTER will end soon.
[No.1, LUO JUN WEI]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: No.1, LUO JUN WEI.
[No.2, SHENG QI]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: No.2, SHENG QI.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: No.3, XU SHI HUAN.
[No.3, XU SHI HUAN]
[No.4, PENTOR]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: No.4, PENTOR.
[No.5, CAI CHENG YUAN]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: No.5, CAI CHENG YUAN.
[No.6, EDEN]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: No.6, EDEN
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: The voting will last
for five seconds.
[Voting ends]
[After the performance of Team BUTTER]
KRIS: Wow.
[Only tension lingers backstage]
KIM SEON JAE: I'm so nervous]
[Sigh]
[Why is GUN WOO even more nervous?]
GUN WOO: Come on, the Polaris.
[Polaris!]
[Choose the Polaris first]
It’s time to decide the Polaris.
WANG KUN: The Polaris needs to sing and dance.
[Who wants to be the Polaris?]
KIM SEON JAE: Who wants to be the Polaris?
-GUN WOO: HIJIRI.
-Do you want to be the Polaris?
WANG KUN: Yeah, I want it.
[Polaris candidates, HIJIRI VS WANG KUN]
Okay.
[The Polaris will be chosen through dancing]
-GUN WOO: Okay. Who is first?
-HIJIRI.
WANG KUN: HIJIRI first.
HIJIRI first.
[HIJIRI First]
GUN WOO: Five, six, seven, eight.
GUN WOO: OK.
[Wang Kun Second]
GUN WOO: 6, 7, 8.
WANG KUN: Because I’m an All Star,
WANG KUN: and all my friends are watching,
[I will win]
WANG KUN: I will win.
[Then?]
GUN WOO: 6 7 8.
GUN WOO: OK. OK.
GUN WOO: Our Polaris is...
[Who is our Polaris?]
[The Polaris of Team Glitch Mode is HIJIRI]
WANG KUN: Who is it?
GUN WOO: HIJIRI.
-WANG KUN: HIJIRI?
-Thank you.
HIJIRI.
WANG KUN: It's okay.
[Isn’t life like this?]
WANG KUN: This is life.
WANG KUN: As long as I am still
WANG KUN: a part of the team, and put up
a good performance.
[Agrees immediately]
WANG KUN: Yes.
[Why it's HIJIRI? Strength is the foundation]
KIM SEON JAE: Dancing is his strength.
[Why it's HIJIRI? Strength is the foundation.
And strong body language]
KIM SEON JAE: His expression, body language,
KIM SEON JAE: and how chilled he is.
[HIJIRI was chosen to be the best member
for the HIJIRI]
KIM SEON JAE: So I chose HIJIRI.
[First practice day]
GUN WOO: Let's practice.
[They learn the dance together]
[HIJIRI suddenly stops practicing the dance]
♫This is a fatal situation♫
[Start to practice the song alone]
♫Shutting me down, uncontrollable♫
♫Everyone says I'm too much♫
HIJIRI: The Polaris has more parts
HIJIRI: than any of the vocalist 12345.
[The Polaris has the most parts]
HIJIRI: I must reach the goal through practice.
HIJIRI: This is the most important mission of
the Polaris.
GUN WOO: He was practicing by himself.
GUN WOO: Then it would be a solo show.
[If he practiced by himself, it would be
a solo show]
GUN WOO: We're a team.
GUN WOO: We should practice together.
[GUN WOO gathered all the members]
GUN WOO: Have a seat.
GUN WOO: It's important to show your
personal abilities,
GUN WOO: but we are evaluated as a team.
GUN WOO: Teamwork is very important.
[Teamwork is very important]
[Team comes first during practice]
GUN WOO: When we practice,
GUN WOO: we should always bear that in mind.
[HIJIRI kept silence at what GUN WOO said]
[Interim Check D-day]
[Team Glitch Mode Interim Check]
HANHAE: Come on.
CHOI YOUNGJUN: Three, two, one.
♫Scratch that bring it back♫
[From HIJIRI, the Polaris's part]
♫In front of you, Glitch Mode♫
♫My entire body is faulty,  reload♫
[Is HIJIRI singing all the time?]
♫Shutting me down, uncontrollable♫
♫Everyone says I'm too much♫
[HIJIRI's part lasted 55 seconds out of 127]
♫Miscode♫
♫It's a state of emergency♫
♫It's only you or you on repetition (Mhm)♫
[HIJIRI's part accounts for 43%]
♫Trouble trouble like a miscode♫
[When assigning the parts]
HIJIRI: I have parts I want to sing.
HIJIRI: The main vocalist.
HIJIRI: And vocalist 1 and 2 part.
GUN WOO: Vocalist 1 and 2.
GUN WOO: Are there any parts to sing?
HIJIRI: All of them.
GUN WOO: All of them?
[HIJIRI is responsible for the Polaris,
and main vocalist part]
♫Accelerating heart Go, speeding up♫
[HIJIRI made a mistake in the lyrics]
♫This emotion, no words can
Can't get enough♫
[Making mistakes again and again]
[The Guider Corps look serious]
♫cratch that bring it back♫
♫In front of you♫
-HANHAE: OK.
-HUI: OK.
HANHAE: It’s so difficult.
LEE SEUNG GI: Where should I start?
CHOI YOUNGJUN: HIJIRI.
[As the Polaris]
[As the Polaris, you don't have any strengths]
CHOI YOUNGJUN: As the Polaris, you don't
have any strength.
CHOI YOUNGJUN: As the Polaris, you don't have
any strength.
CHOI YOUNGJUN: You have to improve
in every way possible.
CHOI YOUNGJUN: Even if it means swapping
the Polaris.
[Even if it means swapping the Polaris]
CHOI YOUNGJUN: I saw your performance today.
[One of the teams who are not ready for the
stage]
CHOI YOUNGJUN: I think you're one of the teams
CHOI YOUNGJUN: who are not ready for the stage.
[I think you're one of the teams
who are not ready for the stage]
CHOI YOUNGJUN: Your team is not ready.
GUN WOO: It's really over.
[It's really over]
HIJIRI: The Polaris's part
HIJIRI: is the most difficult part.
HIJIRI: So it’s a little unfair.
LEE SEUNG GI: Now it’s meaningless
to give a BAD sticker.
LEE SEUNG GI: It's meaningless to give
a BAD sticker.
[It's meaningless to give a BAD sticker]
LEE SEUNG GI: Even if I give you a BAD sticker,
LEE SEUNG GI: I don't think you'll work harder.
[Team Glitch Mode]
LEE SEUNG GI: I won't give you any stickers.
[Team Glitch Mode is the first team
without stickers]
WANG KUN: I think they’re right.
WANG KUN: Our performance was a mess.
[Emergency meeting after the Interim Check]
WANG KUN: I think we should swop parts,
WANG KUN: and change the way we practice.
GUN WOO: Although this is a competition show,
GUN WOO: we are a team now.
GUN WOO: Let's swop the Polaris.
[We]
[We should swop the Polaris]
[Even if other members become the Polaris]
HIJIRI: Even if other members become
the Polaris,
["Even if other members become
the Polaris, it wouldn't change the result"]
HIJIRI: it wouldn't change the result.
GUN WOO: Wait.
GUN WOO: What you just said
[Looking down upon us]
GUN WOO: is looking down upon us.
HIJIRI: My part.
HIJIRI: If other members take my part,
[Dance and sing at the same time]
HIJIRI: they can't dance
HIJIRI: and sing at the same time.
You can't sing and dance at the same time.
GUN WOO: Why do you get to decide this?
GUN WOO: Who are you to decide this?
HIJIRI: I'm the most confident.
[I'm the most confident]
[The members turned silent because of HIJIRI]
[GUN WOO couldn't stand it and left the room]
[He eventually bursted into tears alone]
GUN WOO: I felt betrayed now.
GUN WOO: Because I liked him, HIJIRI.
[Because I liked him, HIJIRI]
[During the Signal Song Mission
One Star Practice Room]
GUN WOO: During One Star,
GUN WOO: he practiced so hard.
GUN WOO: I liked him a lot.
[They practiced together and became friends]
[GUN WOO thought they knew each other]
GUN WOO: I haven't decided yet, but...
GUN WOO: I don't know. Let's try it first.
GUN WOO: We have to try it first.
[Will Team Glitch Mode be on stage as usual?]
[The Guider Corps spot something]
CHOI YOUNGJUN: They changed the Polaris.
[Team Glitch Mode changed the Polaris]
YOON: Oh, really?
CHOI YOUNGJUN: They swopped the Polaris.
CHOI YOUNGJUN: It used to be HIJIRI not WANG KUN.
[WANG KUN became the Polaris instead of
HIJIRI]
HANHAE: Yes.
[During the Interim Check]
LEE SEUNG GI: HIJIRI and Wang Kun were
competing for the Polaris.
[When assigning the parts, HIJIRI and Wang Kun
competed for the Polaris]
Yes.
LEE SEUNG GI: It must been a pity for WANG KUN.
WANG KUN: It's okay.
WANG KUN: In the future,
WANG KUN: if his skills are not appreciated,
WANG KUN: I’ll still get the Polaris part.
[After the emergency meeting]
GUN WOO: I think Wang Kun is more flexible.
GUN WOO: About that, what do you think?
HIJIRI: I think
HIJIRI: if other members can do better,
HIJIRI: it's better to
[HIJIRI is giving up the Polaris for the team]
HIJIRI: give the Polaris part to him.
WANG KUN: As long as we do our best for
the crowd.
WANG KUN: We don’t need to worry too much.
WANG KUN: Enjoy the performance.
CHOI YOUNGJUN: Why am I so nervous? I’m nervous.
LEE SEUNG GI: I hope they can do well.
[Glitch Mode by NCT DREAM]
♫Scratch that, bring it back (Shook, shook, hah!)♫
♫In front of you, Glitch Mode♫
♫My entire body is faulty,  reload♫
♫I'm dizzy, dizzy, dizzy, headache♫
♫I spin and spin, I’m in glitch mode♫
♫A never seen before situation♫
♫It's only you or you on repetition♫
♫Trouble trouble like a miscode♫
♫It's a state of emergency♫
♫It’s a bu-buffering♫
♫I'm on that Glitch Mode♫
♫(Hey hey)♫
♫Engine sound, it's dangerous♫
♫A never before experienced pit-a-pat♫
♫You approach, whoop! The whoop!♫
♫Why does my breath stop?♫
♫Accelerating heart, go speeding up♫
♫This emotion, no words, can't get enough♫
♫(Hey hey hey)♫
♫Watch me, I'ma be crazy♫
♫Without even a resistance, hands up♫
♫Reverse it back, into my mind♫
♫Expanding at once, ransom (Okay!)♫
♫Why, why, why is it like this,
This is a fatal situation♫
♫(Ha ha)♫
♫Shutting me down, uncontrollable♫
♫Everyone says I'm too much♫
♫From the sweet, sweet showers you usher in♫
♫My little sprout buds and grows a forest♫
♫Growing up to heaven♫
♫Touching on the Sun♫
♫Regardless of how much they try stop you
you grow♫
♫Trouble trouble like a miscode♫
♫It's a state of emergency♫
♫I'm on that Glitch Mode♫
♫I’m on scratch that, bring it back♫
♫In front of you♫
CHOI YOUNGJUN: XIN CHE's tutting.
[XIN CHE's cute tutting]
[Chu]
[Oh]
♫299 792 per second♫
♫Light Speed Bass Drop Robot Blast♫
♫Start Off♫
♫Light Speed Bass Drop♫
♫Scratch that bring it back♫
♫In front of you, Glitch Mode♫
♫My entire body is faulty,  reload♫
♫I'm dizzy, dizzy, dizzy, headache♫
♫I spin and spin, I'm in glitch mode♫
♫Never seen before situation situation♫
♫It's only you or you on repetition♫
♫Trouble trouble like a miscode♫
♫It's a state of emergency♫
♫It’s a bu-buffering♫
♫I'm on that glitch mode♫
LEE SEUNG GI: You've improved a lot.
[Appearance+Tutting cuteness+Hand attack]
CHOI YOUNGJUN: Face attack and hand attack.
HANHAE: Face attack and hand attack.
HANHAE: That's right.
[Satisfied. Good job]
HUI: Well done. You’ve really improved a lot.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: It's time to vote for this team.
[It's time to vote for this team]
[Team BUTTER with different charisma]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: If you like Team BUTTER
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: with different charisma,
[Team BUTTER 1]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: please press number one.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: If you prefer
[Team Glitch Mode with their viral dance]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: Team NCT DREAM Glitch Mode
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: with their viral dance on stage
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: please press number two.
[Team Glitch Mode 2]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: The voting will last for
five seconds.
[Voting ends]
[Good job.]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: It's time to talk to the Guiders.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: Guider HANHAE.
[What does Guider HANHAE think of
this round?]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG: What do you think of this round?
HANHAE: Let's start with Team BTS BUTTER first.
HANHAE: BUTTER is not an easy song.
[A difficult song with high notes]
HANHAE: So during the Interim Check,
HANHAE: I was quite worried.
LEE SEUNG GI: Compared to what we saw
in the Interim Check,
LEE SEUNG GI: PENTOR has improved a lot.
[PENTOR improved a lot compared to
Interim Check]
LEE SEUNG GI: You've made great progress.
I really appreciate it.
LEE SEUNG GI: But it’s a pity
LEE SEUNG GI: that it seems you're still
[Not focused on either singing or dancing]
LEE SEUNG GI: struggling to focus on
LEE SEUNG GI: dancing and singing.
♫When I look in the mirror♫
[For example, too focused on dancing]
♫I'll melt your heart into two♫
[For example, too focused on dancing,
so his singing wasn't clear]
♫I got that superstar glow♫
LEE SEUNG GI: That part needed more practice.
[Every member has areas needing improvement]
LEE SEUNG GI: But thank you for your hard work.
[As a team, they delivered a stable performance]
EDEN: Thank you.
PENTOR: Thank you.
HUI: Team Glitch Mode
HUI: changed parts many times during practice.
[Team Glitch Mode suffered during practice]
HUI: Right? You've been through a lot.
HUI: Especially GUN WOO,
[Especially GUN WOO]
HUI: you put in so much hard work.
[Especially GUN WOO, you put in so much
hard work]
GUN WOO: Oh, I'm sorry.
LEE JUN HYUK: GUN WOO really worked hard.
[[As friends who saw it]
[As friends who saw it, they can feel GUN WOO's tears]
YOO JUN: It breaks my heart.
HUI: How can I lead the team
and deliver a better performance?
HUI: I can see the thought you've put into
this.
HUI: So I really appreciate it.
[Dance+Vocal, a quality performance]
HUI: You delivered a quality performance.
HUI: Thank you. Thank you.
GUN WOO: Good job.
[I don't think I can dance...]
HIJIRI：Give my position (Polaris) to other members.
HIJIRI：I can't do it well.
[I don't think I can dance and sing at the same time]
[Why can you decide that?]
GUN WOO：Why can you decide that?
GUN WOO：Who are you to make this decision?
[The differences in opinions are getting harder to bridge]
[The rift in their relationship is growing deeper]
[But as a team, they're working together again.]
GUN WOO：Come over at this timing.
[As the leader, GUN WOO leads the team to the end.]
♫In front of you, Glitch Mode♫
GUN WOO：I heard the acknowledge of my hard work in the evaluation
GUN WOO：and I choked up.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Now I'll announce the result.
[It's time to announce the result.]
EDEN：The possibility of Butter winning is higher.
GUN WOO：I hope we win.
[The difference in votes between the two teams]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：The two teams
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：only have a one-vote difference.
[[The difference in votes between the two teams] [Only a vote]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Only a one-vote difference.
EDEN：But when I heard the difference,
EDEN：I couldn’t predict the result at all.
XIN CHE：This vote gave me a lot of pressure.
KIM SEON JAE：I should have looked forward, but I didn't dare to.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Which team will win?
[By a one-vote difference,] [which team will win?]
KIM SEON JAE：Please.
KIM SEON JAE：I can't look anymore.
[Me too]
[I believe we won't lose]
PENTOR：I believe we won’t lose.
WANG KUN：Losing may not be in our dictionary today.
[Losing is not in my dictionary]
[Team Glitch Mode wins]
[Team Glitch Mode receives the benefit]
GUN WOO：Until the last moment, even before we got on the stage,
GUN WOO：I said that the result couldn't be predicted.
GUN WOO：But in the end, we won by one vote,
GUN WOO：and I was so happy in that moment.
["Thank you so much"]
HIJIRI：Thank you so much.
GUN WOO：Good job.
[Choking up]
HIJIRI：GUN WOO
HIJIRI：really did a lot for the team.
HIJIRI：I wanted to thank him sincerely.
[We finally say what we really wanted to say]
GUN WOO：I'm sorry for being too harsh to you.
[And...]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Team Chk Chk Boom VS Team Guerrilla.
[Now]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Now please reveal the result.
[Now, the result is revealed.]
[Team Chk Chk Boom VS Team Guerrilla]
♫Boom♫
[Team Chk Chk Boom shows unexpected charm]
♫Vamos, I know that you want it♫
♫Boom♫
♫Lobos, we cannot stop hunting♫
♫Ratatata I'mma make it Boom♫
♫The Guerrillas (Break the wall)♫
[Team Guerrilla who showcased high energy]
[Who will win this round?]
[Team Chk Chk Boom wins]
KAWK GUN：Awesome!
KAWK GUN：Really?
KAWK GUN：How could this happen?
[Team Chk Chk Boom receives the benefit]
YOO JUN：Good job. Good job.
KAWK GUN：This is not a dream, right?
KAWK GUN：Awesome!
[Complicated feelings]
KAWK GUN：Really?
[Looking back]
[Looking at his teammates standing under the dim light]
LEE JUN HYUK：Ah...
[Feeling sad]
LEE JUN HYUK：Good job guys.
LEE JUN HYUK：What a pity. What a pity.
CHEN XUAN YOU：Let's go home.
LEE JUN HYUK：I just felt it was such a pity.
LEE JUN HYUK：But
LEE JUN HYUK：I won't regret it.
LEE JUN HYUK：I also witnessed DA EUL's growth.
LEE DA EUL：This result
LEE DA EUL：may be my fault.
LEE DA EUL：I feel very sorry towards
LEE DA EUL：my big brothers and teammates.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Who will win?
HIKARI：Thank you for your hard work.
HIKARI：I was so happy.
["I was so happy."]
MICHAEL WU：Not only practicing with him
MICHAEL WU：but also
MICHAEL WU：we are always in the room together.
MICHAEL WU：I think we are very friendly with each other,
MICHAEL WU：very good friends.
[Starlight Boys]
[The first round of competition continues]
[A fierce battle for the benefit]
♫Boom Boom Boom Boom Base♫
HUI：Such a good job.
♫Get hijacked Don't like me then tell me♫
♫How you like that like that♫
♫Sorry Sorry Sorry I I I♫
CHOI YOUNGJUN：Wow, so relaxed.
[The result of this K-POP Generation Battle is?]
KWON EUNBI：Awesome!
[The result of this K-POP Generation Battle is?] [Awesome]
[The result of this K-POP Generation Battle is?]
[The result of each round after the competing performances]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Now, the winning team of each round will be announced.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Who will win?
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Team Boom Boom Bass VS Team Sheesh.
SUN JIA YANG：We will win.
CONGB：We can win.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：Team XXX wins.
[What's the result of Team Boom Boom Bass VS Team Sheesh?]
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：K-POP Generation Battle...
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：the first trainee is...
SHAO ZI HENG：I may get the first place.
YOO GWAN WOO：I think I can get the first place.
HAN GYUL：I think I can be the first.
LEE SUNG KYOUNG：It’s XXX trainee.
[Who is the trainee that shocked everyone?]
[Search “Starlight Project” on iQIYI International for more exciting content]
Search “Starlight Project” on iQIYI International
to enjoy endless exciting projects every week.
[Login to iQIYI International and write a letter to help your beloved boy realize his dream]
Login to iQIYI International to write a letter to the boy you like.
If your letter gets picked,
it will be featured in the “Starlight Boys” project section.
[Download iQIYI's international app for multi-language subtitles]
International members can download iQIYI's international APP with multi-language subtitles
to watch more exclusive videos in advance.
[Join iQIYI VIP to get extra Light-up Chances]
Join iQIYI VIP
to get extra Light-up Chances
and support your favorite Starlight Boys to debut.
[Search #Starlight Boys# on Weibo to check out the boys' wonderful performances together!]
Search #Starlight Boys# on Weibo
to check out the boys' wonderful performances together!
[Rank 47-56]
[Light-up Result on November 7, 2024 at 9 PM (KST)]
[Rank 37-46]
[Rank 23-36]
[Light-up Result on November 7, 2024 at 9 PM (KST)]
[Rank 10-22]
[Rank 01-09]
[Light-up Result on November 7, 2024 at 9 PM (KST)]
♫Boom♫
♫Vamos, I know that you want it♫
♫Lobos, we cannot stop hunting♫
♫Boom♫
♫Ratatata I'mma make it Boom♫
♫Boom Boom Chk Chk Boom♫
♫Boom♫
♫Vamos, I know that you want it♫
♫Chaos, we so catastrophic♫
♫Boom♫
♫Ratatata I'mma make it Boom♫
♫Boom Chk Chk Boom♫
♫I got it back, turn the board over, this game♫
♫One chance right now at this time♫
♫Like that (hoo) Short and intense escape♫
♫No next, just follow me easily (ha ha ha)♫
♫Boring, boring, sick, and tired, again♫
♫Stretch out now, look at the New World (New World)♫
♫Boring, boring, sick, and tired again♫
♫So bored now, so long♫
♫Mm, disappearing emotions♫
♫Mm, expressions are losing the light♫
♫Mm, laughter is controlled♫
♫Only numbness left, no-oh♫
♫Side step, right, left to my beat♫
♫High like the moon, rock with me, baby♫
♫Know that I got that heat♫
♫Let me show you 'cause talk is cheap♫
♫Side step, right, left to my beat♫
♫Get it, let it roll♫
♫Ice on my wrist♫
♫I'm the nice guy♫
♫Got the right body and the right mind♫
♫Rollin' up to party, got the right vibe, smooth like butter♫
♫Hate us (Love us)♫
♫Fresh boy pull up and we lay low♫
♫All the playas get movin' when the bass low♫
♫Got ARMY right behind us when we say so♫
♫Let's go♫
♫Scratch that bring it back (Shook! Shook! Ha)♫
♫In front of you, Glitch Mode♫
♫My entire body is faulty,  reload♫
♫I'm dizzy, dizzy, dizzy, headache♫
♫I spin and spin, Iʼm in Glitch Mode♫
♫A never seen before situation (Mhm)♫
♫It's only you or you on repetition (Mhm)♫
♫Trouble trouble like a miscode♫
♫It's a state of emergency♫
♫It’s a bu-buffering♫
♫I'm on that Glitch Mode♫
♫(Hey hey)♫