♫ Grudges and karma, right and wrong ♫
♫ Tears and blood in the past life ♫
♫ A parting lasting for years ♫
♫ Keeps the truth hidden ♫
♫ Fate is full of twists and turns ♫
♫ Misfortune and happiness intertwined ♫
♫ Let the wind take away obsessions and lies ♫
♫ Through storms and uncertainties,
I devote myself to you ♫
♫ At least you share my joy and sorrow ♫
♫ Unraveling mystery fearlessly in this dream ♫
♫ Hand in hand with you,
I wander this splendid world ♫
♫ My heart remains untainted
by the mortal dust ♫
[Melody of Golden Age]
[Episode 31]
Unlimited expenses don't mean
that the corrupt officials
can line their own pockets.
I wonder how many people are involved.
It could probably shake
the entire imperial court.
They've completely enraged
the Empress Dowager.
It's a sensitive matter.
Nothing has happened yet.
I'm afraid the Empress Dowager plans
to investigate secretly
and eradicate the problem.
So what should we
do now?
They might find me
disrespectful for rejecting the marriage.
I'm afraid I will be sidelined.
You won't despise me for this, right?
I'm afraid
I can't find someone more shrewd than you.
Nor can you find someone
who loves you more than I do.
By the Empress Dowager's decree,
the Imperial Guards
will look into Princess Runing
and Prince Xian,
and monitor the Imperial Inspectorate.
Is the Empress Dowager
suspecting Prince Xian?
It's probably not just that.
By the Empress Dowager's decree,
the Imperial Inspectorate
shall secretly look into the Zhou family
and keep an eye on the Princess of Valor.
Report everything
without holding back.
Also, monitor the Imperial Guards in secret.
If anything comes up,
report it immediately.
I accept Her Majesty's decree.
Madam Xu.
I've prepared some fine tea from Junshan Island
brewed with snow water
from the Tianshan Mountains.
Won't you stay for some tea?
The tea is too cold in nature.
What a pity I can't taste it.
Vice Minister Lai, please stay.
I hope you carry out
the Empress Dowager's order
cautiously and prudently
without any mistakes.
Thank you for your kind reminder, Madam Xu.
Great tea.
Shen Du had the nerve to turn down
the marriage bestowed by Mother Express.
I have underestimated Yan Xing.
How interesting.
I didn't expect the cold and merciless Shen Du
to actually fall in love.
Anyway,
it's good news for us.
If the Imperial Guards
side with the Princess of Valor,
it will be even harder
for you to obtain
the position of Prince Regent.
Don't you find it weird
that Mother Empress hasn't punished
Shen Du severely?
After Mo Qianzhi died, the position
of Yingzhou Governor remained vacant.
I heard that
Shen Du had been attacked
before he returned to Xiang'an.
He entered the palace
to see Mother Empress overnight.
After that,
he was bestowed with a marriage.
Too much of a coincidence.
I wonder what secrets Shen Du
has discovered in Yingzhou.
I believe that
the Empress Dowager grew distant
from Shen Du due to his refusal.
She barely summons him these days.
Some palace maids have reached the age
to be sent back to their hometowns.
The Empress Dowager summoned Lai Luozhi
and bestowed several maids upon him.
It's obvious that Lai Luozhi
is favored
by the Empress Dowager nowadays.
The Imperial Inspectorate will eventually
overpower the Imperial Guards.
It is too early to say that.
Zhang Baohuan suddenly fell ill.
It's very fishy.
Sir.
I feel that something huge
is brewing in the court.
People are unfathomable.
I'll keep a closer watch
on the Princess of Valor.
Uncle Lan, he is a friend.
Men of Dacang are not to be trusted.
He is also after that person.
The Saintess Daisi wasn't the only victim.
You believe in him?
Yes, I do.
Here.
Thank you.
Uncle Lan.
You served Saintess Daisi for many years.
We want to know
what happened back then
in detail.
It's been over ten years.
Back then, Daisi was
still the saintess of the Jinwu Tribe.
After the Jinwu Tribe sent envoys
to pay homage to Dacang,
Dacang also sent envoys
to Jinwu in return.
The Jinwu Tribe and Dacang have been
in touch ever since.
The common folks were free
to travel back and forth.
Once the saintess
was doing charity work
on the street…
Easy. There's enough for everyone.
That's when she met that person.
It was just a random encounter.
The saintess didn't pay much attention to it
and soon forgot about it
after she returned.
Because she was a saintess
who was bound for life not to marry
or fall in love with anyone.
She lived solely for the people of Jinwu.
But somehow,
they met again very soon.
But this time,
they met at the court banquet
of the Jinwu Tribe.
(How could it be such a coincidence?)
- Saintess.
- The saintess had rarely met any men.
She was innocent and pure.
But once she fell in love,
she was like a wild horse
breaking free of its reins.
After the welcome banquet,
during the days that the envoys stayed,
[Daisi]
Daisi had frequent contact
with the envoys of Dacang as the saintess.
And she did that
to get close to that man from Dacang.
What is this?
Daisi. Your name.
Unexpectedly, this man
proposed
to learn the Jinwu language from the saintess.
This man from Dacang
was gifted in language learning.
In just seven to eight days,
he learned quite a bit.
And then,
the saintess learned that man's name.
Those three characters
should be etched
in her memory.
But it remained a blur no matter
how hard she tried to recall it.
Their feelings for each other grew day by day.
Very soon,
they became deeply affectionate.
But the saintess had her duties.
In the presence of others,
she had to restrain herself.
But at that point,
all she could see and think about
was that man from Dacang.
She forgot
all about her duties.
But good times don't last.
Trouble arose
very soon.
Will you come to Dacang with me?
I know you have a special status.
I've used all my luck
just to meet you.
How could I ask for more?
No. I will go with you.
Of course, I will.
From then on,
the saintess
could no longer be found.
Some said they saw her
dressed in the attire of a Dacang woman,
riding a horse towards Dacang,
following that man.
Jinwu did not want it to be a scandal
and proclaimed that
the saintess passed away due to illness
and erased her identity.
After that, the Jinwu Tribe
severed its tie with Dacang.
I thought that
this man from Dacang
and the saintess
would be together for life.
But to my surprise,
not long after,
I saw the dying saintess
right in this dilapidated house.
Saintess.
Saintess, what happened?
I am no longer the saintess.
Saintess.
Come back with me.
Everything will be fine.
It's too late.
Where is he? Where is that man?
He deceived me.
He tricked me
into revealing the secret I should keep
and teaching him how to
control moths with medicinal powder.
I was such a fool.
Why did I fall for the trick?
When I discovered that
he bore evil intentions,
practiced evil crafts,
and even tried to manipulate others
with those crafts to do his bidding,
he harbored the intent to kill me.
Saintess.
It's too late.
Everything is too late now.
I've sinned gravely.
- Death will do me justice.
- No!
Saintess.
This man truly deserves the most painful death.
Calm down first.
Sooner or later we will catch him
and expose him to the world.
Uncle Lan.
Check these and see if he
looks like anyone in there.
This man.
[Imperial Inspectorate]
It's him.
It's the man from Dacang.
You found him?
Where is he?
- I'm going to kill him.
- Uncle Lan.
Leave it to us.
Rest assured.
I will definitely
make him pay the price
to do Saintess Daisi justice.
Are you watching, saintess?
That man did so many evil deeds.
Surely, karma will get him.
He shall die a miserable death.
Saintess Daisi
once saw that treacherous man
teaching someone to burn down
a granary with evil crafts.
The saintess denounced him
for harming the people of Dacang.
Yet that treacherous man scoffed and said that
the one who harmed the people of Dacang
wasn't him,
but…
but
the Empress Dowager
of Dacang.
And the one who made him burn the granary
was the Empress Dowager's close relative
from the Zhou family.
When Saintess Daisi fled,
she took the token of communication
between the man
and the arsonist.
It is this jade pendant.
Yan Xing.
I hope it's not too late.
Empress Dowager.
I have something to report.
Minister Lai, what is it?
I wish to impeach Sun Tan,
the Marshal of Inspectors in Gannandao,
for dereliction of duty.
Sun Tan led the inspectors
in Gannandao to investigate the case
of the Half-faced Demon
as I have personally witnessed.
How did someone with merit
end up guilty in your story?
Empress Dowager.
I gathered evidence of Sun Tan
abusing his power
and profiteering from bribery.
I'm presenting them to you.
Please have a look.
The laws of the Dacang regulate that
taking what is not one's own is theft.
The governor shall not
embezzle public property or accept bribery.
Those who accept bribes
shall be hanged to death.
Sun Tan abused his power
to amass wealth and collude with bandits.
The evidence is conclusive.
Empress Dowager, please allow me
to put him on sentence.
Empress Dowager.
The Imperial Inspectorate
may have convicted the suspect through torture.
Has Sun Tan really
committed such a heinous crime?
Please look into it.
Great Chief Shen.
Your courthouse is also known
as the Devil's Court.
You have cruel tortures just like we do.
But now,
you pretend to be merciful
to protect the criminal, Sun Tan.
Why is that?
Enough.
I'm a bit tired now.
Leave the evidence behind.
We will discuss it another day.
- I take my leave.
Leave us alone.
Prince Xia--
One must be concentrated when pruning
branches and leaves.
What do you think?
Doesn't it look much better than before?
Your Highness…
Your Highness.
Lai Luozhi has been dominating the court
and detaining officials
with random accusations.
Now he's even reached out to Gannandao.
Judging by his conduct,
he will be a great threat to you
even if you become the Prince Regent.
Should I find someone to impeach him
at the court meeting tomorrow?
Prime Minister Zhang.
Withered leaves will eventually fall.
Even if we stop the autumn breeze,
can we stop the winter snow?
What do you mean, Prince Xian?
Nothing.
These people from Xichen and Nanlang
showed up recently, right?
Yeah, people from all walks of life are coming
from all over the world.
These people from Xichen and Nanlang
came to Xiang'an for a living some time ago.
Pay extra attention
during the patrol.
Understood.
Your Highness.
It's Shen Du.
I really can't stand it.
How dare the White Ghost
openly turn down the marriage
and embarrass Princess Jia'an?
Your Highness.
You shouldn't let him off easily.
Shen Du
is just like his father.
They don't know what's good for them.
Mother Empress was kind to him.
Yet he didn't know
the importance
of seeking support from a patron.
You've watched Jia'an grow up,
spending more time with her
than I have as her mother.
Naturally, you would feel for her.
The dignity of the royal family
matters the most.
Mother Empress has been humiliated.
Things won't be easy
for Shen Du even if
we don't make a move.
Liuniang.
You are the best.
You've become a Chief Director,
yet you still help me sort out the files.
Have you ever
looked down on me
as a Senior Clerk
when I was nobody?
Right.
Try this.
You brought it from Gannandao?
It's much sweeter than the ones in Xiang'an.
Here.
The honey from Gannandao
is exceptionally sweet.
It's not only used for fruits
but also human flesh.
Yan Liuniang.
I hate you.
Lu Chuichui.
How dare you let Director Yan
sort out the files for you?
What were you thinking?
Didn't you use to boss Director Yan around?
I…
That was in the past.
Right, Director Yan?
Director Yan.
Times have changed.
Now we are
colleagues of the same rank.
And you are married to the Great Chief.
Therefore, I will count on you
to look after me from now on.
Please don't say that, Director Wu.
Her Majesty was kind enough
to make me the Chief Director by honor,
but I'm still a staff
of the Ministry of Justice.
I still follow
your instructions to work on cases.
I'll count on you
to take good care of me.
Fair enough.
Your endless cliche
is making me sick.
Feng Gui.
Take a seat.
Since you still see me as the director,
I think I should
give you some advice.
Now that you are married to Great Chief
and promoted,
you've become the leading female official.
But as the old saying goes,
"It doesn't last long
to burn oil with fierce fire."
Do you know that
the Empress Dowager
favors the Black Fiend
over the White Ghost now?
Look at you.
The wives of other high officials
are adept at dealing with people
to learn secrets
that may be useful for their husbands.
Who is silly enough
to bury her head
in files and stay in the morgue
all day long?
I'm just saying.
Vice Minister Lai is in power
and he's arresting officials quite often.
The Empress Dowager
indulges and spoils Vice Minister Lai
more than she does with Zhang Baohuan.
The Empress Dowager never refuses
his request for arrest.
The court officials all feel threatened.
How can Lai Luozhi be so autocratic?
So,
Liuniang.
Think about it.
How can the Black Fiend
allow the White Ghost
to be on an equal footing
with him?
To be honest, even if it were me,
I would surely hope
that there's only one
merciless law enforcer.
Thank you for the reminder, Director Wu.
The more
I know my husband,
the more I realize that
he's treading on thin ice
in that high position.
I don't know court politics.
Nor do I know how to help.
I can only do my job well
to not cause him any trouble.
You don't
cause him trouble?
Lai Luozhi is killing innocent people.
Can't anyone do something?
- What's going on?
- Marshal Xu.
If you refuse to deal with it,
I'll ask the Empress Dowager
in the imperial palace
whether Dacang is still
ruled by law.
Shut up.
Get back to work.
I don't care if you're suicidal.
But our staff and I don't want to
have our ears cut off by the Black Fiend
in the middle of the night.
Mr. Xu.
What happened?
Lai Luozhi arrested Sun Tan.
Sun Tan?
The Marshal of Inspectors of Gannandao?
Wasn't his file delivered
to the Dali Supreme Court
just after the court meeting?
The Empress Dowager hasn't given a verdict.
How could they arrest him already?
The Imperial Inspectorate took him
into custody without a verdict.
But one day
in the Imperial Inspectorate's prison
means ten fewer years to live.
If it goes on like this,
Sun Tan might be dead before
the Empress Dowager gives a verdict.
Vice Minister Lai has been dominant
for a very long time.
In the end, it's up to the Dali Supreme Court.
Aren't you crying to
the wrong people here?
Don't you know the staff
at the Dali Supreme Court?
They're timid and afraid of trouble.
This case was initiated
by the Imperial Inspectorate
and it involves the inspectors.
They have already handed it over to you.
They handed it over…
Headache. Feng Gui…
I am here. What's wrong?
Director Wu, rest and recover.
If the Ministry of Justice
can't do my buddy justice,
I don't mind barging into the palace again.
- Slowly.
- Let's go.
Director Wu isn't
any more courageous
than those at the Dali Supreme Court.
You're trying your luck with the wrong person.
Yun Que.
Why are you with Marshal Xu?
I am also an inspector.
Why can't I be with Marshal Xu?
Go back to work.
Understood.
I take my leave.
Mr. Xu.
You have always been outspoken.
Why are you so cautious today?
Don't you remember
that I'm also the Sixth-Tier
Chief Director
of the Ministry of Justice?
Speaking of ranks,
I'm on a par with Director Wu.
I also have the authority to try cases.
I can apply to be
the presiding judge.
I knew it.
Ask Liuniang for help.
Liuniang.
Aren't you going to
offend Lai Luozhi?
Didn't you say you wouldn't
cause trouble for Shen Du?
Yeah.
I just said I wouldn't cause him trouble.
Liuniang, I know
things are tricky
in the court nowadays.
Shen Du must be having a hard time.
You'd better
stay out of it.
But it concerns you.
And Sun Tan has helped us
a lot in Gannandao.
He would help us
if we were in trouble.
Liuniang, thank you.
Since I've agreed to help,
we must plan it carefully.
Follow me.
Let's go.
Vice Minister.
That Sun Tan is tough.
We've tried everything that doesn't kill him,
yet he still refuses to talk.
Since when did we
become
so soft and lenient?
It doesn't matter whether he confesses.
As long as he is not in Gannandao,
the inspectors there
won't be able to do anything.
Whoever tries to block my path
will have a taste of my fierce measures.
Mr. Xu, do you know what solid evidence
Lai Luozhi has against Sun Tan?
Do you know how we became inspectors?
The court recruits chivalries
for investigation and arrest.
Exactly.
We managed to spread our network everywhere
and secured more access
to information than the court officials
because we were recruited
as people from all walks of life
in the first place.
Before we were recruited,
many were bandits who robbed people
or skilled thieves
with nimble fingers like me.
We couldn't just sever our ties
with our old friends.
Lai Luozhi could easily
pin any charges on anyone.
I'm worried that
Sun Tan isn't the only target in this case.
Lai Luozhi may have been
arrogant and domineering,
but he has never dared to provoke us.
But Gannandao was in dire need
of reconstruction
after the case was solved
and he arrested Sun Tan.
Was he targeting the inspectors
or Gannandao?
Liuniang, you just came back
and may not know
what had happened in Xiang'an.
Mingsheng Temple,
where Princess Runing resides,
is often visited
by the carriages of Princess of Valor.
Princess Runing and Princess Yong'an?
His Majesty is young and slow to speak.
How much longer can the Empress Dowager
reign over Dacang?
Nowadays, many people believe
that the Princess of Valor is more likely
to gain power than Prince Xian.
Has Princess Runing decided
to support the Princess of Valor?
Princess Runing
holds the highest status in the Xiao family.
If she takes a stance,
it'll surely change the dynamics in the court.
Moreover, the reconstruction of the Ming Hall
was close to an end,
yet they slowed it down.
You can even say that
they've stopped the work.
It happened shortly after we returned
from Gannandao?
Also,
Xiang'an has seen
a lot more foreigners
from Nanlang and Xichen recently.
Each thing may seem
quite random on its own.
But if you connect them…
Could there be
some connections there?
Liuniang.
I stand by what I said.
So many people in the court
are watching you and your husband.
I bet you know that.
I won't blame you if you decide
not to help me.
Mr. Xu,
we survived multiple attacks
on the way back from Yingzhou
thanks to the help of the inspectors.
If not for this token,
I wouldn't be able to see you today.
It's time to return it
to its rightful owner.
Liuniang.
Sun Tan may not come out
of the Imperial Inspectorate
unscathed.
But if he has been wronged
or has something to say,
I will surely help him.
Can you help me
see him?
I will draft an application
to be the presiding judge right now.
Sun Tan may be locked up
in the Imperial Inspectorate,
but the presiding judge
should at least be able to question him.
Liuniang.
I will join you.
He's… he's bleeding so much.
Will he die?
Do you think anyone
would care about his life and death here?
Go back and wait for me if you're scared.
I am Yan Xing,
Chief Director of the Ministry of Justice,
who's presiding over Sun Tan's case.
I'm here to summon Sun Tan for interrogation.
Sun Tan is under custody here.
I'm afraid you have no right to summon him.
Can I at least interrogate him in the cell?
Only two people are allowed in.
Wait for me at the Ministry of Justice.
Then I'll wait for you outside.
[Imperial Inspectorate]
Marshal Sun.
It's me.
Yan Xing.
Have you joined that villain?
I am made the presiding judge.
I'm here to do you justice.
The Imperial Inspectorate
accuses you of accepting bribes
and colluding with bandits.
Tell me if you're wronged.
I'll report it.
It's pointless.
If there is injustice,
Marshal Xu and the other inspectors
will risk their lives to rescue you.
I will also give it my all
to seek justice for you.
The more you help, the more people die.
Just leave.
Sun Tan.
I'm not dead yet.
Marshal Xu.
[Marshal of Inspectors]
This token
is still waiting for you.
Hang in there.
[Marshal of Inspectors]
Director Yan, I have something to say.
Okay.
Okay, I'll take notes.
Most of the inspectors
came from all walks of life.
We were all captivated by Marshal Xu's aura
and joined the group as inspectors.
In Gannandao,
I naturally hoped to build wide connections
with the talented as Marshal Xu did.
So-called "collusion with bandits".
What about accepting the bribes?
This I can't deny.
I did take money.
Gannandao has many merchants coming and going.
We inspectors
protect them from bandits.
They pay us to show their gratitude.
I used that money
to treat my buddies.
You can defend yourself and find the merchants
to testify for you
to get a lighter sentence.
Liuniang.
How come you just don't get it?
Lai Luozhi wants to take out the leader
of the inspectors in Gannandao.
Marshal Sun.
Do you know the reason?
After Mo Qianzhi died,
Lai Luozhi put his people
in Yingzhou as officials.
Gannandao is on a key location at the border
leading directly to Xichen.
People can even take a detour
via Gannandao all the way from Nanlang.
Without the inspectors there,
the border…
Xiang'an has seen
a lot more foreigners from Nanlang and Xichen.
It seems Lai Luozhi
intends to dominate Gannandao.
But what he's aiming for
is far beyond that area.
He's probably plotting with foreign powers
to commit treason.
Marshal Xu.
You'll need evidence even if
you want to frame me.
Mrs. Shen.
You came to visit my workplace,
yet you kept slandering me.
It really put me in a difficult position.
As the presiding judge of this case,
I tried the main suspect Sun Tan
and recorded his testimony
based on the procedure.
The inspector accompanied me for assistance.
There was nothing inappropriate.
Is that so?
Mrs. Shen seems to have
become more sharp-tongued.
That was the preliminary trial.
Once I organize the case files
and hand in the report,
I will be back for the second trial.
Vice Minister Lai, you are obliged to ensure
the safety of the suspect.
It depends on his fate.
No one can be guaranteed
to stay alive in our jail here.
How dare you!
Marshal Xu.
Director Yan.
Go back.
I don't intend to keep you
and Mrs. Shen here today.
Don't be so nervous.
However, I do have a word of advice.
The criminals arrested
by the Imperial Inspectorate
won't be freed so easily.
You'd better think twice
about what to note down,
what to report,
and what to keep to yourselves.
♫ One glance affirms the fate between us ♫
♫ Upon meeting again,
I know you're the one for me ♫
♫ Gaze at the stars,
dreaming about the old times ♫
♫ We are forever bound ♫
♫ Before the candlelight,
do not ask my thoughts ♫
♫ Affection binds us, forever and ever ♫
♫ The evening breeze tells of my deep love ♫
♫ From now on, I have someone to cherish ♫
♫ With deep affection, you are the one for me ♫
♫ I share the autumn moon
and spring breeze only with you ♫
♫ Your palm lines ♫
♫ Your gaze ♫
♫ Our love is deepening ♫
♫ With deep affection, you are the one for me ♫
♫ I share the autumn moon
and spring breeze only with you ♫
♫ Your palm lines ♫
♫ Your gaze ♫
♫ Our love is deepening ♫
♫ You are the one for me ♫
♫ Embracing each other,
how serious we are about our love ♫
♫ Every moment is treasured ♫
♫ From dawn to dusk ♫
♫ You and I, forever inseparable ♫
♫ You've stormed into my world ♫
♫ Growing immersed,
I become reckless for love ♫
♫ I break through obstacles
with unmatched resilience ♫
♫ Because you are my responsibility ♫
♫ With deep affection, you are the one for me ♫
♫ I share the autumn moon
and spring breeze only with you ♫
♫ Your palm lines ♫
♫ Your gaze ♫
♫ Our love is deepening ♫
♫ With deep affection, you are the one for me ♫
♫ I share the autumn moon
and spring breeze only with you ♫
♫ Your palm lines ♫
♫ Your gaze ♫
♫ Our love is deepening ♫
♫ You are the one for me ♫