LOVE & CROWN
ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL "MY QUEEN"
BY XIE LOUNAN
EPISODE 8
All the poisons
have already been destroyed.
Why then does the Begonia Pendant
still react so strangely?
Could it be that there are still
other toxins hidden within the palace?
Princess Ying's mind is unclear.
Her words cannot be taken as truth.
Your Majesty, Your Highness,
I mean no disrespect.
It is by His Majesty's command.
Should a single lamp
be lit in this cold palace,
a guard's life must be taken in exchange.
I'm truly fearful.
Ying.
Ying. Ying.
I'm your brother.
I have come to see you.
Qianqing!
Come.
Ying.
It's so cold,
remember to keep your shoes on
from now on.
Ying. Stop painting.
Your brother and I have come to see you.
Ying.
I brought you osmanthus
and red bean dumplings.
After you eat them,
you should go to sleep early.
How did you know I like these?
Who are you?
Then do you want to eat them?
When I've killed them all, then I'll eat.
Kill whom?
Why don't you help me,
and kill them all?
Mother, this teacup is exquisite.
Fine porcelain, so clear and delicate.
Ying's illness has always come and gone.
After much effort to nurse her,
her confusion still outweighs her clarity.
That Xiao Huan
is determined to take our lives!
Mother.
Ying gave poison to the Empress,
and attempted to assassinate His Majesty.
She was only punished by ten days
without lighting a lamp.
That punishment
is already merciful enough.
Ying has never been of sound mind.
- But why did she become this way?
- You know the reason well.
Had it not been for that great fire
at Luling Palace back then,
when Xiao Huan abandoned her,
she would never
have been so deeply scarred.
Then why did Luling Palace
suddenly burn for no reason?
What do you mean by that?
You are my own flesh and blood,
the child I carried for ten months,
born through hardship and pain.
Do you not know why,
or for whom, I have done all this?
So Mother has always known
the truth behind Ying's madness,
yet chose never to tell her,
encouraging her
instead to resent His Majesty.
Is this, Mother,
what you call love for me and Ying?
So,
it is because of your sister's matter
that you have borne a grudge
against me all this time.
You were in Southern Chu
for so many years,
yet not once did you send a letter home.
Whatever I asked you to do,
you brushed aside carelessly, and even
stood against me.
Mother. You speak too harshly.
Does it hurt?
It does not.
Mother,
please be at ease.
Now that I have returned,
I shall protect you and my sister
with all that I am.
I will never let
either of you suffer again.
The injustice Ying endured,
I will never forget.
Well? Did you meet His Majesty?
Does that mean I can stop practicing?
Look at me, do I look like I've met him?
Then what should we do?
His Majesty could summon
Song Lanxi at any moment.
He values him so highly.
Even if I practice until I'm perfect,
the moment His Majesty
sees the real one, I'll be exposed.
His Majesty is gravely ill now.
He is unlikely to grant
an audience for the time being.
As for you, put your mind
to practicing your calligraphy first.
We'll talk once you've fooled
the officials in the Capital.
Come, show me.
Your writing does resemble his,
yet it still lacks spirit.
Anyone who has seen Song Lanxi's true work
will see through it at a glance.
Song Lanxi is a master of calligraphy.
A four chi scroll of his sells for
more than a hundred liang of silver.
How could that be copied so easily?
At the start, you insisted
on accompanying me to the Capital.
You boasted
as if nothing were beyond your ability.
I said I wished to go to
the Capital with you,
but did I say I meant
to impersonate Song Lanxi?
If you think my writing is poor,
do it yourself if you can.
This robe of mine is suited to
the Dragon Boat Festival season.
It is costly and difficult to make, you…
What now?
- What are you doing?
- Do not move.
TURTLE
Do not be angry, Your Highness.
Please look.
This is the character
I have practiced for over a month,
the one that most resembles his writing.
TURTLE
Here.
Characters like this,
how many can you write?
I can write not many.
- About two hundred or so…
- Two hundred or so?
Come, write them all for me.
Quickly. Sit.
Come, write.
Your Highness, you're blocking the light.
I can't have anyone standing here
when I'm writing.
Fine.
Hurry and write.
For the Grand Tutor's kindness to me,
I would give my body and soul,
and repay it fully.
At the palace examination,
I will take first place.
Good.
You may go.
Well? Any word of Cangcang?
She claimed she was going to
the Summer Palace,
but went to the Sword Cottage instead.
It seems her visit to
the Sword Cottage isn't simple.
Then Father means…
Regarding Li Lu's death,
she has never let it go.
How is the truth
she seeks coming along?
Master.
I miss you.
The longer I stay in the palace,
the more I miss
the carefree days I had here.
But you're gone.
Xiao Huan won't even give me a reason.
Master,
what exactly were you all hiding from me?
The imperial family is heartless,
yet Xiao Huan keeps helping me.
Why is that?
Why did you kill my master?
I promised him I wouldn't tell you.
What did you say?
What aren't you allowed to tell me?
What are you all hiding from me?
You're back, little glutton.
What do you want to eat?
I will make it for you.
Master, is it ready?
What gift are you giving me?
You may open your eyes now.
What a beautiful pendant.
This is a protector I give you.
You must keep it with you from now on.
Well? Do you like it?
I do.
Father never remembers my birthday.
Master is much better than Father.
Thank you, Master. I really like it.
As long as you like it.
Master,
can you tell me
why Xiao Huan
had to kill you?
Who?
Luo.
Cangcang.
Speak. Why are you here?
I came to pay my respects too,
to share a drink with him.
But Master never drank Bamboo Leaf Green.
Are you really here to pay respects?
Cangcang,
Father
was worried about you.
Luo,
do you still remember this pendant?
This Begonia Pendant
was given to me by Master.
He said it would keep me safe.
I remember.
I only learned recently
that it is a treasure beyond price.
With it on me,
no poison can get close.
Master was protecting me all along.
But I do not even know why he died.
I do not even know why he died!
Am I that useless?
Cang…
Cangcang.
I remember when I was little,
I loved leaning against this forge.
No matter how cold it was outside,
it was always warm here.
Tell me,
when have you ever approached me
without a purpose?
No, My Lady. It was Father…
Master forged the Rex Sword for you
and you used that very sword to kill him.
- How am I supposed to trust you again?
- I…
How am I supposed
to grow old at your side,
to live with you in harmony?
Since I became empress,
I've swallowed every grievance.
In the palace,
there hasn't been a single day
I didn't try to uncover the truth!
Tell me the truth!
Do you want me to hate you
for the rest of my life?
Do you
not want to hate me?
I…
I don't want to hate you.
I don't want to hate you!
I hate myself.
Once,
I even thought
of roaming the world with you,
sword in hand.
Leave.
Go!
Stay away from me.
I don't want to see you.
Master.
Master…
I want to…
I want to learn sword-forging from you.
I'll stay here
and wait for you.
So,
you still love him.
After everything,
you still…
You still love him.
Cangcang, you're awake.
You drank too much last night.
Cangcang,
do you remember what you said last night?
What did I say?
You didn't say anything.
Strange, I remember
it being so warm here last night.
How come this morning,
now that the sun is out,
it's suddenly chilly?
I remember there was a cellar
at home once,
just like this,
warm in winter and cool in summer.
Strange,
why is there a cold draft here?
Cangcang.
Could it be there's a cellar here too?
Let's look.
Cangcang.
Try this.
It's so cold.
Why is the wind so strong?
Could it be there's a cellar underneath,
connected to Sword Cottage?
Take out the sword.
I didn't expect Master
had hidden a place like this.
Cangcang, look.
These belong to Tang.
Every time I mentioned Tang,
Master would say it was in the past.
But in his heart, he never really let go.
This is…
This isn't Master's wife.
I remember how she looked,
round-faced,
with a mole at the corner of her mouth.
Then this…
How could her portrait be here
with Master?
These eyebrows and eyes,
why do they look so familiar?
Cangcang, let's verify this later.
This is the Ghost King's mask.
How could it be
in your master's Sword Cottage?
This is…
How could this be?
Cangcang, look at this.
STONE MAN PRACTICING GU ARTS
Stone Man…
Secret art…
This is the secret art
of the Ghost King of the Lingbi Sect.
Could it be that Mr. Li Lu is…
Impossible.
I don't believe it!
How many days has the Empress been away?
Report to Your Majesty,
it's been fewer than five days.
Any news?
None that I've heard.
Your Majesty.
Has the Empress sent any word back?
Her Majesty's letters are not here,
but there are a few of
Mr. Song Lanxi's writings
that leaked from
the Prince of Yuzhang's Manor.
Why would Song Lanxi
be staying in the manor?
He said he was injured on the road
and needed to recuperate at the manor.
I have received some good news.
Though perhaps not entirely good news.
Some bad…
- Though not exactly bad.
- What news?
His Majesty just issued an order:
Because he is seriously ill,
the final imperial exam is postponed.
It's good news.
But I wonder, could it be
because he discovered something?
Impersonating Song Lanxi in the Capital
is a capital offense.
I am also complicit.
Naturally, I shall protect you.
If you want to go, go yourself.
I'm not going.
After Ling Cangcang entered the palace,
the first gift she received…
Do you know what it was?
What was it?
A finger of her adoptive brother,
Luo Xianxue.
So,
you may not trust me.
Between us, there is no common interest.
However, we share a common enemy.
Then what should we do?
If he discovers
I'm impersonating Song Lanxi,
you must save me.
Your Highness,
Mr. Xu Feng, requests an audience.
Which Mr. Xu?
- No.
He is a student of Mr. Ling Xuefeng.
Ling Xuefeng?
What should we do?
Your Highness,
I heard that Mr. Song Lanxi
has been ill for a long time,
and Grand Tutor Ling is very concerned.
This is Physician Liu,
a miraculous healer.
Grand Tutor specifically sent him here
to diagnose Mr. Song.
To be honest,
Mr. Song's condition is indeed serious.
To be precise,
on the way here,
he was attacked by assassins,
and the injuries were severe.
Then, in that case,
please summon Mr. Song.
Mr. Song, have you disguised yourself?
Mr. Song was severely injured
on the head and neck
when on the way to the Capital.
His vocal cords were damaged,
and he cannot speak for now.
Since the injuries are severe,
- Physician Liu, please take care of him.
- Yes.
Mr. Song was attacked in the night,
and was greatly frightened.
Since then, he has refused
any physical contact with others.
Mr. Song,
I have admired you for a long time.
Your calligraphy is renowned
throughout the land.
Now that I see you,
I wonder if you might grant me
a few characters.
This…
Mr. Song's calligraphy
was already circulated yesterday.
Why can't he display it publicly today?
Xu Feng, you are taking this too far!
But
since you are Grand Tutor Ling's student,
I naturally have to show him some respect.
Mr. Song,
what do you think?
Someone, bring ink and brushes.
WUYING HALL
CALLIGRAPHY OF SONG LANXI
Song Lanxi has always been modest.
Why has so much calligraphy
been circulated?
It is said that too many people
came to request his writing,
and Prince of Yuzhang had no choice
but to ask Mr. Song to comply.
I doubt it.
Your Majesty, what seems off?
Along the way,
there were too many strange things.
Since Your Majesty is doubtful,
then when the Prince of Yuzhang came
to request an audience a few days ago,
why didn't you ask directly?
I had just punished Xiao Ying,
and if I saw him now,
wouldn't it only cause trouble?
After all this time,
unable to master a single character of Xi.
Your Highness.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF, SONG LAN
Song Lanxi of the Western Garden
in Guzhou,
a character worth a thousand gold coins.
This writing is now given to you.
Since that's the case,
I wish Mr. Song a speedy recovery.
Your Highness, I take my leave.
I'm suffocating.
No.
I nearly died of fright!
If Xu Feng found out, I'd be finished!
If I'm caught impersonating
an imperial official,
how many heads do I have
for Xiao Huan to chop off?
I can't believe you even know that!
How dare you let Zhong Lin
impersonate Song Lanxi?
Song Lanxi was assassinated
by your father-in-law.
If I hadn't done it,
how could I have kept it from him?
Kept it from him, or kept it from me?
As soon as I returned,
I came straight to the palace
to confess to you.
But you refused to see me.
I haven't yet punished you
for failing to protect him,
and you blame me instead.
Fine. Fine.
Then please punish me, Your Majesty.
It would be best to punish
Zhong Lin's crime along with mine.
Are you trying to use
Zhong Lin to threaten me?
I wouldn't dare.
Zhong Lin is just a commoner.
How could she
possibly threaten Your Majesty?
But I heard that
the Empress misses her dearly.
Then you will bear Zhong Lin's crime.
Your Highness, you just saw for yourself.
Ling Xuefeng's people already believe
that Song Lanxi
is living safely in my manor.
If you punish me now,
wouldn't that cause pain
to loved ones and joy to enemies?
So this is your plan.
You're using Ling Xuefeng to pressure me.
I wouldn't dare.
If Ling Xuefeng knew that
Song Lanxi was dead,
it would benefit neither of us.
Why not maintain the lie together?
You truly have a lot of nerve.
Your Majesty, please calm your anger.
I am trembling with fear.
Having me cover the lie for you
is not entirely impossible.
But you must do
one thing for me in return.
What is it?
Have you heard of Li Chengtian?
Li Chengtian?
He was once a senior minister
in the court.
After losing to Ling Xuefeng,
he retired to the countryside.
Yet his name remains illustrious
among the gentry.
Many upright officials in the court
were his students.
Song Lanxi was also his student.
Indeed.
Your Majesty is truly cunning
and strategic.
So Song Lanxi was merely
a lure to draw out Li Chengtian.
Ling Xuefeng killed his beloved student.
What would he feel?
Your Majesty intends for me to summon
Master Li out of retirement.
What do you think?
TAKE CARE, SONG LAN
Greetings, Father.
Song Lanxi is not dead.
Impossible. I personally struck him down.
TAKE CARE, SONG LAN
This is Song Lanxi's calligraphy.
Since you personally attacked him,
there must be hidden circumstances.
I will investigate further.
Get up.
All traces of Li Lu's interactions with us
should be cleared away.
Rest assured, Father.
Everything has been properly handled.
But…
I know you cannot bear it.
And as a father, neither can I.
Yet this is the truth
she most wishes to know.
It is also what she must face.
But Young Lady refuses to believe that
Li Lu is the Ghost King,
thinking instead that someone framed him.
- Who does she suspect?
- She has not mentioned it.
She is heading straight to the palace now.
WUYING HALL
Is the Empress's favourite
pear blossom honey all ready?
Prepared long ago.
Your Majesty, the Empress has arrived.
Why does Your Majesty
look so surprised to see me?
I just thought
you would be happier to step out
of the palace for a while.
Why should I be happy?
This is pear blossom honey
from this year's harvest.
Taste it.
You haven't finished speaking.
Why would I
be happy?
Should I be happy
that my master is the Ghost King?
What are you talking about?
All along, you've had people following me,
never leaving my side.
Don't you know what I'm talking about?
I had them follow you to protect you.
Since you admit it,
then the items of the Ghost King
in the Sword Cottage…
You were the one who placed them?
You are suspecting me
of framing your master?
No.
If I truly wanted to frame your master,
why wait until today?
Then tell me,
why did you kill my master?
I promised your master
I wouldn't reveal the truth to you.
Fine.
I'll find out myself.
Cangcang, have you considered
that perhaps the truth
is more than you can bear?
If I didn't know the truth,
how could I bear it?
Ling Xuefeng,
are you betting that
I wouldn't break my vow?
Grand Tutor Ling has been kind to me.
He helped me avenge my daughter's wrongs.
He allowed me to live again.
For him, I would face mountains
of blades and seas of fire,
even if my soul were to shatter,
I would not hesitate.
If I told you that it was Ling Xuefeng
who abducted your daughter?
All of this
was orchestrated by him as a bitter ruse.
Impossible.
It's impossible.
Everything I saw was real.
Everything I did was of my own free will.
I was not used by anyone.
I will never regret it.
Is that so?
Then these words,
would you dare to say them to Cangcang?
Do not tell Cangcang the truth.
Understood.
A promise from the sovereign
is never broken.