What about Yeon-hwa?
She fell asleep at midnight.
Wait.
Try it.
Be generous.
Don't let that bad guy
see our intention at first sight.
Didn't the chef say
Qin will protect us in secret?
Where is she?
Secret protection.
That's...
You're protecting me in secret, aren't you?
Wait for me.
This is my specialty.
[Kyoko, bad goose.]
Try it.
Is Li and the money bag okay?
Don't worry.
The money bag is quite messy these days. It's fine. It's fine.
in the money bag these days.
Let him go out to vent his anger.
Where's Zhan Mao'er?
Let him out
Zhan Mao'er.
The Oiran of Wafang.
A confidant of Lotus.
Damn you!
Gongsun has left.
Come out!
Isn't this the government's dog?
Come to our beggar alley.
to show off.
Take advantage of Chef Shen
What are you talking about?
We're fighting for Qin.
We're just asking about something.
Cat Zhan.
Warrior Zhan.
When did he come to the beggar alley?
Do you remember?
Don't see me off.
Okay.
Wait here.
I'll get someone to teach you a lesson.
Don't see me off.
Come again.
Sir.
I'll pull out all your hair next time.
Let's go.
Don't hit me in the face.
Forget it.
I got beaten up.
and the money was stolen.
Zhan Mao'er.
You scoundrel!
I'll teach you a lesson.
You're fine now.
You want something to happen to me?
Help me get the rice.
How dare you!
You've been working hard.
It's understandable that you're angry.
Come on.
Sit down and talk.
If you take me as your target,
I'll put up with it.
But what's wrong with Qin?
He didn't even leave the kitchen.
Shen Shaodwen,
You are so cruel.
Do you know I almost died outside?
I said you were fine.
but you're fine.
Just two dishes?
I didn't get anything from the beggar alley.
But I got it from the alley stall.
Zhan Mao
came to the beggar alley six or seven years ago.
We also got the incense.
The boss said
Hongyi.
Big Sword.
Chef, it's not wrong this time.
Now we have witnesses and evidence.
We just need to ask Peng Hyo-yu for an arrest document.
No hurry.
You are not.
Zhan Mao'er's next target is not you.
It's me.
He saved you.
No wonder.
No wonder you asked me to make a scene.
There is no nobleness on the thorns.
But we are not close.
Shen Shaodwen,
You are so loyal.
Gongsun Li.
Don't talk when eating or sleeping.
Eat well.
Am I right?
You knew Zhan Mao'er was the murderer,
You still want me to make a scene?
You're not using me as your target.
You used me as a messenger.
You used me to send him letters.
You also asked me and Li
to investigate some trivial things.
It's okay.
I've figured it out.
You want me to buy time, right?
You let Zhan Mao Er know his whereabouts are exposed.
Give him time to escape.
To repay him for saving his life,
Shen Shaodwen,
You even abandoned me.
Don't forget.
In terms of saving my life,
I saved you too.
That's why it's true.
Justice and law.
What does it mean to you?
What am I to you?
You want to keep Zhan Mao'er?
Fine.
I'll go to the government office to find Peng Xiaoyu.
Gongsun Li,
I really don't want to show my cat to the government.
You admit it?
I don't want him to see the officials.
because of the string pattern
The mandrill case
and the silver robbery case seven years ago
the same person.
If it was Zhan Mao'er,
If it weren't for him,
it means Peng Xiaoyu wronged the wanderer seven years ago.
So many lives were killed by Peng Xiaoyu.
Peng Xiaoyu wouldn't dare to reverse the case.
I want you to investigate.
I really want you to be sure
The mandrill is Zhan Mao
So you're afraid
that Peng Xiaoyu
Peng Hyo-yu will kill the cat.
If so,
the real murderer will be free.
You are still in danger.
So...
I misunderstood you.
You are...
For my own good?
You think too much.
Here.
Let's eat first.
We'll report to the government after dinner.
No matter how big the world is,
eating is the most important.
You're angry.
to calm down.
Isn't it good?
Eat more if you like it.
Here.
Can you be gentle?
Okay.
Grandpa Zhan.
The officials have been here.
They were sent away.
Don't worry.
We won't betray you
The mandrill made the whole city
in the city
Is he a human or a ghost?
If he is a human,
he's really not a person.
Bastard!
You tortured those two girls.
Alright.
I have something to do later.
Get lost.
Okay.
Rest early, Grandpa Zhan.
I'm so full.
Do you have tea?
Gongsun Li.
You're so ugly.
I've lived for 20 years.
No one has ever said I'm ugly.
Take a look if you don't believe me.
What's wrong with my face?
When did it grow?
I don't know
Give me a helmet.
There's no such thing.
Give me your hat.
I'm not covering my face.
You have a neck too.
It's on the neck too
I can't face anyone.
Look at your body.
Don't go.
We have to find Peng Hyo-ok.
Go by yourselves.
Is the money bag okay?
But I'm going to make him
to trigger the wind.
He cherishes his looks.
he wouldn't dare to go out.
He just scolded you.
You're so mean.
I told you
the next target of the mandrill is probably him
Can we really let him run around
How many eyes do I have
to take care of him.
You know that?
Just leave him
with me on the street.
What?
Did I offend you too?
The murderer killed people around Lotus
just to frame him.
As long as he doesn't touch the lotus,
the murderer can't frame Lotus with his death.
If he cares about it, it will be chaotic.
He didn't see this level.
So you asked him to investigate the case with me
to make him unable to
so he can't go to the vase.
Not only that,
I want to starve the murderer.
Starve the murderer?
Three days after Hongyun and Ziyan went missing,
after they went missing.
On the night when her body was found,
the body of Hongyun appeared.
So we can infer that
the murderer committed another crime
after seven years.
It's as if a long drought brings joy.
Once you see blood,
it becomes more and more unstoppable.
The more he wants to hurt Gongsun Li,
the more we want him to leave.
to show up.
But he had no chance to do it.
The murderer
must be starving.
A person who is starving
give him a good meal.
Guess what he will do.
He's going to kill himself.
What I want
is that he risked his life
to lure the snake out of its hole.
So you still don't believe
Zhan Mao is a mandrill
The lotus
made me understand
there are two skin in front and back.
Whether it's good or evil,
you may not be able to read one or two sides.
As for us,
set the cage to catch snakes first.
Whether it's true or not,
we'll know when the snake comes out.
But there must be a bait to lure the snake out of the hole.
Could it be...
I'm sure she'll cooperate with me. I'm sure she won't.
she will cooperate.
If I knew there was such a beauty in the world,
we wouldn't have to break the trap again.
Lotus,
Thank you for taking the risk.
Now you know what to say.
You didn't come up with the idea.
Forget it.
A worthless body.
If we can catch the murderer,
if we can catch the murderer.
Why haven't you recovered yet?
It's just the wind.
Li,
Don't worry.
Father.
Don't you think I'm ugly?
Is he your biological father?
Didn't I ask you to send it to them?
The kitchen is empty.
I brought the medicine back.
No one is here.
They must be chasing Zhan Mao'er.
Unfortunately, I can't help.
Did you post the poster all over the street?
No.
The street is peaceful.
Just two dishes?
You're angry.
Here.
Calm down.
That dish
the dish.
They don’t want me to report to the government.
Shen Song.
I hate you.
You did this
to prevent me from reporting to the government.
I must report this official.
Hello?
You're dismissed so early.
It's not dismissed.
I went to watch the fun.
Miss,
have we met before?
What happened
with your face?
Don't scare her.
I'm fine.
A good man is not afraid of ugly looks.
I told you.
I'm not ugly.
It doesn't matter.
There are always handsome heroes.
Pretty doesn't necessarily mean anything good.
Don't give up.
I told you.
Forget it.
Fine.
You just said
everyone in the government went to watch the fun.
What fun?
I went to the tile.
Vase?
Don't you know?
Rumor has it that
The Oiran will perform tonight.
I won't accept any money.
This chef
is crazy.
I heard that lotus girl is beautiful.
What do you want to complain about?
Why don't you put it aside
Let's pick up a loophole together.
It was leaked. Slow down.
Let me tell you.
There are many people here.
If you cause trouble later,
I won't be able to take care of you.
Okay, okay.
You should be careful too.
Let's see what we can do.
Are you listening to me?
Stay here.
I'll be right back. Don't move.
Men are so troublesome.
This guy is so strange
Chef.
You use lotus as bait.
I can protect her.
She also agrees.
Yeon-hwa is my friend.
Let me tell you about her past.
not to be used by you.
Let's go.
Hongyun, Ziyan.
I'll avenge you.
Oh no.
Qin.
We've known each other.
You hurt me too.
Qin, you can't catch me.
I told you, I don't trust the officials.
I didn't expect it was Zhan Mao'er.
I told you it was him.
but you didn't believe me.
I know you have a personal relationship.
But in life,
it's inevitable to misjudge people.
But now that the truth is revealed,
we can just take him down.
Qin can't win
to win against him.
Since he's not wronged,
let's ask Peng to arrest him tomorrow.
No matter who the monster is,
we must do our best to get rid of the evil.
The monster must die.
Yeon-hwa.
It's worth risking your life.
The chef finally found the murderer.
Hongyun and Ziyan.
can finally rest in peace.
The thing you worshiped just now was strange.
I've never seen it before.
It's my tradition to worship Lord Stone.
Bow to them when they have hope.
for peace of mind.
Who?
You've worked hard too.
Rest early.
You said people have two skin.
good or evil.
he may not be able to read one or two sides.
We treated Zhan Mao'er as a good man.
But he fell into the trap and refused to arrest.
Is it good or evil?
Did you read it?
Chef.
Let me ask you.
If he is one of good and evil,
all on the skin,
what should we do?
Evil prevails justice.
Become evil with kindness.
Someone from the government came just now.
Why isn't Li here?
I thought
if it wasn't Zhan Mao'er,
we found the yard earlier.
there might be a change.
I asked him to keep watch.
Who are you?
What a good kung fu!
Help me.
Don't worry.
With my iron ruler,
no one can touch you.
Where is he?
Where is she?
Miss,
I’m Lord Li, the official of the government office.
I was ordered by the chef
to investigate the case.
the chef.
Bring me to your lord.
What a coincidence.
We can't stay here for long.
Let's go.
Come in.
Thank you.
You came back empty-handed
I brought a new friend.
What are you doing here?
A thief.
You're here too.
How many times have I told you?
I'm not a robber.
I'm with this chef.
I went to see you at the vase.
I couldn't find you. I'm sorry.
You know each other?
More than that.
Miss Heroine,
I gave up my poverty
Only light tea
Good tea.
You only know good tea without drinking it.
It's obvious
Where did you get the dragon ball
The good tea in the kitchen will cost money
What are you mumbling about
What tea?
Let me introduce.
This is
is also an expert in searching.
We met once.
I just don't know
Just call me Rong Hua.
Nice name.
She's pretty too.
I feel like we've met somewhere before.
Are you the chef?
Shen Shaodwen?
Yes.
It's your plan to lure the snake out of the hole.
It's risky,
we managed to lure out the real culprit.
Wrong.
You have no idea.
Zhan Mao'er was indeed lured out.
You did lure out the swordsman in red
But the mandrill
Not him
Not him.
I found a suspicious man
I found a suspicious person.
who followed him all the way.
When I fought him,
I saw his eyes.
No pupils.
There's another strange thing.
His joint twist
is different from ordinary people.
If I don't meet him in person,
I won't believe it.
In the world
in the world
You must be mistaken
You don't believe that I picked this loophole?
Yes.
Why don't you stay and guard?
I can't defeat him.
If it weren't for you,
we would have let the monster go wrongly.
We wronged someone.
Then, Imperial Envoy,
how will you thank me?
I have nothing.
The Imperial Envoy won't just thank me
for nothing?
If you ask for more,
I won't accept it.
Even if
even if you sell them all,
I don't care.
Actually,
I don't want much.
If you have anything new,
take me with you.
No problem.
You should have told me earlier.
I'd love to.
You can't be alone at night.
and make her family worry.
It's okay. I'll see her off.
Li.
Let's go to the yard now.
Go ahead.
Ask Miss Rong Hua.
Send her home.
You're a girl.
I hate people who break the bridge after crossing the river.
What a pity.
What are you looking at?
Wait for me.
You mean he disappeared here?
We saw it for real.
That person
suddenly disappeared.
Is that really a monster?
I checked.
I couldn't find any trace.
The smell of blood is strong.
Is someone dead again?
Maybe the boy guarding the yard
You found his lair.
he won't let him go.
Don't worry.
I, Gongsun Li, will protect you.
You will be fine.
Gongsun Li.
Imperial Secretariat's Residence?
That's right.
I am the son of Minister of Revenue.
Gongsun Li.
Are you Gongsun Li?
I've heard a lot about you.
Miss,
Have you heard of me?
More than that.
He's a playboy.
He has a sharp tongue.
There are empty bricks.
Are you looking for traces
when opening the secret door.
Smart.
Come here.
It's fun.
But how can we find the pattern
How do we find the pattern?
Up, two.
Down five.
Two lines.
The password is
The calculation formula.
Look.
Just open it.
Miss,
I have some.
Thank you.
Chef.
He's dead.
Dead
Chef.
What's wrong?
You remember?
Who are you?
I am you.
I...
[13 years ago]
A parasite
We became the same person.
A parasite.
A parasite is a matchmaker.
Two will share one body.
Live and die together.
[We will never be apart.]
Monster!
No!
Something's wrong with him.
Chef Chef
Look at me
Chef, wake up.
Don't use heavy pupils.
Be careful of backfire.
Wake up.
Wake up!
Wake up
Chef wake up
Chef
Are you okay?
Kill him!
Chef.
Chef Shen Song
Chef
Let go.
Let go!
Kill him!
Song!
Shen Shaodwen
Shen Shaodwen!
Let me go!
Shen Shaodwen.
What’s wrong?
If he is one of good and evil,
with one skin,
what should we do?
Evil prevails evil.
Becoming evil with kindness.
What's wrong?
Two will share the same mind.
One will live and die together.
and never separate.
Let go of me!
What are you doing?
I'm going to use the Parasyte Jutsu as a matchmaker!
Let go of me!
I'll give you an evil eye.
If you succeed,
it will be my other hand.
If not,
you can only say that you're unlucky.
Let go of me!
I want your eyes.
Monster!
Chef!
Wake up.
Wake up!
Chef!
Chef.
Shen Song.
Wake up.
Chef
Chef.
Shen Song.
Actor table.
Zhang Chenxiao.
Jin Jiayue.
Hu Bosen.
Jiang Boxuan.
Liang Jingchen.
Zhang Fengjun.
Jia Qingqing.
Wang Lu.
Feng Dalu.
Lei Peng Yu.
Wei Lantian.
Liu Ziqiang.
Pan Yunde.
Shao Junze.
Chef Sun, Yong Yulin.
Li Panpan.
Lord He.
Chen
Tang Junnan.
Guo Shuai.
Zhou Rui.
Xia Qing Xiang.
Sheng Junyu.
Kong Jinyun.
Ruonan Zhang.
Yuze.
Liu Qingquan.
Yang Yifan, Pan Xiling, Li Xinru, Shan Hai Quan. Hao Li.
Wang, Xin, Kong Jinyun, Cheng, Dragon, Yang, Han. Zhou Xinghong.
Wang Qingpeng, Liang Dongxiao, Zhang Yulong, Yao Changlin. Du Xiaoxiao.
Bi Zhiqiang, Chen Zhi Peng, Ai Dong, Liang Dong Xiao. Zhang Xiaotong.
Cai Lisa, Qin Jiahui, Wang Yuqing, Meng
Ran Chunting, Jacky, Zhang Xinyu, Wang Hanpeng. Wang Haichao.
Zhang, Zhang Rongkun, Zhang Xiaoxiao, Yao Jiahui. Qian Libin.
Ma Hailang, Wang Penghao, Zhang Xianxian, He...
Li Yongbing.
Yang Haitao.
Hello. Hello.
Xue Zhiyong.
Liu Feifan.
Xu Xuhui.
Zhang Liwei.
Photography group 1.
Yang Liming.
Zhang Xiaoran.
[Photographer, J-Yan]
Zhang Asia.
You Shuangxi.
Yang Qingqu.
Hwang Jung.
Zhang Ting.
Yue Tailei.
Zhang Pingyu.
Tiger Wang
Wang Yun Zhuang.
Art team.
Yang Shuai.
Mao Yundong.
Tian Chunyu.
Wan Jiacheng.
Jang Jin-seung.
The editing team.
Special effects team.
Zhang Jizhi.
Wang Yusheng.
Audition company.
ASTRO.
OHAN astrolabe.
Liu Xinxin.
Actor assistant director Yao Zhiyuan Weng Jian Wu
The venue team.
Zhang Shiwen.
Production of film and television.
[Yang Shu Hua]
Yang Shuhua.
Zhang Bin.
Tong Zhizong.
Yang, Kang.
Team Leader Chen Ching.
Three-dimensional animation.
Single Lifeng.
Wang Chen.
Feng Zuhao.
Ding Yuxi.
Li, Cheng.
PR executive team.
Beijing Noisy happens to be a cultural company.
Li Qianwen.
Wang Wenwen.
Zhao Ying Rui.
[Post]
[Post Production]
Production unit.
Shaanxi Publishing Yida Culture Co., Ltd.
Da You Genius (Beijing) Cultural Development Co., Ltd.
Photographer unit
Zhejiang Dongyang Mingyou Media Co., Ltd.