Look!
What is this?
What is this
It's everywhere
What's going on?
Duke of Security.
You really came.
The man behind Wang Ping
Push him out to plead guilty
to put an end to this as soon as possible.
But the Duke of Security borrowed the mother and son's bodies
to make a big deal out of it
to dig up the old case.
Guess
he's willing to end it hastily?
Guess again.
The mother and son in the Earth Temple.
He used the chance to spread rumors
The Imperial Envoy abandoned the city and beheaded him.
Everyone in the capital wants to see it.
To him,
isn't that
when you fall asleep?
So,
he will make a move.
Are you crazy?
You're crazy too.
There's no security in this world.
How many lives do you have?
Are you gambling like this?
Since I met you,
since I met you.
You're right.
What if he really
he won't come?
Then kill me.
and establish the dignity of the magistrate of Kaifeng.
How dare you!
You dare?
I dare not.
Don't worry.
My head
can't fall off.
Didn't you say
Duke of Security inherited Mr. Guan's will.
Grain lost and virtuous.
You're so ungrateful.
Break white into black.
You can't tell right from wrong.
Duke of Security.
was written by Duke of Security.
Now he's making a big fuss.
This is the spirit of the Duke of Security.
Wang Ping, the dead in prison,
is a disguise.
Not only did he disturb the investigation,
but also framed the Imperial Envoy Shen Song.
He is not a witness.
He is a sinner.
Imperial Envoy Shen Song
is innocent.
Innocent.
What are you waiting for?
Untie him.
Let him go. You can't frame a good person.
Great!
Great.
I didn't see anyone suspicious.
This rope...
Yes.
Tie a knot
Tie grains on the knot
Pigeon pecks grains.
Break the knot.
and spilled it.
Keep the change.
Since he planned this,
he won't find it.
Swordsman.
With a big knife,
At that critical moment
And then?
Go on.
The Duke of Security is here.
What does the Marquis look like?
Did you see it?
The Duke of Security is a ghost.
How can you show your real body in the daytime?
It's only a matter of time
Words spread all over the sky
It's like snowing in June.
The Duke of Security is telling the world
Shen Song.
I’m wronged.
After the order of the Security Marquis,
Shen Song is innocent.
His decree has been abolished.
Your Grace is wise.
Peng Xiaoyu didn't even dare to fart.
and gave it to Lord Shen.
to Lord Shen.
My father trapped me.
I didn't get to see it.
We lost our grain.
Grain loss and virtue.
How did the Duke of Security know
about Fengdeku?
Is it because of the leak?
Our people are all cooked.
without anyone knowing.
Unconsciously?
Yes.
Only ghosts know.
Ghost!
There's really a ghost.
We lost our grain.
Fengdeku
It's an official warehouse.
I remember
it was a warehouse.
It's an important clue.
We should start from the granary.
Fengdeku?
Qin...
Aren't you going to take a look?
Qin.
As you know,
I don't want to get involved in the power struggle of the imperial court.
I became the Imperial Envoy
to prove
for the Shen family one day.
I thought
Duke of Security was a despicable man.
But later I found out
what he did
is the way of doing good.
Qin.
At this point,
I still don't want to get involved in the court.
But if I help him,
it's hard not to go deep.
Your master...
I don't know his position.
So I had to...
So you won't die this time.
Gong Sun Li and Zhan Mao Er know it.
Even Peng Xiaoyu knows it.
You kept it from me
because I was afraid that my master would let me stop you.
Qin.
I dare not believe you.
Are you afraid to believe
or not?
You don't have to trust me.
I don't care.
But from now on,
let's pretend we never met.
Qin, where are you going?
Qin, don't go.
Qin.
Why are you doing this?
It's a good thing.
From now on,
we will
know each other well.
When you're in a good mood,
What a ugly smile.
Just now at the door,
I was bewitched by a bell.
After climbing up,
I saw the golden house
and Yan Ruyu.
It must be your bell.
Don't.
The kitchen is small.
can't tolerate you.
I'm a man.
It's inconvenient for men and women.
This
is my specialty.
Kyoko, bad goose.
Look how loyal he is.
Don't provoke me.
When you die,
if I give you any money for your funeral,
I lose.
When I was sick,
I heard your voices in my ears.
I know you want me to wake up.
But I shouldn't wake up.
I'm a monster.
I got kicked out!
A long tongue.
It's none of your business.
I told you
you'll be unlucky if you care about a man.
Isn't this...
Am I right again?
The master has ordered us to do it.
What?
I can't come to you without your order?
If this is all you want to say,
I'll cut off your tongue.
I'll take it back and cook some snacks for the cook.
Are you really tempted?
A piece doesn't have a heart.
How to move?
Master ordered you to follow Shen Song.
If you leave like this,
What will you do now?
I told you to study more.
It's called a dead end.
I want to leave him first.
and let him know that he should trust me.
It'll be easier later.
He fell into the well.
It's all because of a stubborn mouth.
with a bare mouth.
You...
This is the grain delivery record of last month.
This is the record of folk funds.
Bong Deku.
13,700 dans.
Samtong Storage
6,475 dan.
Is there any problem?
Since the disaster in Ludong,
there are 100,000 dan of grains from the treasury.
Including the food donated by the rich monks,
over 163,000 dan in total.
Half of them
to Ludong for disaster relief.
The other half stays in the capital to help the refugees.
In other words,
there are more than 80,000 dan of grain circulation in the capital.
Not only that,
but also private soup kitchen.
daily porridge.
in total,
more than 100,000 dan.
But the people are still hungry.
100,000 dan of grains
can't feed refugees for a month.
It doesn't make sense anywhere.
There's a problem with the distribution of food.
Someone opened up
to steal the people’s food.
In order to collect the money,
and mixed sand into it.
So the porridge in the soup kitchen
There's sand.
All relief grains in the capital
were scattered in Fengdeku.
And Duke of Security pointed at Fengdeku.
I think he knows what's going on.
We should go to the Bondeku.
This is...
Princess Rong Hua sent a volunteer donation.
Since it's a reward from the palace,
we can't punish it casually.
Or did you ask His Majesty for permission?
and get permission.
We can only put it in storage after checking.
Excuse me.
see you off.
I have work to do.
Let's go.
Mr. Gongsun.
This belongs to my friend.
Just think of it as a ransom.
A lot.
Consider it a charity donation from Prince Rui's Residence.
Head Tian Deng of Fengde Warehouse.
Greetings, Tian Dian.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
Mr. Tian
was also a warehouse
How do you know the difference?
Shoulders lower right and left high
It's caused by the weight on your right shoulder
Mr. Tian is more obvious
He's always capable
From the warehouse,
The world is different.
The world is tough.
It's not easy to have a job.
I can still get the attention
It's a blessing
to promote a manager.
I can only remind myself
to work harder.
This is...
Not everyone in Bondeku knows how to read.
They only know the names of the vault.
The disaster relief is urgent.
I couldn't wait to do the accounts.
So I came up with this idea.
If there is any grain,
we'll keep the signature as a note.
100 dans as a square.
On the contrary,
to transport 100 dans,
will be cut off.
Good idea
Mr. Tian is capable.
I heard that Duke of Security
is suing us
to sue us
for losing food.
I've checked
in and out.
Nothing is wrong.
Please take a look.
and clear our name.
There's something wrong with the Bondeku.
There's something wrong with Bong Deku.
Didn't you say
this account is right?
The accounts are right.
It proves that they are familiar with this.
We couldn't find anything.
But the chef has to check the attendance record.
That's why they didn't expect it.
Those who stole grain know they will check the accounts sooner or later,
they will make it even.
But other details will be ignored.
But someone was careless
and didn't go to work.
Let the rat who stole grain
to transport food.
The records were seamless.
Everyone's name is written clearly.
No one is absent.
What's the problem?
The storekeeper said the storekeepers were illiterate
Even grain carving counts
But why does it have to be at dawn?
at dawn?
You mean
the whole attendance record is fake?
Not all the storekeepers
to steal grain.
How do we investigate this?
The thief changed the attendance record
to hide the wood in the forest
to make everyone a suspect.
But at least we know one thing.
The food thief
is in the warehouse of Fengdeku.
That's right.
So we just need to keep an eye on Bong Deku.
and see how the grains get out.
But Bong Deku is heavily guarded.
What do we think?
I have no choice.
But you have.
I...
You need to beg someone.
Who is it?
I said
these are mixed with grain.
Don't you believe me?
I dare not.
But...
What?
Prince Rui's Residence won't lie to you.
It's good that I didn't get even with you.
We don't need these grains.
It looks diaphragmatic.
Don't be angry, Your Highness.
Go.
Change grain for the royal mansion.
Check carefully.
You have to do it well.
Yes.
No need.
We're short of food.
Take these as relief for the victims.
Yes.
Move.
Slowly.
Are you done?
Thank you, guys.
Let's go.
I'll buy you a drink.
Okay.
Let's go home.
Let's go.
Are you sure
they will come to transport food at night?
I'm not sure.
If they don't come,
we'll starve to death here.
Not bad.
You're well prepared.
Just eat
Is it a bit choking?
Catch.
Not bad.
You're so thoughtful.
Do you want wine?
No way.
Are you going to live here?
Chef
It's so boring
What are you waiting for?
Not even a poem?
Come on.
Ten pots of Qibao raise thousands of households.
but he taught him to fight.
Green Pearl House.
Are you mocking me?
Hush.
Did they catch up?
No.
Hurry up.
It'll be hard
it'll be hard.
Yes.
Hurry.
Hurry up. Be careful.
I'm not familiar with it
I don't think he's a storekeeper.
Yes
This way and you're still spraying.
Don't push me.
Hurry up. Hurry up.
What's that sound?
What's going on?
I heard something just now.
Did you hear that?
I heard it too.
Hya!
Something's wrong. What's wrong?
I thought they'd be safe
I thought they'd be quiet for a while.
and ambush at Bondeku.
to try my luck.
But on the night they were exposed,
why did they commit the crime?
I checked the rooms.
No one is on duty.
and stole it.
It should be cooked.
How about
find Peng Xiaoyu?
and ask the government to help.
The capital is huge.
If we don't seize this opportunity,
and find the rat hole,
If they stop,
I'm afraid the government
it'll be hard to find another chance.
Even if I think it's wrong,
I have no choice.
Chef
Why is no one here
Where are they?
What's that smell?
Oh no.
It's smoke.
Maze.
Gong Sun Li.
Chef.
I finally caught you.
The master said you'll follow closely
you'll follow him.
They really followed us.
Throw it into the clam room
Chef
Where are you
Chef, say something.
Chef
Is the chef you?
You're useless.
Forget it.
He's always like this.
Why is there no door in this room?
Could it be...
we're underground?
Lord Shen, Lord Gongsun.
Our master said
your dignity
in this clam room.
I'm starving.
What a pity.
Try this ribbon.
What ribbon?
Snake powder.
Chef, come on. Come on.
I had a dream just now.
I dreamed of a skull.
It's so scary.
Snake.
Zhan Mao'er.
Master.
Have you found it?
Did you go to Feng Le Restaurant?
I asked him myself.
He said Lord Shen was not here.
The people in the kitchen didn't come back last night.
They must have gone somewhere and caused trouble.
Everyone else is taking care of their children for their old age.
Why is it my turn
become a retirement guard?
It's not as good as our feet.
The young master is older than us.
he has his own idea.
Don't worry too much.
The young master has been close to Lord Shen recently.
Although he made some noise,
But
your reputation has improved a lot.
A matchmaker has come to visit us recently.
Matchmakers?
Please treat him well.
With his reputation,
we don't expect him to be a good match for us.
There's only one thing.
The other party wants the innocence.
If this woman is powerful,
she must be able to control him.
You can't be weak.
Don't be fooled
by his mouth.
Only in this way
can I be at ease.
You're right.
Right, Chiyu?
Princess.
Bad news!
It's all your fault.
I was going to roast it.
My princess.
There's nothing in this mansion.
Why do you have to eat that?
Why are you in such a hurry?
What's wrong?
Oh, right.
Gongsun Li.
Gongsun is gone.
The servant of the Gongsun family
I'm asking around.
He said
with Chef Shen.
It's really gone.
Great.
The chef said
if we don't come back by noon tomorrow,
please go to Fengdeku
to make a scene.
How?
In the name of the royal mansion,
in the name of the royal mansion.
Scared the rat out.
Make a scene.
Don't let a rat out.
If we can't find him today,
we won't go back.
Yes.
Your Highness.
It's been half a day.
You saw it too.
The person you're looking for isn't in our Bong Deku.
None.
We've checked the warehouse.
He's not here.
But there are no signs of fighting.
He probably left.
It's almost done.
Keep a few people here
Mr. Tian.
You can ask around.
about Prince Rui's mansion.
My father lost a walnut last month.
The housekeeper is still searching the backyard.
You must find
even if you have to search the whole capital.
If you see my people,
Call me. Okay.
Yes.
Qi.
Let's go.
Take care, Princess.
Don't move.
Stand up slowly
Chef
Look who he is.
You thief!
Stop!
Over there.
I'll go after him.
This...
Rice.
Rice
It's rice
Chef.
We finally found it.
They're all here
How can I live?
Give us some food.
Save us.
Save my baby.
Baby.
Is it good?
I can have a good sleep after eating.
It's delicious.
Mother.
It hurts.
We've gone so far.
but still failed.
There are so many caves inside.
It's full of food.
We can't catch up.
Why are you so clumsy?
If Qin was here...
What are you talking about?
The food here is so moldy.
but the people outside died of hunger.
Duke of Security.
I saw it.
Now,
the people in the capital
can be saved.
Today, I know
what the way of college is.
In this field,
the security guard may go further than us.
Chef.
Are you still catching him?
I'm not arresting him.
I want to see him.
[Oda Tadoku of Fengde Warehouse]
Greetings, Tengai.
Shoulders.
Right, lower, left, high.
Tadoku!
Come again.
There's food Wake up
Eat up.
Take care.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
Lord Guan, show your presence.
If Lord Shen finds the granary,
We...
We have food.
Thank you, Lord Guan.
Excuse me.
Serve the tea.
Okay.
Take care, Young Master.
Does Tian Deng know how to read?
Yes.
He said he studied with his master for a few years.
Later, he became homeless.
Later,
I worked in the pawnshop for half a year.
He was chosen two years ago when he was selected as a storekeeper.
That's right.
If you can read, you can make fake records.
This person
But he's gone.
She's gone.
When you
when she went to Fengdeku to look for us,
I met him for the last time.
He never showed up again.
He wants to run.
Actor table.
Wang Youseok.
Zhang Chenxiao.
Shi Junqiao.
Xia Zhenyan.
Qu Peilun.
Hu Baoshan.
Wang Zexuan.
Long Yan Nian Ye Peng
Zhang Fengjun.
Lee Myung-woo.
Wei Qian.
Another hook.
Ruan Yunji.
Sharran Wang.
Yu Qinghui.
Gong Sun Li's servant, Qiu Junxian.
Jing
Long Peihe
Xu Yunlong.
Qin Mingliang.
Yang Shuping.
Zhou Rui.
Ruonan Zhang.
Ghost, Po, Sun Xiaoyin.
Song Jingwei.
Liu Jingyao.
Sophie.
to perform.
Mao Yundong, Liu Xintong, Wu Linghui, Yu Muchen. Zhou Yin Xiao.
Duan Yunyun, Qian, Jing, Zhang Aiping, Liu Xiaoyun. Wang Yuqing.
Cai Lisa, Qin Jiahui, Peng Xuejin, Liu Xiaoyun. Chen Xiaomei.
Ou Yuanjie, Liu, stewed, Du, Xiao, Su Quan Yu.
Yi, Zhang, lock, Zhou Zhiping, Lu Zheng Jia, Yang Sen.
Wang Haichao, Li Jianyang, Tang Zhiyuan, Yin Danny. Wu Ruoxuan.
Chu Hou Cai, Xu Jiarui, Yang Zixuan, Chen Yiliang Wang Sheng Kai.
Wang Zi Chun, Liu Yunxi, Ye Drcchen, Yang, glutinous. Quanzhi.
Ma Hailang, Wang Panghao, Zhang, Chong, Sun Xiaoxian.
Fang Tao Xi Wang Mingyang Chen Junyi Yan Hongyang Li Mingsheng.
Yuan, Hong, Yin Zimo, Wang Mingyang, Fang Tao Xi. Liu Mingxun.
Director team.
Yang Dongliang.
Chen Haige.
Jiang Yuran.
Shi Mingming.
Liu, Zhen.
The chief producer, Jia Ziqun.
Wang Zhao Nan.
Xu Zhitao.
Photographer Sun Wei.
Wang Jinshan.
Zhanfeng.
Chen Zhengye.
Photography group 2.
Photographer, Sukum.
Yi Seong Song.
Lee Deok-ji.
Sand.
Camera, help Yang Qingqu
with the pilot Liu Bin Qi and Qiu Chaoyang.
Lighting team 1.
Wang Shengjun.
Gao Lishan.
Lighting group 2.
Wang Kaixin.
Guo Zhenlong.
Martial arts team.
Wang Liang.
Fan Yiwen.
Liu Chunli.
Guo, Wei.
Tiger Wang.
Tian Chunyu.
The prop team.
Wan Jiacheng.
Luo Zhiqiang.
Zhang Huan Huan.
Wang Yusheng.
ASTRO
OHAN astrolabe.
Ming Shang's masterpiece (Beijing) Film and Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Yang Shuhua.
Zhang Dongyin.
Hao Shao.
Xiaowen Li.
Dan.
Three-dimensional production.
Harbin Dark Horse Film Co., Ltd.
Director, Qin Zhi Teng.
3D model.
3D animation.
Ding Tung.
Feng Zuhao.
The post-production team
PR executive team.
VENT. Louder.
Li Qianwen.
Promotion in the station.
Total Spearhead.
Beijing Sweet Radish Culture Co., Ltd.
Beijing iQIYI Technology Co., Ltd.
Beijing Guangtong Film Culture Co., Ltd.
[Beijing Cultural Development Co., Ltd.]
The filming unit