[English subtitles are available]
[Hello There]
[Episode 1]
[Joy]
Boss.
-Boss! -Boss!
-Boss! -Boss, what's wrong?
Is it another outbreak of blood vessel disease?
Did you wake up because of scare?
Luckily, it was just a dream.
Zhuang. Ba.
How's the thing I asked you to do?
Don't worry. It goes well.
Have some more.
As the famous Young Mistress of the Tang Sect in Shu,
I have a blood vessel issue.
If I can't find the destined one,
I'll age quickly to death before 25.
But I haven't achieved
my ambition.
How can I be trampled by fate?
My fate is controlled by me instead of God.
My destined one.
I'm coming.
What the hell, Boss?
What new posture is this?
Bad news! The Tang Sect's female tyrant
is here to catch men again!
Everyone, please don't be afraid.
I only want him.
Others can just do what you need to do.
You want us to abandon our friends?
Impossible.
Impossible for us to disagree.
Don't come over!
Don't come over.
Here, teardrop mole guy.
Let me give you a blood test.
Wait. You female tyrant.
In this way you can only get my body
but not my heart.
How dare you break my necklace?
Keep it safe.
Stop right there!
Stop!
Are you done?
I...
Stop following me.
Stop right there!
Stop!
Boss.
What are you playing?
What am I doing?
Get him! Get him!
Okay.
What are you doing?
Run!
Aren't you good at running?
I won't run anymore.
Run?
No.
Not him.
Boss. Boss.
Look.
God finally opened his eyes.
Two at a time.
Isn't this the blue teardrop mole guy
in my dream?
Guards!
Boss!
Surround them!
Go!
Gentlemen,
what are your names?
In the wilderness,
it's fate that we met.
Someone is looking for death.
Isn't that fate?
What did you say?
I said you were looking for death.
Darn wooden-head, let go of me!
Let me kill her.
Otherwise, I'll...
Don't get into trouble.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
Have you asked me?
If you don't take it in the easy way,
then don't blame me for giving you the hard way.
Attack!
I'll help you.
Idiots. I have to do it myself.
Let go!
Boss!
Boss.
You...
Boss, let's catch a hostage.
Go.
I didn't expect you really are something.
Do you want to go back with me
and be my wife?
Shameless!
Don't you think I'd have a secret weapon
since I've been dominating in Shu for years?
I'll show you what I've got!
Look! Darts!
How dare you sprinkle the tickling powder on me!
I'll kill you!
Put me down!
Put me down if you dare!
I'll kill you.
It's too stiff.
I'm calling you.
You two...
Don't go.
Put me down!
Isn't that the female tyrant from Tang Sect?
She finally got what she deserves.
-What are you looking at? -She is hung on a tree.
Put me down!
-What a shame. -That's right.
She's finally getting what was coming to her.
She deserves it.
Come back.
You embarrassed me.
I won't let you off.
[Qinglong Inn]
Sir, this is your dessert.
Enjoy.
Don't you think I'll forgive you
with a couple of sugar snacks.
Impossible.
Li Chengxi, let me tell you.
Unless you let me tie the rope...
Either eat it or I'll tie you up.
It's not delicious at all.
I just don't want to waste food.
Where are you going?
Are you going to kill someone?
Don't get in my way this time.
I told you that unless you're protecting yourself,
you can't kill people.
Then why did you take me with you out of the mountain if we can't kill people?
We're going to the Tang Sect
and find the Book of Yueque.
That's right.
Let's wipe out the Tang Sect
and then get the Book of Yueque.
Li Chengxi, if you tie me up again,
I'll be really mad at you.
Will Boss be okay?
Of course she will be fine.
Doctor.
The damage to Young Mistress Tang's body is worse than expected.
The blood vessel issue has been induced in advance.
I'm afraid she won't live to 25 years old.
How does this happen?
What should we do?
Is there a way to stabilize her condition?
Forgive me for my incompetence.
There is no cure.
We can only let her rest well.
Don't let her get too excited.
She definitely can't wear down her body too much.
Otherwise...
I'll take my leave.
Boss.
Boss, you're awake.
I thought...
What did you think?
If you hadn't held me back,
I would have beaten them up.
They made such a fool of me.
I must take revenge today.
Go and check
where that red guy and blue guy live.
Okay, we'll go right away.
Go.
Let's go.
-Chief! -Chief !
Yan.
What's going on?
How did you get hurt so much?
Senior sister,
I was looking for my destined one.
But Senior sister, let me tell you.
I might have found him already.
Listen to me.
Well...
Here's the thing.
On a dark night,
the chickens were crowing and the dogs were barking.
Although the process of our battle
was a bit intense,
my sharp sixth sense told me
that blue guy must be my destined one.
Yan.
The Tang family's blood vessel issue has been there for centuries.
It's not as easy to solve as you think.
You'll be an adult in two months,
and you can inherit the chief position.
You just stay here and recuperate.
Don't run around.
If I can't find my destined one,
I will age quickly to death before 25,
just like my brother.
It'll be a waste to be the chief.
Senior sister,
isn't it good enough that you are the deputy chief now?
Just be it forever.
As for me,
I'll focus on finding my destined one.
There are seven years left.
I believe I will find him eventually.
The Tang Sect's blood vessel issue will be solved.
Yan,
you're the only descendant of the Tang Sect now.
I can't let you take the risk anymore.
As for those two,
we don't know who they are so they're dangerous.
I'll find them for you.
You just stay here and recuperate.
Senior sister.
Don't be capricious.
I hate you.
Let me tell you.
Today, I was the one who got bullied by the female tyrant.
Tomorrow it will be your turn.
What's that sound?
Go and take a look.
Don't let anyone enter theTang Sect.
Yes.
Zhuang, didn't I ask you to meet me up outside
with the password?
Why are you going in?
It's me.
This way. Hurry up.
By the way.
Why did you raise your hand?
Great job, Zhuang. We're connected mentally.
There's someone over there. Go and have a look.
Hurry up.
Go!
Get in there.
Where are you going?
When did Zhuang's waist become so narrow?
Mosquito.
It's buzzing.
Ba. Ba!
I'll use a hidden weapon to distract him.
Let's sneak out.
You want me to poke his eyes
and tickle him?
Okay.
Stop it.
Zhuang,
you are getting better.
Where are you going?
Why are you running around?
This way. Let's go.
Hurry up!
Who are you?
Zhuang.
Where are you escaping?
What's wrong with Ba?
We were hiding in the crack of the fake mountain.
There was a bastard
farting all the time.
And then he fainted like this.
Tell me about it.
The thief just tried to poison me as well.
Who dares to break into the Tang Sect at night?
Young Mistress, why are you here?
Senior Chang.
I just saw a man in black barged into the Tang Sect
and he ran that way.
Take someone to have a look quickly.
What man in black?
The only men in black I saw
are the three of you.
Senior sister.
We are just
dressing in black
to chase the man in black.
Take her to the ancestral hall.
Yes.
Senior sister! Senior sister!
Let me explain.
[Ancestral Hall of Tang]
Today, in front of your parents and brother's memorial tablets,
you can speak for yourself.
How long are you going to keep messing around?
Senior sister,
I'm not messing around.
I'm saving my life.
I'll find him for you.
Don't worry about it.
Reflect on yourself here.
Brother, I found that
[Memorial Tablet of the late brother Tang Sishi]
senior sister got into the habit of making a fuss about everything.
I, as the young mistress of the Tang Sect,
am forced to kneel in the ancestral hall every day.
Do you think this makes sense?
Brother, if you are really in heaven,
why don't you help me and appear in senior sister's dream?
Tell her to give me more freedom.
[Memorial Tablet of the late brother Tang Sishi]
Brother, you are my biological brother.
You must keep your promise.
After I track down my husband,
I'll bring him to meet you.
No. It's ominous.
[Memorial Tablets of Tang family's ancestors]
Dear ancestors,
I'm sorry for being rude.
Please forgive me.
I was just talking nonsense.