What's wrong
Just listen to my arrangements today
ah
You did all this
yes
Let me tell you
These dishes are all specialties of my hometown
This bacon
It's only found in my home
And then there is this pastry
You can only eat it during this season
And this egg yolk cake
I tell you
This is super delicious
And this chicken leg
Spiced chicken drumsticks for you
Ah, wait
It’s too much and you eat it too
Excuse me
I don't blame you, I mean
Well, we have plenty of time today anyway.
But I have a lot of things planned today
That's all right
Anyway, there is plenty of time
If you can't finish it today, I'll do it tomorrow.
no tomorrow
Okay, I'll do as you say today.
Then tell me your plan
Is this the time when the time has come?
Deal with the school competition with the princess
Then we get to noon
I spent the morning doing business
yes
Of course, it’s mainly about the princess
Don't worry about it today
Okay, then we'll go shopping as soon as we finish our meal.
After shopping, go to the theater
After watching the play
Let’s go eat Babao Tofu at Zuixianlou
OK
My favorite is Zuixianlou’s Babao Tofu
Go as soon as you can
Eat quickly
good
Driving at the Fourth Princess's Mansion
yes
Dr. Hei Cong
Meet Her Royal Highness the Princess
I'm here to give Ye Weiwei a follow-up consultation.
Are the princess and Guard Ye going out?
Doctor Cong, I want to talk to the princess
Forget it, follow-up consultation is more important
Then there is Dr. Laocong
OK
please
Go and wait for you
I finally understand
That Yuan Mingyu has been tossing
I'm afraid you'll never get a chance to get the fish charm again.
Today is the last night
I will definitely get the fish charm
uncle
Do you think I would be a good emperor?
If you are not a good emperor
That's because your uncle didn't educate you well since childhood.
Then after I die, I won’t be able to see your father, emperor, and empress again.
See you at the same place tonight
Common people meet the emperor
Long live the emperor
Um
who is he
Report to the Emperor
Why did the father come suddenly?
Oh, where am I?
I'm afraid you'll be angry with your father.
I don't dare
I heard
This is the hidden guard you specially asked the doctor to treat.
yes
It is all his credit that this disappearance case was solved.
I didn't take a closer look before
You look like one
deceased
What is he going to say to the princess?
Princess
What are you thinking about?
Father just now
It's so strange
It seems that the emperor does not doubt me
what does it mean
Um
It's a good thing that the emperor can come
Too
If the father attends the game
Next, we just need to ensure that our people can win.
Everything fell into place
But when the emperor comes like this
Sun Xiang's chances of winning are even smaller.
Did you hear what I said?
After hearing this, I really need to think of a solution
What's wrong
Princess
Miss Sun is not willing to read the questions you gave her at all.
Miss Sun, I just got the news
My father will also attend the game
This way your probability of winning is even smaller.
Please adapt
I already said that
You want me to compete and you want me to win
I want to win the fair and aboveboard
If you insist on letting me read these books
Then I won’t participate
You really don't look at it
Jinlan locks the door
yes
Why
let me out
Former Mingyu
Really convinced
Princess
How is Miss Sun?
Still not persuaded
Originally we were going to go shopping today
Go eat Babao Tofu
Yes, my father delayed me until now
Then let's do it tonight
Have a few drinks
as compensation
It's him
He actually sneaked into the palace
leave you alive
But you want to throw yourself into a trap
Someone coming
exist
Go and bring Dr. Cong to me.
yes
Wait a moment
Keep an eye on that guard
The slave will do it now
Why
Still have to get to this point?
Common people meet His Majesty
Hum, we finally meet
The common people don’t know what your majesty means
Don't know what it means
Someone is coming
exist
Take him out and chop him
yes
Dog thief
You remember it, brother Feng
Haven’t seen each other for more than ten years
we finally meet
I was blind at first
How could I be with a treacherous thief like you?
be brothers
OK then
I asked directly
then
Where is the little prince you took away from the palace now?
snort
You're not stupid enough to think I'm going to tell you, are you?
don't tell me
You are already in my hands
I believe
The little prince will always appear
Do you believe it?
what to believe
It has nothing to do with me
Hao Lai Ren
exist
Keep him in the palace
No information should be leaked about this matter
yes
After tonight we will say goodbye
Princess
do not blame me
Liu Chun Liu Huan Liu Liu Xinyue Tang Shichao Wang Ze Deng Jiageng Lu Liu Shuangyan Chen Ying Ma Xiaoyi Wu Qingqing Chen Junsheng Beichang Wang Liu Zhenshengwen
Liu Dengjia Geng Lu Liu Shuangyan Chen Ying Huanxiao
Liu Shuang
Liu Liu Deng Geng Yi Tianjie