Aunty, do you want some chocolates?
Sure, why not.
Thank you.
Craving for sweets,
are you feeling troubled?
Problems with Sham?
What’s the issue?
You can tell me.
I’m good at solving problems.
I don’t know, Aunty.
I don’t know where to start.
Is it Sham's issue or yours?
Definitely me.
I’m the problem, it’s me.
I knew it.
So what’s wrong with you?
Many things.
I can’t be relied upon.
I don’t know how to communicate.
I don’t think about others.
Long story short,
I am one giant red flag.
Jeff said the same thing about me.
He called me a red flag.
What are these flags actually about?
Okay, a red flag is like a warning.
This person can’t be trusted.
So don’t get close to her.
For a green flag,
this person is a good one.
All her qualities are on the checklist.
Then there’s the beige flag.
This one means she’s a bit strange,
but still acceptable.
So, does that mean red flags like us can’t have relationships?
Not really.
I think it’s possible
if we change ourselves into green flags.
So, how do we change?
That’s the thing.
One more time.
That’s enough.
Just a few more, Master. Come on.
No.
What’s wrong?
Is he tired?
He’s bored.
How can I leave him when he’s like this?
Physical health is one thing.
Mental health is another.
I’m scared he might get depressed, Bob.
Understood.
The other day, when we went on the road trip,
there was this one interesting place.
I think Master Akiro will like it.
How about we take him for a little trip?
Maybe it will lessen his boredom.
-This is a good idea. -Right?
Where to?
Rin!
I want to go feed the fish.
Okay, you go. I’m going to rest.
BIANCA: MUM, HAVE YOU LANDED?
Something on your mind, Bianca? You’re quieter than usual today.
It’s nothing. I had a fight with my mother.
I see. What about?
The usual. She wants me to live my life the way she wants it.
I used to fight with my mother like that too.
Then, I thought I escaped my karma when I had two obedient boys,
but I can see that Rin is going to be headstrong just like me.
But the love between mothers and daughters will always endure.
It's okay. Don't worry.
KASHIMA CITY
This is Kashima.
What’s in Kashima?
It’s a surprise.
We’ll arrive soon.
Let’s go.
I haven’t been here since I was a teenager.
What are you boys doing?
Follow me.
Let's go.
Okay guys, we’re going to have a race!
I’m going to win.
One, two, three!
Wait for me!
Today is a bit of a special day for Rin.
What will she be doing?
Rin will be doing her "Hajimate no otukai." Her first errand alone.
Just to buy some things at the mini mart.
Okay. I will drive her there.
No. She has to make her way there by herself. She will walk.
You want her to walk? Alone? She’s only seven!
I know, right? I did my first errand at four years old!
It’s way past time for her.
Rin!
-Come here! -Okay!
I want you to go to the mini mart, the one we always go to.
You know the way, don’t you?
I want you to go get us some ramune and some dorayaki.
And get three sticks of dango from the dango-seller near the mini mart.
-Got it? -Got it!
Well then, here.
-Goodbye. -I’ll be off now.
Okay, be careful.
Take care.
Okay.
It’s amazing. Nice, Bob, beautiful.
Okay, Bob. Now you have amazing footage.
What you need now, is a story. What is the story?
Come on, Bob. You can come up with a story. You’re Bob, after all.
What’s the story?
I’m so glad to see you having fun today, Master.
It feels good to play with the earth again.
I feel... connected again, to the earth.
I haven’t felt this since the last time I made something with clay.
Sham,
you know the question that Karma asked me the other night?
She asked, "If you had your life to do over again,
and you couldn’t do pottery, what would you do?"
You remembered? But you were drunk.
I was very drunk.
But it takes more than that for me to lose my faculties.
Anyway, I think I know the answer to her question now.
What?
I’m just going to the toilet for a bit.
My stomach is acting up.
Sure. I’ll just be here.
Bianca?
Don’t help her. She has to do this alone.
Okay.
My first life, as I knew it, is over. Now, it’s time for my second one.
I want to spend it embracing, "Wabi sabi."
"Wabi sabi"?
The nature of all things is impermanence.
I have forgotten this simple truth. Or I've let it go a long time ago.
Pottery was my life, but there is more to life than that.
There’s so much more to life.
There is beauty in everything, as long as I am present to experience it.
And that experience too, will pass.
So it goes with each passing moment, over and over.
To embrace what comes, to see what is beautiful and to let go of what leaves.
This is "Wabi sabi."
Sham.
Thank you for bringing me here, so that I may remember this lesson.
It was Bob’s idea.
Was it? I must thank him, then.
Where are you, birdie?
I’m sorry!
Excuse me, Mr. Bear?
I need to get to the mini mart, which way do I go?
Thank you, Mr. Bear!
Thank you!
Hello!
Bob, I think Master really enjoyed himself today.
And I feel like he has made peace with his illness.
I feel a bit more at ease.
Praise be to God. I feel relieved too.
Thanks, Bob,
for recommending this place.
It’s definitely a powerful remedy.
Actually, this wasn’t my idea.
It was Karma’s idea.
She thought if she suggested it, you wouldn’t listen to her.
Why would she think that?
Sometimes, it’s a bit hard to talk to you.
That’s nonsense.
Grandma!
Back already?
That was quick!
-Here. -Okay, thank you.
You bought all these?
Dorayaki.
Dango.
Did you do it all by yourself? Did anyone help you?
I was confused at a street but there was Mr. Bear walking along
and I asked him and he showed me the way.
Good job.
That was the right thing to do, ask if you need help.
Come, let’s drink ramune.
-Ramune? -Ramune.
This one’s yours, Bianca.
Teach Bianca how to open the bottle.
-It’s delicious! -Good?
That’s good. Open the other bottle.
Did Karma say that she finds it hard to talk to me?
Not exactly.
But, come on.
Before she left, she wanted to see you, but you didn’t want to.
That’s an example.
It wasn’t the right time, Bob.
I wasn’t ready to talk to her at that time.
But weren’t you the one who said there’s no right time?
That’s different.
I don’t think I’m hard to talk to.
When you guys went on the roadtrip,
and she fell and cut her hand.
Hadri helped her.
I was calm. I wasn’t angry.
You know about that?
It’s good that you’re okay with it.
I was so close to slapping that guy.
Like this, this is Karma’s hand, right?
He washed and washed...
What are you talking about?
What did Hadri do?
Of course it’s hard to let go.
Your instinct is always to protect the child and keep her safe.
Yes, exactly!
But at the end of the day, the child must become independent,
and you must let them. Even if it pains you to do so.
So this is what all mothers go through?
This was just a small taste of what motherhood is.
It’s not easy, Bianca.
Letting your child go into the world is
one of the hardest things you’ll ever do.
Sham.
Don’t be mad.
What I told you earlier, it wasn’t actually that bad.
I was being dramatic.
Sham,
don’t be angry with Karma.
Okay?
Don’t be like this.
If you’re like this, what about your relationship?
So, what am I supposed to do?
I don’t know.
Just don’t be like this.
Maybe this is your wake-up call, to fix what needs fixing.
Or maybe this is
a sign for you to
fight for this relationship.
So, all this time I haven’t been fighting?
Haven't I done my best for this relationship?
It’s always me who has to accept her,
who has to understand her,
who has to support her.
What about me?
Who is supporting me?
Boys, today has been wonderful.
Thank you.
I’m going in first. I really need to pee.
Sham.
Please thank Karma too, for suggesting this outing.
How did you know that it was Karma’s idea?
Who else would think of such a thing?
Certainly not you boys.
She is a real gem.
I know you have problems right now, but you shouldn't let her go.
You will regret it.
Take it from someone who already walked that path.
It’s so awkward now.
Sham doesn’t hide it at all when he’s angry.
I feel like going home.
It doesn’t feel good staying here like this.
You’re going home?
Let’s fly together?
I think I have to go home too.
To talk to my mother.
I have to do a bit of consoling.
WAYS TO REPAY SHAM’S MONEY. GET A JOB AND PAY INSTALLMENTS.
HADRI: KARMA, I’M IN KUALA LUMPUR NOW. YOU’RE BACK TOO, RIGHT? LET’S HANG OUT?
So you're bad at communicating?
Did he block me?
Double kick!
More!
I don’t think you understand how this could look to other people.
Mum!
How dare you bring a man back home.
Is there nothing going on between us?