♪Dark clouds shroud the long trail
where the sun descends♪
♪Must we only meet by chance
and never again?♪
♪To be parted forever in an instant♪
♪Time flies never to be recalled♪
♪When your smile is embedded
in the starry night♪
♪We are puppets of twisted fates♪
♪Constantly intertwining♪
♪Dissolving in the crowd♪
♪Perhaps out of reach and out of sight♪
♪Constantly flashing through my dreams♪
♪The sudden icy wind blurs my vision♪
♪The rain drew that day to an end♪
♪How I wish your beauty♪
♪I want to love you,
love you, love you, love you♪
[My Divine Emissary]
[Episode 24]
[March 2nd, Thursday]
Today marks the day
you arrived in Qi Kingdom.
Would you recognize me?
[Heart Thumping LOVE]
I'm exhausted.
It's raining.
Do you have an umbrella?
I brought one. Let's go together.
Okay, cool.
- Let's go.
- Did you bring the umbrella?
Nope, I forgot.
My mom called
and said she'll come to pick me up soon.
You don't have to wait for me.
Go ahead first.
Bai Lian is right.
Maybe I‘ve gone mad.
Mengmeng.
Mom!
Li Mengmeng. I'm gonna catch a wave.
See you!
No way she's coming.
Mengmeng.
Duo.
Let's go together.
[Meiyijia Convenience Store]
Let's go.
Oh, by the way, Mengmeng,
I want to show you something.
I'm sure you'll love it.
Take a look.
Hold on.
Let me wipe your hands.
What's the treasure?
[Heart Thumping LOVE]
You're kidding me!
It's real!
Bai Lian signed it
right in front of me.
Is Bai Lian super handsome?
He's the hottest guy
in the entire universe!
When will I
ever get to meet him in person?
How about
[Heart Thumping LOVE]
we take a selfie with him?
Sounds good.
[Heart Thumping LOVE]
[Courtesy umbrella!]
Courtesy umbrella!
[Two years later]
Are you hungry?
How about we grab some late-night snacks
before heading home?
I...
I want to have dumplings
from Zhang's Restaurant.
Okay.
Or... let's forget it.
Zhang's Restaurant is so far away.
It'll take more than an hour
for the round trip.
I'd better go home early.
Ever since I started working,
we haven't had much time together.
Come on.
Mengmeng.
When is your mom free next week?
I'd like to formally visit her.
Formal visit?
You're exaggerating a bit.
I can't just be casual
the first time meeting your mom.
Okay.
You have work tomorrow.
Better go home and rest early.
Okay.
Bye.
Goodbye.
♪Two small worlds♪
♪Across light-years of love, connected♪
♪With each other's promises♪
♪We build a kingdom named Memories♪
You're back.
Mom, where are you going?
I'm going on a business trip.
How many days?
About a week.
Have a safe trip, Mom.
I will.
Take care, okay?
Alright.
[Mengmeng]
My mom is going on a business trip.
Can you buy some dumplings
and bring them over?
Love you!
Wait for me.
From Zhang's Restaurant.
Smells so good.
Why did you arrive so quickly?
When you messaged me,
I was already on my way.
It's raining heavily outside.
And it's late.
It's not safe for you to drive back.
Stay at my place tonight.
Here are some clothes
my cousin wore last time he stayed over.
You can make do with them tonight.
It's okay.
I texted Bai Lian.
If the event ends,
he'll bring me some clothes.
Really?
Why are you so happy?
Haven't you seen his new drama?
He's super handsome.
I envy the female lead.
He's not that handsome.
I even have a picture of him
wearing infant pants.
So silly.
I will show you next time.
I don't want to see it.
I know that
you knew him.
But you kept it from me, didn't you?
If we hadn't bumped into him last time,
would you have kept it a secret?
He's busy.
Next time, let's invite him to dinner.
And Duo.
Of course.
I haven't told Duo
Bai Lian is your uncle yet.
I want to give her a surprise.
I'm going to take a shower.
[Qi Yan]
The clothes
are in the master bedroom closet.
Casual wear.
Help me pick out something casual.
The address is
188 Wutong West Road.
[Heart Thumping LOVE]
Spring Garden 7270.
Got it.
The event will probably end around 9 PM.
I'll bring it to you
as soon as it's over.
What are these?
These are all my skincare products.
Amazing.
Do you really need to use so many?
You buy so many game consoles.
You play with each one every day.
Is Bai Lian coming or not?
He didn't answer the phone.
Hurry up and take a shower.
Our Bai Lian is too busy
to pick out clothes for you.
Who's Bai Lian?
Our...
Our uncle, Bai Lian.
Uncle.
Come and sit.
I've prepared it for you.
Enough, enough.
You need to take care of your skin
to look handsome.
But I noticed
that the one you used just now
isn't the same as this one.
You're so observant.
Because this one suits you better.
It's about to expire,
so I need to use it up quickly.
Okay.
Looking handsome.
Let's go to bed.
I've made up the sofa for you.
I'll sleep on the bed.
And the sofa is for you.
The event ran late yesterday.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'll bring it to you right away.
I'm almost there.
♪When a gust of wind brushes past♪
Pretty handsome.
♪Unafraid to forego a chance
to quench our thirst♪
♪Like camels walking with eyes closed♪
Mengmeng.
What's up?
Do you really like Bai Lian that much?
♪Unfamiliar sorrow♪
No.
I just
simply like this character. That's all.
Besides, Bai Lian
isn't as handsome as you.
♪I understood all that for you♪
♪But you have disappeared♪
Got it. Keep going then.
♪How should I stop?♪
♪Loving you feels like another lifetime♪
My Mom.
Hey, Mom.
Do you have a package to pick up?
A package?
No, I don't.
Weren't you on a business trip?
A critical patient
came in last night at the hospital.
I got so busy I forgot to tell you.
The meeting switched to online.
Mom! Mom!
I'm coming down now.
Let's pick up the package together.
It's okay, no need.
It's not heavy.
It's fine.
I'm hanging up now.
Quick, quick!
My mom's back.
She is downstairs.
Madam, let me help you.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Here.
Madam, which floor are you on?
I'm on the seventh floor too.
Alright.
Stop being mad.
I'm already in the elevator.
Hurry up and open the door for me.
Is your girlfriend mad?
Girls all have their moods.
Just cheer her up.
Don't forget
to schedule some time with your mom.
Got it. Let's go.
You're such a handsome young man
and so polite too.
I wonder which girl
is lucky enough to have you.
- Mengmeng.
- Mom.
Bai Lian.
Boyfriend?
He...
He came to deliver something for me.
Hand it over to me.
Bye.
- Bye.
- What's with the goodbye?
We're at the doorstep.
Come on in.
Come on,
quickly entertain our guest, Mengmeng.
Don't be silly.
Please, come inside and have a seat.
Madam,
- I am busy now.
- Hurry, hurry.
Hold this.
He seems busy.
Not busy at all.
You're in my home,
what's there to be busy about?
Come on, quick.
Come, have a seat.
What's going on?
I don't know.
My mom just suddenly came back.
So,
where's Qi Yan?
I didn't know you were coming,
so I didn't prepare anything.
It's a bit sudden.
Here.
Have a peach.
Thank you, Madam.
You're called Bai Lian, right?
Yes.
Actually, you don't need
to go through all this trouble.
I just came to drop something off.
Yeah, Mom.
You don't need to keep him.
He has a lot of jobs to do.
He's busy.
- Don't bother me.
- Right.
Your name sounds familiar.
You look familiar too.
I remember now.
You wait.
- What...
- Mom.
Mom, where are you going?
Mom, stop.
No need.
No need, no need.
Let me tell you.
He looks exactly like that male star
you liked in high school.
Exactly.
There are pictures in your room.
I'll go look for them.
What are you doing?
I remember
you were obsessed with idols back then.
Now you're shy?
Now you're shy.
- Now you're shy.
- Madam.
No need, really.
Not a big deal.
I must find it for you.
Too alike.
Step aside.
Where was it?
I remember it was here.
Found it.
Found it, found it.
Mom, Mom.
- Let me take a good look at you.
- What's up?
Mom.
What are you looking at?
You're so beautiful today.
Oh my goodness.
No fever, right? Everything is okay.
Mom, let me tell you.
The phone...
This picture's unclear.
Let's look at another one.
Clear, clear. It's this one.
You're here.
You are...
Madam. This is my nephew.
Nephew?
So, you're here
to see Mengmeng and Bai Lian, right?
Right.
I still need to drop him off at school.
I'm leaving first.
Mom.
Working.
Why are you working on the weekend?
Besides, you're all grown up now.
You can take a cab to school.
Come, come.
Look at the pictures.
Come. Look.
Doesn't he look like you?
Come on.
Here you go.
Have a peach.
- Thanks, thanks.
- Madam.
Actually, it's not that urgent.
Not urgent?
Fine. Sit down please.
Your nephew's all grown up now.
Actually,
he's two months younger than me.
I'm the elder one.
Two months?
Right.
Madam.
So, doesn't that mean
he should call Mengmeng Aunt?
Come on, come on.
Let's not talk about that.
Come on.
Take a look.
Doesn't he look like you?
Handsome.
-Doesn't he really look like you?
- So handsome.
Really looks like you.
I'm telling you.
Isn't it?
Madam.
Actually, this is me.
What? Are you a big star?
What big star?
I'm just acting
and singing.
Oh my goodness.
So amazing.
Amazing.
I said you're so handsome.
Turns out you're a big star!
Bai Lian.
Where are you from?
Who else is there in your family?
My family consists of my parents and me.
We're a family of three.
I am from Lingbei.
Being an only child is so great!
-Madam, I...
-We only have Mengmeng at home too.
Is it tough being a celebrity?
It's alright,
not too tough.
I don't believe it.
Look at how slim you are.
Have dinner here.
I will make some soup for you.
Madam.
You don't have to bother.
I have to head back to the office later.
Madam, I love drinking soup.
Do you really have to go?
You know what?
This soup tastes amazing.
You'll regret it if you don't try it.
Madam.
I do love soup.
Mom.
Actually,
Qi Yan is my boyfriend.
It must be my manager
urging me to return to the company.
I have to leave now.
Qi Yan, right?
Where are you from?
Who else is there in your family?
I...
Mom.
If you keep asking like this,
you might as well ask them
to show you
their household registration.
Did you bring your
household registration with you?
I know you are just joking.
You're really funny.
You know what?
Maybe from now on,
I don't have to just drop you off
at the building entrance every time.
I can walk you right to your front door.
After all,
I'm now officially your boyfriend.
I have to remind you.
Don't think
just because my mom likes you,
you can do as you please.
If not, then what else?
Mom.
It's okay.
You two carry on.
How about we pause for a bit
and grab dinner?
Mom, you didn't even knock.
And you didn't close the door.
My mom had asked us to have dinner.
It's fine.
That's so nice.
I'd love to stay here forever.
That won't do.
I want to
grow old together with you.
Be careful not to step on the crab.
That's not it.
Fairies don't grow old.
Fairies?
It's group activity.
What's going on with you two?
Exactly.
You two, stop being so clingy.
Everything's prepared. Let's go.
What do we have?
You'll find out in a moment.
You see,
every time there's food,
she is off like a shot!
This.
Food.
Is this ready to eat?
Yeah, it's cooked.
What are you grilling?
Beef skewers.
No oil was added.
They're almost done.
About to be cooked.
Turn them over. Turn them over.
That one.
Here you go.
Tastes good.
Try it.
Is it good?
- Especially fragrant.
- All these familiar faces
and everything that seems like
it truly happened...
- Here you go.
- It often makes me wonder
if everything in Qi Kingdom
is real.
Try this one.
The Internal Research Pavilion
in my dream.
- Have some.
- Yang City,
Lu County,
and...
Dad.
Smells so good.
It's like everything happened yesterday.
Which world
is truly real?
I want a cola.
I want cumin.
If you ask me to choose...
Try it.
Hey. What's up?
Why are you zoning out here alone?
Here, Cola.
Let's go, have some meat.
Hey, it's Cola!
So obedient.
Indeed, very obedient.
Too cute, isn't it?
Just as cute as you.
I want to pat the dog's fur.
What are you doing?
I think I would choose now.
Because,
- at least at this moment,
- Come one.
- everyone is by my side.
- Cola.
Food's ready.
Here you go.
- Have more.
- Thank you.
Thanks.
- Have a sip.
- Try this.
Okay.
It's Li Tao.
Hi, Li Tao!
Hi!
Hello!
Hi, Li Tao!
Where's Lu Huan?
You know,
if you get too caught up in filming
and can't make it back, that's alright.
But hey, it's my birthday.
Why are you calling Sai Xue?
Got a special trick up your sleeve.
Come on, come on!
I have to go film now.
I'll change first
and we'll make plans later.
- Alright.
- Bye.
Bye, Li Tao.
What's going on with those two?
Don't look at me. I know nothing.
What about the birthday cake?
Don't you need a cake for your birthday?
Right.
Where's the cake?
♪Happy Birthday to You♪
Thank you, thank you.
Make a wish.
I'll make a wish.
I hope
we all have
days like today every year,
and we're all happy every day.
Great.
Happy birthday.
Let's make a toast.
- Happy birthday!
- Come on!
- Cheers, everyone!
- Cheers!
Happy birthday!
Cheers!
♪Fight for love now♪
♪While the time♪
♪Is just right♪
♪End the story with an exclamation mark♪
♪A new goal♪
♪Take pride in yourself♪
♪Fight for love♪
♪You can do it if you dream of it♪
Come on, come on!
♪Bringing you into my dream♪
♪For an adventure♪
♪That belongs to love and youth♪
♪You light up the stars♪
♪Waking up the moon to watch you♪
♪The steps to growing up♪
♪A beautiful flower just for you♪
♪May it blossom with your smile♪
♪Filling the air with warmth♪
Stories with a happy ending
have always existed,
no matter it's the present,
the past,
or the future.
♪Our dreams fly with the wind♪
♪Showing off your colors♪
♪Right here, right now♪
♪Proving that you exist♪
♪Fight for love now♪
♪While the time♪
♪Is just right♪
♪End the story with an exclamation mark♪
♪A new goal♪
♪Take pride in yourself♪
♪Fight for love♪
♪You can do it if you dream of it♪
♪Warm sunlight♪
♪Reflecting in your clear eyes♪
♪Unveil your own shine♪
♪Gleaming with a radiant line♪
♪The question marks on the blackboard♪
♪Pause at every dawn and dusk♪
♪You never yield and you never resign♪
♪Our dreams fly with the wind♪
♪Showing off your colors♪
♪Right here, right now♪
♪Proving that you exist♪
♪Fight for love now♪
♪While the time♪
♪Is just right♪
♪End the story with an exclamation mark♪
♪A new goal♪
♪Take pride in yourself♪
♪Fight for love♪
♪You can do it if you dream of it♪
♪Fight for love now♪
♪Running freely♪
♪Side by side with the morning breeze♪
♪I have my steadfast beliefs♪
♪A new goal♪
And
Qi Yan.
So,
you're not just a good dream of mine.
♪Set ablaze with desire♪
♪Dreams come to light♪
♪March forth with might♪
♪Dreams take flight♪
♪Towards the horizon♪
♪Dreams in motion♪
♪Eternal youth, devotion♪
You woke up.
I'll tell you what.
I had a dream.
What did you dream about?
I dreamt that you became a novelist,
and I time-traveled to ancient times.
Then fell in love with the Emperor.
Who did you fall in love with?
The Emperor, of course.
We've only been married
for a short time,
and you're dreaming of
falling in love with the Emperor?
No, no!
You're the Emperor.
♪When a gust of wind brushes past♪
♪The sand and wind burn with passion♪
♪Unafraid to forego a chance
to quench our thirst♪
♪Like camels walking with eyes closed♪
♪When the rain falls
into a rare silence♪
♪Thinking of hardships
you and I don't know♪
♪No need to hum the wind's song♪
♪Uncaring of the darkening skies♪
♪I understood all that for you♪
♪But you have disappeared♪
♪I am lost in the dark♪
♪How should I stop?♪
♪Loving you feels like another lifetime♪
♪But yearning flows into a poem♪
♪For us to meet again♪
♪Requires the promise of a millennia♪
♪Watching the rain hail down♪
♪It's like you're still beside me♪
♪When I want to cross over♪
♪To touch you♪
♪But I can't see your fading face♪
♪On the opposite shore♪
♪How do I voice this?♪
♪My heart beats uneasily♪
♪How I long to hold tight♪
♪To the loneliness in your hands♪
♪Yet you warn me♪
♪Any closer and I'll be set in stone♪
♪The sunset deep in your heart♪
♪Of the day you most loved me♪