♪Dark clouds shroud the long trail
where the sun descends♪
♪Must we only meet by chance
and never again?♪
♪To be parted forever in an instant♪
♪Time flies never to be recalled♪
♪When your smile is embedded
in the starry night♪
♪We are puppets of twisted fates♪
♪Constantly intertwining♪
♪Dissolving in the crowd♪
♪Perhaps out of reach and out of sight♪
♪Constantly flashing through my dreams♪
♪The sudden icy wind blurs my vision♪
♪The rain drew that day to an end♪
♪How I wish your beauty♪
♪I want to love you,
love you, love you, love you♪
[My Divine Emissary]
[Episode 15]
[Sai Residence]
What are you doing here?
Why can't I be here?
I still have some things to deal with.
You guys go first,
I'll join you later.
Hurry up then,
the Lantern Festival
won't wait for anyone.
Let's go, Mengmeng.
Don't forget what I told you.
Don't worry.
Mengmeng.
Today is the Lantern Festival.
Let's go buy some new clothes.
I don't want to.
I'm short of money.
I'll buy it for you.
No need.
Hey! I suggested buying clothes.
So naturally, I'll pay for them.
What's your relationship?
Why do you pay?
Because I like her.
Does she like you?
If she doesn't like me,
does she like you?
Alright then! Let's ask her.
- Come.
- Just ask! Come on.
You two,
can you stop arguing?
I...
I'll buy clothes myself. Is that okay?
Both of you look like wealthy people.
The clothes in our shop
are made of fine fabrics.
Miss, feel free to look around.
Sir.
This one is nice.
You have good taste, Mister.
This garment
was handcrafted
by the royal embroiderer of Su City.
It's the only one.
Why don't these ancient clothes
have tags?
How much is it?
I don't like the color of this dress
and I prefer something simpler.
This one should be woven
from triple-layer silk.
As thin as a cicada's wing.
Light as air.
That's right, that's right.
This fairy silk garment is the same as
the one worn by the Noble Consort.
The same as the Noble Consort's?
Is there something better?
Yes, there is.
Wait a moment.
I'll find something for you.
No need to trouble yourself.
I'll take this one.
I quite like it.
[Virtuous Mansion]
Why did you take so long to come out?
The bed is tidy,
no trace found.
He definitely
didn't sleep here last night.
Not sleep here?
I heard that before he stayed
in the Sai Residence
he lived in the city.
Did he go back
to his old place to sleep?
The Lantern Festival has begun!
[Archery Booth]
Shoot this arrow into the bull's-eye
and you'll get a reward.
The more bull's-eyes you hit,
the bigger the reward.
I didn't expect
to see such stalls in ancient times.
What did you say?
Nothing.
I meant the dog is cute.
Do you like it?
- I'll win it for you.
- Wanna give it a try?
- Let's go.
- Come on.
Mister,
care to give it a try?
I see. It's a kind of little game.
[Archery Booth]
Don't underestimate it.
It's tricky for many people.
But for me, it's no big deal.
How many arrows should I hit
to get that thing?
Five arrows.
Let's see who hits five first.
Sir,
bring the doll over.
Gentlemen,
there's only one
of this doll left.
How about this?
You guys pick another lantern.
Are you doing this on purpose?
So what if I am?
It doesn't matter.
I'm hungry.
Shall we go eat something?
Here you are.
Candied hawthorn.
What would you like to eat?
I am thinking.
Sir.
I want crab meat baozi,
radish cake,
and rice noodle rolls.
Okay.
Mister Yan.
Why don't you come over
and see what you'd like to eat?
Sir.
One of each for everything.
Okay.
What a temper!
Are you showing off to me?
Do I still need to compete with you?
How can you tell you're richer than me?
In Qi Kingdom.
There aren't many richer people
than him.
It looks like you still
remember who I am.
You two gentlemen, hurry up and eat.
Come on, Mengmeng. Eat this.
I finally found you.
Why did you come so late?
Isn't this
the most important part?
Mister Yan,
have this.
A special of Yang City.
Thank you.
Would you like one too?
How is it, Mengmeng?
Is this not tasty?
It's okay.
If it's not tasty,
I'll eat it.
Oh,
I almost forgot.
What's this?
A tradition of the Lantern Festival.
Couples tie themselves together.
If they endure
until the end of the festival,
they'll receive a reward.
Mister Yan.
Care to give it a go?
Better to obey than resist.
Aren't you the richest person
in Qi Kingdom?
Do you still need this money?
When in Rome, do as the Romans do.
Mengmeng.
Why don't we join in too?
Let's see who can last till the end.
No need.
Mengmeng.
Thanks for your help.
Could you please act in a play with me?
What makes you think
I'll cooperate with you?
Have you forgotten?
I took a fancy to you at first sight.
You are so outstanding.
You'll definitely find someone
more suitable than me.
Forget it.
If you don't like me,
there are plenty who do.
So,
I will help you.
[Tongyun Inn]
[Tianfeng Road, Tongyun Inn]
This is the map of the Sai Residence.
It is really bustling today.
If it weren't for Master's orders,
I'd really want to go out
and have some fun.
We're here in Yang City
not to play around.
If you mess up the main task
just because of some fun,
Master will be unhappy with you.
You will be punished.
Did Master forget to close the window
when he left?
Mengmeng.
I can't help but feel that
your lantern looks better than mine.
Oh, please.
Both your lantern and mine
were made by me.
But I just feel like
yours is better than mine.
Is it because...
Because of what?
Because you're holding it.
Stop with the cheesy lines.
What lines?
By the way,
why did you say you like me?
Is there a reason
why you need to like someone?
If there is,
then it's not genuine.
It seems calculated.
Hold on,
fold it here...
Careful.
Likin' someone...
- Here.
- Don't you really need reasons for it?
Do I need to?
Don't you need to?
Do I?
Oh, forget it! I won't argue with you.
But...
I've got someone in mind already.
Okay.
No biggie.
I like you, though.
It's my thing.
It doesn't concern anyone else.
Even if you don't feel the same,
won't stop me from being good to you.
Right?
Besides,
sooner or later,
you'll come around to liking me.
Enough.
Give it back to me.
I won't.
I don't want to.
Give it back to me.
No.
Give it to me.
No, I don't want to.
No.
Give it back to me.
So,
why don't we make a wish with this?
I envy Mengmeng
for having such a devoted gentleman
following her
and protecting her.
Actually,
she's done a lot for me too.
You just don't understand.
Then...
Let's put more effort into this.
It's fireworks.
Let's go and have a look.
Come on, Mengmeng!
Let's go and watch the fireworks.
Hurry up.
Come on, hurry.
Aren't they beautiful?
♪Dark clouds shroud the long trail...♪
Even if I'm not there,
he will still watch the fireworks
with someone else.
He'll send out river lanterns
And he might even fall for another girl.
♪When your smile is embedded♪
♪In the starry night♪
♪We are puppets♪
♪of twisted fates♪
♪Constantly intertwining...♪
Money!
Money is there!
♪Perhaps out of reach♪
♪and out of sight...♪
Give it to me!
How come there are people
picking money over there?
Hurry up!
Over here!
Toss some more!
Give it to me. This is mine.
♪I want to love you,♪
♪Love you, love you, love you...♪
She's here.
You two talk it out.
I'll leave first.
♪I want to love you,♪
♪Love you, love you, love you♪
Do you still want to keep it from me?
Until when?
No, I don't.
Why are you doing this?
What reasons? What hardship?
Can't you tell me
and not insist on bearing it alone?
Mister Yan.
You've mistaken me.
If I have indeed made a mistake,
then I'll take this back.
You can't take back
what you've given me.
How do you know
this was a gift from me to you?
What other reasons
or excuses do you have?
Do you want to tell me
everything at once?
There's nothing else.
♪You're the legend of the future♪
♪A guest from tomorrow♪
♪The stars we once gazed♪
♪Used to flow through your veins♪
♪I must have heard it in a dream♪
♪You agree in my ear♪
♪Love is the soul of life♪
♪The eternal flame♪
♪You are the candle of wishes♪
♪Illuminating me when palms meet♪
♪My birthday is joyful because of you♪
♪Sing the songs you've sung before♪
♪See the moonlight you've seen before♪
♪You are the thread
tied to me for years♪
♪Unable to sever♪
The Lantern Festival ended too soon.
We haven't had enough fun yet.
I'll treat everyone
to a meal
and a drink.
How about that?
Okay.
I'm hungry.
This is the Sai Residence.
There's no reason for you to treat us.
You're all my guests.
Let's go.
I'll treat you all.
Just drinking is boring.
How about we play a game?
A game?
What game do you have in mind, Miss Sai?
There's a popular game
in Yang City lately
called Truth or Honesty.
Truth or Honesty?
It's basically two people
playing rock-paper-scissors.
Whoever loses
has to answer a question
from the other person.
If they can't answer,
they have to drink.
Isn't it just Truth or Dare?
Have you played it, Mengmeng?
Come on.
It's okay.
If you don't want to drink,
I'll drink for you.
This sounds fun.
I'll go first.
Rock, paper, scissors,
shoot!
I won.
I'm willing to accept the loss.
Ask away.
Can I ask anything?
Of course.
I'm an open book.
Where's the Sai Residence's treasure?
Again.
Come on.
Rock, paper, scissors,
shoot!
I won again.
Ask away.
What are you,
a Ximi person, doing in Yang City?
Some things are better left unsaid.
Is there anything you can't share?
Don't play dumb.
I said I can't say it.
Why are you forcing me?
I won't let you drink. Speak.
Do you have some secret purpose?
I'm here to find a wife.
Find a wife.
To find a wife?
Do you have to
come to Yang City to find a wife?
I don't believe it.
Believe it or not.
You...
Another round!
Hold on. Hold on.
I'm done playing with you.
I want to play with Mengmeng.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm feeling a bit dizzy.
I'll play with you.
Let's play.
Rock, paper, scissors,
shoot!
I won.
I'm not that interested in you either.
Let me think about what to ask you.
I want to ask, I want to ask...
Mister Yan.
Since you mentioned
you have an engagement with Mengmeng,
why don't you tell us
about your relationship?
Two months ago,
she spent time with me on my birthday.
I remember that day vividly.
I mentioned I wanted the moon,
[Mengmeng gifted it to Yan.]
then she gifted it to me.
That was when I realized
that having feelings for someone,
the heart
would started pounding uncontrollably.
And uncontrollably
wanted to be with her.
But one day,
she suddenly said goodbye
because she had to return home.
However, I missed her terribly.
So, I kept searching for her.
Finally I found her in Yang City.
Mengmeng.
Is Yang City your hometown?
My hometown is beyond the moon.
Mengmeng.
Do you want to go back home
but fear making me angry,
so you pretended not to recognize me?
Mengmeng.
I won't give you
another chance to leave me.
Even if we face difficulties
in the future,
we'll face them together.
Even if one day
you really want to go back home,
I will find you.
I...
Don't feel well?
Just let me vomit.
Don't come near me.
Mengmeng.
Your Majesty,
we've found a clue.
Come with me.
What have you discovered?
I went to his previous residence
and found this blueprint.
Indeed, something fishy is going on.
This is the Sai Residence.
But I don't know where this is.
Keep an eye on him.
Perhaps, he can help us uncover the truth
about the disaster relief grains.
Understood.
Qi Yan.
Where are you?
Where could he be?
Did you see Mister Yan?
He seemed to
have gone in that direction.
Over there.
It's so dark.
Let me guide you.
Thank you.
You're very kind.
He seems unfamiliar.
Why is it getting darker here?
I just saw Mister Yan
heading that way.
He seemed to be right ahead.
I'll head back first.
You search around.
Alright.
Your Highness,
are you sure about this?
Mengmeng.
Qi Yan.
I finally found you.
Mengmeng.
Your Majesty.
It seems safe here.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Your Majesty.
I like you.
You...
Did you hear me?
I'm serious.
I like you.
Like you very, very much.
Extremely much.
Alright.
I know.
And...
And before, I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
I always felt like
I didn't belong here.
So
I thought
we would eventually separate.
But now I understand.
As long as
we can be together for one day,
I'll cherish every moment.
Alright.
Why do you like me?
Probably just out of habit.
Whenever you're not around,
I feel particularly irritable.
No wonder Li Tao said
you didn't need a reason
to like someone.
If you can tell the reason,
it's all just a scheme.
And you?
Why do you like me?
Because every time I need you,
you're there for me.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, are you in there?
These mosquitoes outside are too much.
If you're not in a hurry,
let's go to the room and talk.
Did he hear us, didn't he?
Hurry up
and get us out of here.
Yes.
What did I just say?
He is waitting for me to rescue him.
Why are you still making me wait?
It'll be done soon, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, I'm here.
I told you to rescue us.
Why did you come down?
Your Majesty, I...
Your Majesty,
please wait.
I'll lower the rope.
Kong An.
Let me check.
Your Majesty.
This is clearly a dry well.
Why are there
so many things stored here?
So much rice.
The Sai family is indeed wealthy.
Despite the shortage of food everywhere,
they still have so much.
But why hide the rice here?
Aren't they afraid of it getting damp?
They're not worried about dampness.
But rather,
they fear someone discovering it.
The relief grain from the court
is being escorted
by the Sai Family Escort.
This is the relief grain.
Hey, keep your voice down.
The bottom of this well
is still very dry.
There isn't even any moss.
It means the well cover
is usually closed.
So,
the little guy
who led Mengmeng here just now
intentionally set up a trap
to lure us down here.
Second Prince.
I didn't do well.
I was recognized by that Mister Yan.
Get up.
Yes, Your Highness.
It's not your fault.
You should
avoid appearing
in front of them in the future.
They should have discovered
the relief grain by now.
No merchant would remain indifferent
to such a large quantity of grain.
Master Sai will arrive
in Yang City soon,
and our plan
can be implemented immediately.
If it weren't
for Master Sai's vacillation,
Second Prince,
you wouldn't need to
go through so much trouble.
Second Prince,
I brought the money.
Where's the goods?
It's not enough.
What's the meaning of this?
Didn't we agree on the price earlier?
Such a large quantity of grain
isn't just what you Ximi people want.
I went to great lengths
to secure this grain
for Second Prince.
How much more do you want?
Add another fifty percent.
Let's go.
Second Prince,
take your time to consider.
[Sai Residence]
The Sai Residence is indeed not simple.
Kong An, search carefully again.
Yes.
The map in the Second Prince's room
probably marks that well.
Who is the Second Prince?
It's Li Tao.
What?
Li Tao is the Ximi Second Prince?
Miss,
are you trying to lure them all here?
Are you awake now?
Still feeling dizzy?
A little.
No more drinking so much in the future.
Got it.
You just said
Li Tao is the Second Prince.
What is he doing here?
I was wondering about that too.
How could a member
of the Ximi royal family
be in the Sai Residence?
It wasn't until today
when we saw that batch of relief grain
that everything made sense.
He discovered the relief grain.
Why would he deliberately lead us here?
Could it be that
he found out your true identity
and intends to report you?
His real purpose
is only that batch of relief grain.
I'm just a pawn
in his plan.
Ever since the drought in the north,
grain and rice have only been allowed
to be sold by the government.
The south isn't short of grain.
Moreover,
this batch of relief grain is enormous.
It's been quite some time
since it was stolen.
Yet it's still in the Sai Residence.
This shows
that they don't want to distribute it
but rather make a big business deal.
The Sai Residence embezzles relief grain
to do business with the Ximi.
But since it's for business,
why did Li Tao
sneak into the Sai Residence?
Perhaps the deal
hasn't been negotiated yet,
so he had to sneak in
and force the Ximi Second Prince
to handle it personally.
Now Li Tao knows the location
of this batch of relief grain.
But the quantity is huge.
He has no way
to move the grain
without alerting the Sai Residence.
So, he needs to find a scapegoat
to actively discover this grain.
And then he can do business
with the Sai Family..
I see.
The mantis stalks the cicada,
unaware of the oriole behind.
He wants you to move the grain first,
then he'll snatch it
from you.
He's too cunning.
But he
didn't consider
Your Majesty's identity.
What should we do now?
Mister Sai will be returning
to the residence soon.
Should we wait for him
to return before taking action?
Come.
We can
wait for the right moment
and use this method to deal with it.
Like this.
[Yang City]
[Safe Travels]
Hey, buddies!
[Sai Residence]
Quick, tidy this up!
Everyone, go back
to your wives and children.
Alright!
Mister Sai.
Come on!
[Sai Residence]
Mister Zhang.
Did you manage
to find buyers for that batch of grain?
What grain?
Mister Sai, stop pretending.
Everyone in Yang City knows
you have a batch of grain
and you're looking for buyers.
The whole Yang City knows?
Indeed.
I came early
to make sure no one else grabs it first.
Mister Zhang,
are you kidding me?
It's illegal to trade grain privately.
Perhaps someone spread rumors.
My family indeed has grain.
But it's only enough for us
and our brothers to use.
Really?
Mister Zhang,
we have a long-standing friendship.
Can't I lie to you?
As soon as I got wind of this,
I was thinking about
how to distribute this grain.
So, it was just a misunderstanding.
Mister Zhang, since you're here,
please come on in
for a rest.
No need.
You've had a tough journey.
I won't bother you.
I'll take my leave then.
Take care.
Farewell.
Old Master.
There's news about grain
at our Sai Residence.
What's going on?
Since last night,
rumors have been
circulating in Yang City.
Some of the prominent families
have been inquiring openly
or discreetly.
Have you found out
where the news came from?
Please forgive me, Master.
We haven't found out yet.
It's been several hours
since last night
and you still haven't found out.
Trading grain is a big deal.
Are you suggesting
you want our Sai Residence
to be searched?
I...
Master, it's my fault.
Dad,
you're back!
Why is Fu kneeling?
Did something happen?
I ordered you to report
as soon as there's news.
Get out.
Yes.
Dad,
you've been away
on this escort mission for so long.
Did you bring any gifts for me?
How could I forget
the gifts?
The gifts are all in the carriage.
After a while,
once they're done cleaning up,
someone will come by to deliver it.
I knew you are the best to me!
By the way,
about the portrait
I gave you of the young men,
did you find anyone you love?
Oh, right, Dad.
We've had some guests
at our residence these past few days.
Why haven't I seen them?
You'll see them tonight.
Eat more. Eat more.
Here, have some.
Isn't Mister Li supposed to be here too?
Why haven't I seen him?
He's busy.
Don't worry about him.
Let's eat first.
I heard
that Mister Yan
is from the Su City Chamber of Commerce.
You are really promising.
Mister Sai, you're too kind.
I am just sheltered
by my ancestors' prestige,
unlike you
who built such a vast Sai Commerce
from scratch.
I heard that
you have a military supply order
from the border.
I remember last winter
when I escorted the goods to the border
and encountered a sandstorm.
It was almost impossible to return.
You seem to have remembered wrong.
Last winter, there was turmoil
on the border,
and the court
closed the commercial routes.
Our business suffered because of it.
I'm getting old.
It's easy to mix things up.
No, no.
This time,
I brought some fabric back.
Sai Xue,
take Miss Li
to see if there's anything she likes,
make a few outfits.
Consider it my apology
to Mister Yan and Miss Li.
Got it, Dad.
Mengmeng, let's go.
Oh, right.
Did you return the indenture to Miss Li?
I almost forgot.
I'll have Lingdang do it.
Let's go.
Looks like I've spoiled
my daughter too much
and neglected Miss Li.
Mister Yan,
I'll take a drink as my punishment.
Mister Sai, you're too kind.
Mister Yan, are you planning to
take Miss Li back to Su City?
There's no rush for that.
I still want to discuss a grain trade
with you.
So Mister Yan,
you've heard about that
ridiculous rumor too.
I wonder
who's spreading such nonsense.
Your Majesty has ordered that
only the government
can handle grain transactions.
This seems like
a setup to frame my family.
True or not,
I don't know.
But what I do know is that
dealing with this grain
is like handling a sticky candy.
It's precious,
but it can be hard
to manage and clean up
once it's in your hands.
In Yang City,
there are plenty of merchants
eager to buy grain.
If I did have grain,
Mister Yan, what advantage
do you think you'd have?
I don't have
any special advantages.
Just one thing,
I'm not short of money.
If indeed you have grain, Mr. Sai,
I'm willing to buy it
at a price three times
higher than the market rate.
Mister Yan, you're quite generous.
If I truly had grain,
then I'd definitely seek out you
to make this deal happen.
I am waitting for good news from you.
Mister Li.
Where's Miss Sai?
She's in her room
picking fabrics with Miss Li.
She asked me to bring Miss Li's package.
Lingdang.
Mister Sai wants you.
Okay, I'll go.
Please do me a favor, Mr. Li.
Please return this package to Miss Li.
Let's go.
Indenture?
He turns out to be the Emperor of Qi!
♪When a gust of wind brushes past♪
♪The sand and wind burn with passion♪
♪Unafraid to forego a chance
to quench our thirst♪
♪Like camels walking with eyes closed♪
♪When the rain falls
into a rare silence♪
♪Thinking of hardships
you and I don't know♪
♪No need to hum the wind's song♪
♪Uncaring of the darkening skies♪
♪I understood all that for you♪
♪But you have disappeared♪
♪I am lost in the dark♪
♪How should I stop?♪
♪Loving you feels like another lifetime♪
♪But yearning flows into a poem♪
♪For us to meet again♪
♪Requires the promise of millennia♪
♪Watching the rain hail down♪
♪It's like you're still beside me♪
♪When I want to cross over♪
♪To touch you♪
♪But I can't see your fading face♪
♪On the opposite shore♪
♪How do I voice this?♪
♪My heart beats uneasily♪
♪How I long to hold tight♪
♪To the loneliness in your hands♪
♪Yet you warn me♪
♪Any closer and I'll be set in stone♪
♪The sunset deep in your heart♪
♪Of the day you most loved me♪