Young Master,
you just recovered.
It's cold outside.
You don't have to stay with me.
I'm going to visit
my brother Zimo today.
It's been three years,
Zimo.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Where are these girls going?
Why are they all wearing the same clothes,
Qing'er?
Do you remember,
Mr. Pan once said,
Girls here
can study and read like men,
In this city,
there are even schools specially set up for them.
You can learn all kinds of
foreign languages, art and Chinese languages.
Factory pier,
high mountain and sea,
You can see the scenery
with your own eyes.
Not to mention reading and reading,
the children of our tribe,
I've never left the house for generations.
Brother Zimo, ride faster.
This is my first time riding.
It'll fall down soon.
If we say,
we will never go back again.
Do you want to live here with me
for the rest of your life.
Why did you stop the car?
Mr. Pan is telling the truth,
this place is a hundred times more prosperous than the Xue family.
I like it here.
I don't want to leave you.
But the Xue family
is the place where we were born and raised.
We can't enjoy ourselves.
We must also keep our tribe
away from ignorance.
Then we'll
give Mr. Pan the River Rock,
Let his treasure be opened to protect the peace of the four sides.
Let's work hard together.
Make our settlement
look like this place.
Brother Zimo,
don't worry.
The rise and fall of the Xue family
is in my hands.
Pan Jun
Shi Miaomiao has been arrested by Fengchen Jun,
you don't want He Luoshi anymore?
Who knows what Fengchen Jun's grandson can do?
Dr. Pan,
Boss Jin is here,
I believe nothing will happen.
Pan Jun!
Pan Jun, get out of here!
All of you, get out of the Xue family.
No,
Sister-in-law,
We didn't pay the rent.
That's not true, is it?
Here, take the money.
I don't want your money.
If I ask you to leave,
Chief Priest Xue is a good man,
We can't make it
through the winter here without him,
But you foreigners,
you lied to Young Master.
You forced
Chief Priest Xue here.
Get out of here, all of you!
Get out!
Stop!
Young Master
I was the one who announced Xue Zifeng's death,
but
he dared to turn a blind eye to Zi Mo,
He did nothing to save the lives of 30 people,
and he poisoned me.
He kept me in a coma for three years.
I didn't give him the punishment of killing bones with thousands of insects.
I've given him my last dignity.
Are you making a noise here,
to resist the reprimands of the gods of the sun and moon?
Doctor,
this must be a tarantula.
The toxicity is second only to Zhenlong of Ziwu.
Do you know what's the most important thing about hunting?
There can't be any trouble. Where's
He Luoshi?
Where's He Luo Shi?
If you don't bring it here tomorrow,
you'll be my next specimen,
Get lost
The gods of the sun and moon protect Xue Zifeng,
the high priest of Xue family, for violating clan rules,
Young Master Du hid the truth from the truth,
and he deserves to be punished.
Execute.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
Let's pray to the glorious gods of the sun and the moon,
and ask Young Master
to spare Chief Priest Xue's punishment.
Exempt Chief Priest Xue from punishment.
Young Master,
you saw it too.
These people don't want Chief Priest to die,
which means Chief Priest Xue has merits
and virtues with them, right?
Besides, he's not guilty enough to die.
Sis Yan Yun,
do you think this move
can guarantee to save Chief Priest Xue?
I don't know.
There are a lot of people now,
so don't make any mistakes.
I hope you can think about it carefully, okay?
How about this?
Can you show Pan Jun some respect?
Just take it as I saved you.
I … I saved your life.
For my sake,
can you spare him?
Scratched! Scratched!
It's showing.
Look,
this eagle suddenly fell to the ground in the sky at night,
I'm afraid there's a grudge.
The God of Sun and Moon is obviously working.
The incomparable God of the Sun and Moon.
Who are you?
Think about it.
The incomparable God of the Sun and Moon.
Not good.
Young Master He Luo Shi
is in trouble. Something happened to the ancestral hall.
It's the Golden Ghost,
which uses Aconitum mongolicum for its poison,
People who get hit
will fall into a coma instantly.
Luckily, he didn't hurt his life.
You'll recover soon after you wake up.
With such a precise shot,
it must be Jin Shun.
He hurt people but didn't kill them,
so he must have been coerced, right?
Let's go back to Ling City now.
If Jin Shun is threatened by Fengchen Jun,
He Luoshi will definitely be sent to Yaxin Pharmaceutical.
That's right.
I have to get Heluo Stone back.
What if the river stone is lost?
Everyone,
don't worry.
Young Master and Chief Priest Xue
will find a way
to take back the Heluo Stone.
Young Master,
please allow me to bring some troops.
You arrived at Ling City overnight.
Kill Fengchen Jun,
take back Heluo Stone,
Let's all go.
We're all going.
-Let's all go. -Young
Master,
Young Master,
Go find Dr. Pan.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Young Master.
I heard that you fainted
so you can hide your eyes and ears.
Dr. Pan,
I invited you here.
I want to show you that
the real river stone is here.
However,
Luo Shi was stolen,
As Zerg,
I'm afraid we need Dr. Pan
to give us advice.
If we take Luo Shi back together,
I promise you as the Young Master of Xue clan.
When Luo Shi is recovered,
I will take
our Zerg,
Sacrifice a treasure that
the great family
has protected for thousands of years He Luoshi is for you,
But,
But why?
Your father, Mr. Pan Yingxuan,
is a great benefactor of Xue clan.
More than ten years ago,
Mr. Pan came here to treat the patients of the clan.
He stayed up day and night,
cured dozens of people
in Xue's clan of pneumonic plague,
Not only that,
but he also brought us civilisation and culture,
He taught the children here to read and write,
and introduced Mr. Wang to us.
He also brought us books,
and more and more people
started to go out.
To learn what's out there.
He brought back the civilization.
At that time, Zimo and I
went out to see the outside world
because of Mr. Pan.
That was the happiest time
in our lives.
Mr. Pan's unfulfilled wish,
I remember it every day.
If Zimo hasn't finished his journey,
I will definitely continue for him.
Back then,
our Xue family
failed to repay Mr. Pan's kindness,
But now,
I've decided to give the river stone to your Floral Branch.
to help you open the treasure.
I believe that as Mr. Pan's son,
you can fulfill his wish very well.
I just hope,
when the treasure is opened,
Can it really be as rumored,
my Zerg treasure,
To save the world from war and strife,
that's all,
Only then can my Zimo rest in peace.
My father has been gone for 12 years,
and I complained about him for 12 years.
I didn't expect that
in the past 12 years,
You've been saving lives,
and you can let
people like Zimo,
Determined to get out of the wilderness.
Don't worry,
I, Pan Jun, will do my best.
Bring Luo Shi back.
The Xue family, who can strictly guard against death,
stole the river rockstone,
It's not easy for you.
I also got the Heluo Stone for you.
Help me get rid of the golden silkworm.
Boss Fengchen,
you promised me.
You promised me.
By the way, what did you just say?
Golden silkworm,
can you help me get rid of it?
Shi Miaomiao is a descendant of the water system,
she poisoned her,
How can it be so easy to solve?
Are you kidding me?
If I die,
I'll be the first to take you as my back.
Try it if you don't believe me.
Why are you so impatient?
Did I say I won't untie you?
Shi Miaomiao is in my prison now,
so I'll ask her to help you solve it herself.
Can't I?
Am I not thoughtful enough?
thoughtful
You're thoughtful.
Boss Fengchen,
I'll leave now.
I'll get going then.
Inside, right?
What a coincidence. Look, we ran into each other here.
It's no coincidence that he came to me
to cure the poison.
Of course.
I specially brought your Mo Yu Bracelet here.
I have to trouble you
to personally detoxify the golden silkworm for me.
Give me something.
Who would have thought that Jin Shun,
who has always been cunning and clever,
was tricked too?
It's not something interesting.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
Believe it or not, I'll kill you.
Stand up.
Let go!
Let go of me
Oh, my god.
Okay.
Dr. Fengchen told me
to prepare a very big meal for you
on the way,
Are you playing dirty?
I'm telling you,
tell Fengchen Jun,
If I see him again, I'll bite you to death.
To prevent thieves from stealing,
My father once entrusted Senior Jin Wuyi
to make a fake river stone,
Pretending to be genuine.
And the one that Jin Shun stole,
is a fake river stone.
True Luoshi,
why didn't you
build a fake Luoshi?
At the end of Ming Dynasty,
Luo Shi was stolen by thieves,
My father and ancestors
have never seen the real Luoshi.
Let alone fake them.
Later, after exploring treasures in Bamen Mountain,
although we got the real Luoshi back,
But the whereabouts of Senior Jin Wuyi is unknown.
Luo Shi naturally won't have a chance to copy it.
What role does it play in the treasure?
Carrying River Rock across the tunnel,
it's said in my collection of gold-based heavenly artifacts,
The greatest value of Heluo Stone
is that it can resist the dangerous mechanism of Bamen Mountain
and the poison of thousands of poisonous insects.
Rumor has it that
there are all kinds of strange flying insects in the tunnel of Bamen Mountain,
Only by carrying River Stone and Luo Shi at the same time,
can we pass smoothly.
But Senior Shi Yu
also carried the Heluo Stone,
After she passed through the tunnel,
she went crazy.
What's going on?
But it's clearly stated in the book,
you can pass it smoothly with two stones.
There's nothing special about it.
Why bother to pursue the truth?
No matter what,
you know what I'm thinking and asking for,
I won't say any more,
but I hope you can help my Xue family
to steal the throne,
Take back the real Luo Shi.
I'm counting on you.
A gentleman of the gold department,
Me,
Think about it,
if we only steal Luo Shi back,
They will definitely
go back to the Xue Clan's settlement,
Then it will be another fierce battle.
If we replace real rockstones
with fake rockstones,
He thought he had got it.
When the time comes, we'll take the real river stone
and return it to the Xue family settlement,
So,
Xiao'e must make a fake Luoshi
as soon as possible,
When you go to Yaxin Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd.,
Chief Priest Xue will send troops to protect you.
It's rare that
the raw material of Heluo stone is taken from meteorites,
The internal process is so complicated, I … I'm afraid it won't
work.
Many years ago,
Zimo and I,
I've visited all kinds of skilled craftsmen,
tried to copy them,
I didn't succeed,
but I hope I can help Xiao'e.
Give me four hours.
I will be able to make it real.
You're finally back.
Let's go.
Mr. Jin, someone wants to see you.
Why are you here?
Yanyun,
it's been a long journey,
Thank you for your concern,
but we don't seem to know each other well,
Don't pinch me.
Mr. Jin,
actually, we're here today
to ask for your help.
Have a seat.
Make tea for everyone,
Yes
Just tell me what you want to eat.
I'll ask Luo Xiu to prepare for it.
I want to see Fengchen Jun.
She deserves to be called Madam Matsui, who is famous for Yaxin.
Mount Tai collapses in front of me without changing color,
I'm not Mrs. Matsui.
Not from beginning to end,
Okay,
I'm sorry. How about
I call you Miss Shi?
Miss Shi, do you know?
When I first met you,
I was deeply attracted by you.
Don't get me wrong.
It doesn't mean that men and women are erotic.
You look
just like my mother when she was young,
Really?
In fact, we are really like
all the people in Ashin,
They did it for power and money,
and plotted against each other.
But you,
you use your own life and water system treasures,
In exchange for the freedom of all female workers.
Fengchen admires you.
You're wrong.
I'm different from you.
I will never use other people's blood.
In exchange for your own success.
Stronger animals prey on weaker ones.
Survival of the fittest
is the eternal truth of this world.
You sacrificed a strong man
for the weak.
That's the real short-sighted move.
Do you think you helped those weak people?
Will they be grateful to you?
Will they become strong?
No, I won't.
They will only get weaker and weaker.
Weaker and weaker,
until they are completely eliminated by the world.
The Zerg treasure hasn't been opened for a thousand years,
is it really because you Zerg people are incompetent?
You are bound by these
so-called hypocrisy.
If you want to open the Zerg treasure,
you need someone like me, Fengchen Jun,
But no matter how many experiments you do,
how many experts you hire
and how much money Yaxin invests in you,
You still can't figure out a way
to conquer my Zerg treasure,
Don't think too much.
If
I get the Five Series Secret Treasure,
And found a way to fight against the mechanism.
Then,
open the Zerg treasure,
It's just a matter of time.
I'm telling you,
the Zerg treasure will never fall into your hands.
You're wrong again.
Pan Jun asked me out today,
he wants to use the Five Series Secret Treasure,
In exchange for your freedom.
I really can't bear to leave you.
I'll say it for the last time.
Xiao'e, you and Yanyun,
you two unlock the lock and exchange stones.
Attract the attention of those people,
Yan Ying. I'm telling you,
Your mission is very important.
If you can't attract them,
they won't be able to get in.
Ouyang Yanying,
you are the man of Ouyang family,
I'm also an adult.
You have to make it clear in front of the right and wrong.
Heluo Stone is the treasure of Xue clan of Zerg.
You can't fall into the hands of others.
If you waver
because of someone.
You don't deserve to be my brother.
Just keep talking,
can you stop imitating grandpa's tone?
What right and wrong?
What Ouyang man?
What do you mean?
Don't you have your own thoughts?
Don't you have your own sense of right and wrong?
I didn't or you didn't?
Okay,
Let me be clear with you.
Kim So-mi works for Yaxin,
Lingcheng has her own business everywhere,
Everyone calls her Boss Kim,
Yin Yang Road and Fengchen Jun,
You did those cruel experiments on Ziwu.
Do you think she didn't attend?
You know all the evil deeds of Yaxin,
and our second grandfather in Mount Fuzhou,
Can you promise me?
Didn't Kim So-mi get involved in any of these things?
So what?
She is our mother.
She gave us all our lives.
Whether it's true or not is true or not,
can you stop using the theory that you think is correct?
You're here to teach me.
Why don't you take care of me?
Ouyang Yanying,
you've grown up.
Well,
I want to ask you,
Are we still going to save Ziwu?
Do you still take the river stone?
Save,
Take it.
Boss Jinjin,
Yanying,
Why are you here?
I want to talk to you about something.
Come up, then.
It's personal.
Can I go out for a walk with you?
Okay. Get in the car.
Get in the car.
Xiao'e,
I'll leave the safe to you.
No problem. Just leave it to me.
When it's done, I'll call five black-pillow orioles.
They have pleasant calls and are easy to distinguish.
Just listen carefully.
Okay,
When that's done,
let's meet at the back door.
Brother Pan,
the secret treasure I forged,
Maybe ordinary people can't tell.
But Fengchen Jun
has investigated our Zerg
thoroughly inside and out,
If something goes wrong,
I'm afraid,
Xiao E
Ziwu suffered a lot for us,
also
Shi Miaomiao might be in danger at any time.
We can only give it a shot.
Don't worry about it.
Even if we know there are tigers in the mountains,
I have to be biased towards Tiger Mountain.
Let's go.
Hurry up!
Close the door.
Mr. Fengchen, please welcome him.
Oh no.
As promised.
Mr. Pan Jun,
stop talking nonsense.
I've brought the stuff.
Please
I'm here with sincerity,
so don't leave any back hand.
I have to show my sincerity.
Miss Shi,
let me put it on for you myself.
You don't have to pretend to return it to its original owner.
If you are sincere enough,
you can return my water system treasure to me.
Have you brought what I want?
It's a gold secret treasure.
Earth and Fire Secret Treasures.
Have a cup of coffee first.
And my secret treasure, the Spirit Pivot Needle.
If you don't have the Five Series Secret Treasure,
you won't be able to open the Zerg Treasure anymore.
Could it be that
you're willing to do it.
You don't need to talk nonsense.
As long as you let him go,
all these things will be yours.