[English subtitles are available]
[The Romance of Hua Rong 2]
[EP23]
I knew
I couldn't get out of here today.
But this drawing of cannon,
will never be in the hands of Wanjiang.
This guy
looks like a harmless sheep,
but he is really a wolf in sheep's clothing.
Did you kill Master Yi?
Is Hua Rong acting or not?
Words are but wind,
but seeing is believing.
Give your life to me!
Couples quarrel, no disturbing.
Rong,
do you really need to say that?
Dealing with people like Jin Tong,
We have to make the quarrel look real.
Your Highness,
Empress Dowager suddenly fell ill.
Your Highness and Ms. Hua Rong are summoned to meet her.
Didn't Grandma just come back from the temple?
Why would she fall ill suddenly?
The Empress Dowager always as fit as a fiddle.
But today she heard that
Your Highness and Ms. Hua Rong wanted to get a divorce.
Then she was so worried
that fell ill.
Has she seen the doctor?
Yes.
The doctor said
it's a psychological problem
which needs psychological treatment.
I'll leave first.
Rong?
Where's Cheng?
Cheng?
Cheng.
Cheng, you've come to see me.
You've come to see me.
Grandma,
stop pretending.
What did you say?
I can't hear clearly.
Oh my ears...
I can't hear anything.
Grandma,
if you go on like this,
you'll really get ill.
Right, right.
Fine, fine.
No pretending.
You two are smart.
I can't fool you.
Don't blame grandma for lying to you.
Grandma is getting old
and may pass away anytime.
I'm thinking
when I am alive,
I can see my kids
are living good lives.
Bai's life is uncertain.
You two
can't hurt me anymore.
Here,
Rong.
I am sure
you're my granddaughter-in-law.
As long as I am alive,
you can't be apart.
Don't worry, grandma.
This time, Rong
will certainly appreciate your gift.
Grandma,
Duanmu Bai
was saved by one of my sworn sisters.
He's under medical treatment now.
I promise you,
I'll ask him to see you
as soon as he recovers.
Really?
How could we lie to you?
Great!
Didn't you
plan to get a divorce?
This is
a long story.
But as long as you know that
what we are doing
is for the sake of peace between the two countries.
There will be no harm to South Desolation.
That's all.
Got it.
If I don't trust my grandson and granddaughter-in-law,
I don't know who I can trust.
Right.
By the way, grandma,
it's not convenient for me and Rong
to meet alone now.
I hope you can leave a side room for us,
so that we can avoid surveillance
and meet under the name of visiting you.
A side room? No!
I'll put you both in a couple's suite
in Tianchi Pavilion.
Grandma.
Rong is shy, isn't she?
General Jin,
Hua Rong and Qing Shangcheng have been officially divorced.
I saw her tear up the marriage certificate
with my own eyes.
Everyone knew about it,
and even the Empress Dowager was ill for that.
Well, it turns out Hua Rong isn't lying.
I think so.
But there's one thing I don't understand.
Qin Shangcheng knew
Yi Feichi is killed by you.
Why didn't he confront you?
It's simple.
He was going to go ahead
and pretend he already has half of the drawing of cannon,
and use it as leverage
to draw forth the other half from Hua Rong.
It's reasonable.
I guess
Qin Shangcheng's next move is
probably going to exchange drawing with Hua Rong.
It's time to go find Hua Rong.
Why did you find time
to have tea with me today?
I come to ask after you
because I worry that you are affected
by Empress Dowager's illness.
I see you feel ill at ease.
Do you hesitate
due to Empress Dowager?
I do feel guilty about grandmother.
But the national interest trumps all else.
I have divorced Qin Shangcheng
without hesitation.
Then what's bothering you?
Qin Shangcheng offered to trade half of his drawing
for half of mine,
and then we share the drawing.
I wonder if there's a catch.
I think
you can agree.
Don't get me wrong.
You don't have to give Qin Shangcheng
the real drawing.
There are lots of able men in South Desolation.
Qin Shangcheng will find experts to identify.
We can make just a few minor adjustments.
It is the so called
a miss is as
good as a mile.
Don't worry.
My Lieutenant General, Wu Ren,
used to be in firearms camp.
He is loyal to me,
so he is the most suitable person.
You guy?
Don't have a suspicion, sister.
I don't have the drawing,
and it's useless for me to see this half.
Besides,
I have already proposed that
Wanjiang is willing to share the drawing with Tianchu
to jointly restrict South Desolation.
Okay.
That's a deal.
I offer the drawing,
and you offer the person.
After it's done,
we share it.
But it's an important thing.
I want to choose
the time and place.
It's up to you.
Have a cup of tea.
It is so ingenious.
Your grandson will love it.
No.
Tomorrow,
I need you to get a drum skin
at the Music Shop on the south side of city.
Yes, Empress Dowager.
Here comes His Majesty!
Queen mother!
Mother...
Queen mother,
weren't you...
I pretended.
Can't I?
Since queen mother is healthy,
I'll leave first.
Come back!
Are you still angry with me?
Since you became the Emperor,
you haven't had dinner with me.
Today,
you have dinner with me.
Don't just eat vegetables.
You've been working day and night.
Take some fish to refresh yourself.
Queen mother,
I don't want to eat fish.
Besides, recently,
I am blazing of heart-liver fire.
I'd better eat more vegetables.
Eat as your will.
Speaking of which,
those fishing rods you sent me
are rotting.
I am
getting old.
I should get more exercise.
How about I go fishing
with you tomorrow?
Queen mother is going fishing with me.
I would love to.
Queen mother,
I'm full.
I'll take my leave.
Empress Dowager,
the Emperor's favorite food is grilled fish
since childhood.
Why did he suddenly say that?
How are you doing with the drawing of cannon?
His Highness said he had a plan of his own.
I dare not interfere too much.
You can catch a big fish with a long line,
but you may also lose the bait.
I want you to keep an eye on this,
just in case.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I wonder if Your Majesty has been
losing appetite recently.
I know you like to read my mind.
But there are things
you shouldn't ask.
I am sorry.
General Wu Ren, please focus on the drawing.
General Jin and General Hua Jr.,
please leave for a second.
Sister,
the drawing is exquisite.
Wu Ren needs to concentrate on
the drawing process
without any interference.
Hope you can understand.
In his cautious nature,
before copying half of our drawing,
he would combine the two
and give them to Wu Ren for identification.
That would be
the best time
to get a full drawing.
Right.
And just give me a few minutes,
I can remember the full drawing.
Jin Tong must have learned about
your photographic memory from Jin Yiwen.
So this time...
Right.
I won't bother you.
Just leave it to me.
Are you going to copy the whole drawing?
As for remembering something else,
I might not be as good as you.
But memorizing a drawing,
that's what pirates do.
Trust is the foundation
for bilateral cooperation.
How can I not see the point?
Then thanks General Wu Ren.
Thanks.
General Jin,
Roughly how long it will take General Wu Ren to draw?
Half an hour is enough.
It should be halfway there by now.
Why hasn't Qin Shangcheng come yet?
How do you think Qin
will get the drawing?
I wouldn't have gone to so much trouble.
I will just run in and grab it!
How could the Lord be as stupid as you?
He must stand on rooftops
with binoculars,
watching Wu Ren drawing it,
and then memorizing it in his head.
That's the best way.
Do you know it?
My lord.
Sit down.
Your Highness,
what are you doing?
Don't you know it clearly?
Why does he have a whole drawing?
Doesn't Your Highness have half of it?
Qin Shangcheng,
so this is how you do it.
It's so direct and arrogant.
I like it!
If it hadn't been for your cooperation,
it wouldn't have gone so smoothly.
So you couple pretended to fight with each other,
but secretly working together.
You are a good actress.
You, too.
Haven't you always been acting, too?
We're just
fighting fire with fire.
You seem to be trying to
make an enemy of Wanjiang
instead of peace talks.
On the contrary,
we're doing this
for real peace talks.
Your Highness,
how do you explain this to His Majesty?
I have my own plan.
Qin Shangcheng,
you burned the map,
you burned all of us.
When war returns,
what can you rely on?
Only when the drawing is gone
can we have a chance for genuine
trilateral peace talks,
and can we have the real peace.
You pissed me off so much.
I'm afraid we can't talk.
Peace talks are major events of the three countries.
Do you have the final say alone?
General Jin,
I have written a letter to
your brother about it.
If you continue to go your own way
and affect the plan for the three countries,
you will be an eternal sinner,
and then there won't be room for you in Wanjiang.
How dare you!
How dare you threaten our General Jin!
If it weren't Wanjiang,
your capital would be occupied by South Desolation!
General Jin,
forget the peace talks!
Return to Wanjiang immediately
to tell His Majesty about this!
Enough!
You don't get to talk here!
I will never forget
what happened today.
Let's go!
Fishing is about peace of mind.
You seem to have something on your mind.
Queen mother,
I have been very busy recently.
I didn't sleep well last night.
Don't be worried too much.
Oh, right,
this is the Roselle soup
I had Nanny Duan make.
It can calm the nerves.
Have a taste.
Thanks, queen mother.
You are not my son!
Once drink Roselle soup, Duanmu's family
will have red neck.
Guards!
Queen mother,
dead people
can't come anymore.
Who?
Who!
Who are you?
Kong Lin!
I didn't die!
If I kill you now,
the game will be boring.
When we were in Imperial Alliance,
you wanted to contend for the
last emperor's testamentary edict.
You...
It's exactly what you think.
But,
it's too late now.
I want you to see
the South Desolation change the emperor,
and your son claim me as his father.
Everything you own
will be mine.
He had taken medicine.
And I had cured his broken hamstring.
Every means had been tried.
He should have been recovered by now.
Why he still can't walk?
Now,
all I can hope for
is what Crab calls a wishing bottle.
Dreams do come true if you really believe.
All I want now
is that Duanmu Bai's leg
can recover soon.
If then he wants to leave,
I'll let him go.
Go and boil this medicine as soon as possible.
Okay.
Go.
Duanmu Bai!
What happened!
I was thirsty and hungry,
looking for something to eat.
How can you take care of yourself after leaving me?
It's so hard for you to eat a grape.
How can you leave?
If my leg gets better,
would you still take care of me like this?
At that time you can do anything you want.
You don't need me to take care of you.
Thanks.
How does it taste?
So sweet.
Your Highness,
Cra...
Crab's letter.
I didn't see anything.
I didn't know anything.
I'm not gonna say anything.
Shut up!
Bring me the letter.
What's wrong?
Crab said grandma fell into the water while fishing,
and now she is unconscious.
Mr. Duanmu,
you can walk!
When did your leg recover?
Three... Three...
Three days ago.
Why would you lie to me?
Oh, I know.
Do you think
I'm gonna kick you out
when your leg is healed?
You can't bear to leave me.
This is the face cream
with grape seeds as guiding drug,
which has the effect of activating blood stasis
and remove scars.
Do I have scars on my face?
Don't think too much.
I just don't want to owe you anything.
You owe me something
which should take a lifetime to pay.
Now grandma is in a coma,
and even the doctor could do nothing.
It seems that we had to wait for Duanmu Bai's return.
Your Highness,
the Empress Dowager's medicine is ready.
Why are you here?
Where is Nanny Duan?
In a rage, His Majesty
executed all the soldiers and maidservants
who had served the Empress Dowager.
Nanny Duan's whereabouts are still unknown.
Maybe she has fled.
Even Nanny Duan is dead.
Duanmu Qingcang must be hiding something.
Did he execute in a fit of rage?
Was he hiding the evidence?
There is something fishy about it.
I'm going to ask him face to face.
Mu Qing,
if you are alive,
you can see
Duanmu Qingcang is at odds with his son
and his brothers,
you can see
how I take Duanmu Qingcang's all lifelong business
at once,
and you can also see
your choice at that time was wrong!
It was wrong! Wrong!
How could you choose him?
Take a look! Take a look!
Now I have no one
to share my high position and great wealth with.
Soon,
I will send Duanmu Qingcang
to you very soon.
I want him to tell you
how he was trampled under my feet,
how I twist his son
around my fingers.
Around my little fingers!
My little fingers!
How could my grandma fall into the water?
Cheng,
don't make a noise
in front of your mother's secrificial tablet,
or else it will not be proper.
Dare you swear in front of her secrificial tablet
that grandma's drowning is really an accident?
Cheng,
I knew your heart aches for your grandma.
But my heart aches more than you.
Your mother
can see your filial piety.
She also can see
my determination to unify the world!
My mother hoped that
one day
you would wipe the blood from the blade,
and beat the swords into ploughshares.
Beat the swords into ploughshares.
Graze cows and horses on the grassland.
Every family no longer has the pain of lovesickness.
No worries about the war within a thousand year.
If you want to beat the swords into ploughshares,
there should be no wars in a thousand year.
Therefore,
you should understand
why I want to unify the world.
Well, Cheng,
did you get
the drawing of cannon?
The drawing was destroyed.
There's only one drawing in the whole world now.
It's in my mind.
You're threatening me?
It's you lied to me first.
I have asked Yi Feichi.
After I returned to Tianchu,
you were still forcing him to draw it.
You didn't want the peace talks at all.
You think
I'm really afraid to hurt you?
That depends on
whether you want the drawing or not.
But on one condition,
you need to sign an armistice,
and
get me and the Tianchu Mission
safely
out of the South Desolation.
You are indeed my son.
You even know how to balance things out.
I just don't want to be pushed around
or used.
Why is there a strange medicinal smell on him?
What's this?
It was found
in Nanny Duan's baggage.
I guess it's the toy grandma told Nanny Duan
to make for Daodao.
Your Highness,
be happy.
Rong,
don't be upset.
Duanmu Bai's medical skill is very good.
When he comes,
he can cure grandma.
Wait!
It sounds strange.
It was a suicide note written by Nanny Duan.
So grandma
had long suspected Duanmu Qingcang's identity,
and had asked him to go fishing with her
to try him with Roselle soup.
Nanny Duan heard that
all the people around Empress Dowager
died after the drowning accident.
She knew that she was going to die soon,
so she decided to write everything on it
to avenge the Empress Dowager.
Then,
is this a fake Duanmu Qingcang?
Exactly, yes!
- My Lord.
This is a
fake Duanmu Qingcang.
My Lord,
what is this?
It has the smell of fish.
I recently smelled a strange medicinal smell
on Duanmu Qingcang.
So I went to the Spring-back Hall.
This is the ointment for burns and scalds,
which can eliminate pus and toxin,
and remove rotten skin.
It's the best drug to treat burns.
But Duanmu Qingcang was not injured recently,
let alone burned.
Burn...
Is it...
Yes.
It's Kong Lin.
Isn't he dead?
He's not dead.
He must have fled out of the secret chamber,
and sent his guys to assassinate us
the night of the jail delivery.
In this case,
Duanmu Qingcang was not the one
who broke the promise
and killed Zou Yitian,
but Kong Lin.
Is the real Duanmu Qingcang
dead?
He's in danger now at worst.
So if that's the case,
how can we prove this Duanmu Qingcang
is not the real one?
There's one person who's a breach.
Your Highness.
Don't.
Take a seat.
Thanks, Your Highness.
I've stayed in South Desolation so long,
But I've never heard you playing the Chinese zither.
I am not sorry for the pain in the player's heart,
but sad that no one can understand her pain.
Many accidents have taken place in the palace.
How can I play the zither?
This zither
is the Fumeng Zither from Wanjiang?
Surely nothing can escape your notice.
This zither is a rare treasure in Wanjiang.
I heard it was lost in the war.
I can't imagine that
it's in your hand.
So
are you from Wanjiang?
Of all that Your Highness has said,
the last sentence
is perhaps the key point?
Indeed,
I was born in Wanjiang.
Both my parents are zither player.
However, treacherous court officials of Wanjiang
accused my father of plotting rebellion in his songs.
My parents were killed.
I was exiled.
It's His Majesty
who cut off my bracelet and anklet,
and saved me.
If it wasn't for His Majesty,
I would have disappeared
like this Fumeng Zither.
In contrary to Your Highness,
I was born in Wanjiang,
but my heart
belongs to South Desolation.
Then
you know His Majesty better than I do.
Don't you think His Majesty
is different from before?
What do you want to say?
This is a fake emperor.
Nonsense!
Our Shadow Guard only recognize
His Majesty's handprint.
It hasn't changed recently, how can he be fake?
Thanks a lot.
You let me know my father is alive.
What do you mean?
You can check for yourself.
The zither needs to be played more often,
so it can be adjusted
to have pleasant tweedle.
My Lord.
I'm back.
I have learned from My Lord
to take precautions.
I had soldiers sneak into South Desolation
before the tunnels were sealed.
Get to the point.
Okay.
The soldiers have figured it out that
now the capital is heavily guarded.
These places are
the Imperial Palace, the Secluded House, granaries,
firearms warehouse, and three major wharves.
My father must be in one of these places.
We must rescue him as soon as possible.
Tomorrow is the time for trilateral peace talks.
It's the best time to debunk Kong Lin in public.
If only Duanmu Bai were here,
he must know Kong Lin best.
Crab,
I brought him here.
Sis!
It is not too late?
You've come just at the right moment.
Where's Duanmu Bai?
He went to check on his grandmother.
Follow this prescription,
give medicine to the Empress Dowager every day.
Remember,
don't tell anyone
I have visited the Empress Dowager.
Yes.
You can leave.
Grandma,
I'm back.
Don't worry.
I will make you better.
I told you,
sooner or later,
you and I will have another drink together.
Since I can survive,
I can have a better life.
I saw you smile.
I guess grandma's all right.
Yes.
I have every confidence
that I can save grandma.
But how did grandma fall into the water?
What is going on?
Duanmu Qingcang
pushed grandma into the water.
Why?
Because this father
is pretended by Kong Lin.
Our guess is that Kong Lin escaped from
the secret chamber that day,
sneaked into the palace and captured our father.
Kong Lin first sent assassins to kill us,
and then pretend to be our father,
sent Fuqin to rescue me,
but not you.
His purpose
was to drive a wedge in our relationship.
He wants to torture our father
by turning us against each other.
You mean our father is still alive?
I know from Fuqin
that our father is still alive.
But it is not known where he is being held.
You know Kong Lin.
Do you have any clues?
Yes.
There are two places.
One
is the Secluded House,
which is the house
father gave Kong Lin.
That's where he taught me
kung fu and art of healing.
Kong Lin said that
all the machines in the place
were designed by himself,
and they were all impregnable.
If you put it that way,
it's probably the place.
Another place is the Imperial Palace.
There is room in the palace for felons.
Perhaps Kong Lin took the opposite approach,
thinking that the most dangerous place
is also the safest place.
So he just kept father
close to him.
Why don't we take action separately?
You go to the Imperial Palace.
I go to the Secluded House.
Not now.
Both the Imperial Palace
and the Secluded House
are heavily guarded.
We only have one shot to save our father,
so we have to get it right the first time.
Peace talks will be held tomorrow.
The troops will be concentrated on
Prince Mu's Residence at that time.
Then,
whether it's the Imperial Palace,
or the Secluded House,
there will be chances.
What about the peace talks...
I believe in Rong.
As long as they can stall for time
until we rescue our father,
we can turn the tables.
Your Majesty.
General Wu,
no need for this.
I wonder
what do you want from a foreign general?
I heard that General Wu's grandmother
is also a native of South Desolation.
Your Majesty is busy
but still have time to care about
a little guy like me.
Don't put yourself down, General Wu.
In the operation of
attacking our Luocheng,
you did a great job.
Besides,
you are proficient in firearms.
However,
you didn't become a vice general
until you were 40.
Aren't you
overqualified?
Your Majesty may speak frankly.
General Wu is indeed a straightforward man!
Then let's get this straight.
At the peace talks tomorrow,
I want you
to kill someone for me.
Then the position of the General
of the South Desolation
will be vacant.
Rong,
are you worried that
something unexpected will happen tomorrow?
I am thinking
even though I used to be mediocre,
I was not afraid of anything.
I always said
I want to fight with you side by side.
Now my kung fu is as good as you,
but I became obsessed with gain and loss.
That's because you are a mother now.
You naturally think about it a little bit more.
In that case,
I am a bad mother.
After getting pregnant,
I never gave Daodao even one peaceful day.
Do you remember, Rong?
I promised you that
no matter after you married me
or had kids,
you can still be yourself,
you can still be that
dauntless Swordswoman Huahua
who has a strong sense of justice
and ready to help the weak.
Actually,
Daodao
won't become our biggest concern,
but our greatest motivator
and spiritual support.
Right,
mother is powerful.
Whether it is for Daodao
or for the people of the world,
whether there are immense difficulties or dangers,
we have to get through it
and win the final victory.
That sounds like Swordswoman Huahua.
No,
I can't.
It's okay,
Qin Shangcheng.
We're just putting on a show
to fool Jin Tong.
Haven't we tricked Fuqin before?
I can act.
But if I need to speak out your shortcomings
and pretend to divorce you,
I really can't do that.
Because you don't have any shortcomings.
How is that possible?
It's impossible to have no shortcomings.
It's just because you love me.
In my eyes and in my heart,
you are perfect,
without any shortcomings.
Then you can make up two.
It's fake anyway.
I will not believe.
Well, I'll just say two shortcomings,
but they're made up.
You certainly won't be angry,
will you?
Yes.
Then, Rong,
I'll say.
Your shortcoming is
being so beautiful
that makes me fascinated.
I didn't know I was that beautiful.
Then have a guess.
What's my shortcoming?
What's that?
I'm short of you.
You are so cute!
Love you so much!