[lively instrumental music playing]
["Shine" by Collective Soul playing]
♪ Heaven let your light shine down ♪
I can't tell if this is just a bad idea
or the worst idea in history.
At least I have ideas.
What does Jeff Ellis have going for him?
Name one thing.
- A car. A credit card.
- The highest GPA in our class.
- Parents who love him. A conscience.
- Yeah, I said one thing.
Rendell, we don't need to do this.
The puppet is good enough.
The puppet sucks.
- [laughs] Nice. Way to build me up.
- [young Rendell] Sorry.
I mean, the concept of the puppet sucks
when we have this instead.
Behold.
Caliban. Straight out
of Shakespeare's The Tempest.
Only slightly more compact.
- [eerie whoosh]
- [Caliban grunting]
[snarling]
- [young Jeff] Are you kidding me?
- [Caliban grunting]
[grunts]
- [whimpering]
- [gasps] Holy shit!
Isn't it awesome?
I can't wait to show Lucas.
[snarling]
- [yelping]
- Oh my God!
There's wood enough within!
[grunts, laughs]
He knows his lines. That's his first line.
No way. Absolutely not.
That thing goes away now.
Get rid of it, Rendell.
[Caliban grunting]
You guys are no fun.
Caliban.
Where is he?
Hey, guys.
Mr. Ridgeway said we should meet
in the theater in 15 to go over Act 4.
Gordie, man.
I thought you were out putting up flyers?
How's the Caliban puppet going?
[Caliban grunting]
What the heck was that?
Um...
- A squirrel ran in.
- There's a bat flapping around.
Which is it? A bat or a squirrel? [laughs]
- Hey, Gordie, let's... let's just go...
- Wait. It's over here, whichever it is.
[tense music playing]
[objects clattering]
Hey, little guy.
[Caliban] The red plague rid you! [bites]
Ow! Shit! It bit me!
Be not afraid. The isle is full of noises.
What the eff?
[yelps]
[Gordie] What is that thing?
- [Caliban grunting, banging]
- Is someone gonna answer me?
Give me the key.
[banging inside pail]
[Caliban grunting] My hand!
[young Gordie] What is that thing?
Show it to me.
Oh, thought I had it.
No way. You caught something
under that pail.
You and Jeff did something.
Gordie, let's go to the health center
and get the nurse...
I know what I saw!
Just 'cause I'm nice to people
doesn't mean I'm stupid, Rendell Locke.
You know, it would be really great
to feel like I'm not just a bit player
in your stories.
One of these days,
I'm gonna matter to you.
[door opens, closes]
Way to go, Rendell.
Oh, come on. He'll be fine.
- Think of the big picture.
- [pail clanks on floor]
This is proof of concept.
I mean, now we can create something bigger
for the actual production.
[scoffs]
[window whirring]
- [chuckling]
- Could you stop playing with that?
[window whirring]
[Captain] These horseless carriages,
they may be my favorite thing
about this world.
How long have they existed?
Cars?
[sighs] About 100 years.
How fast can you go?
Drive it faster.
[engine revving]
It could go faster than this.
On the highway, maybe, but...
- Faster!
- Okay.
Pretend you're being chased.
[revving]
[Captain laughs]
That's better! [laughing]
[window whirring]
[accelerating music playing]
Whoo!
Yeah!
- [tires squealing]
- [Captain screaming]
- [grunts]
- [Ellie gasps]
[panting]
[continues panting]
[whimpering]
[Captain laughing evilly]
[Ellie huffs]
[panting]
[birds chirping]
[breathes deeply]
- [Captain roars]
- [Ellie grunts, gasps]
[coughing]
Ellie, did you truly believe
that was gonna work?
[panting]
If I didn't need your assistance,
I would just squash you like a bug.
[panting]
- Come here! Get up!
- [screams]
[Nina scoffs] You're Sam?
In this body.
[Bode] He was a ghost.
Mom, he saved us.
No, he let us out of the pantry.
It's hardly saving us.
[Bode] No, before.
He taught me how to guide the birds
so I could get back into my own body.
And he showed Kinsey
where to find the Angel Key.
So, you guys are all right
with him being here?
- [Sam] Mrs. Locke...
- [inhales sharply]
I can never apologize enough
for what I did to you and your family.
Even if Dodge manipulated me,
I won't make any excuses for it.
[voice breaking]
All I can say is that I'm sorry.
I am more sorry than you can ever imagine.
You expect me to forgive you. I...
I don't expect you to. I'm... I'm just...
I just want the opportunity
to help you and your family.
[emotional music playing]
Kinsey.
I'm not ready to forgive him either...
but he did help us.
[Tyler] Right now...
[inhales deeply]
...we need some more help.
All right,
but that's as far as it goes.
Fair enough.
[Kinsey] Tyler, you, me, Rufus, and Sam,
we'll go after Ellie.
Mom, Bode, you guys try
and break into the Harlequin Chest.
Get the rest of the keys.
That we can do
or at least try.
[seagulls cawing]
[Gordie] Kenny, that is great!
Ahh! It always makes me happy
when we get a big name
for Summer Shakespeare by the Cove.
Hey, um, while we're talking about actors,
I had an idea.
[clears throat]
What if I played one of the soldiers
who sees Hamlet's father?
Well, I... I don't think
they have to be young men.
- No. No, of course.
- [door rattling]
- [table squeaks]
- [object shattering]
Hey, Kenny, I gotta run.
Good talking. Let's...
Let's pick this up later, okay?
Great. Bye.
[suspenseful music playing]
- [dramatic music plays]
- [Ellie grunts]
Ellie. What is this?
What's happening here?
- Gordie, just... [exhales sharply]
- We're not here for conversation.
[whispering] Now get what we came for.
Are you robbing me?
He wants something you've got.
A key.
A very old key.
I don't have any idea
what you're talking about. What key?
[sighs] It's inside your head.
[young Ellie] We know it was you, Gordie.
[young Gordie] What the hell
are you talking about?
Look, we know you went to Mr. Ridgeway
and told what you saw.
He just finished giving us
the third degree.
I don't know what I saw yesterday.
He's talking about canceling the play.
[young Erin] Gordie,
you were freaked out.
We get it. No one blames you.
We just wanna help you understand.
And how are you gonna do that?
[solemn music playing]
[key crunches]
[accelerating music playing]
I have so many questions.
Come on. We'll give you answers.
["Anything Goes"
by Dionne Warwick playing]
♪ Good authors too
Who once knew better words ♪
♪ Now only use four-letter words
Writing prose... ♪
[young Erin] Wow! Look at this!
[gasps] Ellie, check this out!
♪ And good's bad today ♪
♪ And black's white today
And day's night today ♪
♪ When most guys today
That women prize today... ♪
What is this place?
This is where
you keep your memories, Gordie.
Ah-ha.
♪ Hey, anything goes... ♪
[young Gordie] Hey, little guy.
- [Caliban bites]
- Ow! Shit! It bit me!
[panting]
[echoing] What the eff?
What is that thing?
Is somebody...
Found it.
- Found what?
- Your memory of what you saw yesterday.
We're just gonna borrow this along with
the memory we're making right now.
You're gonna what?
I'm so confused.
That's why we're here, Gordie,
to get you unconfused.
[song fades]
This is insane what you're saying.
All of it.
It's only because
you can't remember magic.
I'm sorry, but whatever you're suggesting,
it's not happening.
Now, I would appreciate it
if you would just go...
- [groans]
- [Ellie] Oh!
- [gasps]
- It's not a request.
[Gordie grunts]
- [sinister music playing]
- Let go of me. I'm calling the police.
- Are you, now?
- [gasps]
- [screams]
- [glass shattering]
What are you doing?
[Gordie and Ellie panting]
I am not afraid of you.
[groans]
- [Captain grunts]
- [Ellie gasps]
[groans]
[mouthing] No.
- [groans]
- [Captain exhales]
What happens if he dies
before you retrieve the key?
[sobbing] I don't know.
Oh.
Better hurry, then.
Ellie. [gasps] Ellie.
Gordie. [cries]
You didn't deserve this.
Ellie, do what you have to do
to save yourself.
[inhales sharply]
[sniffles]
I'm sorry.
[crunching]
[dramatic music playing]
[shallow breathing]
[Ellie breathes deeply]
Well...
[chuckles]
the sooner you give me my key,
the sooner you can return to tend to him.
[grunts]
[Ellie grunts]
[music intensifies]
Jamie!
Oh my God. I'm so glad to see you.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm back in my own body.
That's good.
- [Bode on phone] I need to warn you.
- Bode.
What's going on over there?
Look, you both need to know.
Gideon's on the loose in Matheson,
so please be careful. Stay inside.
- Is your mom all right?
- She's fine.
Just be on alert. I gotta go.
[end-call sound plays]
[door shuts]
You think this is actually gonna work?
[sighs] When they built this thing,
there weren't any power tools, right?
I guess not.
[object clatters on floor]
So, Bode,
when Dodge was in your body,
the way you were acting with Josh,
that was all Dodge, right?
You like Josh.
He's fine.
I-It's just... [sighs]
Can we really trust him?
He was trying to find the Black Door.
He didn't actually know what it was.
- [sighs]
- And, yes, I trust him completely.
[sighs]
Let's just open up the chest.
Try the saw.
[whirring]
[saw straining]
- [clanking]
- [Nina squeals]
[whirring stops]
[sizzling]
Uh...
Not good.
[whirring]
- [clanking]
- [high-pitched whir]
[whirring stops]
[sizzling]
Looks like we're gonna need to
up the ante.
I feel like a horrible, irresponsible mom.
You're not irresponsible.
We've got this,
which we'll use when the wood burns enough
for us to use that.
See?
Totally safe.
Got a light?
No way. I've got this part. Stand back.
Okay.
[lighter clicks]
- [laughs] Yes!
- I'm definitely a bad mom.
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
[Nina scoffs]
It's using magic to protect itself.
Okay. Uh...
I have one more idea.
[seagulls cawing]
I don't see anyone.
[Tyler] But Ellie's car is here.
Let's go around back,
see if Kins found a way in.
This is bad.
This is really bad.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Tyler panting]
[Kinsey panting]
He's got a pulse,
but he's lost so much blood.
- We need to put pressure on the wound.
- Which one?
I don't know. Both of them.
Mr. Shaw needs to get emergency treatment,
or he's going to die.
My mom's got a first aid kit in her car.
I can get bandages
and compresses and call 911.
but you need to help my mom.
All right. Um...
You and Sam stay here and look after him.
Sam should go with you.
He's in an Echo's body.
He can protect you.
[operator on phone]
911. what's your emergency?
You need to send paramedics immediately
to the house of Gordie Shaw.
He's been stabbed. He's bleeding badly.
[curious music playing]
["Put On A Happy Face"
by Dick Van Dyke playing]
[cheering]
♪ Put on a happy face ♪
[Sam] This is actually pretty cool.
Every theater must have
some of Gordie's memories.
Which one do you think they're in?
[song ends]
This better not be a wild goose chase.
It's not.
These keys have cost you your friends.
They've threatened the life
of you and your son.
Why do you stand in my way?
[Ellie] I've been to your world.
It's hopeless.
It's full of terrible things.
You judge, and yet your kind created a key
with the sole purpose
of subjugating others.
Another to pillage
the private sanctums of the soul,
and yet another
that burns everything that it touches.
Your kind and mine,
we aren't far apart.
[scoffs]
You're insane.
Just get me my goddamn key.
Gordie, you're here early.
I couldn't sleep. Too excited.
Actually, I'm glad I caught you.
Look, I know how hard you worked
on that Act 5 soliloquy.
Thank you.
But I've decided to give the part
to Rendell Locke.
I'm sorry, Gordie.
Oh. Well, he'll do great.
But you'll be our understudy.
Still an important role to play.
Sure. Thanks, Mr. Ridgeway.
[door creaking]
- [door closes]
- Whoa. It's Dad.
[young Rendell] It's bullshit.
I tried out as a joke.
It ought to be yours.
No, really. It's a sign of respect.
Mr. Ridgeway knows
that I learn everybody's lines
so I can jump in anywhere, anytime.
He... He trusts me. That's the thing.
It's... He really...
I'll drop out.
Look, don't you dare!
I don't wanna get the part like that.
Even background characters
have a part to play.
Don't tell yourself
you're background, Gordie.
You're so much more than that. All right?
Let's go.
[sinister music playing]
[Captain] Where are we?
Under the stage, where he keeps
all the stuff he doesn't wanna look at.
[Captain chuckles]
What kinds of thoughts and feelings
does Mr. Gordon Shaw want to avoid?
- His hate.
- [screeching]
- His fear.
And his rage.
- [roaring]
- [Captain yells]
[roaring continues]
[Captain yells]
- [yelling]
- [hatch closes]
[Nina] Gideon knows what happens to him
if he steps into the well house, right?
Hang on, Mom.
[grunts]
All right.
Great, that should do it.
Even if he gets the last key from Ellie,
he'll never be able
to get the rest of the keys from the chest
without walking into the well house.
Not bad.
[door opens]
Wait, what?
- [Nina] More magic.
- [Bode] Okay.
[inhales deeply] This is gonna be
a lot harder than I thought.
[rumbling]
["Good, Good Morning"
by Network Music Ensemble playing]
♪ Good, good morning meeting ♪
♪ We're gonna have a great time together ♪
♪ We got a lot of information
A perfect situation... ♪
Not sure any of these are right.
["Good, Good Morning" continues playing]
What are you doing?
Listening.
That's how we've
always found the keys before.
Hearing anything?
Who could hear anything over that music?
Give it a rest!
- [music warping]
- [lights flickering]
Nice one.
I didn't do anything.
The lights are going out.
Thanks, Sam. Appreciate the update.
No, I mean forever.
- [sighs]
- I think Gordie's dying.
[shallow breathing]
Somebody's coming.
[suspenseful music playing]
[music intensifies]
- [Tyler] It's Ellie.
- [sighs]
Oh! Oh! Oh my God!
- What are you doing in here?
- We came to help you.
Where's Rufus?
[dramatic music playing]
[Rufus exhales]
- [knocking on door]
- [paramedic] Paramedics. Open up.
[exhales sharply]
- [knocking continues]
- [paramedic] Paramedics. Open up.
Oh no. Oh no.
Oh, no, no. They can't see the two bodies.
He's safe. He's outside with Gordie.
Where's Gideon?
I trapped him in the stage basement.
Did you get the key?
Not yet. What is he doing here?
It's okay. He, uh... He's Sam.
Long story.
[liquid oozing]
[Kinsey] Maybe Sam's right.
- Do you know where the key is?
- [sighs] It's in there.
I hid the key
in the pocket of Prospero's cloak.
Okay, let's do this.
Get the hell out of here.
Lo, how he mocks me!
Wilt thou let him, my lord?
"Lord," quoth he.
That a monster should be such a natural.
Lo, lo, again.
Bite him to death, I prithee.
[student] Trinculo,
keep a good tongue in your head.
If you prove a mutineer, the next tree.
The poor monster's my subject,
and he shall not suffer indignity.
I don't understand.
It's not there?
[Ellie] It has to be.
I put it in here myself. I...
[student] Marry, will I.
Kneel and repeat it.
Not there. We need a better spot.
[scoffs] It'll be fine.
[dramatic music playing]
[music intensifies]
[sighs]
Erin must have moved it.
She didn't think
it was a safe enough spot. Shit!
- [liquid oozing]
- [students speaking indistinctly]
[creaking]
[foreboding music playing]
Okay, screw the key. We gotta go.
Without the key?
He's dying.
We don't wanna be stuck in here.
Why, I said nothing.
[student] Mum then, no more. Proceed.
[young Gordie] Tomorrow,
and tomorrow, and tomorrow...
- This is different.
- What is this?
...from day to day, to the last syllable...
[pants] Let's go.
[young Gordie] ...our yesterdays
have lighted fools the way to dusty death...
You've got them all over your face.
Are they good, Gordie?
The best!
Life is but a walking shadow...
[Ellie] Wait!
[young Gordie] ...a poor player, who struts...
We were just here.
[young Gordie] ...and then is heard no more.
[old groovy music playing]
[young Gordie] I didn't mean to upset you.
I didn't mean to upset you.
How long have you known?
A while, I think.
You should have told me. [echoing]
[young Gordie] You're not listening to me.
[Gordie's mom] It's just a phase.
[girlfriend] You should have told me.
I'm not talking about this.
Fine. Okay.
[young Gordie] ...who struts and frets
his hour upon the stage
and then is heard no more.
["The Trolley Song"
by Judy Garland playing]
[young Gordie] It is a tale
told by an idiot.
Mom, please, if you would just meet him!
[door slams]
I'm thrilled to unveil
the new Matheson High School theater!
- [cheering]
- [Tyler exhales sharply]
- This is pointless.
- [piano playing]
- [sighs]
- [indistinct whispers]
What's that?
[whispers continue]
Whispers.
I hear whispers. [pants]
[whispers continue]
[breathing heavily]
[breathes deeply]
Having trouble finding your way?
The whispers are coming from there.
Go. Talk to him.
I've got a plan.
[piano continues playing]
[indistinct whispers]
In my world,
beautiful music can be made
by pulling apart a soul.
So let's end all this.
Mmm, give me the key,
and we can all leave together.
Play games,
you could find out what happens here
when the lights go out for good.
We couldn't find it.
It wasn't where I left it.
- [key clicking]
- That's a lie.
That's a goddamn lie!
[whirring]
[frantic music playing]
[Captain grunts]
If you know where the key is,
grab it, and then you need to go.
What are you doing?
Slowing him down.
- Try going out the front of the theater.
- [grunts]
What treachery is this, Bolton?
- [Sam grunts]
- [Captain yells]
- [groans]
- Sorry, not Bolton.
Run! Go, get out of here!
What about you?
I'll meet you outside his head. Go!
[indistinct whispers]
- Kins.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- [Tyler] Kinsey, come on!
- [keys clicking]
[whispering intensifies]
[frantic music continues]
[sighs]
Brilliant.
[Captain grunts]
- [cranking]
- [yelps]
- [crashing]
- [gasps]
[Ellie and Tyler gasp]
[Tyler sighs]
- Whoa!
- Oh shit!
Sam!
[Sam] Go!
Seriously, go!
[yelps, grunts]
[grunting]
- [grunts]
- [Sam groans]
[grunts]
[body thuds]
[piano creaking]
- [piano clangs]
- [groans]
[pants, grunts]
[Sam panting]
No!
[siren wailing]
BP is crashing.
- [monitor beeping rapidly]
- V-fib, he's coding.
- Defibrillate him.
- I'm doing that now.
- Charging and clear!
- [defibrillator shocking]
- [girlfriend] You should've told me!
- [Gordie] Last syllable of recorded time...
- I didn't mean to upset you.
- [Kinsey] What is that?
We're stuck in a loop.
[paramedic] No change.
ETA is ten minutes. Just keep him alive.
[paramedic] Giving him one dose epi.
[Gordie's mom]
I'm not talking to you about this...
[siren wailing]
[panting]
Mr. Shaw. Mr. Shaw.
[frantic music continues]
[panting]
What do I do?
- [knocking on door]
- [officer] Matheson Police. Open up.
[knocking continues]
[officer] Is anybody in there?
Open the door. This is Matheson Police.
[knocking on door]
[officer] We have reports of a stabbing.
Sir.
- I'm gonna need you to turn around.
- Wait, I didn't do...
- Put your hands against that wall.
- [grunts]
Do you have any weapons on you?
Any sharp objects?
Please, no. I didn't do anything.
- [monitor dinging]
- [siren wailing]
We're losing him!
[frantic music continues]
[Gordie's memories
unintelligibly overlapping]
[heart beating]
[music intensifies]
- [heart beat stops]
- [music stops]
[lively instrumental music playing]