[lively instrumental music playing]
[siren wailing]
V-fib! He's coding!
[monitor flatlining]
[defibrillator charging, shocking]
[somber music playing]
[young Gordie] "Yea, all which it inherit,
shall dissolve."
"And, like this
insubstantial pageant faded,
leave not a rack behind."
"We are such stuff as dreams are made on,
and our little life
is rounded with a sleep."
[nostalgic music playing]
[Ellie] You guys!
We can't just keep running!
[Kinsey] He's dying. And we're...
[Tyler] We're gonna get outta here!
[music intensifies, stops]
- [flatlining]
- [paramedic 1] Push one more epinephrine!
[paramedic 2] Pushing one more epi!
[tense music playing]
[flatlining]
- [beeps]
- [paramedic 2] I got something!
I think it's Gordie!
He's trying to show us the way out!
[all shouting, grunting]
[Tyler] What the hell?
We've gotta go through it. Come on!
[all panting]
Rufus! Rufus!
Gordie's gone.
- Rufus!
- [officer] Freeze! Police!
- [gun cocking]
- Do not move.
Put your hands up on the wall.
- Mom, are you all right?
- I am. Are you okay?
- Shut up, all of you.
- Turn around!
- Where's Sam?
- I said don't talk!
- [panting]
- [tense music continues]
[buzzing]
[Captain roars]
Listen to me. We can explain,
but we all need
to get out of here right now.
- Johnny.
- [heart beating]
- [Johnny] What is that thing?
- It won't make any sense.
Please! We just have to go!
[heart beating]
You're seeing this, right?
You don't wanna go in there!
[Captain yelling]
[dramatic music playing]
[grunts]
- [gasps]
- Freeze, right there! [grunts]
Where's my damn keys?
- Stop!
- [groans]
- [gun fires]
- [grunts]
[panting]
[body hits the floor]
[heart beating slowly]
[both panting]
Sam.
[labored breathing]
[somber music playing]
- [labored breathing]
- [monitor flatlining]
[monitor flatlining]
[exhales]
[birds chirping]
No.
[panting]
This way.
Hey, get back here!
[Captain groaning]
No. No, it's not.
Stop.
- You stop!
- [gun firing]
[groans]
[grunts]
[panting]
[Kinsey] Oh! [pants]
[all panting]
[somber music playing]
[sighs]
I'm so sorry, Ellie.
We can't let Gideon win.
[key crunches]
Run!
Do whatever you have to do
to keep those keys from Gideon.
- What about you?
- Don't worry. We'll go someplace safe.
You still have the Creation Key?
[Kinsey] What does it do?
You can make anything come to life
just by drawing it,
by drawing a sketch of it.
Now go!
Come on, come on!
- [gun firing]
- [Captain groans]
- [knife swishes]
- [officer chokes]
[dramatic music playing]
[exhales]
[Kinsey] Come on! We gotta go!
[dramatic music playing]
[both panting]
[panting]
- [Kinsey and Tyler panting]
- [gasps]
And you can't get the chest open?
No, it's impossible.
What about Tyler and Kinsey?
[sighs] Nothing yet.
I'm starting to get worried.
[banging on door]
Who's that?
- [banging continues]
- [Ellie] Josh! Josh!
It's Ellie and Rufus!
[panting] We need your help.
Okay, come in.
[frantic music playing]
[both panting]
- Shit!
- Uh...
The key! The key!
Okay, here goes nothing.
[whizzing]
- That's pretty cool. Okay.
- [muffled thud]
- [loud music playing on speakers]
- [confused chatter]
[whizzing]
- [Kinsey] Excuse me!
- [Tyler panting] Sorry!
Good thing you won't remember this.
- [banging on door]
- [people gasp] Oh!
- [man] Stand back, stand back!
- Stand back.
- [banging continues]
[alarmed chatter]
- [people yelping, clamoring]
- [grunts]
- [man 1] Oh my God!
- [man 2 yelps]
[grunts]
- [Kinsey panting]
- We can't outrun him!
Wait! Give me the key!
What are you doing?
Getting us to Keyhouse.
[Tyler] He's coming!
[Captain panting]
[Tyler] What is that? A bicycle?
[whizzing]
[Tyler] Nice.
- [grunting]
- Ty, we gotta go!
- [tires screeching]
- [Captain grunts, groans]
[body hits the ground]
[heroic music playing]
Go! Get out of here!
[engine starts]
[tires screeching]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Captain grunting]
[exhales]
You.
Hmm...
- [grunts, groans]
- [Captain grunts]
[Josh groaning]
[groaning, huffs]
[engine starting, revving]
[tires screeching]
Clever device.
- [engine revving]
- [tires squealing]
[yelps, groans]
[panting]
[dramatic music playing]
[tires squealing]
Whoa!
- [horn blaring]
- [tires screeching]
[tires squealing]
[engine revving]
[Kinsey] That's Josh's car.
[tires screeching]
Hah.
I think it's Gideon!
How does he even know how to drive?
[Captain growls]
Come on!
[revving]
[accelerating music playing]
- [tires squealing]
- [Captain] Turn for me! Turn!
[screaming]
[crashing]
[engine revving]
[exploding]
[grim music playing]
[groans]
[dramatic music playing]
[panting] What happened?
Where's Rufus and Ellie!
- [panting] They're safe! Yeah!
- [Bode] Did you get the key?
Cool! What does it do?
Whatever you draw with it
becomes a real version of that thing.
No way! Like what?
Like a door. Or a motorcycle.
You guys drew a motorcycle,
and it came to life?
Are you guys hurt?
We... We got the key, but...
Gordie didn't make it. Gideon killed him.
Oh my God!
Wait, where's Sam?
He was trapped inside when Gordie died.
Wait. What? What does that mean?
I think it means...
I think it means he's dead too.
But we... we don't have a lot of time.
Gideon's on his way here right now.
- Did you get the chest open?
- No, we tried everything!
- It's protected by magic.
- [breathing heavily]
Okay. If we can't get the Alpha Key,
then we have to find a way
to get Gideon in the well house.
Or maybe we can use the Creation Key
to draw some weapons.
Or both.
[crickets chirping]
[animal howling]
[Captain breathing heavily]
[Tyler] Hey, Gideon!
Over here!
Here I am, boy.
You're looking for these, right?
You insult my intelligence.
As if I don't know the rule.
Did you honestly believe
that I would just walk through that door
and disappear for you?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Oh, no, of course not.
But here's something that you should know.
Whenever you choose to emerge,
I will make sure that your death
is painfully exquisite.
[breathes deeply] Uh...
I guess you've got me.
But no...
you have some clever little trick.
Well, kind of.
[engine starts]
- [grunts]
- Watch out! Coming through!
[grunting]
It's working!
[straining]
[grunting]
[powering down]
- [engine revving]
- [grunting]
[grunting]
Come on!
[yelling]
[straining]
- [grunting]
- [clanking]
[yells]
Uh-oh.
- [Captain growling]
- [clanks]
[grunts]
- [grunting]
- [gate clanking]
[growling]
[bricks tumbling]
[grunting]
[grunting, yelling]
[bricks tumbling]
- [thudding]
- [bricks tumbling]
- [grunting]
- [rumbling]
And thus ends this prison.
We need the Alpha Key. It's the only way.
I told you we can't get into the chest.
There's no way to defeat magic.
- Unless you have magic.
- [door opens]
We've gotta get out of here!
- Give me the key.
- What?
The Creation Key! Give it to me!
[frantic music playing]
[whizzing]
Wow, very amazing key.
[clinking]
[sighs]
- [dramatic music playing]
- [glass shattering]
- [Tyler] Kinsey!
- [Kinsey screaming]
- [Captain] The key!
- [Kinsey gasps]
Or she dies.
- [yells]
- [Captain growls]
No.
You fucking die!
- [Kinsey screams]
- [growling]
[snarls]
- [Kinsey screaming]
- [snarling]
[screaming]
[Tyler yells]
- [Nina grunts]
- [Captain grunts]
[epic music playing]
[demonic scream]
[sighing]
He's gone.
It worked.
- We did it.
- [sighs]
[both panting]
Did you see that?
What?
The portal got smaller when he fell in.
Why would that happen?
Two keys went in with him.
Wait, what are you doing?
I just need to test something.
That's the Head Key!
[whooshing]
[gasps]
You're right.
Tossing the key in made it smaller.
You can't just throw away keys
without consultation.
We can board it up or build another door.
That didn't work too well
the first time around, did it?
We could build a stronger door.
One that no one could get into.
Look. I, um, think we all know
what needs to happen here.
We need to give up the keys. [sighs]
Throw them all back where they came from.
But they've helped us so much.
Have they?
I mean, they're the reason Dad's gone
and so many other people.
Eden, Jackie, Joe, Gordie.
[Tyler] And all the original
Keepers of the Keys.
Gideon was right about one thing.
The keys, they never belonged to us.
Mom, come on. We can't just give up magic.
I'm sorry, bud.
But I agree.
- The keys aren't good.
- [sighs disappointedly]
[Nina] They make people
do terrible things.
They corrupt people.
They cause harm and pain.
Even your father,
he couldn't resist them.
[Nina sighs]
I think Tyler's right.
Me too.
[Tyler sighs]
So I'm outvoted, then.
I was hoping this could be
a unanimous thing.
Bode, what is it you want from the keys?
Just one more thing.
If we can do that...
[sighs]...then I'll agree.
[birds chirping]
Shotgun!
Seriously, again?
Dibs on music!
[laughs] So much for
a quiet carpool to work.
Still time to play hooky.
- Ugh. Tempting.
- [Rendell] Mmm.
- See you tonight. Love you.
- Love you.
Hey, your mom,
she loves AC/DC in the morning.
Play it really loud.
Okay, Dad.
[chuckles]
- [car door closes]
- [engine starts]
[sniffles]
[keys clacking]
[door opens]
[laughs]
Forget your hockey gloves again, Ty?
[door closes]
[Nina] Rendell.
[exhales]
[emotional music playing]
[chuckles]
Oh my God.
[all laughing]
[Tyler] You should've seen us
cleaning those spiderwebs
before Mom got home.
[laughs] I don't even wanna know all
the things that I missed pre Memory Key.
Like the time I went to Coachella
and back for a day.
Now that was cool.
Oh... [laughs] You are definitely
your father's daughter.
[laughs]
- See, the keys weren't all bad.
- [Nina] Mmm.
No, not always.
It doesn't change the fact
that we have to get rid of them.
Hey, you're doing something
that I was never strong enough to do.
I wish I could've...
[inhales deeply]
...protected you from all this,
but now you get to finish what I started.
I'm so proud of you.
But don't you miss the keys?
Didn't they make you feel special?
[sighs]
Yeah. Yeah, they did.
But, uh, I spent a long time
trying to hold on to that,
and it never compared
to every day with you guys.
[breathes deeply]
This was the real magic.
This is all I ever needed.
You've learned something
that I never could.
[alarm ringing]
[sighs]
One minute left.
I wish we could stay longer.
Eh, I know.
- [laughs] Me too.
- [sighs, chuckles]
[breathes deeply]
But you gotta go live your lives.
That's all I want.
For you to be happy.
You won't remember this.
No, but you will. [sighs]
And that's all that matters.
The past is always with us.
[exhales sharply]
- Come here.
- [Kinsey sniffles]
["Breathe" by Ásgeir playing]
♪ Shivering stars drift around
In the sky ♪
♪ I lie calm under their watchful eyes ♪
♪ In my heart I can feel it and why ♪
♪ That wherever I go
I'll find my way home ♪
I'll find my way home... ♪
[key clicking and cranking]
[whooshing]
["Breathe" continues playing]
♪ Where the fair winds
And following seas ♪
[whooshing]
♪ Slowly rush in and put me at ease ♪
[portal whirring]
♪ I will set sails and follow the breeze ♪
♪ And wherever I go
I'll find my way home ♪
[vocalizing]
[whooshing]
[screaming]
- [screaming]
- [creature growling]
[screaming]
[creature screeching]
How's that for a lobster trap?
[audience cheering]
[creature grunting, trilling]
Nephropidae forever!
- Nephropidae!
- Whoo!
And that is exactly why
I will be taking my fake blood recipe
with me to the grave.
[all laughing]
Um, so, when can we expect
a Splattering 3?
[audience] Yeah! [cheering]
Yeah!
[laughs]
Um, that's a tough one.
We're all hyper-focused
on college tours
and applications these days.
But hey, never say never, right?
No. No, I can say that I will never wear
that Nephropidae suit ever again.
[audience laughing]
I noticed you gave special thanks
to Sam Lesser in the credits.
Weird choice considering...
Well, you know.
You know, that's not something
we really wanna get into.
Sam was a troubled kid.
But if a killer lobster
is capable of redemption,
then so is Sam Lesser.
Uh, yeah, I think I see another hand
just out there.
[audience murmuring and cheering]
[Scot] Hi there. Big fan, brilliant film.
But I have to admit,
you did Nathaniel dirty.
- What? Not even a proper on-screen death?
- [laughs]
- [all applauding]
- [Kinsey laughing]
[cheering]
[joyful orchestral music playing]
[audience cheering and applauding]
I can't believe you're really here.
Yeah, well, just till Monday,
but it was worth the jet lag
just to see the look on your faces.
[Zadie] Let's grab our stuff
and head to Doug's garage to celebrate.
It might be hard to imagine,
but I've actually missed Doug's garage.
I think I still have your smoothie maker.
- Now it's a party.
- Right? We'll meet you there.
So how are the Lockes faring these days
without their keys?
Surprisingly well.
Normal feels nice.
It'll definitely be weird in a year or so.
I'm just sorry we couldn't keep
the Memory Key for you and the Savinis.
Listen, don't be.
You know, maybe that was
the genius of The Splattering.
Magic will always exist.
We got it on tape,
and no stupid rule about forgetting
is gonna take that away from us. Never.
[chuckles softly]
And Rochester is going well?
Yeah, yeah.
It's challenging, but I like that
and made some good friends.
No one like this lot, of course.
Obviously.
No one like you.
I've missed you.
It's hard, isn't it?
Pretending it doesn't hurt?
You know,
RISD has a pretty awesome
global exchange program
if I get accepted. [chuckles]
Hold on. Are you saying you might
find yourself on my side of the pond?
- Maybe.
- [chuckles]
Would that be a good thing? [chuckles]
Kins, there's... there's good.
There's great.
And then there's like...
like another tier of excellent.
And that's where you find us.
[chuckles]
[romantic music playing]
[all laughing]
And then we took a kayak
to the Rock Islands
and went for a swim in the lake.
It was amazing.
Totally worth
the multiple jellyfish stings.
The fact that the lake
is literally called Jellyfish Lake
should have prepared us for that.
I've driven on the Highway to the Sun.
It doesn't literally go to the sun.
[Nina] So what you're saying is,
"Don't have Duncan
book our next family vacation."
[Duncan] Well, that's a bit hyperbolic.
I do have tamer options available
for the timid.
- [Duncan laughs]
- We miss anything exciting here?
Well, I was assaulted
at the Meeting House.
And then my car was stolen and totaled.
So anyone who tells you
that there is less crime in a small town
has never been to Matheson, Massachusetts.
- Did they catch them?
- No, not even any leads.
But on the plus side, that means I can
test drive some new rides this afternoon.
[Brian] Oh.
Need any help?
Really?
Sure. I'm an excellent negotiator,
and I'll make sure you don't get swindled.
- That would be great.
- [laughter]
[Bode] Oh my goodness!
[indistinct chatter and laughter]
- Shotgun!
- Oh man!
- [Jamie] You snooze, you lose!
- [Nina] Good luck. [chuckles]
- You sure you don't wanna come?
- Oh, I'm quite sure. Have fun.
- Bye.
That's good to see
that Bode's finally warming up to Josh.
Yeah, he scored some extra points
when Bode heard
that he rammed Gideon with his car.
Even though Josh can't remember doing it.
Is that weird?
- [chuckles] No. Not as bad as I thought.
- [horn honks]
On the other side,
there would have been so many questions,
but now we can just all move on together.
Clean slate.
And the well house?
[Nina] I was thinking
I might put up a greenhouse there.
[Duncan] I love that idea.
Or, and I'm just spitballing here,
a little guest house
for when your favorite brothers-in-law
come to visit.
- Throw in a hot tub.
- [Nina laughs]
- Not sure that's gonna happen.
- [Duncan laughs]
But you'll always have your room upstairs
for when you come and visit often.
No, Josh is for sure gonna turn that
into his man cave or something.
Oh, funny. No, it's yours.
Always.
- [emotional music playing]
- [sighs]
[chuckles softly]
[Nina chuckles]
- [Duncan sighs]
- [Nina chuckles]
[birds chirping]
Okay, so we've got
plenty of sandwich stuff in the fridge,
and I'll be home before dinner.
Oh crap! Is that toothpaste?
- [Rufus] Mom.
- [sighs]
You've got this.
[sighs deeply]
[inhales deeply] Are you good?
Yeah, just finishing
the last chapter of Squadron Strange.
Impressive.
So do Sergeant E and her troops
eventually find their way back home?
They realized they already were home.
[inspirational music playing]
[Ellie kissing] See you later.
Break a leg.
We're so thrilled
you've decided to come back.
Thanks. Feels good.
The timing couldn't be more perfect,
with fall sign-up starting today.
[Ellie] Can't wait.
- [chuckling]
- Hopefully, we get a decent turnout.
I think you could say that.
Welcome back, Coach Whedon.
[students cheering and applauding]
[Ellie laughing]
[indistinct cheer]
[Carly on phone] You're just lucky
I sweet-talked Glen
into giving you your job back.
[Tyler] Yeah, I hear the talent pool
for underpaid, overworked
construction workers in Montana is vast.
You know you love it.
I do, actually.
Looking forward to getting back.
But first, road trip.
[Tyler] Yeah, so if I make good time,
I should be able to meet you in Nashville
by Tuesday morning.
Ooh, and we have to stop in Colorado
at the UFO Watchtower.
For sure. Plus, maybe a little detour
into Baja, California.
Where Glen will be calling
to fire us both.
[chuckles]
[Bode] Why are we packing your car now?
Because I'm heading out at sunrise,
and I know what you're like
when you have to get up before 8:00.
Yeah, and we've officially retired
from battling monsters.
[Bode] Hey!
I threw some breakfast bars in here.
Sorry. [laughs]
- I couldn't help myself.
- Thanks.
So, can we come visit you?
Of course, but I'll be back
in the fall for your birthday.
With Carly?
Possibly.
I already invited her.
What? We text.
[inhales deeply]
[sighs]
[nostalgic music playing]
I never thought I'd say this, but...
I'm gonna miss this place.
Even if it's a little Norman Bates.
- Turns out it was a lot Norman Bates.
- [Nina and Kinsey chuckle]
Who's Norman Bates?
[Kinsey chuckles]
[joyful orchestral music playing]
[Bode] Wait.
Do you guys hear that?
Hear what?
What are you hearing?
Nothing.
Absolutely nothing.
[sweeping orchestral music playing]
[music stops abruptly]
[indistinct whispering]
[music resumes]
[music ends]
[lively instrumental music playing]