What do we do?
You are embarrassing me. Stop crying.
I am not dead.
Don't do it.
Don't ever do it. I will never
see you again if you do.
If you do it again, I will never see you.
Don't you dare.
Hey.
Does that punk know?
Know what?
That you look like a baboon when you cry.
Also, you are a crybaby.
Shut up.
Don't tell me you will do it again.
Why are you crying so much?
You will tire yourself out.
Gosh. Don't eat your hair.
Don't.
Come on. Don't eat it.
What are you doing here?
Are you okay?
Why do you keep showing up?
Since I am here, you can go now.
Who are you to tell me to go?
You.
I pity you.
Who do you think you are?
I told you to go.
Just go.
No, you should go.
What?
You should go.
Don't text or call me.
Don't come looking for me at home.
You make me sick.
I will go for today since
I see that you are okay.
I will have more chances in the future.
Are you trying to pick a fight?
I told you not to hang around Dongman.
Aera.
You should know your place.
What?
I will make it clear
since you look confused.
The reason why he's holding
your hand right now is,
not because he wants to.
He's doing it to show me.
Hey.
What do you know?
Pick up the phone when I call.
If not, I will take it as
if you want me to visit.
Why are you glaring at me?
Did you really grab my
hand for her to see?
Why did you grab my hand?
I don't know.
I am hurt.
She is pure evil.
How could she even think
about coming back to you?
Still, she waited for me for two
years when I was in the military.
Huh!
I really don't know why you
think she waited for you.
I told you. I saw her in a
karaoke room with some guy.
She genuinely likes to sing.
Aha.
She genuinely likes to sing,
so she was singing a duet
alone with a guy at midnight.
It is all in the past.
You look like it isn't all in the past.
It is so obvious what she'll do and how
big of a sucker you'll be for her.
It is very clear to see.
What is so clear?
Do you know everything about us?
What?
-Us?
-I mean...
Why are you pouncing on words? You
know that's not what I meant.
Sure. I shouldn't get
involved in your business.
I shouldn't care even if you
do something moronic and die.
Mister, go kill him.
Wait. I meant to tell you.
Hold on. Calm down first.
My brow is all ripped up.
I am injured. I am telling
you I am injured.
I am glad you are alive.
You are lucky you didn't die.
Street Fighter's True Identity
That is so good.
So, you did land a punch, right?
I don't know. I got beaten
up too much to remember.
Watch.
He shook a little after being hit by you.
People are so quick. When
did they shoot this?
Who else? It must be Taehee.
Mr Yang?
Why are you calling him Mister?
Hey.
Those jerks completely duped you.
That's why they didn't
shoot Karel's face at all.
-Those scumbags.
-Karel?
Do you know the guy who fought me?
Look here.
This tattoo is their symbol.
Thank you, thank you. Oh, thank you!
Your wife will be okay.
And...
Yes. Money. Money go.
I go money... What am I saying?
Tell him I sent the money for
his wife's medical bills.
You...
He knows. He checked
right after the fight.
Hey, thank you.
Yes. What? What is it?
Try your best to avoid him.
Because you will lose.
Wow. What did he say?
The public doesn't know about Karel.
He just coached his nephews at home.
But what family is his like?
Brazilian jujitsu champions
for three generations.
The guy you fought is their second son.
The nephew that he trained
informally at home
is the UFC legend, John Carlos.
It is like a kindergartner landed
a punch on a college student.
You won.
Here is your protein-mixed coffee.
By the way, coach.
You bought him a business
class air ticket.
You are so generous with
other people's money.
Then? Should I have someone with a
broken rib fly coach to Brazil?
Is his rib broken? Why?
Dongman landed an attack 58 seconds into
the fight. It broke two of his ribs.
But the thing is, it
wasn't a kick but a hook.
Play the video again.
-Okay.
-You heard what Karel said, right?
How would I know what he said?
He said to do all you
can to avoid Dongman.
What?
He said you'll lose.
That punk. I gave him money,
and he spews out nonsense.
So? Will you go to the
hospital or the gym?
The hospital? Are you sick? Are you hurt?
He wants to get a chin Botox touch-up.
Let's go to the gym.
Yummy.
Seolhui, just say hi and leave.
I don't want you staying there.
The cookie is over baked.
You are not listening.
-I am going.
-Make a lot of money!
Make a lot of money!
Dongman.
Why are you running around the
neighborhood from the early morning?
He needs to be beaten up more
to give up MMA fighting.
He wasn't beaten up enough.
-Not enough.
-Hey.
The swelling is down.
Seolhui. Are you going to
the baby's birthday party?
Yes. How do I look? Do I look sweet?
-That is what you look like.
-What?
The Cheongdam-dong, subtle look. You
know, the subtle but luxurious look.
I know.
Actually, you can just wear trainers. You
look like the ideal daughter-in-law.
Elders like the puppy type like you.
Really? Look who's talking!
You are the kitten type
that guys go crazy over!
Really?
Am I? A kitten?
Why aren't you saying anything?
I am offended.
Why would a human talk
while animals are yapping?
Geez.
Dog, enjoy the birthday party.
Cat, let's go eat.
Why would I eat with you?
Eat with your girl, Hyeran. Your Hyeran!
Why is she being different?
Why is she getting annoyed?
She is acting like a girl.
Wait for me!
EBC Announcer Recruitment
Required Qualifications
KBC Announcer Recruitment
You have passed round one.
What?
Goodness.
It went through.
It went through? What did? Where?
I don't see anything.
I made it through round one
for the announcer job.
You did?
They want to interview me!
Oh gosh! That is great!
Hey.
What do I do?
What do I wear? What should I wear?
Hold on.
Hey, you.
Are you not...
What?
Why do you go around like that?
I know we are near home, but...
What?
I am going crazy. Why won't she pick up?
What use is a phone if you don't pick up?
Seolhui, hang up.
You drive me crazy. You
said you don't have much.
-Give it to me.
-Don't get it on you.
You should have taken a cab if you
have this much stuff, not the subway.
I was afraid there would be traffic.
Do you have liquid in here?
Yes, a few bottles of
the sweet rice drink.
You said you just made a
little bit of snacks!
How can I send that to our
future in-law's party?
I made little bit of japchae, some
rice cakes and a tiny bit of jokbal.
You know those are my specialty.
How could you forget that?
Where's your brain?
Still, this isn't necessary.
I know this much isn't necessary.
What was that?
Are you two close?
Hello.
Who...
Madam lives on the fifth floor.
She is our landlady and
she moved in recently.
Miss, not Madam.
Call me Ganako Hwang.
Hello.
By the way, do you wallpaper
the rooms yourself?
Why should I waste money on laborers?
I dislike people who don't
work and play all day,
more than anything or anyone.
Make sure to pay your rent on time.
One more thing.
No matter how close you may be,
you cannot sleep in the
same room together.
Well...
Why would we even do that?
I shut out and prevent
all possible advances.
Those on our floor are more innocent
than monks living in a temple.
What are you looking at?
I like how resolute the
guy is for a change.
Make me some instant coffee.
I like it sweet.
Where do you think you're coming?
I am blocking you out.
Why is she getting upset all of a sudden?
I said stop acting like a woman around me.
I guess you are ready to get married.
I can't believe you baked cookies.
It is because I got bored
after work last night.
Hey, why do you work so hard anyway?
Quit when you get married.
Your dad turns off the TV whenever
he lands on a home shopping channel.
He can't stop thinking
that his daughter is,
always on the phone taking orders.
He says it makes him sick and angry.
I just have to sit down
and answer the phone.
There it is.
Will you come in and say hi?
No, of course not.
I am not dressed well enough.
I think you look just fine.
-I told you to get bangs.
-Don't touch my hair.
My goodness.
When you see Jooman's mom, ask her when
to arrange meeting between families.
Okay, I will.
I'll go now.
They must be heavy.
-Are you really going?
-See you.
Take care and answer
your phone when I call!
To solve the North's nuclear
issue, President Trump
reportedly decided to put pressure on...
Should I just nuke her?
Hyeran Returns to TV
How dare she show up in
front of Dongman again?
Also, he is about to fall for her again.
Get your coffee from a temple somewhere.
Share a coffee with Hyeran.
Your Hyeran...
Are you talking about me?
You...
Hello.
Amazing. Is this where you live?
Do you want to become an announcer again?
With me as a role model?
Do you have a habit of coming now?
I dropped by to see you
before visiting Dongman.
I have something to tell you.
Say it or not. I don't care.
I won't do anything you want.
-Aera.
-What?
Can you see how childish you're being now?
Then what?
Shall I sit here with you and talk
over a cup of coffee or something?
Alright.
I will just get to the point.
Dongman and I will start over.
What?
Why would he...
Did he say he would?
Hey, he has still
never been married.
Does it have to be the man
who makes a comeback?
Now I have it all.
Money, connections and name value.
Now, I really just need Dongman.
I told you never to show
up in front of him again.
I am not here for your permission.
It is a notice.
He is mine, so...
Are you saying I should stay away?
No.
Don't make yourself any more pathetic.
What did you just say?
Who are you calling pathetic?
You hang around pretending
like you are his friend.
It is quite funny.
It is better to be crazy
than being pathetic.
Hey.
I told you I can hit women too.
Think about it.
Was there ever a time that you beat me?
Hey, unit 101?
I take back what I said,
involving you and a temple.
Why do you keep getting on my nerves
by getting upset?
Why do you keep acting
out of your character?
Are you acting out of your
character these days?
What for?
That's really sad.
Hey.
Your Hyeran is in here. Take her away.
Dongman.
What are you doing here?
I got worried and wanted
to see how you are doing.
Should I be grateful?
I told you to answer your phone.
Hyeran.
When I heard of your divorce
honestly,
my heart sank.
When you called me,
I thought I could barely breathe.
His heart sank?
That idiot is at it again.
Sure. That loser and the witch
are made for each other.
I won't care about
neither of them anymore.
A call from me was enough
to make you nervous.
Yes.
I was worried about this.
I got afraid you would put me through a
replay of our horrid five years again.
Do me a favor.
Please get lost.
You didn't have to bring all these.
And this is sweet rice
drink that my mom made.
People who tried it ask her
to send them bottles of it.
She sent two bottles.
Why did she send us jokbal?
This is what my family
sells in our restaurant.
She didn't use any additives. She
broiled it in medicinal herbs only.
Cover it up. It reeks of pork.
Everyone has morning sickness.
Don't overreact.
Jokbal is pork. That is
why they smell like pork.
Thank you so much for the
thought and effort,
but we are going with
a brunch party theme.
Jokbal doesn't fit the menu.
What is in the suitcase?
Are you traveling?
Well...
I made some for you to give out
to the guests as they leave.
My goodness. Look at those!
Weren't you busy at work?
I took a day off. I had to do
something for Minseo's first party.
By the way, did Juman
say he can't make it?
Did you try talking to him?
Mr Kim.
What do I do now?
All of a sudden, it...
I need to make 100 copies of this.
I think I broke it.
What do I do? I think I broke it again.
Why do I keep causing trouble?
Move over.
Don't get your clothes stained.
Hey.
Open the door. Let's talk.
Moobin
Hello, Moobin.
You're at the department store?
Why are you there?
You are going to wait
for me until I am done?
You should just curse at me.
Why do you keep getting mad?
It is not like you.
You hang around pretending
like you are his friend.
It's funny.
Okay, let's meet.
Let's talk. Where are you going?
Let go.
Where are you going now?
Why do you care where I go?
It is just...
I didn't call her.
She came on her own.
Why are you telling me that?
Do you like me?
Or do I like you?
Let's keep our boundaries.
I don't want that crazy witch to pity me.
Let's behave.
This printer tends to get jammed.
When you print double-sided,
insert pages separately.
You have ink on your face.
Mr Kim.
Thank you so much.
I have to buy you a drink today.
There is this new souvlaki place.
It is really good,
and the atmosphere is great.
Let's have a drink today.
Well...
I have a heavy workload,
so I have to work tonight.
Then, do you want to watch
a movie this weekend?
I have family plans this weekend.
What about tomorrow for dinner?
Tomorrow...
I need to watch a soccer game.
I said I was thankful!
Let's have a drink. Why are
you complicating things?
Dear, don't give me that kiss.
To Aera
Sorry. I don't know what this is about.
But I am sorry anyway.
Hurry up. Why are you not keeping up?
What is this?
Why did you put my shoe size down?
What?
Why is this so detailed?
Taught by the Sydney
Olympic Silver Medalist
I don't know if women in this
town will find you appealing.
I mean, as an instructor.
This is so strategic.
I don't even know why
I asked him for help.
Come here.
-Hello.
-Welcome.
-Did you eat?
-Yes.
I wanted to meet the star fast.
-The star?
-Hello.
-Let's see.
Go to the restroom and wet
your hair for a picture.
What is this? What is it for?
Counterattack. The prelude
to counterattack.
What?
You need to give a response.
-Sir, have you confirmed everything?
-Yes.
I have Carl Carelas' hotel
check-in information,
and his departure information
right after the match.
Taksu's scheme is quite messy.
This will make a story.
Right. Did you think I was
going to let this go?
Look at you. You look cold,
but you are so warm-hearted.
Get ready to die from today.
I have booked your debut match.
Are you serious?
You are the one who
needs to counterattack.
You didn't look too bad
fighting that Brazilian.
Coach Hwang, can I call you my brother?
-You!
-Guard.
Guard.
Look here. Lift one arm.
Here we go.
Good. Come in.
Different pose.
Okay.
All right. Here we go.
Sorry you two, do you mind moving over?
You too. Thank you.
-Last one. Here we go.
-I am sorry.
Good one.
Stand up straight.
Good. Looking great.
Great. Here it is.
I think that is enough.
Let's go for a smoke.
-Good job.
-Thank you.
-Hey.
Come and be my sparring partner.
Sorry?
You don't want to?
I will.
My goodness.
Hey, why would you get an interview?
It is for something.
I see. When you got beaten up?
I saw that.
You got beaten up and I cracked up.
If I were you, I would have
quit from embarrassment.
That is not it. I got tricked into it.
Don't talk back.
In this gym, you are the sandbag.
Whose sandbag? Mine.
All right, Dongman? Take my punches.
Here I go.
I almost forgot.
Congrats. From Seolhui's Mom
I forgot the most important thing.
Goodness, I am tired.
Mother, you can leave it. I will clean up.
-Seolhui.
-Yes?
Sorry, but can you set this table up?
Sure. I will do it now.
She makes me feel so uncomfortable.
She even baked these cookies.
Is she the one your brother
started dating in college?
-Her mom sells pig's feet, right?
-For a man
to be successful, he has to
consider the girl's family.
He is such a moron.
We call her the Crawling Seolhui.
Her family has nothing, so
she crawls in front of us.
-Goodness.
-Hey.
It is better that way.
Your sister-in-law is
going to be disciplined.
She is not my sister-in-law.
You don't know who is going
to walk down the aisle.
Then,
should I cancel Juman's blind date?
What does her family do?
They own a restaurant.
They own a restaurant in Garosu Road.
Aera!
Why did you come all of a sudden?
I suddenly got the day off.
I made a surprise visit.
You sure love surprises.
Why aren't you wearing your uniform?
What?
The thing is...
I have a stomachache, so
I was going to go home.
Get in.
Miss Hwang. Are you leaving already?
You should look around. There
are many new releases.
This place has bad rumors.
Rumors?
You need to control those
that visit the place.
Pardon?
King's chairman's second wife.
She is known for her hobby in shoplifting.
On top of that,
I heard an innocent staff
had to kneel and apologize.
Pardon?
Oh, that incident?
You are pretty brave.
These days, that kind of incident
would lead to store closure.
All of you need to take
care of things properly.
What I want is simple.
No matter which department store it is
no VIPs should be able
to abuse their power.
Are you telling me to expel her?
It is simple and righteous.
That is,
what a promising department
store should do.
You must really love Japanese music.
It is another Japanese song.
How is your stomach, Aera?
Does it hurt often?
I have a minor irritable bowel syndrome.
Today, I had a few things happen to me.
I hear it has a huge
psychological influence.
You can't get stressed.
Having you show up like this
isn't actually that good either.
Did I make you uncomfortable?
I just missed you a lot.
If I give you a surprise visit to the
hospital, you'll be uncomfortable too.
I think I would love that.
If you would surprise me,
I would be so happy.
I will make sure to call next time.
Moobin.
I was just embarrassed.
I wasn't sure if I should
tell people this or not,
but I quit work.
I see.
There is something else I want to do.
What is it?
It is embarrassing to say.
Can't you tell me?
Well...
An announcer.
An announcer?
Really?
I just passed through the documentation
process, so I'll go for my interview.
I'm not saying this to make you happy.
I think it suits you really well.
-Really?
-Yes.
Why do I feel so happy?
I think it is cool that you quit and
it is exciting that you passed.
But honestly, I am most thankful
that you told me everything.
Why are you so thankful?
I don't know.
You weren't sure if you could
tell others, but you told me.
That means,
we aren't 100 percent strangers anymore.
Hey.
Did you clean this up?
I could have done it.
No, it wasn't me.
-Really?
-Enjoy.
Seolhui, you are working so hard.
By the way,
when should we,
have the parents meet?
Right, we should set the date.
But I recently hurt my knee. It has been
so hectic getting treatment and all.
Why?
Are your parents rushing you?
No. I just asked.
Oh, my little one.
Oh, my pumpkin!
Baby, look. There are flowers.
Kim Taksu
57, 58...
59.
80, 81.
Why are you looking him up?
56, 57.
Aren't you training? Did you
practice your 100 punches?
How can I do it 100 times?
-I am not like this kid.
-60.
Bro, Taksu is having fun at a club.
Bro?
I mean, coach.
Why do you care if he is at a club?
It is just...
The more I think about it,
it makes me upset that they fooled me.
I am speechless.
Why? You were always fooled.
You were like that since middle school.
Hey, what are you thinking?
Don't think.
Your brain isn't meant to be used.
Sonya.
I don't even know who Alice is.
How can I have her number?
Fine, just show me. Let me look.
Sonya.
Do you want to die? So, it is true.
You texted Alice first, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
Then, why won't you show me your phone?
Just show me proof.
This is a matter of trust.
Do you really want to die?
Seriously. Should I just show it to you?
I could, but what really
bothers me right now,
isn't the false rumor about
me hitting on Alice.
It is that you don't believe me.
Shut up and just show me your text.
Sonya, watch your mouth!
Sonya, I am a sportsman.
I would never act like a thug.
Hey. Alice and I are in the same group.
You really are a thug.
We know that already.
You don't have to worry.
We already took care of all the press.
Of course.
Also, please don't call me anymore.
Mr Yang.
One moment, please. Geez!
Dongman. What brings you here?
He must be downstairs.
What?
Aren't you going down?
I think I have to finish this call.
I am too busy.
Sonya, I am going to the washroom.
Why are you taking your
phone to the washroom?
Hey, Dongman. What are you doing here?
I am okay. Don't worry.
Taksu.
I didn't know zip about jiu jitsu,
but I got to learn it thanks to you.
Thank you for helping me train
with the famous Brazilian coach.
I wasn't ready for it. Such a thug!
How can you attack a drunk person?
Hey, Taksu.
You jerk.
Give me your best shot.
No matter how hard you try,
you will end up on the ring with me.
Youngsoo. Kyungah.
There is one from a guy.
Hayun.
Hey!
Congrats. From Seolhui's Mom
Seolhui's...
Did her mom come by?
She must have sent it by the
hand of Crawling Seolhui.
There are 300 dollars in here.
The in-laws went out of their way.
Hey. She isn't an in-law.
Juman. I thought you had to work late.
How did you come?
-Where is she?
-Over there.
Honey.
You said you couldn't make it today.
What is it? Let go.
Mom. All of you.
Don't look down on Seolhui.
If you do, I won't forgive you.
Juman.
Sons are all useless.
Seolhui.
Did you call him?
No. I am sorry.
What has gotten into you?
You don't go to your in-laws
during the holidays!
Then, why must Seolhui clean
up after your son's party?
She is a precious daughter,
in her family too.
Get your act together.
Hey. You tell him.
Did we make you work?
No. I did it because I wanted to.
Juman. I wanted to do it.
Stop being angry.
Treat Seolhui well.
Don't look down on her.
-My goodness.
-What's wrong with you?
Am I so great?
I come from a poor family.
I went to a local college and
am only an assistant manager.
Whom do I have to thank for that?
All four years of college, she
worked and paid my rent,
and supported me when I started work.
Not you people!
It is Seolhui.
You should bow to her and thank her.
Don't do this.
What a great boyfriend.
Are you even going to marry her?
You are not so...
Sure, I may not marry her.
But,
if I don't marry her,
I won't marry anyone else!
Juman.
Hey!
My stomach!
You are going to watch
me go in again, right?
No.
I am going in with you this time.
Why would you go in with me?
Why do you keep saying you
will go into a woman's home?
Are you that...
Uneducated?
This is how one actor
proposed to his actress wife.
My goodness.
You should stop surfing the web.
You are prettier in my
eyes than that actress,
so I added to it.
You always massage your legs yourself.
When did you see me do that?
Pardon? I wasn't staring or anything.
Fine. I will say you didn't stare.
Right, you aren't well.
I will bring this in and then leave.
No, I can carry it.
You can't carry this up five
flights of stairs. Let's go.
Geez!
I said it is okay.
I can take it from here.
I will drop this off and then go.
I can really take it from here.
I will just drop this off.
I will take it.
Wait, Moobin.
Hold on. I need to tell you something.
Moobin, I need to tell you something.
What is it?
-Pardon?
-Why are you going up?
Why are you going up?
That is not it.
-Aera!
-Miss.!
Hey!
-Aera.
-Hey!
Don't go to my house again.
Were you worried that I
would be working too hard?
Didn't you like that? Did you get annoyed?
You are too submissive.
What do you lack that you
are like that to me?
It is not because I lack anything.
It is because I like you.
It is because I like you so much,
that I want you to like me.
That is why I want your
family to like me too.
Do you like me that much?
-Yes.
-Goodness.
You know, earlier, when you
got all angry and stuff,
I thought you looked kind of sexy.
Are my lips here?
I was so happy that you came.
I thought you had to work late.
Did you play hooky because
you worried about me?
Your mother texted, so I left early.
My mom? She did?
-Yes.
-My mom texted you?
Yes.
It was the first time she texted me,
so I was really surprised.
My mom doesn't know how to text.
Okay.
-A suit, okay?
-Okay.
Okay.
Friends are the best.
-Look at that.
-How adorable.
Eat slowly.
He takes after me.
-You must have been hungry.
-Right?
That moron. That idiot.
She acted all fine in front of me,
but you are a complete idiot. Moron.
That jerk!
That jerk. That disgusting family.
I am going to!
Where is it? That jerk.
Forget getting married. Don't show
your face in front of Seolhui again.
I won't let a family like
that have my daughter.
Forget getting married...
Juman. How are you doing?
It has been a while.
Seolhui went to the
birthday party by herself.
She likes you very much.
Please be good to my daughter.
What is wrong? What is it?
My mom
cleaned up the garbage.
What garbage?
My mom must have seen everything.
She must have seen everything.
Don't cry.
Mom.
Seolhui's Jokbal
So?
When are the families meeting?
Would it be this month?
What about Seolhui?
Is she doing well?
Honey.
Yes?
Should we close this shop,
and open a restaurant?
What are you talking about?
It is just,
I don't like that Seolhui has to,
have parents who own a jokbal store.
It is IBS. Irritable Bowel Syndrome.
Really?
-Is it serious?
-Yes.
Her stomach was full of gas.
Then, she fainted because of gas?
That is not common.
I think she fainted from the
pain caused by the gas.
That means, she was extremely stressed.
How much did you stress her out
that she fainted during a date?
She is okay now, right?
You saw her release the gas, right?
I want to die.
Yes. Twice.
Once was very long.
I can never open my eyes again.
Bar? Soju? Beer? Answer,
or you get nothing.
Are you sleeping?
Are you ignoring me?
Hey.
She is really getting to me.
Hello.
-What...
-You. Unit 102.
Are you on route to unit 101 or
the announcer who came back?
Pardon?
The Unit 101 girl
fainted and was taken to the hospital.
Aera?
-Aera is now in the hospital?
-Yes.
Severance Hospital. Room 2701.
The Royal Suite room.
Not again!
I am awake now.
Are you awake? Are you okay?
Huh?
You fainted earlier.
Your belly was filled with
gas because of your IBS.
Thankfully, the gas came out.
It wasn't serious, but
the gas had to come out.
Please stop.
Please stop talking about gas.
Can't you take this out for me?
I want to go home.
You should sleep here tonight.
I want to go home. It is uncomfortable.
Why do you always want to go home
when you are with me?
Dongman
Why won't she pick up? Why did she faint?
She's strong enough to knock down a cow.
Dongman
Don't answer that.
Aera, can't you look at me?
-Sorry?
-The truth is,
this room is very expensive.
I wanted to do all I
could to impress you,
so that is why I requested it.
I didn't even get this for my mom
when she had her appendectomy.
Why are you telling me...
Actually, I am off today.
But I went and got my gown to look cool.
I want to do anything to impress you.
Why do you find me so uncomfortable?
Why does your stomach hurt
when you are with me?
Why is this guy so sweet?
He is giving me a cavity.
I'm really telling the truth.
I think about you all day long.
I think of any excuse possible.
The massager, having the day off...
Just to see you one more time.
Please stop.
I am feeling weak today.
A person's heart gets soft
when they are hurting.
To me, you are like...
A goddess.
It is just,
when I look at you, even if
you don't say anything...
Even just
by looking at you,
my heart
goes crazy.
You can't do this when someone is sick.
That is low.
Then, I will be low today.
I...
Dongman. This isn't what you think.
It hurts!
Who was that?
I think it was Aera.
-Dongman, that stinks.
-Did he poop?
Pretty boy, you did well.
It is all yours.