I closed my eyes for just a short time,
and when I opened them...
Can you hear me?
Give me something now.
...the world had changed.
Oh, Do-jae.
Who... are you?
In the blink of an eye, I realized...
I'm sorry.
...it was not the world that had changed,
I had.
Number one.
Number two.
Number three.
Try again.
Again.
It took a very long time...
One... two... three...
four... five...
six.
Number seven.
Try again.
12.
For the first time,
you got them all correct.
...until I could recognize
the things I love.
Hairstyle, clothes,
walk, smell...
Mother.
speech, and habit.
I'm back.
When I started to recognize you,
the one I love,
using all those things,
You're back.
the last person I could not recognize...
was me.
Maybe it was from that moment.
Among the ones I can recognize,
that I must recognize,
and the ones I love,
the fact that I was not included...
EPISODE 8
I have't loved myself since that day.
Not even once.
I am not sure
if it's alright
for a person like me
to love you and myself.
Will you be OK
with me?
Do you mean it?
I do.
I can't believe it.
Prove it.
You like me?
Yes.
Even if I'm not beautiful?
Even so.
Thank you.
For liking me.
For liking me,
even though I am like this.
What should we do about the contract?
There is no such thing any more.
I ripped it up.
So I am the only one who has the contract.
I feel nervous.
We broke up.
But we are dating.
We decided to date.
But the media will say we broke up.
HAN SE-GYE AND SEO DO-JAE ARE FRIENDS
It happened to be that way.
Do it one at a time.
One!
Is that why poured the drink for yourself?
Is that why you didn't eat?
No. Never.
He made you get drunk.
He made you suffer so much
that you couldn't eat.
I won't accept this relationship.
It was because of work.
It was all because of work.
It was all because of Chae Yu-ri.
Next...
is a more important problem than that.
Answer directly.
Did you...
confess your feelings?
No.
He did. I refused.
I told him I will quit, but Seo Do-jae...
That is good, then.
U-mi.
I'm really sorry.
Reporter Park,
I have a good report for you.
Look at that. They already broke up.
Already?
Because of busy schedule?
Why did they bother in the beginning?
Because of personality difference?
They broke up to focus more on work.
-Now?
-Maybe she ran way again.
HAN SE-GYE AND SEO DO-JAE SEPARATING?
Did you see it?
The director
and Han Se-gye are separating.
Han Se-gye and Seo Do-jae's separation
from couple to friends.
Han Se-gye's side confirmed
the separation.
The reason for the separation is
to focus on her work.
I told you the news will be out soon.
I heard this from my informant,
which surprised me a lot.
How can I respect
the owner family?
What do you think, President Kang?
I am sure you did not call me
to post malicious comments together.
I heard you got very upset
at President Kim.
You are a woman of determination.
Amazing! Great!
President Kim was such a cheap shot,
unlike how he looks.
I am sure you didn't call me
to praise me either.
Let's gamble.
I am good at gambling.
My bet is not on Seo Do-jae,
but on you. What do you think?
You have a big dream.
Gambling only works when the players have
a similar amount of betting money.
What?
Your crappy cards
and bluffing will not work.
Most of all,
you are not holding good cards.
How dare you choose me?
Know where you stand.
The Chairman is
a stylish person.
However, he will not give the company
to his step-granddaughter
instead of his grandson.
Do you really think I wouldn't know that?
Are you being this bold because of him?
He has not come back to Korea yet, right?
Rumor has it he is having a good time.
You said he was love crazy!
Even crazy love ends.
I guess he is crazy.
I told you to keep your eye on him.
He will be in the society section
of the newspapers.
I will do my best to prevent that.
You say that.
Saying it is easy.
Solve this now, unless you want
a smaller salary.
Excuse me?
Salary reduction!
How are you?
Not well!
Why did you make such a press release?
Our director got dumped?
Does it make sense?
Why not?
That is what our Se-gye said.
She dumped him.
Considering it's not a real relationship,
we took a lot of risks already.
How much more should we concede?
Maybe you don't understand
what "taking a risk" means.
No, I don't.
Maybe it's office jargon.
I wouldn't know
as I am cut out for on-site work.
Do you think we will be the only ones
who get a blow?
Your side will also be hit hard.
That is what I am saying.
Both of us will be hit,
and we want to get hit a little less.
I cannot have a conversation with someone
who is so low.
Do you understand now
how low you guys were?
If you realized how low you were,
you wouldn't do this to me,
but talk to your director first.
Thanks for lunch.
My son is creating all kinds of trouble!
Darling, that is not a weed.
A plant that looks like a weed
has to be pulled.
You shouldn't do that!
It's hurt already.
You should cover it with dirt
and pat it nicely.
Please talk to Do-jae.
He won't listen to me.
Is there anyone who listens to you
more than him?
If I go, I feel like I would pull him
like a weed.
So, you go and pat him.
How do you feel?
Sorry. I ruined the trip.
Why do you apologize for your sickness?
You should apologize to yourself
for harassment.
I'm sorry.
Isn't today shooting practice?
Will that be OK?
Yes.
I am going to meet with an action team.
Alright.
Filming will begin soon.
Take good care of yourself.
Go.
Director,
may I ask you a question?
Yes.
Why does it have to be her?
Yu-ri?
Yes.
Why do you like her?
She is not like you.
How?
I want to know.
She loves herself too much,
unlike you.
You two have
completely opposite problems.
So...
take good care of her.
Hold here.
Senior, I heard you got separated.
Don't act silly when I am holding a gun.
People say it was because of rumors.
It that true?
It feels awkward to be called senior.
You spoke with no respect before.
Me? When?
"Me?"
"When?"
I guess I was drunk.
I have a bad drinking habit.
I lose memory and stuff.
When did you get separated?
Is that why you acted that way
on the trip?
Did you drink so much
because of the separation?
You said you don't remember.
No, I don't.
-Senior...
-Hey!
Don't talk to me.
Do you know?
I saved your life.
If I didn't get help,
you wouldn't be here.
You are making a lot of noise.
Shall I shoot her?
What?
That would be a waste of bullets.
That is not true.
Write the facts.
A beautiful separation for each other.
That's it.
I feel so embarassed.
Do you know what kind of trouble
I was in?
Since when have you been
in the relationship?
Since yesterday.
Why did you ask me to send
the report to the media?
Just... because.
-I quit.
-No.
-Then, raise my salary.
-I'm going home.
-No.
You still have 30 minutes left.
Did you have an appointment
with your father?
Father, why did you come?
Oh, I was in the neighborhood...
and I wanted to see you.
Is that what my mother asked you
to say here?
The rubber trees make scars on them
to fully live their lives.
Also, some fields are burned
to support new lives.
Every tree has a scar.
Even though your love did not work out,
-it will be the basis--
-That's not it.
It's OK. It's always like that
in the beginning.
Then you grow...
and forget.
That's not it.
Don't be too mad.
If it's too hard,
cry or something.
It's not hard.
A good woman will show up.
She does not have eyes for a good man.
How can she break up
with such a nice man like you?
Does she want to reconsider, by any means?
I am sorry. I shouldn't have said that.
Would you like a drink?
It's not working. We should find a way.
Fully agreed.
Why did you send that to the media?
You made things more complicated!
It was your idea.
So, you go ahead right after I said it?
Should I not have done that?
You are so dull.
I am not used to it.
Don't say that!
Why?
You don't like me like this?
No, I get so sympathetic.
It hurts my heart.
That is touching.
Of course. You don't need to be touched.
Do you see anything different
about me today?
That's the question men hate the most.
That's why I'm asking.
Your earrings look good on you.
I knew it. You are not like other men.
You have good taste.
Are you praising me, or yourself?
-Me?
-Hold on.
OK.
What are you doing?
I'm not doing anything.
I need to go home.
See you at our next secret rendezvous.
Han Se-gye,
call me when you get home.
Why?
I'll worry.
Oh my god! What was that?
He really acts like a boyfriend.
Where did you go?
You scared me!
That is...
someone I know was bereaved, so...
Someone you know was bereaved, so...
you went out with such pretty earrings?
Did you go to see your "uncle"
in this messy situation?
How did you find out?
About uncle?
How do you think I found out?
You said everything at the interview.
I am cancelling all the interviews,
and you are...
Tell your uncle to cancel
the T-road company interview
as smoothly as possible.
Shall... I?
No...
Let's not cancel.
Why? What are you doing now?
A risk is an opportunity.
I am not sure
if this is right thing to do.
Just trust me.
Oh my goodness.
Big news.
What is it?
What now?
What is going on?
What? What is it?
Han Se-gye is in the lobby right now.
-Wow.
-Oh dear!
Han Se-gye?
Han Se-gye is going to our floor now.
Wh...what is happening?
Why did she come after breaking up?
-To meet the Director?
-The Director?
-Should I go out and check?
-It will be too obvious.
I... just don't know what to do.
This is the model of the airplane
we plan to purchase, and...
We need your approval to proceed...
I AM HERE. HEADING FOR INTERVIEW ROOM.
Where are you going?
Do you want a salary cut?
Big news!
She just... arrived.
Han se-gye, in the hallway.
So she just arrived
and is walking in the hallway.
What if she comes
to the director's office?
What do we do?
I'll pretend that I got lost
and check the situation.
Why would you get lost in our building?
You are even a team leader.
Right.
Take your toothbrush.
Why a toothbrush after lunch hour?
That is even more suspicious.
Pretend you have braces.
They always need to brush their teeth.
But I don't have braces.
Pretend you have a lingual orthodontic,
inside your teeth.
Oh, genius!
You came to work?
Are you going out to work?
Please take good care of yourself.
I'm asking as a director.
No worries. I am a model of this company.
Good luck!
Call me when you're done.
-We'll get something to eat.
-OK.
-It's on me.
They are so cool.
I thought I was in Hollywood.
The air is cold.
They are the ones who broke up.
Why do I feel like I am dumped?
Oh my god, oh my god!
I never spoke to you that casually.
I know.
Your acting has improved.
I was very nervous.
I guess it wasn't too obvious.
I guess that's why your hand was cold.
Sorry, it was my colleague.
Shall we continue?
I guess you are doing well.
We were afraid you might cancel
the interview.
It's not like we shouldn't meet
just because we broke up.
He is a good friend.
And I respect him as a person.
Can we begin the shoot?
Yes.
Is that what they call
"a cold and handsome man"?
Oh, just a minute.
I got a business message.
I haven't texted you.
Who are you talking to?
Yes. Just a minute. Almost done.
Are you even listening to me?
-Are you?
-Wha... What?
Never mind.
What should I do now?
Now you can...
go home.
Go home? Already?
Yes. Go home.
-Hey. Give it here.
-Why?
It makes me nervous. Give it to me.
Why? I did well.
You just have to reveal it.
When did I reveal it?
What's up with your profile picture
on the messenger?
That hand!
It's Seo Do-jae's hand!
What are you talking about?
It's just an ad.
Are you an elementary school kid?
No. Even they are better than you.
Even they don't show their relations
that way.
Hey!
Why are you suddenly putting on perfume?
Why?
It's to make you feel good.
To change the atmosphere,
the mood, and the subject!
Pew! It smells!
Look ahead.
You're going to crash. Look ahead!
I said I'm not going anywhere!
I won't leave until you go in.
I am going in!
After I see you go in, I will wait
out front for 30 minutes, and then leave.
Jeez. I'm going in now. Watch. I'm going.
You watch out.
Behave.
Don't cause trouble.
Don't worry.
That was too much!
What's up with your pass code? 10041004?
Are you obsessed with angels?
Should I change it to a number
I don't care about, like 0116?
You care about it now.
Stop saying such things out of the blue,
I said.
You smell nice.
You don't do this any more?
I don't need to.
I don't forget your smell.
I will only wear this one.
I can't even change my perfume.
This relationship is so particular.
I would appreciate it if you would think
rather than particular,
this relationship is unchanging.
I would appreciate it, too.
By the way,
a secret relationship is so thrilling!
Having a secret is so fun.
I've been uneasy, sad, and lonely.
Now, we will be uneasy, sad,
and lonely together.
Can we be not uneasy, sad,
and lonely together?
I will try as hard as I can.
I feel better!
That light bulb...
why haven't you changed it?
I've been waiting
until I become a tall person.
Shall I change it for you?
Oh my!
Could you do that one more time?
What?
Pull your shirt and watch off.
You find that attractive?
So cool and sexy. But It's funny!
You are funny and cute, but sexy.
-What are you doing tomorrow?
-Working.
-I'm going to work, too.
-Why?
I don't want to work. I was wondering
if we could afford not working.
Wow. This is the first time
you said you didn't want to work.
What's going on?
I guess you really like me!
Yes.
So it would seem.
Do you know what I just thought?
You will be so surprised.
"I want to change right now.
Then, we could be together."
This is...
the first time I want to change.
Really.
What was it like the first time?
I did everything.
I went a church to pray,
to a temple to bow 108 times,
and to a shaman for a rite.
But I am OK, now.
After difficult times,
something I want comes true, too.
Just like now.
Or...
to realize my dreams,
I needed those difficult times.
No matter what the sequence is,
I want you to be happy.
So it would seem.
I am...
very happy now.
Go carefully.
Don't get caught.
I will.
I won't get caught.
Seo Do-jae.
Shall I drive you?
We're already here.
Good night.
So...
what are you going to drive home?
Huh?
This is my car.
Good night. Sleep well.
Thank you for the ride.
Go in. I want to make sure you get in.
Would you like some ramen before you go?
I told you to stay home.
So you bring him here?
U-mi, it's not like that.
I knew it when you put the perfume on.
You just have to make me work at night.
Secretary Jeong, it's not like--
I knew it when you looked in the mirror.
Residents reported that suspicious
people are wandering around,
-it turns out to be these two!
-You two sure look suspicious.
You are pulling your hats down
and avoiding eye contact.
What's your name?
You U-mi.
You-mi?
Ah, You-mi?
Oh! I'm so sorry!
You two walk like that.
No wonder people feel nervous.
When he shows his face,
everyone tries to fight with him, so...
Yes... I am kind of like that.
I guess I didn't cover him enough.
Now they are using the police to fight.
Right honey?
It looks like you're trying
to fight with me.
Anyway, watch out.
-Yes. Sorry. Go in.
-Sorry.
Sorry.
Go in.
-Go in.
-Don't worry.
We will try to stay home.
I will lock her in.
Where are you touching? Honey?
You, Han Se-gye!
I so wish I had a makeup removing machine!
What are you doing?
I've done this many times. Don't worry.
My friend gets wasted often.
As Han Se-gye is an actress,
I take care of her skin.
I am not going to get up
or anything like that.
I am so tired I cannot lift a finger.
Why?
Thanks to your friend.
They got separated?
It would be fine if that was all it was.
But they chose to have a cool separation.
So I have a lot to think about.
And President Kim just talks nonsense.
Why doesn't he do it on his own?
He shouldn't call me to come...
I usually don't tell others
something like this.
Why did I say this?
Because I listen.
It's because no one listened
to you before.
I will listen to you.
Tell me everything.
What is this?
What?
You want something from me.
Wow. How did you know?
I am a businesswoman.
What is it?
You have a lot of money, don't you?
Do you want to donate?
You are selling donations like blankets.
If I make a donation,
what will you do for me?
If you make a donation,
I will smile.
You said my smile is worth money.
Where did you get this much stuff?
From someone who likes smiles.
She is tenacious.
What do you mean?
It looks like she is in great pain.
After her son's death, she donated
his heart to another kid.
Giving my kid's heart to someone...
I could never do that!
What's the use?
It would be gone once it's buried.
I think I would feel better
to know that my son's heart is working
for another kid.
Did you decide which calling
you will take, Julianus?
I made the decision
a long time ago, Father.
Come home.
How did you find me?
It doesn't matter. Just come back,
before your mom really passes out.
I can't live the way mom wants.
I get it, so come home.
That is how we wrote the contract.
Look at this
and tell me if that is possible.
Does it make sense to take a week off?
I wrote that in the contract for a reason.
If you don't abide by the contract,
I will have no choice
but to take legal measures.
We will go to another town soon,
so just be patient.
Or you go and talk
to the director directly!
Even the main role is not doing this.
Don't push it too hard.
Wow.
What the...
Do you like to make people nervous?
Do you like to pick fights?
You wanted to take time off.
Why don't you just stay out of the film?
For whose benefit?
For all of us.
We're the ones who have to suffer
if you cause trouble.
That's enough.
Apparently, you are busy pretending
to have a good break-up.
Can you try that hard for your work?
Please?
Then,
let's do what we can.
Are you crazy?
You might get in big trouble.
You don't have many days left.
It will be worse without me.
-You grew up after being dumped.
-I was not dumped.
Right, you dumped him!
What did I hear?
"He's a good friend"?
"I respect him as a person"?
How do you know? You don't read about me.
Oh, someone told me.
Who?
Someone.
Fine.
Let's try.
Tell me when you feel danger.
I will take you out of the site
like an abduction.
I will get the OK sign the first try,
so we will finish quickly.
I will give them tons of free time.
Do you want to volunteer your free time?
Sorry. I will be too busy playing.
What about donations then?
No thanks. I wanted to,
but I don't anymore, since you ask for it.
Zipping your mouth would help
you recruit volunteers.
I went to the Welfare Center
that we visited before.
The woman you saved....
as I heard,
she gave her dead son's heart
to another kid.
Wow, that is admirable.
Not everyone can do it.
You can't say
"good job!", either.
I know.
I think about her sometimes.
I think of her empty eyes. They looked
like seeing the end of the world.
One world must have ended
for her.
It's a good day to drink!
What about rice noodle soup
for our hangovers tomorrow?
-OK?
-OK.
OK.
See you tomorrow.
I will bring Gging-ggang.
Leaving already?
I can't stay out too late
when I am staying someone else's house.
Good night.
Bye.
Such a nice coat!
He is making a dramatic exit...
-Aren't you worried?
-About what?
He said he became a slave.
He told Ahram that he slept on the street.
-What did he say to you?
-I didn't ask.
He is a grown man. He will be fine.
-What kind of friend are you?
-I did that because I am a friend.
We should make sure.
Is this OK?
What if he gets abused by bad people?
-We are the bad ones here.
-No.
I'm back.
You are a bit late.
This is funny.
This is...
I've heard you've been looking
for my weakness.
But I think I am the one
who found the weakness,
just now.
I'm not following you.
I am not her weakness.
I am going to leave the house.
Thank you for letting me stay.
Ryu Eun-ho!
You guys leave, too.
We will talk tomorrow.
I told you...
we are the bad ones.
This is for the chandelier, after my wage.
Do you know how much it is?
I searched for the lowest price.
It was 388,000 won.
You were more frugal than I thought.
And this is
a small token of my appreciation
for letting me stay here.
-What will you tell your friends?
-I'll tell them the truth.
The truth?
It was a sort of my job.
When are you leaving?
Tomorrow.
-When did you decide?
-Today.
Will you still come if I call?
I don't mean anything else.
I am just asking because it's bothersome
to find a good maid.
Even if I find one,
it takes time
for her to get used to my house.
Will you call?
Then, I will come.
When did you find out
the price for chandelier?
Right after I broke it.
Kids these days are too aggresive.
OK then.
I will call, and you come.
It's too sweet.
I told him I don't eat breakfast.
Good soup.
My stomach feels much better now.
Oh, the best hangover soup is...
rice noodle soup.
-About yesterday...
-Let's eat.
Why should I feel so small?
You are the one who talked--
Get this straight.
I haven't sold your information.
Are you dating with her?
-Really?
-No!
OK. You don't have to be upset.
This is a matter of respect among friends,
and respect to someone who took me in
when I had nowhere to go.
But... how are we supposed to understand
what you said?
Talk in detail.
Sorry. I followed you
because I was worried.
I know.
That's why I am not saying anything.
Should I do it?
The donation?
Yes.
And you say "Yes" so fast...
Are you fully awake?
And sober?
She is completely awake.
She is not offering to buy a house.
I only make promises I can keep.
Are you going to the filming place?
I should.
That's also a promise I need to keep.
I am sorry, friend.
We were just worried.
Good girls.
What's this?
Did we get the time wrong?
-No.
-What time are we supposed to be here?
-We are even late.
-What?
What's this?
For your happiness.
From Han-Se-gy's fan.
Your uncle likes to make a big deal.
Do you only buy fish with money?
Why didn't you call before you came?
Do I need to inform you
when I come to my office?
You cannot even do your business right?
I am doing my work right.
I heard you broke up with the model.
I told you she is an actress,
not a model.
How did you find out?
I'm on the internet.
Everyone is talking about it.
You got dumped here and there.
You are so incapable.
Good work, Grandpa.
You surfed the web on your own.
You cannot handle a woman,
but you can still talk.
Stop, please, and leave.
You don't have to rub salt in the wound.
Do you want me to handle it?
How, with your money?
She has lots of money.
That's why you got dumped.
You have to give what she needs the most.
How does a businessman not know that?
What she wants the most is...
not to see me anymore.
You are so incapable.
Yes, I am broken.
And you, too.
But now that I know of your existence,
I came out into the world.
Maybe... you've been waiting for me, too.
I've been waiting...
to throw your broken life
into the trashcan.
Cut, OK.
Cut OK. Get ready for Scene C-5.
Le't's get ready.
Will you really be OK?
Should I call it off?
It's OK. I have one scene left.
-We just need to shoot on more scene.
-I am so nervous.
I still have two days left.
It could be up to five days off.
It is OK. I think it will be OK.
You are my mistake and imperfection.
When you disappear,
I will be complete.
-Cut, OK.
-It is OK!
Are you OK?
How old am I?
Assistant Director!
One of the child actors didn't make it
because he was sick.
What?
Ah, shit!
The director will be very upset.
What can we do?
He doesn't have any lines,
so bring anyone.
He just has to stand there.
OK.
Move quickly.
Somehow I wanted to bring...
kids' clothes.
What's size of clothes?
Between 9 and 10.
Then, I will be 10,
to reduce the generation gap.
You look young.
No, he does not know
anything about acting!
Another kid will do the line.
He just has to stand there.
-We will take him for now.
-No!
-Why don't we have a mom?
-Cut!
Let's do it again.
Action!
-Why don't we have a mom?
-Cut, cut, cut!
Take it slow. Again!
Action!
-Why don't we--
-Cut!
Let's take a break.
I did not want to be part of this,
but I can't help it.
Kid!
Kid? Me?
-Yes, you.
-You are a kid, too.
Right. I am a kid, too.
Hey, friend.
Do it like this.
Why don't we have a mom?
No, no, cut, cut!
That is not it.
Why... don't we have a mom?
Like that!
Why don't we have a mom?
Give him the line.
Then, where did I come from?
Where should I go to?
Cut! Great. Good job!
What's your name? Where is your mom?
You act really well.
Do you have an agency?
I am from DM...
Hey, he has been taken.
Great job, my dear actor!
He's with World Entertainment.
I should get a booster seat or something.
Sorry.
No worries!
You even took one more scene
than scheduled.
You did so well. Great work!
They are going a few different places,
so take a good break.
I felt a bit sad
when I didn't get the main role.
But this is convenient.
I know. Should we keep taking
supporting roles?
This is a great idea.
Hey, by the way...
how will I get home?
There you go!
We did it! Sit.
Do you really have to eat this?
Should I rinse it?
It looks too spicy for you.
-It's OK.
-No!
It's not good. Give it to me.
You are grown up in your heart,
but your tummy is still a kid's.
You will get sick if you eat this.
I really wanted to eat spicy tteok-bokki.
True that!
This is strong flavor!
I was scared to death.
I thought you would be discovered.
Me too!
I am glad you weren't discovered.
Eat. Eat all you want, my sweetie!
Hey, would you stop?
Would you stop saying "hey" to me?
FROM: MOM
What are you going to do?
What can I do?
I can't pick up.
Your life is...
Have a drink!
Let's drink!
Did you call Seo Do-jae?
No!
Come here, come.
Han Se-gye, mom is here.
Mom?
Mom!
Who is this?
Subtitle translation by Yoonji Choi