Let's go on a date, Song-i.
I'll come pick you up.
Cool. I'm fine with any place.
Who have you been texting so often lately?
Who do you think it is?
Are you seeing someone?
-Yes.
-What? Since when?
Who is he? Is he from our school?
I'm here. Meet me outside.
Already?
I'll be down soon.
I have to go. My boyfriend is here.
-Boyfriend?
Gosh.
Song-i really has a boyfriend?
Holy cow!
BANG LP RECORDS
Two egg buns, please.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Let's try it.
It's good.
When should we tell Tae-o
that we're going out?
Right.
It's kind of awkward now
because we missed our timing.
But keeping it a secret is fun.
Gosh, you scared me.
What are you doing?
Were you waiting for me?
Why would I be waiting for you?
Is the owner of this house not allowed
to stand in his own front yard?
When did I say that?
Why are you always so grouchy at night?
Get out of my way.
Where have you been until this hour?
I was...
at school!
I had...
to work on my project. That's it.
Aren't you going to bed?
I'll go to bed when I want to.
Okay.
I'll head in first, then.
Right.
A man and a woman can fall in love
if they see each other often.
I should be relieved that
it's Do-hyeon and not some jerk.
Picturing the two of them together...
What's wrong with me?
THE REAL REASON
Okay. I'll meet you at the library
after class.
I'll call you.
What is this doing here?
Han Song-i!
This is yours, isn't it?
Is it?
Isn't it obvious?
Didn't I tell you to clean up
after using the bathroom?
Do you know how unpleasant it is
to find this in the bathtub?
-Ga-rin has long hair too.
-Song-i.
I've known you for 20 years.
I can tell this is yours.
Just get rid of this right now.
Goodness...
Gosh.
Does he think he's a hair expert
or something?
Song-i!
I almost tripped and fell because of this.
I'm sure I left it on the rooftop,
but I found it there this morning.
Didn't you say this is your house?
You should take care of your own stuff.
Did you put it there?
No.
What's with that face?
Song-i.
I've known you for 20 years.
You don't think
that I'm lying to you, do you?
It's not that.
It's just weird that the tent is here.
It should be on the rooftop.
I don't care!
Take this up to the attic, now.
What's his problem?
There isn't even much space up there.
That was really immature.
I'm really not this petty.
Tae-o, you're much better than this.
You're tolerant, understanding,
and you know
how to approach someone
in an honest manner.
Sounds like someone really loves himself.
You scared me.
What are you doing?
What do you think I am doing?
I'm looking for auditions.
I can't believe
I'm going through this all over again.
You should rest
until you clear your head a little.
Being hasty can make things worse.
Hey. Do you think my face is the problem?
-You just realized that?
-I thought so.
My handsome face doesn't exactly fit
with the current trend.
Should I get a nose job?
Stop talking nonsense and get out.
I'm stressed out as it is.
You've been in a bad mood
ever since we got back from Gangneung.
Don't you ever mention Gangneung again.
Get out!
Can't he take it to the attic himself?
HOME-COOKED MEALS FOR TAE-O!
A NUTRITIOUS AND LOW-SODIUM DIET!
SAUCE
He still has this.
WALNUTS WITH ALMONDS AND ANCHOVIES
TO HELP TAE-O GET SMART!
WATERMELONS, TAE-O'S FAVORITE!
How are you doing?
Is the acting thing going well?
Call me.
I'm staying at Tae-o's and I'm doing well.
Whatever happens, happens.
MISSING PERSON
NAME: O GA-RIN, AGE: 23
Dear God,
please do not lead me into temptation.
REWARD: 10 MILLION WON
Okay.
I should throw this away
so that I don't become tempted by it.
Holy shit!
I'm sorry.
Did I scare you?
You could have knocked. Why were you
just standing there like that?
I just...
What?
Do you have something to say to me?
No, never mind.
Did you tell everyone else
that I accidentally told you about it?
So, you do know that
what you guys did was wrong.
The truth is,
Tae-o was against it the whole time,
but we insisted--
I don't want to know.
For the time being,
let's keep it to ourselves.
Why?
Receiving an apology is useless...
when I'm in this mood.
I'm so stupid.
Why in the world did I say that?
Tae-o's going to be furious
when he finds out.
I can't believe myself!
Oh, gosh.
What am I going to do?
This place is amazing.
You showed me the best view on campus too.
-I'm just returning the favor.
-There is no need for that.
You don't have to return
the favor for everything I do.
Maybe you're right.
It's my favorite view of the city.
The hanok and the buildings
built from different eras
are standing together harmoniously.
You don't get to see such a view
easily in Seoul.
You're right.
It's wonderful.
We should get something to eat.
This place is expensive.
Let's go somewhere else.
That's what I always do.
Let's just eat here. It's on me.
Wow, it's beautiful.
Thank you.
This is really good.
Eating this makes me want to
make a lot of money.
I think that when I'm with you...
What?
Never mind.
Architects don't earn much, right?
That's how it is.
You work overtime
even when you're employed.
According to the seniors who've graduated,
it's the same as being a student.
You're talented enough
to find a job at a big company.
If you think about the salary,
wouldn't that be a better option?
True.
But I promised my dad
that I'd become an architect.
I can't get out of it now, can I?
You said your dad built the house
you used to live in, right?
Yes.
I saw it on the day we first met.
I liked it. It was nice and cozy.
I'll buy that house back for you
when I make a lot of money.
You're going to have to make a fortune.
I will, for you.
For me?
Well, I...
It's just wishful thinking.
I'm not sure...
if this is an appropriate place
to kiss you.
What?
Hey, don't get the wrong idea.
Wasn't it intentional?
Of course it wasn't.
Are you sure?
The number you have dialed
cannot be reached...
Hey, you're home. I didn't see your bike
outside so I thought you left.
I sent it for a tune-up.
Why?
Does your girlfriend not like the design?
I think it's me that she doesn't like.
I don't think she's mad at me or anything.
She replies whenever I text her.
But...
for some reason,
it feels like she's keeping her distance.
She doesn't pick up when I call her.
Did I do something wrong
when we went to Gangneung?
She's been acting odd
since we got back from the trip.
LET'S GO ON A TRIP TOO. I'LL TAKE CARE OF
THE PLANE TICKETS AND THE HOTEL.
Tae-o.
Yes?
If you found out that...
the person you care for lied to you,
it would hurt, wouldn't it?
Of course.
I'm sure it would.
It would be a huge blow
for narcissists like you.
What?
Song-i.
Emotional scars deepen
depending on how long the lie stays a lie.
Plus, there's nothing more hurtful
than finding out the truth
through other people.
Confessions...
must come from the person
who's been lying.
We're done. I have to be
at a construction site tomorrow.
Hey, wait.
Don't you have anything to say to me?
What? Say what?
Wow, you're unbelievable.
Hey, you know what?
Clean all this up before you go.
Is he that upset
over his relationship problems?
This is so embarrassing.
It will be humiliating
if I run into someone I know.
I'd better get out of here quickly.
DREAM SCHOOL SCORE
DREAM SCHOOL SCRIPT
Choe Hun?
Oh, hey.
What's this?
There's a get-together today
at a tripe restaurant
near our school after work.
I'll pass. I don't feel so good.
Maybe it's because I had beer yesterday.
Hey.
Isn't that Se-hyeon?
What on earth?
Anyone would think
that those two are dating.
You've seen it too, right?
Se-hyeon flirted
with one of the guys on our team.
Apparently, they watched
a movie together too.
He was convinced
that things were going well with her.
Maybe that's how she always plays it.
She makes them think they've got
a chance with her so she can use them.
Does Tae-o know this too?
What did you say was on the menu again?
Tripe.
I should pig out then.
I haven't had tripe in a while.
If you bribe them,
they could put in a good word
to get you cast.
Not in a major supporting role, but
as part of an ensemble or a swing dance.
-It's great meeting you.
-Thank you.
-Shall we clink our glasses?
-Yes.
All right. Guys, cheers!
-Cheers!
That's a lot of meat.
Let's dig in.
-I need to lose weight.
-Just eat up.
Eat up, everyone.
-Enjoy.
-It's so good.
I've been here before.
What am I going to say to him?
That I think his girlfriend
is seeing someone else?
And that she might go on a trip
with that guy?
Plus,
there's nothing more hurtful
than finding out the truth
through other people.
Why did he have to say that?
Why fill up your own glass
when you've got us?
Dae-geon.
Finally, I get to drink with you.
It's really hard to
get you to drink with us.
You'll be a senior next year, right?
Any idea where you'll apply to?
Well, my first choice is Donggwang
Architectural Firm, where you're working.
After all, it's the best in this country.
I feel honored.
I need to drop by the school to pick up
some documents from the professor.
Let's have dinner together sometime.
I'll give you a few pointers
on your resume.
I'd really appreciate that.
Don't thank me.
It's the least I can do as your senior.
-Thank you.
That will be 15,000 won.
-Here you go. Thank you.
-Let's go.
SONG-I: HAVING TRIPE
Having tripe at the get-together.
Don't drink too much.
Call me when you head home.
Excuse me?
Yes, coming.
HAN SONG-I
Hello?
Hello? Is it you, Song-i?
Dae-geon?
I left with your phone
because it's the same one as mine.
I see.
I'm sorry to ask you this,
but could you come to school?
I'll call you back in ten minutes.
To the engineering building?
Yes, thanks a lot.
Get in.
I'm okay. Here's your phone.
Here.
Thanks.
You'll take the bus, right?
I'll drop you off at the bus stop.
I'm all right, really.
Come on. You're making me
look like a weirdo here.
That's not it.
Save me from the embarrassment and get in.
I'll get out by the main entrance.
Thank you.
Did you drink a lot?
No, I feel fine.
You're a heavy drinker.
Wait.
I think you just passed the main entrance.
Let's take a quick spin.
The weather's great for a drive.
There's no need to hurry home, is there?
So, you want to join my company?
I'm well acquainted with people from HR.
You know, he does weird things
to girls at the observatory
after getting them drunk.
OBSERVATORY
STUDENT UNION BUILDING
We'll have two servings of meat dumplings
with Coke and Sprite.
Okay, two servings of meat dumplings,
a bottle of Coke
-and a bottle of Sprite, right?
-Yes.
OBSERVATORY
ADMINISTRATION BUILDING
COME TO THE SCHOOL OBSERVATORY. QUICKLY.
DO-HYEON, TAE-O,
HYEON-JI, MIN-SEOK
YU-RIM, SO-MIN,
SEUNG-JUN, MIN-AH
TAE-O
Come to the observatory.
I'm in front of your house.
I have to talk to you about something.
Please come outside.
MESSAGE FROM DUMB SONG
Come to the observatory.
That was random.
Hey, do you remember
my senior Lee Dae-geon?
That annoying jerk?
-What about him?
-He's a trainer for the interns.
She has a boyfriend.
I'm sure Do-hyeon will be there for her.
Man...
DUMB SONG
CALL
The number you have dialed
is not available.
Please leave a message after the tone.
It's been so long since I last came here.
A memorial hall will be built in its place
since the astronomy department's gone.
Which is why there are hardly
any people who come here.
To Hansung University, please. Quickly.
Did you know that this place
is a hot place for couples?
Is it?
I had no idea.
Why...
do you think I brought you here?
I've been expressing
my feelings for you all along.
And you said you wanted to work
at my company,
even when you knew how I felt about you.
Well, the reason I want to work there
isn't because of you, but--
Doesn't that mean...
you feel the same way?
What are you talking about?
I know that you like me.
Am I wrong?
What are you doing?
Don't make things any worse
than they already are.
Open the door, now.
Then why did you get in my car?
I'm regretting it more than ever.
So open the door.
Unlock the door before I call the cops!
I know that your battery died.
Han Song-i!
-Tae-o!
-Song-i.
Hey, are you all right?
What happened?
Why are you at the observatory?
Did that jerk bring you here?
Let's just go.
Come on, let's go.
There seems to be
a misunderstanding, but...
Tae-o!
Stop it!
-Hey.
-I said, stop!
What did you do to her here?
-Tell me!
-Hey!
I'm wearing glasses!
You can't hit me.
Don't hit me, please.
Thanks for the help.
It was a bit hectic, wasn't it?
It's good to have many customers.
Let's see...
Come to the school observatory. Quickly.
You let that jerk just go like that?
I'm okay, really.
He blurted out some nonsense,
and that was about it.
He shouldn't have brought you here
in the first place.
Are you stupid?
Why did you get in his car?
He offered to drop me off at the bus stop.
Why won't you listen to me?
How can...
I told you that there are dirty rumors
about him and that you should be careful.
He eventually brought you here, didn't he?
I'm sorry.
The bus stop was close by,
-so I didn't think he'd--
-Where's Do-hyeon?
What?
Where is your boyfriend right now?
You knew?
The number you have dialed
is currently unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
When did you find out?
When we went to Gangneung.
Gangneung?
The pool!
The pool...
You guys were together
in a wide, open space.
Don't you think it'd be weirder
if no one saw you?
Then why didn't you say anything?
I waited for you to tell me.
But you didn't say a word.
I'm sorry.
I was going to tell you
when we were in Gangneung.
But then Hun got really upset,
and it just didn't seem like
the right time to tell you.
And once I missed my timing,
it kind of felt awkward to bring up
the subject again.
Forget it.
It takes a few lies for friendships
to gradually fall apart, I guess.
The day I was kicked out of my house,
that day,
Do-hyeon was there as one of the movers.
What?
It wasn't at your place
when I first met him.
After getting kicked out,
I met him again at your place.
The next day, I bumped into him again
when I went to get
a part-time job at the library.
I wasn't lying when I said
that he was a guy I worked with.
Why didn't you say that it was Do-hyeon?
I don't know. I...
I guess I was drawn to him
from the very beginning.
I was afraid you'd notice that,
so I intentionally avoided mentioning him.
It's just like
when you pretend to be nonchalant
about the person you're interested in.
I didn't mean to lie to you.
Don't be mad. Please?
Hey, Do-hyeon.
Tae-o, do you know where Song-i is now?
She's with me right now.
-With you?
-I'll take her home. You should come over.
What happened?
Did something happen to her?
Let's talk at home.
Hello, this is Kim Ji-hyeon speaking.
I...
Well, I...
Hello?
I called because...
Please go ahead.
Well...
I... I have...
something...
to tell you...
regarding O Ga-rin.
I...
I saw her...
working at...
a supermarket.
It's called...
Happy Mart.
Are you not mad at me anymore?
I'm not mad at you.
But I still feel like
I'm walking on eggshells right now.
Does it make you feel uncomfortable
that I like your friend?
My pride was hurt.
Because of the fact...
that the first guy Song-i liked...
was Do-hyeon and not me.
-It's not that.
-What is it, then?
I'm such a selfish jerk.
It's because...
Do-hyeon is too good for you.
-What?
-Let me tell you something.
Do-hyeon's a really popular guy.
Not as popular as me, though.
Hey, I'm pretty popular too.
You call having a pervert stalking you
being popular?
You talk as if you were quite a hotshot.
Well, I am definitely not a coldshot.
Do-hyeon!
What happened?
Why is your phone turned off?
My battery died.
I'm sorry.
I got worried because I couldn't
reach you after you sent that text.
Why did you go to the observatory?
Something came up.
-What is it?
-Ask your girlfriend about it later.
Tell me, what happened?
You should go inside.
I'm going to have
a little chat with Do-hyeon.
Wait, he knew all along?
Hey, is that important right now?
You've been lying to me all this time.
I was going to tell you...
I'll go inside then.
Call me when you're done talking.
Okay.
Do you want to...
grab a drink?
What's there to have a drink for?
It's just Song-i.
MEN SAID,
"THIS IS WHEN IT FELT LIKE A FLING."
WE WERE ALL TALKING TOGETHER,
THEN SHE TOUCHED ME.
You must have been pretty pissed at me
back in Gangneung.
Why?
Because I bad mouthed Song-i's boyfriend,
when I didn't know it was you.
You did hit a nerve.
I might do the same in the future.
Regardless of the circumstances,
if you two get into a fight,
I'll side with Song-i first.
If she gets upset because of you,
I'll say bad things about you.
Song-i is lucky you have her back.
From your perspective, I understand
that my presence may get on your nerves.
But Song-i and I share
a 20-year-long history.
My history with Tae-o
is something that can't be helped.
As you know, you can't change history.
Even if I behave fastidiously
from time to time,
I hope you understand.
Let me ask you a favor as well.
Let go of the sense of responsibility...
you have towards her.
I'm there for her now.
I'd be more than happy to do that.
If there's anything you want
to know about her, ask away.
Such as her favorite things,
what she absolutely hates,
and what to do to make her
feel better when she's upset.
I know Song-i inside out.
No, that's okay.
I'll get to know her myself.
Getting to know someone...
is what it means to be in a relationship.
You're right.
I like Song-i a lot.
I want our relationship to work.
Okay.
Well...
I'm sure you'll do a good job.
DRIED POLLACK SOUP
Wow. You made all of this for breakfast?
It's nothing much.
-Set the table, will you?
-Okay.
You can't call this "nothing much."
All these dishes
take so much effort to prepare.
I'm considerate enough to know that.
Try it.
It's phenomenal.
You actually made this?
It's your mom's recipe.
I found it in the attic.
Her recipes are very detailed.
Oh, that?
Why did you keep this in the attic?
I'll cook everything
in this cookbook for you.
There's no need.
It's not like you're on a cooking show.
I'm serious. I always keep my promises.
Let's see. For dinner,
steamed conger...
This one's a bit challenging.
Try this, too.
You made bulgogi as well?
Come and sit down. I made breakfast.
Hey, Hun. Come and have breakfast.
Okay.
I'll grab something to eat later.
-What?
-What are you talking about?
Can't you see that Song-i made all this
for us this morning?
You should be grateful for the meal.
I'm sorry!
What was that?
Sorry about what?
I...
told her.
Told her what?
That night in Gangneung,
when you guys had
all gone off somewhere...
I told Se-hyeon that we all live together.
What?
I'm so sorry.
Why, you...
Were you waiting for me?
Yes. I have something to tell you.
That's too bad.
-I have to be somewhere now.
-It's regarding my place.
I'm really sorry.
I don't know what to say.
It's not that I don't understand.
I think I would've done the same...
if my friends had no place to stay
and I had rooms available.
Why didn't you ask me about it
when you knew?
I didn't want to be the one to ask first.
It was bad enough that my pride was hurt.
I didn't want to look pathetic
by bringing it up first.
I'm really sorry.
It's not that I was trying to lie to you--
My head gets it, but my heart doesn't.
Do you know why it hurt so badly?
Han Song-i.
I know you couldn't tell me
because of her.
No, that's not true.
You hid it from me because
you were worried that I'd make a fuss
if I found out
that Song-i was living with you.
Isn't that the real reason?
Apologize.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to hide it from you.
I don't want you to just say you're sorry.
I want you to show it.
Tell Song-i...
to leave.
I want her out of your house.
I'll accept your apology then.