Caution: The show is created for entertainment purposes only. Please exercise caution while watching.
Honey! // Where will you take my husband to?
I do nothing wrong!
If I don't think that up myself...
I think...
Boom might probably interested in you.
I...
I like you, Mr. Uea.
What I want to say is...
I have a boyfriend.
This is my boyfriend, Uea.
I don't want to ruin the mood.
Uea, you should call me "mom" as well.
[Woof Woof Woof!]
[Woof Woof Woof Woof!]
[Woof!]
How can you tease him. Hahaha
Huh, Jade. You're so funny!
Everyone's gonna say that I'm cute!
As cute as a dog?
Huh?
[Woof Woof!]
Faii replied : OMG! Like father like son! LOL.
Gun replied : You said h looked alike dog? LOL.
Muay replied: That's hurt, Faii!
Gun.
Hm?
You are son of a...!
I gotta back home.
What? Come on, Jade~
Don't mad at me.
Um.
Wait for me~
Let's go.
Let's go to our home.
so we can pack things for the trip.
Um.
[Is that true we're just friends?]
[but I think we're much more than that.]
[Our friends say that we made like a pack.]
[I don't know what do you feel about me.]
[but I think you have feeling for me.]
[Things between us makes me feel good]
[I don't think I can keep it anymore]
[Can we change from friend into boyfriend?]
[Are you thinking what I'm thinking?]
[Can you say it first? Say it now!]
[boyfriend. I wanna be your boyfriend.]
[It's up to you, just say it.]
[I like you.]
[Don't wanna be just your friend.]
Sea trip
Hey! // Ah!
Don't you shirt have a button?
Hm?
Are you getting jealous?
If so, will you button up?
Nope.
Cuz I want you to get a big jealous on me.
Fine.
Are we good?
Ok Ok Ok.
I've changed my mind.
I will do it up.
Ok now?
Another button.
It's no button anymore~
Put the mask on as well.
Um.
Hurry up.
Alright~
[So call me out baby.]
[Together we can go crazy.]
[You and me in the night, I'm feeling alright. Now I got you and I want more]
[So call me out baby.]
[Together we can go crazy.]
[You and me in the night, I'm feeling alright. Now I got you and I want more.]
[You're one of a kind.]
[Nobody's breaking your spirit.]
[You're looking so fine.]
[Nobody's breaking your, breaking your....]
[You're keeping up with steps I take
So we just dance along.]
[Yeah, we dance like no one's watching]
[So call me out, call me out, baby.]
[Hey! So call me out, baby.]
[Together we can go crazy.]
[You and me in the night, I'm feeling alright. Now I got you and I want more.]
[LINE message]
Jade sent : How was your trip?
Jade sent me a message.
Let's take pictures for him.
Hmmm.
King.
No.
Jade sent : Aww. I wanna have trip like you guys!
IG caption : Trip in the sea was feeling so hot, but nothing's hot like you and me.
What the caption is!
Why?
Trip in the sea was feeling so hot,
but nothing's hot
like you and me...
Hmmm.
That's blasting.
How about yours?
IG caption : Coffee or me?
I gotta go.
You like being here?
Um.
You choose this island...
because...
I really wanna stay here.
I know why.
You know me!
Every single time!
Stop it!
Let's take a sight.
Where do you wanna go for the next long weekend?
This is just first day of weekends.
I wanna spend time with just the two of us.
Don't you wanna come home?
Hm.
We will.
I'd absolutely take my boyfriend to meet my parents.
Hey.
I talk to your mom more than talking to you.
Do you know it?
Woahh.
Alright.
Boyfriend of the year.
I wanna know...
how good of you
as being a boyfriend...
1..2..3!!!
Woo!
Get drunk?
Not yet.
Do you have anything else I can eat?
You said it yourself.
So...
Can I have something hard?
Wanna sleep?
Um.
Turn off the lights then.
Uea!
What happened, Uea?!
Are you sure?
Um.
If I got you by my side,
I could sleep.
Good night, baby.
Umm.
Good night.
King! Uea!
Can we stop now?
I know it's good,
but I want to take it off already.
Gun.
We can't deceive the consumer, you know?
Here, take it and do some research.
Woah.
Why don't you go with me, King?
I won't ever leave my boyfriend.
Could you please stop flirting?
Um.
Just go.
Fine! I'll do it alone!
Are you happy?
Um.
King.
Wake up.
King~
Hmm, no.
Aren't you going to hang out with friend today?
Wake up.
I'm awake.
Get up then.
Help me.
Um.
Good morning.
What morning?
It's already 10 a.m.
Go take a bath.
Hmm.
Then I'll take a bath first.
and wake you up after that.
Umm.
Tonkao, if you have not enough money, you can tell me.
It's enough.
I feel bad, you're so considerate.
Don't mention it.
So... does mom still ask you for money?
Sometimes.
But I didn't text back.
Do you understand me?
Yes.
Thank you for still taking care of me.
I love you, Uea.
I'm going to study. Hope we meet again soon.
Sure.
Who did you talk to? Your voice was so sweet.
Hm?// It's Tonkao.
It'd be great if you talk to me like that.
Are you getting bored of me?
Huh?
There's no way that will happen.
Hmm.
So when are you going to meet your friend?
Hm?
At noon.
Hm.
But It might go all the way to the evening.
So I may come back late.
Um.
I'll wait for you.
What are you smiling for?
My boyfriend is cute.
So I want to smile at him.
Hmph!
I wanna squeeze you. Take this!
Eat it and stop fooling around!
Um.
I'm chewing!
1 year later.
Will we be caught by Uea?
I've never lied to him.
Argh!
You don't tell, I don't tell. How will he know?
But you know I'm not good at lying!
Sh*t! I'm stressed out!// Hey! Why are you so nervous?
You're just here to help me choose a ring.
Are you not nervous at all?!
Of course, I am.
I'm very nervous. But I tried to keep my cool.
Please tell me if you have any preferences.
Um...
My lover likes the basic style.
Basic?
Then it should be this one.
What kind of person is your lover?
I'll help you choose.
Um.
My lover?
He's arrogant, moody and likes to overthink things.
King!
I'll tell Uea about this!
But he takes a very good care of me...
and I love him more than anything.
Good saying.
Can I take a look at that one?// Yes, sure.
This is the new product of our shop.
It's a 0.7 carat white gold ring.
What do you think, Jade?
Is something wrong?
What's wrong?
Boohooo.
I'm touched.
You've never be this good since I know you.
Is that a compliment?
Um, of course!
Both of my friends are going to settle down! *sob*
I'll have this one.
Yes, sir.
Dad, mom.
I'll propose to Uea next month.
Did you think it over?
Yes.
I've decided that Uea...
is the love of my life.
We're not going to stop you.
Because after all this time you make us believe that...
you will be a great couple.
Thank you.
I'm still your son,
Got's brother,
and the same family member.
What's more is...
I want to love someone...
and take care of him for the rest of my life.
You've grown up, King.
I'm happy that you're happy.
I can't wait to see your ring.
I've looked for it.
Here.
Let me have a look.
King!
This... I think...
Isn't the diamond too small?
Ha?
It won't stand out when you take photos.
Why don't you choose it carefully?
Let him decide. It's up to him.
But the bigger, the better.// Um.
Why?
The bigger one will be more beautiful!
Let's take a photo.
Hahaha.
Argh!
When did you come back?
Just now.
I'm surprised!// Can you kiss me?
Hehe.
What did you do?// Hm?
It looks good.// I made salad.
How was it? Are you tired?
Hm?
No.
Sit down first.
Massage here.// Nonsense.// Will you do it?// Maybe.
Are you hungry?
Not much.
There's always traffic jam on Valentine's day.
Uh-huh.
Actually,
we can cook something at home.
Or else you'll have a stomachache.
I don't want to make you tired.
And I want a change of atmosphere.
If I'm with you,
I won't be tired just from cooking for you.
Hmm.
Talking like this, do you want to do something that's not eating?
Focus on driving!
Drive properly, King!
Give me attention. It's Valentine's day.
Kiss my cheek.
I can't feel it.
Drive!// I'm driving! You haven't touched me!
I know it. You're always like this!
You...
What are you doing?
Asking you for a hand in marriage.
Here?
Um.
Right here.
King love Uea.
Next year...
will you marry me?
Um.
Why did you choose to propose here?
I want to let everyone know about us.
That after this...
I'll take care of you...
and love only you.
Wow, congratulations!
It's very lovely!
Hello, mom.
Hello, dad.
You've become my child, Uea.
Welcome to our family, Uea.
Thank you.
Congrats, Uea!// Tonkao!
I wish you a lot of happiness.
If I can help with anything, you can always tell me.
So cute!
I hope you guys to be very happy,
and love each other for a looong time.
Who knows that my office mate, who's also my FWB,
will be the simple happiness that I've been looking for.
I love you.
Um.
I...
love you too.
[Can we change from friend into boyfriend?]
[Are you thinking what I'm thinking?]
[Can you say it first? Say it now!]
[Please understand, I wanna be your boyfriend.]
I've warned you that...
don't play with Anol.
[Can we change from friend into boyfriend?]
Let's give them a round of applause!
[Are you thinking what I'm thinking?]
I wanna catch the bouquet! Throw it!
Throw it!
One, two, three!
[Don't wanna be just your friend.]
Awww, oh my god!
You got it, Jade!
You caught it!
I'm sorry.
Do you accept trainee here?
We do.
[You and me are just chilling]
[but I'm thinking much more than that]
[I don't wanna be your friend]
[Can we change into a boyfriend?]
[Am I just a home only when you feel alone?]
[Are we just friend no matter how much I love you?]
[I think I has crossed the line]
[You and me are just chilling]
[but I'm thinking much more than that]
[I don't wanna be your friend]
[Can we change into a boyfriend?]
[Am I just a home only when you feel alone?]
[Are we just friend no matter how much I love you?]
[I think I has crossed the line]