Caution: The show is created for entertainment purposes only. Please exercise caution while watching.
I'm sorry for avoiding you.
and...
have a sharp tongue with you.
Is that your ex?
Why being so blue?
To hell with him!
You deserve better, I knew it.
To be honest...
If it wasn't you...
I might ask for being a...
Friend With Benefits.
You're so damn hot.
Wait.
We've gotta set the rules first.
Sure.
Just tell me.
First rule,
We will make love...
not more than twice a week.
Woah.
Too less.
If you're not ok with this,
call it end now.
I didn't say I'm not ok.
What's next?
Huh?
Ah.
Second rule,
Do not make any love bite.
I don't like bruise.
Fine.
That's all?
and always ask for my consent.
If I say NO,
It means NO.
Always wear condom, too.
Don't butt in me at the office.
No one mustn't know about us.
Even Jade,
Must not know, too.
That's all?
and!
either you or me fine the one...
to be with...
We have to end our relationship right away.
This includes...
when you or me want to end this,
we call it the end.
Fine.
That's all?
Not yet.
one more,
If you sleep with another one,
I will end this relationship right away.
Hey.
If you can't accept the rules,
so don't start it at all.
Call it the end NOW.
Fine.
I won't sleep with another one.
It's not even the problem.
I don't like you.
You don't like me.
It's just sex.
You think the guy like you can follow the rules?
Hm?
I don't know.
If I sleep with another one,
I promise I won't lie to you.
um.
Fine.
I have one rule.
If I can't sleep with another one,
I think twice a week is too less.
I need 4.
Too much.
No.
I won't do it.
3 is fine.
Just 3 times a week, deal?
Hm? Mr.Anol?
I ask for only one rule.
um.
Fine.
[Is that true we're just friends?]
[but I think we're much more than that.]
[Our friends say that we made like a pack.]
[I don't know what do you feel about me.]
[but I think you have feeling for me.]
[Things between us makes me feel good]
[I don't think I can keep it anymore]
[Can we change from friend into boyfriend?]
[Are you thinking what I'm thinking?]
[Can you say it first? Say it now!]
[boyfriend. I wanna be your boyfriend.]
[It's up to you to, just say it.]
[I like you.]
[Don't wanna be just your friend.]
Just drop me here.
What do you wanna buy?
I can wait.
Drop me here.
I will walk in there.
Why walking?
Don''t want anyone seeing us together?
If you get it, then drop me here.
I have to go.
Uea!
[I love you sign]
Keep your naughty hands.
Hmmmm.
I mean massage me!
I don't wanna have kid like you!
Please let me go, mom! I'm sorry!
You embarrassed me!
Are you avoid my call?
I'm just ask for a little bit money.
You have to come home this Sat.
Your dad asked about you. So boring.
Don't accept the call?
What happened, Uea?
nothing.
My mom wants me to come home.
Um.
You should go home.
King.
Hm?
Tonight...
you can come if you want.
You don't go home?
No.
I haven't back home for a long time.
Are you okay, Uea?
Well...
Just call me when you arrived.
I'll pick you up.
King.
Here.
Your shirt.
Oh. It's here.
Keep it in your car.
Sure.
Hm?
What?
Hey!
Come with me?
Where?
Ahh!
What're you gonna do?
Let me dry your hair.
I can handle it.
No. Come here!
Ahhh/ Ummm.
[It's kinda feel good.]
Come here.
[Can I be your boyfriend now?]
[Are you thinking what I'm thinking?]
[Aye.]
Hm?!
What're you doing, uncle Sorn?
What're you doing?!
I don't like it.
Did I scared you?
I'm sorry.
I promise.
I will never do things you don't like anymore.
Uea.
Oh./ Ah.
This is for you.
This is mine?
Yeah, take a look!
Whoa. Colored pencils!
I like it so much!
You like it?
so you can do your drawings.
Cool?
Uea. Can you teach me how to draw?
Of course!
What're you gonna draw?
Well...
The mountain...because...
It's the easiest one.
Just a mountain?
Yes.
Go ahead.
Hm.
Here. Ahhhhh.
Wait. You should guide my hand.
Hm.
What're you doing, uncle Sorn?
Mosquito! The big one! It's gonna bite you here.
[Please forgive me]
Can you forgive me?
I won't do anything...
that you don't like again.
This is from me.
Not from the others...
Are you sure you don't want it?
Please...
Ueaaaaaaaa!
Uea.
Wooo.
Ah.
Are you teasing him, King?
I'm sorry.
Ahhh.
I'm not mad at you anymore.
Hmmmm. What did you do, King?!
Tell me! Hm?!
Shut your mouth.
Tell me now!
King.
Why don't you wait for me? I'm not finished talking to you.
Why you're so hurry?
Are you an infant?
Do I need to look after? / Ah. Ah. Ah. Anyway.
Just don't stand me up!
You guys are hanging out together again!
But when I asked you to eat red pork rice....
No one come with me!
Ueaaaa.
Kinggg.
Please eat red pork rice with me./ King, pleaseeee
Hello, Mr.Anol.
What's up?
Nothing.
Just wanna call you.
For what?
so...
You're not hanging with Gun?
I'm not hanging with him.
or even another one.
If it wasn't you.
I have to go.
I feel sleepy.
Heyyyy.
Too shy to stay?
I-said-I'm-sleepy!
Ah. Ah. Ah.
I promise I'll be a good boy tonight. I'm not going anywhere.
Why telling me?
Just want to.
Why, Mr.Anol?
Don't bug me.
Um.
I'll text you when I arrived.
Don't worry about me.
Who cares?
Well.
King.
Who're you talking with?
Secret.
Fine. I don't wanna know.
so...
Can we go?!
I wanna get in now!
Let's go.
King (Incoming calls)
If you don't reply me, I'll come to see you.
I tried to cheer with her so long!
Why don't she interested in me?!
What a boring!
Ahhh.
Shhhh* King! You...
You do nothing, why did she look at you?!
How to do that?!
Please tell me the trick.
Stop put this f*cking thing in your mouth.
Why? It's kinda cool.
I'm not looking for a high rate type.
but why I can't catch any girl?
so,
What's your type?
Ummmm
Can you give an example one from the office?
Oh.
Fah, the accountant.
She's so damn cute!
I might flirt with her if she's still single!
Wait. Wait. Wait.
There's another one.
so cute.
Uea.
Ouch.
Hmmm. Gun.
Why did you hit me?
Don't cross the line.
I'm just giving an example!
Thought I need to go home alone.
Can I give a toast with you?
Ummm.
I don't drink today.
Can I cheers with this?
So cute.
Er.
Fries are nice.
Can you order more?
Huh?
Sh*t!
You're not King!
Hurry up!
Ok.
King sent at 3:10 am. : I arrived home already.
King sent at 3:10 am. : Come back alone. Sleep alone. So lonely.
Uea: Gun told me already.
Ah. Uea. Sawasdeekrub. [Hello]
I'm hungover.
Need coffee?
Ah.
I'm about to get it.
I will do it myself.
Ah. Ok.
Ah.
Sh*t.
What happened?
The dust is in my eyes.
Hey! Don't squeeze.
Come here.
There's another one. So cute.
Uea.
What're you doing?
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
Leave me!
What're gonna do?
We're in the office now.
It should be me asking you.
What're you gonna do?
What the hell happened to you?
I don't like it.
I'm getting jealous.
Jealous?
Don't kidding me by saying that.
What if I'm not kidding?
You never settled down with anyone.
Don't talk to me like that.
I've already fixed the part you asked, King.
Is there anything else?
Nope.
Ah, then...
I'm going home.
Uea, Jade, good bye.
Good bye.
Good bye, King.
Um.
Mongkol, I'm going home, good bye.
Wait!
Where are you going?
Uh... I'm going back home.
Why would you leave before seniors like us?
Understood.
Wait a minute.
Yes, sir.
There is so much to do. My back hurts.
Hey, Jade.
Don't forget to check your inbox. I've already sent you the file.
Okay.
Keep fighting.
I'm leaving, Uea.
See you, everyone.
See you.
Jade.
I'll go to the bathroom.
Um.
Uh.
He sent me a blank file again!
Really?
There is not even a single layer!
How could he do this to you?
That's horrible.
I think...
I should tell Bas about this.
Hey!
It's useless.
You are being too kind, Jade.
Is there anything I can do for you?
It's alright.
I'll do this tomorrow.
Are you leaving?
Um.
I'll go to the bathroom first.
Get ready and wait for me.
Um, I'll wait for you.
My room tonight.
Will you come?
So you no longer avoid me.
We've come to this point...
How could I keep avoiding you?
Can we do it like this again next time?
Why do you agree to sleep with me?
Why are you asking this now?
I don't know.
I feel like...
If I had bothered you from the start,
you would have changed your mind.
Besides,
You don't seem like you'd be interested in this stuff.
So I want to know why you let me do it.
I guess I just wanna f*ck up my life even more.
Since most of the time...
my life isn't great after all.
Then...
Will you let me be a good thing in your life?
Someone like you?
At least,
I'm good in bed.
Enough!
I'm still upset with you, you know?
Is that so?
Yes, I am.
You still parked in the same spot, Uea.
Pock?
So if I want you to talk to me,
I have to come to your office?
Let go of me!
No.
Why?
Can't I just hold you?
Are you deaf?
Get out of my life!
I won't.
You made a one side decision with our break up!
I won't let you go that easily.
What are you looking at?!
Huh? What the f*ck are you looking at?!
Pock.
Let's have a real talk.
Hm?
Pock!
Hey! What are you doing?
Butt out!
You're the one that should butt out!
Tell your friend it's not his business!
If you won't let him go,
I'll call a security!
You want to fight me?!/ Hey!
Huh?!
Talk to me!!/ No!
Stop looking!
Are you looking for trouble?!/ Hey, Jade!
I have nothing to say to you!
Hey! Stop!
Freeze!
Aren't your father a politician?
It won't be good if you're in the news, right?
It's a misunderstanding.
I'm sorry.
Are you alright?
Yes, I'm fine.
Okay, I'm leaving then.
Thank you.
Let's get back to work.
Uea!
Are you really alright?
Are you hurt anywhere?
I believe
Pock won't end it like this.
Will you report against him to the police?
Report who?
Uea's ex-boyfriend.
He came and made a scene.
Did he do anything to you?
Not yet.
I called the security in time.
Hey!
What if he go to your condominium?
He won't dare.
Let's file a police report.
Uh.
Let's do that!
Never mind.
But I think you should.../ I threatened him about his father.
He wouldn't dare to do anything to me.
Why are you spacing out here?
It's nothing.
Why don't you temporarily move into my room?
Kinggg! King!
Hurry up!
A bug needs to be fixed immediately!
You go fix it first.
Yes, yes. Let's go! The boss is calling!
I'm going to bed.
Noo.
What's the hurry?
Uea, stay with me.
Uea, Uea, Uea.
I. am. replying. aren't. I?
I'm replying, aren't I?
(King sent a photo)
Can I make a call?
Nope
(King is video calling)
You said no, but still answered my call.
Uea, don't end it!
I'm feeling lonely.
I need someone to sleep with me.
Why are you telling me, then?
Ah.
Why wouldn't I?
I only have you.
I'm lonely.
Can I come over?
For what? It's already late.
To sleep, of course.
Please, mr. Anol.
I'm going to sleep.
Then leave the call like this. Don't end it.
You're acting like a child, King.
I just want to lie down and look at you.
Do as you please.
I'm going to sleep now.
Hmm, Uea!
Not the feet!
Hm?
Um.
Are you happy now?
Yes, I am.
Um.
So...
I'll sleep.
Sweet dreams.
I'm going to sleep.
[You and me are just chilling]
[but I'm thinking much more than that]
[I don't wanna be your friend]
[Can we change into a boyfriend?]
[Am I just a home only when you feel alone?]
[Are we just friend no matter how much I love you?]
[I think I has crossed the line]
Woahh.
We'll get off work in just a moment!
I feel like I got a lot of work done today. Do you think so?
King?
Do you feel like you accomplished a lot of work?
Eh? Nobody talks to me.
Oh, guys. I'll be leaving first for today.
I have a meeting and dinner appointment with our boss.
Oh, hello.
Hello./ Hello.
I have a dinner appointment with my boss.
Really?
What a high-pitched tone.
I'll take my leave.
Oh my, how could he?!
He is the last to arrive and the first to leave!
What a jerk!/ Right?
Well, now I know why we got troubles today.
King! Your shirt is an inauspicious color!
What's inauspicious?
You see, the marketing team said that...
The clients don't use promotion because there're a lot of bugs!
So how does that relate to the color of my shirt?
It sure does! Take a close look at this.!
It's Friday, so Black is inauspicious!
You should wear a lively Blue like this!
Lively!/ Yes.
Hm.
Oops!
Oppa (Older brother in Korean) is calling./ Hehehe.
Hello? *Speaking in Korean*
Hello.
Brother, I love you!
Oh?
Oppa?
Don't go!
Why?
He broke up with me!
See? Muay, I told you that your pants is an inauspicious color!
Did you watch the Chae show?
Moddam clearly tells you what color you should wear.
Yes, I always watch it.
But they laughed the entire show, so I didn't understand a thing.
I think they're quite good though./ Whatever!
Hahaha./ Boohoo.
Hey, King!
Remember to check the best color next time.
Yes, maam.
Good.
I'm leaving, guys. Good bye.
Wait a second./ Huh?
Aren't you working OT?
No way, my child is waiting.
Boo.
Say, your child or your hubby?
Fine!
My hubby is waiting.
I have a husband, after all.
Hello, Waeo?
2,500 like always.
Stop it, Muay! Don't call Waeo. Let's go home!
Treat me to a Soju.
Alright, 3 bottles, my treat.
Hahaha.
You're acting like a madam.
Hehehe.
I've got a backache, don't wanna work anymore.
You can go first, Gun.
Huh? Why?
It's not that much.
You can go. I'll take care of the rest
Then, I'm going first.
Jade.
Hm?
Wanna go together?
There's a buy 1 get 1 free promotion
Wow.
4 - 6 p.m.
Shit!
We've 15 minutes left!
Gun, let's go!
Don't you think you agree too fast?
Why not? Hurry up!
Hurry!
Uea!/ Huh?
Wanna join?
Urr...
Wait! I was just being polite.
I know you wouldn't come. Let's go!
King!
Wanna go?
Ha?
You don't have to go. Let's go!
Hey, hey!
What else?/ I forget something.
Good bye./ Good bye.
Speed up, we're late!
You can go first, Uea. Don't wait for me.
Um.
Er.
So...
I'm leaving.
Yes.
Hi./ Pock!?
All your friends have already left, huh?
No one can protects you from now on!
We already broke up!
Can you get the f*ck out of my life?!
I told ya. I won't break up with you!
But I have a new boyfriend!
Oh, really? Where is he, then?
Help!
Pock!
Keep resisting!
Happy birthday!
It's your birthday gift!
Why are we unable to make this an overseas trip?
We can have fun everywhere, though.
Because we have each other.
Uea! You came.
I was waiting for you.
Can you stop doing this to me?/ We need to talk.
Are you such a player?/ Player?
Mom! Mom!
Take this! Is one man not enough for you?!
[You and me are just chilling]
[but I'm thinking much more than that]
[I don't wanna be your friend]
[Can we change into a boyfriend?]
[Am I just a home only when you feel alone?]
[Are we just friend no matter how much I love you?]
[I think I has crossed the line]
[You and me are just chilling]
[but I'm thinking much more than that]
[I don't wanna be your friend]
[Can we change into a boyfriend?]
[Am I just a home only when you feel alone?]
[Are we just friend no matter how much I love you?]
[I think I has crossed the line]