Episode 28
We are on the bottom.
I feel almost suffocated.
We should be there soon.
I'm afraid of heat.
There's a black hole ahead.
Elder Huaxiong told me about the danger.
I told you guys.
We must be careful when we go in.
Be careful.
Especially you.
Don't touch things you shouldn't touch.
No, Tianzhen.
You're hurting my feelings.
I...
You're that kind of person.
No, Brother, you tell me.
Am I that kind of person?
Brother.
Look, Brother is angry.
It's all because of you.
Stop talking nonsense.
Just go.
I...
No, I...
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
If that's so...
Come on.
Don't you know we've become the first one who has been caught from this.
Go and look for the security guards.
Wait.
Fire!
It's so real.
I have a feeling that this place is unusual.
The closer you get, the more painful it gets.
We must hurry and find it.
Otherwise, there will be danger.
I'm afraid that I can't protect you.
It's okay.
As long as there are seven fairies, it's fine.
This must be a underground mine with a magnet.
The closer we get, the more people's impression will be.
Later, we'll try not to touch the east wall here.
It's okay.
I'll lead the way.
Seven fairies, I'm coming.
Hey!
Thank you, everyone.
I think I'm dizzy.
Everyone, be careful.
Don't look at the east wall.
We can't recover for long.
We have to climb like the elders.
Then we can move forward.
I'm hallucinating.
Xiao Ge has a phone.
Xiao Ge,
scan the code and add a WeChat.
I don't have a WeChat.
Xiao Ge,
then leave me a phone number.
I have yours.
Everyone, pay attention.
Think about our goal.
Yes.
Seven fairies, let's go.
Let's go.
Come on.
Oh!
This is too hard to find.
We've climbed for a long time.
I feel like
we've been around a few times.
I can't feel
where the line of the east wall is.
Where is it?
I'm going crazy
around this second needle.
Is it a hallucination?
I have to kneel.
Nonsense.
It's because
the magnetic field here
is already strong to a certain extent.
The time and gravity
are already twisted to a certain extent.
How about
we go back first?
It's not a good idea
to find such a blind place.
Next time,
we'll choose a direction
by ourselves.
We'll keep looking.
We can find it.
Tianzhen, can this hole
change at will?
It can get bigger or smaller.
How many holes have we turned?
I think I've been through 18 holes.
We don't have the ability to sense it.
I don't know either.
The most horrible thing is
we've been climbing for so long.
Do you feel hungry?
Yes.
I'm full.
Or else,
let's go back.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm too heavy. Let's go.
It's really been two hours.
I feel like we've been here
for a long time.
It's really
recovered.
It's been so little time.
It's gone.
No.
I really don't believe it.
I'm so tired.
I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
Fatty, don't sleep.
I want to vomit.
You...
Let's stop.
Don't waste your energy
on this.
Little guy, do you have any other ways?
For example,
blow up this hole.
I've tried the black crystal.
The black crystal is very hard.
Then we have to
lie down like this?
I feel like
we've been here
for a month.
We've been lost for a long time.
We'll really get lost here.
What?
What are you two doing on the ground?
I've been climbing.
Wu Xie, follow me.
I'm coming in.
So this is how you get out.
I've got the power.
Look.
What is this?
Don't follow...
The magic of qin.
Okay.
This is the magic of Elder Kuaxiong's last life.
I don't know why,
the closer I get to him,
the more painful I feel.
The qin tree's qin
has a lot of radioactive substances.
So this is why
it has the magic of bewitching people.
It bewitches you.
The same goes for the qin tree's magic.
So when Elder Kuaxiong
took it as his priest,
everyone bowed down
and saw the magic.
And in the cave,
all our illusions
and the lost sense
were influenced by it.
And on the wall of the cave,
the high-precision black crystal
formed a light reflection.
It had a big impact on us.
Look at that.
Fatty.
I told you not to...
What is this?
Salt.
It's indeed a hallucination.
I feel like I'm in a real place.
Fatty,
you've got the mechanism.
I told you not to take those things.
This is the mechanism
I set up in the sea.
Let's go.
It's only been half an hour.
Hurry.
Brother.
Isn't he in front of us?
Where did he go?
Brother.
Why did he leave
in the dark?
He must have his own
secret.
Yes, yes, yes.
He has a phone problem.
Call him.
I'll go.
It's going to be a scam.
I know.
What's the point of giving it to the country?
The words on it
probably mean
Snow Mountain.
Where is the Holy Land?
There's no Snow Mountain in the west.
Snow Mountain in Kunlun.
Snow Mountain.
What does it have to do
with the Snow Mountain in Yunding?
It's okay.
This is a place
where culture is originated.
Right?
That's the origin of Chinese mythology.
Yes, yes, yes. You know.
Okay.
Come.
Fatty.
Look.
Is the glow in the wali
a piece of egg?
I know.
This is a piece of bomb
from the K-80 series.
It's an airplane bomb.
You said it was an American bomb.
Are you crazy?
It was a common airplane bomb.
Although they export it to
different countries,
it's a waste.
It wasn't an earthquake.
What do you mean?
It was caused by humans.
They targeted here.
We have to go back and tell the villagers.
Oh my god.
What's wrong?
What should we do?
Let's go.
Over there.
Wait.
It's too late. Let's go.
Hurry.
Stop.
Don't run.
Don't.
It's a misunderstanding.
What's wrong?
I didn't hurt Kun Da.
Tell me.
I don't want to
have an accident.
Your girlfriend?
Ning?
What's going on?
Give us one.
What do you want?
We want one too.
Give us five.
Run.
No.
This is for you.
What's that look?
I just didn't think you would
return it to me.
Thank you.
What did you say?
Nothing.
You returned everything to me.
I'll treat you to a meal.
I just saved your life.
You should treat me to a meal.
You're not leaving?
If you stay, I won't cook.
I can only treat you to instant noodles.
Okay.
Sir.
Ning,
looks like your trick
didn't work on Wu Xie.
Now let me do the honor.
Hello, Wu Xie.
I'm happy to see you are back
safely.
Are you kidding me?
Wu Xie, I really
want to be honest with you today.
Wu San Xing is not worth my trust anymore.
All these years,
my cooperation with him
has been very difficult.
He not only cooperates with me,
but also with others.
He can betray his friends,
and also betray his family.
Stop.
Don't say that.
You just want me to deal with Wu San Xing.
But I'm not interested in what you guys are doing now.
I'm not interested in him either.
You can do whatever you want.
Your attitude
surprised me.
We've been fighting for so many years.
You've helped me a lot.
I'm grateful to you.
That's why I asked Ning
to save you.
This time is different from the past.
Your uncle San Xing has been in trouble.
He needs you more than ever.
He doesn't want you
to get involved in our business.
But this time is different.
You...
He will invite you to go to the Cloud Sky Palace.
But he can hurt you once.
He won't hurt you again.
If you cooperate with us,
at least you can be sure
that he won't abandon you.
Don't refuse him.
Think about it carefully.
I'll be waiting for your answer.
You can go now.
No, I...
Do you think it's time to explain?
I'm leaving.
I'm not eating take-out.
I heard it.
You don't believe them, do you?
I'm stupid.
Your girlfriend will be angry.
Hello?
What are you doing, little boy?
Come here.
Who?
Where are you?
Where else can I be?
Come here, come to Xingxing House.
What did he say?
What are you doing?
Go to Xingxing House.
Now?
Let's go.
Master Hua, the signal was not working
since we arrived at Qiu De Gou's camp yesterday.
Sorry for not hoping in a veryд 1 month ago, Lmeri Top9 player who also played just before signing for this year's player competition.
I know you hate me.
Tell me, what's the matter?
I don't have much money.
My nephew, in Guizhou...
Don't mention Guizhou.
If I were you, I would never mention Guizhou.
You don't care about me anymore, do you?
What's wrong?
What else do you need from me?
How can you talk to your uncle?
Wu Xie, you're an adult.
Don't be a child.
Wu Xie, don't be a child.
Look, the boy.
He got it a few days ago.
How delicate.
I was wondering,
such a delicate thing is ruined by someone else.
Who?
My nephew.
Here, don't be shy.
Don't be shy.
My nephew,
about the Zhang Junfa,
I told you not to mention it.
It's too innocent.
Wu Xie.
Uncle San,
actually, I'm happy that you asked me to come.
I thought,
no matter what, you have to tell me something.
Even if it's something you made up,
you have to tell me the truth.
Actually, I thought I was brought up by you.
I know you best.
Yes, although I have to tell you the truth,
I'm not a child.
Yes, although you lie to me about trivial things,
I believe you.
I believe those strangers.
At least you won't hurt me.
But I was wrong.
My nephew,
I'm sorry for some things in the study.
Just scold me a little bit.
Just get angry.
Uncle San,
you said you know me best.
You know I hate the tricks of fake Yanping.
You even use such Yanping to fool me.
What do you want to do?
I'm just kidding.
I want to see your real skills.
Or I'll give you the heirloom.
I'll leave it to you.
Look.
This is real.
Where did you get it?
I used a few ancient tombstones
to exchange it for the Qiu De Kao.
You suddenly become a psycho
or the Qiu De Kao became a fool?
What are you talking about?
The Qiu De Kao is a fake.
He never does business with the real money.
That's just your deal.
There's something I don't know.
Don't be too stubborn.
It's not good.
Uncle San.
There's been a lot of things
that happened to me recently.
I spent a lot of time looking for you.
I wanted to know where you were.
I wanted to know what you were doing.
But I couldn't find the answer.
You're always my uncle.
Am I still your nephew?
Of course you're my nephew.
You're my nephew.
Why don't you give me the heirloom?
I'll give it to you.
Don't worry.
You called me here
just to give me the Uncle Zhang Guo.
Just to give you the Uncle Zhang Guo.
Then you're not afraid
that I'll find out what tomb I'm going to.
I'm not done yet.
I told you.
You're my nephew.
My nephew.
It's not over yet.
Besides,
the water is so deep
and it's dangerous.
I'm afraid you'll get into trouble because I love you.
Now that you're grown up,
you don't listen to me.
Fine.
You're idle.
What?
Help me?
You want me to help you?
You're still a soldier.
Kid, I'm telling you.
You need to cherish something.
You and your uncle go to the Cloud Sky Palace.
You can rest assured in Uncle Zhang Guo's heart.
Don't want to help Uncle Zhang Guo?
Fine.
Uncle Zhang Guo,
if you want me to go,
I'll go.
Let's go.
Fatty.
You want me to help you?
You're still a soldier.
Kid, I'm telling you.
You need to cherish something.
You and your uncle go to the Cloud Sky Palace.
You can rest assured in Uncle Zhang Guo's heart.
Uncle Zhang Guo.
It's ready.
Try it.
This wine is soft.
It's very refreshing.
It's like seeing a person.
It's a new product.
Try it.
Uncle Zhang Guo,
you asked me to come today
just for the sake of wine, right?
Yuchen,
I asked you to come to ask you for a favor.
Can you lend me your copper fish?
I know.
It has a great relationship with the Cloud Sky Palace.
You're old.
The copper fish is in my hand.
You're a little bit more mature.
How is it?
Uncle Zhang Guo,
I should teach you like this.
Yes.
I'm teaching you this time
for Wu Xie's sake.
I hope we don't break our relationship.
Don't mention this
in the end.
I know who you're working with.
I also know how true
and false your words were.
It's strange.
We're all cousins.
You and my uncle
have different personalities.
Why are you so different?
Your tone
sounds like a man of two words.
What do you mean?
You're so young.
If your father knew
you were so successful,
you still couldn't trust your uncle.
How could I trust you?
You thief.
You're so mean.
I'm very sad.
Master Hua, the old house is broken.
The security officer has agreed to disappear.
They're trapped by Wu San Xing.
Master Hua, the surveillance cameras have been transferred.
It's been transferred to your computer.
The footage taken by the security camera
in the study corridor 2
is the mysterious A-S.
The security camera
is in the study corridor 2.
Wu Shi speaks on the phone.
Master Hua asks him
if he can help Wu concerning his thin brother's nature program.
Wu silly,
can you help me now?
I feel think about what to do,
which is the right one and the right one.
Along with the assistance from uncle
no two went to the wrong place.
Wu Shi sent him a to-do list.
He built up a very long list,
which may involve years of FT,
so medios may help him.
He asked me to go to the Sky Palace with him.
You agreed?
No matter what, he's my third uncle.
Wu Xie, if you need me, I can go with you.
It has nothing to do with you.
Okay.
Since you've decided, I support you.
But it's too dangerous for you to go alone.
I'm worried that you'll be in danger.
How about this?
I'll ask Jia Sha to give you a tracker.
You can wear it.
If there's any danger, I'll find you as soon as possible.
Thank you.
Really.
Wu Xie, let's talk.
There's nothing to talk about.
I have something important to do today.
This is very important to you.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
Wu Xie, don't misunderstand.
I gave you this because I don't believe in Jason.
I don't want to see what happened in the tomb happen again.
Through this, we can communicate with each other.
For example, I can tell you in time what Jason did.
Here.
Here you can shoot a video and then send it in time.
You can take a video of what happened inside the Sky Palace.
If you don't want to take a video, I can't help it.
But in fact, we can't hurt you at all.
Because you've always been on guard against us.
But those you've always believed in,
may not be so reliable.
How can you go to guard against them hurting you?
It's not a bad thing to leave a way for yourself.
I'm sorry.
So you're so good-mouthed.
If you think I'm right,
that's because you've thought about it for a long time.
But you dare not admit it.
You agree with my opinion?
I'll think about it.
Believe it or not,
I'm not here because Mr. Koudelka asked me to.
I'm here on behalf of my opinion.
I hope you can understand.
I understand.
I'm leaving.
Come on, eat something.
Drink some water.
Why are you looking at me?
What are you doing?
Thank you.
Why are you thanking me?
You followed me without saying anything
when I said I was coming to Cloud Sky Palace.
Isn't it normal?
What if I come here and there's something good?
Okay, okay, let's be serious.
How can you be so sure that Cloud Sky Palace is on Mount Changbai?
Your third uncle told you?
Third uncle has his purpose.
I don't know what it is.
But I've found this when I went back to Beijing.
There's always a painting on my grandpa's notebook.
Because there's no explanation,
I don't know what he's drawing.
Then I found it by accident.
Isn't this Longmai?
Through the night, through the five meters
I got an answer in the darkness
The