gonna cook
exactly chocolate
I'm sorry, I'm not sure if I can help you.
The Ghost's Guard?
The long-living street in front of the East Street.
Go!
We're lost!
13th Master,
You better jump over!
I'll cover you!
Hurry!
13th Master, I'm running out of bullets!
I'm running out of bullets!
Jump!
Hurry!
Send Hua out.
Little Third Master!
Hurry and answer me!
Little Third Master, Wu Xie!
Where are you, Little Third Master?
Where are you, Wu Xie?
Little Third Master...
Little Third Master has fallen.
Little Third Master,
I'll save you!
You can't go down!
This kind of lowly man...
Little Third Master,
I'm sorry!
You can't go down!
Pan Zi!
Xuan Zi,
Where is Little Third Master?
You must know where he is!
I don't know!
Little Third Master told me to tell Wu Xie.
Wu Xie will take us to him.
Little Third Master...
Little Third Master!
Come over here.
Little Third Master...
It's not going well...
Little Third Master
It's not good...
Little Third Master,
I'm leaving.
Third Master.
Run!
You can't get through this.
Hold on!
Light the fire!
Run!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Come on.
Third Master!
Help!
Run!
Xiao Ge.
Why are you here?
We have to leave this place quickly.
Have you thought out what your Third Uncle said to you?
The place where Xuan Wu died.
Third Brother.
In this world,
there is no such place.
If someone is buried in such a place,
his descendants will die.
Many tragic things will happen to him.
It won't be strange.
This is the worst feng shui in the world.
It's all gathered together.
Of course,
this feng shui treasure
is the same as the nine dragon petals.
Moreover, this is the East and West Imperial Tomb.
How can the feng shui be different from the place where the emperor was buried?
Feng shui is for people.
What if King Wan Nu is not a person?
How can King Wan Nu not be a person?
When we came here,
the totems,
paintings,
and the snake-eye-catching copper fish of Chen Ping A Si were all recorded.
King Wan Nu is not a person.
The information on the copper fish is incomplete.
If we can get all the snake-eye-catching copper fish back,
maybe we can figure it out.
But,
to put it another way,
since you are telling me this in this way,
it's very likely that
if you tell me this directly,
the outsiders will not understand it.
If that's the case,
we can't understand it in the way we want.
So,
only you can understand what I'm trying to say.
This is the special way you communicate with each other.
I don't know.
I don't understand.
Don't worry.
Take your time.
Xiao Ge,
let's go further.
Let's go.
The grave is red.
I wonder where their destination is.
I don't know.
King Wan Nu,
these people
are the people who brought him down.
This is the place of Xuan Wu Ju.
He said that as long as you tell me this,
you will know where the entrance is.
A month ago,
San Shu knew where the entrance of the underground palace was.
It's impossible.
My wrong, wrong, wrong!
Who are you?
Tell me,
who am I?
Xie Lian.
Lian Huan.
In this world,
only one person can harm you.
That is me,
your San Shu.
Think about it.
Who loves you the most since childhood?
It's me, your San Shu.
Then you guys go first.
You,
follow me back.
Be careful.
Who shot just now?
Me.
Me?
And me.
Then you three stay here.
The others, leave here.
Why?
Hurry up, we don't have time.
Okay.
This is not my idea.
It's your San Shu's idea.
San Shu?
You are also San Shu's person.
Don't ask so much.
When the time comes, I'll take you to see San Shu.
You guys ask yourself.
Xiao Ge,
do you think that Shun Zi
really deliberately separated us?
He pretended to be a fool all the way.
No one cares about him.
He could have told me
about San Shu secretly.
Why did he deliberately separate us?
Also,
why did Si A Gong
ask Shun Zi to go back with you?
Why not ask Hua He Shang
to be his own person?
Could it be
he left us
to spy on me and Fatty Wang?
I don't know.
Wait a minute.
Did you lose it?
Maybe.
Take a break.
Take a breath.
This route is a bit strange.
Hua Ye,
is there anything wrong?
By the way, Hua Ye,
our next schedule
is like this.
After handling this,
we need to hurry back to Chang Sha.
This way, we can attend
the night's
singing and dancing party.
Secondly,
we have already told Miss Xiu Xiu
about this.
She has said she understands.
Also,
the last thing is about
the picture of the tomb.
We blacked in
the database of the Chude Gou
and confirmed that the picture is real.
Jia Sha,
Hua Ye,
sometimes
I am too stubborn.
Hua Ye,
look.
The signal
did disappear in this position.
It is indeed here.
Hua Ye,
do you think
this is the place
that Chude Gou
has deliberately arranged?
Then why did he
bring us here?
What is his purpose?
He is not hiding anything.
He is obviously
giving us a show.
Let's go.
Hua Ye,
the door is not locked.
Could there be an ambush?
It seems that
Qiu Dao Kao is very confident
about his own foundation.
Let's go.
Hua Ye,
the door is locked.
Let's go.
Hua Ye,
the door is locked.
Xiao Kun,
where should we go?
Let's go and hide first.
Hua Ye,
I go and check this side.
the door of the study is open.
Let's go.
Mr. Hua, this is Mr. Wu's diary, right?
Looking at the handwriting, it's his.
His handwriting is not a few people's.
This is Mr. Wu's diary, learning from his grandfather.
He also wrote a book.
Mr. Wu's diary
Mr. Hua, this must be the trap of Qiu Dekou.
You...
If she's alive, we have to leave now.
Mr. Wu's diary
Rest well.
Drink some water first.
Xiao Ge.
What is this place?
This is a dirt building.
This building is probably where the engineers of the Heavenly Palace used to rest.
It's just a temporary shelter from the wind and sand.
Besides, we don't have much food.
Xiao Ge.
Then why should we let those people go?
Is there any shelter?
You're walking fast.
Fortunately, we're lucky.
After we fell down,
those people didn't chase us anymore.
Don't worry.
We know where the curse is.
Let's replenish our energy first.
Let's rest quickly.
Don't be afraid.
Those people are hiding and running away.
Don't think about it.
Rest quickly.
We still have a long way to go.
Xiao Ge.
It's good that I met you.
Otherwise,
I don't know how long I have to endure alone.
What about others?
Others...
They all ran away.
What about Fatty?
He can't not follow you.
Xiao Ge.
Why is this still a broken bridge?
I'm so heavy.
You can still lift me up?
Xiao Ge.
What's wrong?
Do you feel better?
I just don't know if those people will come back.
I don't think so.
The wind and sand here will disturb their senses.
Xiao Ge.
We've been waiting for you.
It's not a big deal.
Xiao Ge.
Xiao Ge, I'm tired.
I'm tired.
I see that you have a little bit of my life.
I was taken by that big bird.
It's not that I want to go back to you.
Do you know that?
So I can't follow your surname.
My surname is Wang.
Fatty Wu.
You...
Didn't I tell you?
What's wrong with you?
You...
Enough.
Stop it. Hurry up.
What?
Eat or not?
Fatty Wu.
I'm embarrassing you, right?
Come on, Xiao Ge.
Eat something first.
You see, Xiao Ge is still the one who is in charge.
I tell you, this is the internal conflict of the people.
It's not a conflict between the enemy and me.
You know that, right?
Enough.
When Wu Xie recovers tomorrow,
we will go to meet everyone.
We can't leave with the wound.
Everything is ruined.
Listen to Xiao Ge.
You're awake, right?
Get out of my way.
I'm going to sleep.
Fatty Wu.
Xiao Ge, look at him.
This...
Anyway, I don't change my surname.
My surname is Wang.
I don't change my surname because I don't want to change my name.
Wang Fatty.
My surname is Wu.
How tiring is Wu?
So many things happened between you and your family.
I have to take care of it.
If Wu San Xing comes,
my third uncle...
is too troublesome.
Wang Fatty.
Come here.
Shao Zi Guan.
The things in here
can only be used to make us
be able to get out of the archaeology room.
It's not a good place.
The things in here
can only be used to make us
be able to get out of the archaeology room.
It's not a good place.
It's the name of the archaeologist.
No matter how much you say,
it can't change our origin.
Third Uncle.
What era is this?
Do you still expect to live on your own?
It's time to change your mind.
Look at your boss.
An underground engineer.
He's so clean.
How much respect does he have?
How can he be so useless?
You're so useless.
You come or I come?
Fine, I'll come.
I'm good at left hand anyway.
If my right hand is cut,
it won't affect my chopsticks.
Lian Hua.
Xie Lian Hua.
Third Uncle.
Who is it?
Come out quickly!
Third Uncle.
Why did you kill me?
You want my life?
I treat you as my brother.
What should I do?
We can only live for one.
Who are you?
What's wrong?
Only you can understand what your Third Uncle designed.
This is a special way for you to communicate.
Xie...
You had a nightmare again?
I probably know what that last sentence meant.
What does it mean?
Then...
Yes.
What does it mean?
Let's wait until I'm sure.
I'm sorry.
Come, Ting Ting.
Drink some water.
Drink some water and then we'll leave.
I told you to drink water.
No need.
If you think there's nothing wrong,
let's go.
There's still a long way to go before the tower.
I'm telling you, you blind man.
If it weren't for the birds,
I wouldn't have followed you.
Come on.
These people, if they all go to the museum,
can they cause a stir?
This is the horse-drawn dragon in the burial pit.
It's usually used to welcome the king
or the team on a trip.
But, Brother Yang, this kind of burial pit
usually only appears in underground caves
or in the burial pit.
How could they go there?
They're not going to die.
They're going to die.
The king of the ten thousand farmers
is going to die.
If the king of the ten thousand farmers
sees this place,
he will be killed by the super family.
Tianzhen,
this is the clothing of the Eastern Xia people
in the murals.
Don't just do it.
These things are weird.
Maybe there's something wrong with them.
They can still live.
Stone man,
you can't just leave.
Stone man.
These people
should have been in the river for a long time.
Their faces are blurred.
It's also because they were soaked in water for a long time
and were washed away by the river.
What is that?
The craftsmen were lazy.
They didn't do well, so they buried them in the river.
I don't think so.
Have you ever seen someone throw garbage
so fairly?
Did you notice that
all the craftsmen were going in the same direction?
It's like they were in the army.
They were all going in the direction
of the king of the ten thousand farmers.
They were all substitutes for the living.
epidemic
The wind blows in the wind
The wind of loneliness
How can I resist the wind?
I pass through the night
I find the answer in the darkness
The scenery of time is looking at the flowers blooming
The unwavering faith is following the wind
The wind blows in the wind
I forget how to resist the wind
I pass through the night
I find the answer in the darkness
The scenery of time is looking at the flowers blooming
The unwavering faith is following the wind
The End