It's good to have someone to talk to.
I don't want to think too much.
What?
Are you still upset
about what happened today.
Although I didn't mean it,
I always feel
I feel sorry for her.
I know you didn't mean it.
But they don't think so.
I still think it's good to be a demon.
Being a demon?
It's always me.
I can be happy.
But being a human is different.
You have to be careful with your words and actions.
I think you've improved a lot.
Looks like your books
are worth reading.
Maybe.
I didn't think like that before.
You...
Why are you staring at me?
I just think
today.
Really?
What?
Am I
very pretty today, right?
Yes.
Let me show you something.
Do you know who this is?
She is the embarrassment of the four beauties.
Floral Immortal, Lady Yang.
Look at her necklace.
What do you think?
Is it nice?
Yes.
Look again.
Who is this?
This is the closing moon of the four beauties.
Diaochan.
Look at her necklace.
Her necklace
is exactly the same as Lady Yang's.
That's right.
You should know this.
This is the sunken fish of the four beauties.
Beauty.
Look again.
the necklace she's wearing.
I know.
She wore the same one with the first two.
Right.
So?
you think
I don't look good wearing this necklace?
Or am I not as pretty as them?
You're prettier than them.
But
this necklace doesn't match you.
But you gave me this necklace.
I'm the first young master of Lincheng City.
How can I always be controlled
like you?
So today,
a necklace today.
A necklace that suits you.
You want to give me a necklace?
Yes.
For me?
Of course.
Do you have something
to ask me?
What can I ask you for?
Then why did you give me the necklace?
I happened to see this necklace
on the street today.
I think it suits you well.
Try it on.
Really
Really.
What do you think?
Do I look good?
Yes.
Very nice.
Then leave this to me too.
I can wear these two.
This one doesn't match you.
And it's old.
I should have thrown it away long ago.
Why did you throw it away?
I bought it with money.
What a pity.
This necklace doesn't match you.
is worthless.
I should have thrown it away long ago.
You look good in this.
You look better than them.
It's getting late.
Go back and rest.
Really?
They're all pretty.
Lady Yang.
Diaochan.
After applying it,
it will definitely make you unique.
I'll take a look.
Miss, what would you like?
Waiter.
I want an osmanthus-flavored fragrance powder.
Okay.
Smell it.
Miss,
We just bought
new lipstick.
It suits you very well.
Try it.
I'm the most beautiful woman in the world.
Who is the most beautiful woman in the world?
Who?
I am the most beautiful woman
in the world.
Who dares to compete with me?
I...
the most beautiful woman
in the world.
How is it, Xu?
I didn't expect
to recover so quickly.
So,
my body
completely recovered.
Great.
Thank you, Brother Xu.
In this way,
my wish
my years of wish.
I can also make my mother
rest assured.
I can finally return the Internal Dan
to Lin.
I'll be free.
What's wrong, Xu?
Aren't you happy
for me?
Of course.
Then why do you look like that?
You may not
return the Internal Dan to Lin.
What?
No way.
Why?
The Internal Dan has completely integrated
into your body.
in your body.
So you mean
the Internal Dan
in my body.
Don't worry.
Cheng,
do you trust me?
Of course I do.
Just trust me.
I'll find a way to solve the problem.
But
I need some time.
Xu,
I have another question.
Go ahead.
I asked Shrimp
I asked Shrimp to find a master
to find a master.
Because at that time,
about Lin.
So I’m afraid
because of the Internal Dan.
so I tried to protect her.
But recently, Lin
is getting weaker.
Is it because of this necklace?
No wonder she found you.
What?
Nothing.
This is...
that sucks blood.
Luckily you found it in time.
Otherwise, it would be bad for Lin.
Leave this to me.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you, Xu.
Hurry up.
Wait for me.
Hurry up. We're going to be late.
Yes.
Sorry.
Sir is here.
Coming.
Hello, sir.
The winner of this year's kite festival
has been chosen.
I hope all the students
can keep up the good work.
No matter what the result is,
no matter what the result is.
The winner of the paper kite festival is
Hong Li.
Hongli.
You're the winner.
I...
Why me?
Thank you, sir.
Okay.
Congratulations.
Miao'er.
Where is Wanwan?
Didn’t you say
you bought yesterday?
I wanted to win the first place
to make a wish.
You're a demon.
What wish do you have?
Do you want me to marry you?
You are
in yourself.
We fairies
make a wish?
Why are you laughing?
Cheng Lin.
Cheng... Cheng Lin.
Master.
I need to talk to Lin.
Can we talk in private?
This is for you.
You deserve it.
This...
I've
with Mr. Yu.
I will give you
in a few days.
Why?
Your paper mandarin duck.
If it wasn't broken by accident,
it would have been the best.
By the way,
I have another request.
I want you to help me
ask Zhang Wanwan out.
Ask Zhang Wanwan out?
Well,
I like her.
But I feel embarrassed.
You like Zhang Wanwan.
Okay.
I'll help you.
Really?
I'll go back and wait for your good news.
Thank you.
This is love.
I must help him.
You're amazing.
Amazing!
Our dragon is flying!
The dragon is flying.
Mr. Cheng, are you drinking tea?
Miss Zhou.
It’s time to enjoy tea.
But the flower hall
in this floral hall.
for our students.
So,
I usually carry it with me.
If you don't mind,
I would like to invite you
to taste it with me.
Thank you, Miss Zhou.
I have something important to do.
I’m leaving.
Mr. Cheng.
The schedule made me
lose face in front of everyone.
I just want to invite you
to enjoy tea and flowers with me.
as compensation.
OK?
Mr. Cheng.
Have some tea.
Thank you.
Mr. Cheng.
Today,
I want to play
for you.
Young Master, what do you think?
Go back.
Let’s go.
Mr. Cheng, have some tea.
Okay.
You're right.
The fruit tastes terrible.
Mr. Cheng.
Go after him.
Why don't you go after him?
Don't you like him?
You should get him if you like him.
Idiot.
Zhang Wanwan.
How could you talk to Jung-yeon like that?
Shut up!
You have no idea
when I listen to you.
Wanwan.
What’s wrong?
Zhang Wanwan.
What are you doing?
Jung-yeon, are you okay?
Do you know
Only when you become beautiful
can get
what you want.
I'm the most beautiful woman
in the world.
7OPWORKS
Sheng Ga He