Stop drinking.
Who won the sword battle today?
Do you want to know?
It's a secret I can't tell you.
So you're all here.
I've been looking for you.
It's been a few days.
You've grown taller, Yoko.
Who are you calling Xiaoye?
I'm a nine-tailed Phoenix Fairy.
How can I be laughed at by you all the time?
Look at Jun Xu.
He never laughed at me.
By the way,
I found
a good place in the mortal world.
Let's go together.
Okay.
Sure.
Let’s go, Yuli.
Look.
Isn't this place
for training?
I didn't expect
there would be such a cave in the mortal world.
How did you find out?
Don't you know who I am?
I'm Fengxian.
What's so great about Fengxian?
I'm the Crown Prince.
Then is Jun Xu or Fairy Crane?
Maintain the balance of the Three Realms.
are all immortals.
What's wrong?
Am I wrong?
Right.
It's too quiet here.
Jun Xu.
How about we play a game of Go?
What about Shamo?
You guys go play Go.
I'll go practice the piano.
You should practice
you should practice.
Yuli.
Let’s go practice.
No.
You guys go ahead.
I have something to do. I'll get going.
Could it be...
we were immortals in the last life?
Cheng Qi is the dragon's son.
and Fairy Crane.
And I...
Fengxian.
Is the confidant you just mentioned
also a woman?
You haven't seen each other for a long time?
Where is she now?
She...
is far away
is right in front of me.
Tell me.
What did you do to her?
I entrusted her to you.
How could you bully her?
Lin.
Is the one Jun Xu likes
is me?
Lin.
What are you doing here?
We've been looking for you.
We thought you were lost.
Miss Lin,
Did you sleep well last night?
Yes.
That's good.
I prepared some food.
Let's eat together.
No, it's okay.
We're leaving.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Where are you going?
I'm starving.
Stop talking.
Just come with me.
Mr. Xu
is kind.
Home is better.
The air is nice and quiet.
Right
Sorry, succulent meat.
I made you suffer.
It's okay.
But why
end up like this?
I don't know.
I'm so confused right now.
What is it?
Don't worry.
Even if the whole world
abandoned you,
I still have succulent meat.
I will always be with you.
But Lin,
what are we eating tonight?
Don’t worry.
As long as I have a bite,
I won’t
I won't let you eat more meat.
Okay.
Shrimp, Xie.
Eldest Young Master.
Get me a horse.
I need to go to the temple.
No, no.
Although Miss Lin abandoned you,
and left you,
you don't need to be a monk.
That's right.
Young Master.
There are plenty of flowers in the world.
Why did you find that demon?
There aren't many.
And it has a bad reputation.
Who said I'm going to become a monk?
Lin said
she lived in a temple
living in the same temple.
So I must find her
and make it clear to her.
You have no idea
how important she is to me.
Remember to bring more money.
If she doesn't want to
come back with us,
we can't let her
suffer from hunger outside.
Don't just stand there. Let's go.
You know what?
I heard that
on the engagement day,
on the engagement day
in the pavilion.
Yes.
Rumors are spreading in the mansion.
I also heard that woman
the daughter of Zhou Mang, Minister of Personnel.
Zhou Jing Yan.
This young master
looks aloof,
I didn't expect you to be such a player.
You're right.
But why do I feel that
Young Master and the daughter of the Zhou family
are more suitable.
Young master.
Let's go.
Our young master is a loyal man.
Why should they
comment?
You talk too much.
Young master.
I said it wrong.
Lin.
You are the best.
With our condition,
we can eat and drink.
Here, try my soup.
I told you.
I'm here.
you'll have a lot of meat.
I think
Maybe it's going to rain.
Looks like the rain is heavy
Look at this door, succulent meat.
Okay.
Don't sleep tonight.
Mine.
Forget about the meat. The door is important.
It's raining so heavily.
I wonder how Lin is doing.
Shrimp, Xie.
Hurry up.
Yes, Young Master.
Xie, faster!
What happened?
Young Master.
The wheels are stuck in the mud.
Shrimp
Push harder.
I've tried my best.
Eldest Young Master.
Why are you down?
It's raining heavily.
in such a heavy rain.
How can I
to my parents?
But the carriage
can't get out even if it's stuck here.
It's not far ahead.
Let's walk.
Young Master.
This...
Forget about the carriage. Let's go.
I can't live anymore.
You can't enter Cheng Mansion.
I can't go to Jun Xu's place either.
I must
die in this shabby temple tonight.
Do you think
is Cheng Qi really that kind of person?
What kind of person?
Ungrateful.
A playboy.
Wait.
Is this how you use
Is this how you use it?
It doesn't matter.
I mean,
how could he be so ungrateful
and hurt you so much?
How would I know
Cheng Qi is?
I think
it must be Zhou Jing Yan.
Look at her
when she flatters Cheng Qi.
is obviously problematic.
Tell me.
was it too dark that day?
Cheng Qi had poor eyesight
and drunk.
Maybe he mistook
Joo Jeong Yeon?
I mistook her for me.
What are you looking at?
Where is this place?
Why is it so dark?
Yes.
When it gets dark,
he has bad eyesight.
In that case,
I misunderstood him.
Did he really
as me?
So...
what he said that day
not to others.
but to me.
Am I right?
Yes.
You're always right.
I'm sleepy. I'm going to bed.
I haven't finished yet.
Succulent meat.
Can you chat with me for a while?
It's fine if you don't want to.
Why are you angry?
I wonder
Cheng Qi is doing now.
Young Master.
It should be here.
Lin.
Cheng Qi.
Young master.
Lin.
Cheng Qi.
You...
What's wrong?
It's my fault.
But it's not what you saw.
Trust me.
Cheng Qi.
You...
Lin.
Shrimp.
Call the doctor.
Okay.
Succulent meat, Xie.
Send someone to pick us up.
Okay.
Lin.
Wake up, Lin.
Doctor.
Is she all right?
The Frost Binding Form.
Weiyang is depressed.
the symptoms of cold and fever.
The three medicines I prescribed
can cure the evil
and expel the cold in her body.
I believe she will get better tomorrow.
Thank you, doctor.
You’re welcome.
I’ll leave now.
I'll take care of Lin tonight.
Go back and rest.
I think Lin
is lovesick.
If you're not here,
the patient won't recover.
If she wakes up at night,
don't provoke her.
You must talk to her.
Okay.
I’m leaving.
Sorry, Lin.
You only care about me.
But I made you
so much grievances.
I'm sorry.
Ao Qi.
If you hand over the divine memorandum today,
I can spare his life.
Shamo,
Live well.