When you were unconscious,
when you were unconscious just now.
I didn't care.
What do you care about now?
You are so troublesome.
Lin.
How is it?
Is he out?
I...
I tried my best.
What's wrong?
Your Internal Dan
is working in my body.
Otherwise,
why would I
chest tightness and shortness of breath.
I feel so bad.
No way.
My Internal Dan
is the spiritual object I've cultivated for a thousand years.
It's good for nothing.
Even a mortal can eat it.
Why do you feel so sad?
You lied to me again.
I'll tease you.
No, no.
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
Wake up.
You must be fine.
If anything happens to you,
I don't have Internal Dan to save you.
Wake up.
He's still breathing.
We can only wait until he wakes up tomorrow
when he wakes up tomorrow.
Why am I so unlucky?
Why am I so easily fooled
This is so easy to be fooled.
How dare you call yourself a demon?
Wake up.
Have you figured out a way?
If I can,
am I still here?
Are you not going to leave
you won't leave, right?
I have to wait until
return the Internal Dan to me.
You're dirty.
Go take a shower
and get changed.
Why should I do it when you tell me to?
Besides,
I didn't bring any clothes to change.
Only after I wash them
can you talk to me.
Besides,
I need some clothes
of servants.
What do you mean?
A servant?
I...
Have you heard?
There was a woman
a woman
woke up together this morning.
What?
Young Master slept with a woman.
Really?
Who told you that?
It doesn't matter.
As we all know,
for a long time.
Really?
Yes.
Maybe the Cheng family will have more children.
Who knows?
Maybe
this woman wants to enter the house.
Put up a notice right now.
Be sure to reward him.
We must find
who can catch demons.
Catch...
Hunting... Hunting demons?
Yes.
Go.
Okay.
Yes.
Let's go.
What?
Are you lost?
This is a forbidden place in the fairy realm.
How did you get in?
I'll take you out.
Don't bother.
Just tell me
how to get out here.
I can walk by myself.
Such a beautiful hand.
Why did you hide it?
What’s your name?
Yuli.
My Lord.
You must wake up.
Waiter, a pot of tea.
Okay.
Someone unveiled the ranking.
Hey.
It's been a morning.
No one can unveil the ranking.
Let's go back.
What are you talking about?
What if those two demons change
and harm Eldest Young Master?
A brave man will be rewarded.
Haven't you heard of it?
Stay here.
I'll do it again.
Yes.
Knock.
Please lead the way.
So cute.
Good boy.
Thank you.
It's been three thousand years
to be reincarnated.
His soul is still weak.
But now he has
in his heart.
was absorbed
by his mortal body.
Sir,
did you see anything?
If I'm not mistaken,
this lady
is not a mortal, right?
Your Internal Dan
should be in this young master's body.
Yes.
Can you tell me
how I should retrieve my Internal Dan?
Since the Internal Dan has entered
in your body,
It means the Internal Dan is fated to be with you.
Besides,
seems to have a heart disease.
The Internal Dan has protected him.
I sensed the Internal Dan.
has entered
your meridians
is repairing your body.
So...
the Internal Dan
can't be taken back for now.
What?
Her Internal Dan
is repairing my body.
What should I do now?
Now,
it depends on fate.
Fate?
So you mean
I have to wait until
fully recovered.
You're destined to meet him.
Please don't worry.
The Internal Dan
is repairing your body,
but it's not damaged.
Just wait for the right time
I can help you
return the Internal Dan.
Due to the guidance of the Internal Dan,
you may have some connection
with your senses.
So for the time being,
you two can't be separated.
What?
We can't be apart.
What if fate doesn't come?
he won't recover.
he won't be able to get the Internal Dan back.
That's right.
Why didn't I think of that?
Then I'll
to cultivate alchemy.
A living person?
Yes.
Kill him.
That's right.
It's like killing a chicken to extract an egg.
Then chop him into pieces
Marinate it
Enough.
One said he wanted to cut you open and get the elixir.
and said he would cut you into pieces to eat meat.
and drink your blood.
and stew your bones into soup.
These two demons
are really ruthless.
If it weren't for me,
I'm afraid the living things
have been eaten by them.
That's right.
We can't keep them.
Otherwise,
do something.
I'll stall them for a few days.
Go to the city
and find the most famous sorcerer
to see if there is any way
to subdue them.
Okay.
I'll be right there.
Please wait here.
I'll get the master.
Thank you.
What's the matter?
Are you Master Yuli?
Is your young master
by some demon?
No.
I didn't say anything.
How did you know?
Master.
Master!
I finally found the right person.
Do you have
to break it?
Don't worry.
Money is not a problem.
That's right.
It's her.
Master.
please
save my young master.
This is a demon hunter bell.
As long as you tie it
on that demon,
it can weaken her energy.
When her energy is gone,
I can subdue her.
You must keep it well.
and return it to me.
Thank you, Master Yuli.
Master.
I finally made it.
I’m back.
Yuli.