[The Tasty Florida
[Episode 8: Should I just follow my heart?]
His eyes... were always looking in your direction.
And I hated that.
But you know me.
I always go after what I want.
♫ Do you remember that melody ♫
♫ It came carried by the wind and stirred something in me ♫
♫  Whenever it might be, and wherever I might go,
I set forth on the road ♫
♫  To chance. A weary tread ♫
♫ A draft of a step. I am content, so good ♫
♫ Life is trick, but it’s not over ♫
♫ Please know that it is still worth living ♫
♫ Love is real and love’s forever ♫
From now on, if you want to cry or if you need someone to talk to...
don't drink alone. Just call me.
♫ All I need, anything really ♫
Yes, Chef!
♫ An "I love you". Just that is enough. Finally ♫
Something like this?
It's the first time you've really wanted something, isn't it?
I've liked him from the very beginning. I just didn't understand how important it was.
♫ Although I didn’t even know what I was feeling ♫
♫ You’ve always been in the same spot waiting for me  ♫
♫ You’re the only one for me. I need you ♫
♫ It's you. I want to tell you  ♫
But I think Eun Gyu is difficult to figure out.
I can't tell what he's thinking.
♫ You’ve been brightly smiling at me at all times ♫
♫ Now it’s my turn to be brave and come to you ♫
♫ You are here in every moment ♫
♫ My love, My all, My everything ♫
What are you doing here?
There was some dust... I'll leave now.
Why come here for that?
- I thought you'd like it.
- That's the problem.
You dummy. You didn't even know when I'd be coming here.
I knew you would come.
I'll be honest with you.
I like you.
♫ It’s you. So that our hearts that connected never change ♫
♫ I will always stay in the same spot and protect our bond  ♫
♫ Because you’re the only one for me. Because there’s only you ♫
♫ I promise I will love you every day like in the beginning ♫
♫ It's you ♫
From now on, I won't make your heart suffer. I'll tell you everything.
That's a promise! I've been telling you everything all this time.
I like it.
Like what?
The weather.
Just the weather?
I like it.
I like you.
♫ Oh baby, why are you crying so wearily?  ♫
♫ What is causing you trouble? ♫
♫ Look at that twinkling star up in the sky,
it is shining just like you  ♫
♫ Oh baby, you are so pretty  ♫
♫  Even if life deceives you.
Even when you are suffering too much alone ♫
♫ I am by your side, forever and ever ♫
Here's your "Rice noodles that keep you thin as noodles." Jjajang stir-fried rice noodles.
Enjoy your meal.
♫ You are a shining star yourself. You don’t have to try so hard ♫
Hey! You are making me feel sad for being single.
Don't do that here. Seriously, don't.
- So annoying.
- Stop that.
♫ I softly reach for your ear ♫
♫ You are a shining star yourself. You don’t have to try so hard ♫
♫ You are so dazzling, shining with a light unique to you ♫
I didn't have a dream.
But seeing people happy just by eating my cooking,
also makes me happy.
I could feel why you love the restaurant so much.
Now I think I can do well even without you.
I'm so proud.
So, you can go to Florida.
I know you miss your dad.
Hyung Ji Soo and I will look after Tasty Florida.
As for the position you'll leave vacant, it'll depend on how you behave.
But if someone more handsome shows up, we might fill the position.
Seo Hae Won.
You're like this again.
What? Say that again. You'll hire a new guy?
- Really?
- Yes.
[1 Year Later]
- Our last customer for today. Ms. Kim Seon Hyung?
- Yes, here.
Hello. What would you like to order?
Two jjajangmyeons, please.
Two jjajangnyeons? Please wait.
Channel Manager: angie_986
Coverpage: hhnike
♥♥ A big thanks to the Chief Segmenter: miss_rochester and the Segmenter: pilar_velasquez and a_hauth_238 ♥♥
♥♥ A big thanks to the Chief Editor and English Moderator: kakashiandme, to the General Editor: xialogne and the Translation Editor: emilyazel ♥♥
♥♥ A big thanks to the Korean-English Subbers: eighteen, yg_1301, yura12, callmesaena, 2sharonrose, icedteaaddict, kbabybear and yukhta_g13_117 ♥♥
♥♥ Thank you to all the other language Moderators and their team. ♥♥
♥♥ And at last a big thank you to the viewers, who watched and supported this series. ♥♥
Thank you. We hope to see you again.
Thank you.
Thank you. We'd love to see you again.
Thank you. Goodbye.
- We're finally done for the day.
- Finally done.
You didn't even mention you were coming back.
Were you happy all by yourself? In Florida.
♫ Oh baby, why are you crying so wearily?  ♫
♫ What is causing you trouble? ♫
♫ Look at that twinkling star up in the sky.
It is shining just like you ♫
♫ Oh baby, you are so pretty  ♫
♫ Even if life deceives you,
even when you are suffering too much alone ♫
♫ I am by your side, forever and ever ♫
♫ I want to kiss you on the lips ♫
♫ I softly reach for your ear ♫
♫ You are a shining star yourself. You don’t have to try so hard ♫
♫ You are so dazzling, shining with a light unique to you ♫
♫ I want to kiss you on the lips ♫
♫ I softly reach for your ear ♫
♫ You are a shining star yourself. You don’t have to try so hard ♫
♫ You are so dazzling, shining with a light unique to you ♫
[Tasty Florida]
Thank you all for your hard work today.
♫ See that blue ocean over there?
I want to jump in with a splash, Baby ♫
♫ I want something a bit more special.
I just want to feel new moments with you ♫
♫ Turn the volume up, Turn it up.
We can hear the sound of my heartbeat ♫
♫ Welcome to my Florida.
Our ocean slowly spreads out just for us ♫
[The Tasty Florida]