[English subtitles are available]
[Sunshine by My Side]
[Episode 10]
-Okay.
-There were people who thought
that I shouldn't get a divorce at 36,
but I did.
What's there to be afraid of?
Bing.
I'm here to fix your pipe.
Your ex-husband?
It sounds like him.
Don't make a sound.
Sit here and don't move.
I...
Coming.
I'm here to fix the pipe.
Did Liang Shanshan tell you?
It's telepathy.
I knew it that our...
No.
Your water pipe must be broken.
Your telepathy has a delay.
It's already fixed. Go back.
No, no, no.
Well...
The pendant light in the kitchen
keeps swaying.
Did you know that?
I'm afraid that some day
it might...
No.
It might fall and hit you.
What are you doing?
You're not letting me in.
Is someone home?
It's none of your business
even if there are 100 people in my home.
The tap in the bathroom is a bit...
It's fixed.
There's a light here.
Don't forget our current relationship.
Let me see the pipe.
Not bad.
You even learned how to fix this?
Didn't you want to fix the light?
What's wrong with it?
It sways.
It's fixed by itself.
Not bad.
You started cooking by yourself.
You even made three dishes and a porridge.
I even learned how to fix pipes.
Cooking is nothing compared to that.
I'm independent.
Gotta be strong.
When you're alone at home,
you must close the windows, doors,
and everything well.
You're living alone now.
I'll ask my friend
to set up
a smart security system for you.
This way, everything can be seen.
Everyone can see it?
Don't worry. I won't look.
Well,
if you need any help,
just call me, alright?
Why did you ask Liang Shanshan
to call me?
Won't that bother you?
No, nothing about you
is a bother for me.
Are you done?
Is there anything else you need to repair?
If not,
just go home.
Okay.
I'm leaving then.
I'm really leaving.
Go.
Bye.
I'm seriously leaving.
I'm leaving now.
You don't know how to walk anymore?
-Let me teach you.
-Don't...
Please don't get physical.
If you feel scared alone,
you...
If you're scared, I can stay with you for a while.
Sheng Yang.
Sheng Yang, come out.
I’m here.
Why are you so childish?
He left.
I told you to sit here.
Why did you hide?
Didn't you just get divorced?
I was afraid he'd misunderstand you
if he saw me.
You're quite considerate.
There's nothing to misunderstand.
Can't I have a friend
to help me fix the pipe?
Sure.
Then,
I'll ask him to eat dinner with us.
Go ahead.
Ex-husband,
Director Jian asked you to come back for dinner.
Just kidding.
Why would I embarrass my friend,
right?
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
We're divorced already.
It's me.
I'm the one who's afraid.
Look, I even hid.
It's not cold yet.
It's still hot.
I can sleep here. It's good.
I feel free.
Would it kill you to speak first?
You fixed the pipe,
cooked the meal,
washed the dishes,
and even cleaned the kitchen.
I'm sitting here like a couch potato.
I love it.
Let me tell you.
I really need a friend like you.
How about
I mop the floor for you?
I have a cleaner.
But thanks.
So,
it's getting late.
Yes.
I'll get going.
You should go home and rest.
You have a storm to face tomorrow.
Cheer up.
Actually,
if possible...
Of course,
if it's not a disturbance for you,
can I stay a little longer at your house?
Can I leave a little later?
You don't want to go home?
No.
I...
It's mainly the injury on my face.
I'm afraid my parents will see it when I go home.
They will definitely ask me all sorts of things.
What if I accidentally reveal
that I beat someone up in the company
and I might even lose my job?
Then,
I'll really be dead meat.
So,
I want to sneak back
after they fall asleep.
You'll help a friend out,
right?
Don't you have any other friends?
Aren't you my friend?
Yes.
Director Jian,
don't worry.
I...
I'll just stay
in this area.
I promise I won't bother you.
I...
I'll be like your statue
and not move at all.
I swear
you won't notice my existence.
Okay?
You're a living person.
If I couldn't notice your existence,
it would turn into a horror movie.
Look at the place you're sitting in.
Every day at this time,
I always sit somewhere to space out
or work.
That spot is right across from you.
Alright, I'll let you have this place today,
my friend.
I need to work.
Don't just sit there.
You
can have this area.
I...
I promise I won't make a sound.
Go ahead.
Lin,
for the reference of the makeup…
It's what we said in the meeting.
Organize the brand concepts
mentioned by the brand
and the problems
that I pointed out.
I'll add more in,
okay?
How would I know?
You'd have to ask them.
Sheng Yang?
Why aren't you all sleeping?
I've never seen you all sleep before.
The Portuguese team continues to attack.
Thank you for taking me in last night.
Sorry for disturbing you.
Thank you,
Sheng Yang.
Our son didn't come back all night.
Did he text you?
Who knows where he went.
He didn't even call.
Luo Meijuan,
I'm talking to you.
Enough.
Stop it.
We're too old to be childish now.
Are you done with the tantrum?
Here's your card.
Gifts blind the eyes of the wise
and stop their mouths.
From now on,
we'll spend our own money.
I don't want to live according to your mood anymore.
What are you doing?
No.
We just had a small fight yesterday.
Right?
We had a cold war all night.
What's wrong with our relationship now?
You're really acting up now.
Don't you think I'm annoying?
I'm always being unreasonable
and fight with you about money.
Exactly.
You think I'm stingy.
Tell me,
why am I frugal with food and items?
Other than food and items,
is there nothing else in your life?
I walk back and forth in front of you every day.
Why can't you see me?
I'm not blind. Of course I see you.
You see my body,
but not my heart.
You thought all night
and really improved a lot.
Your heart...
Isn't your heart a big, wide river?
There are steaks floating in the water,
and candlelit dinners,
right?
And dresses.
Super expensive
and shallow things to show off with.
I'm not scolding you,
but regular people like us should just live normally.
We can live without being particular.
Have you taken your keys, phone,
and wallet?
Boss,
I understand
the company's arrangement.
I thought about it all night.
I couldn't think of any good reason
to stop us from getting fired.
But if possible,
could you give me two more minutes?
I want to share my thoughts.
[Work Plan]
These
are the three projects I'm currently in charge of.
These two proposals
have been accepted by the client.
The next step is to submit the samples
to the marketing department for evaluation
and edit according to the feedback.
[Mid-Autumn Festival Park Hyatt project Gantt Chart Work Plan]
This
is the contract
for the short film.
The director has already signed.
Next week,
they'll start filming.
I would like to ask the company
to give me another chance
to finish these three projects.
View it
as closure for myself and the company.
Even if I leave,
I want to perform the last task well.
I don't want to cause too much loss to the company.
For these three projects,
one is due this week.
[Work Plan]
The post-production
for this one can be completed
before the end of next month.
During this period,
I will work hard
on all the tasks assigned to me.
I know.
It's useless for me to say these now.
You must think
I'm just trying to find ways to stay,
but...
I can't think of a better way.
I can only use the most direct way
and be honest with you.
Also,
Song Chen is from another city.
If he gets fired,
and he can't find a new job quickly,
he'll have to go back to his hometown.
Boss,
he did it because of me.
If the company is really going to fire us,
can you fire me first
and keep him for a while longer?
At least let him
finish his work at hand.
Then after he gets fired,
he can tell the others
that he has completed projects independently.
Boss,
you're not going to fire him?
Why not?
I know you've suffered.
Take a few days off.
Go home and calm down.
I'll give both of their bonuses
to you this quarter.
Come back to work when you've calmed down.
That…
That's it?
You just
scold them,
have them write a self-reflection,
deduct some money and that's it?
Boss, I'm injured.
I got injured for the company's benefit.
My beating
was all in vain?
What do you want to do then?
Fire them
and you do all the work?
Xiangqian, you're going to work?
Qiao.
What's wrong?
Have you and Sister-in-law
made up?
Nope.
She wants to split up.
Is it that serious?
It shouldn't be.
I don't know why.
I don't want to know either.
She keeps acting up now
and no one can stop her.
It's just an argument.
Women say some harsh words
so her husband can coax her.
You have no idea.
I always coaxed her when we were dating.
No matter who was right or wrong,
I was always the one who apologized.
Hey,
that's what you should do.
Why?
Do men not feel hurt
or have emotions?
Don't try to convince me.
All these years,
I always think of
my husband and son first.
Yes.
I only buy and cook the food they like.
Has anyone ever asked me what I like to eat?
In our family,
Sheng Yang ranks first.
His father ranks second.
I'm always ranked last.
I just follow behind them
and act as their nanny.
It's all the same for us women.
They say, "You're in charge of the money."
They make it sound nice.
"Money management."
You have to have money before you can manage it, right?
It's only 5,000 yuan a month.
It's not enough to spend
even if you scrimp and save.
But it's better now.
I returned his card.
I'll spend my own money now.
I don't have to worry anymore.
I'll buy whatever I want.
You'll only feel dignified
by spending your own money,
right?
We didn't fight for such a long time before.
She even gave me my card this morning.
What is this?
Does she want a divorce?
Our son is already an adult
and she's doing this now.
Isn't this upsetting?
My son has grown up.
He can live on his own.
If I don't treat myself better,
at this time,
I won't be able to enjoy myself when I'm older
even if I want to.
Yes.
Shop.
Today, we're going to do revenge spending.
Of course.
I work in the supermarket every day.
I only dare to look at the discounted products.
I don't even dare to think about
the slightly more expensive things.
[Glamorous Skincare Gift Box]
Let's go check over there.
Has she changed recently?
Is something bothering her?
Of course not.
She attended a classmate reunion.
After that, she started flattering herself,
dressing up more,
and even saying pretentious things,
like wanting to pursue her inner world.
It looks more like she wants to jump over the moon.
Could it be
that she met someone
at the reunion?
Xiangqian,
don't think too much.
Don't take it to heart.
I was talking nonsense.
You know her well.
She just wanted to buy a dress.
It means she wanted to buy it long ago.
She wanted to buy it long ago.
That means the problem existed for a long time.
Xiangqian,
Listen to me. Don't think too much.
don't take it to heart.
I'm sure there's no problem.
Xiangqian.
What is this?
Seriously…
Look at the durian.
I've always wanted to taste them,
but I couldn't bear to.
Meijuan,
durian is very expensive in this season.
Expensive?
I'll buy two.
I want to taste it
and see if it's smelly or fragrant.
Let's go.
Pick a big one.
Here's one.
This is so expensive.
I won't buy it if it's not expensive.
I'll put the cart back.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Luo,
these are all yours?
What's wrong?
You don't want to live anymore?
What are you talking about?
I want to live a good life.
Yes.
Here.
Swipe my card.
Luo,
the card's balance is insufficient.
Insufficient balance?
Why don't you check
if you have other cards?
Let me see.
Okay.
Use mine.
Sorry, Li.
I embarrassed myself in front of you.
You didn't.
Is anything wrong today?
Are you in a bad mood?
If you're in a bad mood,
shopping can cheer yourself up.
Look how good at shopping you are.
The lobsters just arrived this morning.
They're very fresh.
Do you know how to cook lobsters?
I'll tell it how to cook them.
You need a chopstick
and stab it
from the tail
all the way to the head.
Then take it out
to release the urine.
This way, it won't smell bad.
Then take the back of a knife
and hit the head.
Knock the lobster out
and then cut its head off.
Li, that's enough.
Indeed, this job isn't for you.
It's bloody
and you have to kill.
Ask your husband to do it.
Have him put on a glove
and cushion himself with a rag.
Otherwise, it'll hurt his hand.
Put it in the pot after it's done.
It's so delicious.
It's too expensive to eat.
I'd rather it eat me.
Look at you.
Just eat it. One meal doesn't matter.
I don't know what's wrong.
I bought so many useless things.
I thought I would be happy after buying them,
but now, I feel worse.
These things
cost me two months
of our living expenses.
I can imagine
what they'll say after I go home.
I don't understand.
What's wrong with improving your life occasionally?
Do you, Luo Meijuan,
not deserve to eat well and dress well?
You've lived frugally all your life.
Can't you
splurge a little
and be willful for once?
You earned this money yourself.
You didn't steal or rob anyone.
You got it fair and square.
What's wrong with that?
Thank you, Li.
Actually,
I don't have to eat or use expensive things,
but can't I look at them?
Can't I, at least, think about them?
I just want someone to tell me,
"Luo Meijuan, you deserve to live a good life.
You deserve new clothes
and good things.
You don't have to
keep looking at the discounted items."
That's okay.
I know.
I should be satisfied
that I have food and a roof over my head.
Then go shopping.
To buy what?
Sheng Yang is not married yet
and we have four seniors to take care of.
Yes, they are fine now.
But if they fall sick,
how many days in the ICU
can we afford with our salary?
Do you really think I'm that ignorant
or that I like wasting money?
I'm just tired.
I wanted to vent
and take a breather.
I understand you.
Li,
I rambled to you for so long.
Don’t take it to heart.
Just treat me as a trash can.
Throw away all the bad things here.
Forget it.
It gets annoying after a while.
What's annoying about it?
We are colleagues.
We meet every day.
If you're happy,
I also feel relieved.
Why don't we return
these useless things?
I'll ask Zheng for help.
Okay, we'll return them.
Okay.
Let's return them.
Let me help you.
What was I thinking?
I bought so many
useless things.
[July Advertising Agency Notice of Criticism]
[1. Deduct Sheng Yang and Song Chen's bonuses for this season
2. Compensate all medical fees of Wang Youde, leader of Creative Dept. Team 2
3. Sheng Yang and Song Chen will be publicly criticized in the company]
Look.
What did I say?
Boss won't fire the two of us.
Get to work.
Mom, Dad, I'm back.
I worked overtime last night.
It was too late,
so I just slept at the company.
Recently, the company made budget cuts
and won't even reimburse the taxi fees now,
so I didn't come back.
I didn't want to wake you two up either.
When do you come back early?
When do you not work overtime?
Stop chattering.
Wait,
what's wrong with you two?
Madam Luo?
Sheng?
Ask your mother.
Look at what she's done.
What have I done?
Don't you know what you've done?
What is there to know?
Come.
Tell me.
Let your son be the judge too.
What disgraceful thing have I done?
Come on.
The photo is right here.
I caught you red-handed.
Dad,
I think you misunderstood.
What did I misunderstand?
I saw it with my own eyes.
They were holding hands.
What did I misunderstand?
Luckily I went.
If I didn't go,
who knows what they'd do after that?
Dad,
what are you talking about?
My mom is not that kind of person.
I don't know if she's that kind of person or not,
but she did that kind of thing.
You must be mistaken.
No.
Son, listen.
I'm going to divorce him.
After the divorce,
whether you want to stay at home or move out
is up to you.
No, no, no.
Mom.
Let's sit down and talk.
Well done, Luo Meijuan.
I get it now.
You've found a new love.
Sheng Yang, listen.
Don't stop her from pursuing happiness.
Dad, don't be angry.
Sit down.
Let's all have a nice chat,
okay?
I'm not angry.
No.
I'm going to find a new lover.
I'm going to enter a whole new world.
No one can stop me.
Brave.
It's good that you admit it.
I've told you 10,000 times, Sheng.
I'm vain.
I love to buy dresses.
I love to dress up.
I do all this for myself,
not for men like you.
Is it that hard to understand?
Son, can you believe it?
She spent so much effort in dressing up
for herself,
not for others.
How is that possible?
Dad, why not?
Don't be so old-fashioned.
Look at your son.
He called me old-fashioned.
So what?
Do you know how ridiculous he was?
He stalked me.
He followed me to work.
I've never been so humiliated at work before.
I wouldn't have seen if I didn't go.
Do you believe him or me?
Okay, okay.
Stop.
You two sit down first.
Sit down. Listen to me.
Listen to me. Sit down.
Dad,
I think you must have misunderstood.
Mom,
please explain.
Think about it.
We've known Uncle Li for so many years.
Dad, one more thing.
If Mom wanted to do that kind of thing,
would she have done it in broad daylight
in front of all those people?
How many years have you two been married for?
Don't be like this, okay?
Enough. Stop it.
I get it now.
You're just a pot-stirrer.
Don't say that.
If I'm the pot-stirrer, then you…
I'm the crap in the pot, okay?
I'm crap.
Stop acting sweet with your mom.
The whole world knows you two are family.
I'm just the extra one here.
This...
Here's the photo.
She bought a dress worth 3,000 yuan.
It's all your fault.
You kept pushing me to buy her a dress.
She's being blatant now,
showing off like a peacock spreading its feathers.
Who are you talking about?
If you have to
blame this on me,
I'll take it.
I've endured you for a long time.
You don't have to.
What are you enduring for?
You're not a punching bag.
From now on,
do your own laundry,
cook your own food,
and do your own cleaning.
If you need anything,
or if you can't find anything, don't ask me.
Let's pick an auspicious day and get divorced.
Mom, stop it.
You're talking about divorce again?
You've said it my entire life
and I'm sick of hearing it.
Move out if you're sick of it.
You're a young man in your 20s, almost 30,
and you stay at home every day.
The other kids are all independent now. What about you?
Yes,
you do pay me,
but are your pennies and nickels
enough?
You are
exactly the same as him.
Not a single bit different.
Like father, like son.
Luo Meijuan, you're amazing.
Fine.
He was your son when he bought you things.
Now, he spoke up for me,
and you tell my son to get out.
Amazing.
Yes, he's your son.
He inherited
all your genes.
All the bad things were inherited from you.
Yes, all bad things were inherited from me.
Mom.
Sheng Yang must be horrible.
Mom!
Because there's nothing good about you.
He took after me entirely.
Fine, I'll listen to you.
Let's divorce!
Let's see who he takes after.
Dad!
Take after whoever you want.
Listen,
I don't care.
Dad!
It's up to you all!
Really?
He interviewed you?
Why?
Your husband is eloquent.
See,
you should read more books and newspapers.
Right?
You're amazing.
You're going to be on TV.
Are you jealous?
I'm making your dream of becoming an actress
come true.
You're a superstar.
Actually,
compared to being on TV,
having Yang
and our family
makes me
much happier.