[English subtitles are available]
Yang.
You look so pretty today, Sis.
I have a reunion to attend,
so I'll take two hours off.
Please take my shift for a while.
Okay, no problem.
Go ahead.
Who is this?
Are you really Meijuan?
You look so beautiful.
Li, don't fool me.
Do I really look good?
It's inconvenient
to work in this outfit.
This is the first time I've seen you dress up like this.
You look so elegant.
Dress like this from now on.
See you later.
See you.
Doctor.
I can't work with my arm like this.
When can I get the plaster cast removed?
Your wrist joint is half dislocated.
You can remove it yourself in a few days.
That's a relief.
Sign here, right?
I suggest you stay in the hospital for a few more days.
No, no, no.
I have a lot of things to do.
There's no family here to pick you up?
No need.
Look.
My roommate is here to show her love.
Okay.
Thank you, doctor.
Thank you.
I...
Do you need my help to walk?
Of course.
Should I
apologize to you as well?
Of course you should.
You never apologized in our years of marriage.
Make it formal.
Kneel here
and kowtow to me.
But are you wronged?
You're not.
Help me.
Look at Jian Shuang.
Even if she's good at accuracy since she plays ice hockey,
wasn't she afraid that she might beat me too hard
and I might become a vegetable?
Besides, I always treat her well.
Good.
You're still so loquacious.
That means you're fine.
When people get sick,
they get to know what's most important to them.
What is it?
Family.
Don't tell me you changed your mind about our divorce again.
No.
Don't.
Don't make it look like
I'm clinging to you.
Of course not.
You are not that kind of person.
Even if you are crippled,
you can still find girls ten times younger and prettier
than me.
Alright?
I don't even want to talk about that.
You see, I've been hospitalized for so many days,
but none of them came to see me.
They've all been hanging out themselves.
One of them even
called me and asked me to go
pay the bill for her.
Aren't you angry at all?
Isn't it interesting to hear?
You've already entered the state of being divorced?
We've long been family, haven't we?
But
if you have a girlfriend,
and I have a boyfriend in the future,
and we still treat each other as family or friends,
how will they feel?
Who cares?
As long as we are happy.
What?
So you've found yourself
a boyfriend?
No.
That brat from last time?
What brat?
Listen to me, Jian Bing.
Even if we're divorced,
we can't rush to find someone new.
Right?
Look at you.
If...
If you rush into a relationship unwittingly,
it would be irrational,
right?
You have to pick carefully.
Don't do yourself wrong.
Especially when it comes to age-gap relationships.
It's trendy now,
but nothing trendy lasts long,
right?
If you find someone younger than you,
who's not mature at all,
he'll cause you a lot of trouble in the future.
You are not young,
but are you mature?
No, I'm not.
I'm a giant baby, right?
So, in fact,
all relationships in this world
are age-gap relationships.
When do you men ever grow up?
If you're truly mature,
sign this.
You're so cruel.
I thought you were here to pick me up.
Turns out you're here to give me the divorce agreement.
It's not like that.
I am here
to pick you up.
I'm just dropping it off.
Cut it out.
I couldn't give it to you when you were hospitalized.
Next Wednesday.
Don't be late.
No. What do you mean next Wednesday?
Let me check my schedule first.
You're free.
Indeed.
No meeting, no shooting mission.
You've planned it for me.
Before you go, dress yourself up.
Yes.
The sense of ritual, right?
Mature people won't miss
important moments in life.
Get it signed.
It's inappropriate
if it drags on any longer.
Is this pearl real?
Of course.
Meijuan is here.
Meijuan.
Looks like Limei is late today.
Your dress
is so beautiful.
You look great in it.
Is it?
My husband bought it randomly.
You've already ordered?
It was already like this when we arrived.
I think
Limei ordered it.
Limei
is rich and generous, right?
Yes.
You're not bad either.
I heard that your son
works in a big company.
He must make a lot.
No, not like that. Just to make ends meet.
Make ends meet.
Look how competent her son is.
Her son is so capable.
Limei is here.
Limei.
What took you so long?
Sorry, I'm late.
It's okay.
You even brought us gifts.
You're late.
I'm late.
Sorry.
Sorry I'm late.
What gift?
Meijuan, I brought you a gift.
How could I accept it?
It's okay. I prepared gifts for all of our classmates.
Hurry up. Where's mine?
Don't worry. You'll get yours.
This is for you.
Look at your hands.
They look like they've never done any manual work.
Look, they're so white and tender.
How do you take care of them?
Look how sweet she is.
All of us
are pretty, right?
Of course.
The color is so beautiful.
Isn't it?
Yes.
Meijuan.
By the way,
I want to ask you.
Is Sheng Yang
interested in
my daughter or not?
Why didn't your daughter show up at their last date?
She's disobedient.
She regrets it now.
How about
giving her another chance?
What do you think?
Meijuan.
Let's set another date.
Okay.
You're so nice, Meijuan.
How about putting these two clips
back to where they were before?
This one?
Yes.
Shanshan, thank you so much.
Normally,
you must be drinking Long Island Iced Tea
in a karaoke bar, right?
How about I make you drink?
Be quick.
We have to deliver the video tomorrow.
Don't fail me.
I dare not.
If I fail,
Director Xue will jump down from the hospital bed and hit me.
Is he normally so tough?
Of course. He's much tougher than you.
I'm not tough at all, okay?
I'm more like a gentle elder sister.
I'm nice enough
to come here and supervise video editing for him today.
I turned down a lot of dates for this.
You two are really close.
You must have been friends for years.
We were high school classmates.
So you were childhood sweethearts?
Don't use this kind of romantic word
on me and him.
I witnessed
him destroy countless nice women myself.
Ms. Liang.
So you don't have any dark past
yourself?
Do you want me to share it behind your back too?
Is the hospital's security not working?
Why did they let you out?
I have so many things to do.
How is it, Master Deng?
It's not easy to edit videos with Ms. Liang, right?
She has a whole lot of ideas, right?
What do you mean?
You've had a long day.
I'm alright.
No.
Go back home.
I'll edit the video here tonight.
I'm really okay.
I can carry on.
If you don't go, I may change my mind.
You'll have to stay here with me all night.
Hurry up.
I'll leave then.
Go back now.
Bye, Director.
-Thank you.
-Bye, Shanshan.
Bye. Take care.
I didn't expect
you could really sit here and edit the video.
Nonsense.
You must think it's not easy
drinking and socializing out there.
Now you know it's no easy task editing videos too, right?
Not really.
I still like socializing more.
I'm leaving.
Don't.
Are you free tonight?
A bunch of people are waiting for me.
Turn them down.
Have a drink with me here tonight.
Okay?
Fine.
So annoying.
Check out the video we edited first.
Sis, you're back.
Meijuan.
Why are you back so early?
I only took two hours off.
What happened to your dress? You looked great in it.
Why did you change back?
Did I look good?
Yes. You looked so pretty.
That's not something I should wear.
Why not?
What's wrong? Are you in a bad mood?
No.
Saying no.
Look how long your face is.
Still denying it.
I should have
applied more hand cream.
Purple sweet potato.
2 kilograms, 3.67 yuan.
Why four glasses?
Who are the other two meant for?
No one.
They're all mine.
I just want it to look more lively.
You're indeed a Gemini with blood type AB.
As expected.
Well.
You don't eat dinner, right?
And you should be in a bar by now, right?
So I prepared more wine
so that you can
drink with me without distraction.
Right?
I should thank you.
This first toast
is to thank you
for taking care of me while I was hospitalized.
Although it wasn't long,
you still
spared time to visit me.
And you found an old nurse
to take care of me.
Thank you.
The second toast
is to thank you
for working hard for our company all these years.
You brought in
the clients for us, right?
Our company won't be able to survive without you.
The third toast
is to thank you.
Liang Shanshan.
Liang.
Ms. Liang.
You've been by my side all these years.
As long as you're still willing to scold me, Liang,
I feel relieved.
The fourth toast...
I can't make up any more lines.
I'll just drink it up. You can drink as you wish.
Enough. Stop drinking.
Come on.
Are you really toasting to thank me?
You're clearly trying
to drown your sorrows by drinking with me.
Here.
Sir, you got it wrong.
The fruits should be weighed over there.
Okay.
Hand cream. I bought it for you.
Talk later.
The baby cabbage is 4.60 yuan.
Here you are.
Li.
You...
Why did you buy this?
I bought it at a discount. It's not expensive. Take it.
I was just saying.
I'm already in my 50s.
No one cares about that.
You really took it to heart.
You don't need to worry about Sheng Yang anymore.
You should focus on making yourself look good while you are still young.
You should apply it. Your hands need to be taken care of.
It smells good.
Not bad.
I'll take it then.
Take it.
By the way, I need to get some meat weighed.
The weekend is coming. I'll cook something nice for
my husband and my son.
No problem.
I've set the date with Jian Bing.
Next Wednesday,
we'll go
get our divorce certificates.
I,
Xue Yiming,
is single again.
Shouldn't I celebrate?
I, Xue Yiming, have become
a bird that flies freely again.
Shouldn't I celebrate?
No wonder you've been so dramatic today.
Why do I feel
so upset?
Why do you feel upset?
Why? Tell me why.
How would I know why?
You can tell yourself why.
When I was discharged today,
I was thinking about
coming here and helping you
get the video editing done.
Jian Bing.
I thought she was there to pick me up.
10000 words
are omitted
here.
I also felt a little dizzy.
I was thinking
maybe I should go home and take a rest.
Then it occurred to me that if I go home,
there wouldn't be anyone in such a big house.
Why should I go back?
I'd better come and work here in the company.
I've never thought of going home for so many years.
But now,
I don't have a home anymore.
What have I been doing over the past decade?
Besides losing hair and gaining weight,
what else have I done?
I've become all alone.
Can you understand how I feel?
Don't you still have a bunch of girls in your phone?
At least, you still have your drinking buddies.
They are all young girls.
They won't be willing to listen to me talking about this.
I can pay their bills,
but I can't talk to them about this.
How should we get along in the future?
So, thank you.
Don't touch me.
Thank you, Liang.
It hurts.
It should hurt.
Thank you
for drinking with me.
I feel so bad.
Give me a hug and comfort me.
Go away.
You must look down on me, seeing me like this.
Don't you look down on yourself?
Liang indeed.
You put a dagger directly in my heart
without mercy.
Spot on.
I just can't stand you
pretending to be affectionate and depressed here.
Don't you know
why you feel sad yourself?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
I just feel very sad now.
Then let me tell you why you feel sad now.
Because the one who's always cleaning up after you
is gone.
You men just want
to have fun outside,
and keep it lively at home as well.
You want to have people
that can make you happy both at home and outside.
You want to look glamorous on the outside,
and feel comfortable on the inside.
Don't you just want to have a shoulder to lean on when you're back home after having fun?
One day
when you lose control,
break down,
and you can't keep sailing anymore,
you still want there to be someone
at home who can
take care of you,
and let you live the rest of your life happily at an old age.
Right?
I didn't think that much.
Time to eat.
Coming.
The dumplings are good.
Mom, give it to me.
You don't have to work overtime today?
No, I brought the work back.
Your team leader makes you do all the work.
What kind of person is he?
You are the one to blame.
Why did you name me this?
Sheng Yang.
Of course I'm like a sheep that's ready to be killed.
Get lost.
As an upright man,
you should count on your own efforts.
The dumplings are delicious. Eat more.
Be upright.
It's so hot.
Slowly.
Blow it.
Haven't you noticed
there's something different about me today?
Ms. Luo.
Aren't you afraid your dress may get dirty, cooking in it?
What season is it?
Why are you still wearing such a thin dress with short sleeves?
Show off as you want.
You'll behave when you catch a cold.
Dad, you know?
My mom went to a reunion today.
A reunion?
Were there any men there?
She posted it on her WeChat Moments.
Didn't you see it?
You posted it on WeChat Moments?
Mom, the dumplings are delicious.
See?
Still flattering themselves at such an age.
All of them wore scarfs.
It was indeed a Spider Web Cave.
That's not right, Dad.
My mom was very pretty when she was young.
You mean
your mom is not pretty anymore?
That's not what I meant.
That's exactly what you meant.
I'm not...
It's so obvious.
That's exactly what you meant.
What's wrong?
The dumplings are delicious.
She's saving them for you.
Eat more.
Mom.
Are you not eating?
I'm full.
You must have pissed her off again.
Go away.
Your don't know how to talk.
What do you mean she was beautiful
when she was young?
Now that she's old, of course she doesn't look good.
I didn't mean that.
That's what you meant.
You're always like this.
You always make me take the blame.
I saw a joke on my phone a couple days ago.
It was so hilarious.
Every spring, when the weather is great,
the tree is full of old ladies, just like fruits.
Sheng Xiangqian!
They were standing on the tree and taking photos
when the tree suddenly broke.
Each of them was fined 200 yuan.
Dad.
My team leader
bullies me at work every day.
He gives me so much work that I can't finish.
You chose the job yourself.
Since you chose it, don't complain.
I'm not complaining.
The point is I can't finish it.
That's good.
This is like a test for you.
Yes, I understand how it works.
Don't stare at the computer screen for long.
You should protect your eyes.
Don't worry.
The dumplings are delicious.
You just don't want
to admit that you have nothing now.
You've lost everything.
So you become soft now.
You're scared.
Enough. Stop drinking.
Why are you here?
The video has to be done by tomorrow.
Let me tell you.
This is what's most valuable
about you right now.
It's also the only thing that's respectable about you.
Alright.
I'm sober now.
Since you're sober now, clean this up.
It stinks.
Why should I clean it up?
The cleaner will do it tomorrow.
How can you be so lazy?
Jian Bing didn't discipline you well.
She never disciplined me on these things.
This is also what I liked the most about her.
What's the point of liking her?
It didn't stop you from cheating on her.
If she
were you, right?
I could buy you a purse.
Right?
I could treat you to a big meal,
and transfer some money to you,
and it would be over, right?
Am I that kind of woman in your heart?
Besides, this kind of thing
would never happen to me.
Right, you're the one
who buys purses for boys, right?
You are the one who treats them to fancy dinners
and buy them limited edition sneakers,
right?
She's different from you.
I told you.
She's someone that
demands emotional value.
She must be the only one.
Only looking at each other,
and letting ten years pass like a day.
She wants me to treat her like when we first met.
Do you think it's been easy for me these years?
Shut up.
Clean this up.
Stop talking nonsense.
Hurry up.
You have to work tomorrow.
Don't turn the editing room
into a karaoke bar for real.
Find a recycling bin and throw these away.
You can also throw yourself away while you're at it.
Do you know which bin you belong?
Which one?
Hazardous waste.
Calling her melodramatic since you're cheap.
Typical. She's too good for you.
If you don't deserve her, just admit that.
There are so many men in the world.
There must be someone that deserves her.
Don't regret it when she finds someone great.
All right.
Get back to work.
I'll clean it up.
Are you eating alone?
Why didn't you peel one for us as well?
Can't you do it yourselves?
What's wrong with you?
You didn't wash the dishes either.
Who did you wrong?
Come here.
Even if I come here,
the dishes are still unwashed.
Is the word "nanny" written on my face?
Was I born to be a servant
for the Sheng family
and serve you two?
Wait.
Tell me if you need anything.
Go away.
Who offended you?
No one.
You're being ridiculous.
Dad, what's wrong? I'm working.
Something's wrong with your mom.
Did you offend her?
Dad.
You know I didn't mean that.
You always shirk the blame on me.
Forget it.
If my mom is really angry,
I'll apologize to her.
No need.
But what you said is true.
That shouldn't have done anything to your mom.
Maybe it's menopause.
She's in a bad mood and emotionally unstable.
Women are so hard to serve.
When she was young,
she was gentle and obedient.
The older she gets, the more disobedient she becomes.
She won't tell you what she wants.
She wants you to guess.
It's like guessing lantern puzzles.
I really don't know what I say may offend her.
I really don't know what she wants.
Dad.
Maybe I know what my mom wants.
What does she want?
Think about it.
She put on this show tonight
just to show us her dress.
She wants beautiful clothes.
What clothes?
Just that kind of
expensive and branded dresses.
Like the dress she wore tonight.
How old is she to buy dresses like that?
What's the point of that?
Your mom likes
flashy things like that.
They're of no use,
and they take so much room and money.
You don't understand it.
Perhaps for Meijuan,
life is not just about daily trifles,
but poems and dreams.
What are you talking about?
How can there only be daily trifles in the Sheng family?
I'll make her a cup of chrysanthemum and wolfberry tea,
and kick her to her dreamland.
Dad.
Happy wife,
happy life.
Okay?
This is bad, Mr. Sheng Xiangqian.
How much
is that dress you mentioned?
It's not cheap anyway.
Is 300 enough?
300?
300 for two sleeves, perhaps.
Yang.
Let's talk about it.
Look.
A young man
in his 20s,
living with his parents.
Doesn't this count as taking advantage of his parents?
Should he be like
other young people,
and offer his family some allowance?
Look, the food expenses.
The rent.
A mother
and a child.
It's so hard for her to bring up a child.
Dad, stop it.
I've got it.
Can I pay by scanning the QR code?
You...
Why are you making it about you?
Do you want it or not?
Yes.
Let me tell you.
To deal with Luo Meijuan,
we must work together.
Alright, take the money.
Here.
QR code.
Done.
I've transferred it to you.
You've received 1,200 yuan through WeChat payment.
By the way,
do you know which one to buy?
You do?
How would I know?
This is your fault.
It's my fault again?
This is the disadvantage of not having a girlfriend.
If you have a girlfriend,
you can ask her
about it now, right?
Well, you've been married for decades,
but you still don't know.
I'm aiming far.
Impressive.
Wait.
I haven't washed it.
Well.
You want to eat it?
Wash it yourself.
Off you go, dear father.
After a month of cooling off,
are you sure you still want to proceed with the divorce?
Yes.
Okay, it's completed.
It's done, right?
Yes.
Okay, thank you.
Are you going back to the office?
We can take my car.
I'll go location scouting with Peng later.
Is it far? I can give you a ride.
No need. He'll pick me up later.
Okay.
Then...
See you in the office.
Bye.
Hello, Peng.
Brother. Let's go?
Well, you can go back.
I want to take a day off today.
Okay.
Beauty.
Me?
Yes.
Look around this hall.
Aren't you the prettiest?
Thank you.
What kind of business are you here for?
I'm getting a certificate of being single.
Are you single?
Yes.
I'm single too.
Do you want to get married?
Let's get married in a flash.
Are you insane?
Hello, what's wrong?
Hello? Can you hear me?
I'm outside.
It's okay. I'll leave you to it.
Wait.
Today is Wednesday.
You two just finished the procedure, right?
How could I forget that?
Why don't you come find me now?
Where are you?
The karaoke bar. I'll get you a separate room.
Okay.
Shanshan.
We have to count on you
for the next project.
No problem.
You have to find me
a better director.
No problem.
I trust you.
You can rest assured.
Okay, I totally trust you.
Shanshan.
Hold on.
I'll get another room for you.
Shanshan.
This is...
Mr. He.
Let me introduce.
This is one of the founders
of Jian Yi Advertising, my bestie,
Director Jian, Jian Bing.
So you're Director Jian.
I've heard a lot about you.
Come on. Fill the cup.
She's a lightweight.
I'll drink tea instead of wine.
A toast to you.
It'll be such a disappointment if you don't drink.
She really can't drink much. I'll drink for her.
I quit drinking recently. I'm sorry.
You quit recently? So you used to be able to drink.
Do me a favor.
Today,
drink this glass of wine.
You can't be too healthy.
It's boring. What do you think?
Mr. He, you're right.
I'll drink this as
a toast to you.
Alright.
Thank you for supporting our company.
Director Jian, please.
Mr. He.
We...
Fill the cup.
Just stay here.
Director Jian.
I've seen a lot of your works.
They're great.
I...
Really.
Thank you very much.
I think I want you on our next project
as well.
Thank you, Mr. He.
Let's drink. Let's not talk about this.
Don't drink too much.
You can really hold your liquor.
Pass me the wine.
Come on.
Director Jian.
Thank you.
Mr. He.
Director Jian's works are good.
And you're forthright.
Here.
Let me.
Cheers. Cheers.
Share your opinions.
Which one should we choose?
What works does he have?
Boss.
We've always been filming with Director Chen's team.
They want someone younger,
who's full of ideas.
Maybe they think Director Chen's concept
is a bit old.
These clients
are so spontaneous.
Just like my kid.
They always like better things.
But I think...
Boss.
You see.
Director Chen's team is so experienced
and easy to control.
Won't it be a pity if we don't use them?
These are their works.
How about him?
I heard
it's pretty hard to communicate with him.
And he's not very cooperative.
Who should we choose?
Boss.
How about
we have another discussion with the client?
Maybe we can ask Director Chen's team to shoot a sample first.
Sheng Yang.
You were very creative
last time when we were comparing notes.
Share your opinion
from the perspective of young people.
Which of these directors is better?
I think
none of them is suitable.
Boss.
Can I recommend someone that's not on the list?
Tell me about it.
I know a director.
She's done many advertisements.
She has her own style and ideas.
I think she suits our product very well.