Heartbeat
The brightest signature on the canvas of youth
A deep yearning for passionate love
Never fades
Fills every gap in daily life
Point A to point B
Lays out the
entire trajectory of life
The longing to "have a proper relationship"
Like looking through a shop window
At the warm light
Letting work schedules go offline
This is so much fun
Muting social masks
Letting go of identity concerns
To feel two genuine hearts
The charm of being honest with each other
Regaining the courage to feel moved
Gentle waves lap
The sea breeze is slightly intoxicating
The height of summer, 2025
Ten singles hoping to move forward with love
From Jiangsu, Zhejiang, and Shanghai
On two remote islands far from the hustle and bustle
Quietly meet
Hello
Would you like something to drink?
I just had something
You really look like
a "man straight out of a comic"
On the island
They will be accompanied by the sound of waves
Washing away the busyness and fatigue of reality
Experiencing the purest form of social life
Even though we've just met
It feels like everyone
has known each other for a long time
Let's see who can swing higher.
Okay.
On the journey,
they don't know each other's age,
nor ask about their professions.
They experience the purest version of each other.
Here we go.
Missed it.
Hello.
I saw it.
It feels like I've seen you,
but not completely.
After you reached out to chat with me that day,
did you regret it?
No.
I don't
regret any of my actions.
I want to
keep this feeling
going with you.
This is so romantic.
It's not just about liking you.
It's the you right now,
the you from the past,
and all of you.
On this journey where we shed our identities,
only two true hearts remain,
interacting with each other along the way.
Here it comes
When jasmine blooms, it's a sign of a fluttering heart
This program is brought to you by
Kang Shifu Jasmine Tea, with floral aroma and fresh tea flavor
as the title sponsor
Go on Xiaohongshu to discuss the show
and see exclusive content from the guests
Xiaohongshu
"Signal of the Heart" Season 8
Official content discussion platform
One capsule for 72 hours of resilient shine
Improves hair quality from the root
This program is brought to you by
Sponsored by Pantene Bubble Elastic Hair Mask
Thanks to our imaging experience officer
Huawei nova 14 series phones
Full focal range, maple red textured portraits
Capture your heart-fluttering moments
2-hour rapid repair
3 days to fight "late-night fatigue and aging"
This program is brought to you by
Estée Lauder Advanced Night Repair, 7th generation
Sponsored broadcast
Immersive soundstage, resonating with heart-fluttering moments
This program is brought to you by
Equipped with 23-speaker luxury sound system
Sponsored by Lynk & Co 07 and 08
Reduces dark circles
Gives your eyes a natural microcurrent effect
Brightens overnight
Heart pounding with excitement
This program is brought to you by
Marubi Little Red Pen Eye Cream
Sponsored broadcast
This is the world's
sweetest
social observation reality show
Kang Shifu Jasmine Tea "Signal of the Heart"
Season 8
We're here
Very happy
in this hot summer
we can once again
with passionate hearts
together
with "Signal of the Heart"
ignite
this beautiful midsummer
Alright
Welcome to all our Heartbeat Cupids
Hello, everyone
I'm Xu Minghao
Last season
still left me wanting more
so this season
I hope to spend it with all of you
enjoying even more heart-fluttering moments
I also hope to see them here
find their own love and friendship
So I hope this season
can also keep us company even more
How does that sound?
Yes, this season will
be by your side even more
I'm Ma Boqian
And then
I think mainly from
the things that happen to the Heartbeat guests
make us reflect on some things
whether it's about life
or about future relationships
they can all be inspiring
I'll try not to be so loud
but since Hanikezi is here today
to be honest, it's a bit hard
because with her
we're the kind of people
who have "battled" through all kinds of shows until now
I hope you can control yourself
So next
let's shift our attention to
Hanikezi
Let's welcome our new friend
Hello everyone
I'm the new Heartbeat Cupid
This is actually my first time
officially "shipping" couples
And I quite enjoy "shipping" couples
because watching others fall in love
is a very joyful thing
and also a very happy thing
Yes
Hello everyone
I'm very happy to be back on
"Signal of the Heart"
I hope this season
can also bring everyone
my perspective
and straightforward analysis
This time, Brother Xu
has returned again to
our "Signal of the Heart."
How do you feel now?
I'm very happy to be back at
"Signal of the Heart" again.
I'm even more looking forward to seeing the follow-up
to the last time we met on the island.
What's really cute about Brother Xu is that
he always follows every couple
and gets super excited
and totally invested
really, really invested.
Next,
let's welcome
our Chun Ye.
I have a goal for this season.
I want to become
a crane worthy of Yang Ruqing.
Worthy of Yang Ruqing,
worthy of Yang Ruqing's
"capable" label for a crane.
But did Yang Ruqing ask you for anything?
No, I mean ability.
A capable crane, that's what I mean.
Now it's the eighth season,
and "Signal of the Heart's"
peach blossom tree
is also continuously
growing strong
and bearing fruit.
So here,
let me share with everyone
that our "Jin Zhao" couple
in May of this year
have achieved a happy ending.
They got engaged.
That's great.
So everyone knows
the after-sales service of "Signal of the Heart"
is really impressive.
Alright, next
let's also
look forward to
our brand new season eight
and see what it will
bring to everyone
in terms of different and special experiences.
This time, we are
using a trip as the format
to bring everyone together.
It's the first time we're starting off with a trip.
I also think
it's a better way to get to know each other.
Actually, it's about creating an opportunity
for everyone to have more chances to understand each other.
Right.
Because you'll see more sides of them.
You can have more
insight and understanding of each other.
More or less,
you can find out
whether the two of you are compatible in many ways.
Yes.
Traveling is still
a real test for two people
and their relationship.
But traveling has an advantage when it comes to feelings of attraction.
It allows two people
to experience that spark during the trip
in a deeper way
and more clearly.
In real life,
when people are dating,
they also feel
that sometimes
the feelings we have for someone
are influenced by many
external factors.
Traveling can actually
let you quickly see a person’s
behavior patterns.
You can quickly
and accurately judge
what this person will be like
in a future relationship.
You get a general idea.
Right.
We always say
that saying,
if you want
to get to know someone,
the best way
is to travel with them.
Exactly.
You can find out
their lifestyle,
how they express themselves,
their eating habits,
and everything about them.
You can get
a quick understanding.
Yes.
Alright, next up
is the
first
dinner where everyone from both islands meets
I'm really looking forward to our
night when everyone finally gets together
All the Heartbeat Cupids
let's get ourselves ready
and start our
Kang Shifu Jasmine Tea "Signal of the Heart"
Season 8
Here we come
Let's go
Shanghai
Everyone's about to meet
Yeah
They're here
So excited
They have gifts too
Just like us
Yes
Everyone looks so handsome and beautiful
This is just too handsome
Wang Lechen
I love watching the dinner parties the most
They always dress up so specially
They changed into a new outfit
the really formal kind
What is he going to do?
He changed seats.
Now you can see who is coming.
Yeah.
Wang Lechen looks so different in a suit.
When guys put on formal wear, they suddenly
look like a different person.
He looks really good.
So handsome.
Is it possible the others look great too?
They haven't appeared yet.
It's possible.
Here they come.
This is...
This should be Lan (Xu Rulan), right?
Yes, it's Lanlan (Xu Rulan).
So beautiful.
Really beautiful.
All dressed up for the occasion.
Hello.
Hi.
He was amazed.
Where do you want to sit?
I'm fine with anywhere.
Hello.
Hi, my name is
Wang Lechen.
I'm Xu Rulan.
Lan as in the color blue.
Are you from the other island?
I think I saw your photo.
They haven't met before.
Yeah, this is the first time.
Dressed up like this for the first meeting?
I think anyone would be moved.
Definitely.
The dinner part is really amazing.
Have a seat.
Okay.
Do you want some tea?
It seems like this is the only thing to drink right now.
Then I'll have one without sugar.
Okay, I'll get it for you.
Thank you.
Thanks.
He's nervous.
Say something quickly.
"Silent mouth," hurry up and say something.
"Silent mouth."
Aren't you usually lively?
Yeah.
Why was I the first one to arrive?
When you went into that
cabin on the island,
what number were you?
The third.
I was the first.
You were the first?
Yes.
He twitched.
His mouth is...
She keeps staring at him.
And she doesn't say anything.
"Silent mouth," what are you even doing?
What are you laughing at?
Nothing.
It's just that we suddenly stopped talking.
It seems like they say that over there, you all are
very "I" types (introverts), right?
No.
Actually, I'm more of an "E" type (extrovert).
Really?
Yeah.
What about you?
I'm a strong "I" type (introvert).
That must be tough for you.
Then I'll come up with a topic.
Find a topic.
She's really confident and open.
Alright.
(Xu Rulan) Lanlan is just
not nervous at all.
She's very relaxed.
She always feels like
she can control the whole situation.
A woman with a very strong inner self.
That must be tough for you.
Then I'll come up with a topic.
Sure.
Host a meeting for the two of us.
Just the two of us.
I really like watching this kind of thing.
We should have two friends with us.
Back then, we went to your place.
Yes.
We exchanged with each other.
Right.
Did you have fun?
It was pretty good, just...
Xiao Fang (Fang Yijiong)
Very "I" (introverted personality)
Wang Yifan was just always smiling.
Yeah.
From your photos, it seems like you love to smile too.
When I saw that...
The photo from when we were choosing.
Yes.
And you're also the friendship-type lover, right?
Are you?
Yeah, I am too.
I want to switch.
Switch to where? Next to you?
Sit on this side.
Yeah.
Why don't you sit over here?
A bit more in the middle.
Okay.
Or over here.
Please have a seat.
So sweet.
Okay.
What do you think about sitting next to someone?
I think it's a considerate gesture.
Maybe she sensed
that the guy felt awkward being stared at by her.
He might have felt embarrassed.
So she decided to sit next to him.
Right, I want to ask something.
Teacher Qianzhuang,
is sitting next to someone more intimate
or is sitting across from them more intimate?
Actually, sitting next to someone
can also be a way to hide a little.
Because when you're face to face,
the sense of immersion with each other
is much stronger.
But the timing of her changing seats was quite clever.
She did it right after saying
"We are all
friendship-type lovers,"
then she changed seats.
So she really did
show a sense of friendliness,
at least a kind of acceptance.
Minghao, which type are you?
Are you the type who dares to move around?
Or do you also just find a corner?
I wouldn't.
I would.
I just naturally do what I want to do.
That's great.
She's really brave.
If it were me, I'd be glued to my seat.
I wouldn't be able to move.
How long after you came in did I arrive?
About
I didn't really check the time
It should be around ten minutes or so
Yeah
So you were sitting here alone
Didn't you have nothing to do at all?
Yes
I was just about to
start cleaning up for a bit
Give Wang Lechen some time and he gets excited
I think it's nice that we sit side by side like this
As soon as they come in, we can
greet the guests, right?
They're here
This is
Looks a bit like Wang Jue
Wang Jue
Beautiful lady
Hello
Hello, we meet again
Do you want to sit here or over there?
I'll sit here
Sure
This seems to be everyone's first choice
I sat here when I came
She sat here when she came
It must be the spot the first person to come in chooses
would pick
Okay
Let's sit
Alright
How long have you been here?
I was the first to arrive
I told you pink really suits you.
Yes.
White looks good on you too.
Thank you.
And your hairstyle looks great today too.
But this is actually the first time you two have met.
That's right.
So, how does it feel to be switched over there?
It's amazing.
I think they're having a lot of fun over there.
Aren't they?
Of course.
I want to know what you guys
did on the island yesterday.
We went to watch the sunset.
We watched it at the lighthouse.
It was beautiful.
I really want to see the lighthouse photos you took.
To make up for the fact that I didn't get to see the lighthouse.
I have them.
There are lots of group photos too.
Can I see them now?
They're all here.
They're all right here.
Anyway,
It's fine, you go ahead and look.
Show me the group photos so I can be jealous of you.
You guys are so good at taking photos.
You were the one behind the camera for their photos, right?
They posed themselves.
No.
At first, Duoduo (Ke Ailin) arranged it.
After she finished taking photos,
I helped take some for them.
Duoduo (Ke Ailin).
We've turned into tourists in the photos.
We're acting cute now.
The pose is really good.
These two girls' eyes
are especially expressive.
Yes.
That's great.
Next time, let Duoduo (Ke Ailin) take the lead.
All of us together.
I feel like Lanlan (Xu Rulan)
picked up on some information.
Did it happen?
No wonder you wanted to switch over there.
This side is at a disadvantage.
She wants to switch too.
You still have a chance to choose.
Actually, you can switch.
Yes.
If I don't choose, I'll just sit here.
Very clear.
Okay.
Very determined.
Wang Jue likes him (Wang Lechen).
For now,
she's determined to sit across from him.
Teacher, could this sometimes also
reflect the girl's feelings?
Yes.
Xiao Fang (Fang Yijiong).
Meticulous Xiao Fang (Fang Yijiong).
When he wears glasses and when he doesn't,
he looks like two different people.
He looks better without them.
Yes.
Hello.
This is also our first meeting.
I haven't met this person before.
Wang Jue
Hello
He said it out loud
her name
Hello
You are
I'm Fang Yijiong
We've met before
Yes
Hello
Pick a seat
Actually, Xiao Fang (Fang Yijiong)
has a good impression of Xu Rulan
He'll probably sit
next to her
I'll just sit here
across from her
I have a feeling
Later, when Xiao Jiao (Jiao Zhiheng) arrives,
sit next to her.
Sit next to Xu Rulan.
Hello, Xiao Fang (Fang Yijiong).
Are you having fun?
We really missed you after you left.
You and Wang Yifan.
Happy.
Hello, roommate.
He said he only slept two hours yesterday.
Yeah.
Why?
Couldn't fall asleep.
Aren't you the one who...
Aren't you the one who never gets insomnia?
You tell us.
Because I was switched out.
That's why I had insomnia.
Too nervous.
My mind was just...
pretty chaotic.
Silly smile.
Sending out signals.
Today, Xiao Fang (Fang Yijiong)
isn't wearing glasses.
Still not quite used to it.
Is it a different style?
It is a different style.
When we were choosing the profile cards,
we saw one with glasses
and another one where you weren't wearing glasses.
But in real life, you actually wear glasses.
So which one did you choose?
Actually, it was us
who discussed and chose based on the love personality type.
It's because
your type is the possessive lover.
That's a type we didn't have on our side.
Actually, you can't really say
it's completely the possessive lover type.
I might just need more companionship.
The "to be possessed" type.
Who do you want to be possessed by?
Actually, when we were choosing,
there was another reason.
It was because you weren't smiling in that photo.
You looked so serious.
Is it this photo?
Yes.
It's one of the few photos where I'm not smiling.
Yeah, he usually smiles a lot.
I want to see it again.
Then you should smile more.
Okay, I'll try.
Alright.
So girls really like guys
who smile often?
That's right.
Of course, it depends.
You have to look good when you smile.
I don't look good when I smile.
You look great.
Give me a smile.
When I smile, I look like
a "silly son."
No.
You're really cool.
Give us a smile.
A shy smile.
See? Even your shy smile looks great.
It's fine, keep watching.
Xiao Jiao (Jiao Zhiheng)
Hello.
We're old acquaintances.
Can I sit anywhere?
Should I sit across or next to you?
Friends,
He should sit next to her.
Xiao Jiao (Jiao Zhiheng) must be
next to Lanlan (Xu Rulan).
Sit next to her, next to her.
Can I sit anywhere?
Yes, sit wherever you like.
Please, have a seat.
He pointed over there.
Send him away.
Please, have a seat.
He won't do that.
Okay.
Impossible.
That's not you.
It's over.
He realized.
He has to stand.
You have to stand.
You have to stand too.
He'll definitely stand.
Stand up, bro.
Once you sit down,
you won't want to get up.
By the way, how should I address you?
Jiao Zhiheng.
You can call me Xiao Jiao.
Alright, I'm Wang Lechen.
"Le" as in "happy,"
and "Chen" as in "morning."
Easy to remember.
Yeah, it's pretty easy to remember.
Did he just do a serious mosquito-catching act?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Sorry about that.
I didn't mean to.
What's going on here?
You can even get competitive over this?
That mosquito-catching bit
was really "dramatic."
He's the one
who's famous for being an extrovert.
Actually, he
isn't that much of an extrovert.
When he's alone,
yeah.
He is.
Are you an extrovert?
Wang Lechen, are you an extrovert
or an introvert?
I'm an introvert.
You're an introvert too.
So nervous
that the day before yesterday,
I kept picking at my cup.
He didn't even know who it was.
I knew it was you.
He's so
over the top.
He said he's
a native of Shengsi Island.
Really?
Yeah.
Yesterday, Jin Yuxing actually believed it for a moment.
Even I believed it.
Do you want to guess about him?
Where did he come from to Shanghai?
Take a wild guess.
Do you know?
You don't know either.
Sounds like somewhere in Zhejiang.
Any hints?
Or maybe say something in your dialect.
If I speak in my dialect, it'll be too obvious.
Way too obvious.
Yeah.
Just say something.
We've never heard you speak it.
Okay.
Our dialect is just...
Why are you like this?
See, when others talk, he doesn't want to say anything.
Yeah.
But as soon as Lanlan (Xu Rulan) says it, he's fine.
You can try guessing a direction first.
Sounds so familiar... wait a second.
Is it south of Zhejiang?
It's probably about the same latitude as Zhejiang.
Anhui
No
Wuhan
Changsha
No
I think he's a science student
No, I'm a liberal arts student
Are you really a liberal arts student?
Got one point back
Turned it around
Sichuan
It must be that he didn't say it correctly
Mine
I didn't say it correctly, did I?
I'm shocked
It could be that
No, I'm not joking.
I think Xu Rulan
is a key figure.
Lanlan (Xu Rulan) and
Chenchen (Wang Lechen)
Both of them are probably in similar situations.
Yeah.
Each of them will be compared.
They'll get more attention.
The center of the vortex.
Right.
But I think there might be some overlap.
Maybe Lanlan (Xu Rulan) towards
Chenchen (Wang Lechen)
might also have something going on.
Vortex against vortex.
But why did Jiao Zhiheng
not sit next to Lanlan (Xu Rulan)?
I’ve always wondered about this.
He was led by Wang Lechen.
See?
Whatever.
Okay.
He would definitely sit over there.
Come on.
Let’s keep watching.
Duoduo (Ke Ailin)
Duoduo (Ke Ailin) is here.
Duoduo (Ke Ailin) has such a great personality.
Wang Lechen
Everyone, please stand up.
Hello.
Hello, baby.
Feeling happy now.
She should sit next to Chenchen (Wang Lechen).
Sit down first.
She's so cool.
Sit next to Chenchen (Wang Lechen).
Then I'll sit here.
Please sit.
Beautiful girl.
Wang Lechen and Duoduo (Ke Ailin)
Let me help you carry that.
Is it this one?
Hello.
(What) part is this?
Three-minute self-introduction.
Okay, like this.
Then I'll go first.
Introduce.
Myself.
My full name is
Ke Ailin
It means "Dad loves Mom."
Her dad and mom.
I'm shipping them.
This way of naming
is a really good idea.
My surname doesn't work well for this.
If you use this kind of
"Dad loves Mom" name,
what would your name be?
No.
Pick a character from inside.
I like it.
The long one.
You like the long one.
Last night, we
practiced the "er" sound hard.
I thought about it after I got back.
If we want to make it sound more affectionate,
what should we call it?
Jue'er (Wang Jue)
She seems a bit
happy now.
She's happy.
Happy now.
It's a bit like that in Peking Opera,
the character.
The lead performer.
Yesterday,
we started saying
as soon as we woke up, we'd go find you.
We were even saying, when you got up,
why didn't you come find us?
We kept worrying
that maybe you
might be a little bored alone.
But she lost the "Ganmaoling" joke.
Look, when Duoduo (Ke Ailin) came, he
he felt better.
Now Wang Lechen is comfortable.
They don't know.
So did you tell her?
That joke from yesterday.
It's hard to explain.
A little.
A little secret only they know.
I can explain it to you in detail later.
Okay.
Here they come.
Who is here?
Jin Yuxing.
Hello.
I stood up for you.
Just in time.
It's fate.
Long time no see.
Come on.
Pick your favorite seat and sit down.
In that case,
I'll sit over there then.
It really has been a long time.
Even though it's only been a day,
it feels like I haven't seen you all for a week.
I feel like we've grown distant.
How come you seem
so much taller all of a sudden?
Me?
Him.
Yeah, it feels like you and Wang Lechen both got a lot taller.
That's really interesting.
Opening remarks.
Still catching mosquitoes.
Still catching them.
Xiao Jiao (Jiao Zhiheng) is really funny.
You left too early this morning.
We originally wanted to visit.
You guys.
But you had already
left.
We were really disappointed.
Because we brought gifts.
Yeah.
I really didn't expect that
the boys would also
be switched out.
It's just that
it's a bit of a pity.
We didn't get to
say goodbye to you.
And then
we left first.
So did you later
catch a cold?
No.
Why do you think I would catch a cold?
It's nothing.
That's so funny.
He didn't get it at all.
What they're laughing at
is Ganmaoling.
He still doesn't know that was Yuanyuan (Lu Yuan).
who gave him Ganmaoling.
But they came yesterday.
Before they arrived
that place must have been peaceful.
There were only the sounds of seagulls
and the sound of the waves.
After they arrived,
yeah.
The first person I saw was
Xu Rulan.
She left a strong impression.
She was wearing that
yellow
pale yellow dress.
She was looking at the sea.
Right?
Yeah.
You still remember the color of my dress?
Because I thought
it looked really nice.
He made it really obvious.
That look in his eyes means something.
Just now, Xiao Jiao (Jiao Zhiheng)'s
look in his eyes
Are you trying to express that you miss someone?
I'm not the one who should be expressing that.
You know, after you left,
someone was really sad.
Finally, it's been said.
Please, hurry up and say it.
I'm getting so anxious here.
Yeah, I was wondering why
he didn't just say it sooner.
You know, after you left,
someone was really sad.
Is it okay to say this now?
Hurry.
"Cold Medicine Girl"
Show up quickly.
It's time to show up.
Lu Yuan
She brought cold medicine.
Yes.
Hello, everyone.
Speak of the devil.
"Cold Medicine Girl"
is online.
She's here.
Hello, Yuan'er (Lu Yuan).
Hello.
Hi, where should I sit?
Please choose.
She should sit directly across from Jin Yuxing.
I'll sit here.
Is that okay?
She picked the right seat.
When we first saw Jin Yuxing,
the first thing both of us
said was
Long time no see.
This phrase of his
has many meanings.
Can I pour myself a glass of water?
Thank you.
It's okay, you can put it down.
I'll do it.
Pour some first.
Okay.
May I ask your name?
My name is Jiao Zhiheng.
Zhiheng is a bit hard to remember.
You can just call me Xiao Jiao for now.
Xiao Jiao (Jiao Zhiheng), okay.
My name is Lu Yuan.
You can call me Xiao Yuan.
Lu Yuan.
Yes.
What did you do on the island yesterday?
That's a rather
important question.
On the island, we
rode electric scooters,
chased the wind,
and chased the sunset.
You watched the sunset too?
Yes, that sunset
was beautiful.
Yes, we went to see it yesterday too.
Because yesterday
the weather was great.
Yes, the weather was great.
Yeah.
The one we saw from the guy,
is the (test result) label.
It's on all of them.
Market philosopher.
Yeah.
So when you cook,
it must be really delicious too.
He has his specialties.
He can cook beef.
Cooking is also a plus.
What's the dish you're best at?
The one I make most often,
for example,
braised pork.
Or
wasabi giant river prawn.
Giant river prawn.
I really love eating giant river prawn.
And things like cilantro beef.
Just simple home-cooked dishes.
Impressive.
So impressive.
He can cook beef.
His beef is really delicious.
Yeah, he can also cook shrimp.
Braised pork.
Yeah.
He's really good at it.
Really good at it.
Very impressive.
Don't.
Please, I'm begging you.
Sorry.
That reaction is really cute.
Xu Rulan should be able to do it too.
Really?
Why did you suddenly mention me?
I can do it.
So silly.
When the time comes, please help me out.
What if I mess up?
No problem.
Help me out.
I'll assist you.
I'll do my best.
I'll make it for everyone.
Ours.
Xiao Fang (Fang Yijiong)
Um...
Spicy food tolerance
improvement plan
Right?
Right.
Teacher Xiao Fang (Fang Yijiong)
I'll add more numbing and spicy flavors for you.
Spicy food training class
Yes, spicy food training class.
I'll add more spice for you too.
It's okay.
Rice mixed with chili peppers
Such a "vicious" dish.
Xiao Fang (Fang Yijiong)
Really so "I" (introverted personality)
You really shouldn't let
"E" people (extroverted personality)
treat you like a "toy."
Actually, it's not that bad.
If they can treat me like a "toy,"
I would still be
pretty happy about it.
Pretty happy.
Here
Who here is most likely to treat him like a "toy"?
What do you think?
Who?
Then I think it might be Xu Rulan.
Oh no.
This comment from Xing-ge (Jin Yuxing)
really made Xiao Jiao (Jiao Zhiheng)
probably feel a bit "blown up."
He dug this hole himself.
And then jumped right in.
It's her.
She's the most extroverted.
I think both of them are very
evenly matched.
That sentence has multiple meanings.
I hear something.
Who's here?
Wang Yifan.
Hello.
We meet again.
Yes.
Look.
Where should I sit?
I'll just
sit nearby.
Okay.
Wang Yifan sat down
next to Xiao Fang (Fang Yijiong)
She seemed casual about it
but actually it was
a deliberate choice
I think what you said makes sense
Your sudden approval
made me doubt myself again
I feel like I've already been
treated as a "toy" by Xiao Ma
Hello
My name is Wang Jue
We met that one time on the boat
That's right
You two
And then we
Yes
waved to each other from different boats
How are you so beautiful
So the last one is
the guy I haven't met
Wait a second
Are you sure
This is the
guy you said you haven't met
You all
have met before?
We greeted each other on the boat.
We said hello on the boat.
Hello.
Yes.
My name is Jin Yuhang.
"Jin" as in "gold".
"Yu" as in "Yu the Great".
"Hang" as in "industry".
Wang Yifan.
And "Yi" is
"Yi" as in "art".
"Fan" is
like in "smooth sailing".
"Fan" as in "sailboat".
Right.
So isn't that
just missing
Ruilong.
You saw Ruilong, right?
I saw him.
What did you think?
My impression is
I'm just waiting for Ruilong
to make a grand entrance.
Ruilong.
I want to see him.
You seem really interested in Ruilong.
Because
he described
He said
when he (Fang Yijiong) saw Ruilong,
he was really impressed.
Superior jawline
He really is so handsome
Okay
Looking forward to it
He really looks good
He really is handsome
Here he comes
Hello, everyone
Hello
Come, pick a seat
Have a seat
Everyone is so beautiful
He is really cute
Long time no see
Shengsi, I really miss you
A pun
Their code words
Miss Shengsi
That's the island, right?
Shengsi Island, right
Right
Long time no see
Miss Shengsi
Right
Ruìlóng, do you want to go first?
Introduce yourself
Sure, my name is
Ruìlóng
Hello, Ruilong.
So cute.
We've been waiting for you for so long.
Sorry.
I'm late.
A bit late.
The journey was exhausting.
Just got off the plane.
From
Pudong Airport.
That distance.
So Ruilong is
What kind of mixed heritage?
Swiss.
So you can speak
German,
English,
German, English,
French,
Chinese,
and then
Swiss dialects.
He's so talented.
The Swiss dialect is
Swiss German.
So impressive.
He's really amazing.
He can even understand
some Cantonese.
A bit of Cantonese.
A bit of Spanish.
A language genius.
He found the secret to languages.
You know?
People like him
are so impressive.
I'm from Shanghai.
I studied German in college.
That's impressive.
I'm glad.
Nice to meet you.
Yes.
Why don't you start a class?
Just one month.
Let's see how much you can learn.
It's up to you.
It's up to Ruilong.
Half an hour every night.
Take notes in a small notebook.
Did you notice there are two more seats?
Who are they for?
Are there really going to be more people?
I think they might be newcomers.
I'm sure there will be.
I think I heard a phone.
I don't think so.
Who got a message?
Only one person got it.
He has a message.
Jin Yuxing got it.
The exciting part is about to start.
I'm so nervous.
Show up already.
So soon?
Looking forward to it.
This outfit isn't easy to pull off.
She gives off a bit of a big sister vibe.
This should be that mature, dominant style.
Her legs are pretty long.
The new arrival checked in advance
the results of the travel edition love personality test.
She will choose one
member of the opposite sex she wants to get close to.
and sit next to him.
Devoted lover
Friendly lover
Possessive lover
I would choose this one.
She picked Jin Yuxing.
I think I got a message
saying a mysterious guest is coming.
Jin Yuxing is quite popular.
Really?
Yeah.
Jin Yuxing needs to make sure
there's an empty seat next to him.
That means a girl is coming.
A girl?
Yeah.
He's really in demand.
Yuan Yuan (Lu Yuan) really is something.
One wave hasn't settled before another starts.
Just moved to that island,
and now a newcomer is arriving.
They're here.
I hear something.
I'm so nervous.
Purple is really popular this year.
Yeah.
It'll definitely work.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
Hi.
Hi, everyone.
Hello.
Let me introduce myself first.
Why don't we sit down first?
Okay.
Seats.
What should I do?
Jin Yuxing.
There's an empty seat here.
I'll sit over here.
She wants to sit next to Jin Yuxing.
Yeah.
Go ahead and sit.
She seems very generous.
My name is Sun Hanqing.
The "Han" from "cultivation."
The "Qing" from "clear water."
You can all call me Chichi.
Chichi (Sun Hanqing)
Yes.
Because I really love to eat.
Chichi (Sun Hanqing)
Yes, it's easy to remember.
You can call me Chichi.
Chichi (Sun Hanqing)
It's because of work.
That's why I can meet everyone today.
I'm very happy to see you all.
She loves to laugh.
Thank you.
My name is Jin Yuxing.
"Jin" as in "gold."
"Yu" as in "Yu the Great who controlled the floods."
"Xing" as in "industry."
You can use the pronunciation from "astronaut" (yuhangyuan)
Use the "yuhang" pronunciation
to remember my name.
Yuhang.
You can also call me Yuxing, yes.
Sure, that's easy to remember.
That's easy to remember.
He seems very cheerful.
Is that guy mixed-race?
Yes.
That's right.
You can guess where he's from.
His name is Ruilong.
Sweden.
Close.
Switzerland.
Right.
What?
Guessing where you're from.
That's too far off.
I already guessed it right.
Guessed Switzerland correctly.
Got it right on the first try.
Yes.
No.
Second try.
Impressive.
Don't say it.
We've gotten closer.
There’s a bit of a spark between the two of them.
I guess you’re an extrovert.
Me?
I am indeed an extrovert.
But my extrovert score
isn’t very high.
Now everyone is
Everyone’s an extrovert.
All the girls are extroverts.
Then I might be
the least extroverted one.
Are you from Hangzhou or Shanghai?
You can guess.
Shanghai.
Yes, that’s right.
Besides Shanghai and Hangzhou, are there any others?
Yes, I’m from Yiwu.
Yiwu.
Yiwu, Zhejiang.
So are you
a Shanghai native or just working in Shanghai?
I’m from Jiangxi.
I can really handle spicy food.
Yes.
I also love spicy food.
I can eat spicy food too.
Yeah, I can handle spicy food as well.
His expression.
Lu Yuan doesn't look very well.
What have you all been up to these past few days?
We went to a small island to have fun.
We split up and went to two different islands.
You went on a trip?
Yes.
Chichi (Sun Hanqing): That's right.
Only I was working.
You all went traveling.
We have to go back to work tomorrow too.
Yeah, same here.
We just went to two islands.
One was Shengsi Main Island.
The other was Huaniao Island.
Was it fun?
It was fun.
I'm jealous.
At that time, we went to two islands.
Five people were on Huaniao Island.
And five people were on Shengsi (main) Island.
Then, on the second day,
Jin Yuxing felt a sense of responsibility.
He thought the girl chose him.
So he felt it was necessary to
introduce many things to her.
At that moment, I saw Jin Yuxing's thoughtfulness.
Because I think
usually, if you just
arrive last and there are many people,
actually, at that time,
whoever shows you care and warmth
will make you feel the most
Yes.
impressed.
I think first impressions are very important.
With so many people,
how can you make the person you like
or the person you're interested in notice you?
So, in this case,
he clearly made good use of this advantage.
He managed to leave an impression on others.
At that time, we went to two islands.
Five people were on Huaniao Island.
And five people were on Shengsi (main) Island.
What did you do?
It was me and
Xiaoyuan (Lu Yuan) who went to the lighthouse to watch the sunset.
Like that.
It must have been beautiful.
Let me show you the photos.
Hurry, show her.
Yes, this is the lighthouse.
It's from Chinese National Geography.
This one looks great.
And we also saw
the sunset.
This is really beautiful.
The photo is really well taken.
Yes, it's very nice.
Actually, it was like
we took a short trip.
And then
during this process,
we could get to know each other better.
Like that.
But we still don't know each other very deeply.
So next,
I think there is still more
we can share.
I think it's fine.
Actually, I wasn't that late either.
Yeah.
But I think
it was worth it.
Yesterday, we waited for you.
They waited for them.
And today, we
waited for Chichi (Sun Hanqing).
Welcome.
I think Chichi (Sun Hanqing)'s
whole approach
shows she's a very smart girl.
Because there's a detail about her,
when it came to Ruilong,
she told Ruilong,
"I guessed it right on my first try."
Then, next to Jin Yuxing, she said,
"Don't say anything."
With the very first question she asked,
she quickly
created something between her and Jin Yuxing,
she created
a little secret only they knew.
By doing this,
I think she wasn't being offensive,
and at the same time, she gave off
a sense of interest
and a signal that she wanted to get to know him better.
And actually, just now
during this process,
we've heard countless times
about
E-types (extroverted personalities)
and I-types (introverted personalities).
This topic
was already discussed
with Hani in the pilot episode,
and also with you.
You both
prefer
I-types (introverted personalities).
I like it when he's colder outside,
just quiet.
And then at home, the two of us can
I like that special preference,
a kind of treatment that's different from others,
just for you.
It's a kind of pattern,
wanting that special feeling,
wanting to be the special one for him,
to be treated differently.
Introverted on the outside,
extroverted on the inside.
Right.
But my E (extroverted personality)
means he doesn't have to be that way at home.
He doesn't need to show his extroverted side.
He can just be himself.
But I want a strong response.
I don't want a lukewarm response.
I think I tend to like people who are the opposite of me.
Because I'm already very introverted.
And if the other person is also introverted,
Yeah, that's what I mean too.
I'm someone
who tends to get lost in my own
emotions.
So I hope the person by my side
can help me
feel stronger
or more motivated.
So
if they're a bit more extroverted than me,
it might feel more comfortable being together.
Sometimes I just feel like
their kind of energy
makes me feel recharged.
Because I usually feel like I don't have enough energy.
So I really need that
energy to lift me up.
Actually, I think I can also become
quite outgoing
like that.
And the energy of extroverted people
that kind of energy
is like sunbathing during the day,
it can make your whole energy
feel comfortable from the inside out.
But it can't be
too extroverted.
If they're too extroverted,
I will
end up completely exhausted.
Okay.
Everyone has prepared gifts in advance.
Please decide the order of drawing lots yourselves.
And
announce who prepared the gift you draw.
Announce who prepared the gift you draw.
Looking forward to it.
For more exciting content, please check the extended version.
Let the newcomer pick first.
Then I won't be polite.
I'll go first.
I picked the biggest one.
I'll choose this one.
Okay, take a guess.
Guess.
How did you know?
I gave it.
This jasmine green tea is really tasty.
My jasmine honey tea is also delicious.
This Master Kong jasmine honey tea
has the perfect blend of jasmine and tea aroma.
They're blended just right.
Mine also has a rich jasmine fragrance.
If you savor it, there's a sweet aftertaste.
Time to eat!
Delicious.
This table is really too long.
Let me share these with everyone.
I'll use this as a serving spoon.
Here you go, Duoduo (Ke Ailin).
Thank you.
Is it okay if I put this here for you?
Do you eat beef, Xiaoyuan (Lu Yuan)?
Do you eat this?
Yes, thank you.
You're welcome.
Do you want to try this?
Thank you.
We've all taken some.
So busy.
Butler.
Xiao Jiao (Jiao Zhiheng) is actually very thoughtful.
I'll serve you first.
Plate.
Thank you.
Then this piece.
Should I just put it here?
Let's see who can eat faster.
You lost.
A man's competitive spirit.
You two, see who finishes chewing first.
Whoever swallows first wins.
I've already swallowed.
What?
Is it that hard, bro?
Bro.
Look.
Put the little flower in that collar.
A little thoughtfulness.
Very romantic.
The lid isn't open.
This is a new suit.
The pink is so delicate.
It looks like a group of groomsmen and a bride.
Excuse me.
Let me serve everyone.
Special blend of Master Kong Jasmine Tea.
This looks so pretty.
Yeah, this special blend looks delicious.
Can I have the orange one?
Do you want to swap with me?
Sure.
Thank you.
Thanks.
What's the one in the middle?
Is it loquat?
Loquat.
Lemon.
Jasmine.
Come on, everyone.
Happy New Year.
Wishing us happiness every day.
Happy.
Cheers.
Alright.
The cucumber one is so refreshing.
It's really good.
It's not that cloying kind of sweetness.
It's light.
This one is also very refreshing.
Slightly sweet.
We want some too.
Master Kong Jasmine Tea special blend.
Really, there really are.
Two identical versions.
Can I have both of them?
I'm being a bit greedy.
Okay.
For all of us Cupids,
we've prepared the same special drinks.
Our Master Kong Jasmine Tea
lets us experience
the party atmosphere from afar.
You really are greedy.
My drink is called "Mo Mo's Heartfelt."
You can taste the Master Kong Jasmine Honey Tea's
rich jasmine fragrance.
Mine is "Mo Ming's Heartbeat."
In the fragrant, low-sugar jasmine tea,
there's refreshing loquat added.
It really tastes great.
Delicious.
Let's keep watching.
Cheers!
This is mine.
There's a card.
Can I look at this?
There's writing underneath.
Whoever gets someone's gift
has to answer the question in their hand.
I think this is the most exciting part every time.
Then I'll ask you.
How do you feel about
your journey of finding love so far?
Are you satisfied with it?
Why?
I'm definitely satisfied.
Because I think
no matter what,
regardless of who I end up having feelings for,
I feel
at the very least, I've met
a wonderful group of friends.
And for me,
if you had to prepare another gift,
which member of the opposite sex would you give it to?
Why?
This
is very obvious
and straightforward.
He looks like he changed color.
He really is
a "chameleon."
You all thought he used a filter, right?
He didn't use a filter.
What should we do?
He's so shy.
His neck is all red.
He turned red so quickly.
"Little Red Dragon."
Of course, it's for the same person.
This is fate.
Can you even answer like that?
That's clever too.
Very clever.
The person who got my gift
Xiaoyuan (Lu Yuan)
May I ask, tonight
will the person you have feelings for change?
So exciting.
You're really going all out.
Did you hear that clearly?
Yes, I heard it clearly.
She needs to answer carefully.
No.
No change, she hasn't changed.
That's really brave.
Still choosing that one.
Jin Yuxing.
Yes.
Next.
I'll do it.
Please have the person who received your gift choose someone.
Exchange seats with someone of the same gender.
Right.
I've been waiting for him all along.
Are we switching seats?
I just didn't feel that
this thing would
be this simple.
Come on.
Switch.
Very straightforward.
Very obvious.
Exchange seats with someone of the same gender.
Go ahead and switch.
Will he switch with Fang Yijiong?
It's possible.
He'll probably still go to
Lele (Wang Lechen)'s side.
He might switch with Wang Lechen or Ruilong.
You...
Why is it the two of us...
laughed?
Then let's switch.
It's obvious he wants to
sit next to Xu Rulan.
Yes.
Come.
Butler, switch seats.
Come on.
Should I bring it over?
This shot
is a battlefield.
In a moment, all of Wang Jue's
You will see all of her
body positions are like this.
Feels like we're playing a murder mystery game.
He's happy now.
Afraid I'll see it, right?
Did you see it?
No.
Look, it's already started.
Is it happening?
It's already started.
Is it me?
My question is,
please describe, during the island trip,
in those two days,
the moment that moved you the most.
Why?
Answer properly.
Why is my question so long?
The most touching moment.
That's a good question.
Duoduo (Ke Ailin)
Feels like three pairs of eyes are watching.
It should be when we watched the sunset.
Because I had been looking forward to the sunset for two days.
I think unexpected encounters
are truly the best arrangement.
It's a bit vague, but
I can answer like this now.
Yes, he really was looking forward to the sunset.
Then let me ask.
I'm asking you.
Yes, Lanlan (Xu Rulan).
In the upcoming romantic journey,
do you have any wishes you want to fulfill?
I think whether it's during this time
or after the show ends,
all of us can
go on another trip together.
Okay.
That's very similar to our wish.
I agree.
During this romantic island trip,
if you had to
name one thing you regret,
what would it be?
Xiao Fang (Fang Yijiong),
the thing I regret is
I was switched out.
If he says that,
then it must be Lanlan (Xu Rulan).
Then I really
That's impressive.
Come on, say what's on your mind.
I sent the (sunset time) message too slowly.
That's pretty obvious.
It's Lanlan (Xu Rulan).
This one—
His is especially obvious.
He sent the (sunset time) message too slowly.
So you didn't get a chance to see the sunset, right?
Right.
That's exciting.
He drinks a toast by himself.
What?
I think
the first person to send
the (sunset time) message to someone of the opposite sex
can invite the other person to join the activity.
So did you already join the activity?
Yes.
Alright.
Got it.
I'm going to ask now.
Please choose a member of the opposite sex.
Ask her so far
what her impression of you is.
He’s going to blush soon too.
Choose a member of the opposite sex.
How should I choose?
Then I’ll choose the person who asked the question.
I’m going to blush (feel warm).
They’re all so good at answering.
But this is the safest choice.
Because you don’t know much about me.
It’s just a first impression.
The first time we met was on the boat.
It did feel a bit distant.
At the time, I told Xiao Fang (Fang Yijiong),
I said I felt this guy
was really strong.
Strong.
Back then, under the sunlight,
because you guys were probably on the shady side,
while we were on the sunny side.
So I said at the time,
I said,
he seems a bit tanned.
But now I think you look quite fair.
But today, you seem very reserved.
Because that day, you were actually
the first one to wave.
I thought you would be the type
who’s very
outgoing.
Really?
Maybe.
But this question
there's only one person feeling lost here.
That's Yuan Yuan (Lu Yuan).
Right.
When asking Jin Yuxing now,
Jin Yuxing actually didn't really
direct the question to someone he spent a whole day with.
Someone he spent a long time with.
He asked from a very neutral standpoint.
But at this moment, being neutral
is also his way of expressing himself.
So Yuan Yuan (Lu Yuan) then
feels an even bigger gap.
But the two of them have always
not really had the right connection.
Yeah.
Is it my turn now?
Yes.
Please invite one person of the opposite sex and one of the same sex
to describe their first impression of you.
Okay.
Then I'll invite
you two.
I think
well,
she's very easy to get along with
and a very observant girl.
I really have been observing everyone here.
Yeah.
Is it my turn?
Because when you came in,
the first thing you did was introduce yourself.
I think
you seemed pretty confident and natural.
Can I answer
my first question again?
I just thought about it.
Because when she answered,
we hadn't heard Jin Yuxing's answer yet.
May I ask if the person you're interested in tonight
will change?
Yes.
She changed.
That means it's not.
Right, it's not Jin Yuxing.
So that means
it's Wang Lechen.
Yes.
She definitely did this because
she heard Jin Yuxing's answer.
She changed her mind on the spot.
She said, "I regret it."
"I don't want to make this decision anymore."
This behavior
is actually pretty bold.
You go ahead.
I'll do it.
Okay.
Mine is...
You should answer this question.
Up to now,
has anyone of the opposite sex made your heart flutter?
If so,
please take a sip of
"Mo Mo Qing Xin"
or "Mo Ming Xin Dong" special drink in your hand.
This is a really good question.
You really know how to ask.
Every one of these questions is great.
She keeps staring at him (Wang Lechen).
This is also very direct.
Ask.