We're in Xinjiang.
Why isn't it moving?
Be good, sweetheart.
Turns out it's following me.
Then you have to follow me.
Now I'm the one following you.
Guess I'll have to steal you away.
Let's ride off together.
Life is a vast wilderness.
I really like you.
My heart is fluttering.
Me too.
Heart Signal Apartment
The final long-distance date is coming.
I'm definitely choosing this.
I've made up my mind.
I'll go with you.
What about these two?
Let's see what they say.
Tension's in the air.
It's time for a showdown.
Does the order of choosing matter?
I definitely won't team up with Yifan.
Then you should've just now...
...gone up first.
It's fine, you can still change now.
My suggestion is...
I hope we follow the girls' wishes.
Don't.
Here it comes.
That thing floating in the water...
What is it?
Aquatic plant.
Grass in water is called aquatic plant.
Wipe the lens.
You're good at finding things.
I think...
First, I want to state my position.
What position?
Accompany.
It feels different being together.
We're here.
When jasmine blooms, it's Heart Signal.
This show is brought to you by
Kang Sifu Moli Cha, floral and fresh.
as the title sponsor.
Xiaohongshu
Your lifestyle and interest community.
Supporting Heart Signal guests.
Xiaohongshu
Heart Signal Season Eight
Official content discussion platform.
Reshapes hair core protein from the root.
Bouncy and shiny for 72 hours.
This show is sponsored by
the new Pantene Shengtai Paodan Series.
as a sponsor.
Thanks to our imaging experience officer.
Huawei nova 14 series phones.
Full-range red maple portrait texture.
Capturing your Heart Signal moments.
Quick repair in two hours.
Three days to fight "late-night fatigue."
This show is sponsored by
Estée Lauder 7th Generation Little Brown Bottle.
as a sponsor.
Smart upgrade, Heart Signal heats up.
This show is sponsored by
Smart experience, fully upgraded.
The new Lynk 07.
Lynk 08.
as a sponsor.
Fades dark circles.
Eyes with a natural micro-current.
Brightens overnight.
Heart Signal beats.
This show is sponsored by
Wanmei Hongbi Eye Cream as sponsor.
This is the world's
sweetest social observation reality show.
Kang Sifu Moli Cha Heart Signal
Season Eight.
Welcome, everyone.
It's another week.
Welcome back, Minghao.
Minghao.
Let's share
what happened last week.
Shall we?
Leyuan couple is sweet as can be.
That cliffside confession.
The one picking flowers.
Then shouting "I like you."
So sweet.
The whole world was just the two of them.
Yeah.
It's totally
a "couple's" daily life.
But when traveling,
they talk about everything.
Actually, you get more sparks.
Yes, that's possible.
It could happen.
Because it's not that
being together
is best done by
traveling.
Right.
Because in this process,
everyone's lifestyle
and way of expressing
Yifan and Yuxing.
Their
date scene looked great.
It was raining.
Watching a movie outdoors.
But what they talked about
was really a bit off.
They even said it was a "trial."
Yeah.
The date wasn't really
pleasant.
But Zihan and Chichi,
you can feel
every time Zihan is with Chichi,
their time together
is truly high quality.
Yes, definitely.
Absolutely.
Minghao, soon
the new week is coming.
The new week is coming.
Is there anyone
whose story you're looking forward to?
Or do you think
Xiaofang and Rulan should
will
develop even better.
It's the final
push time.
Final push.
Yeah.
So let's look forward to it together.
Let's watch together, shall we?
Okay.
Alright, next
I'm also curious
after everyone meets up,
what stories will unfold.
Everyone, our Heart Signal stories
begin now.
Let's go.
Where is this?
Qiandao Lake.
Near Hangzhou.
What did you do today?
Drove.
Drove all day.
From there,
drove to here.
Drove to here.
What about you guys?
Where did you come from?
Take a guess.
I can't guess.
I went into a "movie."
In a movie?
What do you mean?
A movie in the rain.
Is that really how you'd describe it?
No, it's real.
Really.
It's not just a nice description,
the place was actually recreated.
It's that Miyazaki style.
Where is it?
A cherry blossom valley.
That sounds nice.
But there are no cherry blossoms now.
Can we start eating now?
Everyone, let's dig in.
We had a heavy rain last night.
We were watching a movie.
Which movie did you watch?
"Begin Again: Meeting You in New York"
Meeting You
We watched it during the rain.
Was it at a theater?
No, just a projector.
That's how it was.
There was a screen.
Just the two of you?
His long-distance date
A misunderstanding in choices
Still hasn't been cleared up
She (Sun Hanqing) still doesn't know
why Yuxing didn't come.
Let's each share one thing.
The happiest activity here
If I had to pick the happiest
Maybe watching a movie on a rainy day
It really was.
No matter when it happens,
it's a rare experience.
Teacher Jin taught me
many life lessons.
How did Yifan start calling Yuxing
Teacher Jin?
When did you start calling me Teacher Jin?
She just called you Teacher Jin.
I heard it and thought, "Who is that?"
I think it's because they talked it out.
So the way they address each other changed.
But from Chichi's perspective,
sometimes secret nicknames between two people
can make others feel a bit jealous.
It can.
Makes you wonder if there's something between you two.
Right, because she totally
doesn't know the backstory.
She doesn't know Yuxing and Yifan talked it out.
Yeah.
Today we went to
the top of the mountain, the view was nice.
What kind of view?
Rolling hills and peaks.
Well, not that dramatic.
Not that exaggerated.
Just
I think it's about right.
Small peaks lined up one after another.
Very peaceful.
Did you watch the sunrise?
No, just the blazing sun.
Just the blazing sun.
Got sunburned, you know?
Already
went for a "tan."
Yeah, went for a tan.
Did he (Zihan) notice
that Chichi's
mood was a bit down?
So he tried to lighten the mood.
Yes.
But I'm thinking about something.
If you were Yuxing,
would you want to use this chance
to just tell everyone
the order of the profile stickers last time?
Would Chichi then know
that you had
a reason for not coming?
Yeah.
But that's not possible.
I think he'll definitely
find a private moment.
So,
what fun things are there at the hotel?
Other stuff.
A place to sing.
Yeah, and there's a barbecue grill.
Barbecue grill.
And a "Top of the World" spot.
Top of the World
The highest point.
Do you have to walk up there?
Yes, you do.
But at night,
you probably can't see much, right?
If you want to see, you'll always find something.
That line
What's up with that?
Now even the way I talk
I talk like that too.
Same style.
Yeah, I've been influenced.
Gotta think about what it really means.
No, that line
is only true in a different setting.
The important things can't be seen with your eyes.
Yeah.
You have to see with your heart.
That spot
is just for enjoying the atmosphere.
This kind of talk
is for those who get it.
What made you happiest?
Night tour of Nanxun Ancient Town.
Why?
First, I'd never been there before.
And also,
I had a great chat with Duoduo on the boat.
We really had a good time talking.
It's the people that matter.
Yeah.
What about Dr. Fang?
Had a late-night snack last night.
It was fun.
Was it the buying process that was fun?
Or the eating part?
The process was fun too.
Eating was also fun.
Last night's snack was great.
Taking photos was fun too.
What did you eat for the snack
to be so happy?
A whole lot.
A lot.
Ice cream, ribs,
local yuanxiao tangyuan,
and more.
I think this trip
made up for regrets.
We split into islands back then.
And many hadn't been to the islands.
I think it made up for
those travel regrets.
After this trip,
the experience in the cabin
was truly
very complete.
Let's go for a walk.
Let's go.
How was today?
It was pretty fun.
Tonight, we can really have a good talk.
We really can have a deep talk.
Slow down.
Okay.
So, next is...
Right.
It's what we just talked about.
That place for singing.
So beautiful.
Barbecue.
Is there a late-night snack too?
This is...
You sing, I'll grill.
Then we grill, and they sing.
Sure.
I can grill too.
I can join you guys.
Then the three of us will grill.
Is it this one?
Yes.
It's this one.
When you brush it, move it to the side.
Right.
What should we sing?
"Encounter" works.
Feels like we all know "Encounter."
Let's listen.
Yifan, try this one.
Okay.
Let's order this then.
Fan it a bit farther from the fire.
Otherwise, the fire won't calm down.
This one's burnt again.
Let me do it.
You three are so "funny."
Grilling so seriously.
All for you to eat.
It's burnt.
I just put it on and it burned.
The fire's too strong.
Sing a song.
Sing.
Pick one we can all sing.
Let's do a Phoenix Legend song.
Come on.
Everyone knows this one.
I know it.
Come on.
What's this?
"Above the Moon."
It really is Phoenix Legend.
I just said let's do one.
Phoenix Legend song.
Someone with the same taste as me.
So catchy.
This song is perfect for gatherings.
Great for getting hyped.
I'm gazing far away.
Above the moon.
Too high.
Yesterday forgotten.
I only know these two lines.
So stylish.
Brother Herry (Liu Zihan)
Awesome.
You're really awesome.
Let's sit for a while.
Those two are so natural.
They just end up sitting close together.
How bad is your singing, really?
I'll sing for you sometime.
Embarrassing in public.
In front of so many people.
It's fine to be embarrassed.
How was your day?
Not great.
Because I didn't know what you guys did.
I didn't see you today.
I wondered what you did today.
"Help!"
Actually, that word is important.
Very important.
That word unlocked
all of Dr. Fang's worries.
Right.
I didn't see you today.
I wondered what you did today.
I was thinking as soon as I left
what you all were doing.
Because weren't we
three people coming together?
But when we left, it was just two.
Who told you to text on day one?
Sorry.
It's fine now.
Next time.
I'll be the fastest at everything next time.
And those two can't help
but smile when they look at each other.
Right.
See?
They have this
really good thing.
They always talk things out.
Right.
What did you do today?
How was your day today?
No overnight grudges.
She's good at showing her feelings
and affection.
Right.
So Dr. Fang doesn't have
any anxiety left.
It's all resolved.
Some are happy, some are sad.
It's complicated.
Brother Jiao.
Don't look back.
Look forward.
I think the result doesn't matter.
The process is what matters.
We think the same way.
Yifan comforted Xiao Jiao.
Because they actually feel the same.
What's this?
Come on.
I really...
You've definitely heard this. Go.
Jiao, your turn.
Go ahead, first line. Go.
You go first.
The vast horizon is where my love lies.
Flowers bloom at the foot of endless green hills.
What kind of rhythm
is the most swinging of all?
What kind of singing brings the most joy?
Curving rivers flow down from the sky.
They run to a sea of countless colors.
Fiery songs are what we look forward to.
Singing as we walk is the freest way.
If we sing, we sing with all our heart.
Come on.
The most beautiful clouds
Let me keep you here with all my heart.
Stay here.
Sing gently with the brightest ethnic style.
It's the sky's most beautiful look.
Getting hyped up!
Zihan's presence is actually pretty important.
Let's pick "King of Love Songs."
Let's do a relay.
Sure.
"King of Love Songs"
You're so hard to forget.
Drifting in and out of my heart.
Your turn.
How do you sing this part?
How much courage does it take to change?
That sounds right.
Churning feelings
How do I calm them down?
Let's do "Heart Too Soft."
Heart too soft.
How do you sing it?
Carry all the problems alone.
Falling in love is always easy.
Getting along is too hard.
If it's not yours,
don't force it anymore.
Your turn.
When you get to this line,
Don't.
Take it away.
This is just too much of a coincidence.
It's a classic.
Why is it those two, just by chance?
That's hilarious.
If it's not yours,
don't force it anymore.
Your turn.
Done.
Do you guys want to pick a song?
Pick a song.
See if there's a song
everyone can sing together.
Let's take a look.
It's right here.
Next, let me see.
What can we sing?
Next.
Is it a Jay Chou song?
Everyone knows those.
Probably.
Right?
But Jay Chou's songs
I think Jay Chou's songs are tough.
It's fine.
Feels too high.
Or maybe JJ Lin.
Jay Chou.
Or maybe someone like Zhang Jie.
Sure.
This is...
This one's nice too.
Is this one too sad?
Way too sad.
That's it.
What kind of man is that?
This line also feels...
"When You"
We can sing this together.
Go ahead.
When your eyes squint with a smile,
When you say it's late and you can't sleep,
I want to tell you
but I'm afraid I'll say it wrong.
I really like you, do you know?
Thinking too much.
Back to bed.
We'll meet in dreams.
Without any hesitation.
Say it out loud.
I want to say
When your eyes squint with a smile,
When you say it's late and you can't sleep,
I want to tell you
but I'm afraid I'll say it wrong.
I really like you, do you know?
Come on, sing.
Are you charged up, Zihan?
Go ahead.
A little bit charged.
Let's switch songs then.
Today is just a...
Sing.
A bit sad.
Don't want to sing.
I'll do it then.
Can I turn my volume up a bit more?
Really, Yuxing has to find a chance to say it.
But I'm also wondering
if she's waiting for Yuxing
to explain something to her.
Looks like you really enjoy singing too.
Yeah, I go wild singing in the karaoke room.
I'm a "mic hog."
Yeah.
I know every song.
But I sing every one badly.
No.
I think you sing pretty well.
What's the next song?
It's "Soy Milk and Fried Dough Sticks."
No.
"Soy Milk and Fried Dough Sticks"
Why did Zihan leave?
Look at his angle.
How is he up there?
I'll go up and check.
Okay.
Go take a look.
Alright.
It's so hard, not easy at all.
Really.
Rarely see Zihan like this.
Zihan bro
Really all alone
at the Top of the World
Top of the World
Do you want to sit for a bit?
Let me
Okay
Thanks
Your spot here
is amazing
A bit risky
The riskier the place,
the safer it feels
True
This is a good place to think
When I really
enjoy a moment
I get scared it will
disappear in a flash
and slip away
Yeah, so I tend to
go up and down
Right, like now
I'm at a low again
Because I just felt so happy
But it doesn't feel real
Me too
I think the happier the time,
the more it hides
a cliff-like, sudden goodbye
Yeah
So now I want to
record it from a third-person view
Lanlan probably sensed
Zihan's
mood today
They're friends
It's so quiet here
Right?
Nice view too
Why are you suddenly here?
I just told Zihan bro
We feel
a lot of things
at first, maybe
you're immersed in a happy place
but you need a moment
to step back
Have you figured out
your feelings these days?
Have you decided?
I asked you first
I don't know
That answer
Not many days left
Final sprint
Yeah
Let's go, let's head down
Because there really aren't many days left
I hope everyone can
in this final sprint
find the right moment
to say what you want
and do what you want
get it all done
That's more important than anything
Honestly, I want to hold it in
Yuxing should find a chance
to talk to Chichi
and express himself
They need some alone time
He wants to give her space too
He doesn't want her
to feel too pressured
Right
Come on
Let's keep watching
Xinjiang
What time did you sleep yesterday?
Slept from three to five, couldn't sleep after
You really didn't sleep
I did, three to five is still sleep
You know last night
I dreamed all night
Me too, all night
Really?
Really
My dream last night was so complex
I can't even explain it
Did you dream of each other?
I had so many dreams in a row
I kept dreaming, one after another, all night
If you're tired, I'll get that
capsule for you
No big deal
Don't be like that
Even being tired now feels happy
Not tired anymore
I feel for you
What's the use of feeling for me?
I don't want your sympathy
Today I feel reborn
It was too late last night, so I didn't look for you
I could only look at your light
Let's review
Otherwise, it's still unresolved
Come on
So after you thought about it yesterday,
what was your conclusion?
What did they do yesterday?
So your previous long-distance was three years?
How did you handle it?
I went to visit every week.
Darn it, I spent
more of my time so we could
be together as much as possible.
Long-distance really comes with more
challenges and difficulties.
That's true.
It's the issue of long-distance.
It's actually a pretty big problem.
It's just...
Are you willing
to spend time and energy
to try, or
to work things out with the other person?
Right?
Would you accept the other person's efforts?
I would.
It depends on
your mindset and the other person's attitude.
Some people
might not be able to accept your way of working things out.
Some people just
can't figure it out.
That happens sometimes.
You probably haven't faced this before.
I've never done long-distance.
Are you studying for two years or three?
Three years.
So, three years.
You still have three years left.
So right now,
you're still open to long-distance?
She wants an answer.
How should I put it...
Because it's been a long time
since I did long-distance.
But
I know what long-distance feels like.
Because you
aren't really part of the other person's life.
A lot of things, you still
project your own ideas
onto the relationship.
But how things really are for each person,
only you truly know.
It depends on how well you work things out.
So you still can't accept it?
Is that what you mean?
She still cares about this answer.
I'm not saying whether I can accept it
the long-distance thing.
Because if you just look at this one thing,
it's too vague.
Even if I say I can accept it now,
what happens in the future
none of us can predict.
What I mean is,
after this phase ends,
can you accept it then?
It depends on how things work out.
She didn't get the answer she wanted.
I don't want you to struggle internally.
And I don't want you to
deny certain things because of this.
All I can say is,
I'll do my best, but
how it actually turns out,
I can only
follow my conscience.
Yeah.
So it's still possible, right?
She still wants to be sure.
Yes.
What should I do?
Lu Yuan wants
to confirm if Le Chen
can accept a long-distance relationship.
And Le Chen's attitude
is just
to work things out.
But you know, maybe I
I know you can't promise.
It's not that I can't promise, I mean
I don't want you, in this role,
to feel the same pain again.
But when you're thinking about it,
you can just think about your own feelings.
You don't have to think about me.
It's hard for me.
Hard for you to what?
It's hard for me to do that.
So do you still need
more time to think?
Or do you already have an answer?
The two "little selves" are fighting.
Let me have a moment later.
When I get off, I need to be alone
for a bit longer.
How's your "little self" battle going?
Thanks for your effort.
It's not hard.
Life is tough.
Wang Le Chen.
Is it really that hard to be brave?
For you?
It's not hard. What's hard is
how to accept it.
Do you not trust me, or yourself?
That's actually our biggest difference.
I still don't get it.
Get some rest.
It's tough for both of us.
Honestly, what I'm thinking now is
if what you're worried about
like long-distance,
in my view, maybe
it's not that
three years will definitely change things.
I mean, the way you act
I just don't care
how this relationship goes,
what the outcome is,
or what the process is.
I hope you always
take responsibility for yourself.
Whatever you do should
follow your own heart.
I won't do things I'll regret.
And don't do anything just because
you feel you have to compromise.
I hope you never do that.
I won't. This is my choice.
These are all things my choice brings
and what I have to bear.
So when you're thinking about it,
You don't have to think about it.
How I'm feeling.
Of course I have to consider it.
How could I not think about it?
Then you should
just think about it a little.
Don't overthink it.
I can't just think about it a little.
Because for me,
this is a really important thing.
It's important to me too.
I kept thinking about today all last night.
Let's calm down first, and then
I think what's more important is
when we're offline,
or after this is over,
we can really get to know each other.
Actually, for you,
your understanding of me
I can only say it's maybe
twenty percent.
Twenty or thirty, yeah.
Twenty or thirty.
I'm also someone who
doesn't want any relationship
to be completely
without knowing the other person
and just start it so easily.
And I think that
if you start without knowing each other,
it's careless to begin a relationship.
It's really irresponsible to both people.
That's why I haven't started anything.
Because I prefer the kind
where both people get to know each other
and then focus and commit
to building a relationship.
I don't want to rush into it.
So I think the main thing is
really,
if we're serious about this,
I truly think the experiences
we've had in the cabin
set the bar pretty high.
Can't start high and end low, right?
Right.
Because that would be a big letdown.
But what I worried about before was
you might not want to keep going
after the cabin is over.
That's not true.
I never meant that at all.
Yesterday, I thought that's what you meant.
No.
Maybe I didn't express myself well.
You really did
Maybe yesterday you were asking
with that question in mind,
so my answers came out that way.
So you didn't get
what I meant.
Apologies.
Sorry.
I'll bow to you later.
Alright, I'm happy now.
I thought you understood.
No.
It's good we talked it out.
The weather's better today than yesterday.
Thanks to your good mood.
We had to talk it through.
Otherwise, I'd have held it in all night.
Could stir up a storm anytime.
Scared me to death.
This was a sudden moment
of drama on our trip.
It's a long-distance thing.
This question
I think it's good to talk about it
This is something that must come up
in a relationship between two people
that you have to face and deal with
I think it's because
this "trial romance trip"
gave the two of them a chance
to spend time together privately
and put this issue
on the table to solve
in a space like this
From what I heard
in that conversation just now
maybe at first, Luyuan asked
if you could accept a long-distance relationship
and when
Lechen couldn't give
a definite answer
Luyuan might take it as
this is something that's doomed to fail
But just like in that talk
Luyuan actually understood Lechen meant
to wait until after the cabin experience
and see how they get along
before making a decision
And I think because of their age gap
they're truly at different life stages
One has to work
and the other is going to Beijing for grad school
So the questions she asks
and what she cares about are different
Yuan just wants to be sure
But Lechen
maybe based on
some practical concerns
says they need to adjust
and see how things go in reality
That's true
Long-distance relationships really are
something you need to plan for
It's not like this time
with the "trial romance trip"
where you just go on a whim
For example, you need a plan
to meet once a month
for how long
and where, and so on
This really needs
planning and communication
Yes, I agree with you
In this "trial romance trip"
we saw the distance from attraction
to commitment
In real life
it also starts with a spark
but you have to go through a process
before you can make a commitment
and be sure the other is the one
Before, this process
was invisible to us
But this time, because of the "trial romance trip"
we got to see it
and discuss it ahead of time
Because in the cabin's pure romance setting
usually
this doesn't really come up
It's usually about
values
or what kind of relationship you like
still stuck in the dating context
But this is actually about real life
focusing on reality
and the problems you might face
That's the meaning of the trip
Are we riding?
Give me a ride
Let's go
I'll take you
for a spin
We should be able to drive a big loop
Sure
For you
You should pull it tight
It might get a bit fast
Wang "Takumi"
What you said
Wait, I'll tighten it a bit
Tie it tight, in case it flips
Then I couldn't escape
You just can't escape
Can't escape his grasp
Wang Lechen, I hate you
You hate me?
Let's see, where to drive
Circle around over there
Awesome
We can try this too
Feels like my face is shaking
Awesome
Give us a direction, "Captain"
Straight ahead
Go
Lechen turns right on purpose
Turn right
A deliberate right turn
Turning right, the force comes here
They're so happy
Careful
See, another right turn
Refreshing.
Covered in grass.
Feels like I have grass in my mouth.
Will you look at me?
Look in the mirror.
Just keep it on.
Here, this part of yours—
Your crown is really flat, see?
The crown is flat.
How did it get like this?
But it's fine, really.
Don't move.
Lower your head.
You really treat me like a mirror.
Of course.
Why are you pursing your lips?
It's Heart Signal.
Like this?
Okay.
Sit.
Actually, I really like
the way they get along.
I think it's comfortable.
They've really opened up.
When you're on the grassland,
it feels so vast.
Everything else seems so small.
Yeah.
Come on, let's see
what's happening at Qiandao Lake.
Everyone is
doing something over there.
Should we head out?
Let's go.
Let's take a walk first.
Sure.
If you want—
I'll go with you.
Okay.
Alone now, hurry up.
Singing really made me
a bit tired.
Zihan is here too.
Zihan is so supportive.
We can sit over there.
There are four chairs there.
Are you sad?
Me?
I'm not sad now.
Not sad.
Singing makes me happy.
Should I say it?
Say it, it's time.
Where do I start?
You don't know where to begin?
Just start from there.
The guy should speak first now.
Right.
Because he needs to explain.
Nights like this have a gentle breeze.
Watching a movie outdoors feels nice.
Didn't you watch it?
I did, but—
It's not the same as watching with you.
Very good.
How have you been these past two days?
See, she has to ask.
These past two days,
pretty good.
How about you?
Yesterday I went to see—
Did you go to the zoo yesterday?
I really like the zoo.
I also made pizza.
I think these two days were fun.
Really?
Say it.
Just—
The topic's already here.
Can I ask?
What?
When you picked that group—
How did you choose?
See, she has to ask.
Explain it well.
This is important.
How did you choose?
Actually, at first I
chose you.
Finally.
That night,
I just looked at your order.
And then—
I took my card and put it
on that—
in the middle column of yours.
But later,
I ran into a big problem.
We discussed until
after four o'clock.
No one would give in.
Nobody wanted to compromise.
Later, I thought
if I didn't
make a sacrifice,
maybe it couldn't be solved.
Yeah.
It was already morning by then.
Sad character.
Now I'm one more.
Are you someone who sticks to yourself?
Depends on the situation.
Depends on what it is.
When you do
what you want to do,
do you
stick to your own ideas?
Not always, I can be
pretty influenced by others.
He didn't get what the girl wanted to hear.
They're not on the same page.
Yeah.
I think
maybe one-on-one is what I want most
when I'm in a crowd
I don't really like to talk
Honestly, I've always thought you're like
the Quiet Flower we put together
What is that?
What is it?
Why?
Because
I think when the Quiet Flower is
swaying in the wind, it's
pretty quiet
But its English name is
bellflower
But it also seems like you can hear
some
echoes of bells ringing
But it still gives a very quiet
and peaceful feeling
You think I'm peaceful?
Yeah, I think it's like
swaying alone in the wind
It's very
So does that mean your view of me is pretty
just
My previous understanding was quite
one-sided
Actually, she feels she doesn't know him yet
But what do you think you are like?
I think I'm like a sunflower
Sunflower
We've always been positive
positive
never give up
growing toward the sun
chatting
Doesn't a sunflower have
seeds?
He's as abstract as ever
Doesn't a sunflower have
seeds?
easy to snack on
Thanks
Another lame joke
You've cried yourself out
You're hurt too deeply
Why does it feel like every song chosen
has something they want to say
instead of just picking a song
You've cried yourself out
You're hurt too deeply
You've loved too foolishly
Feels like up to now
we haven't talked much
I think we've talked quite a lot
But it feels like our conversations
the depth of understanding
is kind of
pretty shallow
That's true
The pace is a bit slow
Yeah
A little
feeling
Before, you
I think before, you were
just
a green train
"clank"
What does that mean?
And sometimes you have to
add some coal
pull that lever
I think you're describing yourself
Really
I'm not that bad
I've already
I've gotten so anxious I knocked on your door
Yeah, so sometimes you
go "beep"
and then smoke comes out
I've really
gotten so anxious I knocked on your door
And you still call me a green train
Then you're the Brave Train Hero, okay?
To be honest
I really like Brave Train Hero
But right now
mentioning Brave Train Hero
isn't great
Then you're the Brave Train Hero, okay?
The smile disappeared
See, she doesn't even want to reply
That sigh
We really can't keep talking
Do you think
is feeling more important or is getting along more important?
Good, that's a great question
I think
both feeling and getting along
are pretty important
But
feeling is a bit more important
Genius is ninety-nine percent sweat
plus one percent inspiration
I think that one percent inspiration
is more important than ninety-nine percent sweat
more important
Do you think in relationships
this saying applies too?
Yes
I think for two people to get along
you need that one percent feeling
plus ninety-nine percent getting along
First comes the feeling, then getting along
becomes smoother
and you really click
What do you think?
Of course
Of course, both are important
But getting along is also important
I think my sense of security is pretty low
Actually, I think
what you need is
more encouragement and companionship
Right?
I really need encouragement
and companionship
Their vibe also makes me
feel a bit uncomfortable watching
It's uncomfortable for everyone
They're not on the same wavelength.
They're not in sync.
Each is talking past the other.
Maybe if she hears
how hard he's trying
to make this happen,
she might feel a bit better.
Yeah.
Right now, it just feels like
it's not that clear.
It's too understated.
Chichi has already shared
her pain points with him.
She basically handed it to him,
asking him to explain.
But Yuxing just skipped over it.
His abstract way right now
I think it's
not the kind that makes people happy.
Chichi keeps hoping for Yuxing.
But time after time,
he doesn't give her that satisfaction.
This whole conversation
is honestly just
so worrying.
It's concerning.
So Chichi might slowly
pull her feelings back.
Don't we have any happy songs?
What do you want to sing?
Let's do a cheerful one.
Sure.
Let's sing something upbeat.
You want to sing
what kind of happy song?
In this cold, unfeeling city,
at these modern, decadent parties,
whenever the guitar noise starts up again,
That's impressive.
This group
is the "No Company Quartet."
Where did you go?
I went up to change clothes.
Then I saw Lanlan and Dr. Fang off.
Singing really is wonderful.
Music truly is a great thing.
I see you guys are still singing.
Is it possible the three of us
are more alike?
Sad people see sadness in others.
Sadness.
But really, there aren't any sad people.
We're just
just
sharing the same mood.
Yeah.
Is there any food left?
I'm actually a bit hungry.
I'll go take a look.
I'll just check quickly.
We just grilled a lot of food.
We can bring it all out.
Ouch, that hurts.
Don't leave just yet.
Let me do it.
It's "battered and bruised" every day.
You.
Me.
Yeah.
Each other, I guess.
I don't.
You don't.
No.
I think I'm sure of my feelings.
And I feel like my challenge
was completed really well.
I think I did great.
One hundred percent.
That's a fact.
Real barbecue.
Did you see that fire?
I think we still need a challenge.
To separate it out.
Just
What are you doing now?
Are you doing it with
a clear purpose?
Or do you have to get something?
Those are two different things.
I think, first of all, people are free, right?
And if you truly like someone,
the first thing is,
I want you to be happy.
If possible,
I hope we can both be happy.
Do you have any questions?
No questions.
But I'm not happy.
I think the reason you're unhappy is
You
are focused on your
sunk costs.
Your effort and investment.
You're not satisfied with yourself
and what you've done in the past,
or are you unhappy with that person
for not giving you feedback?
Those are two separate things.
No problem.
Really good.
I need feedback.
But if there's no feedback,
I start to have doubts.
I really agree with what you said.
Everyone needs feedback.
And also,
If the other person gives a little feedback,
you feel safe to invest a bit more.
Yes.
I think that's fine.
Everyone has their own pace.
Some people move at
zero point two speed.
Your pace might be two point zero speed.
But the key is before,
she said she's a fast-paced person.
I think actions matter more than intentions.
I feel everyone's self-perception
isn't always accurate.
So I think
you can't use what someone says
as a
reference standard.
You should go by what you feel
as your reference.
Right.
So maybe this
side glance
is so cute.
I really think having
a friend like Duoduo
is amazing.
Really.
So nice.
Duoduo actually opened up
from that moment before.
If she hadn't opened up,
she couldn't say these things.
Maybe romance didn't happen,
but at least there's friendship gained.
Yes.
Can we leave this place?
Can we go back for a walk?
Let's go.
We're a bit cold.
Let's go back and sit for a while.
Okay.
When you're done,
we can take it back to eat.
Yeah.
All good.
Sure.
You go ahead, yes.
You go.
Thank you.
I understand.
Why do I just want to stay in the living room?
It's hard for people to control
their facial expressions.
When you receive
a lot of negative emotions from others,
do you become negative yourself?
No.
Then your self-healing ability
is pretty good.
Yeah, my healing ability is strong.
I'm good at healing myself.
You know, I cut my hand.
I just cut it yesterday.
Today it's already healed.
My body is like that too.
My mind and body are the same.
Yeah, my mental and physical strength are both strong.
One person.
Duoduo isn't just good at self-healing.
She heals others well too.
Alright.
It's over.
Food's ready.
Let's go.
I feel really happy.
We did so much tonight.
Sang songs, grilled meat, and chatted.
See you tomorrow.
Alright, see you tomorrow.