Surfing now.
Life needs that one brave step.
Just like a family of three.
Yeah.
Careful.
It's hard to remember every single day.
Today I'm a happy kid.
So sweet.
Welcome to my turf.
This is so fun.
Today I fulfilled
a little dream I always wanted.
So much fun.
So sweet.
A princess carry in the air.
I'm a strong person.
But sometimes you don't have to be so strong.
Then next time I'll come to you and cry.
I can't take it anymore.
I've never seen Initial D.
What's Initial D?
Generation gap.
I'll go home and do my homework tonight, okay?
I'm glad you like it.
Today was really happy.
I just want to smile when I see you.
Do I look that funny?
Not funny.
You're good-looking.
See, did I miss more times
or did you miss more times?
Sure.
How does it feel to lose?
Ride the mini-train with me.
We played it safe.
Every time you
hit the spot where I jump.
Smooth sailing.
Everything goes well.
When jasmine blooms, it's a heartbeat signal.
This program is brought to you by
Kang Shifu Jasmine Tea, with floral aroma and fresh taste.
as the title sponsor.
Go to Xiaohongshu
to support your favorite couple.
Xiaohongshu
Heartbeat Signal Season 8
Official content discussion platform.
Restructures hair protein from the roots.
Elastic and shiny for 72 hours.
This program is sponsored by
the upgraded Pantene Peptide Bubble Series.
Sponsored broadcast.
Thanks to our imaging experience officer,
Huawei nova 14 series phones.
Full focal range, maple-inspired portrait quality.
Capture your heartbeat moments.
2-hour rapid repair.
3-day anti-fatigue from staying up late.
This program is sponsored by
Estée Lauder Advanced Night Repair, 7th generation.
Sponsored broadcast.
Smarter upgrade, warmer heartbeat.
This program is sponsored by
the fully upgraded smart experience
with the new Lynk & Co 07
and Lynk & Co 08.
Sponsored broadcast.
Reduces dark circles.
Gives your eyes a microcurrent effect.
Brightens overnight.
Heartbeat pounding.
This program is sponsored by
Marubi Little Red Pen Eye Cream.
This is the world's
sweetest
social observation reality show.
Kang Shifu Jasmine Tea Heartbeat Signal.
Season 8, here we come!
It's another week.
I really feel like
after my first time here,
I couldn't sleep well.
I think there's an "occupational hazard" here.
I'm always thinking about him and her,
or him and her.
He loves her.
But she doesn't love him.
But he still loves her.
Last night I kept singing a song.
It's David Tao's "Love Me or Him."
So next,
let's do a quick recap.
Which moments
made us feel
truly unforgettable?
Jiao
made it snow in summer.
Like Dr. Fang
and our Lanlan,
the two of them
are already getting close.
I think
the motorcycle scene
that moment
really was
just
stuck in our minds.
It replayed for at least three nights.
That was so romantic.
What about you?
For me, it's Lechen and
Duoduo.
With Duoduo, I just feel
why worry about
things that
aren't even problems?
It's like they're trying to prevent arguments.
We might
never face those issues.
Why assume them in advance?
I think it's such a pity.
Their argument
made me feel like
maybe
having a crush
and being a good match might really be
two different things.
Yeah.
But with Chi Chi,
I think there's more suspense.
Chi Chi and Yu Xing,
and Chi Chi with Zihan,
their group seems
the least predictable.
It's the hardest to tell.
Last week's date
really was
like a roller coaster.
The whole date
process
had its ups and downs.
It felt like a real emotional ride.
This week's story
is about to begin.
Let's see what
Heartbeat Apartment
will bring
inspiring new stories.
Looking forward to it.
Are you making a soup?
Yeah, just a soup and that's it.
Are you following a recipe on the spot?
I never memorized any recipes.
I just cook based on what we have.
You're a natural talent.
Really?
Yeah.
You're putting pressure on me.
I'll make a stew later.
I'll stir-fry some green beans.
Alright.
Have you ever ridden the mini-train?
No.
How about we go check it out now?
Chi Chi.
Hi.
Hello.
Did you just get back?
Yeah.
Them.
Us, them.
Herry is cooking.
He made Mapo Tofu again.
Smells so good.
Did you eat yet?
No.
You haven't?
Did you guys eat?
Not yet.
No.
Then let's go first.
So you came down to
welcome you.
That's really great.
You can open the kitchen door over there now.
Can I open it?
Yes, you can.
Who came back?
Take a guess.
Chi Chi.
Did you hear that?
I didn't hear.
Is it Chi Chi?
Yeah.
Chi Chi.
What's up?
Look at that expression.
Did they open the door over there?
Yeah, it's open.
I want to learn how to make egg rolls.
Okay.
We're making Tom Yum soup.
I want some.
No problem.
It'll be ready soon.
What?
Then I'll go cook over there.
Feels like the vibe is a bit off.
Seems like the mood from last time in the car is still here.
You guys have nothing to eat tonight.
We'll send some food over from our side.
No way, we really have nothing.
There's no one on your side now.
Really?
Yeah.
I just opened it, didn't I?
Yeah, just opened the door.
Yeah, you're the first to open it over there, babe.
Here comes someone useless.
No need to look back.
No.
Can you chop vegetables?
I can.
Then you can
Just
go over there and cut this into
Strips, right?
Put it in the soup.
Half for each person.
Cut into strips.
Yeah.
Just
Because the cutting board here
Or never mind.
I'll cut this first.
Then do the other thing.
It's fine, I can go cut it over there too.
It's okay.
I'll cut this first.
I can slice the salmon.
Let me do it.
Thick slices—do you prefer thick or thin?
Thick.
Thick slices.
Alright, let's do that.
You went to work today.
How did you know?
You told me today.
Who told you?
You did.
I told you?
I’m going back to Yiwu today.
Yeah.
You forgot, didn’t you?
I said Tuesday or Wednesday back then.
No.
No, I clearly said the ninth.
Right.
Okay, so that’s it.
You remembered wrong.
No, I didn’t.
It’s my own schedule.
How could I get it wrong?
You’re kind of funny.
Their vibe is totally different.
So when did you get back?
I got back about fifteen minutes before you.
Hi, everyone.
Ruilong’s here.
Hello.
You guys can...
What are you doing?
Salmon.
Salmon, yeah.
You can take it over.
Okay.
Seasoning.
Yes.
I’ll get it later.
Let me check how to make the omelette first.
Ruilong is making tamagoyaki again.
How many eggs do you usually use?
Three eggs.
Then beat them.
Whisk them.
What do you add next?
Your secret seasoning.
Right.
Hello.
You haven’t eaten yet?
No.
Not yet.
Perfect timing.
I brought fish too.
What kind?
Perch.
What do you mean?
Really? What else can you make?
I really want to order.
I don’t know.
You go first.
Let’s see what I can refuse.
Fish.
What kind?
Perch.
He noted it down.
How do you cook it?
That fish.
Steamed.
Raw.
That works too.
You ordered the fish, you chop it.
I can’t.
Aren’t you good at helping out?
Alright.
I’ll chop it.
I thought you meant I’d cook it.
You don’t even need my help for this.
Don’t you wash things pretty well?
Then just watch from the side.
Cheer me on.
Go for it!
Sounds like a couple talking.
If it’s too hard, just steam the whole fish.
Steaming is fine too.
How do you want to cook it?
Braised.
Then just steam the whole fish.
I’ll get you a plate.
There’s one here.
There’s a big one over there.
Because it’s the middle part.
I’ve already peeled off the outside.
No, you need to peel this.
Show it to Lechen.
The inside looks a bit like the outside.
Just pick out the good parts.
Yeah, just pick out the good ones.
Can I give it a try?
Sure.
I’ll go over there.
Impressive.
You need to pay attention to this.
When it finishes rolling to the edge,
you can lift it up and wrap it in.
I know.
Right.
You can try it.
Then you can lift it up.
Hello, everyone.
Hi.
Smells so good.
What are we making?
We’re learning Rui Long’s egg rolls.
Do you want to try?
Rui Long’s mini class.
Egg roll.
Staring.
That look.
Very direct.
Xiao Yuan, do you want to try one?
I’ll give it a shot.
Go ahead.
Okay.
Put it in first.
Lift up the egg.
Lift the egg.
Lift this egg.
Yes, lift it.
So it can go underneath.
Got it.
Thank you, Teacher Rui.
Duo Duo is here.
Egg roll?
Yes.
Alright.
Next time, roll it in.
Okay.
Is Duo Duo watching Le Chen?
Yes.
This needs to be filled.
That’s right.
Yes.
Let me handle this.
Finish the last layer.
Okay.
This one’s done.
Wang Jue, go try it.
I’ll give it a try.
Yes, you try it.
Alright, I’ll try.
Next.
Let’s line up to try this.
How’s it going?
Still ended up in pieces.
Are you making braised or steamed?
Steamed.
Alright.
Did you try?
What?
This one.
No.
Let’s line up and try.
Braised is fine too.
Do you like braised?
I eat steamed.
Me.
No picking, just steamed.
No picking, it’s steamed.
You don’t know how to braise, right?
I do.
Steamed.
Steamed tastes good.
Are we eating together?
That works.
What are we making?
Green pepper fish head?
Sashimi.
So good at hiding your skills.
Duo Duo still cares a lot.
Just like Duo Duo said before,
if you don’t
clearly say no to me,
I won’t let go.
That’s her personality.
It's ready, let's eat together.
Food tastes better when we eat together.
Yeah, it's tastier with more people.
Bring the rice over.
Should I carry the rice over?
Take this.
I'll carry this then.
It's hot.
It's a bit heavy.
Let's go over there.
Looks like they're almost done over there.
Put it in the middle.
Here.
Liu Zihan, teacher.
Piece of cake.
Your other three dishes
look a bit overshadowed now.
They're kind of losing their shine.
True.
Here.
Looks amazing.
I should really take photos with my phone every day.
Use a bowl for the soup.
Sure.
Hand it to me.
I'll give each of you a little.
Let me do it.
Uh...
You sit down.
Okay.
Let me do something.
Otherwise, I really have nothing to do.
Alright.
It's rare for me to cook.
Show some support.
That's true.
This...
I put my whole heart into this.
Used everything I had in the fridge.
Let the chef try it first.
Eat.
I want corn and luncheon meat.
Corn.
Sit here.
Sit way over on the edge.
I want to eat but I also don't.
Just a little rice.
Mixing Mapo tofu again.
Is the fish ready?
The fish is ready.
Time to add another dish.
This fish—
The grand finale is always the best.
It looks great.
Try it.
At this moment, Duoduo still doesn’t know
the bass was ordered by Lu Yuan.
It’s so delicious.
This is really my first time making bass.
Tastes good.
He made the fish for Lu Yuan.
The first time is always the tastiest.
This fish tastes like fish.
Right?
Very fresh.
Your compliment just now was so genuine.
Full of warmth, one hundred percent.
It’s not about saying it tastes good.
It’s like saying this chicken tastes like chicken.
Does this fish taste like fish?
Then this beef is pretty beefy too.
Nice, dinner and a comedy show.
Let’s go.
Their romantic dinner is a prize from the sports event.
Yeah.
Another rainy day walk, my favorite.
So you’re in a good mood today.
The air after the rain is so fresh.
Don’t you think?
Take a few more breaths.
Once we walk out this road,
outside should be
pretty nice too.
It’s quite close.
Yeah.
We’ll be there as soon as we step out.
They must be enjoying their meal.
Yeah.
This is so cute.
Nicole, who put that little clip on you?
Cute.
So cute.
Little strawberry.
The four of them are having so much fun.
They’re really enjoying the food.
Hello.
You four actually came back.
We’re full.
Full.
Why are there only three?
Where’s Jiao Ge?
He’s moving.
Moving.
Where’s Xiao Jiao moving to?
So let’s do this.
What’s this?
That’s the room swap card.
Room change privilege card.
I don’t want it.
My sleep quality won’t let me switch.
I need to be on the second floor.
Thanks.
So Xiao Jiao can move over.
Because they’re all on the second floor.
Xiao Jiao isn’t there.
Moving.
He’s coming to join you.
He’s joining you now.
Great roommate.
You’ve got a roommate now.
Ruilong, you’ll be living alone.
I’ll be living alone.
I want to go check on him.
Before he leaves,
The friendships in the house are really strong.
Back.
Ruilong.
How’s it going?
Let’s chat.
Maybe we should
have a final talk.
Chat a bit.
I’ve made up my mind today.
I’m purposely leaving some things behind.
Then I’ll come move a bit each day.
He’s so funny.
I’m really a bit reluctant.
Heard you’re moving.
Packing up.
So what’s that about?
It’s for you to pick a room, right?
Yeah.
Take your luggage up first.
Go check out your bed.
He’s helping him carry it.
You can take a look around.
He’s welcoming him.
Thank you.
Come on.
Welcome to your new home.
It’s all about fate, right?
The one from the dinner.
Did we meet too late, or just in time?
Didn’t expect that.
Really didn’t expect it.
How do you feel about this side?
At least now I understand how I feel.
Yeah, it really can only...
It’s just a feeling.
It really is.
You only realize after experiencing it.
Isn’t that a good thing for you?
I’m starting to feel something.
It should be Lu Yuan.
Lu Yuan.
That’s right.
Is he going to write today’s little card?
The little gift he gives every day.
Pure Love Warrior.
No.
You...
You can’t look at this.
That thing...
This is a remote control.
Remote for what?
It was that day...
A gift I prepared.
Yeah, that day.
Prepared one that day.
A gift for her.
During dinner.
It can be controlled remotely.
I set up a snow machine outside.
Making snow.
And it’s remote-controlled.
His expression.
He made a snow machine for her.
Yeah.
Park.
Outside the dining window.
Don’t laugh at me.
I’m not laughing, you’re just so romantic.
Alright, I need to hurry.
Are you giving it now?
Or later?
Now.
It’s close by.
The good thing is, he can give it first.
Hello.
I was just about to open the door.
I heard something outside.
Do you want to go out?
No, I’m just alone.
And you’re all in pairs.
I heard something outside and thought...
Yeah.
Now, on this floor,
everyone’s paired up.
This is for you.
Thank you.
I’m so happy.
Every night,
It’s mainly for her.
I give her snacks and stuff.
I worry she’s not eating enough.
I’ve learned something.
Learned a lot.
He really is...
It’s rare in this day and age.
Very uncommon.
Really rare.
To have such determination.
He’ll succeed at anything.
Yeah.
I’m coming in.
Okay.
I brought you Kang Shifu Jasmine Tea.
Low sugar.
Take a sip and relax.
Thanks.
I was just looking for something to drink.
Jasmine fragrance mixed with subtle tea aroma
Refreshing and soothing, really delicious
Take a sip
You instantly feel more relaxed
Let’s go work out in a bit
Soon
Okay
I want to check something
Check the wheel
Chi Chi’s
Chi Chi’s key was taken
Who?
It should be Zihan
Yeah
Zihan came back the earliest
Was it Zihan or
Yu Xing?
I think it’s Zihan
Because Zihan seems like
the type to do this
Right
By the way, let me ask
I found a secret
So it’s you, right?
So it must be Zihan
Yu Xing, did you see
who took the card?
I didn’t see
Yu Xing really seems clueless
What thing?
The key
What key?
It’s not him either
When?
Chi Chi’s key
You didn’t open it
And you don’t know who took it
This is so suspenseful
Who is it?
Probably Herry (Liu Zihan)
Who is it, really?
This is tough
I think it’s Zihan
I trust my first instinct
Herry (Liu Zihan)
I think it’s Yu Xing
Why, Xu Ge?
Why are you so sure it’s Yu Xing?
I don’t know, just a feeling
Just a hunch
It has to be Zihan
Because Yu Xing isn’t that proactive
If it’s Yu Xing
That would be a huge surprise
That would be wild
Here they come
They’re here
Time for the mini-train ride
Will I get lost?
I’m a bit scared I’ll get lost
Bye
Hurry up and go
I really want to know who it is
It should be Zihan
It must be Zihan
He still needs to make up for something
So you’re the one who took it
Who is it, really?
Who?
Herry (Liu Zihan)
It has to be him no matter what
I hope it’s him (Zihan)
Yu Xing
Please
I want to applaud Yu Xing
He’s awesome
Chi Chi is about to go crazy with happiness
So you’re the one who took it
So happy
So you didn’t expect it was me, right?
I really didn’t expect that
Impressive
Happy
When did you
I took it when I got back today
Yeah, I grabbed it as soon as I got off the car
Great job, Yu Xing
Action!
It's really hard to imagine.
It's truly hard to imagine.
He actually managed to adjust his frequency like he said.
He said he wanted to make adjustments.
He wanted to speed up.
Or I think he
could sense Chi Chi's confusion.
Yeah.
So should I prepare anything?
Should I bring some water?
Do we need water?
Maybe.
Is there anything else we might need?
There are quite a lot of mosquitoes over there.
There are a lot of mosquitoes.
Lots of mosquitoes.
Plenty of mosquitoes.
Should I give her something then?
I'll take a bottle of this for her first.
I'll bring her a bottle of this.
But she won't get bitten by mosquitoes.
I'll be the one getting bitten.
He's just too cute.
But very thoughtful.
Do you have a small bottle of that stuff?
That mosquito repellent.
Can I borrow it for a bit?
Yeah.
Let me borrow it first.
I'll bring it to spray for her.
Because I think
they all seemed to have it at first.
They deliberately kept everyone in the dark.
So I think I should
play along too.
So you got tricked.
Yeah, totally tricked.
Heartbeat mini-train.
This is really heart-fluttering.
Finally got to ride it.
I think Chi Chi can feel it too.
(Yu Xing) was very clear for the first time.
Yeah.
Happy.
Look how happy she is.
Just holding hands directly.
I really didn't expect it.
I truly didn't expect it.
You didn't show any sign today.
that could be noticed.
Really?
Yeah.
So it's
Is that a surprise?
Or
Or were you a bit startled?
It was quite a surprise.
I noticed it.
You can't hide the look in your eyes when you like someone.
It's true.
So caring.
Because I think what you said yesterday
wasn't really
a lot, right?
Not much.
Yeah.
I feel like
I didn't even get to know
one percent of you.
Yeah, I wasn't in a great state last night.
So I wanted to have this chance
to get to know you better.
Yu Xing is great.
I think you're a pretty calm person.
But then you said
you're not that calm.
You're actually intense.
I'm super intense.
But you didn't say why you're intense.
Then I asked you why.
And then you just
went silent, and
said, "I'm just intense."
You didn't give a reason.
You just didn't.
Just...
It's about energy, I guess.
Maybe I just
can do a lot in one day.
I don't know how intense you really are.
But
You're pretty stubborn.
Why?
How am I stubborn?
No, I'm just joking.
I just think you act tough sometimes.
Sometimes you're slow to realize things.
I'm so happy.
So who did you originally think
would open your Heartbeat Message?
I don't know.
Yu Xing has never asked so many questions before.
Yeah.
I only found out later.
I really want to
play badminton with you.
He's inviting you.
I haven't picked up a racket in two years.
Yeah, you can try it out.
See if the racket suits you.
I haven't put the grip tape on yet.
Do you know how to wrap grip tape?
I do.
Yeah.
That's impressive.
I'll do it for you.
I'll show you.
When I compliment you,
you get really happy.
Yeah.
Chi Chi is already
acting like a girl in love.
She's been smiling since she got in the car.
Smiling nonstop.
She’s kind of smitten.
I want to ask you something.
Can you still eat?
I'm asking.
No.
We have to find a court.
Is there going to be a next date?
Pick the badminton gym.
They're already planning the next date.
Sounds good.
What's wrong?
Nothing, I'm just looking at your questions.
My questions are pretty
basic.
Because
at first
I thought they were just early-stage questions.
Actually, I think I could change them a bit.
So what do you want to ask?
You can change them.
You can just ask me directly.
That look in your eyes
My first question is
If you divide your free time into ten parts
between socializing, being alone, and with your partner
how would you split those ten parts?
She also asked Herry (Liu Zihan)
She and Herry (Liu Zihan) are
exactly the same
Yeah, last time with Zihan
they talked about it
Let's see how he answers
I might
give
seven parts to my partner
Your partner gets seven parts?
I was just about to say
six would already be a win
but he said seven
even more
Your partner gets seven parts
two parts for socializing
Right
Two parts, and one part for being alone
One part for being alone
Whenever I have free time
Whenever I'm not busy
I just want to be with my partner
That feeling
That's pretty good.
Whenever I have free time,
Whenever I'm not busy,
I just want to be with the other person.
This feeling
is really nice.
When I'm socializing,
I actually want to bring
the other person
to meet my friends or family.
I think that would make me happier.
You're hiding your true self.
You,
I find him really cute now.
Seriously.
I really like him.
The second question is about your upbringing.
Your upbringing.
Yeah.
When I was little,
I spent more time at my grandma's place.
My parents were very busy.
They had lots of work calls.
Sometimes while talking to them,
they'd get a call
and forget what we were just talking about.
So,
I subconsciously thought
that being proactive in communication
or trying things on my own
would be ignored.
Yeah.
It was the same when I was little.
Were you raised by your parents?
Not really.
It was more my grandparents.
Maybe that's why I've been independent since childhood.
And then,
I kind of grew up free-range.
I feel like my sense of security is pretty weak.
Whether it's in close relationships
or in friendships,
I can see that.
He noticed it too.
Yeah, I really need
to be
affirmed.
Yeah.
I really need affirmation.
I need to be seen and accepted.
Chi Chi expresses her needs very clearly.
I think that's great.
I think you should just say it.
If you have issues in a relationship,
would you choose
I'm someone who faces problems head-on.
Would you choose direct communication?
Yes, I communicate directly.
I'm very straightforward.
That's really good.
Because my T value (rationality) is high,
I might
not be that emotional.
I'm more rational.
Yeah, I'm a problem-solver.
When a problem comes up,
I deal with it right away.
I think about solutions.
But I might overlook the other person's feelings.
That's just her personality.
Yeah.
Actually, I think you even
hide part of your emotions
on purpose.
Right?
Maybe.
I tend to suppress my emotions.
Let me say again,
I think I'm definitely more proactive than you.
But today, I was the one who took the key.
That's because every day
I get off work really late.
Yeah.
You're just a bit
more proactive than me.
Why are you being picky now?
This is just too sweet.
I really enjoy chatting with others.
If we get along,
I tend to lose track of time.
But I'm really happy tonight.
I'm not sleepy at all right now.
It's because
you invited me.
It's settled.
These two are good to go.
It's done.
Should we stamp it?
Stamp it.
Yifan
Have you ever ridden the mini-train?
I did two nights ago.
Zihan
Zihan is asking Ruilong.
Zihan is already venting by boxing.
Why does this feel like a sad gym session?
Channel frustration into motivation.
Two are happy, two are upset.
One is just watching the drama.
Will he regret it?
Herry (Liu Zihan)
Will he regret not going?
Making that move.
Because if you do it, others can't.
No one else can do it again.
There will definitely be some regret.
I think he already
feels a bit uneasy inside.
Because last time (on the date)
when the conversation ended,
it wasn't that pleasant.
He did write a letter though.
Here.
He must feel a bit
hopeless now.
And at this moment,
she (Sun Hanqing) rode the mini-train again.
That makes it even harder, I think.
Yu Xing and Chi Chi
seem to have
a mutual effort in their relationship.
Chi Chi also has
a tough side.
And Yu Xing noticed
Yu Xing, inside,
has an introverted side.
He’s opening up for Chi Chi.
Yu Xing finally
gathered the courage to take that step.
You’ll see them on the train
teasing each other,
acting playful.
Yu Xing rarely shows this side to others.
You’ll see it.
So I’m really looking forward to those two.
But I’m still a bit worried.
Because before,
every time Yu Xing interacts with Chi Chi,
he’s always in a good state.
His struggles come up
when he’s with Yifan.
Can he adjust his state
and get back on track?
A new day has begun.
Looking forward to it.
Dr. Fang
Yifan
Wang Jue is wearing glasses.
She has that cool, elegant beauty.
Hello.
Hi.
Le Chen
What are you washing?
Cucumber. Want some?
Are you having this for breakfast?
Come on, let’s see what else there is to eat.
Okay.
Finally woke up early enough to see someone.
It's not that early.
Today I’m a business person.
A day to style my hair like an adult.
What’s for breakfast?
Whatever’s available.
There’s noodles. Do you want some?
Let’s cook noodles then.
Sure.
It’s been a long time since I
got up to make breakfast.
Just make something simple.
Let’s eat cucumber together.
Eating cucumber.
Do you want your egg more cooked
or less cooked?
Half-cooked.
Like this?
That’s a bit too raw.
So you don’t want a runny yolk?
I mean, it looks
You’re picky.
but it’s runny when you eat it.
But it still looks
Smells so good.
This is what love looks like.
Cooking breakfast for you.
Those two really
are a good match.
It should be almost done.
Almost done.
Feels like it’s not enough.
A little is enough for me.
I don’t need much.
That small bowl is enough for me.
Don’t pretend.
That’s not your usual appetite.
It really is.
No, it’s not.
You’re still growing, eat more.
Do you want one egg or two?
One.
Two.
Really?
You’re really feeding me like a pig.
They look so happy.
Thanks.
These two are so nice to watch.
This egg is good.
Of course.
What did you two talk about last night?
What do you want to hear?
Let’s hear it.
Something interesting.
One day, Jiao Zhiheng
was chatting with me
and suddenly asked,
Chen,
what if we both like the same person?
What would you do?
At that moment,
What kind of reaction is that?
Who?
He thought you
liked Lanlan.
No.
He was just asking.
You really can’t tell?
How did you guys figure it out?
It’s so obvious, man.
He might as well
write it on his forehead.
See?
He practically wants to write it on his face.
Finished eating. It was delicious.
All done.
So we can head out together later.
Sure.
Date booked.
If you put yourself in his shoes now,
and you were Jiao Zhiheng,
what would you do?
Because when I went to talk to Jiao Ge,
I told him I felt
my situation was pretty similar to his.
Why did you go to Jiao Ge?
Just to talk to him
about some recent confusion
and a few things going on.
So do you have any confusion lately?
Will she say it out loud?
If I have confusion,
I can't tell you either.
Why not?
Do you want to hear it?
Go ahead.
The source of my confusion is you.
How could I tell you that?
She said it.
She really said it.
She's so brave.
That's really heart-fluttering.
You have to be this bold.
Just say it.
That's such a Lu Yuan way to express it.
The source of my confusion is you.
How could I tell you that?
Compared to saying it on a date,
this feels more natural.
She feels really secure.
That's why she can say it.
Let's go.
Okay.
Let's head out.
What do you do when you're alone?
Read.
Go to the gym.
Watch movies.
Binge shows.
I thought I was the only one this boring.
Turns out everyone is pretty boring.
I need to be alone
to recharge myself.
I need to clear my mind.
Feels like lately
I've been talking the most.
I've never talked this much before.
Is this your talkative phase now
or your quiet phase?
I guess it's normal.
Really?
You're probably a bit more talkative than normal.
Right now,
I'm normal.
I feel like finding topics is exhausting.
Right?
Yeah.
If two people can really
be comfortable together without talking,
that's not easy.
True.
So those cards you have,
Which cards?
The two date cards.
Yeah.
Well...
That's hard to say.
Acting cute.
Honestly, my first thought
was to write your name twice.
I really didn't expect it at the time.
Didn't expect what?
Didn't expect you to come so quickly.
If I hadn't come quickly,
I was afraid both cards would be gone.
But honestly, for the first card,
I wrote your name right away.
I wrote your name on the first card.
He's confirming it for her.
But honestly, for the first card,
I wrote your name right away.
Openly expressing your feelings.
That's really nice.
He really moved her.
Those two will definitely work out.
Yeah.
At that time, my
guess was
maybe you had two blank cards.
Or you wrote down
someone else's name first.
Then left one card blank.
And whoever came to you,
you'd write their name.
Why did you think I'd do that?
Because I just couldn't figure it out.
I couldn't tell from your previous
actions.
Yeah, I couldn't see it from your behavior.
It made me feel a bit
hard to read.
Yeah, hard to read.
There's a lot of uncertainty.
It just made my mind feel messy.
I finally understand a little now.
Finally got it.
You just figured it out?
You just got it.
Little scatterbrain.
So when I went to Jiao Ge,
he comforted me.
How did he comfort you?
He said not to be too anxious.
Were you really that anxious?
Honestly,
it wasn't that bad.
But yesterday, when I talked to Jiao Ge,
there was an important point.
It's true that
the end of the cabin is actually the real beginning.
Yeah.
He's really thinking about the future.
Alright.
Do you still look forward to the mini-train ride?
If you get it, then I will.
Look at Chen Chen.
His state with her now
is actually quite different.
He seems so relaxed.
Very comfortable.
He can't stop smiling.
Watching this part,
it feels like the two of them
are giving each other
energy, recharging each other.
They're powering up together.
It's so comfortable.
Really comfortable, super cozy.
When I see Chen Chen,
he's actually a responsible guy.
Even though before,
he didn't really
express himself much,
he was always observing.
And once Le Chen figures things out,
he adjusts his signals
really well.
Very certain, very clear.
We used to think
Lu Yuan's signals were strong.
But now, why does it feel right?
It's because Le Chen is on the same wavelength.
They're in sync.
Their way of thinking is also similar.
Both are pretty rational.
In their ideas,
and thought patterns,
they match well.
Yeah, that's so important.
So next,
in our little house,
soon,
we'll welcome
our second
Open Day.
I heard there's a mysterious
guest coming.
I'm coming out.
Really?
You went?
I joined.
It wasn't just you, right?
Not just you?
You went too?
Three of us.
No.
All three of you went.
Come on, let's see
who came.
What's with all these dishes?
This is
hot pot.
Someone's showing off their skills.
Everyone made dishes.
We need to label them.
So fancy.
Why do the guys seem so talented?
It's like a "Chef Competition."
It feels like
everyone's going all out today.
Something big
is about to happen.
I'm really looking forward to this part.
The mysterious guest.
Who will the mysterious guest be?
Who is it, really?
Get your best dish ready.
So what are you planning to do?
Tomorrow.
I might make spicy hot pot.
What you made today was delicious.
Why not make it again?
Today’s dish is fine.
Then maybe make two dishes?
Yeah, make one more.
Three dishes would work too.
How many are you making?
I was planning to make two dishes.
One with cauliflower.
One with stir-fried pork and peppers.
They already have stir-fried pork and peppers.
I know.
But I still want to make it.
Everyone’s trying to outdo each other.
What are you using this water for?
I want to make brown sugar water.
Isn’t today for keeping warm?
Le Chen, how many dishes are you making?
Two.
Everyone’s competing.
Did they say what time?
I don’t know.
Then we’ll just have to cook faster.
I’m pretty curious.
Who’s coming today?
Who actually came?
Hurry up.
Just skip straight to that part.
They’re here.
Ma Boqian.
What?
Seems like it.
Let’s go.
This should be the one from earlier.
Yo Sheep Ranch.
Going again.
I was really looking forward to it.
Turns out...
Xu Ge gave it.
It’s too much.
Now it feels like...
We’re out.
Deer.
Sika deer.
Horse.
Calling a deer a horse.
Alright, then that’s a horse.
Horse.
Ma Boqian, look at the deer!
I want to go too.
I’ve always wanted to go.
They can just stroll around here.
Yeah.
Just walk around.
Take a stroll.
Chat a bit.
Go for a run.
Yeah.
You and Shen Mengchen,
do you like coming to parks like this?
Shen doesn’t really like walking around.
But I really love it.
Whenever we’re together,
she’ll walk with me.
I’d love to live here.
Right?
Yeah.
This is it.
Let’s sit down.
Let’s wait a bit.
Why are there still people here?
Actually, I’m pretty...
worried about meeting the elders.
Elders.
No one’s older than him, right?
Maybe family is coming today.
I don’t think so.
Actually, I’m pretty...
worried about meeting the elders.
Why?
Because I’m the type
who speaks bluntly but makes sense.
That kind of person.
You know?
You’re afraid of saying
too much,
too little,
too harsh or too light.
Yeah.
I can’t get the balance right.
You know?
So, may I ask,
have you met elders before?
Of course I have.
They’re here.
Who?
Is it the moms?
Really?
Are they really the moms?
The family and friends are here.
Hello.
Haitao.
Welcome.
Please come inside.
The girls' family and friends.
There are moms, friends, and sisters.
And me.
I'm here for no reason.
What's going on?
Hello.
Welcome, everyone.
Sister.
Mom.
Lu Yuan's mom.
Ai Lin's mom.
Yifan's best friend.
And actually, today, you see,
It's all moms and sisters here.
No dads were invited.
I think if dads came,
their eyes would be
full of "killer intent."
With dads, it's not just checking.
Everyone would be eliminated.
Right.
When moms come,
their eyes are filled with joy.
That's how I see it.
Before coming, mom
Did you talk to dad about this?
Yes.
He told me
to take a good look.
That's what he said.
He asked why dad wasn't invited.
I said, maybe next time.
I said, next time.
Chi Chi's mom is so cute.
I'm with Xu Rulan.
You could say I'm her older sister.
How long have you been together?
How long has it been?
Since 2018 until now.
Seven years.
It's been seven years.
After getting to know her,
Rulan is very perceptive.
She can also
inspire people, she's that kind of kid.
Welcome, friends and family.
Thank you.
Welcome to our older sister.
I'm Lu Yuan's mom.
To be honest,
When she first came here,
I was a bit worried.
Because she
when it comes to dating and relationships,
I brought it up with her,
but she was pretty
resistant to the idea.
So,
I didn't force her.
In my opinion,
I let her do as she likes.
Whatever makes her happy.
Then she suddenly joined this show.
Mom, what did you think?
What's going on?
Yeah.
At first, I asked what kind of show it was.
I asked, is it a proper show?
A proper show.
She said yes, so I agreed.
Because she's still in school.
That's right.
I'm still a little worried.
And now, sitting here today,
it feels like a parent-teacher meeting.
It really does.
Our show is very proper.
We've been running for eight seasons.
I really didn't know.
To be honest.
Mom is very honest.
Honestly.
Mom is so cute.
I'm Wang Yifan's colleague.
We're best friends in Shanghai.
Best friends talk about everything.
Yeah.
Has she ever told you
what her ideal type is?
Her ideal type is someone
just like this gentleman here.
Like this gentleman.
Someone very strong and fit.
Ma Boqian looks so macho today.
I haven't introduced everyone yet.
This gentleman
is joining us today
as our male guest.
What qualities does he have
that you think
Yifan would like?
Yes, he's handsome.
Handsome.
But looks are nothing compared to his talent.
They're worth nothing next to his talent.
Right, I rely on my personality.
He laughed at his own joke.
I think it's so funny.
Alright.
If these guests come on stage,
then you're definitely the ideal type.
Ideal type.
I wouldn't.
This is so much fun.
So happy.
This makes the kids happy.
Look at that.
They took it seriously.
Really.
Has Wang Jue ever talked to his sister-in-law about this before?
Like,
what her ideal type is?
The first thing Wang Jue wants
is to handle emotions well.
Because no matter what the issue is,
or who’s right or wrong,
if you don’t manage the girl’s emotions,
no matter what you say to her,
she won’t listen.
That’s impressive.
Well said.
First, calm her emotions.
So I also hope
our little sister
can meet someone like that.
But there’s one more thing.
You can’t just always give in.
Right.
You have to have your own sense of self.
Actually, in a relationship between two people,
it's not about how I change myself,
but about being myself
while still fitting together even better.
Right.
You can't keep compromising yourself.
Don't lose who you are.
Isn't that true?
Mom, you're so kind.
You keep saying
how much you miss your daughter.
You're happy and content.
Really happy and content.
But at the same time, I don't want
you to lose yourself.
Because only then, the two of you
the feeling of being together
and the state you're in
will be more genuine.
So basically,
if he is true to himself,
the relationship will last longer.
Yes.
Exactly.
I'm Ke Ailin's mother.
During the time I've spent with my daughter,
I've been with her a lot.
As her mother,
I think being there for her is really important.
Because when a child is alone
in a strange city,
it's very lonely.
Especially when she's sick,
like having a cough or a cold,
she feels helpless by herself.
My daughter often gets coughs and colds.
I video call her often.
I always think about
her health and happiness first.
A mother's care is always here.
Yes.
As a mother,
I think if a boy
can give a girl
happiness,
companionship,
and guidance,
that's what a mother hopes her daughter will find.
A boy like that.
That's very well said.
Of course,
no one can be perfect.
You can't give everything.
You can't have it all.
It's impossible.
If we get just one thing,
and it's what the girl wants,
I think she'll be happy.
Very happy.
For example, me,
I value companionship.
Maybe he spends more time with you,
but isn't as good at making money.
That's okay.
You have companionship,
so you should be happy.
You got what you wanted.
Just having one thing can bring happiness.
That's really well said.
Really.
You can't have everything.
I think all the moms
right from the start
have elevated the show.
I'm about to cry.
Yeah.
Makes me want to cry.
When she said that just now,
I felt the same.
It made me think of my own mom.
I thought of my daughter.
A mother's words are
gentle yet strong.
Yes.
They're powerful.
She really wants
her child to be well.
So,
she truly hopes
there will be
someone worthy of trust.
We’ll be meeting the guys soon.
Let’s all ask them questions.
How about it?
We’ve prepared so many questions.
I think we should just ask whatever we want.
Just ask anything.
Yeah.
If the two of them are in a long-distance relationship,
and something comes up,
what would he actually do?
How would he show it through actions?
To express his love?
That’s so real.
First, I want to see if someone
can stay committed for a long time,
and be loyal.
So now,
let’s write down the questions we want to ask the guys
on these cards.
Let’s start.
These questions just keep coming.
They’re really intense.
I’m already on my third question.
We were supposed to write just one.
But I wrote three.
I’m so nervous.
We’re about to meet them.
Why is there only one cutting board?
I’ll be done soon.
Everyone’s scared off.
Sis,
I’ll give you two more cards.
I’m feeling a bit stressed over here.
Feels like it.
Do you think we still have plenty of time?
I’m not sure about the time.
It’s all so rushed.
So you think it’s possible
for a mystery guest to show up halfway?
Alright.
Let’s take
all our questions
and meet up with the guys.
Let’s go.
We’re heading out.
I can’t wait to see how the guys react.
Me too.
I’m already excited about these questions.