Shall we raise our glasses and start eating?
Let's raise our glasses.
Come on.
Have a pleasant journey.
Cheers.
We've met again.
Enjoy the trip.
Here we meet again.
Cheers.
Let's eat.
I'll try this soup first.
For crab, do you want the claw or the pincer?
The claw.
This counts as the claw.
Either is fine, you choose for me.
Just put it here.
Okay.
Do you want some turtle?
I don't eat it.
I care about looks when I eat.
Care about what when eating?
Also care about looks.
Do you want some?
No, really.
It's fine, I just ate.
Okay.
I just had a little.
You're so considerate.
Thank you.
Brother Herry (Liu Zihan)
Caretaker personality.
I think today's food is delicious.
It's tasty.
Today's food is good.
I think so too.
Today's food is really delicious.
What's this bowl for?
Thank you.
No idea.
Can I have a small piece?
Of the turtle.
Turtle, sure.
Yeah, I just want to try it.
Thank you.
Teacher Zihan is quite
funny.
I said I wanted to try turtle.
I've never had turtle before.
He gave me a piece of chicken.
Is there other meat in here?
I thought it was just turtle.
I get it now.
This dish is called "Turtle and Chicken Surprise."
This is definitely chicken.
Let me do it.
I thought it was all turtle inside.
I said the texture feels kind of off.
No one announced the dish name.
Do you want some lily?
This lily is sweet.
It's delicious.
Do you want some?
If you want, I can swap it for you.
She wants to laugh whenever you talk now.
Eating lily is kind of abstract.
I'll take this turtle
and swap it with you, okay?
Sure, no problem.
I can tell.
Now I want turtle.
"Turtle and Chicken Surprise" with you all.
I want "Turtle and Chicken Surprise."
Saying goodbye to you all.
I'll go with Teacher Duoduo.
What's wrong?
I know the bond with chicken feet runs deep.
But I've had a lot of this already.
Then I'll do it.
Why are you laughing again?
They're so weird.
What's up? Share with us.
I'll draw you another one tonight.
Draw one for me.
Lan Lan, draw one for me.
Sure, I can.
I'll draw one for you.
Have you seen his drawing of Yuxing?
No.
You even showed Lan Lan your drawing.
Don't move.
Just look, just draw.
This angle is pretty good.
I can only
I can only draw you like this.
I'm done drawing.
I'm done.
Sorry.
I didn't show it to anyone else.
Didn't show it to anyone else.
No wonder she kept looking at me and laughing today.
It kind of looks like me.
It's Doctor Fang, the "soulful artist."
Let's go for a walk.
Let's go.
No, the lyrics of the love songs we picked
are all so sad.
So sad, but some things
really hit home.
They hit so close.
Yeah, they really do.
So true, really.
Now I get how love songs are written.
Yeah, I never felt that before.
Right.
Tasting the bitterness of love.
You know it's bitter from the start.
But
I don't think love itself is bitter.
It's like your own recipe.
Depends on how you season it.
Yeah.
Just like this short trip of ours.
I was surprised too.
But I could kind of guess it.
About his choice.
Maybe it wasn't his choice.
So at that moment, I thought of Lechen.
Because when I think of him,
I really feel much better.
That night, watching his fireworks,
I was truly happy.
This feeling inside me
just keeps climbing higher.
The two of them truly embody
The brave enjoy the world first.
The brave and the lucky ones.
Yes.
You added that ending.
Because there are plenty of brave people here.
Yeah, there really are plenty of brave people.
Alright, it's sealed away now.
Hey, film a transition shot for me.
I've been looking forward to this.
Sure.
How do you want to shoot it?
Just head that way.
So I walk that way, right?
Yeah, I'll go.
Should I follow you, or what?
That works too.
I'll follow you.
Okay.
Let's go.
Alright, you're out of sight now.
Can't see you anymore.
You're out of view.
You're walking like it's a runway.
Let's see.
Looks good.
Got the transition shot.
That's good.
I'm really happy with this Xinjiang trip.
That's it.
Just shoot this.
I can't learn that dance.
Let's take a couple of film shots.
Brought the film camera but didn't use it.
Let me take a photo of you.
Take a cool photo of me.
Just look cool, that's enough.
Do you want full body or half body?
Either is fine.
Alright, three, two, one.
What kind of photo do you want?
Hand me the sunglasses.
Strike a pose.
Three, two, one.
Okay.
This one should be perfect.
I trust your skills.
Let's sit for a bit.
What did you think when you saw the graduation gown?
Didn't expect it.
Really didn't expect it, huh?
That's great.
When did you start thinking about it? On the plane?
Yeah.
What did you originally want to write on the kite?
I actually really wanted to
write some worries on it.
Then cut them off.
But I ended up writing something positive, right?
Yeah, because you set a good example.
I think I
suddenly wanted to change direction.
What worries did you want to write?
Way too many.
You could've left some for me.
There's no end to worries.
Let's fill both sides, front and back.
We can eat now.
I don't think I've ever sat outdoors
and eaten from sunrise to sunset.
If we can eat until dark now,
we're really good eaters.
Do you want any condiments?
No, I'm good.
You like to mix them.
What condiments do you mix?
Just scallions.
Cilantro.
Add some garlic, soy sauce, and vinegar.
That's it.
You don't want sesame paste?
I don't eat sesame paste.
You don't eat sesame paste?
You're really different from when I first met you.
You gave me a totally different vibe.
I'm really curious.
When you all first met me,
what did you think I was like?
Like, when something sad happens,
I can quickly detach.
And I stay calm about everything.
That's actually true.
It was like that for the first two days.
By the third day, I showed my real self.
Didn't talk to you much on the third day.
Wasn't it the dinner party?
Yeah, I was upset.
So after spending time with me,
do you think the me you first met and
the me after we talked
are very different?
Not really.
Just that the impression is deeper now.
So at first,
the impression I gave you was
like how I am now.
Just
a little girl.
Just someone who's been through
a few things, a little girl.
Still an immature little girl.
Not immature.
I mean,
that's why I say
you've been through things.
I just feel like the impression you give me
is that you're very strong at your core.
But in that strength,
there's so much unspoken pain.
So much silence.
That silence has shaped you too.
Let's talk about something happy.
I think that's great.
It's just bittersweet memories, right?
I think you're really amazing now.
But you said before that you're boring.
I don't think that's true.
You have a rich inner world.
I can totally feel it.
Really?
I don't even feel it.
I can sense it when we talk.
No, I feel like my inner world is pretty messy.
Messy but full.
It's so chaotic.
It's colorful.
My mind is fighting every day.
This heat wave is blowing right at my face.
Scoot over a little closer.
It's fine, I'm getting a facial sauna.
Yesterday we warmed up by the campfire.
What?
Yesterday.
Say it again.
Warmed up by the campfire.
Say it faster.
Campfire.
Today it's the heat wave.
Okay, I'll blow it your way now.
Give me a facial sauna too.
My only regret today is
not getting the kite up in the air.
The kite flying high.
I think maybe later.
We can still fly it again.
Sure.
Let's do it later.
Feels like the wind will pick up soon, right?
We'll fly it later.
Did you tell it?
Did you send a message?
Say it now.
Okay.
Wait for a bit of wind later.
I'm getting roasted out here.
First time sunbathing till eight thirty at night.
Do you always eat this slowly?
You seem like a sloth.
No, I actually eat fast.
My dad eats super fast at home.
So I feel I can't make him wait too long.
That's why I eat quickly myself.
Then can't you just
ask the other person to eat slower?
Eat together?
Why not say it?
I know my dad too well.
But do you know what he's thinking?
What do you mean, what he's thinking?
Like, do you know his true feelings?
I do. Are you sure?
He just
isn't good at expressing himself.
Do you feel you missed out on
some parental affection in childhood?
Yes.
Why?
No company.
No sharing, no response.
Not none, just very little.
How come?
Were they busy with work or what?
Yeah, our family was busy back then.
Both of them had their own things going on.
So I often
barely saw my dad.
Is there something you most want to say to your dad?
What I'd most want to say to my dad
Actually, at home
I rarely talk with my dad.
I can tell.
Has he ever
said anything mushy to you?
I don't think so.
Later, I found something from my elementary school days.
A letter my dad wrote to me.
The last line he wrote was
"You'll never know how much Dad loves you."
That was the only
heartwarming thing I've ever heard from him.
So are you proactive in expressing
things like "I love you"?
Would you?
I might want to.
I hope to give others what I never had
and really wished for.
To give that to someone else.
To make up for it.
To compensate for it.
Compensate by giving to others.
Let them feel the regret I might've felt.
Eating feels great.
So good.
Let me soak up some more sun.
Feels so nice.
Suddenly I'm starting to like the mountains.
So beautiful.
Where should I sit?
Right here.
I got this ready for you.
Stick it on.
Thanks.
You stick it on first.
Have you ever gone to the movies alone?
No.
Thinking about it, I don't think I have.
But I've thought about it many times.
Feels too lonely, right?
Do you remember
there was a chart
What was it?
A chart of loneliness levels.
Which level do you think you'd reach?
My loneliness level
is probably pretty low.
If I really want to be alone
I don't think being alone is loneliness.
It's just me sorting myself out.
I think loneliness is more like
when you really want to talk to someone
but can't find anyone.
Like when you really want to
go to the movies alone
and don't know who to text.
So that means I'm truly lonely, huh?
You really don't know who to text?
Really.
You still have to tell someone about this.
And then
Explain what's up.
The thing is, I don't know who to tell.
About going to the movies.
I think it really needs
a good atmosphere.
And two people can enjoy it together.
The kind you can actually sit through.
Do you want to watch with the opposite sex?
You can watch with a friend of the same sex.
I didn't say with the opposite sex.
I just mean at least
Even between friends of the same sex
there can be misunderstandings.
I just think watching movies
I don't mind what genre it is.
I do mind.
Then let's watch what you like.
But what if the other person doesn't like it?
Isn't that kind of awkward?
You really don't need to overthink it.
And that time was funny because
there were only two people in the theater.
Me and one other person watched that movie.
That's nice.
Then I sat way in the back.
I just watched the movie there.
What holiday was it back then?
I really enjoy eating alone.
And having hotpot by myself.
I truly enjoy eating alone.
Hotpot alone is fun too.
And going to the doctor alone.
That feels so real, so alive.
Now I always go to the doctor alone.
Because I don't want others to know.
Just some minor aches and pains.
At that time, I was in a state of
deep inner struggle,
feeling very anxious.
But after I went, I realized
there were so many patients in ER,
my pain seemed so small in comparison.
That feeling.
Yeah.
Do you know why I want to fly a kite?
Actually,
Didn't you say you read books?
And listen to music.
What I really want is
to make up for some childhood regrets.
I remember the last time was when I was little.
It was at a square near my home.
Flying a kite there.
It was a Saturday.
After that,
I never touched a kite again.
Why?
Never had the chance.
To fly a kite again.
Everything just sped up.
I noticed, in the cabin,
or when we go out together,
many things you do are about
searching for what you missed in childhood.
That's part of it.
But I see more of myself
in you, like a reflection.
From your past experiences,
I might understand a bit more.
Maybe I kind of know
what you want.
These regrets, for us,
maybe we never had the chance
to face them.
They might stay with you for life.
Or else I'd cry my eyes out today.
Cheers.
That's nice.
You'll sleep well tonight.
Hope so.
Bye.
See you tomorrow.
This is Via Ferrata.
I want to try this.
And rock climbing.
I want to play.
You guys go ahead.
You go ahead.
I'll watch from below.
I'll watch from down here too.
My knees can't handle this.
Well,
You guys go ahead.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Let's go.
There are two routes.
Easy and hard.
Which one should we pick?
I'll take easy.
Easy.
Relax.
Yeah.
Thanks.
How about the hard mode?
Then you two take the hard route.
You two go for the hard route.
We'll take the easy route.
Yeah.
What do you think, Jiao?
You want the hard route?
I'll go for the hard route.
Easy route.
What's going on?
I'll go first then.
Which one is the easy route?
I'll follow your route.
Just go on your own, right?
Wherever Jiao goes, he goes.
What did he choose?
He picked the brave mode.
Then I'll take this one.
Okay.
You two are way too fast.
I can't even find Jiao.
Is Jiao still here?
He should be on the upper level.
I'm up here.
I'm watching you guys.
This part up here is fun.
Really?
Because there's only one rope.
Nothing else.
It's really tough.
It's brave mode now.
Let her go first.
I'm afraid I'll wobble as soon as I get up.
Do you need a bit of challenge?
So easy.
I can tell.
No.
Didn't you say it was too easy?
Is this the challenge you gave?
That's it?
Doctor Fang.
What?
That's all there is.
Is that it?
That's still not enough.
Then go back and do it again.
Come on, choose.
Balance beam or this, or this?
Up to you.
This one.
Which one? This one.
This balance beam.
Okay.
I've decided to switch.
Doctor Fang, you go first.
You go first.
Yeah, you can change the order.
I'll go first.
Do you two have any sneaky plans?
I really want to step on you.
What did you say?
Can we go one on the left, one on the right?
Who wants to go left and right with you?
I should've stayed down there with Duoduo.
Give it a kick.
You kick it for him.
It's useless, doesn't help.
Doesn't help.
Jiao-ge
Jiao-ge is the real brave one.
This thing up here is actually pretty fun.
Really?
You think it's fun, huh?
Jiao-ge, I want to come up.
Jiao-ge
What?
You want to come up?
This one's pretty tough.
You're so fierce.
Bet you couldn't tell, right?
No, I could tell by looking.
But when you actually did it,
it's still a bit surprising.
It's still a bit surprising.
I really want to give her a kick.
So naughty.
I'm telling Lan Lan.
She said she wanted some excitement.
Doctor Fang, I'm at the finish now.
Be careful.
No problem.
It's a small thing.
I even did the splits for you today.
It's fine.
"Help!"
Is that okay?
Not exciting enough.
Take this route.
Okay.
This one's a bit better.
You two are kind of...
Kind of going at "light speed."
Are we fast?
Yeah, you're sticking so close.
You have to chase closely.
Learned something new again.
Gained some new insight again.
It's really fun.
Super cool.
That thing up there.
Lan Lan is the real deal here.
She totally changed after going up.
There's cake here.
The cake you like.
How is it?
You tell me.
In this setting, what do you think
is the one thing you need most?
Right now?
Yeah.
Like, if you're camping outside
but don't have any other gear,
what would you want most?
What do you mean, no other gear?
Like a speaker.
Game console, movie screen, or phone.
Or something else.
Definitely a movie screen.
Because you can play music on it,
and watch movies too.
That's pretty versatile.
Right?
It has to be multifunctional.
Like, the kind that comes with
Just a movie screen.
I think it should have a speaker.
And a projector, like that.
Then you can only watch movies on it.
Only movies, huh?
Then I'd pick a speaker.
Music.
Music really can
make people feel relaxed and happy.
Are you also the type
who always plays music at home?
I actually like playing music alone.
Me too.
Especially when showering,
I play some music.
Singing along by myself is pretty
enjoyable.
Actually, about your question,
the gear isn't that important.
I think people matter more.
I think, for you,
who would you most want to be with here?
That question is more important.
Because sometimes,
even when waiting for a flight,
in a boring situation,
if the people around you are
different, then
it's still fun.
Sometimes I think the journey
isn't that important.
But the process really matters.
Even just being on the road,
can be happy.
I also think the process matters more.
Where you've been is just a result.
I think that result
is something most people can get.
But your journey is unique.
Most people can get the result?
Yeah, like for example,
say I've been to
somewhere.
I've been there too.
But everyone sees different scenery.
It's different.
So what they see is their journey.
And who you go with is part of it too.
That's part of the journey.
And what happens along the way
is also part of the journey.
And my favorite thing is sharing
fun stories with good friends
funny moments.
Or funny moments with family.
Or childhood stories.
They're really interesting.
Those happy memories,
You told me before,
the scar on your hand is from
when you fell as a kid?
It looks a bit like a crescent moon.
Yeah, I think it's super cool.
It does look pretty nice.
Right? It's got character.
You sound so proud saying that.
What?
If someone else fell,
they wouldn't get such a cool scar like mine.
Let's go for a walk together.
Sure.
Okay. It's comfortable sitting here.
Are you doing okay?
These past two days,
I've actually been fine.
I really like how you are right now.
It left a deep impression on me too.
It feels like, during your time in the cabin,
in such a unique environment,
you've been able to
make a small
but different transformation.
It's like slowly finding that missing piece
and finally discovering it.
I used to think I never
had that piece at all.
But now I've found it again
and brought it back.
I've put it back into my own picture.
I'm so envious.
I feel like mine...
Is this mine?
It's yours.
Because I have the floral tea.
I remember that.
That's hilarious.
We all have to go through it.
Fate always has its best plan.
In my view,
I think being in a relationship,
or interacting with someone,
is itself
a process of self-improvement.
It's a state of growth.
Yes, the people and things you encounter
might all be
meant to help you
become more complete.
If I care about someone,
I hope they're happy.
Yes.
And if,
if we're lucky,
maybe we can be happy together.
But if,
luck isn't on our side,
or fate isn't right,
then I wish them happiness.
If you can be happy,
that's what I wanted from the start.
What you just said
actually answered my doubts.
I think...
But I feel that when you sense
happiness,
these emotions,
even sadness, it's actually a good thing.
It shows
you're immersed in
a truly sincere
relationship with everyone.
It means you also
are sincere when you're with me.
You're genuine.
You truly care when we're together.
That's enough for me.
As long as everyone
does their best
and puts their heart into it, that's enough.
As for the outcome, how I choose,
how you choose,
I think it matters, but it doesn't matter.
Whatever the result, it won't affect you.
I'm here to eat.
Come, I'll save you a seat.
I'm saving this great spot for you.
That's nice.
Keep lying down.
How's your conversation going?
Of course, we're chatting well.
We're having a pretty good talk.
Because Jiao and I were in the cabin,
just talking nonstop.
He's a really gentle person.
At our four-person dinner that day,
I asked them a question.
The question was,
Rate something from one to ten now.
But you can choose what to rate.
You pick one to rate.
And then compare
your first day and now.
You can pick anything.
Then rate it yourself.
I'd definitely choose my comfort level.
On day one, I was at zero.
And now?
To be safe, you could say minus twenty.
Minus twenty.
Now I think I'm at nine.
Hey, bro.
Come on.
Minus twenty.
Can you see the Big Dipper now?
No, I can't.
We could see it yesterday.
Or maybe your eyesight is just great.
Duo Duo, you answer one.
Pick anything and rate it one to ten.
Compare day one and today.
Okay, I'll pick one.
My sense of belonging in the cabin.
On the first day, it was
minus twenty.
Minus twenty is the baseline, right?
Today, it's a perfect score.
Yeah.
I just asked them in the car
some other questions.
What questions?
You all haven't heard these yet.
Everyone shares one thing
about their own
friendship and romance
that are totally different
preferences.
I'll go first.
Go ahead.
Friends.
I like gentle people.
The kind who can do a split.
Of course, if you mean physically flexible,
having flexible ligaments works too.
Flexible ligaments and a soft heart.
Just kidding, I mean gentle people.
Whether it's a gentle personality
or a gentle way of expressing.
For relationships, I like
people who act differently
in social settings and private moments.
A big contrast.
I like people with contrast.
Actually, this contrast you mention,
I take it to mean
someone shows one side to others
and saves their truest self
just for you.
Exactly.
It's a kind of privacy, really.
Yeah.
All my friends are genuine.
Many of my friends are
not exactly the same as me,
but at least seventy or eighty percent similar.
Relationships.
I think it's also about
preference.
Like that privacy you mentioned.
Privacy.
Yeah, same idea.
Makes sense.
I think with friends,
I'm more optimistic.
More positive.
I want the vibe around me
to be full of positive energy.
Yeah.
But in relationships,
I prefer someone more delicate, like you said.
Someone who can pick up on emotions.
Yes.
Who notices
the little details.
Makes sense.
Actually, a lot of our answers overlap.
The points you mention
can't fully sum up
what's in your heart.
Of course.
It's just a simple answer, after all.
I want to head back for a bit.
Okay.
I really like walking with my hands behind my back.
They always say I look like
a boss inspecting things.
You do look like that.
Or like
an old security guard.
Can you hold this for me?
Never mind, just leave it here.
Lie down anywhere, any way.
Come on, let's fight.
You took my pillow away.
Whose is this?
It's Lan Lan's.
Xu Rulan is a really smart girl.
How would you rate me?
You?
Let's change spots.
Over there, by the door.
Let's go.
Honestly,
I think your white outfit today
looks really nice.
Thanks.
How's it in here?
Yesterday, we had a deep talk here.
Sesame, open the door.
Rate me.
Rate you on what?
Take out your paper.
Didn't we finish rating already?
I'm serious, I'm sure about it.
I even wrote it all down on paper.
Really?
Yes, really.
You wrote it down on paper?
I really am a...
The second half of that sentence...
You can...
stay skeptical about it.
You don't have to think too deeply.
The noun or adjective before that
is a very...
I think it's a trait I have.
The latter part...
is just a way to show it.
Being smart can't just
show in your cooking
or your quick learning skills.
What about me? How would you describe me?
Serious.
I'm serious.
I separate things.
My friends say when they first meet me,
I'm very...
aloof and distant.
Didn't we talk about this before?
That's really how I am.
It's just...
I also slowly open up.
And become more...
willing to talk.
Because before, honestly,
I didn't know what to say.
Do you think I look fierce?
When you don't smile, you do look fierce.
Like when I'm zoning out,
or my expression
is really calm,
that's just how I look.
So you're just zoning out?
I honestly have no thoughts at all.
They ask, "What's wrong with you?"
"Are you angry or something?"
Yeah.
Tonight, I think your vibe
was kind of intimidating.
Tonight,
at dinner,
my mind was already blank.
At that moment, I just kept
thinking about my craving for good food.
I just wanted to fill my stomach.
Are you the type who's full of energy in the morning
and then slowly uses it up?
Or do you not have much energy in the morning
and need to recharge at noon?
I think it depends.
For me,
it's not like I can recharge
just by sleeping.
You need to do things to recharge.
I think chatting like this
is pretty recharging.
What about you?
Same as you.
Talking makes me feel good.
Yeah.
Actually, sleep only recharges me
just
physically.
Yeah, for my emotions,
it doesn't help much.
What drains your energy the most?
For example,
when everyone's quiet,
and no one talks,
my mind starts racing,
thinking of a topic to discuss.
How can I liven things up?
That's when I start to feel drained.