The second big date at Heartbeat Apartment is here.
Surfing time.
Life requires taking the bravest step.
Like a family of three.
Yeah.
Happy birthday to you.
It feels like the two of us
are evenly matched.
Smooth sailing.
Everything goes well.
Sometimes my thoughts jump around.
But every time you jump,
you land right where I do.
You’re very talented.
You are too.
Really, I am?
A little talent, a big talent.
I ship us.
I can’t take it anymore.
It’s hard to remember every single day.
Today I’m a happy kid.
Falling down together with her.
So sweet.
Three.
Two.
One.
What is it?
This is so touching.
It’s snowing.
Yeah.
This is so romantic.
I’m a strong person.
Sometimes you don’t have to be so strong.
Then next time I’ll come to you to cry.
I can’t stand it.
Takumi is coming down the mountain.
Okay.
What does that mean?
You haven’t seen Initial D?
What’s Initial D?
Generation gap.
I’ll go study it tonight, okay?
I’ve decided, I’ll buy a motorcycle tomorrow.
Chi Chi
Pink basketball
They finally got a one-on-one date.
Chi Chi
Hello
This is for you.
This is a basketball.
What does giving me a basketball mean?
It's because I like basketball.
And also, you can
bring me a basketball.
Right, guess what this is.
This is...
A badminton racket.
A drawing.
What do you think it is?
A skateboard.
A skateboard? Is there one this thin?
Then what is it?
A tennis racket?
No.
You can take a look.
Let me hold it for you.
What is it?
A badminton racket.
Yes.
It's a badminton racket.
Badminton racket.
Then we can play badminton tonight.
Sure.
But I only bought it for you.
It's fine.
It's okay, I can still have one.
Yeah.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I brought a gift too.
What is it?
At the last dinner,
didn't you give me a bouquet?
And that bouquet
had one flower that
never wilts, right?
So I bought a whole bouquet
of flowers that never wilt.
It matches yours.
This looks like that gerbera daisy.
Yeah.
Then we can put it together.
Sure.
Thank you.
We can put it together.
Have you been here before?
No, it's my first time.
I was amazed when I first arrived.
Did you choose this place or...
I originally wanted to
Didn't we say before
that we haven't been to an amusement park in ages?
But
it's raining outside today,
so we changed it to here.
It's indoors.
I think you picked a great place.
You picked a great place.
I'm so happy.
Did you
hear people screaming already?
This is so exciting.
This is intense.
Isn't it easy to get that
suspension bridge effect here?
Yeah.
This is kind of like
Do you dare to try it?
Tarzan
I think it should be
This one should be fine.
This should be
I think so too.
Not as thrilling as a roller coaster.
Yeah.
I feel like every time I...
We can start with the most exciting one.
Sure.
Should we try the swing first?
I want to try this too.
This makes it easy
to have physical contact.
This won't work.
Both are strapped in.
How can there be physical contact?
Hold hands if you're scared.
How do we get on this?
This...
A little nervous.
How high does this go?
When it suddenly moves, I feel really—
It's a bit scary.
So high.
Is this really okay?
I think—
I think I'm really nervous.
The first drop really feels a bit—
Like you're weightless.
This is much better, much better.
This activity is great.
I feel like I've lost control of my expressions.
This feels awesome.
This is so romantic.
This works.
We could—
We could try this too.
It's actually pretty fun.
It's just—
Quite—
Thrilling.
But—
It's the platform that's shaking.
I'm telling you—
It's not me shaking.
No.
It's you shaking.
Really not.
It's not me shaking.
I think your voice is about to give out.
No.
How many stories high is this?
Here—
I guess it's at least three stories.
Why aren't you scared?
I am scared.
Turn around and face that way.
Should we check this?
I'm a bit scared, my legs feel weak now.
Don't we need to check it?
No need to take this.
No need to take it.
Is this—
Do we jump down ourselves?
Yes, you two have to jump.
We have to jump down.
Yeah.
I feel like suddenly—
Jumping down—
Let me mentally prepare myself.
Can you do it? Don't rush.
We have to jump by ourselves.
There's tension.
But you two still need to jump a bit.
They'll jump together.
Yeah.
That scream was so miserable.
I'm telling you, even if you're not scared—
You hear that scream and you start to get scared.
Yeah.
I think—
No way.
Maybe the guys need protection.
You can't think you can't do it.
Okay, fine.
Wait a second.
Hold here.
Okay.
Hold each other.
This spot is great, really nice.
Where should I hold for more stability?
Awesome.
This is what I meant—
We should ride a roller coaster together.
It's the same idea.
They're both a bit shy.
Wait a second.
Go down.
Why are you starting to sweat?
Am I sweating?
You're sweating a lot.
I'm just wearing a lot of clothes.
It feels a bit hot.
You...
Just...
Is that okay?
Can you do it?
Of course I can.
I...
I think...
I think I can.
I...
Really step out a bit.
Don't shake, don't shake.
I'm not shaking, it's not me.
It's really not me shaking.
You're shaking.
He's gripping tightly.
He doesn't want to go down.
Let's count down before we jump.
Five.
Two.
Zero.
Jump!
We're stuck.
Don't be afraid.
I'm holding onto you.
We're about to jump.
Wait a second.
The guy still won't let go.
The guy is really scared.
His grip is getting stronger.
Holding the rope?
Holding on.
Bend your knees.
Squat down.
I can't do it.
Okay, three, two, one, jump!
Protected.
So sweet.
Princess carry in the air.
Hug in the air.
This is good.
This is really good.
Holding completely.
What's going on?
Scoreless streak.
I just can't get up.
Chi Chi seems to really enjoy teasing him.
Super happy.
She looks at him being silly and clueless.
It's really cute.
Yeah, it's the contrast.
So Chi Chi is different today.
Today, she is
the one in control.
I noticed that when people
are in front of someone they like,
they keep smiling foolishly.
Not even knowing why they're smiling.
Their body language changes too.
She just took the initiative
and grabbed his hand back.
He didn't pull away.
Not her.
She grabbed back.
Because she was scared.
She really wanted to hold on.
That's possible too.
I'm really hungry.
Then let's hurry up
and go.
So, did you have fun today?
Yes, I did.
Super happy.
That's great.
I've actually never been to this place before.
And the activities
should all be things we're interested in.
Yeah.
I like hearing that.
Why?
Because they're things we both like.
And what did you say before?
You said I seemed scared.
What?
I think that's nonsense.
Now he's starting
to defend himself.
Yeah.
He's fine now.
Driving.
No problem.
Does it bother you?
I don't really like it.
Being misunderstood.
If you express yourself, you won't be misunderstood.
Okay.
Yeah, I keep saying it.
I really can do it.
So are you someone who expresses
your thoughts directly?
Talking about what matters most to you.
Depends on the situation.
Like at work.
I think I'm pretty direct.
But not when it comes to feelings.
In terms of feelings,
When it comes to feelings, I
I seem a bit
A bit shy.
I'm a little shy, yeah.
See, you're shy.
Yeah, I think he's really shy.
But I think in front of Chi Chi,
he's already pretty proactive.
He's talking a lot.
Yeah.
So you're not good at expressing
your feelings?
But
what if you're misunderstood?
I need to clearly know
that I've been misunderstood.
Only then will I
explain.
Yeah, try to explain.
Really.
Staying up late affects your memory.
So what do you remember every day?
I remember things about you.
You like spicy pork stir-fry.
Yeah.
You like yellow, right?
You like yellow.
That's great.
You usually seem pretty quiet.
But now
You like spicy pork stir-fry.
You like yellow, right?
Not bad, you remembered some things.
Bonus points.
Do you remember my name?
Why did you suddenly ask
this question?
I'm just asking.
Jin Yuxing.
Which "Yu"?
He's acting cute with her.
I'm just asking.
The "Yu" from Dayu, the flood controller.
Okay.
I won't quiz you anymore.
So, do you remember my name?
Of course.
I'm just asking.
Why are you laughing?
You always talk so slowly.
Do you think being slow is good?
It's nice, because I'm fast.
Because I'm fast.
So, do you like me this way?
Feels a bit like romance.
It's nice, because I'm fast.
Are you a rapper?
Yeah, do a song.
I'll perform for you.
Go ahead.
Please start your performance.
Do an improv performance.
This is a rare performance.
What's your stage name?
My stage name?
Chi Chi, that's my stage name.
Chi Chi Cake.
Loves cake.
Okay, loves cake.
Got it, I'll remember.
Right here.
The decor here is pretty unique.
But I've really been to this place many times.
Really?
Yeah, because it's really delicious.
Good choice.
Thanks for taking me out today.
I had a great time too.
I'll start with the spicy pork stir-fry.
Okay.
I see you've been eating nonstop.
Yeah, I can really handle spicy food.
Seriously.
I really like eating with people
who can just keep eating.
It makes me have a better appetite.
Yeah.
And I really don't like it
when I'm still eating
and someone says they're full.
Me too.
It just makes me feel like
I don't want to eat anymore.
Same, I lose my appetite too.
Yeah.
Being able to eat together is so important.
It's really, really important.
Seriously, it's important.
Did you come back right after graduation?
You went straight home, right?
Actually, I didn't really
finish my undergraduate degree.
Why?
Back then,
because of my family's
business situation,
I emailed the school
to suspend my studies
and came back to take over the family business.
So you just came back right away?
From being a student, you suddenly became
From a student to suddenly
Was that a big leap?
Definitely a huge leap.
Back in school,
your only pressure
came from your studies.
If you didn't understand something,
you could just ask your teachers or professors.
But in society, there's no one to ask.
Yeah.
Especially for someone like me
with no work experience.
Totally.
I had no idea how to
run and manage a company.
It was really hard at first.
It was long, tough, and hard to get through.
I could only rely on myself
to figure things out.
Yeah, just figure it out on my own.
Sometimes it was really overwhelming.
Maybe it's only gotten a bit better this year.
This year?
Yeah.
Every year, my mindset and thoughts
have changed.
I do feel like I matured faster.
No wonder your friends say
you've grown a lot in the past two years.
Right?
Yeah, that's probably why.
It feels like
a very unique way to grow up.
There's this feeling of
ups and downs,
a sense of highs and lows.
Yeah, there are ups and downs.
So after going through all that,
do you think those ups and downs
were actually worth it, or...
I wouldn't say now that
I'm grateful for
I mean,
the hardships I went through.
Or anything like that, I just think
you should never be thankful for
suffering—suffering is just suffering.
Yeah, I agree.
So what can you actually change?
It’s already happened.
All you can do is
think about how to make the future better.
I totally agree.
Exactly.
Hardship is just hardship.
Never romanticize suffering.
Yes.
Right.
They don’t appreciate hardship.
I’m truly grateful for it.
I think hardship made me who I am today.
I don’t praise suffering either.
But I’m grateful for my own struggles.
But sometimes I think
what feels like hardship now
turns out to be a gift after a few years.
It’s all a gift.
It’s not about thanking hardship.
I think it’s about appreciating
the person you were facing it.
Yeah.
Luckily, I made it through.
I’m so brave, I’m awesome.
Yeah.
After you talked to me that day,
did you regret it?
Or anything else?
So do you know what you’re thinking?
Do you know your thoughts now?
At this moment?
I’m probably a bit slow to realize things.
Honestly, sometimes
I regret it.
Why do I regret it?
I feel like I got
the answer I wanted at the time.
At least this time, it was effective communication.
I think relationship issues
are really hard to handle.
If it happens to someone else,
then it’s like
being an emotional analyst.
But if it happens
to yourself,
you feel like an idiot.
Why?
I feel like
when I do something,
am I
hurting
some people involved?
And then
maybe that’s why
in some
emotional matters, I’m slower.
Is he saying he’s afraid of hurting Yifan?
I’m someone who moves fast.
I know what I want.
I think matching pace is important for two people.
It really matters.
Yeah, see,
her personality,
I think she wants things quickly,
she wants answers fast,
and needs clarity.
No two people
are naturally a perfect match.
Effective communication
is what helps you sync up, right.
You can
slow down or speed up.
That way,
with good communication,
many problems
can be solved.
If you want something,
you have to try your best to get it.
Do your best.
Look, your eyes are shining again.
I can see all the love in your eyes.
Yeah.
Pack up
As long as you want to go
Change for the other person
That’s a kind of
positive feedback
No one is born
as a perfect match
There’s always someone
willing to
make changes
And the other is willing
to compromise
But I’m worried Jin Yuxing is too slow
No, he’s already adjusting
But last time he talked
he was pretty clear expressing himself
about himself
I think Chi Chi is great
I agree
This girl is really nice
Chi Chi is really generous
I really like her
And she’s already twice
taken the initiative
to solve problems
She won’t keep
holding a grudge
She wants to clarify things
I think that’s great
In future relationships
or in the future
after being together for a long time
I think this
is very important
Communication is key
Yes
Right
Her way
makes it easy for others to be with her
You know, many people have to guess
if you’ll say something or not
But if you think about it
Doesn’t Jin Yuxing also make people guess?
Because I think he speaks vaguely
But
Jin Yuxing said
you can ask
as long as you make the question
clear to him
he will
explain and respond
So I think Chi Chi
understands Jin Yuxing
They both get
each other, they have common ground
Yes
Trying their best to get closer
to what you want
This sentence
doesn’t feel pressuring
It’s very comfortable
And I think Jin Yuxing is sincere
because he analyzes his own issues
He said it’s because
of certain reasons
that he’s slow emotionally
He’s aware of his weaknesses
And the other person told him
If you want it
just do your best
That’s nice
I think
in this group
we’ve felt many
heart-fluttering moments
And in this process
I think they
have their own pace
It’s very
much their own rhythm
Next
let’s look forward to
the next group’s date
Who will it be?
Let’s find out together
Squash
Squash is really fun.
Wang Jue
Jue
So happy.
Hello.
You look handsome today.
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
Have you played before?
I haven’t.
I’m a bit nervous.
Have you played before?
I played when I was a kid.
My dad
used to love playing.
He took me a few times.
Maybe you’ll have to teach me today.
Okay.
And I also
I bought some snacks.
We can eat them after playing.
Alright.
Cream puffs.
Thanks.
Just put them here.
Is it here?
Yes, inside here.
Let’s go.
Can you show me first?
Just
Like this.
But how do two people play together?
You can’t let it stop.
After I hit, you return it. After you hit, I return.
You make it look so easy.
Can you teach me?
I’ll give it a try.
I haven’t played in a long time either.
So I might not be a good teacher.
It’s this vertical angle.
Then swing back.
Hit it backwards like this.
Let me try.
I can return all of them.
Not bad.
Seems like I’m getting better.
At least I can play now.
He keeps feeding her balls.
Yeah, keeps feeding balls.
He’s very gentle.
It’s okay.
This is great.
First time with so many rallies.
Almost.
Success.
How about
See if I miss more
or you miss more.
Sure.
If you miss more times,
What does the loser do?
What should they do?
Maybe treat me to food.
Who treats for dinner?
I think it’s a very
I was just thinking that too.
friendly
No, I think
Promise me one thing.
Just
Ride the little train with me.
Right?
Even better.
That’s impressive.
More than anything we thought of.
Better than all our ideas.
Just ride the little train with me.
Yeah.
We were too conservative.
Ride the little train with me.
I like this invitation.
Little train, sure.
If I miss more times,
Then
Pick a gift.
Okay.
Maybe I’ve already prepared one.
She’s already prepared.
What? You’re already prepared?
Not telling you.
What are you talking about?
So do you want to win or lose?
Do you want to win or lose?
You two should just go play squash.
Best of three, okay?
Alright.
Okay.
You’re not going easy.
This works. Good.
Okay.
Why has Wang Jue suddenly changed?
I think she’s super cute right now.
She’s finally opened up.
Yeah.
Awesome.
Alright, you got this.
Looking forward to it.
So, you’re preparing a gift?
Yes.
Can’t wait.
Don’t guess.
A perfect ending.
Should we go eat?
Let’s go.
That was a direct approach too.
Yeah, she’s brave too.
She’s really brave.
She was brave with Le Chen last time too.
But I think it’s different.
Totally different.
Yeah, I think when she’s
with Rui Long, she’s more confident.
Let’s go.
So pretty.
Let’s start eating.
Okay.
Everything looks delicious.
I think today is a rare opportunity.
Feels like we rarely get this in the cabin.
A chance to chat one-on-one.
Yeah.
Usually, when there are many people,
I don’t talk much.
I’m quiet.
Yeah, I know.
I noticed that too.
So I was a bit worried.
I wondered if maybe
you’re someone who doesn’t really like
for example,
showing yourself in front of others.
I worry about that too.
Maybe it’s hard to get close to you.
Yeah, that’s true.
But today, I don’t think that’s the case.
And every time
whether I talk or write,
I think about it for a long time.
Sometimes I
send someone a message,
I’m the type
who can think for half an hour
before sending a single text.
No wonder after you send a message
it takes so long.
Turns out we’re waiting for you.
Will we have to wait long tonight?
Very clear.
Not sure.
He didn’t say directly.
There’s another question.
What is it?
Maybe you’d like to talk about this?
Your thoughts on
your attitude toward relationships.
Or something like that.
Because sometimes, in my experience,
the more I do,
the worse the result.
It just turns out worse.
No.
No, that won’t happen.
Not in the cabin either.
Bro Jiao won’t let you fail.
Bro Jiao is really great.
Yes.
Bro Jiao really
he’s a
very soft-hearted person.
People like that
are super warm.
They’re super warm as friends too.
Duo Duo is similar.
Very caring.
Really good at taking care of others.
But sometimes not so good
at taking care of themselves.
Just
to consider others’ feelings,
they end up neglecting their own
needs.
Rui Long really understands Duo Duo.
What about you?
I think I'm a pretty extreme person.
I either want the best,
or I don't want anything at all.
That sentence...
And you?
I think I'm someone
who sticks firmly to my own ideas.
I know why I do things this way.
I know my reasons.
And I have the motivation to keep going.
So I go ahead and do it.
I feel true to myself.
That's great, really.
Even if you reject me, I'll keep moving forward.
Hope you find your
best match in the house.
This is so heartbreaking.
I feel a bit sad for Wang Jue.
She finally gathered her courage again.
Yeah.
But I think
anything is possible.
Anything is possible.
They're talking about different things.
It's really brave for a girl to do this.
It's pretty good too.
Everything's been made clear.
No one regrets it.
I've said everything I needed to.
But from what just happened,
I feel even more that Ruilong
is someone
who's very perceptive.
He's not dull at all.
He just makes himself
look dull.
Pretending to be clueless makes things less awkward.
Before Wang Jue
expressed herself so directly,
Ruilong was actually
pretty relaxed.
Then Wang Jue
took a step forward,
and he immediately stepped back.
Then during dinner,
he showed his thoughts
completely
and openly.
He's quite smart.
But I
really hope Wang Jue
can find someone
who sees her as Wang Jue
and as the very best.
Yeah.
She said before
"I don't want to be
the second choice."
Right.
Next,
let's check out Dr. Fang
and Lan Lan's date.
Tulips.
Maybe they have a special meaning.
Here they come.
Thank you.
Did you guess what we're doing today?
Playing ball.
What kind of ball?
No idea.
On the card you drew before,
billiards.
Billiards.
Just take this with you.
Didn't you want to play?
Okay.
Then teach me.
But I think teaching billiards
is also
a great
and romantic gesture.
That's right.
So teach me.
Actually, I'm not very good either.
Then let's
try something we've never done before.
We can
do some novices competing stuff.
Sure.
Today you gave me
your favorite flower.
Yeah.
Sit over here.
Okay.
It's the flower guys like most.
Last time I gave you that peony, right?
Last time it was your favorite flower.
So this time I picked
the flower I like.
But it's my favorite color.
Do you like it?
I love it.
Those two
Look,
their logic for giving flowers is totally different.
Telling you what I like.
Once for what I like.
Once for what you like.
That's bold.
In this relationship,
I'm important too.
So it makes the girl feel
kind of
like meeting a worthy opponent.
So we
I...
Have you played billiards before?
Just a little.
But not very well.
I'm not good either.
Let me try.
Okay.
Your turn.
Alright.
The position of your white ball
is a bit tough for me.
You can hit it again.
If not, just hit it softly.
Billiards is actually a pretty good game.
You did well just hitting it.
I'm really a newbie.
Seeing how bad I am,
does that make you feel better?
It's really novices competing.
I'll break them up a bit.
Didn't you say
you've been playing billiards with friends lately?
Just started.
Really just started.
Okay.
Sure.
I'll clear some of mine.
Then you can
see your balls more clearly.
Alright.
Right?
Okay.
Nice.
You got two in a row.
This one's hard to get in.
I think you can.
See, I told you.
Go again.
Your turn.
Give me a rest, please.
Thanks.
Impressive.
Finally gave you a chance to get some applause.
Keep going.
The cue ball went in.
That's a penalty.
So now you should
I get a free ball.
Can you get it for me?
Okay.
"Bossy" doctor.
Your observation skills aren't sharp enough.
What do you mean?
Your observation isn't detailed enough.
What's wrong?
What's up?
Nothing, I'll tell you later.
Is there something inside?
There's a ball inside.
It's a surprise.
Yeah.
Right.
He thought she would notice.
But she didn't notice.
So he asked her to get it.
She found it.
A small ball.
A blue ball.
Your observation skills aren't sharp either.
Found it.
What do you think this is?
This set of numbers.
A numeric code.
It's a warning with no repetition.
It's the golden window for resuscitation.
It's the number of human chromosome pairs.
Plus the DNA helix structure.
This set of numbers is the code of life.
Which numbers?
Take a guess.
Because she said she's sapiosexual.
She likes smart people.
Which number has no repetition?
Which number doesn't repeat?
Zero.
That's it.
What do you mean by "that's it"?
Zero.
Right.
And then?
Go on.
There's more.
The golden window for resuscitation.
Do you know?
No.
Five minutes.
Zero five.
It's the number of human chromosome pairs.
Do you know this one?
No.
Twenty-three.
The DNA helix structure.
I really don't know.
What structure is it?
Double helix.
Double helix, two.
Yes.
Add it up.
So together it's
Zero five two five.
What does zero five two five mean?
Does this number have any meaning?
No idea.
I didn't give you a gift when you arrived.
Were you a little disappointed?
No.
Not disappointed.
Just seeing you makes me happy.
I'm happy just to see you.
Okay, actually it's a string of
numbers, a code.
leading to where I'll give you a gift.
What’s this?
Try making the first shot.
Okay.
I really like his design.
This is nice.
And “0525” is
us,
the first day
we met.
The day we met.
So sweet.
The day we first met.
He’s really into rituals.
And you know,
what’s most important?
Did you notice?
We’re giving gifts,
but not directly.
You have to stretch out the process.
You want the treasure,
but first I’ll give you
a treasure map.
And when they’re together,
Dr. Fang doesn’t
constantly flatter Lan Lan.
Right.
He’ll say,
“You’re not observant enough.”
Yeah.
Yes.
They challenge each other.
These two are a great match.
Hurry, she’s opening the gift.
Looking forward to the gift.
Such a brain-teasing process.
Is it perfume?
Yes.
How did you know?
Thank you.
Thanks.
I think this
is something you’ll like.
It’s right from the heart.
Do you want to see the others?
A photo of us.
A photo from our first date.
Yes.
Very thoughtful.
That day, I arrived early
and asked the owner to take it for us.
I told him in advance.
So considerate.
You look so handsome.
You look even prettier.
How are you so cute?
This whole sequence
is a bit hard to figure out.
This puzzle.
No.
Aren’t you usually quick at guessing?
Can you hold this for me?
Sure.
Thank you.
Bowling.
So what did you see?
I saw
What is it?
There’s a claw machine.
Yeah.
He’s good at guiding Lan Lan.
This is for you.
The second gift.
It’s also a gift for me.
A note.
I wrote nine of them.
I’ve really learned a lot.
The things I want to do with you in the cabin
are all written inside
the capsule toy.
There are many.
Nine in total.
If you want to do them with me,
you can pick one out
every day.
Okay.
Look.
No matter who you meet,
you have to do one thing with me each day.
Right.
For nine days in a row.
I really feel the charm of intelligence.
Dr. Fang
Before doing this,
he was already
very confident.
Let me show you how to use it.
First,
put a coin in.
Then grab one.
This one.
Like this.
I’m really looking forward to this.
You want to do two things.
One will pop out randomly.
Do you want to check now
or later?
Later.
Okay.
Then keep it.
Alright.
Do you have a pocket?
Yes.
Put it in your pocket.
Sure.
Are you good at bowling?
Do you want to play?
Come on.
Now it’s
our time together.
Start with your right foot.
Right.
No.
You need to step with your right foot first.
Then when you reach that spot,
that’s when you swing your arm, right?
This isn’t what I expected.
Dr. Fang almost swung himself out.
You’re even less coordinated than me.
Try again.
Not elegant at all.
So awkward.
I’ll just run myself.
Alright.
You bowl.
Your form is textbook.
I think you’ll get a strike.
You guessed it.
You’re amazing.
Want to try the basketball machine?
Sure.
Darn it.
Didn’t make a single shot.
Challenge failed.
No way, this is hilarious.
I’m really not good at any of these games.
Claw machine.
I’m decent at the claw machine.
This cute puppy
looks a bit like you.
Let me try.
How did you get two?
Which one do you want?
I want
this one.
This one.
Thank you.
When you got one,
why didn’t you say anything?
Because I wanted to get two.
I’m really mad.
You didn’t get any.
Didn’t get one.
Do you still want to try?
I’m done.
I’m upset.
Then
let’s eat.
I picked
a Thai restaurant.
I love Thai food.
I brought you Kang Shifu jasmine pomelo tea.
Thank you.
And a bouquet.
Such delicate jasmine flowers.
Thank you.
Let’s toast.
It’s the familiar jasmine fragrance.
And the sweet, refreshing taste of grapefruit.
It’s really delicious.
As long as you like it.
Let’s all raise a toast.
And then,
I have something to give you.
Yes.
I prepared a gift for you this time.
She has a gift too.
Try guessing what it is first.
Based on the hints I gave you.
I probably only mentioned that I like playing badminton.
So I think it might be
a racket.
Is that right?
Let me take it out for you.
It definitely is.
This one,
this length.
Yes.
That’s because
I heard you mention before
that you play badminton.
But I didn’t expect, at the sports day,
you played so well.
And we even won the match.
So I
Thank you.
got you a badminton racket.
There are a few other things inside.
But the main thing is the racket.
This is really nice.
And I hope you can
keep doing what you love.
You really play well.
Thank you.
No need to thank me.
I really like it.
A shy smile.
Both of them can
guess each other’s gifts.
They’re evenly matched.
This counts as a surprise.
Really?
Didn’t you give me one today—
a claw machine?
Didn’t you grab a (little ball)?
Let’s take a look.
I’ll open it.
Because you already know what’s inside.
I don’t know exactly what it is.
I just know there are nine.
What is it?
Five minutes.
That staring contest.
Can you look away?
No, you can’t.
You can’t look away either.
No laughing.
Okay.
Then I’ll have to think of sad things.
If you laugh, you have to start over.
Restart the timer.
Okay.
So this—
Doesn’t this mean we just keep staring?
Keep playing until no one laughs?
Okay.
Why are we starting now?
I’ll get shy.
I lost.
If I get serious, you’ll definitely lose.
Who can handle this?
I can’t take it.
No, I really can’t hold it in.
You’re setting yourself up.
I just want to laugh when I see you.
Do I look that funny?
Not funny.
You look good.
Seeing something beautiful makes me smile.
I feel my heart
beats really fast.
Yeah.
So can you really
win a staring contest?
It doesn’t really matter.
That moment of eye contact—
You've already won her over.
I have a suggestion.
Minghao, I want to see you and her have a staring contest.
Let's see who laughs first.
This—
This is going to be great.
Wait a second.
Pinky swear first.
No catching feelings.
You're a family man.
Don't mess around.
So, you can't.
I think doing things with you
that you're not good at
is really interesting.
Yeah, if I'm really good at it
and you're not,
Right.
It's not as fun to play.
Yeah.
When you're not good at something,
I find it
really funny.
Because I think
in life, things that
genuinely make me laugh
and feel happy
aren't that many.
Is your life that tough?
It's not tough.
I just think
my threshold for happiness is high.
Yeah, it's pretty high.
Right, I like being with
people who can make me laugh.
Friends too,
all of them.
Thai food is delicious.
Just looking at it makes me hungry.
Let's eat.
Do you want some shrimp?
Will you peel it?
If you don't mind, I'll peel it for you.
Why would I mind?
This back and forth—
Did you see that?
Someone peels for you and you still mind?
That person is really ungrateful.
This is just awesome.
So satisfying, I love watching this.
I'll peel this and give it to you.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Careful not to drop it in.
I have another question.
Choose one.
Do I look better with or without glasses?
You want the truth?
Yes, the truth.
Honestly, both look good.
But if I had to pick glasses for you,
I probably wouldn't choose
round frames.
What then, rimless?
No.
Square ones.
Of course Xiao Fang should wear square glasses.
Xiao Fang is wearing blue.
Doesn't everyone call me Dr. Fang?
In the cabin,
you were the first
to call me Xiao Fang.
Didn't you introduce yourself
as Xiao Fang from the start?
Xiao Fang.
I feel like she's already acting cute.
Right?
Yeah.
But it really is just my workplace.
Even people younger than me call me Xiao Fang.
At my workplace,
everyone calls me Xiao Xu.
I can't imagine it.
I mentioned it last time.
Said you wore a hat.
And you were at the construction site.
If you put on glasses too,
it's even harder to picture.
Back when I was in school,
I would
have classes like that.
Where you had to wear a hat to the site.
So when your parents named you,
was there a special meaning?
I explained it on the first day.
I forgot.
You don't remember?
You'd better think again.
Darn it.
Did you really say it on the first day?
On the beach.
After the beach ATV ride.
You wrapped yourself in that blanket.
When it was really cold.
Girls always remember.
There's an ancient poem.
"In spring, the river turns green as blue."
Darn it, I dug myself a hole.
That look in your eyes.
I really forgot.
So intense.
I remember now.
A poem.
That poem is called
"Reminiscence of Jiangnan."
"In spring, the river turns green as blue."
I remember now.
And both of them (my parents)
also love the color blue.
But the name "Ru Lan"
really sounds beautiful.
It's so romantic.
What's wrong?
Are you going to play that
no-laughing game with me?
I'm already playing.
So sweet.
I love watching this kind of push and pull.
Push and pull.
So much chemistry.
Don’t you think
after watching something like this,
it feels so satisfying.
Yeah.
It’s like riding
a roller coaster.
It’s really enjoyable.
Can you peel the shrimp for me?
If you don’t mind, I’ll do it.
Why would I mind?
Are you playing that five-minute game again?
I’m already playing.
I’m not memorizing it on purpose,
but it’s just stuck in my head.
It’s just stuck in my head.
I can’t get rid of it.
These two are real pros.
Last time,
their date
was still about
testing each other.
Polite.
But this time,
they’re not holding back.
Yeah.
Dr. Fang really changed things up this time.
Compared to how he used to express himself,
it’s totally different.
Lan Lan is also different today.
It’s the first time seeing her like this.
And Dr. Fang,
it’s also the first time seeing him like this.
These two really have
sparks flying between them.
I think Lan Lan is really into
Dr. Fang.
Because you’ll notice Dr. Fang
is great at guiding her.
Lan Lan likes this kind of
back-and-forth interaction.
She finds it
interesting.
She wants to explore it.
A clash of titans.
Dr. Fang keeps saying
last time it was your favorite flower,
this time it’s mine.
When giving the claw machine, he said
this is a gift for you,
and also for us.
This claw machine
is really nice.
And his way is great
because it gives Lan Lan a reason to get closer to him.
There’s a basis for it.
So I think with love,
sometimes you shouldn’t forget to show yourself.
Express yourself.
I want to get to know you,
but please get to know me too.
Yeah.
Got it.
Alright, everyone,
we’re about to see
our last couple,
Le Chen and Duo Duo’s
date.
Let’s
look forward to it.
Everyone, let’s watch.
Le Chen.
Duo Duo looks great.
Le Chen looks great in a white shirt too.
Hello.
Hi.
Welcome to my turf.
This is awesome.
So awesome.
The diving center.
It’s great.
Today I fulfilled
a little dream I had before coming.
Yeah.
Don’t they both love scuba diving?
Let’s go change first.
Okay, let’s go.
Here.
Hello.
Duoduo has that kind of healthy beauty.
She’s a girl full of energy.
Let’s wait for the coach.
Okay, let’s sit for a bit.
Sit down.
How long has it been since you last dived?
It’s been about half a year.
Then you need to get used to it again.
We’ll start from scratch.
Alright, starting over.
Yes, that pool.
We’ll go scuba diving soon.
You haven’t tried scuba diving before, right?
There’s surfing next to it, I think.
Yeah, we can go surfing later.
If you still have energy,
you can go swimming.
But you don’t know how, do you?
I learn quickly.
Really?
I pick things up fast.
Put on the gear first.
Okay.
Alright, I’ll briefly explain the moves.
When snorkeling on the surface,
we need to use our hands
to hold and steady our head.
Use your hand to guide your direction.
Is that okay?
Can the girls try it once?
Amazing!
Your finning technique was excellent.
The rhythm was great too.
Thank you.
Okay.
Can the guys give it a try?
Don’t be nervous.
I did pretty well, actually.
So cute.
She’s really happy.
Both of them can do it.
Is it still okay?
It’s more than okay.
Very impressive.
Talent.
Let’s do it this way.
After we go down,
let’s swim two laps, okay?
Sure.
I want to go out and play.
The girls are amazing.
I want to swim now.
I really want to try this.
It's kind of romantic.
Sure.
Are you still okay?
I'm still good.
I can do another round.
That's fine too.
I think it's still okay.
I think it's a bit easier than before.
Should we go through that opening?
It's even deeper inside.
Okay.
So much fighting spirit.
You're really determined.
I'm fired up.
I can feel it.
Now let's try scuba diving.
Okay.
Putting on the oxygen tank.
Love.
Nice.
This is so fun.
So much fun.
Really fun.
Fun.
Are you still okay?
I'm still good.
This looks really fun.
Are we surfing?
It's huge.
This wave feels awesome.
Let's warm up first, okay?
We can do some simple ones.
Wrists and ankles. (stretching)
Loosen up.
Okay.
I'm already tired.
I'm tired already.
But Duoduo didn't seem to hear.
Didn't hear.
Okay.
Alright.
Then if you come over here,
Let's pick a helmet first.
Come on.
Yeah, move slowly.
Walk slowly.
Stepped on it.
Step on the board.
No.
Don't.
Feels a bit scary.
No way.
You can do it.
Don't.
The board should lean against the wall.
Step down with your foot.
You got this.
Go for it!
Don't be nervous.
Let me try.
So hard.
Yeah.
Look straight ahead.
Right.
She learns so fast.
She's really good.
So impressive.
Amazing.
Duoduo has so much energy.
Come on.
These two.
Wiping out together
Thank you
Surfing is so much fun
Yeah, this looks really fun
Yeah, it really does
He looks totally wiped out
He kept wiping out with me
Are you out of energy?
I got knocked silly by the waves
Take a break, you look exhausted
No regrets, right?
None, thanks
You look really tired
Want to eat?
Let’s go
A day for building muscle
Let’s eat something first
You worked hard today
It wasn’t hard for me
You seem to have endless energy
Really
You know me
My friend said something about me
She said I’m like a dog breed
A terrier
And she said
Terriers are known for
Always having
Lots of energy every day
She’s right
Yeah
But today, surfing
I just ran out of energy at the end
Right?
The waves made my head spin
I feel like my brain is
Seeing stars already
First time it’s been this vivid
Why do you like scuba diving?
I think
When you stay in the water
It feels so quiet around you
It relieves stress
It’s like
You feel like you’ve
Left the world behind
That feeling is really unique
It truly is
Definitely
So I really recommend you
Give it a try
It’s really interesting
Scuba diving lets me
Forces me to slow down
I’m actually a fast-paced person
I also chase efficiency
But lately, life
Has forced me to slow down
Since coming to the house, do you feel
Any changes?
Me?
I think I’ve changed a lot
At least in
My desire to express myself
I’ve made a lot of progress
But actually, expressing yourself
Is more about
Having someone willing to listen
Usually
Many people don’t really
Empathize with you
Or they don’t really
Care about you
So after coming to the house
There’s someone willing to listen
And even someone who can empathize
Yeah
Actually, I'm really curious.
Have you ever met
guys like me before?
What type are you?
I don't know, what type do you think I am?
How do you define yourself?
I want to see how you see me.
I'm just an ordinary person.
I'm ordinary too. Everyone's ordinary.
Yeah.
I think
when I'm with you,
it's always pleasant.
So, so far, being together
feels easy and happy.
Easy and happy.
Very comfortable.
That's good.
I feel like you really have your own
set hobbies.
I think that's actually pretty important.
I think having a hobby
is really important.
It helps you use your spare time
in a meaningful way.
And through that hobby,
you grow again.
So I'm really grateful too.
I think
everyone seems to give me
positive feedback.
This kind of positive feedback
is something in my daily life
that's hard to get.
What about you?
Actually, I think I'm
someone who never gives up.
I'm persistent.
As long as I care about someone,
Because
when I was in middle school,
there was a girl I was really close to.
She deleted me after she went to college.
But I
tried to add her every year, even every month.
I kept sending her friend requests.
Well, maybe not every month.
Why?
Maybe every three or four months.
Because I think
What were you thinking?
My thought was
her sudden departure
must have a reason.
So I kept trying to add her from time to time.
Until the second year,
she suddenly accepted my friend request.
So how are you two now?
We're good now.
If it were me, I definitely wouldn't do that.
If it were me,
she
if she left, then
that's her decision.
So I respect her choice.
Go with the flow.
She can just reject me.
She can directly reject me.
If she accepts, I probably won't add her again.
Yeah.
As long as you don't reject me,
I think you have your reasons.
So I'll keep trying.
Unless you clearly reject me.
So their ways of handling relationships
are actually quite different.
I think
I'm the one who's more afraid of missing out.
So you try to keep
the important people around you
close.
You want to hold on to them.
Yeah, I think it's mutual.
So the relationship is stronger.
No regrets.
What do you think?
I rarely try to
hold on to friends on purpose.
Because I think
maybe
at every stage
you meet new friends.
Yeah, of course.
Because you're changing.
The atmosphere feels a bit off.
Tastes good.
But I’ll definitely have a late-night snack when I get back.
Alright, let’s talk more back at the cabin.
Okay.
Let’s leave it at that for now.
Alright.
Thank you.
Seatbelt.
Okay.
Do you like Hangzhou?
Actually, I’ve stayed in Hangzhou
for quite a long time.
I think it really is
a comfortable city.
And I feel like
in my whole life
I haven’t really left Zhejiang.
Right?
Like,
I went to college here in the province.
My family’s also here.
So it’s like my whole life
has never really left Zhejiang.
I’ve never really left Zhejiang.
Because it feels like
I’ve always been here,
just going in circles.
Like a spinning top.
Is someone pushing you from behind?
It’s gotten to that point.
It’s already
pushing you forward.
Are you okay with that?
Have you ever
been in that kind of role before?
If I look at it from a third-person perspective,
I think I have.
And I think I’ve been like that in every relationship.
I have.
Would you be willing to hold the whip for a lifetime?
I think maybe I don’t even
feel like I’m holding a whip.
Like when I socialize, people think
Duoduo, you don’t have to entertain everyone.
That’s true.
They both have different traits.
I’m not deliberately trying to amuse you.
Because I’m genuinely happy myself.
I also hope
I can always
stay in this state.
What if the other person still doesn’t change?
What if they still don’t change?
If they don’t change, then so be it.
I’ll just look for
common ground in the differences.
Find common ground in the differences.
It seems like you’re always
comforting yourself.
I’m not comforting myself.
I’ve said before
I’m someone who can let go
but also has trouble moving on.
And I don’t think he’s
never tried to change.
It’s just that everyone changes at their own pace.
I think he is changing.
It’s just that the speed
isn’t what I’d hoped for.
I think adults only choose, not adjust.
Adults only choose, not adjust.
Disagree but respect.
Do you still have time to adjust?
Not good.
This atmosphere
is really not good.
I think it’s sincere.
It’s heartfelt.
It’s impossible for me to just
meet someone who’s a perfect match right away.
Yeah.
So you have to look for
Or maybe
he actually
how likely is it you’ll find that?
I’m not talking about a perfect match.
I mean
the gap between you
is something you can
resolve fairly easily.
Or at least narrow the gap.
Instead of
right from the start
having to do so many things
and spend so much time
just to make it work.
It’s not a long march.
Before you get into a relationship with someone,
do you imagine a lot about your future together?
Or do you think about it in general?
I do.
How far ahead do you think?
From the moment I
decide to be with someone,
I’m already thinking about
us getting married and having kids.
Honestly,
Really?
It’s actually stressful.
Isn’t that expectation
a bit too high?
But I think it shows sincerity.
First of all,
if I enter a relationship with this hope,
when I start this relationship,
then I must be
holding myself to this standard.
But I might not say it out loud.
Like telling you to be a good husband first,
or a good father.
This attitude I’m talking about
is a requirement for myself.
I put myself in a position
where I feel I’m compatible with you,
and able to go far together.
The two of them are completely
different.
I think if
that day really comes
when we have to part ways,
I’ll accept it willingly.
No.
That’s your opinion.
If you had to choose,
would you only choose to walk part of the way with her,
or with her,
walk all the way?
Duoduo.
No, I wouldn’t think that way.
Both of them are
No, I don’t agree.
Love debate.
I just finished watching.
But they’re both very genuine.
By the way,
No, I wouldn’t think that way.
Because you’re going in with assumptions.
I wouldn’t have
those assumptions.
I think no one knows
how far the future will go.
I’ve been thinking about something these past few days.
That is,
feeling moved,
and being suitable
are two different things.
Right.
I think this needs
to be felt, just like when you’re scuba diving.
You have to feel it yourself.
Yes.
Alright.
It’s a bit stressful.
It sounds a bit tense.
But this
they really did discuss
many unique
and worthwhile topics.
Because in previous
conversations,
too often
it felt a bit off.
It always felt
a bit awkward.
But I never figured out
why it was awkward.
I think my thoughts and
Le Chen’s thoughts
are quite similar.
It’s not that
you’ll definitely find
a perfect
match.
But I think you can
find someone generally
suitable.
The small details
can be worked out
between two people.
I wouldn’t want to change the other person.
And I don’t want them to change me a lot either.
Of course, I used to think
I wanted to meet the so-called
It seemed like there would be someone in this world
who
just clicks with you
Yes, so perfect
You’d feel
like the other person matches
everything you like
But later you realize no one is
truly perfect
I have a friend
who never exercised before
Then he met
his partner
At first
maybe push-ups
he couldn’t even do one
Now he can do several
I think he didn’t change just for his partner
but he saw his partner was better that way
and wanted to try
You know what I mean?
That kind of thing goes both ways
It’s not like
I get it
I’m with you
so I want to please you
and become what you want me to be
It feels more like two people growing together
and realizing it’s better this way
Whether it’s choosing or changing
everyone has their own
standard
So the two of them
are both on different
personal standards
while talking
When many people hear about change
they instinctively resist
Why should I change?
This is who I am
But people who change
aren’t giving up themselves
But if the change
is relatively positive
or something you can accept
then why resist it?
Growth itself is a kind of change
But since our audience
is mostly
young people,
I think from
a practical perspective,
choosing the right person
is actually quite difficult.
Especially for those between eighteen
and twenty-five years old,
which in psychology
is called emerging adulthood.
Young people at this stage
have lives
full of changes.
They don’t know
which city to work in,
what career path to take,
or what kind of person suits them.
So for very young people,
I think experiencing
is more important than selecting.
Only by
growing through relationships
can you learn
how to live within them.
You’ll know what suits you,
and what doesn’t.
Sometimes we
not only understand ourselves better
through relationships,
but are also shaped
by them.
Some relationships
have shaped
how we now
view love,
and family,
and all these things.
So I think good
relationship experiences
are very important.
Even bad ones
teach you something different.
It’s all part of love,
it’s a process,
just an experience.
So for young people,
I still encourage everyone
to experience more,
to love more.
Just like we’ve all
heard this saying:
Is the process more important,
or the result?
My instinct is to think
the result matters more,
because I’m result-oriented.
The result is important.
But that day,
I heard someone
sharing their thoughts,
and suddenly
it became clear to me.
He said it’s definitely
the process that matters.
Because the process determines the result.
I personally think these two things
actually go together.
Like you just said,
if you work hard now
to create happiness,
you’re actually building
its long-term outcome.
So two people,
one day,
whether it’s the first day together
or after ten years,
might say, “Let’s get married.”
And the two of them
agree.
Only the process is real.
The result is vague and uncertain.
For me personally,
I think
we shouldn’t focus
too much on the result.
Yes.
Focus on
enjoying happiness in the moment,
and actually,
wherever you end up is where you’re meant to be.
Great.
Our
first day of dates
and second day of dates
are all finished now.
Each
date was really meaningful.
It’s not just about feeling moved.
It’s also a meeting of minds.
And right now,
everyone needs lots of interaction
to get to know each other.
So let’s look forward to
what happens next in the house
and see
what stories unfold.
I want to chat with you.
Sure.
Lu Yuan.
I want to talk with you.
Well,
based on my past experience,
because before,
I moved too fast.
That led to
the whole
relationship becoming
rushed and careless.
Actually, I hope
to get to know someone slowly.
I’m just confused.
You know?
I get it.
Darn it, I’ll go beat up Le Chen.
That’s kind of cute.
But I think saying this
is a good thing.
First of all,
I understand.
Just do what you need to do.
Being happy is most important.
And then,
Yeah, I’m definitely not
just talking without feeling the pain.
I’m someone with back pain too.
You have back pain too.
I have back pain as well.
We both have back pain.
Yeah, I have back pain too.
So,
there’s really nothing we can do.
It’s just
maybe this is
the hardship of love.
I’m trying now
to find joy in hardship.
Find joy in hardship.
You make yourself sound so heroic.
There’s no way around it.
See,
there’s really no solution, right?
No solution at all.
Because
the answer is with the other person.
Xiao Jiao’s mindset is better now.
He used to struggle on his own.
Now he can even
comfort and encourage others.
I think
you should cherish every moment
you spend with him.
Just be together.
Instead of
overthinking everything.
I think we came back
a bit too late.
No, I see some cars haven’t returned yet.
Really?
There’s still a badminton racket here.
Shall we play ball later?
Later.
If you're not tired, we can play.
Playing ball at midnight.
Are you feeling better now?
Much better.
How about your neck?
My neck's still not better.
Is it the left or right side?
Both sides.
Both.
He really cares about her.
Are you tired?
I am tired.
But happiness cancels it out.
All the tiredness.
Is there a little extra happiness?
Maybe even overflowing.
They can't finish a sentence together.
Bro Herry, are you
a slow-to-warm-up person?
I match the other person's vibe.
I become like them.
You're like a mirror.
We just follow along.
That look from Xiao Jiao.
Lan Lan.
Hello.
Hi.
Well...
There should be more change.
Change the subject.
Hello.
Hi.
You're back.
Did you just get back?
We've been back for a while.
We were eating over there.
I thought we were the first ones back.
Who else is back?
Lan Lan.
I made some soup.
I want some.
I'll put my stuff away first, then come down.
I feel awful.
I'll take them to have soup.
Okay.
Go.
Where are you having soup?
The kitchen.
Kitchen.
Does he really want to go over?
No, his soul is already there.
Do you want some soup?
I made soup.
We've all had some already.
It's really good.
Yeah.
Is Chi Chi going?
Sure, let's go.
I'll come back and eat later.
Okay.
Come back and eat.
You have soup first.
I'll go have soup first.
Quick, find an excuse.
Someone invite me over for soup.
Want some melon?
Have some more melon.
Eating melon.
Melon time.
The word "eating melon" is kind of...
You know how to talk.
You really know how to talk.
Wang Jue is blushing now.
Hello, everyone.
Hi.
You're the last one back today.
Chen, what's going on?
The car wheels were speed-limited today.
I really want to sleep.
No, what did you do today?
What about them?
What did you two do today?
And them?
Upstairs.
Over there.
They're over there.
Having porridge.
Having soup.
Don't want to talk about it.
Seems like everyone except Dr. Fang and Lan Lan
is feeling down.
Is it good?
Feels like the atmosphere is off.
It's painful to be stuck here.
Feels like everyone has something on their mind.
In everyone’s heart,
there’s a sense of exhaustion.
This is for you.
What?
Aren’t you the one who...
Thank you.
That’s so thoughtful.
I just happened to see it on the way.
Stop saying it was on the way, bro.
How “on the way” was it, really?
Was it even the same route?
I can’t just admit I went out of my way to buy it for you.
I just remembered.
That thing from yesterday.
I forgot.
I want that book.
It’s up there.
Here, take it.
Thank you.
Thanks.
I’ll return it to you later.
Go read the first chapter, it’s hilarious.
Really? The “Chejing” part, right?
I’m reading the foreword right now.
You don’t need to read the foreword.
Just read the “Chejing” section.
This date,
really was...
really made my heart ache.
Who’s actually happy right now?
Lan Lan.
Dr. Fang.
So tonight,
it’s not over yet.
Everyone, let’s keep going.
Let’s keep watching.
Let’s go.
Good night.
Finally, I can take off my makeup.
I’ll take out my contacts first.
You went out today,
and wore contacts all day?
Aren’t your eyes dry?
Not at all.
I was out exercising all day today,
and my eyes felt fine.
Really?
Then I’ll try it next time.
I think
if you’re out for a long time,
choosing good contacts
is pretty important.
Yeah.
Hi, this—
is what I told you about.
This is the gift she prepared, right?
This color is really...
I think it looks like your eye color.
Panda?
Panda.
Thank you.
They’re all brave.
Panda, guqin
It’s so cozy here.
This is my bed.
Then I’ll come over.
Should I sit here?
Sure.
Are you feeling any better?
I don’t think so.
I’m not very good at
handling friendships and signals.
Right now I feel
powerless.
And I tend to avoid conflict.
And I can’t be like
some really mature people.
She might handle things gracefully.
Even if something’s up between us,
when everyone’s around,
I still show how I feel.
But I just can’t hide it.
I wear my emotions on my face.
Don’t be too hard on yourself.
I think you’ve done really well.
You did great today.
Unlike me, I’m just a “deserter.”
Is it because you’re not sure yet,
or you don’t know how to handle it?
That question really hit home.
I don’t know.
I’m just a mess right now.
After my date today,
I thought it was okay.
It was pretty
pretty good.
But after I got back,
I was confused again.
Us—
Can we add more soup and cook it again?
But it won’t be as flavorful.
Why isn’t the water boiling?
Mine’s already boiling.
Drink something lighter.
Don’t drink too much salty stuff.
I barely added any seasoning.
Is there any winter melon?
Yes.
Mushrooms are fine.
Mushrooms.
I’ll head back first.
Okay.
But after I got back,
I was confused again.
Us—
Are you like this too?
Me too.
Not exactly confused,
but I do feel a bit
like today’s date
was almost like we didn’t go out.
They really connected.
Don’t squish my cream puff.
Sorry.
Total headache.
I think sometimes for girls,
this kind of friendship
means having someone to talk to.
Going through things together.
Yeah, that’s great.
Understanding each other.
Between close friends,
talking things out
is better than keeping it inside.
Saw Dr. Fang.
What are you doing?
Washing a vase.
Do you like it?
Huh?
How could I not like it?
Didn’t expect you got a badminton racket too.
I just sent one out.
And you already got one.
You don’t think
I sent it, do you?
How did it end up back in the room?
No, the box is different.
These two are such trouble.
Here it comes.
Vase.
Thanks.
It’s heavy.
Be careful.
Thanks.
Good night.
Actually, I think this spot is set.
The one knocking
should be Xiao Jiao.
Seems like it’s always snacks for her.
I feel a bit sorry.
Here you are.
Right on time.
Sorry, this is for you.
And this is
for muscle relaxation.
You can use it tonight.
I just think
if you haven't skied in a while,
your muscles might get sore.
Yeah, I was sore all night.
I don't know if today
you'll feel a bit sore too.
I wrote something else on it.
It's written on there.
Thank you.
Okay, bye, good night.
Good night.
Giving gifts every day,
that's really impressive.
Xiao Jiao really is
someone who gives it their all.
This is for you.
You can read it tomorrow.
Got a letter.
Now that you said that,
I want to read it right now.
You can read it today if you want.
It's up to you.
Read it whenever you like.
Then I...
Now I don't know
if I should read it today or tomorrow.
Either is fine.
I just don't want
since you went out today,
reading this to affect your mood.
So read it whenever you want.
You can wait until
after texting to read it, that's fine too.
There are still a lot of variables with these three.
Very sincere.
Really genuine.
There's a second page.
There's another page.
Such a sincere letter.
It's touching.
His way of communicating
is a lot like Chi Chi's.
He lays everything out.
This is his third time explaining.
His texts the past two days were explanations too.
It's actually quite moving.
It does touch you.
These days, getting
a handwritten letter like this is rare.
These past few days of dates
everyone's feeling down
this is what love is
I think this round of dates
most importantly, we need
to give everyone
some time to process
because honestly, everyone
in this little house
during this period
belongs to each other
from strangers to friends
to feeling a spark
to making some
heartfelt connections
everyone's emotions
are really intense
so maybe everyone
expresses themselves to each other
the way we interact
is very intense
I think after this intensity
maybe we all need
a little time
to let each other
process everything
I'm afraid of missing out
I thought things would get clearer
but it's actually more complicated
it really is
thought it would be clearer
Chi Chi was just about to be clear
Zi Han seems to shine even more
yeah, that's true
we're halfway through the show
and we
all kinds of emotions
are intertwined in this episode
yeah
so let's look forward to
the upcoming love stories
and see how they unfold
that's all for today's show
we're ending here
Jasmine blooming is the signal of love
this show is sponsored by
Kang Shifu Jasmine Tea, with floral aroma and fresh taste
as our title sponsor
every Thursday at noon
extra reality show content
unlock more love clues
every Friday and Saturday at noon
watching love with you
Heart Signal family cross-season collaboration
so you can ship to your heart's content
go to Tencent Video Caocangdi
get the same love merchandise as the guests with one click
see you all next time
let's fall in love together
see you next week
Heartbeat Apartment welcomes
its second open day.
There are also mysterious guests visiting.
Who?
I'm coming out.
Really?
You went?
It's not just you.
You went too?
They're here.
The friends and family are here.
This is so much pressure.
The male guests are all stunned.
That's too much.
He's nervous.
I think she's not very happy.
Maybe there are some misunderstandings.
This is a matter of ability.
I'll choose tonight.
Do you think it's appropriate?
That's too intense.
I prefer someone with
a more stable core.
That's the problem.
There's no real focus.
I just came down.
What does it look like?
Very handsome.
I'll come back earlier.
Your cooking is really delicious.
Thank you.
Watch me for a bit.
I'm a bit shy to watch.
When are my clothes not pretty?
They're pretty every day.
Maybe to Germany or Switzerland
for development.
I'll work hard.
I feel like my fins are bigger.
First time hearing that.
Someone saying their fins are bigger.
I just like this kind of messiness.
It's very much your
style.
Pause.
I'm going to judge now.
It's a bit heavy.
I think her answer to you
wasn't satisfying.
Do you feel uncomfortable?
Even I feel uncomfortable with this atmosphere.
Isn't this a bit too soon?
That's right.
The conversation in the car
Why is it always so awkward?
The atmosphere is a bit subtle.
Help.
Today's icebreaker game
is the "Guess the Noun Challenge."
What exactly is this?
Yes.
So your punishment is
Okay.
Can I run away?