What are you studying here?
I'm studying management. What about you?
I'm studying medicine.
Will you be my girlfriend,
my naughty girl?
Lada must break up with that girl
and marry the man I chose for her.
Hello.
If you break up with Lada,
I promise to take great care of your mom.
We're done.
Let's not see each other again.
I've missed you.
Is this the presenter
I have to shoot the ad with?
That's right, Doctor.
Her name is Sanitada or Earn.
She's the most popular rising star.
Then count me out of this project.
Suzie, this photoshoot collection
came out great.
Of course,
you are a beautiful model after all.
You would look gorgeous on any camera.
Are you complimenting me
because you want something?
Not at all. Listen.
I'm just proud of your fame.
Do you know that a hospital contacted us
to have you as their presenter recently?
It's a famous private hospital,
one of the top in the country.
And you'll get to work
with the hospital owner
who is beautiful, wealthy, and talented.
Everyone wants to work with her.
And her name is… Drumroll, please.
Dr. Fahlada.
I won't accept this job.
You have to. I've already made a deal.
It's a seven-figure deal!
If you can agree to it, you can cancel it.
I won't accept any work
related to this hospital.
Why? Give me a reason.
I can't tell you.
Please contact them
and reject their offer for me.
Seriously?
Hello, everybody.
Today, we are honored to have Dr. Wisanu,
a young doctor
and medical equipment business owner,
and the future partner of Dr. Fahlada,
the heir to a famous hospital.
Did I introduce you correctly, Dr. Wisanu?
Actually, that's only half correct.
I'm the owner
of a medical equipment business,
but I'm not anyone's partner yet.
What about the rumors we've been hearing?
I've been pursuing Dr. Fahlada for years,
but she won't give me a chance.
If anyone has tips on how to woo a lady,
please let me know.
You may not be aware,
but she began dating Dr. Wisanu
before moving abroad.
- Suzie.
- Hello.
I've changed my mind. I'll take the job.
Mark your words.
No backing out!
Let's schedule it right away.
What's going on?
First, you didn't want to take the job
and now Dr. Fahlada
is the one refusing to shoot.
Hey, let me ask you something.
Be honest with me.
Is there something
between you and Dr. Fahlada?
Why is she refusing
to shoot the ad with you?
No.
I don't have any problems with her.
- Are you lying?
- No.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Then who's the problem here?
The director?
The staff?
I actually don't know.
Are you lying to me?
Earn, Suzie,
come with me.
Someone wants to talk to you.
No, I'm not in the mood
to talk to anyone today.
The hospital executive
wants to speak with you.
Of course, let's go.
You should have started with that.
May I ask what this is about?
Follow me.
Put this away for me.
You have to be
considerate of others, Lada.
The crew has been here
since early this morning for the shoot
and now you're canceling
without any reason. It's not right.
I agree with Bow.
Your action is uncalled for, Lada.
Who said I don't have a reason?
Then what is it?
Are you afraid of becoming famous?
That's possible
since Lada is an introvert.
If Lada is an introvert,
then I must be innocent, right?
You've been through too much
to be called innocent, Tan.
Hey, Bow.
Take that back.
This is why you don't have a boyfriend.
- Tan! You're a foul-mouthed doctor.
- What?
Wait.
Weren't we scolding Lada?
Why are we fighting each other?
Yes, we were.
Talk.
So what's your reason
for canceling the ad shoot?
Because I don't want to shoot…
with that presenter.
Why?
You don't usually hate anyone.
What did she do to you?
Don't tell me…
Yes, Dad.
I'm talking to the crew
about today's shoot.
Why did you cancel suddenly?
I don't think I'm suitable for this job.
You're the hospital owner.
Who else is more suitable?
Exactly.
You are perfect for the job.
You're beautiful and classy.
No one else is better for the job.
I stand by my words
that I will not shoot this ad.
Find someone else to replace me.
Give me a reason.
Because I don't want to shoot with…
this presenter.
May I join you?
I didn't know
you had become so irresponsible, Doctor.
What are you talking about?
You canceled the shoot
because you didn't want to be close to me.
You're afraid you'll fall for me again,
aren't you?
That's ridiculous.
If it's ridiculous,
then why did you do it?
Prove to me
that you don't have feelings for me.
I'm sorry to say this,
but I don't need to prove anything
to someone like you.
When you're ready,
let's work together again, Doctor.
TEAM OF PROFESSIONALS
READY TO SERVE YOU 24…
Mom!
Earn.
Why did you come without telling me?
How's it going?
I've prepared your favorite food.
Look, there's shrimp.
I'm not hungry.
I just want to hug you.
Hey.
What's the matter?
Tell me.
Is everything all right?
Is something bothering you?
I saw Fahlada today.
She looked at me with disgust.
She even withdrew from the shoot
because she didn't want to work with me.
I see. I understand how she would feel
since you dumped her.
But I still don't understand
why did you leave someone
you loved so much.
It was my fault
for being too easily swayed.
I deserve her hatred.
Do you remember when I was very sick?
Do you know
what my biggest fear was?
I was scared that I wouldn't be able
to spend time with you and your dad.
Nothing in life is certain.
Love is not easy but it's not hard either.
If you have learned how to love someone,
then you must love them well
and learn how to maintain
your relationship.
But in the end, if it's not meant to be,
you have to let it go.
you have to let go.
No.
I refuse to let go.
My list is complete.
It was hectic in the ER yesterday.
Hello.
I'm here to see Dr. Fahlada.
It's you, Earn.
- Hello.
- Do you have an appointment?
- Yes.
In that case, I'll let her know.
Please wait a moment.
Actually, I want to surprise her.
Can you just tell me where her office is?
Also, would you please
hand this food to her?
Well…
I…
Doctor, you are needed
in the OPD ward in ten minutes.
You're stepping up your game.
You are surprising me
with my favorite food,
stir-fried glass noodles.
That's not from me.
Who is it from then?
It's from me.
Don't forget to eat it.
Doctors get sick too.
Ros.
Please leave us.
Okay.
Oh, no.
I guess you grew tired
of stir-fried glass noodles.
I'll cook you something else next time.
No, thanks.
Will you leave quietly
or should I have security escort you out?
Fine, I'll leave.
But I will come back.
I will keep coming back
until you give me a chance.
I won't make the same mistake again.
I will be the one
who heals the scar in your heart.
See you soon.
Oh, my god.
I…
This way, please.
Thank you.
What did you say?
Earn Sanitada came to see Dr. Fahlada?
Yes, and importantly,
she didn't come empty-handed.
She surprised Dr. Fahlada
with her favorite food.
What did Dr. Fahlada say?
I don't know. She kicked me out.
Listen, I can sense a disaster
coming our way.
Me too.
Lada had a hard time getting over her.
Why is that brat back
to rub salt in her wound?
Guys.
What do you mean by her wound?
Don't you have to be
in the OPD ward right now, Rossarin?
That's right. I totally forgot.
I lost track of time gossiping.
- I have to go. See you later.
- See you.
- Hey.
- What?
I'm starting to worry about Lada.
Me too.
What should we do?
Hey, listen.
How about we find Lada a new girlfriend?
They say the best lover is a new one.
Yes, a new lover could help Lada
move on from that brat.
Let's do it.
Does it hurt?
No.
It's very soft.
It doesn't hurt but I sense irritation.
I could be allergic.
I suspect the same.
I'll prescribe you a new medication.
It's almost lunchtime. Are you free?
Do you need anything from me?
You've been taking care
of my skin for years.
Let me buy you a meal as a thank you.
You are my patient.
It's my job to take care of you.
Is that a yes then?
Normally, I only eat a sandwich for lunch.
Actually, she doesn't even have time
for a sandwich today.
She has a long line of patients
waiting for her.
Maybe next time then.
But…
Doctor, is the session over?
Let me interrupt you then.
Ratee, many fans are waiting
for your autograph outside.
Follow me.
Next time then.
- Hello.
- Earn, sit here.
Thank you.
- Hello, Sis.
Hello, Earn.
Oh, my gosh. Hello, Engfah.
No need for formalities.
I'm honored to be working with you.
I'm glad our schedules finally aligned.
The honor is mine.
We are not surprised
why you are so famous.
- Everyone loves how nice you are.
- I agree.
Thanks.
Hey.
Sorry.
Ratee, where are you?
Everyone's waiting for you.
I'm here. Stop rushing me.
Sorry, I'm late.
I'm having my period cramps.
I'm still in pain.
Oh, no, you poor girl.
Why didn't you call me?
Can you work in this condition?
I'll manage. I won't put others
in trouble because of me.
That's the spirit.
- Assistant.
- Yes.
Where should Ratee get her makeup done?
You can take my spot.
Are you sure, Engfah?
He's your personal makeup artist.
Don't worry about it.
I got my makeup done a while ago
because I came on time.
I don't know why I'm laughing.
Yes, Earn is a great actress.
Cut.
Okay, let's see the footage.
Let us check the footage.
Earn.
Are you okay?
Thank you, Engfah.
It's okay.
Gosh.
What's the matter?
Are you thinking of that brat?
How do you know?
Come on. Of course I know.
Look at you.
You've been frustrated
ever since you ran into her.
Ros told me that you even made
a mistake writing a doctor's note.
Yes, she has been frustrated all morning.
She glared at me many times.
I don't want to be like this.
Do you want it to stop?
Bow, do you know how to help me?
Yes.
But I'll need your cooperation.
WISANU
Look.
Speak of the devil.
I was about to mention his name.
Pick it up.
Come on, Lada.
Answer the phone.
Hurry up.
Do it now.
I can talk to him if you don't want to.
- Go away.
If you won't pick it up,
I'll do it.
WISANU
- Come on.
- Hurry.
Hello, Nu.
My company is hosting the seminar
with the Dermatological Association.
I would love to see you there.
Let me check my schedule first.
I'll be there if I'm free.
Your mom told me you've been buried
with work since you got back.
I believe her now.
I love working.
I want to see my patients recover.
I'm jealous of your patients.
Their doctor is kind
and caring.
Thanks.
Are you off work yet?
Do you need a ride?
I've been meaning to visit your mom.
I…
I'm sorry, Nu.
I'm meeting a friend today.
Feel free to visit my mom
without me though.
- They're beautiful.
- Earn's doing great.
- So is Ratee.
- That's right.
Earn really stands out.
Ratee is very outstanding.
Bang, bang.
Okay, let's call it a day.
Yes.
- Good job.
- Ratee.
- See you.
- Bye.
See you later.
Ratee, are you tired?
You did a great job.
The director was complimenting you.
- Really?
- Yes.
Listen, Madame Ple is hosting a party
tonight. Do you want to go with me?
- Yes...
- We can't go, Engfah.
You're not going again?
I have something to do.
What is it this time?
You are always busy with something.
Do you have something against me?
No, I don't.
That means you like me then.
I'm kidding.
I understand you are busy.
We'll meet some other time.
We'll be seeing
a lot of each other anyway.
Sure, I should get going then.
- I'm leaving, Suzie. See you tomorrow.
- What?
What?
You're leaving me here?
I'm meeting someone.
I'm going to get changed.
Pu.
What's with her?
Gosh.
Doctor.
I'm looking for a friend
to watch the new movie with tonight.
Will you come with me?
Don't talk to me like I'm your friend
because I'm not.
Will you go with me as my girlfriend then?
I was joking.
There's no need to get upset.
Can't you talk to me nicely?
No.
How about we go for a ride instead?
- No.
- Let's go listen to some music then.
- How about shopping?
Leave me alone. It's annoying.
I miss you.
I know you hate me.
That's right. I hate you so much.
Doctor.
Wait for me.
Doctor, wait for me.
Doctor!
Earn, watch out!
Why are you following me?
Go home.
I still love you.
Love?
How dare you use that word?
It's true.
I love you.
And I will do everything to get you back.
That's not happening,
Ms. Sanitada.
HEART, FAHLADA & EARN
Whenever you feel overwhelmed by stress,
look at this music box.
It will remind you
that I'll always be here for you.
I want to break up with you.
You are nothing
but a toy I've played with.
Just let me go.
I don't like women. I like men.
I like men.
Do you understand?
I will make it happen.
I told you that
I would do everything to get you back.
SORRY, FORGIVE ME
Who let this lunatic inside?
Go away. Don't come any closer.
How did it go?
It went well.
I'll get these balloons cleaned up.
- Earn, can I take a photo with you?
- Yes.
- Of course.
- I'm a huge fan.
- Thank you. Sure.
- Can you hold it?
- All done. Thank you.
- Thank you.
She's prettier in real life.
May I join you?
I haven't answered you yet.
But I want to see your face.
Just a few seconds is enough.
Wait.
Will you shoot the ad with me?
You don't have to answer me now.
Are you free this evening?
- When I'm done...
- I'm warning you for the last time.
Leave me alone.
Don't be so cold-hearted.
Or it will give you a heart condition.
FBI My Love, episode 1,
scene 15, cut 1, take 1.
The situation doesn't look good.
We can't trust those people.
I'll ask Lieutenant Chan for backup.
Lieutenant Chan?
He won't be of help to us.
We should raid their nest.
Let's go.
Cut.
Ratee stood in the wrong spot again.
Did no one brief her?
I told her many times.
Should we retake it?
There's no time.
Next scene.
Wait. That was Take 10.
Why did you write Take 1?
Well…
She…
It's a lucky number.
With number one,
it looks like we got it on the first try.
What a day.
Move the camera
to film her face next time.
Listen, Ratee.
You stood in the wrong spot.
You completely covered Earn.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry. It was an accident.
My inner actress made me do it.
That's right, Sis.
She was just following her instinct.
I'm not your sister.
- I'm tired.
- Is that so?
Let's take a break.
Go around in circles.
Get some rest.
Do you want to reshoot?
I'll tell Ake for you.
It's fine.
I feel sorry for him.
We're running out of time.
Of course we are.
We reshot it ten times thanks to Ratee.
Engfah invited us to hit the gym with her.
We should go.
I've been feeling a little bloated.
Some exercise would be good for me.
Suzie, you just want to film yourself
working out so you can post it on social.
Oh, my. You know me so well.
Where's Engfah?
She's over there.
I'm glad you can come.
Why don't we leave our car here?
We can come back for it later.
We can reduce pollution by carpooling.
Earn can come with me.
You can drive and meet us there.
Sure, if that's what you want.
But don't forget
I have to post
a workout video with Engfah.
You got it.
Shall we go, Earn?
- Sure.
- Let's go.
Something smells fishy.
Since Lada has offered
to pay for our meal today,
I'm taking us to an Omakase restaurant.
Awesome.
You chose wisely, Dr. Bow.
You guys are unbelievable.
Let's order a full-course meal.
- I'm hungry.
- Let's go all out.
Sure.
Do your shoes hurt, Suzie?
You got jealous, didn't you?
What are you talking about?
You like women, don't you?
Hello, Nu.
I was just thinking of you.
Have you considered
that she might harm herself? What then?
A woman has been hit by a car
in front of the hospital.
You naughty girl,
you always make me worried.
Subtitle translation by:
Pet-chompoo Sa-ngarmangkang