LECTURE HALL
Young-joo, I have something to tell you.
I've had a crush on you for a while now
and given it a lot of thought.
And...
What was my next line?
Anyway.
Will you go out with me, Kang Young-joo?
Who does he think he is?
Don't do it. Turn him down.
Tell him no.
-Don't do it.
-Reject him.
-Turn him down.
-Say no.
-Don't do it, Young-joo.
-Please say no.
What's going on? What's with this vibe?
What's he doing down there?
He's asking Young-joo out.
-Young-joo?
-Here we go again.
-He can't ask Young-joo out.
-Why not?
-Why do you even care?
-None of your business.
I'm sorry.
I'm not looking for a relationship
at the moment.
Move!
Why is everyone so obsessed with her?
What a bunch of fools.
You'll work in pairs
for the next presentation,
which will be in three weeks.
Use the rest of this lecture to pair up
with someone you'd like to work with.
Make sure you're well-prepared.
-Yes, sir.
-That's all for today.
-Thank you, sir.
So, when do you want to do this?
I should lock you up
and beat some sense into you.
Tell me when you're free.
-I'm free that entire week.
-Anytime next week?
Yes. Wait, I can't do Wednesday.
-Hey, Jae-yoon.
-What?
Do you want to pair up with me?
With you?
Well...
I already agreed to be his partner.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
-I'll be your partner. I can ditch him.
-What?
Are you fucking kidding me?
-It's fine. I'll just cut ties with him.
-Hey.
What do you say?
Okay. Thanks, Hyeon-su.
I'll text you later.
Okay.
I'll text you back.
You're going to pull this crap?
Seriously?
You're tossing out ten years of friendship
over some girl?
You scumbag.
She's not just some girl.
She's the Goddess of Engineering.
"She's the Goddess of Engineering."
That's why I'm treating you to a meal.
Moron.
But why did she ask you?
HANKUK UNIVERSITY
MECHANICAL ENGINEERING
What's that supposed to mean?
Don't you find it a little strange?
Why did she try to pair up with you?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm handsome,
and I've got the charm to back it up.
That's bullshit.
I just don't get it.
Hey.
What the...
Unbelievable.
-So why didn't you say yes?
-Why would I?
Why would you turn her down?
She's the most popular girl
in our department.
I don't think she's pretty.
-You don't think she's pretty?
-No, not at all.
-She's not charming, either.
-Get your eyes checked.
-All-boys schools messed you up.
-Watch it!
-You poor virgin.
-You punk!
What, punk?
I've been with a girl.
No, you haven't.
-I've dated before.
-When?
In elementary school.
That doesn't count, man.
You scared me.
What are you doing here?
Am I not allowed to be here?
This place is open
to all mechanical engineering students.
Don't talk about people
behind their backs.
Speak for yourself.
Young-joo, I'll text you!
Do you think she heard us?
You crossed the line this time.
-I did?
-Yes.
What did I do?
-Good to have you on board.
-Thank you.
-Make sure you work hard.
-I will.
She'll show you the ropes.
Hey, Jae-yoon.
What? You two know each other?
That's great news.
Get him up to speed, okay?
Don't worry, boss.
I'll give him some hardcore training.
You've got this.
I've got this, boss.
Welcome, Jae-yoon.
First time working in an ice cream shop?
I may be ugly and lack charm,
but I'll go above and beyond to train you.
She heard everything.
Every last bit.
-Did you see what I sent you?
-I can't believe it.
Is this for real?
-Isn't it ridiculous?
-It really is.
I couldn't believe what I was hearing.
My looks have never let me down
for the past 22 years.
But he thinks I'm ugly.
I'm not charming? Me?
How dare he?
He's the one that looks like
a cross between a flounder and a toad.
-Come on. You're being too harsh.
-It's just ridiculous.
Harsh? I'm just getting started.
My revenge will start
when he shows up to work tomorrow...
Hello? Young-joo?
Are you there?
You scared me.
What?
I didn't do anything.
I was just standing here.
Hey, what are you doing here?
"Am I not allowed to be here?"
Can't I stand here?
This bus stop is open
to all Korean residents.
Hello.
Damn it.
He heard everything.
Every last bit.
I told you I didn't take a single bite.
This is what it looked like
when I opened it!
Just look at it.
Take a close look.
My ice cream turned into sludge
because of your crappy packaging!
Sir, I just checked your receipt,
and it says you purchased this
seven hours ago.
We tell all our customers
to consume their ice cream
-within three hours--
-Hey, miss
Are you trying to lecture me right now?
I'd appreciate it
if you could keep things respectful.
-This is the policy--
-Just refund me.
I want a refund right now!
As I've told you before,
the policy forbids refunds in this case.
Damn it!
What are you doing?
Disrupting the business,
property damage, harassment,
-assault, defamation, and more.
-Hold on.
These are the charges
being brought against you,
and I have video evidence
documenting all of these violations.
Our corporate legal team
will take legal action against you.
But why are you filming...
Feel free to make your closing statement.
Learn how to run a business.
What an asshole.
-Thanks, Jae-yoon.
-Sure.
Are you a double major
in law or something?
I picked it up from a TV show
I watched last night.
I didn't think it'd work, though.
What show was it? I want to watch it.
Don't bother. It's not that good.
Okay.
You know...
That thing that happened...
I'm sorry about what I said
at the bus stop.
The flounder part?
Or the toad part?
Come on now. Who cares about all that?
It's totally fine.
I also talked smack about you, too.
That's right. You did.
So you started it.
I just said you weren't that pretty,
but you compared me to animals.
-It was oddly specific.
-What I meant was--
-You called me a flounder and a toad.
-I'm sorry.
I am.
But it is also true
that humans evolved from aquatic life.
What?
I'll wash the rags.
I must be going crazy.
My favorite professor is Hugh Herr at MIT.
He lost both of his legs in an accident,
but despite that, he became a leader
in the bionic limb industry.
Since he was little...
Damn it, I'm seriously about to lose it.
This flavor over here is a crowd-pleaser.
And the Korean rice flavor...
-What about the rice flavor?
-Oh, right.
It's good.
There we go. That's more like it.
I'm finally coming to my senses.
-I'm off.
-Bye.
Hello.
Bye.
Damn it.
LEE JAE-YOON
#ENGINEERINGSTUDENT #ENGINEERINGGRAM #HKU
This can't be happening!
You've got to be kidding me.
Why is this happening to me?
-Young-joo, time for dinner.
-I'm not hungry!
This is for you.
And this is for you, boss.
You shouldn't have.
-Thank you.
-Thanks, I'll pull them to good use.
Hey, what about Jae-yoon?
Oh no. I only got two pairs.
Hold on.
I almost forgot I had this.
Hey, Jae-yoon.
You can have this.
I get hot easily.
So I don't wear scarves in the winter.
They're too stuffy.
You should give it to someone else.
Should I wipe the glass outside, boss?
It's so hot in here.
Well, we all have our preferences.
Jeez!
You scared me.
Hey, how can you be so clueless?
What?
Don't you know what this means?
What does it mean?
It's my way of asking you out.
I knitted it myself.
Really?
The thing is...
I'm sorry.
I just have no interest in dating you.
What?
I'm sorry.
Oh, okay. I see.
Hey, that's okay.
I get it.
We should go.
What can I get you?
What's good here?
I recommend the Almond Caramel.
We just launched this flavor,
and it's been a big hit.
My Dad is a Caramelon
is also a recent addition.
A lot of people have been asking for it
because of its unique flavor.
Do you have anything sweeter?
-Are you looking for something richer?
-Yes.
Then, I personally recommend
the Chocolate Fudge.
Have a taste.
It's the sweetest flavor we have.
So, are you two an item now?
What are you talking about?
We're not dating.
Really?
That means I still have a chance.
Hey.
I'm just really curious.
Do you think
you're in a position to reject--
What are you trying to imply?
It's just an innocent question.
I mean, you do have a point.
How could I go after someone that pretty?
She's way out of my league.
Don't you think so?
What's the matter?
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
All I did was ask her
for the Almond Caramel.
No, he didn't do anything wrong.
I'm not feeling well.
I think I need to leave early today.
Sure, go on home.
Don't worry. We'll take it from here.
Young-joo.
Damn it, I can't believe I did that.
That was so embarrassing.
Young-joo, the thing is...
-Earlier...
-Damn it!
Where are you going?
Hey, wait up!
Hey!
Are you okay?
-This is so annoying.
-Young-joo.
They always get untied!
What did you say?
These stupid laces always get untied.
Your laces?
Hey.
You should've just asked me.
I know a trick.
If you tie it like this,
they'll never come undone.
Really?
Of course, just watch.
You do this.
And then, you...
Do you really find me that unattractive?
No.
You're really pretty.
Jae-yoon, you jerk.
You said they'd never come undone.
Take all the time in the world, will you?
Can you hurry up and tie them already?
Lee Jae-yoon, Ra In-ho.
-Private Lee Jae-yoon.
-Private Ra In-ho.
What now?
Is it over now?
No!
It can't be.
-Fuck.
-Step back, sir.
Pull yourself together, sir.
Shit.
Fuck.
Why the fuck is this happening?
He got up.
Private Lee.
In-ho.
Corporal Jeon!
Sergeant Kim!
Corporal Jeon.
Please forgive me.
Keep moving.
I feel like shit.
Are you all right?
Hold on.
Look.
Please help me.
No, wait! I'm not one of them.
-Damn you.
-Wait, stop.
He's still talking,
so maybe he's just hurt.
-Let's not kill him just yet.
-Damn it!
-What the...
-Just leave if you're going to kill me.
Did you get bitten by a zombie?
Yes, it fucking bit me.
That's why I'm dealing
with this shitty situation.
You're going to clobber me over the head
when I just got bitten?
You're all jerks.
Get lost. You're all the same.
Get lost!
Given how violent he's acting,
he must be far along
in the zombification process.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
You're really going to leave me?
Please help me.
I really don't want to die.
MONTHLY PROJECT
YOON JONG-SHIN
-Please, I beg you.
-That's Yoon Jong-shin's Monthly Project.
-Please help me.
-What?
-Can we take him with us?
-No way.
Please help me. I beg you.
-Does it hurt a lot?
-What's wrong with you?
Get lost if you don't want to be here.
"Get lost"?
Why are you so rude all of a sudden?
You're the one who told me
to drop the formalities earlier.
If you don't want to deal with this,
just leave.
-Turn your phone off.
-Turn it off.
Hey, stop it. Don't touch me.
-Where is it?
-Back pocket.
HAPPY ACADEMY MANAGER
It's Yoon Jong-shin.
Sorry, I'm a bit drunk.
Fuck, I told you we should've just gone!
-Let's run that way.
-They're coming!
Take me with you!
-Run!
-This way!
Wait for me!
Wait!
Soo-jeong?
Hyung-bae.
Civilians aren't allowed
to handle firearms.
You crossed a line there.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Sir.
If she hadn't stepped in,
In-ho would be dead.
Get it together, Kwak!
Stay focused!
-Kwak Gye-young.
-Yes, sir.
Escort the civilian to the barracks.
The rest of you...
Clear the bodies of the fallen soldiers.
Do you hear?
-Yes, sir.
Let's get you inside.
Sir.
Watch your step.
First Lieutenant Park Sung-wook!
-Pardon?
-I'll brief the brigade about this.
You need to pull yourself together, sir.
Yes, thank you.
I'm going to take a short break.
Look, they're really going in there.
Get back inside.
NECK TO NECK GRILLED INTESTINES
Hey.
Sorry, but this is the only way
you can be with us.
Hang in there, okay?
"Hang in there"?
What's the problem?
It's not like he's going to get better.
Look at his eyes.
They're growing redder by the second.
Then, what? Do you want to kill him?
He's on the verge of becoming a zombie!
You'd better stop looking at us
with those puppy eyes.
That's why we gagged and tied him up.
Stop acting like you're a saint,
for fuck's sake.
Jin-wook!
Words like "saint" are uncalled for.
But "fuck" is okay?
Look at the shitty situation we're in.
How could I not--
You should stop, too.
You'd better not turn, you fucker.
-I'll smash your head in, asshole.
-Stop it.
Just try me.
Maybe we should take out the gag.
-I made it clear that I'm against this.
-Okay.
How much did you drink?
The first round was
at a Chinese restaurant.
I had a bottle of baijiu there.
Then, I went to the Han River Park
and had two bottles of soju.
After that, I went to sober up...
SINSA-DONG HANGOVER SOUP 267
...and had some makgeolli.
And then...
I'm missing something.
What else did I eat?
Just take a look at that spew.
You clearly had some fried rice.
I'm thirsty. Can I get some water?
If it's your third time taking the CSAT,
you should be studying, not drinking.
Planning a fourth attempt, Tripeater?
"A fourth attempt"?
How could you say such a thing?
If I can't get into college this time,
I'll have to enlist.
I just wanted one last drink
before I started studying.
Get him some water.
-Water.
-Me?
Hurry up.
This is complete bullshit.
-How about another drink instead?
-What if...
Hypothetically speaking...
What are you doing?
-I knew it!
-What was that for?
What's wrong with him?
Ta-da. Look at this.
What about it?
Young-joo, you saw it, too.
-The zombies went around him.
-Well...
Yes, I think they did.
It wasn't just some of them.
They all paid him no attention
and were focused on biting us.
Get to the point already.
Two possible explanations.
One, the zombies don't attack the drunk.
Two, if you're drunk,
a bite won't turn you into a zombie.
Being wasted might be our biggest defense.
-"Wasted"?
-That's ridiculous.
-That's crazy.
Then, how do you explain him?
It's just a theory for now.
But how about a drink?
-What?
-How much do we have to drink?
Jeez, we'll be drunk as skunks.
Why are you looking at me?
You're making me feel like shit.
I'm a total lightweight, too.
But it'll be better to move
when the sun's up,
so let's just drink until then.
Okay?
-Let's drink.
-Fine, let's drink.
Can I have a drink, too?
I'd also like a drink.
Damn, they're ignoring me.
That's so shitty.
Our apologies.
We're unable to connect your call
due to an influx of calls on the network.
SWEET JAE-YOON
Jae-yoon, I'm hiding in a barbecue place
that's super close to A Tower.
Call me when you see this.
Ta-da. Enjoy.
Sir, can I get one, too?
Sir?
-You should eat something.
-Thanks for coming.
Eat up.
-Are you crying?
-You scared me.
-I'm not crying.
-Come on, give me a smile.
Stop it.
-You're not tired?
-No, I'm fine.
-Thank you.
-No, it's nothing.
My dad wanted you to have this.
He shouldn't have.
Thank you, sir.
But you know I don't smoke, right?
-Right?
-Hey.
My dad wasn't a smoker, either.
That's true.
I only saw him carry this around,
but I never saw him use it.
When I was little,
I got him this as a birthday gift
with my allowance.
He carried it around every day
and claimed it was his greatest treasure.
He used to pretend like he was smoking
to make me laugh.
Stop it.
-Oh, that's good.
-Stop it.
Young-joo.
1ST AIR DEFENSE BRIGADE 1ST PLATOON
LEE JAE-YOON
CALL FAILED
MY DARLING YOUNG-JOO
Damn it.
Shit. Fuck.
Due to the unexplained riots
spreading nationwide,
citizens are gripped by fear and unrest.
According to our analysis,
the assailants target living individuals
without any apparent motive.
They do not utilize any weapons
and only seek to bite their victims.
In the interest of national security,
all forms of public transportation
will be suspended.
We urge all citizens
to refrain from going outside
and to remain in your homes
with your loved ones.
We'll be back right after the break.
Light as a feather? Completely weightless.
Revolutionize your workout with Moty.
Private Ra In-ho!
Permission to speak, sir?
Read the room, you punk.
What is it? Just say it.
Private Choi didn't turn into a zombie
as soon as he died yesterday.
There must be a reason
it took some time for him to turn.
Such as?
There must've been
something unique in his diet.
Well...
Based on my deductions,
I believe it was all due
to this health supplement he took.
Red ginseng extract.
That's complete nonsense.
It's almost as if you're begging
to be beaten up.
Hey, your tone...
What about it?
You sound like a soldier.
I thought I'd give it a shot.
What?
I have a question for you.
Okay, what is it?
How did you manage to land
such a perfect shot yesterday?
He's right.
I was surprised, too.
Did you learn how to shoot?
This is supposed to be a secret.
I was a competitive shooter in high school
and was on the national reserve team.
What? Seriously?
No wonder! That explains it!
-What was that?
-What's going on?
-Where did that come from?
-What was it?
-What was that sound?
-What's going on?
-Damn it.
Where was it?
Where did that gunshot come from?
It came from the control room.
-Where's the CO?
-He's in the control room.
-Damn it.
-Shit.
Damn it.
-What's going on?
-Wait here.
CONTROL ROOM
Sir, be careful.
Shit, what's going on now?
1ST PLATOON DUTY ROSTER
LIVE AS A SHIELD! DIE IN LOYALTY!
FIRST LIEUTENANT PARK SUNG-WOOK
RETURN TO BRIGADE
If you get 0.209 percent...
-I did it.
-You got 0.209 percent?
-You did? Are you sure?
-I did!
Congratulations! You did it!
You did it!
-I did it.
-You did it!
Well done. I feel great.
I feel so good.
-I'm totally wasted.
-Totally wasted...
Look at that jerk.
You always act all macho and stuff,
but you hold your liquor pretty well.
Can't you just untie me?
I'm pretty sure I have
the highest blood alcohol level here.
-Can we untie him?
-Of course not.
We can't. Sorry, kiddo.
Wait, but when are we actually leaving?
The sun is up already.
But won't it be difficult for us
to deal with the zombies
if we're this drunk?
Hey, nothing is easy in life.
Young-joo, don't worry.
We're going to A Tower.
Do we have to go to that stupid A Tower?
-Who cares about her boyfriend?
-Watch it.
Do you want to go back to studying?
Hold on, Young-joo!
Listen up.
I'll tell you why we should go to A Tower.
One, we'll be safe
since there are soldiers there.
-Jae-yoon's there.
-That's right!
Private Lee will protect us.
And my car is there.
It came all the way from the States.
-The States? That's amazing.
-It has a variety of survival kits.
Please untie me.
Wait, where are you going?
That's amazing. Please untie me.
I have a shovel.
-Young-joo.
-Let's go.
-That's cool.
-Young-joo!
-I'm off!
-Stop right there!
Untie me first!
-Where are you going?
-Untie me.
-Here I go!
-Young-joo!
-And I have a hammer.
-Where are you going? Untie me.
Sorry, I can't untie you.
My car is built for off-road.
It's from the States!
And it's safe!
Where did everyone go?
It's all coming to an end.
What?
There's no reason for us
to guard this place.
Pardon me?
I'm saying I've lost my sense of duty.
Private Lee.
Are you thinking of deserting your post
to go look for your girlfriend?
She could've gotten hurt
on her way here to see me.
It makes no fucking sense
for me to be here.
That's why I'm going to leave
and look for Young-joo.
Then, I shall come with you.
I also need to protect Ha-yul and my wife.
Okay. All right.
It's only right for each of us
to go and protect our loved ones.
Let's go.
We should inform the first sergeant.
What?
Tell him we're deserting?
Zombies, move aside!
I need to go to Jae-yoon.
Stop! Have you lost your mind?
He said zombies don't attack you
when you're drunk.
We need to get out of here. Let's go!
This way.
Wait!
-Hey, zombies!
-Stop it. Please.
-Be quiet.
-Come here! Bring it on!
This way.
-I can beat them.
-No, you can't.
Not a chance.
We're fucking screwed.
They're going to have a feast out of us.
You think this is funny?
Look at you. Did the zombies scare you?
Hey, the zombies might not bite you.
Go and do something.
Then, at least untie me.
There's no time for that.
-Come on.
-Just untie him.
-You go out there then.
-Come on.
-I can't do anything in this state.
-That hurts!
-Okay, fine. I'll untie you.
-Free him.
-There you go.
-He's free.
Now, go.
-Bye. Good luck.
-I'm counting on you.
Seriously, this is...
What's this thing?
Stand up.
-Where are we going now?
-Let's go.
-Wait for me!
-This way.
-Hurry.
-Tripeater!
Hurry up.
CHOI CHUL-WOO,
PARK SUNG-WOOK, JEON HYUNG-BAE
SAFE
SEMI
Salute.
Private Lee Jae-yoon reporting for...
What is it?
Are you in the middle of something, sir?
Well, I was...
I was working
on First Lieutenant Park's case.
I was checking the trajectory.
The direction of...
-I was trying to act...
-A scene reenactment?
-Yes, that's right.
-I see.
I was reenacting it.
The reenactment of the death
of First Lieutenant Park.
What do you need?
Sir, we're about to run out of food,
and we don't know
when we'll be replenished.
But we actually have
a bigger issue on our hands.
-What is it?
-Private Ra, go ahead.
Yes, sir. Allow me to explain, sir.
Do you remember the blackout
we experienced yesterday?
The sudden blackout was caused
by the lack of an ATS.
Yes, I remember yesterday.
When that happened,
it's likely that the hotel's power
switched from the external grid
to an internal generator.
We only have running water
because the water tank is functioning.
At this moment, both the tank and pump
are being powered by the generator.
Therefore,
once the generator runs out of power,
our water supply will be cut off as well.
And when do you think that will happen?
I suspect we only have
a few days before that happens.
COMMUNICATION SECURITY
Line is secure.
Admin Supply Officer speaking.
-This is the battalion commander.
-Salute.
A supply chopper will be landing at 12:00.
Prepare for its entry
and stand by within the base.
Yes, sir.
At 12:00, a supply chopper will arrive.
-What?
This may be your first time
handling a chopper entry,
but if you stick to the protocol,
you'll be good to go.
Safety is our top priority.
Stay sharp, and don't let your guard down.
Is that clear?
-Yes, sir!
Bulletproof vests
will remain on at all times.
Gye-young, check the inventory
and issue one to Soo-jeong as well.
-Yes, sir!
-Thank you, sir!
Damn it.
This is Opera. Fish, do you copy?
Come on, hurry up.
It's coming.
This is Opera. Fish, do you copy?
Can't we just go home in that?
-Can we?
-Should we ask?
-This is Opera. Fish, do you copy?
-Yes, let's ask.