SINGLE'S INFERNO
I think
I like you the most.
-Me?
-Yes.
This is crazy.
During my time here…
How do I describe it?
You've had the biggest impact on me
and made me feel
a lot of different emotions.
And I think I got mad at you before,
-because I was jealous.
-I see.
I think that was why.
Partially, anyway.
The fact that you were even curious
about other women made me jealous.
-So--
-You mean when I told you
I was also curious about Gyu-ri?
Yes, and I thought I'd expressed
my feelings enough,
but you still wanted
to get to know other women.
So I think I got mad at you
out of jealousy.
She's amazing.
-She is.
-Really.
This makes her so charming.
Yes, I get it.
If you weren't attracted to me at all,
you wouldn't even care enough
to be upset or disappointed.
Right.
-But as for me,
-Okay.
I've been a little upset with you
ever since we returned from Paradise.
-With me?
-And…
I had a great time with you in Paradise,
including the breakfast we had together.
But since we came back from Paradise,
the way you've treated me and talked to me
seemed completely different
from how you were there.
I see.
It felt like…
Well, it made me wonder
if you weren't
really yourself in Paradise.
I see.
This can't be the real you, right?
-Right now?
-Yes.
This is the real me.
-That's who she really is.
-Yes.
-Yes, she seems sincere.
-No one is as transparent as she is.
-Exactly.
You're very different here
from when you were with me.
They're both me.
-How exactly am I different?
-Are you saying you're different
-when you're with a group of people?
-When I'm in a group…
How did I seem different
when I was with other people?
Let's say someone else like Ha-bin
or Won-ik is interested in you.
You make it hard for them to approach you.
-I see.
-So it made me wonder
if you're normally the type
to build a wall like that.
-Me?
-Yes, that's how I felt.
That was a weird remark.
I don't get what he's saying.
Yes, he's always like that
whenever he talks to Ha-jeong.
Remember the private conversation
they had in the lodging?
Ha-jeong stated the facts
and was honest with him,
but he kept steering the conversation
in a weird direction.
Is he just dumb?
Is Gwan-hee just dumb?
-Gwan-hee is…
-He's a little…
-He's missing the point.
-It's odd.
So it made me wonder
if you're normally the type
to build a wall like that.
-Me?
-Yes, that's how I felt.
Because I'm not into them.
Because you aren't interested in them?
Yes.
I'm not like that with you, am I?
Well, I guess you do treat me differently.
Exactly.
I was already pretty into you,
so I didn't really want
to talk to anyone else.
Okay. I get what you mean now.
Okay.
I'm sure
it wasn't easy for you
to tell me all this.
Thank you for doing so.
Everyone I talk to here tells me
-that they can't figure out how you feel.
-I see.
So I was also curious.
Honestly speaking,
my mind was made up just today.
What caused you
to make up your mind today?
It felt like I wasn't being honest
to myself about my feelings,
and it was giving me a hard time.
I'm usually not like that,
but ever since I came here…
I just don't want to regret it later.
I'll let you know
once I make my decision.
If I end up deciding on you,
I'll tell you so.
And I'll still tell you even if I don't.
-Yes, okay.
-Okay.
I knew Ha-jeong wouldn't change.
She was so honest and straightforward.
You know what?
In the beginning,
I thought so negatively about Ha-jeong.
I'm so mad at myself now.
-I want to apologize to her too.
-She's so charming.
-I owe her an apology.
-She's amazing.
But seriously,
she completely opened up
to him about her feelings.
I feel like that could've moved him.
In my opinion,
when Ha-jeong opened up
to Gwan-hee about her feelings,
he seemed a bit uncomfortable
as if he didn't have feelings for her.
-I noticed that too.
-He seemed flustered.
I think all he's thinking about
is Min-ji right now.
-I think so too.
-Yes.
I hope he gets to go
to Paradise with Min-ji.
-So he'll know for sure?
-Yes, so he can sort things out.
Who are you set on right now?
-Me?
-Yes.
I doubt it's easy.
Hye-seon is really nice too.
You think so?
She's great,
but I can't really figure her out.
On top of that,
Ha-jeong just told me that she likes me.
Ha-jeong?
That's bothering me too.
Of course.
So I'm a bit torn.
Did you have a good chat?
-Our chat?
-Yes.
I told him that I liked him.
-To Gwan-hee?
-Yes.
I feel so much more at ease
now that I've told him.
So I think I'll be able to enjoy
the remaining four days.
Jin-seok was apparently confused
because my actions didn't match my words.
-Yes, but that's--
-He said he was disappointed.
Well, it's understandable
if you think about it in his shoes.
Yes, but it still frustrates me.
He told me to get to know the others.
He's giving you a chance too.
But why now? This late?
-Is that how you feel?
-Yes.
It may not be too late for you
to work things out. Be good to him.
I doubt that's what he wants.
I think he wants a shot with someone else.
No, you're being so frustrating.
You're driving me nuts.
But didn't I make it clear
about my feelings today?
Don't just end it there.
Rather than just talking about it,
show it through your actions.
Make it easy enough for him to understand.
This is exhausting.
You barely did anything.
-It's tiring. This isn't me.
-It's tiring for all of us.
I even told him that I missed him.
No, that's not enough.
I even once told Min-kyu
that I had missed him a lot.
Good one, Ha-jeong.
That's just…
-Is it not enough?
-No.
-We only have a few days left.
-Right.
If you let things end like this,
you'll definitely regret it.
You'll regret not having done your best
to win over someone you like.
Yes, that's so true.
-She's teaching her a priceless lesson.
-Goodness.
PARADISE
CHOI HYE-SEON & SON WON-IK
-We can see the ocean from here.
-Gosh.
This is so nice.
This is amazing.
The sunset is so pretty right now.
It's so beautiful.
It's so pretty.
-This is perfect timing.
-We came at the perfect moment.
It looks great.
-It smells so good.
-Bon appétit.
Try it.
-How is it? Is it good?
-It's so good.
-Isn't it good?
-It is.
Now, we finally get to ask
each other's age and occupation.
Right.
I'm not saying you look old,
but you don't seem to be too young.
I'm guessing maybe 26?
-What?
-Never mind.
I think… Yes, I'll go with 26.
-Right on.
-Really?
-Yes.
-You're 26?
Yes.
You're really 26?
I guess you thought I was older.
Yes… No, I didn't.
So you're 26.
How old do you think I am?
I thought you'd be my age.
-Really?
-Born in 1998.
I was born in 1993.
-Oh, I see.
-I'm 31.
-Really?
-Yes.
That's surprising.
-Really?
-I'm so surprised.
-Stop lying.
-I'm serious.
-Really?
-Yes.
You're so pure at heart for your age.
-You were born in 1998?
-Yes.
You seem more mature.
-Did you think I'd be around your age?
-No, not quite.
But you seemed very mature
based on your self-discipline,
and the way you think and speak.
So I thought you'd be
in your mid-to-late twenties.
I see.
That makes it harder to guess what you do.
I work in the real estate industry.
I'm a realtor.
Really?
-Do you know what it is?
-Yes.
-Yes, I'm a realtor.
-That's so cool.
I'm still in college.
-You are?
-Yes.
I see.
Really?
You seem to have a good appetite.
I know. Especially today.
But I couldn't eat much
when I first went to Paradise.
I guess I feel more at ease now.
-It's a good thing.
-Yes.
When you won that Paradise-bound ticket…
I thought you'd choose Gwan-hee
to spend more time with him.
Gwan-hee?
That's not how I feel, at least for now.
I see.
-Shall we go?
-Let's go.
-That was a nice dinner.
-It was.
Do you and Gwan-hee click when you talk?
-Well, I thought we did.
-Okay.
But Gwan-hee seems to think
I was very different
when I was in Paradise with him
from how I am now.
He thought I was far from his type
when we went to Paradise together,
but his mind changed
after he met me again in Inferno.
So I have no idea anymore.
That day, he said many things
that showed his interest.
So I'm not sure how he feels.
She just said how she feels.
It wasn't about those two.
Won-ik kept bringing Gwan-hee up.
-There was no romance there.
-No.
PARADISE
KIM GYU-RI & CHOI MIN-WOO
That's a really nice boat.
I know, right?
Oh, the fenders.
One second.
That's quite a big gap.
Let's go.
Look at these. They're so cute.
There's a lot of food here.
-Do you want a glass?
-Sure.
-I'll pour you just a bit.
-Okay.
-My eyes…
-Be careful.
Okay.
Do they look fine?
You're good now.
It must've bothered you.
-There was a strand of hair there.
-Yes, it bothered me.
Something was bothering me.
He always finds something
on his date's face.
Whenever Min-woo is on a date,
he makes it look like a scene
in a romantic movie.
-It's so pretty.
-It is.
The view from Inferno
is actually quite pretty too,
-but this is different.
-Yes, it's different.
It really is.
After spending days in Inferno,
I've been living the dream recently.
Yesterday must've been fun.
You seemed brighter than usual.
I felt rather encouraged.
To be frank, I wasn't adjusting too well.
Everyone kept telling me
-that I was too reserved and quiet.
-I know.
So everyone got so curious about you.
I know.
How old are you?
-Me?
-Yes.
I'm 24.
Twenty…
She's taken aback.
He's the youngest one.
-Wait, you're 24?
-Yes.
-You were born in 2000?
-Yes, 2000.
The millennium.
I see.
How old do I look?
I'm guessing around 25?
I'm 28.
You're 28?
Wait. Really?
You look much younger.
But age is just a number, right?
That's true.
It's just a number.
But you seem more at ease
compared to the first day.
-Really?
-Maybe it's because we've grown closer,
but you're more talkative now.
Did I stutter or something back then?
I wouldn't say you stuttered, but…
-Did I seem nervous?
-Yes.
I began talking more to people
I wanted to get to know,
so I feel a lot more comfortable now.
-It helped me adjust better.
-Right.
Who did you talk to so far?
I got to talk a bit with Si-eun.
And yesterday, with Min-ji.
-I see.
-Those two.
And the others? You didn't talk to them?
No.
That's about it.
You must be curious about the others.
Me?
I've already narrowed down
who I want to know better.
-It's not everyone.
-Who?
Who is that person?
-Yes.
-You better answer wisely.
It might be better to stay silent.
-What about you?
-Me?
-Yes.
-Good job. Way to dodge a bullet.
For me, it's…
It's you.
-Me?
-Yes.
Why do you think I've brought you here?
-He's uncomfortable.
-He's in a pickle.
-You can tell by his face.
-He feels awkward.
I'm just really curious about you.
I felt something
from the moment I saw you.
Even though a few guys
have expressed interest in me
in a roundabout way,
there's no one I'm still curious about.
So in other words, I don't think…
There's no one that I'm really…
-Curious about?
-Right.
I told you I picked you on the first day.
Right.
And I picked you again
the day that Min-kyu joined us.
I'm only human,
so when I saw you leave with him,
I was obviously disappointed.
I see.
What about after that?
I tried to talk to you, but…
You tried to talk to me? Stop lying.
I'm saying I thought about it.
I really did.
But because of my personality,
I couldn't get around to it.
Then I kept missing
the right time again and again.
Since we already know how Min-woo feels,
it feels like the conversation
isn't really going anywhere.
-This view is breathtaking.
-Isn't it?
I've never been
to a place like this before.
Was there someone else
you wanted to come here with?
Are you bummed out
-What do you mean?
-that I picked you?
-Am I bummed out?
-Yes.
No, this is a great experience
and a good memory.
Min-woo isn't giving her
a positive answer.
Experience and memory?
She sensed something was off.
Gyu-ri picks things up quickly.
I was really curious about you.
If I don't click with someone
and I'm not interested in them,
I have no interest
in doing anything with them.
It's not like anyone will do,
so I've already…
Are there six guys in total?
The others are already…
off my list.
That's it.
Min-woo and Si-eun keep missing each other
even though they want to be together.
So nothing's really happening.
There's something there, but…
-Nothing certain happens.
-Yes, exactly.
But Gyu-ri made herself clear.
He may like Si-eun more,
but I think
he's still interested in Gyu-ri.
But I can tell Gyu-ri has
more feelings for Min-woo
than Min-kyu judging from her dates.
-She's leading the conversation too.
-Yes.
-I think she finds him cute, like a puppy.
-You're right.
PARADISE
YU SI-EUN & PARK MIN-KYU
This is tough.
It's so tough. Life can be so difficult.
I wonder how they're doing.
What do you think
Min-woo and Gyu-ri are doing right now?
Maybe they're in a spa?
-Spa…
-I wonder how things are there.
If I sense any kind of change
on our helicopter ride back,
I'd feel dispirited.
I think that's about it.
It wasn't this bad,
but the more I talk to you,
the more it feels like
I have a huge, one-sided crush on him.
-You?
-Yes.
Honestly, it wasn't this bad a while ago.
Paradise is great,
but time flies too quickly here.
It's as if I'm lovesick right now.
I must've rubbed off on you.
Yes, because I honestly think
he should meet other people
-so he won't regret anything.
-Right.
It might even make him realize
that he likes me more.
Spending time with her
will help him make up his mind.
-Are you confident though?
-Yes.
-That you're more attractive?
-Of course.
I think I'm way better.
I really do.
I feel like the older one.
Are you going to sleep?
I should.
Was today more fun than yesterday?
Yes, but we'd already spent
a night alone together in Inferno.
Right.
So I naturally felt more at ease with you.
-As for me,
-Yes?
I had so many questions about you,
and today's date really helped me
resolve all those curiosities.
-Really?
-Yes.
Was it the same for you too?
Yes, we talked a lot on the yacht.
It's nice to get a chance
to talk to you like this.
Yes.
I feel more comfortable around you now.
Then were you not
going to talk to me at all?
-Well--
-What if I hadn't brought you here?
To be frank, you've been busy too.
For real.
What is it?
You're so cute.
Gosh.
Good night.
You too, Min-woo.
Look at all those waves.
Let's run six to seven laps
from here to there.
-We're running?
-Yes.
-Come on.
-Let's go.
I'll have three bread rolls for breakfast.
And lots of milk for protein.
-Let's dip them in milk.
-Okay.
That was a good workout. We did our best.
We did.
Time to eat.
-We should wash the apples.
-Yes.
-Good morning.
-Hey.
Is he drawing a line?
Did you hear that tone?
-Min-young's going to approach him.
-Yeah.
-Hello.
-It's my first alarm… No, I mean…
-It's my first breakfast in Inferno.
-Really?
Did the alarm go off? I missed it.
Really? Yes, I heard it.
-Apples?
-Yes.
Hey, rookie.
I can't really see properly.
Do you know why? I lost my contact lens.
It went down the sink.
So I only have one on.
-Did you see her wink?
-Exactly.
It's her thing.
-Really?
-She really knows what she's doing.
-She's good.
-She is.
-She's an expert.
-She really is.
That was so smooth.
It's not easy
to pull that off so smoothly.
I lost my contact lens.
It went down the sink.
So I only have one on.
Oh, no.
-Jin-seok just fell for her again.
-Yes, exactly.
My gosh.
-I want some water too. Good morning.
-Hi.
She winked at Jin-seok,
then sat next to Gwan-hee.
Something's in here.
What's in there?
Didn't I tell you? I can't see well.
-I…
-This is cool.
-Ha-jeong.
-Yes?
-Are you feeling okay?
-Yes, I'm fine.
-Really?
-I guess I don't look so well.
Everyone's been asking.
You just seem so calm.
I seem calm?
I'm sorry, I'm usually this ladylike.
Sure.
-Come on.
-They don't know how she feels.
The sun is so strong.
-Yes.
-That's why it's called Inferno.
-You can hold on to me.
-Sure. Thank you.
It's hot.
-Is no one here?
-Get some rest in your room.
-See you later.
-Okay, see you.
Bye.
Everyone looks…
-Hi.
-How did it go? How was it?
-How was it?
-Tell us how it went.
I'm dying to know.
You look pretty as always.
What did you do?
What happened here? Did you guys have fun?
-Us?
-We went to bed right away.
-Really?
-We went to sleep early.
We didn't do much.
-We got on a yacht yesterday.
-Really?
-It must've been nice.
-That's awesome.
We watched the sunset.
You did?
-It was beautiful.
-That sounds wonderful.
It was.
So did you have a change of heart?
Pretty much the same?
It was more fun than I thought.
Yes.
At first, I thought…
You thought he'd be super quiet?
That was why I chose Min-kyu
the first time around
because I thought
I'd have more fun with him.
But now that we've become
more comfortable with each other,
and we had already
spent some time together before,
it turned out to be better
than I had expected.
It'd be more fun to go there
after you got close to the person.
Yes, I bet.
It was really great.
How was Gyu-ri?
How do you feel about her now?
I found a new side to her,
so it's become more complicated.
I was able to see
how bright and bubbly she actually is.
Oh, really?
So I had so much fun in Paradise
-with Gyu-ri.
-Really?
Were you interested in Gyu-ri at first?
Yes, in the beginning.
She was the one I picked
for the first impression vote.
But after I got here,
I saw how popular she was,
and I'm not the type
to strike up a conversation.
Then, she suddenly picked me,
so I got a chance
to talk to her for a long time.
Who did you like most until recently?
I wanted to get to know Si-eun.
-Si-eun?
-Yes, to be honest.
That time when we talked…
She was really honest about her feelings.
She took the initiative with me,
so I felt like we hit it off
and had good chemistry.
That's why.
How was everything?
-How was it? What did you do?
-Here?
-Yesterday…
-How was it in Inferno?
-Well, it was…
-Was it fun?
Well, as for the men…
Jin-seok seemed…
-Jin-seok?
-He was…
When we were eating,
I noticed that he was…
That he and Min-young are really close?
Everyone just seems
to think of them as a couple.
-Don't let that get to you.
-I know.
Right, I'll talk to him some more today,
and if I like him the most
among all the guys,
I'll just make him mine.
-Win him over.
-Yes, win him over.
Yes.
I had fun with Gwan-hee too.
As for Gwan-hee…
I thought he kept being curt with me
because he wasn't interested.
-How should I even put it?
-That's what he's like.
So I thought he had
already decided on someone.
I felt like he thought
I was getting in the way
when things were going well
between him and someone.
But it turns out that's just who he is.
It didn't seem like he was set on anybody.
The way he treats me is different
from how he treats others,
so I'm so confused.
You're right.
He never teased me
like he does with the others.
So that kind of confuses me.
Do you think Hye-seon had fun with Won-ik?
Probably.
Hye-seon likes Won-ik so much.
-What?
Does it seem that way to you?
Hye-seon definitely likes Won-ik.
-Really?
-She's always focused on him.
I can see she's really into him.
-Yes, seriously.
-It's obvious.
What?
-What?
-Really?
They're completely off the mark.
Why do they think that?
Let's say you're Won-ik, and I'm Hye-seon.
When they were eating…
-Really?
-And when he was chopping something…
You're so good at mimicking her.
You're so good.
-You're just like her.
-She's always like this.
So I kept watching her.
Do you also think that Hye-seon is…
Yes, I definitely picked it up
on the helicopter ride back.
-I'm certain.
-What did you notice?
How should I put this?
The way she looked at him
and the vibe she gave off.
The nonverbal cues and body language.
It's just a gut feeling.
Stop saying stuff you're not sure of.
-What gut feeling?
-That's what men are like.
-Man, I'm getting stressed out.
-I mean…
It was so obvious.
I'm so annoyed.
Men just don't get women, do they?
I don't think so.
How could they think so?
That was so random.
-I'm in shock right now.
-Where did that even come from?
We see everything from here.
-Right.
-But if you were there…
-You have a point.
-But even so…
I think Min-kyu
was just going along with it.
Ha-bin's the one who's mistaken.
He's way off the mark right now.
In a way, he's spreading fake news.
Seriously.
The problem is
that it's really rattling Gwan-hee.
-Yes.
-That's the problem.
-It's even worse.
-What now?
Gwan-hee's feelings
must be changing every single day.
-He's going to get swayed again.
-I can see it in his eyes.
What now?
Today, the men will play a game
to win a date in Paradise.
Gosh, come on.
Please go to the island on the other side.
The island on the other side?
-I wonder what we'll be doing.
-I have no clue.
What on earth could they
make us do on that island?
-I really can't guess.
-Right?
This hill is seriously…
What did I tell you?
This island is way worse.
-It's a long walk. Look.
-This is the real Inferno.
-The true Inferno.
-How was it here?
There are way too many hills here,
and all the roads are
dirt and gravel ones.
We're literally hiking.
-What's that?
-They're flags.
-Flags.
-Yes.
I wonder what the game is.
Oh, it's a race.
-A race?
-Gosh.
I guess it's a race from there to here.
I should've skipped the morning run.
This is crazy.
Singles.
Today, the men will be competing in a game
for a date in Paradise.
The top three contestants,
in order of rank,
will get to choose the women
they'd like to go to Paradise with.
I'm nervous.
-I think I'll lose.
-Here are the rules of today's game.
There are three flags on top of this hill.
At the sound of the signal,
the men will sprint from the starting line
toward the flags as fast as they can.
-My gosh.
-It's a race?
It's a race.
I wonder how far it is.
-My gosh.
-It's far.
-It's so far.
-It's almost like a marathon.
-It's a marathon.
-Really.
Seriously.
The first three men to seize the flags
will be placed first, second, and third.
This is a battle
between Min-kyu and Gwan-hee.
We've got ourselves a basketball player
and a coast guard.
-It seems so.
-But you know,
Ha-bin may be a professional runner.
-What?
-His job.
-His job?
-An athlete?
In track and field.
-It hasn't been revealed yet.
-Exactly.
He could be a professional runner
for some team.
They're running all at once?
This is insane.
Jin-seok kept saying he was a bad runner.
He seems like the type
who's better at lifting weights.
I think Min-woo and…
-I think so too.
-Min-woo and Ha-bin.
Gwan-hee looks like
a professional athlete with his headband.
You're right.
Men, please walk over
to the starting point.
-Gosh.
-Let's go.
Is that the finish line?
-Good luck, guys.
-Thanks.
Don't get hurt.
This is a simple race,
-but their pride is at stake, right?
-You're right.
Plus, it's hard to run uphill.
Let's check out how the guys look
as they cross the finish line.
It's important.
-They can't show how tired they are.
-Precisely.
They need to play it cool.
Please start running
once you hear the signal.
Get ready.
-It must be tough to run this far.
-It's really far.
-You would know.
-Yes.
-We got off easy with our game.
-I know, right?
Get ready.
The three quickly took the lead.
-They're on their way.
-My gosh!
-Really?
-Oh, gosh.
-Gosh.
-I'm nervous.
-So am I.
-I can't watch this.
-He's really fast.
-Gwan-hee.
I knew he'd be good.
He's so fast.
-Ha-bin is in second place.
-Ha-bin?
-I told you he's an athlete.
-He's in second?
I bet he does track and field.
I can't do this.
My knees hurt.
Jin-seok.
-Good call, Jin-seok.
-It's okay.
It's all right.
-Save that energy to woo the women later.
-Yes.
-He just looked back!
-Hey!
-All right!
-Look at that confidence!
Ha-bin's tired. His legs are giving out.
Gosh, Ha-bin.
-It's a fight for third place. Oh, no.
-It's between Won-ik and Ha-bin.
-Come on, Ha-bin.
-Ha-bin, please.
They're almost here.
Do you see them?
-I wonder who will win.
-I can't watch this.
They're here already?
-I can hear them run.
-I hear them now.
I see orange shorts!
No, I was wrong.
I think it's Gwan-hee.
Gwan-hee.
That's so cool.
-That was cool.
-It was.
-It really was.
-That was pretty cool.
1ST PLACE: LEE GWAN-HEE
Gwan-hee.
He won by a wide margin.
2ND PLACE: PARK MIN-KYU
3RD PLACE: SON WON-IK
Won-ik did it again.
-He's quite athletic.
-He's good at most things.
It's because he's fit.
Great job, guys.
Jin-seok isn't here yet.
Is he walking?
What is Jin-seok doing?
-I think he's walking.
-He must be.
Really? I wonder if he's injured.
-Jin-seok.
-Oh, no.
He's taking a stroll.
-He should limp a little.
-Yes, he should blame it on his knees.
-He's really walking.
-Goodness.
He's really walking.
Jin-seok.
Good job!
I couldn't run because of my knees.
That's right. He said he had bad knees.
-What?
-Who did he wink at?
At Min-young?
My gosh.
Why did he wink at me?
-That's so cringe.
-What?
-What happened?
-Jin-seok winked at her.
I missed that.
They look so tired.
You guys are so fast.
-They're really fast.
-That was impressive.
I found his headband funny,
but then, he ran so fast.
I was quite impressed by him.
Gwan-hee is an athlete,
so I knew he would come in first.
It'd be nice to go to Paradise
with Gwan-hee…
But I'm not so sure about him yet.
Just who will Gwan-hee pick?
I can't even guess.
-He has a really important choice to make.
-Right.
Who he chooses today
will reveal who he is leaning toward.
-It will make things clear.
-You're right.
-They only have three days left.
-Right.
It'll be Hye-seon,
Ha-jeong, or Min-ji, right?
-Yes.
-He hasn't been to Paradise with Min-ji.
-That's right.
But he's heard a few things
that could change his mind.
Regardless of what he heard,
if Gwan-hee has feelings for Hye-seon,
he might talk to her in Paradise
and find out how she feels.
I doubt what he heard
will affect his decision.
-But…
-He seemed quite shaken up though.
-He was.
-He seemed shaken up by what he heard.
But if Gwan-hee chooses Min-ji
instead of Hye-seon,
I doubt Hye-seon
will give him another chance.
-I agree.
-You're right.
How will Ha-jeong feel
if he chooses Min-ji?
If that happens, it'll break my heart.
-Sit wherever you like.
-I want to sit in the shade.
-Sure.
-Right here.
What?
I'm glad they decided to talk.
Did you have fun in Paradise?
You looked like you had fun.
Fun?
It was more comfortable than fun.
I see. I'm glad you had a good time.
I actually wanted to talk to you
when you got back,
but it seemed like you didn't want to.
What are you talking about?
-You wouldn't look me in the eye.
-Me?
-Yes.
-I don't usually make eye contact.
Anyway, I took it as a sign
that you didn't want to talk to me.
No, I did think we needed to talk.
Well, that's how I took it.
What about now?
I knew you'd make that choice
when it was your turn to pick.
But when I saw you leave with Won-ik,
it occurred to me
that you might also want me
to choose someone else.
I'm serious. I thought there was a chance…
-I'd pick you?
-I thought there was a 10% chance.
Because of what I said before?
Yes, that was why I had that thought.
You're upset.
Do you remember when I got back
from Paradise with Ha-jeong?
I asked if you were bothered by it,
and you seemed like you were sulking.
So it felt like you wanted me to sulk
now that the tables had turned.
And the thing is, I asked around
a lot about you.
And everyone said
-that you had your eyes on Won-ik.
-Really?
-That was what they told me.
So I was
quite shocked.
-So I…
-Are you serious?
Now that you're back from Paradise,
I want to know how you honestly feel.
Well, I really don't know.
I know that he's a good person,
but I'm not sure if I'm attracted to him.
-You're not sure yet?
-No, I'm not.
When I was with him,
I didn't feel any chemistry between us.
I really don't know.
In my own way,
I tried to show you how I felt
when you fell during the game yesterday.
DURING WOMEN'S GAME YESTERDAY
There's something in your hair.
Your hair.
Hye-seon. Are you all right?
I didn't brush anything off
of Gyu-ri when she fell.
But when you fell,
I was the first one to run over.
It was my way of telling you
how I felt about you.
And it's something
only you would've noticed.
-Yes, I noticed it.
-Among the six of you,
only you would've noticed it.
So I was shocked to hear
what others thought.
In any case, I'm drawn to you the most.
When you fell during the game,
I was concerned about you.
Even when we eat,
if I feel like you're too quiet,
I get concerned.
That's how I feel about you.
I can't say I didn't notice any of that,
but I sort of wanted to play hard to get.
I guess I'm not too sure.
-I think I understand--
-What I do know is this.
Compared to Won-ik,
I have stronger feelings for you.
I noticed something.
I act differently when I talk to you
compared to when I talk to Won-ik.
Do you have more fun with him?
He's not the fun type.
But regardless,
I wouldn't mind you choosing Min-ji
or someone other than myself today.
Because…
What?
-She's confusing him again.
-She seems too confident.
Because we'll still
have a chance tomorrow.
-We can pick each other tomorrow.
-Tomorrow…
Are you saying
I should go with Min-ji today
and keep going with someone else
until we finally reunite on the last day?
Is that what you're saying?
We went together once,
so do you want to enjoy your time
and just meet in the end?
-What…
-Something like that.
-What are you saying?
-I mean…
-Don't you think you'll regret it?
-Regret what?
I assumed you'd go with Min-ji or Gyu-ri.
-Because…
-No, Gyu-ri isn't for me.
I told you I wanted to get to know her,
so I went and talked to her,
but that was it.
We had a chat, and that was enough for me.
I see.
Are you settling for me
because the others
don't seem right for you?
Do I look like that type?
No, not really.
-But still…
-Not at all.
-Really?
-Really.
I had no idea
he felt so strongly about Hye-seon.
He's gentle as a lamb around her.
-He is.
-He's really calm and doesn't joke around.
She said she wouldn't mind
if he went to Paradise with Min-ji.
Do you think she really meant that?
I think by saying that, she made it
more impossible to go with Min-ji.
There's something about Hye-seon
that's hard to explain.
It's hard to put into words.
-Her aura?
-She's very charismatic.
-Yes, you can feel it.
-You can.
That's why Gwan-hee
is trying not to cross that line.
Do you remember what they said
when they first went to Paradise together?
-They promised to meet in the end.
-Yes, exactly.
DAY 1 PARADISE
I'd appreciate it more if you told me
that even after meeting the others,
you still like me the best.
It'd be more genuine.
That goes for me as well.
So you want to reunite on the last day?
We can share the chocolate
they left us on the last day.
Here's my take.
-He hasn't been to Paradise with Min-ji.
-No.
So she could be saying they should
get to know everyone they're attracted to
and see if they'll still like each other.
It seems like she is quite confident.
When it comes to someone like Gwan-hee,
you shouldn't be too clingy
or open up too much.
-He'll find it boring.
-Right.
But you can't play too hard to get.
He doesn't like that either.
Hye-seon is doing a good job
keeping that balance.
-Hye-seon--
-She shows interest but plays hard to get.
-Right.
-Right?
Hye-seon may be playing her cards right
because she's figured him out.
Or it may be
that she's just not that into him.
You know what I think?
If he's someone that will change his mind
after one trip to Paradise,
-she may not want him.
-Right.
-Don't you think so?
-That could be it.
Gwan-hee must be so confused
after talking to Hye-seon.
-He must be.
-There are so many twists.
I'm totally hooked.
How are you doing?
-What about you?
-I'm doing good.
-Why did you want to talk?
-Because we need to.
Did you feel obligated?
No, it's not that.
"Look at the time.
I guess I should talk to Min-ji now."
-That's not it.
-Whatever.
You're upset.
-I'm not.
-You are.
I think you are quite upset.
-I felt a bit uncomfortable yesterday.
-Okay.
Out of everyone here,
I've gotten closest to you and Min-woo.
I see.
So I was relying on you two,
but Min-woo left, and you…
I was also--
I wanted to talk to you,
but it was hard to approach you.
You can talk to me.
They were just messing around.
I mean, no one's committed to anyone yet.
Right.
It seems like you are committed though.
I'm not committed to anyone right now.
They were just teasing me.
I told them too. You're the only one
I've been attracted to
other than Min-young.
I think they were surprised
because they haven't seen me
talk to anyone else.
I really haven't talked to anyone else.
I don't approach
someone I'm not attracted to.
I only talk to those I'm attracted to.
You're not attracted to the others?
-To be honest, no.
-Really?
I don't feel that attraction.
I'm not particularly attracted
to anyone else at this moment.
I'm not really the type to try.
-Are you trying to make me feel better?
-Of course I am.
-It's going to take you four days.
-I want to…
How many days do we have?
-You have to try until we leave.
-I'm trying to, but aside from that,
I personally find you attractive.
-I am attractive, right?
-You are?
-Gosh.
-That was smooth.
Did you see that?
She's mastered the art of flirting.
"I am attractive, right?"
It wasn't like that.
That wasn't it.
You lack the innocence she has.
Guys know when girls are just flirting,
but a wink like that
-shakes them up, right?
-Of course.
-Of course. Just look at him.
-Absolutely.
I am attractive, right?
-You are?
-I am.
I even told the girls
that I shouldn't care
and just pursue you again.
What? Can I not say that?
Of course you can.
Do you like talking to me?
I do like talking to you.
It's nice.
-Of course--
-It's fun, right?
Yes, it's fun to talk to you.
-I said a lot of good things about you.
-Really?
He seems a bit dazed.
Jin-seok is a bit out of it.
-You're a good runner.
-Really?
-You said you like running, right?
-Right.
How do you feel about the win?
It would've been nice
if I had ranked higher.
I wanted to come in first.
I would've been able
to have the first pick.
That's true.
You would have.
I can tell that Si-eun
is trying to distance herself from him.
She's really bad at hiding her emotions.
-She's very different around him.
-She is.
Did you expect the girls
who won first and second place
to choose who they did yesterday?
Yes, somewhat.
Who would you have gone with
if you had placed first?
-Me?
-Yes.
I think I would've chosen
someone I haven't gone with.
-I see.
-Yes.
If I don't go with someone new,
I feel like I might regret it later
-when we make our final decision.
-Right.
Well… Yes, that's what I would've done.
-Si-eun is very transparent.
-She is.
-She may be telling him not to pick her.
-Right.
-I see.
-I feel bad for Won-ik.
They don't have much time left,
so I think it's better.
You're right.
I want to talk to both Si-eun and Gyu-ri.
I see.
Maybe I should talk to Gyu-ri now.
Go ahead. I'll talk to Min-young too.
There's no one else for me to talk to.
-Is this Gyu-ri's room?
-Yes.
Right now, Si-eun is trying to make sure
-Won-ik doesn't get the wrong idea.
-You're right.
-He should talk to Si-eun.
-What are you doing, Min-woo?
-Come in.
Look who's here.
Is Gyu-ri in? Let's talk.
Were you busy?
Me? Was I busy?
I was avoiding the heat.
Can you hold my hand for a second?
-He held her hand.
What if Si-eun sees this?
No, she can't see this.
Have fun.
I want to come and watch.
The shade is…
This side looks better.
Thanks.
I like your outfit.
-This?
-Yes.
I really had a great time
chatting with you in Paradise.
You've been on my mind ever since,
so I wanted to talk to you.
-That trip must've been nice.
-It must've played a big part.
-His mind changes just like that?
-Out of sight, out of mind.
I guess that's the case.
The timing is always off
with Min-woo and Si-eun.
The Paradise I went to with you
was the most fun.
The thing is…
I get nervous whenever I talk to you.
I become a lot more nervous
than I do around others.
It's just how I feel.
Me too.
We really bonded a lot yesterday.
-We did.
-Doesn't it feel different now?
Compared to that time in Inferno…
-Inferno?
-Yes, things do feel different now.
Yes, I remember that day.
I wasn't very talkative on the first day.
-Right.
-You weren't either.
I find you fascinating.
I keep noticing different sides of you.
And that sparks curiosity, right?
Yes, you're right.
I just can't help but feel nervous
since you're so popular.
-I'm not.
-I bet you'll go to Paradise again.
-Do you think so?
-I just…
I'd rather stay here today.
-Really?
-Yes.
-That was just…
-She's really expressing herself.
I'd rather stay here today.
-Really?
-Yes.
I'd love it if you stayed here too.
Then we'd get to chat some more.
I mean, we're really running out of time.
There's not much time left.
So I'm going to be more honest
about my feelings now.
Sometimes you need to be.
-Right?
-Yes, right.
I'm not saying this because
you might leave for Paradise.
Okay.
I just wanted to make good use
of the little time we have left.
-Gyu-ri's gaze is intense.
-Seriously.
She has a different kind of charisma
compared to Min-ji.
She's looking at him intently.
But I'm not so sure.
Do you really think I'll go?
It's just my guess.
What if I end up going?
If you go?
What can I do?
It's not like I can stop you.
I can't beg you to stay.
If I end up going, stay put and lie low.
Of course I will.
We're all stuck here.
We'll probably just eat.
Don't do anything funny.
If you end up going?
She's telling him
not to talk to other women.
-Right.
-Yes.
It looks like Min-woo is
completely drawn to Gyu-ri.
-Yes, after Paradise.
-Yes.
-He really likes her.
-Yes, Paradise.
He beat around the bush
and didn't express his feelings.
But now,
he even called her out for a chat.
He had feelings for Si-eun,
but it now looks like he's set on Gyu-ri
after their trip to Paradise.
-Right?
-What did it?
The bedtime talk?
-I think that was it.
-Right?
They seemed to have more fun
talking before bed
than they did on the yacht.
And while they were talking,
Min-woo kept tossing and turning.
He kept putting the blanket
between his legs
then covering them back.
Right.
It just seemed so strange to me,
but now I get it.
-It was because he liked her so much.
-Exactly.
-The blanket…
-He felt giddy.
Yes, and while he was feeling that way,
Gyu-ri suddenly said,
-"You're so cute."
-Exactly!
-That's what she said.
-My gosh.
-Gosh.
-This is how Gyu-ri talks.
"Really?"
Right.
"Have you eaten yet?"
"You're so cute."
She has a way of melting your heart
when she talks.
This is just too much.
But this is pretty insane.
-Min-woo is head over heels for her.
-I know.
-He's mesmerized.
-Yes, he's gone head over heels.
She got him good.
Min-kyu. He's like a puppy too.
Yes, his eyes are set on Gyu-ri.
Let's go inside.
Let's talk while I curl my hair
in my room.
-Is that okay?
-What do you want to talk about?
-What good is it sitting out here? Come.
-Okay, fine.
Curl her hair?
-It's time to talk strategy.
-Right.
What was that big sigh for?
I don't know how…
Because it feels like
Gyu-ri is going back and forth
between you and Min-woo?
It's so obvious!
She's being swayed.
-So is that why?
-Yes.
Then you should be a man
and do something about it.
It might make her feel uncomfortable.
No, even if that's the case,
at least you won't regret it.
-Right.
-Yes.
Who are you set on?
-Me?
-Yes.
Ha-bin, right?
No, it's Gwan-hee.
What?
-Seriously?
-Yes.
If I want something, I go for it.
I see.
So I told him too.
-You're really the best.
-Why?
Yes, it's better to tell him
before someone starts spreading fake news.
-They're both set on one person.
-Right.
Will you catch that fly for me?
How do you expect me to catch a fly?
With what?
-They're fast, unlike mosquitoes.
-Catch the fly, will you?
It suddenly came inside.
-She's here.
-She's back.
Look at that smile on your face.
-Hi.
-Hi, am I interrupting?
-No.
-I told him to watch me do my hair.
-I got kidnapped.
Yes, I invited him in.
I had to curl my hair,
so I told him to watch.
-I was bored.
-Is it hot?
It is.
-You look more sunburnt today.
-Me?
-I've been getting so sunburnt.
-Hey, wait.
There's a fly in our room.
I'm way too sunburnt.
-I'll catch it for you later.
-Really?
When I asked you,
you told me you couldn't.
You're so willing to catch it
now that Gyu-ri is here.
-He offered to catch it for her.
-This is fun.
-You said you couldn't.
-I just tried to be sweet.
Like I said, flies are too fast.
-Unbelievable.
-Did you have to comment on that?
You never let things slide.
-You're unbelievable.
-You look way better with wavy hair.
-Really?
-Gyu-ri, can we chat?
Let's talk in the other room.
-No one's there.
-There's an empty room?
Our room is probably empty.
No one was there.
Really?
Is my face that sunburnt? That's not good.
Yes, you're pretty sunburnt.
Hey, get the fly before you leave.
Where is it?
Let me go chat, please.
Gosh, just…
Figure it out yourself.
-Bye.
-Are you serious?
-I'll help you later.
-You're just awful.
-My gosh, Ha-jeong.
-What's with her hair?
-Oh, no.
-She's so cute.
-She messed up her hair.
-Seriously.
She's really something.
-She's adorable.
-She really is.
If you'd made it
to the top three in today's race,
who would you have picked?
I can't decide.
Between the two?
Yes, at the moment.
Really?
You must've had fun yesterday.
It was great.
Is that why? Did it have a big impact?
Yes, very much.
That's why Paradise is a big deal.
-You should go with Si-eun too.
-Yes, that'll help you decide.
Then I should've won.
Right?
-They're all so athletic.
-Exactly.
-He's so cute.
-Look at Jin-seok.
He looks super athletic,
but he didn't win.
-You're right.
-They're finally back.
-Isn't the sun too strong?
-It is.
What are you up to?
-Just chatting.
-Matching colors.
-Are you having fun?
-Yes.
Without me? How could you?
Do you want to chat?
You're leaving as soon as you're back.
Have fun.
-She looks so happy.
-She looks different.
-She's so into him.
-Oh, dear.
-See you guys later.
-Bye.
Have fun.
-I can send everyone off.
-Really?
I should've just gone over
to ask you to chat there.
-I know.
-They're so cute.
This is embarrassing.
-How cute.
-He's finally talking more.
He's adorable.
We're wearing the same color.
You're right.
-What?
-What took you so long to ask?
Won-ik kept you all to himself.
So did you have fun yesterday?
-Me?
-Yes.
What do you think?
-Are you making fun of me?
-No, not at all.
Come on. I would never.
-How was it?
-What?
Nothing much.
I just talked and stuff.
Did you have fun?
Yes, I guess.
I'm sure you also had fun.
After all, it's Paradise.
-Us?
-Yes.
We both just talked about
what was on our minds.
-So you talked a lot?
-Yes, we talked a lot.
I had no idea
we'd end up playing a game today.
Yes, I'm sure you wanted to win.
They were all too good.
-Really?
-Yes, they all run so fast.
You're smiling a lot today.
-Today?
-Yes. You look way better when you smile.
Thanks. You have a nice smile too.
The way your lips perk up.
Thanks.
Did you have a good talk with Won-ik?
Yes.
I guess you'll probably go today.
-I think you'll end up going.
-Our timing was off again.
We're short on time again today.
Today?
-Yesterday--
-We don't have that many days left.
I know. You're right.
We're going to match the couples
who will go on a date in Paradise.
Gosh. Let's go.
We're out of time.
Let's go.
Gosh, let them talk for a bit longer.
-Time isn't on their side.
-Are they doing this on purpose?
I'm back.
-I think you'll go with Won-ik.
-What?
I think you're going to Paradise.
-With whom?
-What's wrong?
-What? With Won-ik?
-Are you crying?
No.
Oh, no. What happened?
What's going on?
-She's crying?
-She must be upset.
-Exactly.
Yes, really.
Oh, no.
I don't want to go out for this.
-You should cry here.
-Okay.
Don't be upset.
-I'll go over there.
-Okay.
I didn't think I'd end up crying here.
But you're still crying.
What is it? Is it frustrating?
Well, we were given time to talk,
-so I went and talked to him.
-Who?
Won-ik.
After that, I talked to Min-woo.
-Are you torn between them?
-I wouldn't call it that.
It's not about making a decision.
I just want a chance to talk,
but our timing's always off.
When you talk to someone, you know
whether to keep pushing forward with them.
I really don't want to…
You don't want to go?
-I want to get some rest.
-I see.
It's just frustrating. That's all.
But I don't think
Won-ik will choose Si-eun today.
-What if he does?
-He won't.
-I think…
-I know it.
-That's just what you want.
-No, seriously.
-He caught on to how Si-eun feels.
-Right.
I think he understood what she meant
when they were talking earlier.
He seems quick on the uptake.
But will he still take her to Paradise
and try his best to win her heart?
Or will he respect her feelings?
-That's for Won-ik to decide.
-Yes.
I hope Won-ik takes Ha-bin.
-Seriously.
-Me too.
-Take Ha-bin instead.
-You're so mean.
-They should go and get hammered.
-Exactly.
And talk about how they really feel.
The winner gets to choose first.
-Yes, Gwan-hee.
-Out of the three…
No. Who will he choose between the two?
Hye-seon.
-Hye-seon?
-Yes.
The Gwan-hee we know
would normally choose Min-ji.
Hye-seon was totally cool
about him choosing Min-ji.
She was too cool about it.
Gwan-hee was taken aback by it.
I think it got to him.
Will they really
eventually end up together?
-Seriously.
-He goes with Min-ji this time.
And they choose each other
for the last one.
This is unimaginable for me.
I'm dying to find out.
Now, we're going to match the couples
who will go on a date in Paradise.
Starting with Lee Gwan-hee,
who came in first,
please select the person
you'd like to go to Paradise with.
I'm dying to find out.
-I wonder who it'll be.
-Me too.
Who do you think Gwan-hee will pick?
-I think…
-Min-ji?
He'll probably pick Min-ji.
Or maybe Hye-seon.
Either Min-ji or Hye-seon.
The person I'd like to go
to Paradise with is…
I think
I like you the most.
-Me?
-Yes.
During my time here…
You've had the biggest impact on me
and made me feel
a lot of different emotions.
Why didn't you show me how you felt?
If I was talking to another woman--
I'd still approach you and ask to chat.
I'm curious about your job now.
Me?
-I told you I like to be honest, right?
-Yes.
I still find you the most attractive.
-Me?
-Yes.
In any case, I'm drawn to you the most.
When you fell during the game,
I was concerned about you.
That's how I feel about you.
The person I'd like to go
to Paradise with is…
I can be myself when I'm with you.
I'm not faking anything now.
It feels different this time around.
NEXT EPISODE
Everything's up to you now.
I could end up with the person I like
if I keep trying.
I'll clear things up for you.
Are you going to bed?
Is it nice?
Paradise didn't mean much to me.
But it feels completely different today.
I felt something special.
I had the hardest time
trying to figure you out.
It was hard to really be sure.
Want to sleep in the same bed?
Okay.
NEXT EPISODE
Am I a decent woman?
Yes, you're definitely attractive.
I missed you a bit.
Will you look at me?
You won't look at me anymore.
A little bit of tension
is necessary for you.
There was someone else
I wanted to talk to.
But after this conversation,
I decided not to.
I'm closer to making my final decision.
I think I'm all good now.
Subtitle translation by: Eunsook Youn