KIM HYEON-JOONG
MOON SE-HOON
SHIN JI-YEON
KIM JUN-SIK
KANG SO-YEON
CHOI SI-HUN
AN YEA-WON
SONG JI-A
OH JIN-TAEK
KIM SU-MIN
SEONG MIN-JI
CHA HYUN-SEUNG
I choose…
Shin Ji-yeon.
My gosh. I got goosebumps.
I'm impressed.
-I admire him.
-Gosh. Se-hoon is really amazing.
Seriously, I got goosebumps.
I got goosebumps.
Se-hoon really impresses me.
-Se-hoon.
-I had no idea he was this type of man.
-He really impresses me.
-My gosh. He was a one-woman man.
This is why he was so upset
about So-yeon's advice.
-Right.
-It makes sense.
-He likes her that much.
-Yes.
-Seriously, I got goosebumps.
-Se-hoon is a real go-getter.
-He's a go-getter.
-A real go-getter.
I'd like to get to know Se-hoon better.
I want to be friends.
If I were in her position,
I would change my mind.
If someone was that serious about me…
Unless he did something really bad,
I would definitely be swayed.
Don't you think so?
-What do you guys think?
-I would definitely feel like
I would like to get to know him.
-Exactly.
-When Se-hoon said,
-I would feel the same.
-"I choose Shin Ji-yeon",
-I thought it was really cool.
-Me too.
As a man myself,
I thought it was really cool.
Right.
I choose Shin Ji-yeon.
The person Moon Se-hoon chose is
Shin Ji-yeon.
Ji-yeon, please come outside…
Ji-yeon, please come outside
and leave for Paradise with Se-hoon.
-I told you.
-He finally succeeded.
Shin Ji-yeon.
Ji-yeon, please come outside
and leave for Paradise with Se-hoon.
Good. I'm happy for him.
I got goosebumps.
-You didn't think I'd choose you, right?
-No.
-What just happened?
-What?
What just happened?
-This is my first time going to Paradise.
-I know.
But we haven't talked
for a really long time.
I just followed my heart.
-Really?
-Yes.
Well, I thought talking there…
would be different.
-Okay.
-I made this decision purely for myself.
Really.
So you don't need to feel any pressure.
-All right.
-Well, you've been there,
-Yes.
-so I want you to…
I'll lead you.
No. I mean…
-I can…
-I heard a lot about it.
Amazing, right?
Gosh, I really admire Se-hoon.
Really?
Seriously.
This is the third time.
Is it the third or fourth?
-This is the fourth time.
-Right? Gosh.
I'm a bit taken aback.
-Why?
-I didn't know about that.
Not at all?
Not at all.
Se-hoon has always been like this.
Lastly, it's the second runner-up,
Oh Jin-taek's turn.
Please choose the person
you'd like to go on a date with
in Paradise.
I choose…
-Please choose the person you'd like
-Just go out now.
-to go on a date with in Paradise.
-No. We never know.
That's not true.
-Really, it has to be you.
-We never know.
I choose Kang So-yeon.
Kang So-yeon.
So-yeon, please come outside
-Have fun.
-and leave for Paradise
-See you.
-with Jin-taek.
Let's go.
-Let's go.
-Shall we?
Yes.
-To Paradise?
-To Paradise.
Gosh, Se-hoon really surprised me.
I feel like things are going
to be different after this night.
-Right.
-Gosh.
Things are going to be so different.
I agree.
Hyun-seung and Ji-a went to Paradise.
And to be honest,
it really made me anxious.
It hurt a lot.
I thought I'd be okay, but it wasn't easy.
It wasn't easy.
It happened before I came here,
so I thought there's nothing
I could do about it.
That helped me move on.
To be honest, I was pretty upset.
I felt like there was
no space for me.
I had so many thoughts.
But I still have questions
I want to ask him.
So I'll keep trying.
So those were their choices.
HANHAE, HONG JIN-KYUNG,
LEE DA-HEE, KYUHYUN
It always makes us feel bad
-to see the unchosen people.
-Right.
-I find Min-ji's attitude really cool.
-Me too.
-She's so cool.
-"Though I came a little late,
I'll follow my heart anyway."
-Right.
-She said she'd keep trying.
As a viewer, I'm so glad
to finally get to hear
what Se-hoon does for a living.
-Right.
-Exactly.
-I forgot.
-I want to know how old he is.
-It felt like he was living in Inferno.
-We've been merely guessing.
-You're so mean.
-Come on. Don't be like that.
-Seriously. You're so mean.
-What a mean thing to say.
Was he born in Inferno then?
Is he a Grim Reaper?
He's someone who lives on that island?
That's another reason why
I'm excited about this.
Getting to know him.
I also wonder how he'll make
the best of the time there.
-That'll be interesting.
-I hope he makes the best of it.
He's going to make the best
of every second he has.
Do we need to wear this?
We do?
-Se-hoon seems fascinated.
-He seems so excited.
He's excited.
I think I hear the helicopter.
There it goes. They're leaving.
There's the helicopter!
Bye!
They probably can't see us.
-Hyeon-joong isn't even looking at it.
-He isn't.
Of course he isn't.
-Min-ji isn't looking either.
-It seems like Min-ji was
-quite interested in Se-hoon too.
-I guess so.
-She looks down.
-At the interview, she said
-that she never gives up.
-I remember.
Min-ji is like
a female version of Se-hoon.
-Female Se-hoon?
-Female Se-hoon.
Are we going to fry the eggs?
I was thinking omelets,
but let's fry them.
We should wash the spring onions.
Right. Let's wash them
and cut them like this.
You know it, right?
Add salt.
-We have a lot of eggs.
-That's enough to make an omelet.
-Leave it. I'll do it. Salt?
-There's so much to wash.
-I need to peel them one by one, right?
-Oh, this.
It's much easier
if you just peel this one layer.
Let me do it.
-Do you know how to do it?
-Yes.
I can't rely on you.
PARADISE
MOON SE-HOON AND SHIN JI-YEON
My gosh.
My gosh. This room is huge.
-This is literally a paradise.
-This room is really big.
-This place is amazing.
-My goodness.
There's a swimming pool here.
-That's one huge swimming pool.
-It looks so nice.
My gosh.
If this is the pool we have…
I think I have to swim.
-Gosh. I don't think I can…
-Sleep tonight?
I might not go to bed.
-Let's see what they've got.
-See if there's anything you want.
-First, one grilled cheeseburger.
-Okay.
-And tomato…
-Spaghetti?
Seafood spaghetti.
You had this, didn't you?
No, I had this one.
-Just the tomato spaghetti?
-Yes.
Ribs sound good too.
-Let's order ribs.
All right. Ribs and a sirloin steak.
-The sirloin steak is great.
-With mashed potato.
-Sirloin steak.
-A sirloin steak, ribs, a burger…
I'll order these first.
-All right.
-Okay.
I'd like to order
one grilled cheeseburger.
Does it come with fries on the side?
I see. Can I have a lot of ketchup?
I'd like to have a lot of ketchup please.
-He wants a lot of ketchup.
-A lot of ketchup.
He's so cute.
The steak. How would you like your steak?
-Well done.
-Okay. The steak…
How about you?
I'd like to have it well done.
Okay. Thank you.
-My gosh. It looks delicious.
-Gosh. It looks delicious.
Let's not act like hungry people.
We need to be elegant here.
No. I've been hungry.
It looks delicious.
You can start first.
-I'll open this.
-Okay. I want ice cream first.
Go ahead and eat up. Let's just eat first.
Before it melts.
Want to try it first?
I'm not feeding…
-I thought you were feeding me.
-No, take it. What should I do?
You want to eat it that way?
Just like that?
My gosh.
It's totally different here.
-I know, right?
-Yes.
-Do you get why we've been saying that?
-Before I came here
-You didn't know it'd be so great.
-I thought
-we could just be open about each other.
-You thought that's it, right?
I told you. Once you come out here,
you want to come here every night.
Cheers.
So how old are you?
-None of us know how old you are.
-Right.
No one knows your age.
I know others' ages.
So how old are you?
-You have something…
-I do? Thanks.
So how old are you?
Let me guess.
-Okay. I'll tell you if you're right.
-Okay.
I can guess it correctly.
Either 29 or 30.
You were born in 1993 or 1992, right?
-No?
-I'm 27.
-You're 27?
-Yes.
-Really?
Then we're almost the same age.
How old are you?
What do you think?
I'll give you one more chance.
I think you're 26.
I'm 25.
Okay. You're 25.
Yes. I'm younger than you thought, right?
-We're practically the same age.
-Right.
So what do you do for a living?
I'm running a business.
A business? What business?
A culinary business.
-A culinary business?
-Yes.
I run a restaurant in Gangnam.
I've been running
this business for four years now,
and I've been working in
this field for about six or seven years.
That's so cool.
That's why he cooked well.
When I go to work,
I have a meeting with my employees.
We talk about how the wine order went
and what we can improve.
When my employees are
on leave, I serve food
and cook in the kitchen too.
-That's so cool.
-Right.
That's so cool.
I should visit.
Tell me where it is.
I'll bring my friends.
Sure. Anytime.
I'll make you something delicious.
Really? I'm really going to go.
-Sure. Come.
-Okay.
After the second time I went to the hotel,
you avoided talking to me, right?
-Yes.
-Am I right?
I chose you both times.
I really did. I voted for you both
the first and second time.
So you went to Paradise
with Si-hun on the first day
and with Jin-taek on the second day.
I tried talking to you,
but you never really responded
or expressed anything at all.
All I heard from you were things like,
"I'm so hot. I'm so tired."
And that made me feel
a little uncomfortable.
I'm the kind of person
who turns my thoughts
and urges into action.
And that's actually why I chose you
-as my date in Paradise.
-I see.
It's not because I want your answer.
I wanted to talk about all this like this.
So you could feel better?
-Yes. To feel better.
-Right.
-To make myself feel better.
-I see what you mean.
To be honest,
I didn't expect you to choose me today.
-You didn't?
-No.
To be honest,
I thought you wouldn't choose me
because I might have
-Right.
-hurt your ego or your feelings.
But you chose me today,
and it really surprised me.
-And it also impressed me.
-But…
I thought it's so cool.
Others wouldn't have done the same.
That's what I think.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Remember what you said
when we had brunch on our second day?
You said you weren't interested
in the person you chose the day before.
Right.
You said that.
-Can I say this?
-What is it?
Right now,
I'm not interested in the person
who I wrote to yesterday.
I want to know what changed your mind.
Do you want my honest answer?
-Yes.
-To be perfectly honest…
Let me take a sip first.
-It's really…
-Come on. You're making me nervous.
I'm not.
It's just that it's really nothing.
It's really nothing special.
It's normally like that, right?
-I really love pink.
-Okay.
I love pink button-ups,
pink T-shirts, and pink shirts.
I just love pink.
You once said
that you liked my pink shirt.
-I like the color of your shirt.
-This color?
-Yes. I like that color.
-Really?
-Do you like pink?
-Yes, I like pink.
-Really?
-All my things are pink.
I should only wear pink.
I have a button-up too.
-Really?
-Yes.
You said you liked my pink shirt, and I…
Seriously.
It's not a big deal, right?
Even I think it's funny.
I think it's hilarious.
-Okay. I see.
-Even I find it funny.
It's funny even to me
that one comment made me fall for you.
Really? That one comment?
-It was the start.
-That was the start.
Yes. That's it.
So that was the start. I see.
Yes.
Well, you really looked good in pink.
-I did?
-Yes. You looked really good in pink.
-Really?
-Yes.
To be honest,
I've been quite distressed
since the second date.
Why?
What distressed you?
You know, this isn't
a normal situation we would encounter.
We barely have chances
to focus on our emotions,
stuck in a place like this.
-Right.
-It made me very sensitive emotionally.
I became sensitive
to every word others say
and even to very trivial matters.
At some point,
I just wanted to get away from all this.
That's when I realized
that I had become really sensitive here.
-I think that's what happened.
-How are you now?
Now, I'm…
-Are you calmed down now?
-I'm calmed down.
I'm talking a lot about my feelings today.
You make me talk a lot.
-I do?
-Yes.
This is fun.
I can't even remember
how many times I said that today.
I wish this moment
would last forever.
-Really?
-Yes. Really.
-My gosh.
-He wishes the moment would last forever.
-He probably means it.
-Right.
After three attempts,
Se-hoon finally went
to Paradise with Ji-yeon.
Right.
I could feel how he has been feeling
-just by watching him.
-Right. It could've been awkward
and it could've been hard
for Ji-yeon to open up.
I'm glad they got
to open up about their feelings.
Right.
Do you think there's a chance
that she'll change her mind?
I think there is.
-You think?
-Yes.
Se-hoon was…
How can I put it? He was very considerate.
-Yes.
-His repetitive choice
-could've made her feel uncomfortable.
-Right.
But he talked about it so casually,
and he led the conversation so smoothly.
-Right.
-First, he made her feel comfortable
and then opened up about his feelings.
That's probably why
she became comfortable.
He said he chose her for his own sake.
To make himself feel better.
Saying that probably
made her feel comfortable
and made it easier for her to open up.
He led the conversation so smoothly.
PARADISE
OH JIN-TAEK AND KANG SO-YEON
Up for a glass of wine?
Sure.
To our second
date in Paradise.
-Cheers.
-It's good.
-It is, isn't it?
-Do you like whole grain mustard?
-Yes.
-Let me give you some.
-All right.
-How is it? Is it good?
-Yes.
Try it with the sauce.
It's so good.
-Really.
-Yes.
To be honest,
when we were on our first date here,
-I felt really uncomfortable.
-Really?
Yes, it was really uncomfortable.
I felt like there was
a huge concrete wall between us.
-I didn't know.
-I…
I felt like there was
a huge wall between us,
- because--
-Why are you saying that now?
-Why not?
-What?
-When do you think I should've said it?
-You could've said it the day after.
-The day after?
-After we came back from Paradise,
you went to Paradise again.
That's why I couldn't tell you then.
Let me drink this.
Jin-taek must feel really uncomfortable.
-It's like he's getting scolded.
-Right.
When I was in Inferno
and when you were here
with some other woman…
did you think about me?
-Yes.
-What did you think?
I just wondered what you were doing.
Did you feel insecure?
-It did bother me.
-It bothered you?
-So when I heard…
-Yes?
you went to bed early,
I thought, "Good."
Were you happy?
I tell you to go to bed early
when I'm not around.
-It makes me feel comfortable.
-Right.
I see.
At first, I was so grateful
that you showed interest in me
and expressed your feelings for me.
Then we got
to misunderstand each other a bit.
Right.
I feel like you're playing with me.
So was I right?
Or was I wrong?
I must say,
this gives me a lot to think about.
Okay.
I think I got to know you better.
What about me did you get to know?
I'd rather not say.
I see.
I was perfectly honest with you.
Right.
Are you okay with it? It might be too--
I actually liked that you were
-honest with me.
-You liked it?
Yes.
We got to know each other better.
What kind of people we are.
Thank you. It means a lot to me
that you think that way.
PARADISE
CHA HYUN-SEUNG AND SONG JI-A
I'm so happy.
-Thank you.
-Great job, today.
I like it.
I guess we don't need
to talk about those things.
What?
Professions and ages?
Yes. We don't need to ask
-things like that.
-I don't remember how old you are.
-You don't?
-No.
I won't tell you.
You need to be open about it here.
-I'll keep it secret.
-Guess.
Thirty-one?
Is that right?
-Did I guess it correctly?
-Yes.
I'm 31 years old.
And I've been a professional dancer
for over ten years now.
I once performed with SUNMI
at a water festival,
and it created a big buzz.
People on the internet
called me the tanned guy.
Gosh, that's a famous video.
-Oh, really?
I worked with singers
like TVXQ, EXO,
Girls' Generation, and BtoB.
That's about it.
CHA HYUN-SEUNG, 31, DANCER
-Do you not know him?
-No. He didn't mention Super Junior.
If he was our dancer,
I would've gotten in big trouble.
By the way, why did you choose me?
You?
If I wasn't interested,
I wouldn't have chosen you.
Right.
I chose you because I'm interested in you.
I see.
I'm glad I won the game
-and got a chance to choose my date.
-Why?
I knew I would choose you,
Okay.
but I thought you'd choose Hyeon-joong.
To be honest,
I was hesitant to choose you.
I thought, if you like Hyeon-joong,
and he likes you too,
then maybe I shouldn't get involved.
Right.
That's what I thought.
So did you think over it?
-I did think over it.
-I see.
But I thought
that my feelings are more important.
That's why I chose you.
Which is more important?
Love or friendship?
-Me?
-If you have to choose only one.
-Between love and friendship?
-Yes.
To me, love is more important.
-It's the same for me too, because…
-Yes?
If my friends don't understand
that love is more important to me,
they're probably not good friends.
Makes sense.
Again, I feel bad for Hyeon-joong,
but as I said, my feelings come first.
My feelings come first.
So Hyun-seung knows how Hyeon-joong
-is feeling.
-He knows.
Which makes Ji-a's feelings
even more important.
They are very important.
How much alcohol can you take?
-One bottle of soju.
-One bottle?
That's a lot.
I get drunk fast
when I drink with someone I like.
Really?
Are you drunk?
Oh, no.
My gosh, Ji-a.
Men love it when women talk like that.
She's completely in control.
There's something I want to do.
Do you want to use the hot tub?
-Did you bring a swimming suit?
-Yes.
Isn't it too small for us?
You're so big.
-No, I'm not. I'm not that big.
-Yes, you are.
I'll do this.
It's like a spa here.
Right.
-They're going in the small tub together?
-In there?
-Let me get in there first.
-Is it warm?
Let me check.
It's hot.
-Is it? Let me turn on the water a bit.
-It's a little too hot.
-What's this? Is it because of the game?
-Yes.
-It must hurt.
-It doesn't.
-Let me see your back.
-It's fine. There's nothing.
Right. It was really red earlier.
I just got a little scratch here.
-Is it okay now?
-Is that okay?
Yes.
Could we…
Be careful.
-It's hot.
-Nice and warm.
Is it hot? Should we cool it down?
No, this is good.
We're going to get tipsy.
I'd love to.
-You'd love to?
-Yes.
I have to let the air out.
I really wanted to take a bath.
-After just one day?
-What?
-Yes.
-I really needed…
-Do you realize whom you're talking to?
-I wanted to do this.
-It was just one day.
Finally, I'm seeing this.
-This thing?
-Yes.
The tattoo.
-Do you want to get a tattoo?
-Me? No, I'm not getting any.
-Don't.
-What?
-Why?
You're already so pretty right now.
-There's nothing.
-Me?
You're already pretty.
-So don't get one.
-No?
Don't do it.
-Don't?
-You're already so pretty.
Are you going to win the game tomorrow?
Me? I want to win.
I wanted to win the race too.
What if I win tomorrow?
What?
Do you want me to choose you?
Do you think I can win?
Will there be two
or three winners tomorrow too?
I want to win too.
Then win.
-Are you ticklish?
-Yes. Don't tickle me. I'm super ticklish.
-You're so dead.
-What?
-You're so dead too.
All right.
PARADISE
MOON SE-HOON AND SHIN JI-YEON
Gosh, this is nice.
-I like that there are no mosquitoes here.
-I know, right?
I got so many mosquito bites there.
I saw your feet earlier.
-I was really surprised.
-I was surprised too.
I want to make an X on every one of them.
I don't have any cream, so…
If we were outside, I would have…
But I don't have any cream.
An X?
What else can I do? Make an X like this.
One X on each bite.
-I'm serious.
-Stop it.
-That's the only option.
-What's…
I'm serious.
When I saw it, I was like,
"Gosh, she needs a lot."
You're killing me.
We almost finished this.
We do still have some white wine.
About half…
I haven't had this much since coming here.
-Really?
-Really.
Ask the guys if you don't believe me.
I only had one sip…
-I asked them a lot.
-I had only one sip and…
I asked them what you like to eat,
what you ate here, what you like…
I really did. I mean…
I may not be the most
strategic person in the world,
but when I do something,
I prepare myself thoroughly.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
What did you eat with Ji-yeon?
-With Ji-yeon?
-Yes.
With Ji-yeon…
Right. She loves Korean food.
Okay.
Her favorite dish was Korean food.
I think we ordered bulgogi.
And as for pasta,
she only likes tomato sauce only.
And as for steak,
she likes it well done.
She doesn't like medium or rare.
I didn't know they talked about that.
Jin-taek is like Cha Tae-hyun.
-My Sassy Girl.
Seriously, when we talked
about it in the lodging,
I heard that song
from the movie, My Sassy Girl.
-See?
-My gosh!
He was right.
-You mean, "I Believe"?
-Yes. That one.
I could hear that song.
"Let me tell you about her."
"Let me tell you about my Ji-yeon."
"She loves iced Americano."
"Her favorite food is Korean food."
I could hear the background music.
If I were Jin-taek,
I would've been like, "Gosh, Se-hoon."
I think I just heard
-Jin-taek's voice
-"Gosh, Se-hoon."
"You're really breaking my heart."
I won't have any regrets now.
-None?
-No.
I think I should swim now.
Okay. Go ahead.
This is what you call happiness.
As long as there's water,
I can play like this all day.
You're like a seal.
-What?
-A seal.
This is nice.
A remote toast.
A remote toast?
Cheers.
Gosh, this is amazing.
Se-hoon is having the time of his life.
This feels different from
when Ji-yeon came here with Jin-taek.
When she was here with him,
she seemed to just follow his lead.
But with Se-hoon,
they're more like friends.
They keep squabbling.
-She seems to be enjoying it.
-Right.
Jin-taek already became Cha Tae-hyun.
-He told him everything she likes.
-Right.
-I think things might work out
-I know.
-between Se-hoon and her.
-Right.
And seeing someone
-so purely happy like that
-Right.
makes you happy too.
Right.
PARADISE
OH JIN-TAEK AND KANG SO-YEON
-Are we going to the spa now?
-Yes.
Gosh, this really relieves
all the stress I've gotten here.
My hard work paid off.
You did a great job.
I was worried you might hurt yourself.
Is your back all right?
-Yes.
-You did a great job.
You could've hurt yourself.
I thought about you during the game.
Thank you.
I had no idea
I'd get to do things like this here.
Before you had to choose today,
were you torn between me and someone else?
No.
Did it sound like I was scolding you?
-Are you afraid I might scold you?
-I wasn't torn.
You weren't torn at all?
No.
Gosh, I'm so happy right now.
-So-yeon, let's go to bed.
-Okay.
I'll turn the light off.
-Good night.
When do you want to wake up?
Seven.
-Seven?
-Yes.
-Good night.
-Do you think we won't sleep
-if we sleep on the same bed?
-What?
Do you think we won't sleep
if we sleep on the same bed?
Gosh. That's a bold move.
-Good night.
-Do you think we won't sleep
-if we sleep on the same bed?
-What?
Do you think we won't sleep
if we sleep onn the same bed?
Should I sleep here?
What if you get
so nervous you can't sleep?
-I can sleep here.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Then sleep here.
Okay.
-I'll sleep here.
-Okay.
I'm going to sleep here, okay?
What?
-I'm going to sleep now.
-Okay.
Night.
For real?
Of course.
Is this for real?
This is a show for adults.
Oh, my goodness.
You said watching the ocean
in the morning made you happy.
Yes.
Seeing you in the morning makes me happy.
Why do you like me?
-Why?
-Yes.
You make me want to take the initiative.
When you're with me?
Yes.
You make me
a different person.
I have a question.
Did you turn the cameras off?
Or did you keep them on?
-We kept them on.
-You kept them on. I see.
Do you know why I laughed earlier?
When So-yeon said
he could sleep next to her,
he must've been really surprised,
-though we couldn't see his face.
-Right.
When she said,
"You might not be able to sleep here",
he said, "I can."
Then he kept asking her.
"I'm going to sleep here. Okay?"
"I'm going to sleep here."
He kept saying that.
I found it so funny.
But seriously,
So-yeon really impressed me.
Right. So-yeon became much more proactive.
-She's changed.
Yes.
She was confused,
but then made up her mind.
-"All right. Jin-taek likes me."
-"I should go with him."
-"I'll give him all my heart too."
-Right.
I guess this is what happened.
But really,
when you sleep with someone
in the same bed, under the same blanket,
even if you don't like that person,
you can develop feelings for them.
Right.
I don't know. Why are you asking me?
-Well…
-I thought you might have…
I've never done that before.
You've never?
Why would I be with someone
I don't like in the same bed?
I guess you're right.
-Wouldn't it be weird?
-You're right.
-So we all haven't done it.
-But I think I know the feeling.
If she said that
to become closer with him,
-it definitely worked.
-Right.
-It was a huge success.
-Really.
-What time did you go to bed?
-I fell asleep right away.
I didn't sleep.
-Why not?
-I couldn't fall asleep.
-Because you were worried?
-My heart hurt.
I'm sure you felt uncomfortable.
There are so many things
I want to say to her.
You must've had a lot of thoughts.
I couldn't sleep at all.
I'm always waiting for Ji-a
here in Inferno,
and Ji-a is always on a date
with some other guy.
I have nothing to do
and no one talks to me here.
I'm always lying here alone.
I feel like Ji-yeon
will start liking Se-hoon there.
You think?
What should I do then?
Then…
Steal him.
It won't be easy. They say
once a man knows what he wants,
-he doesn't change his mind easily.
-We never know
-until we hear what happened there.
-We never know.
Right.
I thought about it a lot.
That's why I couldn't sleep.
I know what I want to say now.
Gosh, I had no idea…
I'd get so emotional here.
We're home.
-"Home"?
-We're home.
We're back.
We're home.
We had fun.
-Yes. I had a great time.
-Me too.
I wanted to stay there longer.
Time really flew by yesterday, right?
Time just flew by.
It would've been nice
to stay there a bit longer.
Now, we are…
We're back here.
Hi, guys.
-Hey, you're back. Welcome.
-Who's this?
-Se-hoon!
-Hello.
Look who's here.
You look so much better now.
How was it?
What? It was nice.
-Good.
You look so much better.
How was it? I'm sure you had a good time.
We went to a spa. Because it was
-our second date there.
-Did you go to a villa with a pool?
You went there twice. I envy you.
You know, we were the first couple
-to go there twice.
-I know.
So it was more fun.
It was our second date,
so we felt more comfortable.
-I wish I could watch you there.
-And…
-Me too.
-I really do.
We went to the spa
and got massages together.
-That sounds amazing.
-Gosh. You did it
-on your second date.
-It was.
We fell asleep
hearing each other breathing.
-Really?
-In the same bed.
So-yeon didn't seem to mind at all.
She was cool about it.
So we slept in the same bed.
We both woke up at around 6 a.m.
and had a serious conversation on the bed.
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
I fell asleep right away.
Me too.
We had so much fun yesterday.
You kept saying I should drink it up.
I've never chugged
a glass of wine like that.
Remember I said I've only
dated men who approached me first?
So I wanted
to try approaching someone first.
But I have never done it before,
so I had no idea what I should do.
I want you to approach me.
What's so funny?
Do you like this better?
I do.
I see.
We had a serious conversation
at six in the morning.
That sounds great.
What about you, Ji-a? Did you have fun?
Hyeon-joong was all teary last night.
Seriously. I had to walk on eggshells.
Why?
He said you're always away
-while he's always here.
-Right.
She's leaving.
She's always leaving.
I talked behind your back
a lot yesterday, Hyun-seung.
-On my way there, I felt bad for you.
-Well…
-How was talking with her?
-We talked so much.
You were the star
of the evening yesterday.
-You were the star.
-Right.
Did you get to say
everything you wanted to say?
-I said everything.
-That's great.
-Everything I wanted to say.
-Do you feel better?
-So much better.
-I'm happy for you.
-That's nice.
-It felt great to get it off my chest.
I thought Ji-yeon would be flustered
by all the things I said.
But she wasn't. She just accepted it.
And she talked about her feelings.
And now, I'll just go with the flow.
Hey! How did it go? I can't wait to hear
about what happened between you two.
-Well…
-Yes?
After some drinks,
we had a serious conversation.
Is that Min-ji?
-Yes, Min-ji is in front of them.
-Oh, no.
It wasn't a misunderstanding,
but we cleared the air.
You did?
I mean, at first, it was awkward,
but it got better as we talked.
Se-hoon told me
about how he's been feeling and all.
That's about it.
Now what? Did it change anything?
He turned out to be pretty nice.
-Right?
-He was really sweet.
-He has a great personality.
-I'm kind of glad we had this chance.
-Really?
-Yes.
So do you think
you know what you want now?
I think so.
That's great.
Gosh. This is…
Looks like Min-ji is interested
in Se-hoon only. Don't you think?
I can tell from the air.
She didn't say a single word there.
-Right.
It could be she was angry inside.
Because Ji-yeon went
to Paradise with the person she likes.
And I thought Hyeon-joong and Ji-a
were a stable couple
like Jin-taek and So-yeon.
I thought they'd just end up
as a couple, but I'm not sure anymore.
-Right?
-A strong rival
-Exactly.
-has appeared.
It's not over until it's over.
Please.
Participants, please put on
your swimming suits
-and come to the beach.
-All of us? No!
Swimming suits again?
Gosh!
This game thing has been
stressing me out since yesterday.
Are the guys supposed
to wear swimming suits too?
INFERNO
I hope we don't have to run today.
I see a lottery box.
Do you think it'll play with our fate?
-I think it will.
-Do you really think so?
Play with our fate?
I'm scared.
It's a lottery box.
-There they come.
-Oh, they're all wearing caps.
Caps?
They're not wearing caps.
I thought they'd be wearing caps.
I guess they're playing with us.
What are we going to do?
I can't even imagine what it could be.
Do we steal each other's caps?
We can't be playing the game too.
I bet we'll play the game in pairs.
What do I do with my earrings?
What should I do?
-What do I do?
-I'm not sure if I can do this.
Why are you jumping?
I'm warming up.
I didn't get to warm up yet.
This is our seventh day
in the hottest inferno
in the world, Single's Inferno.
Today, female participants
will play a game.
Like yesterday, you will play the game,
and only the top three players
will get to go on dates in Paradise
with the partners they choose.
Now, male participants,
please draw a ball
from the box in front of you.
What's that about?
The female participant whose cap is
the same color as the ball you picked
-will be your partner.
-Oh, my gosh!
That sounds exciting.
-Gosh.
-This sounds important.
-It's very important.
-Right.
-This is worse.
-I know.
Male participants, please come out
and draw a ball one by one.
I want to go to Paradise
on my last night here.
Please. Someone sporty.
-I feel like that'll be me.
-This is totally random.
Jun-sik drew a yellow ball.
-That's me.
-Jun-sik, please stand next to Ji-a,
who is wearing a yellow cap.
Please.
Se-hoon picked a red ball.
-Se-hoon, please stand next to Su-min,
-This is amazing.
who is wearing a red cap.
Hyun-seung is a team with So-yeon
-They are a strong team.
-in a blue cap.
We're so doomed.
They're so going to be the winner.
We're going to win.
Si-hun picked a green ball.
Please stand next to Yea-won
-We can do this.
-in a green cap.
-I'm strong.
-Are you sure?
Jin-taek picked a black ball.
Ji-yeon is his partner.
-What?
-Oh, no.
-Now, this is awkward.
-This is not good.
-They're reunited.
-I know.
Hyeon-joong is Min-ji's partner.
Now, we have six teams of two.
I'll explain the game rules now.
Male participants will carry
their partners on their backs.
The first team to steal another team's cap
is the winner.
I'm so nervous.
Su-min.
And Ji-a. Please come out.
Oh, no. Why?
We can do this.
I'm not sure if I can do this.
We can do it.
-Ji-a! You can do it!
-Ji-a must be really light.
She must be really light.
-She's competitive.
-She is?
I mean Su-min.
You can do it!
Let's go.
Pull your head back.
They're coming. Stretch your arm.
-What?
-Stretch your arm.
Stretch your arm.
-It's okay.
-Oh, no.
Oh, no.
Oh, no! Are you okay?
I've never seen Ji-a like that.
Oh, no!
Oh, no! Are you okay?
Now!
-Now! Take it!
-What are you waiting for?
Now! That's right!
The winner is Kim Su-min.
Are you okay? I'm sorry.
I'm okay.
Gosh, that was scary.
Gosh, Su-min.
That was amazing.
-She waited for the right time.
-You should reach out.
-You did a great job.
-You tried really hard.
I really wanted to go to Paradise.
-Well done.
-Do you know who's next?
Now, let's begin the second match.
So-yeon and Yea-won, please come out.
-We're doomed.
-Really?
Who?
Darn it!
We're so doomed.
I'm sorry.
He's sorry.
It's our turn.
I'm sorry, Yea-won.
He's apologizing to me.
He says he's sorry.
-This is like the final round.
-It's crazy.
They're in different weight classes.
I'm scared. I'm seriously scared.
No! Don't go forward!
Don't go forward! Go away!
Go where?
Go!
My gosh. That looks scary.
Go away.
You're so far away.
-Oh, no!
-My gosh!
Gosh, she's good.
She's so far away!
My gosh.
-Kang So-yeon wins.
-So-yeon.
I can't go to Paradise!
-I'm sorry.
-I can't go to Paradise!
Now, the last preliminary round.
Min-ji and Ji-yeon, please come out.
Min-ji's eyes were so…
She said she's competitive.
-She was scowling.
-I wonder what she'll do.
Her eyes seemed so scary.
She doesn't really like Ji-yeon
at the moment.
-Right.
-That's right.
This is exciting.
-Oh, no!
-Oh, my goodness.
What's happening?
-What?
-What's going on here?
-So hectic.
-We won.
Shin Ji-yeon wins.
-Are you okay?
That was a great match.
-Seriously.
-He even kneeled down.
But he managed to hold out.
-He's good.
-My gosh.
Ji-yeon is so good.
Ji-yeon was really good. She's strong.
-She's so strong.
-She's really strong.
Great job.
-What happened though?
-I don't know.
Four times.
I did it four times for you.
-To be honest, I thought Min-ji would win.
-Me too.
-But there was a twist.
-Ji-yeon is so good.
-She is.
-So the three winners can go to Paradise.
-The three girls.
-The winners?
All three of them will go to Paradise.
But just like yesterday,
the winner of the final match
gets to choose her date first.
-So their game partners don't really…
-They don't really matter.
They were just their horses.
Now, let's begin the final match.
The finalists, Su-min,
So-yeon,
and Ji-yeon, please come out.
In the final match, all three teams
will compete at the same time.
The ranking will be decided
in the order of caps lost.
Don't try too hard, okay?
-Hey, Se-hoon. No discussing.
-What?
-No discussing.
-No, that's not what I'm doing.
-Let's get ready.
-Get ready.
-Oh, no. I'm scared.
-Let's go.
Let's go in.
-The blue team.
-For sure.
They're going to win. Look at their form.
I know.
They need to be strategic.
They should beat So-yeon first.
Why are we looking at each other?
So-yeon.
Good.
I'll go behind them.
-Good. This is perfect.
-Let's get closer, Su-min.
Let's get closer.
Now!
Now! Take it!
My gosh. Ji-yeon.
The hat's in the air.
Now! Take it!
What? They both lost their caps.
-Oh, my gosh!
-I lost it.
This is crazy.
Now! Take it!
-Oh, my gosh.
-This is crazy.
-We both lost.
-Right.
What do we do now?
In third place is So-yeon.
In second place is Ji-yeon.
-The final winner is Su-min.
-I'm the winner!
-Congratulations.
-We shouldn't have fought.
I can't believe this.
She won by default.
She didn't do anything, and she won.
My gosh.
Wait. Just like that?
That was so easy.
-That was a piece of cake.
-I know.
Su-min said to Se-hoon…
I wonder who she'll choose.
What do you think?
-I'm guessing Se-hoon.
-Se-hoon?
Yes. Because she said earlier
that she was interested in him.
So I feel like she'll choose Se-hoon.
-Ji-yeon was so good.
-Ji-yeon was really good.
-She was better than I thought.
-I know.
-She was so determined to win.
-Right.
-I could see her passion.
-Right. Me too.
What do you think I should do?
-This is hard.
-Things have become much harder now.
Try to talk
to Se-hoon as much as possible.
Why don't you go talk to him?
I think Se-hoon is the type of man
who likes to take time.
I know. I got the same feeling.
Which is why I don't know what to do.
I think you need to talk to him
to figure it out.
Go talk to him.
If it doesn't work out, I guess that's it.
I lied on the hammock once,
and it was comfortable.
-It is, isn't it?
-Yes.
I want to take a nap like this.
Me too.
-Let's talk.
-You want to talk?
Yes.
I'll go up.
Okay.
This is where I used to sit
and space out every morning.
-Oh, really?
-Yes.
This is where I space out.
-It's so windy.
-It is.
-I don't know what I should say.
-What?
I'm the one who brought you here,
but I don't know what I should say.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
Then I think you should say
everything you want to say.
To be honest, I came to think
I wanted to get to know you
-after our yacht date.
-Me?
Yes. You made me very curious.
But I didn't know back then.
After the voting session yesterday,
and after I heard everything,
I realized what was going on.
-To me,
-Yes?
you seemed like the kind of person
who has to get what he wants
once he falls for something
and who barely gets swayed.
Am I right?
-Me?
-Yes.
-So I was right.
So I want to know what you think.
-What I think?
-Yes.
I'd like to hear what you think
from you, not other people.
You mean you want to know
what I think and how I feel?
Yes.
Where should I begin?
Tell me everything.
Everything you want to tell me.
Okay.
Did you have fun?
It was fun, right?
-I heard you ate a lot.
-I ate a lot.
That's a surprise.
Well, I felt comfortable.
-But you were uncomfortable around me.
-That's a good thing.
It means I'm attracted.
-Were you sad?
-Did you sleep well?
No.
I was tired. I went to bed late.
Around 1:30 or 2 a.m.
I thought I'd be okay,
but it really broke my heart.
I'm serious.
-When my name was called?
-What?
I screamed then.
It turns out I'm taking this seriously.
I missed you too.
I really did. I thought about you.
In bed, before I went to sleep.
So how is it now,
after staying here for a few days?
Well, it's been nice.
-Nice?
-Yes.
-I won the game. Can you believe that?
-Right.
Do you know I've never won?
Right. I've learned so much here.
Now I'm about to leave this island,
I finally have my thoughts sorted out.
I realized, as much as I like giving love,
I like receiving it too.
That's what I learned.
I don't know what you heard
before you came here,
but I felt like
yesterday would be my last chance.
My first and my last
chance to talk to her.
I did also consider choosing you.
I thought it'd be nice
to get to know you better
over a glass of wine.
-But I had only one chance.
-Right.
I asked myself, whether I should use
that chance to get to know something new
or for my own sake.
And I concluded that it'd be right
that I use the chance for myself.
That's what I thought.
Then when I got back…
When I got back…
I found myself smiling.
I found myself beaming with joy.
I'm just…
Do you perhaps want
to get to know me better?
-I'm afraid I won't have enough time.
-Right.
Yes. Really.
Oh, no.
Se-hoon is such an honest person.
Isn't it nice?
-Right.
-He's so honest.
-He is.
-Right.
It's over for me.
Did you talk to him? How did it go?
Sit here. What did he say?
I talked to him, but it didn't go well.
What did he say?
He said he's already…
Made up his mind?
What do I do?
I wonder who will go to Paradise.
Se-hoon is definitely going.
No, we don't know yet.
-You will. I'm sure.
-You never know.
It depends on who the winner chooses.
I have no idea who Su-min will choose.
She talked with Se-hoon a lot.
And he was nice to her
when she first came.
She said it was sweet of him.
Se-hoon must've put
extra effort into grooming today.
-He probably thinks he's going.
-He'd be sure of it.
He probably did his hair.
Concealing his eyebags.
Who knew Se-hoon would see
such happy days?
-Tell me about it.
-I know.
Now, we're going to match the couples
who will go on a date in Paradise.
The winners of the game
who earned tickets to Paradise,
Kim Su-min,
Shin Ji-yeon,
and Kang So-yeon
may now come to the campfire.
KIM SU-MIN
SHIN JI-YEON
KANG SO-YEON
Su-min, you're the winner of the game.
Please choose the person you'd like
to go on a date with in Paradise.
I'd like to go to Paradise with…
-I think she'll choose Si-hun.
-Me too. Si-hun.
I bet it's Se-hoon.
What if she chooses Se-hoon?
She might have changed her mind.
Seriously, I have no idea.
-I think, either Si-hun or Se-hoon.
-Se-hoon.
-Si or Se?
-Si or Se.
Who will she choose?
The person Kim Su-min chose is…
I'd like to go to Paradise with…
Choi Si-hun.
Si-hun, please come outside
and leave for Paradise with Su-min.
Guys, I'm going to Paradise!
-Have fun!
-See you.
-I was right.
Have a good time.
They probably wouldn't want
to stay there in the rain.
-It's hot and humid there.
-In Paradise, they can use the spa.
-And Si-hun was picked by the winner.
-Right.
He may have been hurt by Ji-a,
but he'll be able to heal there.
Thank you so much.
Where's the way out?
-This way?
-Follow me.
I know the way.
-Su-min.
-Yes?
Thank you.
-Su-min.
-Yes?
Let's have fun there.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Next is the runner-up, Ji-yeon.
My gosh.
I wonder who she'll choose.
I'm so curious.
Who do you think she'll pick?
-Se-hoon.
-Se-hoon, of course.
Se-hoon.
Gosh, I'm nervous.
I had no idea who Ji-yeon would choose.
MOON SE-HOON
-But…
-She might choose Jin-taek again.
-I feel like she'll choose Jin-taek.
-No.
-Jin-taek…
-Jin-taek?
-I think she'll choose Jin-taek.
-I think so too.
I have no idea.
She must be torn even at this moment.
She might choose Jin-taek again.
We never know.
When he went to Paradise with Ji-yeon,
I was deeply shaken.
I don't want to be hurt again.
I'm not sure how it'll go.
Depending on Ji-yeon's choice,
-So-yeon might have to change her mind.
-Right.
I'd like to go to Paradise with…
The person Shin Ji-yeon chose is…
Is it really Jin-taek?
I'm so nervous right now.
I'd like to go to Paradise
with Moon Se-hoon.
Subtitle translation by: Sun-young Baek