LEE SI-AN
CHUNG YOU-JIN
KIM MIN-SEOL
BAE JI-YEON
KIM HYE-JIN
KIM A-RIN
PARK HAE-LIN
KIM TE-HWAN
KOOK DONG-HO
JANG THEO
KIM JEONG-SU
YUK JUN-SEO
AN JONG-HOON
SINGLE'S INFERNO
How's your second day in Paradise been?
-Second day in Paradise?
-Yeah.
You sleeping?
"You sleeping?"
That's ridiculous.
Really?
No way.
Are you sleeping?
No.
What a relief.
Thank goodness.
So, how has your second day
in Paradise been?
My second day in Paradise?
How did we end up
in Paradise for two days?
Gosh.
How did we make it back here?
Because you won and came in first place.
That's right.
-Do you feel like it was worth it though?
-What?
What do you think?
It's pretty disappointing.
-Disappointing?
-Yeah, we couldn't talk much today.
I know, right?
I felt today was a really important day.
Right?
I'm not sure.
I don't know
how you feel now…
to be honest.
We barely even talked.
I'm wondering
if you're not curious about me anymore.
That thought crossed my mind.
Maybe it's because you're just tired.
That's what I've been…
trying to think of it as.
Still,
I think I did try hard.
Right.
But from your perspective,
I looked too tired…
-Yeah.
-So it bothered you?
-Is that right?
-Yeah.
Your vibe wasn't the same
as it was yesterday.
Right.
I'm not the type
who expresses things verbally.
Expressing myself with words
isn't my thing.
Is this how tough guys
show their feelings?
I don't really get it.
I can't get used to
the pace of this place.
How can you make
such big decisions in a day or two?
No, I'm not asking you to decide.
I just wanted to know
how you feel right now.
I feel good right now.
Then, you can treat me more kindly!
But this is just how I am.
What am I supposed to do?
I'll try my best though.
You can be more gentle.
Be gentle with me.
Have I ever been gentle with you?
Yeah, you were yesterday.
-I was yesterday?
-Yeah.
Okay.
I'll try my best.
Not a high five!
No, not a high five.
-That's not the time for it!
-Give her a hug instead.
Why are you on Si-an's side now?
Why is he doing that?
He's doing this!
Kyuhyun's been very patient with him.
He's channeling Si-an right now.
Does a high five make sense right now?
"All right, let's go!"
That's ridiculous.
Not a high five!
You're so annoying.
I don't think an ideal relationship
is something you can will into existence.
That's what I think.
Especially, a romantic one.
I see.
But being in a relationship
is about finding common ground.
That's true.
We came from different backgrounds.
-Both you and I.
-Right.
-Right?
-Yeah.
I'm just saying
let's try a little harder.
If it's possible, of course.
-You and I have some similarities.
-Yeah.
We're probably different in many ways too.
I'll try my best too.
I'll work on being a bit gentler.
Cover up.
Should we go to bed?
Yeah.
Let's do that.
I really liked that conversation.
I understand them both.
Even though it was frustrating at times
and there were moments I didn't like,
the conversation they just had
was so beautiful.
-It was ideal.
-It felt comfortable and natural.
-It was nice.
-Yes.
As Si-an said,
a relationship is about putting in effort
to adjust to each other.
That's what you have to do.
But wanting to fix someone
or wanting someone to change
isn't what you should think about.
You can't shape someone
into the person you want them to be.
People don't really change
or drastically become different.
-That's what I think.
-Right.
That's hard.
It's not the first time she's said this.
-Right.
-She's said the same thing.
-She keeps repeating it.
-Yeah.
But I think it's like this.
Even though they know
they're not that compatible,
they're still drawn to each other.
-Yeah.
-Right.
A funny thing Jun-seo said was,
"Have I ever been gentle with you?"
That was…
They're not clicking.
I couldn't believe
he could say that to her.
-"I'm not the gentle type."
-That's not easy to say.
He's the type
to follow that with a high five.
But honestly,
it wouldn't suit Jun-seo
if he tried to act sweet like Jeong-su.
Si-an's asking for too much
to expect that.
She knows he's not that kind of person.
And she fell for who he was.
In such cases,
one person wants their partner to change.
-And the other says…
-Right.
"This is who I am."
They say, "You used to be like this."
They're always stuck in the past
-and bringing things up from then.
-Right.
But Jun-seo thinks, "I didn't change.
I've always been like this. Did I change?"
It's the start of their relationship,
so they set expectations for those things.
That's right.
They're in the same room.
-They're in there together now.
-The silence.
It's Min-seol.
Is she here to vent her frustrations?
Min-seol?
Hey.
I came to hang out.
Have you decided on anything?
Me?
I…
Yeah?
I'm going to push ahead.
To Jun-seo?
Nice. That's so cool.
But…
He went to Paradise with Si-an
to confirm his feelings for on her, right?
The best way to know
is to ask him when he returns.
I'm going to ask when he comes back,
but I'm worried about doing that.
I'm not sure how to bring it up.
I really struggle with people like him.
But honestly, Jun-seo needs to
let me know now, right?
Of course.
We had something
going on between us too.
He needs to clarify things,
so I can sort my feelings out.
Do I have to keep suffering like this?
I recommend asking him
and bringing it up first.
Ask him what?
Should I ask, "Want to drink
Johnnie Walker together?"
"Let's drink some Johnnie Walker…"
Which is better,
"Do you want to" or "Let's go"?
I'll say,
"Let's go drink some Johnnie Walker."
That sounds cuter.
Let's practice.
-Practice what?
-Someone pretend to be Jun-seo.
-Practice?
-Okay.
I'll start.
Go ahead.
Jun-seo, we need to talk.
-Sure.
-Let's talk.
Okay.
We walk.
-We walk and sit down.
-We sit down.
She's unbelievable.
Why?
-Go on. It's fun.
-We sit down.
-How was Paradise?
-Well…
Did you have fun?
-Yeah, we talked about this and that.
-This is hilarious.
Then, did you drink Johnnie Walker?
Let's pretend that he didn't.
-My goodness.
-She's adorable.
He didn't have any, okay?
You asked me
if I wanted to go to Paradise.
Yeah, mention that
and say he gave you the wrong idea.
"I have absolutely no idea."
"I'm just so confused."
That's what I'll say.
You're so hilarious.
-It's insane.
-"Seriously."
"I couldn't sleep at all, Jun-seo."
"Why did you even ask me
if I wanted to go?"
"Why did you look at me
like you were going to pick me?"
-I'll do that.
-Say you were upset.
-Like, "I was upset!"
-"I was upset!"
Yeah. Like, "I thought it would be me!"
"My roommates thought I was going."
"We even said our goodbyes."
-Nice!
-I should say that.
-It's good.
-Is that good?
I love it.
-You think it's okay?
-That's my style.
You're so adorable.
Thanks to Min-seol,
the vibe on Single's Inferno
-is so much brighter.
-Right.
I appreciate it so much.
-It's refreshing.
-Yeah, it's so nice.
Her energy is so positive.
Goodbye.
I got a dopamine rush. It's crazy.
Are you sleepy?
Lean on me.
Wow, we're above the clouds.
Jeong-su.
-Why do they keep sitting like that?
-Right?
If I were Jun-seo,
I would've switched seats.
Take a nap.
Time to sleep.
In the helicopter,
I saw her head on Jun-seo's shoulder.
So…
Since I tend to be a bit conservative,
I had a hard time accepting that
and found myself thinking a lot.
So he's the conservative type.
If he has a hard time accepting that,
did he expect her
to lean on his shoulder then?
Conservative or not,
if a woman I'm interested in
leans on another guy's shoulder…
-Of course, I'd be bothered.
-You'd be bothered.
-It's annoying.
-Yeah, he might start to think,
"She has more interest
in Jun-seo than me."
-For sure.
-Yeah.
I actually see Jeong-su's reaction
as a positive sign,
because being jealous like that means
he has genuine feelings for her.
But even though Jeong-su has
genuine feelings for Si-an,
has he given her
a definite, clear response of how he feels
and expressed them to her?
He hasn't.
But he's sure of his feelings now.
Si-an doesn't know that now though.
-She doesn't know.
-Yeah.
-Right.
-Things just haven't worked out.
This turned out great.
-Yeah, it's great.
-Yeah.
I think this turned out well too.
This one's cute.
-Theo…
-He looks so thin.
-He's become so gaunt.
-He looks haggard.
I'm not surprised.
Is that Si-an next to you?
-I definitely took this photo.
-Yeah.
You took it well.
-The flower ring I gave her.
-Where?
You two look like a couple.
That one looks so cool.
You miss her.
What?
You miss Si-an, don't you?
Be quiet.
-What is it?
-Give me the photo. I'll put it up.
He misses Si-an so much
that he was staring at it longingly,
as if he'd cry.
-It was a yawn.
-Give us one.
I thought I'd ask.
I just yawned.
Si-an went to Paradise, so…
But who knows if going to Paradise
will make feelings grow deeper or not?
Or will things stay the same?
It's uncertain.
I tried to make myself
not become impatient.
Where is everyone?
We're back.
-Wait, no.
-We're finally back.
-I said I wouldn't greet them like that.
-Right.
I need to behave properly
to match my outfit today.
Elegant and graceful.
You've already failed at that.
-Thanks for carrying my bag.
-Sure.
-No problem.
-Bye.
Want me to get the door for you?
Si-an's got it.
How was it? I'm so curious.
-Us?
-Yeah.
It was super fun,
and I had a really good time.
-We had become close on Inferno.
-Right.
-She's listening.
-Yeah.
Yeah.
Going to Paradise after becoming close
made it more comfortable and fun.
-It felt much different and relaxed.
-I bet.
-He's funny.
-You must get along really well.
Yeah, more than I expected.
We were both
goofing around with each other.
I see.
After seeing him on Inferno,
I didn't expect he'd be like that.
It was kind of like that.
We were out of water then.
Time to go see Hye-jin.
Here she comes.
-It's her!
-Hye-jin?
-Hi.
-She's here.
Here she comes.
-Why are you back so early?
-Right?
What did you do yesterday?
Yesterday? We ate ramyeon
and had a party among ourselves.
Yeah, and we all talked with each other.
That must've been nice.
Theo was something else yesterday.
He was something else.
-Why?
-It was just the way he was talking.
I see.
Theo…
Theo.
No.
No?
Did you have fun?
-Did you have fun?
-It was just…
It was fun, but…
I don't know.
I guess he was just tired.
I don't know. Overall, it was just…
I guess I had my hopes up a bit
since we had a nice time the day before.
Since it was back-to-back?
Yeah, since we went back-to-back,
I think I was expecting more.
-I guess more of an emotional connection?
-Communication.
I think I wanted us to be more expressive.
Jun-seo isn't exactly
the warm and affectionate type.
-You know?
-That's right.
-He's a "tough guy."
-Yeah.
He's like a beast.
-"A beast."
-Yeah.
He's always saying, "Hey."
Right. Like, "Hey, you did that?"
Yeah, "Hey, you did that?"
So it wasn't just to me.
-I was hurt over that.
-Yeah, me too.
So I kept reminding him
to call me by my name.
-Right.
-He kept calling me, "Hey."
-That's how he calls you?
-He's always like…
-"Hey, what did you do?"
-Like, "Hey." Right.
-It was just…
-I see.
-It was…
-I asked him too.
"Are you usually like this,
or are you too comfortable with me?"
I asked him in Paradise.
He does tell me he likes things.
-Yeah.
-But…
I'm not sure if he means it.
-Jun-seo?
-He says he likes things.
-Right.
-Yeah.
"Yeah, I liked it. It was nice."
But that's pretty much it.
It's the same with me.
He's like that with me too.
That's all he says to me.
"It was nice," and that's it.
Oh my god, that's not good.
I don't know. So it's a little…
He definitely said he liked me,
but it doesn't feel genuine.
He said he liked you?
I get what you mean.
-Why? How come it doesn't feel genuine?
-What?
Why does it not feel genuine?
I don't know.
Maybe he was just tired yesterday,
or maybe I was expecting too much.
Or maybe Jun-seo and I
have different approaches to things.
So I told him.
I told him what I didn't like
and asked him to be
a bit warmer and kinder.
-He said he'd try to adapt.
-Right.
-And he said he'd work on it.
You even talked about that kind of stuff?
Then, he's totally into Si-an.
I didn't know you talked
about that kind of stuff.
But… I almost forgot.
We were eating.
-We were eating together.
-Okay.
And we were talking about things,
and he said something like,
"Min-seol's been weighing on my mind."
Or something like, "She is on my mind."
-Anyway…
-Really?
Min-seol's name came up,
and I was so flustered.
My goodness, Kim Min-seol.
She started grinning.
How can she be so obvious?
Nothing that happened before matters.
Min-seol's name came up,
and I was so flustered.
I was like, "Jeez."
I thought Jun-seo only saw me
as like a close little sister,
but to hear he was still thinking of me
even in Paradise…
I feel bad for Si-an,
but that made me happy.
I had a hard time trying not to smile.
But I have something to share too.
He came up to me and asked
if I wanted to go to Paradise.
-Really?
-Yeah.
He asked me if I wanted to go.
He told me he likes drinking whiskey,
and he said he likes Johnnie Walker.
I said, "Let's have some the next time
we go to Paradise together."
Yesterday, I heard he drank whiskey.
So I asked him about it.
And he said,
"I haven't had Johnnie Walker yet."
-That's what he said. That's why…
-What on earth?
So I was expecting
to go to Paradise yesterday.
I got my hopes up.
We even said our goodbyes.
-Right.
-Yeah.
-But he suddenly picked Si-an…
-I thought he'd pick Min-seol.
I was so shocked.
So I was thinking
if I got a chance to talk to him,
I really want to ask why he approached me.
But…
On our first trip to Paradise,
I was feeling so much pressure and stress,
and I had a lot on my mind.
But something Jun-seo said then
really stuck with me.
"You don't have to pick me.
I'm choosing you."
-He said that?
-Really?
He told me that.
-The day before yesterday?
-Yeah.
-During your first Paradise date?
-Yeah, during our first Paradise date.
But then,
when we were eating the next day,
he said you were on his mind.
Why bring that up?
It felt like
he couldn't focus on the date.
-But why…
-It could've been because he was tired.
I'm saying why would he tell you that?
Why would he tell you
that I was on his mind?
Anyway, he looked unhappy the whole time.
-You know that awkward feeling, right?
-Yeah.
We finish eating,
and he says, "Let's go,"
and immediately gets up.
-And we hadn't talked much.
-What?
What on earth?
Seriously.
Exactly.
This confusion I'm feeling
isn't wrong, right?
I'm not going crazy, am I?
How interesting.
Yeah, it really is.
Interesting.
I think this could be something
that causes Si-an to waver again.
-This conversation in their room.
-Of course.
Because the person who she thought
was completely focused on her
seems to have said
-similar things to Min-seol.
-Exactly.
-And she could start overthinking again.
-Yeah.
I don't think Min-seol
was trying to stir things up.
There were things on her mind
she was genuinely curious about
and just let them all out.
-Yes.
-Right?
I mean, she hadn't said much
until Si-an said
Jun-seo was thinking about her.
Then, it poured out of her.
-Right.
-That's when she mentioned Johnnie Walker.
-She's not lying.
-Yes, it is true.
But from Si-an's perspective,
she could totally get the wrong idea.
Jun-seo is just…
That scared me.
Today, the women will play a game
to win a date in Paradise.
Come on, no way.
Unbelievable.
Please gather at the pool.
Why is it the pool again?
Incredible.
-I'm suddenly feeling stressed out.
-I'm getting stressed again.
Please.
They have to make them fall in.
You're right.
I guess you push each other in.
Here they come.
This is too brutal.
I'm scared.
Please, I'm begging you.
-I'm scared. Is it this?
-I really want to go.
-Pushing people off?
-It's possible.
This is the most nervous I've ever been.
Me too.
Today, the women will be competing
in a game for a date in Paradise.
Only the top three winners in order
of their ranking can each pick a man,
to take on a date to Paradise.
Today's game is called…
"Push Off the Buoy."
Is that the buoy?
We need to push that?
-So we get on top…
-We stand on it.
We push from on top of it?
The women will stand
on top of the buoy and wait.
When the whistle blows, they will try
to push each other off the buoy.
The risky thing about this game is
you'll see some awesome moments
but also embarrassing ones too.
The girls are going to compete
so fiercely this time.
Hae-lin, A-rin, and Min-seol
will try really hard.
-You're right.
-It's going to be vicious.
-My gosh.
-What do we do?
The three winners of the preliminaries
will advance to the finals.
Please let me make it to the finals.
The matchups will be decided
by drawing balls.
If three people pick the same color,
they will have a three-way match
in the preliminaries.
-A three-way match…
-That'll be the hardest.
-The matchups will be crucial.
-That's right.
I just want to avoid Si-an.
Kim A-rin will draw the first ball.
Please not the three-way match.
-Green.
-Kim A-rin, green.
What is it?
Chung You-jin, red.
Please pick a selected color.
Lee Si-an, green.
It might be a three-way match.
What?
Kim Hye-jin, green.
It's a three-way match!
-My gosh!
GREEN BALL
A-RIN, SI-AN, HYE-JIN
Wow, that's insane.
Take it easy on me, will you?
It's not going to be easy.
We have a three-way match already.
Yeah, that's right.
Park Hae-lin, yellow.
Kim Min-seol, yellow.
-Hae-lin, I want to go to Paradise.
-I want to go.
-Me too.
-Gosh, fate is cruel.
I want to go too.
Bae Ji-yeon, red.
RED BALL - YOU-JIN VS JI-YEON
I'm so scared!
-Let's not be left behind today.
-Yeah, let's not.
-Please, let's leave.
-Yeah, us three should stop.
But we have no choice. One has to stay.
But I'm going against Si-an.
First, those who picked the red ball,
Chung You-jin and Bae Ji-yeon.
Please climb onto the buoy.
-Good luck.
-Let's go!
-Good luck!
-You can do it.
Gosh, it's freezing!
It must be cold.
It's so slippery.
Ji-yeon, I'm scared.
Are you good at sports?
Are you? I think you are.
But I've never tried
anything like this before.
I don't know who'll win.
Doesn't Ji-yeon work out a lot?
-They both seem athletic.
-Really?
You-jin has strong legs,
so she might maintain good balance.
Yeah.
Jeez, your stance looks so stable.
Why are you so stable?
I'm so scared.
She's only saying that.
What if she suddenly changes?
Get ready.
Good luck.
My gosh.
"I'm scared"!
"I'm so scared"!
Ji-yeon!
Wow, a chokehold?
That's a chokehold.
Wow, Ji-yeon!
Ji-yeon!
This is scary.
It's so fun!
No!
-Ji-yeon!
She's not pulling her hair, right?
Wow, Ji-yeon!
Ji-yeon!
Tickle, tickle.
Brownie points for cuteness.
Tickle, tickle!
No!
It's not working.
My goodness!
No!
Wait!
Bae Ji-yeon is eliminated.
The winner is Chung You-jin.
-Great job.
-They're fiercer than us.
I'm sorry.
She used her head.
Wow, this is intense.
This game is so fun.
-Ji-yeon won in cuteness.
-I agree.
"Tickle, tickle" was so charming.
Good job.
Those who picked the yellow ball,
Park Hae-lin and Kim Min-seol.
-Let's go!
-Please climb onto the buoy.
You can do it.
Two people who are eager to go
are up again.
Jeez, this game.
Both Min-seol and Hae-lin are desperate.
-Right.
-Exactly.
-They need to win.
-Yeah. Gosh.
-These two like different guys too.
-Yes.
Why is it us?
I know, right?
I haven't been to Paradise in days.
I have no idea
what's happening on the outside.
I need to win today
and go to Paradise with Jun-seo.
I have no choice but to settle things.
First off, I'm pretty strong.
And I'm tall, so I thought
I'd have an edge in this game.
My heart's racing.
Get ready.
She's strong.
-She's in position.
-What? It's already over?
She's just going to push like that?
Lower your stance!
Get low!
Hae-lin is no joke!
-No, Min-seol!
-Grab her leg, Min-seol.
Grab her leg. Go low.
Nice!
-She's turned the tables!
-Really?
She follows instructions well.
-Nice!
-You can do it!
-A bit more!
It's anyone's game.
-Push!
-Come on!
-Push her!
-Push!
-Come on!
-I'm out of strength.
-Oh no.
She's exhausted.
She's up.
She lifted her…
No!
-Oh no!
Leg splits!
-I won't go in.
-No!
No, I'm not going in!
I'm not going in!
-A chokehold!
-She's hanging in there!
My gosh!
No, I'm not going in!
I'm not going in!
No!
Min-seol!
"I'm not going in!" My goodness!
Yeah, don't go in.
No!
Min-seol!
Kim Min-seol is eliminated.
The winner is Park Hae-lin.
-She's so strong.
-Right?
I'm so tired.
Our poor youngest cast member.
That was intense.
Gosh, she tried so hard.
-Good job.
-You did great.
You were so good, Hae-lin.
She looks really disappointed.
-I'm curious about the three-way match.
-Me too.
All three of us
have different people in mind, so…
-I'm so nervous.
-I'm more nervous.
It's all your fault!
I'm so nervous.
Seriously.
Those who picked the green ball,
Kim A-rin, Lee Si-an, and Kim Hye-jin.
Please climb onto the buoy.
A three-way match
isn't going to be easy.
-They'll target Si-an first.
-I agree
-The other two will.
-Most likely.
It's because she seems strong.
-Right.
-She has a good physique too.
That's true.
I can do this.
Let's go, Lee Si-an!
Lucky you.
Let's go.
-You can do it.
-Let's go, Hye-jin!
Please start when the whistle blows.
Get ready.
Wow, what on earth?
What?
Oh my goodness!
Both of them?
-Wow, what on earth?
-What?
My goodness!
This is no joke.
Kim A-rin is eliminated.
-See? It's game over.
-Right.
She had no chance.
No, I don't want to.
-Hold on.
-Okay.
-Okay. Get up.
-Wait!
Please have mercy on me.
What if she pushes after begging?
-Go easy on me, will you?
-Okay.
Okay?
She's so scary.
She is folded up like a piece of paper.
No!
-Hye-jin, get back up!
-Hang in there!
My gosh, look at them.
-Gosh, they're kicking.
-What is happening?
Hye-jin is doing great.
Watching them wears me out.
Hang in there!
Wait, hold on.
Hold on. I'm so exhausted.
You look like slave hunters.
Hold on.
You need to sit.
No!
-No!
-Oh no!
-My gosh!
She slipped! No!
-What?
-She hung on?
She's like a roly-poly toy!
-She didn't fall!
-She survived?
She survived.
You just have to push!
A little more!
-There you go!
-Push!
Hey, girl.
They're amazing! Seriously.
That's incredible.
They must be exhausted.
Just fall in already.
I'm so exhausted.
-Let's go! Give it your all!
-It's so tiring.
-You can do it!
-I thought I was going to die.
-Hang in there!
-Let's go!
Use your last bit of strength!
She might get pushed out.
-Hold on.
-She's holding on again.
Drop her in!
No!
-Lift!
-She's lifting her?
Is that possible?
Drop her in!
No!
Hang in there.
Kim Hye-jin is eliminated.
The winner is Lee Si-an.
No.
-Si-an must be really strong.
-She is.
-That was no joke.
-What an epic match.
It was an epic match.
You did great.
Seriously. Goodness.
You're too strong.
The final round will be a three-way match.
Chung You-jin,
Park Hae-lin, and Lee Si-an.
Please come out and get ready.
Let's go.
They must be exhausted, right?
I can't bear to watch.
My arms are dead.
Dong-ho, go and have fun.
I'll be here, so have fun.
Hae-lin is good.
You definitely need
long arms and legs to use
-strength in a wide range of motion.
-Right.
But Si-an just finished that last game.
-She might be tired.
-Right.
That's why I said target her first
as a team and then fight.
Because they both want to go with Dong-ho.
Please start when the whistle blows.
Get ready.
What on earth?
I said to team up,
but they went for each other.
It must be because of Dong-ho.
A battle for Dong-ho.
What on earth?
I just needed You-jin to fall in.
As soon as it started,
Hae-lin came right at me.
It became a fight for Dong-ho.
Damn it. No.
What are you doing, Hae-lin?
Then, let me.
"Then, let me."
"I'm scared."
Then, let me.
Hae-lin is so good.
-She knows how to play.
-She's the dark horse.
My gosh, no!
No! Don't get pushed!
-What on earth?
-My gosh!
-They teamed up?
-They're pushing her.
My gosh, no!
No! Don't get pushed!
-Oh no!
-Her body is twisted.
No! Don't get pushed!
Chung You-jin is eliminated.
I took a hit to the gut,
and I wanted to hold on,
but it knocked the wind out of me.
Then Si-an came over, and I fell in.
Hae-lin is so strong.
She flipped her.
It's basically game over.
This is scary.
My goodness.
I have to hand it to Si-an.
-Seriously.
-At the end…
This is scary.
My goodness.
Park Hae-lin is eliminated.
The winner is Lee Si-an.
She's one scary woman.
I'm suddenly scared of her now.
She's a warrior.
That was strategic.
How adorable.
The women's game
to win a date in Paradise.
Here are the final rankings.
First place is Lee Si-an.
Second place is Park Hae-lin.
Third place is Chung You-jin.
The top three women from this game
will each choose a man
in the afternoon to go to Paradise with.
Si-an is incredible.
That was the most intense
women's game we've seen.
-It was amazing.
-Yes.
-She won that three-way match too.
-Yeah.
That was pretty fun.
I really enjoyed watching that.
That was like watching
a men's mud pit wrestling match.
It was intense.
I guess Si-an is made for Paradise.
-It's her destiny to stay there.
-She's destined to go.
It is?
Isn't she the only one who's gone
to Paradise every single day?
She gets chosen a lot,
wins games, and is strong.
There's no beating her.
-You can't.
-She's overpowered.
But I was curious as to why
Si-an was trying so hard.
As the first-place winner,
she chooses someone to go with.
Did she want that right to choose?
I think it had nothing to do with that,
and it was just competitiveness.
You think so?
No, I think she definitely has
someone she wants to go with.
There's only a few days left now.
She needs to confirm her feelings
for the person she wants.
-In my humble opinion, I think…
-Jeong-su?
Ultimately,
-Si-an will end up with Jeong-su.
-Yeah.
In any case, the reason why
she put in so much effort to win…
-We'll find out soon.
-Yes.
-There was also the fight for Dong-ho.
-Right.
We saw two women
fighting each other for Dong-ho.
Hae-lin did say the night before
that she was determined
to go with Dong-ho.
-She looked the most desperate.
-Exactly.
The look in her eyes and her attitude
showed her determination to take Dong-ho.
-Right.
-Yeah.
Min-seol seemed desperate too.
-Right.
-"I don't want to fall in!"
-No one did it half-heartedly.
-Right.
Si-an's preliminary match
was like a finals match.
-Right.
-Exactly.
-I became sad and quiet after I saw that.
-Yeah.
I couldn't bear to watch either.
It was scary.
I didn't expect Hae-lin to do that well.
But she did mention
she was confident she'd do well in games.
You-jin came in third, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Then, if Hae-lin doesn't pick Dong-ho,
there's a chance You-jin could pick him.
If she had fun with Jeong-su yesterday,
it's likely she'll pick him.
-Was it fun yesterday?
-What?
Was it fun?
She's a comedian.
She's totally a comedian.
-She's charming.
-So charming.
I am curious about her feelings.
-You-jin?
-We had a double date yesterday.
-Really?
-At the pub.
You-jin and Jeong-su
seemed like they were having a blast.
-Their vibe…
-They really clicked?
They got along the best.
-But not in that way.
-Who will she pick?
Really?
-We're like friends.
-She feels like a friend?
Maybe they just have good banter.
Yeah.
But the key is who Si-an picks.
-I'm so curious.
-Right.
If Si-an picks Jeong-su,
You-jin won't be able to pick him.
I haven't seen Si-an
and Jeong-su together often,
so I don't know what's going on.
That might be why she'd choose him.
-Yeah.
-Exactly
I think she'll pick Theo.
But that could be a sign of her
making a final decision.
-In the end…
-It's okay to make a final decision now.
Right, but she might still feel confused.
If I were in Si-an's shoes,
I'd just choose whoever I like,
whether it be Jun-seo, Theo, or Jeong-su.
-Yeah.
-I think she'll do that.
And she seems like the type who'd do that.
There's no need to complicate things now.
I think there's no need
to consider anyone else.
Si-an's in the toughest spot.
She must have the biggest headache.
Games just aren't our strong suit.
Right.
How did I look during the game?
Did I seem too desperate?
Actually, you looked pretty.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Really.
-But at the end…
-I shouldn't have grabbed her leg.
-Right.
Why did he tell me to do that?
He had no clue!
Grab her leg, Min-seol.
Grab her leg. Go low.
Why did he tell me to do that?
He had no clue!
I should've pushed her,
but he said to grab her leg.
That is hilarious.
It is a little disappointing.
-I'm so disappointed.
-Yeah.
Still, as long as we try our best,
it's fine.
You're right.
I gave it my all, but it didn't work.
It's not like I didn't try.
I tried my best. It just didn't work out.
I can't do anything about that.
It's all luck.
It's about matchup luck too.
You're right.
If we tried our best, it's fine.
-Yeah.
-You can't control
what happens in the end.
Instead of winning
because someone went easy on you…
Right.
It's better to lose
after trying your hardest.
That's true.
Are they all the ones who lost?
You're right. All of them were eliminated.
I'm so curious
about who Si-an will choose today.
-Right. I think it'll be Theo.
-She'll pick Theo.
Yeah.
Jun-seo's already gone twice.
I hope Jun-seo
doesn't go to Paradise today.
Hi.
You're all dressed up.
Want to head to our room? Or…
Over there.
Where?
Let's go there.
Let's go over there. It's pretty.
Okay.
Si-an, there are only two days left.
-Time flies, right?
-I know.
-Yeah.
-Gosh.
Is there a lot on your mind?
Or are you sorting things out?
I wanted to ask if my approach
has put too much pressure on you.
Not at all.
I always tell other people
that Theo doesn't put pressure on me.
I see. I just wanted to ask you that.
After coming back yesterday
or as time goes by…
if your feelings for Jun-seo
have grown more than feelings for me,
then my actions toward you
could make you uncomfortable.
And you'd worry about his reaction.
That's why I wanted to ask how you felt.
-Honestly…
-Yeah?
After two trips to Paradise with Jun-seo,
it's true that my feelings
for him have grown.
Yeah.
But it's not like I've chosen him either.
Right.
To be honest…
It's so tough
to talk about this with you, but…
Yeah.
I figured it'd be better to hear it
from me than through someone else.
Yeah.
-Am I putting too much pressure on you?
-No, Theo.
Should I keep it up?
Am I still on your mind?
You have to tell me.
You know I like things to be clear.
If I'm the lowest priority
among the three,
then I don't want to pressure you anymore,
unless I'm second.
There are only two days left.
So you have to decide quickly.
Be true to yourself.
I was true to myself
and made my choice to tell you.
I…
-For me…
-Yeah?
-It's Jun-seo and…
Well…
-Jeong-su.
-Yeah. Okay, I'm third in line.
-It's down to those two.
-Okay, thank you.
Theo…
I wanted to hear that.
All the flirting I've been doing…
-Did it make you uncomfortable?
-No, I appreciated it.
I see.
-Theo, you were…
-Yeah?
Gosh, I'm just…
Honestly, I went full steam ahead
from the start,
so I did it knowing I might get hurt.
No, you always expressed
your feelings to me,
so honestly,
I felt really drawn to you too.
But I've kept going…
-to Paradise.
-Yeah.
And we were physically apart.
That's right.
I guess it became
out of sight, out of mind.
Yeah, I agree.
That was the biggest factor for me.
-Right.
-Yeah.
But honestly,
there's no need
to cry or feel guilty about this.
Because I don't have any regrets.
In the real world,
I do express myself when I like someone.
But I don't usually fall
for people this deeply and quickly.
I'm not someone who falls in love easily.
I kept wondering why I've felt this way.
I realized the way I'd been treating you…
Yeah?
It was the same way
as when I first fell in love.
-Right.
-That's why I fell for you so fast.
So I don't regret anything.
I mean, I did everything.
I even gave you flowers.
Let me see your ring.
And here's your flower ring.
Isn't it pretty?
"I missed you."
-I'm leaving.
-Bye.
Take this with you.
I'll work hard
to chop firewood for you.
And I'll cook warm meals for you.
-Okay.
-Got it?
I was grateful.
Those were special times
and feelings for me too.
Gosh.
I didn't bring any tissues.
I have no regrets,
and I want to thank you.
What's wrong with me?
When you think of me,
I hope you remember me
as someone who had an innocent heart
and treated you like a first love.
Yeah, of course.
That's why I feel even more sorry.
I was really happy and…
My goodness.
Gosh. I'm sorry, Theo.
It's okay.
When she said those words and cried,
I felt more relieved and better.
Rather than happy, I felt sad.
But I think that's why I liked her.
She's honest with her feelings.
She's clear
about what she likes and dislikes.
Stop! What are you doing?
Which way do we go? This way?
I don't know.
No, you're good-looking.
Thanks. You're pretty.
Well…
I feel relieved.
-On Inferno…
-Yeah?
I feel we didn't get to
spend much time together, so I'm sad.
It's a bit…
I told him I was sorry.
I told Theo that I was turning him down.
But it hurt more because it was Theo.
He never pressured me,
and he always honestly expressed
how he felt to me.
That's why I felt even worse
about rejecting him.
I was so sad.
-She knows how good of a person he is.
-Right.
When she rejected him…
-She felt bad.
-Yes, she felt so bad
-and had a heavy heart.
-Right.
A guy telling someone he loved them
as if they were his first love…
-That was so cool.
-Right.
I almost teared up when he said that.
-That was how much…
-I was moved.
He loved her like she was his first love.
Gosh.
When you love
without holding back like that,
you have no regrets even if it ends.
-Right.
-Seriously.
If you gave it everything you had,
when things end and you move on,
you have no regrets.
Theo's such a remarkable person.
He's probably at peace right now.
-Yes.
-You're right.
-Si-an won't forget him.
-She'll actually keep thinking of him.
-She'll think back on him in her life.
-Yeah.
Theo really makes a person think.
-Are you feeling okay, Min-seol?
-What?
Are you feeling okay?
-Do I look okay?
-You don't.
You didn't look okay.
I feel really down right now.
Just go talk with Jun-seo now.
He just went into the guys' room.
-Ask him directly and clear things up.
-Yeah.
-That'd be better than being unsure.
-It's straightforward.
-Can I talk to him after dinner?
-The timing might be awkward then.
It'd be better to do it now.
That's what I think.
-Jun-seo seems to be in deep thought too.
-Yeah.
Really?
Okay, I'll go ask.
Want to talk?
-Me?
-Yeah.
It looked like you had a lot on your mind.
Not really.
Really?
She's the one with a lot on her mind.
People say this spot is so nice.
It's not bad.
I think this is the best spot.
-Really?
-Yeah.
You must be really disappointed.
-Me? I am.
-Yeah.
It would've been nice
if you could've gone to Paradise more.
Yeah. That's why I was so determined
to win today's game.
Right.
-But I failed miserably.
-Yeah.
-Why did you do that?
-Right?
You should've tried a bit harder.
I should've given you more tips.
-I really tried my best.
-Yeah.
You've been spoiled, haven't you?
What are you talking about?
Because you've gone to Paradise so much.
-No.
-Honestly, you don't need to go today.
Stop going.
You've gone enough.
-I don't need to go to Paradise.
-Yeah.
But it can still hurt.
-Your feelings?
-Yeah.
-Why would they be hurt?
-I can get hurt if…
Not being able to go
to Paradise isn't the issue.
Right.
It is what it is.
-What did you say?
-What?
What are you talking about by yourself?
"What are you talking about?"
You seem to have a lot on your mind.
-Me?
-Yeah, I was…
-I was just really curious.
-Yeah.
That's why I wanted to talk.
Curious about what?
-Well, after everyone left yesterday…
-Yeah?
I wanted to know why
you wanted to talk to me.
-I talked about this with Si-an too.
-Yeah.
I just told her.
At first, I saw Min-seol
as more of a little sister.
-Yeah.
-But I said she's been on my mind.
Right.
I told her I hadn't fully figured out
how I feel about it.
I told her over dinner yesterday
when I didn't have to.
-Yesterday?
-Yeah.
But the thing is I'm not curious
about what you did yesterday.
I want to know why you approached me.
I told you that's what Si-an
and I talked about.
-So you can't talk about it?
-No, that you've been on my mind.
-I see.
-That's why I wanted to talk with you.
But I chose Si-an,
because I have stronger feelings for her.
To sum it up, I talked with Si-an
and spent more time with her,
and despite some tough moments,
I was able to confirm
my feelings for Si-an in the end.
I've come to terms with my feelings.
At this point, what I'm nervous
and concerned about is
giving my all to Si-an
and still not being enough for her.
Also,
I was trying to be honest
but momentarily showed I was indecisive.
It's up to Si-an to decide.
-He expressed himself clearly here.
-Yes.
That's why I started to wonder
if I seemed like too much
of a friendly younger sister to you.
That's what I thought at first.
But in the middle,
I was a bit torn and confused.
When? After we came back from Paradise?
-Yeah, when we came back.
-Really?
-You were torn and confused?
-Yeah, I was confused.
Why? What was the reason?
The reason was my second time
in Paradise was with you.
-Yeah.
-So…
I had someone to compare you to.
-You-jin.
-Yeah, if we're splitting hairs.
-Yeah.
-So…
It wasn't trying to compare you.
But the two situations naturally
started to overlap.
I found myself enjoying it way more
during my second time.
-Right.
-Yeah.
-Just to put it simply.
The food tasted better,
and our conversations were so fun.
I couldn't help but think,
"Isn't this just better?"
Yeah.
-That was the reason.
-Yeah.
I see.
That's how it was.
I had no idea you were conflicted.
-I don't usually show it outwardly.
-Exactly.
That's why I didn't show it either.
But you had been constantly on my mind.
I've only been to Paradise with you.
I know.
I had so much fun with you.
-I haven't gotten to know the others much.
-Yeah.
I'm still in that position now
and don't think I'll learn much more.
Yeah.
So I'm going to keep choosing you.
That's just how it is.
-I'm not trying to pressure you.
-Right.
I don't feel pressured.
-You don't?
-It's just…
Then, feel some pressure.
It's so uncomfortable.
Really?
No.
I've come this far
trying to be honest too, so…
Right.
I get how you feel.
But…
-I don't want you to feel pressured.
-Yeah.
But I do want you to think of me.
I hope you don't feel
uncomfortable around me.
-Okay, I won't.
-Yeah.
-I'm fine.
-I'll do the same.
Rather than uncomfortable,
I just felt bad.
I see.
I wanted to talk about that.
And I'm thankful to you
for talking to me.
Well, if you don't go to Paradise today,
let's just have dinner.
"Let's just have dinner."
And we can talk more.
My memories with Jun-seo
will remain for a long time afterwards.
And I'm grateful to him.
That's why I feel
a love-hate thing for him.
When I say "love-hate,"
I mean love and hate!
It's infuriating.
What can you do?
I just have to bear it.
She's so adorable.
She's Min-seol the baby! A little baby.
With just a day or two left,
-things are starting to sort out.
-Right.
-Jun-seo made things clear.
-Yes.
Min-seol won't be confused now.
Right, she definitely won't be.
They both said
the best things they could say.
Not only Min-seol but Jun-seo as well
-won't be confused.
-Right.
-He'll keep moving forward.
-Yes.
It's always tougher to be the one waiting
to be chosen than the one choosing.
-I think so too. Right?
-Yeah.
Yesterday, with Si-an…
I held back on expressing myself
to the point that I felt bad about it.
I regret that.
-You held back?
-Yeah.
It's because the pace here
is different from the outside world.
But the idea that we have to make a choice
and become a couple to create an outcome…
I wondered if that's possible
with the level of intensity of this place.
-It's not easy.
-Right.
I'm definitely going to
move forward with Si-an now.
-For sure?
-Yeah.
-You've made up your mind?
So, who are you going to choose?
Me?
-But…
-Gosh.
-Go on.
-I'm really…
-What?
-Honestly, I'm really…
I realized I was more serious
about this than I thought.
I know, right?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, you're about to cry now too.
Yeah.
Being interested
in multiple people at the same time is…
It's been hard to handle.
It's not something
that's possible outside.
But here, it's possible.
But I had feelings
for multiple people at once,
so I just felt like I was…
-Very…
-Overwhelmed?
No, not overwhelmed.
I just felt like a terrible person.
-Don't think like that.
-I know.
But it's also true.
-Yeah.
-But…
It changes from day to day.
And every little action they did…
-kept making my feelings change so quick.
-Right. True.
Gosh, it must be driving you crazy.
Seriously, in just these few days…
But it's still… Yeah.
When I'm in a relationship,
I like spending a lot of time together
and being affectionate.
I like having emotional interactions
that are really lovey-dovey,
even if they're a little cheesy.
But Jun-seo doesn't seem like
a really warm or friendly type.
So I thought if we dated,
there could be some issues.
I might end up really upset.
That's what I was thinking.
Honestly, you can't change
someone's personality.
It's confusing.
So…
I don't know.
I feel like my head's going to explode.
She's very aware of their differences.
She also knows personalities don't change.
She knows.
But I think Jun-seo
would be adorable in a relationship.
Guys who are brusque but show affection
through actions are really charming too.
-They're very charming.
-Yeah.
But the problem for Si-an was
the way he talks to her.
That was tough to tolerate for Si-an.
In any case, Si-an said
she'd pick one of the two.
-Yes.
-Jun-seo or Jeong-su.
Right.
But is she going to try
with Jeong-su one last time?
I think so.
-I think she'll choose Jeong-su.
-Me too.
What do you think? He disagrees.
Why do I feel like it'll be Jun-seo?
The reason is if she had
a great time with Jun-seo yesterday,
like their first date in Paradise,
she'd definitely choose Jeong-su today.
But yesterday was very disappointing.
Wouldn't it be quicker for her
to go one more time with him today
to see if she has feelings for him or not?
Instead of checking Jeong-su again
and then comparing him to Jun-seo,
only to be confused
about who to pick…
-Right.
-It'd be simpler to make sure of Jun-seo
and cut him loose if he's not for her.
I agree with Jin-young.
That's what I would do.
-Jun-seo?
-Yes.
She should pick Jun-seo.
This logic makes sense.
-But Si-an may think differently.
-Si-an isn't a logical person.
Right.
Her first Paradise date was with Jeong-su.
That made a huge impact on her.
So I'm unsure.
My gut says she'll go with Jeong-su.
-To be totally sure…
-Yeah.
It's to confirm her feelings.
Rather than not pick him and regret it,
-she'll go once more.
-She wants to confirm.
Then, she'll decide.
But if she does pick Jeong-su,
I think that will mean
her feelings are definitely set on him.
In this situation, I don't think
she would do something reckless
and go with Jeong-su again
to find out how he feels once more.
I agree because she clearly expressed
her feelings to Theo.
Right.
Okay. How about you, Hanhae?
I think it'll be Jeong-su too.
Then, let's make a bet.
-"A bet"!
-Losers pay for dinner.
Sure, sounds good.
Why are you so eager to lose money?
-They're not picking final couples yet.
-It means I'm that confident.
She's confident.
Sounds good to me.
-We'll split it three ways.
-Sounds good.
I have no idea.
I'm so curious to see who Si-an will pick.
I feel like she'll surprise everyone
with her choice.
Really?
Will she go against all expectations?
INFERNO
Now, we're going to match the couples
who will go on a date in Paradise.
The guys must be nervous.
They must be shaking.
-Their hearts are racing.
-We can feel it!
-They're pounding so fast.
-They're wondering, "Is it me?"
We'll begin with first-place winner,
Lee Si-an.
Please choose the person you'd like to
go on a date with in Paradise.
It'll be Jun-seo.
-Yeah.
-I think so too.
The person I'd like to go
to Paradise with is…
After my second date with Jun-seo,
I realized just how different
his personality is from Jeong-su's.
Jun-seo is the tough guy type,
while Jeong-su is
more of the sweet, gentle type.
Would I prefer someone who's more gentle?
Or do I go with my heart instead?
Even if they're not as gentle,
do I go with someone
I enjoy spending time with?
That's what I'm torn over.
She's on the fence.
-She totally is.
-Yeah.
But this sounds like
she's leaning toward Jun-seo.
Right?
-Her heart's drawn to him.
-She likes him more.
Wait, hold on.
Why are we so curious
about who Si-an wants to date?
I'm busy enough as it is with my own life,
but I'm dying to find out
who she'll go on a date with.
-I'm so curious.
-I'm really curious.
-It has me all anxious.
-Yes.
The person I'd like to go
to Paradise with is…
Lee Si-an has selected…
NEXT EPISODE
I can do anything I put my mind to.
You just have to push ahead.
It's a night full of concerns.
Anything else you want to ask me?
I'm not the type
who gets curious about those things.
It felt like
he wasn't genuinely interested in me.
It was always you from the start,
and that hasn't changed.
You made it possible
for me to earnestly take part in this.
You will now make your final decision.
The person I'd like
to leave Inferno with is…
Subtitle translation by: Hye Min Eom