LEE SI-AN
CHUNG YOU-JIN
KIM MIN-SEOL
BAE JI-YEON
KIM HYE-JIN
KIM A-RIN
PARK HAE-LIN
KIM TE-HWAN
KOOK DONG-HO
JANG THEO
KIM JEONG-SU
YUK JUN-SEO
AN JONG-HOON
SINGLE'S INFERNO
It's a bit of a shame to sleep, right?
Yeah, maybe there's more
we could talk about.
It does feel a bit disappointing
to just go to sleep like this.
What was your first impression of me?
-What?
-Your first impression of me.
You were like a beast.
A beast? Because of my hair?
No, it was because of your actions too.
I thought they'd have some chemistry,
but I didn't expect this.
This is an explosion of chemistry.
They're stirring the imagination.
In any case, we aren't sure
of what actually happened.
No, we aren't.
I wish we could get rid of the blankets.
Aren't there any see-through blankets?
Because of the blankets… Jeez.
They're so annoying.
What actually happened?
-Right?
-The blankets…
-Yeah.
-They're in the way.
And up until now, Si-an has never shared
a bed with anyone in Paradise.
This is a first.
And I don't think it's just one person.
-It's both of them.
-Right.
They both opened up to each other.
This night is going to be
a huge turning point for these two.
That's what we can all predict.
Isn't it basically a done deal?
-Right?
-Yes.
-Really.
-I think so too.
Si-an has totally opened up
her heart to him.
But it's Si-an…
That's right.
It's not set in stone yet,
but he's climbed to the top spot.
He took the lead.
-But the others are still in the race.
-They are.
-The order could change at any time.
-They could climb back on top.
PARADISE
KIM A-RIN & KOOK DONG-HO
It's now starting to hit me
that we're in Paradise.
Yeah.
Yesterday was so…
It didn't feel real.
Talking to you was fun yesterday.
Yeah, it was so fun.
And things feel different
from our first conversation.
It felt different.
I felt so comfortable.
I think I let myself relax around you.
No. When we first talked,
I thought you were boring.
But you seemed like a calm person,
and when we talked,
you seemed like a deep person.
When we got comfortable
and talked yesterday…
I don't seem deep now?
What?
-No, that's not it.
-Do I seem shallow?
Not at all. It was…
I think we have the same sense of humor.
-That's a relief.
-Yeah.
-Conversations need to be fun.
I really don't want to go back.
Just wait here and start cleaning.
Have everything cleaned up.
You weren't like this before.
At least in the beginning…
I feel like I've been conned.
I think I've been conned.
Something's gone wrong.
PARADISE
LEE SI-AN & YUK JUN-SEO
-So that night's over.
-Morning has come.
I wonder what happened.
Did you sleep well?
-My eyes…
-Yeah.
-The sun is so bright.
I can't breathe.
-What?
-I can't breathe.
Is she resting on his arm?
Seriously?
-She is.
-You're right.
She's resting on his arm.
Who are you?
Just kidding. I can't even see.
-Sleep a bit more.
-What?
I'll wash up first.
I always lose my mind on these two.
-Right?
-Wait, the cameras…
Were the cameras rolling all night?
-Nothing happened…
-Nothing should.
-There are cameras.
-We're all adults.
Jun-seo's the youngest though.
Right, he's the youngest.
I thought Jun-seo was
a really shy and reserved type of person.
-But in bed…
-He can be forward.
I guess it's true
that still waters run deep.
He is a beast.
-He was a beast after all.
-He was a beast.
-Are you ready?
-Yeah.
How do I look?
Today's the first time I dressed nicely.
-You look nice.
-I do?
Hold on.
I'm a little scared.
This is kind of scary.
Okay.
-Jun-seo, you wanted…
-Yes.
Straightened hair
with a little volume, right?
-How hot is it now?
-It's 200 degrees Celsius.
It's 200 degrees Celsius?
My hair's going to turn into a broom.
-No, this is how you make it straight.
-Really?
-Hold on.
-What?
It's becoming too straight.
-Stay still.
-Hold on.
Stay still.
Let's straighten it all out first.
You sure this is right?
-Wait, stay still.
-I can tuck it back better now.
This is fun.
-Does doing that add volume?
-Yeah.
I look like a well-groomed dog.
Hey!
-Hey!
-Am I in a rock band now?
-Hey.
-Am I?
You want me to do some headbanging?
Let me see.
Hey, hold on.
Hold on a second.
Lift your chin up.
Look.
It does straighten hair well.
-Right?
-Yeah, it's cool.
What do you think? Do you like it?
I think it's okay.
-For real?
-Yeah.
I look pure and innocent…
with this long, straight hair.
The guys are going to fall for me.
I'm in trouble.
There will be eight girls today.
You're so annoying.
What do you think?
-It's not bad.
-Are you sure?
Good job.
It's so hot.
Spending one night together
makes a huge difference.
Paradise made a huge impact.
It's huge.
Wow, you straightened your hair.
Your hair is so soft, like a puppy.
-Isn't it like a puppy?
-Yeah.
You remind me of our family's dog.
I checked the mirror
and looked like a well-groomed dog.
Your hair is so soft and nice.
Straight hair suits you well.
You used to look a bit wild,
but now you seem tamed.
-I guess he's been tamed.
-The wolf became a puppy.
-Thanks, Si-an.
-Sure thing.
I ended up getting all the attention.
Gosh, how did this even happen?
Si-an and Jun-seo have basically
returned as a couple now.
Yes. I think there's no going back now.
-I think Jun-seo is all in now.
-I don't think his feelings will change.
-I agree.
-Si-an is also pretty much…
-Yeah, pretty much.
-Yeah.
-Because…
-Yes.
They shared the same bed,
and her head rested on his arm, which is…
Of course.
-It's a big deal.
-It is.
-Yeah.
-It's a thing that swayed her a lot.
But I think she could still waver.
-I agree.
-Yeah.
Everyone has different standards.
Si-an may believe in her mind
she resisted his physical contact.
But she seemed to have liked it.
-Right.
-If she didn't, she'd never…
But one thing is
Si-an didn't initiate any contact.
She didn't.
-So that may show a chance to be swayed.
-Right.
That's why I think
it's still unclear for now.
INFERNO
I'm feeling unsettled.
Why? What's bothering you?
I think it'd be good to have
a lot of conversations today.
Honestly, I haven't been able to
talk much with Dong-ho.
-Make sure you do it today.
-Except for the second day.
And A-rin probably knows
everything by now, right?
-About what?
-About your feelings.
Yeah.
It might be upsetting
to overlap with a close roommate.
-I wasn't bothered before.
-Yeah.
Rather than upsetting,
I think it just bothers me.
But of course, it would bother you.
What do I do?
When A-rin comes back,
I don't want to hear
about how things were for her.
Then, don't listen.
She'll probably bring it up.
Then, just don't ask to begin with.
She'll just talk about how it went.
We don't want to know.
We really don't want to know,
especially if it's with someone
I'm interested in.
I wonder what they're up to.
Aren't you hungry?
I'm not hungry at all.
-Why not?
-I'm hungover.
-You're hungover?
-Yeah.
Why did we drink so much?
We drank really quickly too.
They went down easily last night.
-That's true.
-Yeah.
-They're here.
-What?
-They're early.
-Right?
Hey.
Yo.
Hi.
What are you eating?
They're earlier than we expected.
Right. We thought you'd come back
at around lunch.
-You were just hanging out?
-What were you up to?
-Hi.
-Hey, did you have fun?
Hi.
Goodness.
Did you have breakfast?
We did.
Did you have fun?
-I've gone so many times…
-Is that why?
We only drank water.
I feel like I'm going to die
from this hangover.
You have to hear this.
How much did you drink?
-What did you drink?
-I'm not even joking.
We had 80 proof whiskey.
-You said you can't drink.
-About half a bottle.
-We drank that.
-You drank half a bottle?
Apparently, they were having
separate conversations.
We were asleep but also talking.
They were different conversations.
They weren't conversations.
We were just saying things.
She would talk. Then, I would talk.
We'd clearly be asleep.
But he would talk to me, so I'd respond.
-Two separate conversations.
-Then, we'd sleep again.
I really wasn't interested,
but I was also curious.
I really didn't want to know
what they did.
But of course, I was curious.
What did you two do?
We went swimming.
Gosh. That must've been fun.
Man, it was as cold as winter.
-Seriously, I was freezing.
-Really?
You hate swimming though.
-At the pool?
-But you went swimming?
We were walking around.
It was like what we did during the game.
-It was so cold.
-It was freezing.
-We were shivering like this.
-Right.
But the fact that it was
my first time there…
-Yeah.
-That's right.
We had some amazing food.
We just ate and drank.
-Those two don't want to hear it.
-Exactly.
How was it?
I mean, what's there to say?
Dong-ho's face was just glowing.
-No, it's not like that.
-Yeah, right.
But we talked a lot.
He seems to enjoy talking.
-That's surprising.
-Yeah.
Isn't that similar to you?
-You love to talk too.
-Yeah.
-I love talking.
-You do.
He seems to enjoy it as much as I do.
You seem to get along well.
That's why it was great.
I felt so many new things.
We joked around a lot.
You two got really close.
Yeah, I think we did.
-Going to Paradise really changes things.
-I guess so.
Maybe that's why
everyone says you have to go.
How about you, Hae-lin?
I've made up my mind now.
Already? You've made up your mind?
-I was debating between two people.
-Yeah.
But after talking with Jeong-su,
I made up my mind.
To pick Jeong-su?
No, I'm not sure about that.
I don't think I can tell you that yet.
Okay.
Si-an, hurry and tell us.
What happened after drinking like that?
-I can't wrap my head around it.
-No.
-What?
-No, it wasn't like that.
I just got a little emotional. That's all.
Why did you get emotional?
Maybe I'm really losing it?
This is too funny. I'm so curious.
I'd been holding a lot inside,
and Jun-seo kept…
-Did he draw them out?
-Yeah, he did.
He drew out the emotions I was holding in.
Did he comfort you?
He just kept saying
it's good to be honest.
I see.
Earlier, you were sitting
right in front of us on the helicopter.
After dozing off for a bit,
I opened my eyes.
And right as I was
about to close them again,
I saw it happen.
Jun-seo grabbed Si-an's head
and rammed it onto his shoulder.
That's right.
I was startled.
So I acted like I didn't see
and closed my eyes again.
After seeing that, I thought,
"They've become really close."
Jun-seo has a way of making you swoon.
He just does what he wants
without hesitation.
I think that's what makes you swoon.
He even comes right out
and says he likes you.
That's it. It's just that.
Nothing else matters.
After coming back from Paradise,
I felt like things had been cleared up,
so I felt more at ease.
There were a lot of moments
that made my heart race.
My interest in him has shot up.
It ended up like this.
How was it talking with Te-hwan?
-Come on and tell us.
-Spill the beans.
Did you guys drink at night?
Just a tiny bit of champagne.
I was upset after hearing
about those two though.
To be honest…
For us, we just had dinner
and went swimming.
And when we went to bed,
we only said a few words and fell asleep.
But according to what Si-an said,
he kept talking to her the whole time
while lying down.
But they were both really drunk.
-Really?
-Yeah, so…
They were just rambling while drunk.
Right. They did drink whiskey after all.
Should I go to Paradise too
and have some whiskey?
Seriously.
I can't handle whiskey at all though.
I guess Jun-seo is really on your mind.
Isn't that obvious?
I'm grinding my teeth right now.
-How was it, Te-hwan?
-Me? I loved it.
-You did?
-Seriously.
That's awesome.
We talked a lot.
We exchanged our timelines
and everything we've experienced
from the beginning
until yesterday in Paradise.
We reflected on the times
we missed each other.
We talked a bit
about our dating styles too.
It was really fun. We talked a lot.
I kept thinking, "Time flies."
Yeah.
Today, the men
will be competing in a game…
It's for Paradise.
…for a date in Paradise.
Everyone, please gather
at the Korean wrestling arena.
Here it comes.
-This is going to be so intense.
-Yeah.
Jun-seo and Theo.
-You're right.
-It'll be intense.
-I think Jong-hoon will do his best too.
-You're right.
They're actually going to wrestle?
This is going to be
such a physical battle.
-For real.
-Right?
My goodness.
Here they come.
Why am I getting nervous too?
Today, the men will be competing in a game
for a date in Paradise.
Only the top three winners in order
of their ranking can each pick a woman
to take on a date to Paradise.
Today's game is…
-Wrestling.
-Of course.
I knew it would be wrestling.
If any part of their body above the knee
touches the ground first,
or if a contestant steps outside the ring,
they lose the match.
The three winners of the preliminaries
will advance to the finals.
We just need to win one round.
-Yeah.
-You're right.
The matchups will be crucial.
The matchups will be decided
by drawing balls.
Kim Jeong-su, please select a ball.
KIM JEONG-SU - GREEN BALL
YUK JUN-SEO - RED BALL
JANG THEO - YELLOW BALL
They all picked different ones.
KOOK DONG-HO - RED BALL
It's Yuk.
Kook and Yuk.
-That's tough.
-Yes.
Oh no.
This isn't going to be easy.
RED BALL - JUN-SEO VS DONG-HO
AN JONG-HOON - GREEN BALL
GREEN BALL - JEONG-SU VS JONG-HOON
I drew the ball I didn't want to draw.
Today's not going to be easy.
It's the Si-an derby for them.
They have to win to move up.
-Both have great physiques.
-Yes.
-Yellow by default?
-By default?
Theo and Te-hwan.
It's a battle between the two Ts.
YELLOW BALL - THEO VS TE-HWAN
We will begin the first match.
Kim Jeong-su and An Jong-hoon.
Please step into the ring.
I can't predict who will win.
Gosh.
-Let's go!
-Good luck!
-You can do it!
-Hey!
Please start when the whistle blows.
Get ready.
Look at his thighs.
Yeah.
I have no idea who'll win.
They seem evenly matched.
You can do it.
-This is no joke.
-This is intense.
This is intense.
It could go either way.
This is amazing.
My gosh.
It's like a finals match.
I'm worried they'll fall out of bounds.
-My goodness.
-My gosh.
I'm worried they'll fall out of bounds.
Wow, look at Jeong-su.
I can't tell who'll win.
-You can't get tired.
-Exactly.
-They're tired.
-Hang in there.
His foot went out.
He didn't get to try any techniques.
-It's such a shame.
-Right.
Kim Jeong-su wins.
Great job.
Unbelievable.
Next, the contestants who drew red balls,
Yuk Jun-seo and Kook Dong-ho.
Please step into the ring.
You can do it.
Let's go.
You never know.
-Dong-ho might be stronger.
-Right.
-He could be good at it.
-He's tall too.
He might have been
on the wrestling team too.
Jun-seo looks like he'd be really strong.
-He's super sturdy.
-Yeah.
Just don't get hurt.
You can do it!
Please start when the whistle blows.
Get ready.
This is scary.
They're like bulls.
They're just bulls.
Look at them hold their ground.
He's stronger than I expected.
-Dong-ho?
-The weight class difference.
Yuk Jun-seo wins.
He took him down.
It ended without anyone getting hurt,
so that's good.
Look over there.
Look. It's all dug up.
-Both are so competitive.
-Nice.
-Nice. Good job.
-Great match.
That was cool.
He wouldn't budge.
Brush off your chest.
They're both fiercely competitive.
He's like a bull.
The contestants who drew yellow balls,
Jang Theo and Kim Te-hwan.
Please step into the ring.
-I'm interested in this match too.
-Theo.
-Show us, Theo.
-Please, Theo.
You can do it.
But the height difference…
One of them is taller…
Being taller is an advantage.
-Is Te-hwan strong?
-He's strong.
I have a feeling Theo will do well.
He looks strong.
Having long legs could be a disadvantage.
Yeah, the center of gravity is higher.
Please start when the whistle blows.
Get ready.
Who's going to win?
You can do it.
Kim Te-hwan wins.
Gosh, what's Theo going to do now?
He's falling further behind.
Yeah, what's he going to do?
Te-hwan is strong.
-That was quick.
-He's good.
The three who advanced to the finals
are Yuk Jun-seo, Kim Te-hwan,
and Kim Jeong-su.
The final match will be…
-A wrestling showdown.
-What?
-"Showdown"?
-What's that?
-A wrestling showdown.
-What?
-"Showdown"?
-What's that?
-The three of them together?
-They're all competing?
If one person defeats the other two
and secures two wins,
the game will end.
…the game will end.
It's a tournament.
They're making it a tournament.
So if they all keep ending up
with one win and one loss,
they could be wrestling all day.
-Isn't this a test of endurance?
-Yes.
I guess that's why it's called
"a wrestling showdown."
-This is going to be intense.
-Yeah.
We will begin the first match.
Kim Jeong-su and Kim Te-hwan.
Please step into the ring.
Jeong-su has a good balance.
-He has a good sense of balance.
-Yeah.
And good energy too.
This is all about energy.
Please start when the whistle blows.
Get ready.
Gosh.
-Spread the legs.
-There you go!
He went for the inner leg.
He's going for the spin?
My goodness.
-My goodness.
-What happened?
That must have hurt.
What happened?
Kim Jeong-su wins.
They're all so serious.
It's so intense.
That must hurt.
We will begin the second match.
Yuk Jun-seo and Kim Te-hwan.
Please step into the ring.
Good luck.
You can do it.
This is going to be fun.
I think he'll lift him up.
-Is he going to flip him?
-Lift and…
If Te-hwan wins, it'll be epic.
This will be fun to watch.
Please start when the whistle blows.
Get ready.
There's pride at stake
in front of the women they like.
-Getting lifted is humiliating.
-It's embarrassing.
Te-hwan can't back down now.
Wow, he won.
Yuk Jun-seo wins.
-Unbelievable.
-Amazing.
Wow, he won.
Yuk Jun-seo wins.
Wow, you're so strong.
-Unbelievable.
-Amazing.
As expected.
FINAL RANK OF 3RD PLACE
TE-HWAN - 2 LOSSES
We will begin the last match.
Kim Jeong-su and Yuk Jun-seo.
Please step into the ring.
-The winner…
-He gets to go.
-Yes.
One way or another,
Si-an will go to Paradise again.
-Yes.
-It seems so.
They came in first and second
in the first game.
You're right.
Jun-seo?
I think Jeong-su will win.
He doesn't budge.
There's nothing you can do.
But you may never know.
I've felt Jun-seo's strength.
When Jeong-su was my opponent,
I tried harder to give it my best.
I think you never really know
until you're up against them.
And I'm not lacking in strength either.
So I thought I'd be able to win.
If you lose the game, you lose her.
-For real.
-Yeah.
Please start when the whistle blows.
Get ready.
Wow, they're so steady.
I was rooting for Yuk Jun-seo.
I'd like to go with him again
and spend a little more time together.
It's over.
-Someone spun the other.
-Who was it?
That's right.
Yuk Jun-seo wins.
Incredible!
That was no joke.
-That was a proper throw.
-Yeah.
That was real wrestling.
You're right.
As expected, he's the strongest one.
He's too strong.
-He lifted me.
-He's a bull.
It must be tiring.
Right?
The men's game to win a date in Paradise.
First place is Yuk Jun-seo.
1ST PLACE, YUK JUN-SEO - 2 WINS
Second place is Kim Jeong-su.
2ND PLACE, KIM JEONG-SU - 1 WIN, 1 LOSS
Third place is Kim Te-hwan.
3RD PLACE, KIM TE-HWAN - 2 LOSSES
The top three men from this game
will each choose a woman
in the afternoon to go to Paradise with.
I'm curious to see who they'll pick.
I really wanted to go with Si-an,
but I was frustrated and angry
about not being able to go.
So I kept grumbling to myself about it.
Gosh, nothing's working out for him.
-Honestly…
-There's not much he can do.
-There really isn't.
-The only thing he can do is hide her bag.
He can just hide her bag.
That's…
-There's no other way.
-Si-an's travel bag?
Yes, that's the only solution.
Or he can go and hide inside her bag.
One of the two.
It's a really tough situation.
-I feel so bad for Theo.
-It's not easy.
Starting now, enjoy a date
with the person of your choice.
Bye.
-I booked a reservation.
-Good luck!
-With who?
-Dong-ho.
They're jumping right into it.
You have to make use of this spare time.
Si-an, come on out.
You scared me!
-He came right over.
-That's the way.
He has to be quick and find a way.
Where are you?
You want to come in?
It's your first time here, right?
Yeah, I've never been
in the men's room.
-Where's your bed?
-This is mine.
-Here?
-Yeah.
What?
-What?
-What is it?
-Why are you so awkward?
-It's awkward! I don't know.
-What is?
-It's awkward.
-Why are you suddenly awkward?
-What?
-Why are you being awkward?
Well?
-I don't know.
-You seem to have gotten prettier.
-What happened?
-Here we go again.
Do you want a flower?
I hid it here for you.
"I missed you."
-I'm leaving.
-Bye.
Take this with you.
What?
I MISSED YOU!!
-A surprise for her.
-My goodness.
Surprises are his specialty.
I wanted to say I missed you earlier,
but I felt embarrassed.
Why are you so awkward all of a sudden?
I don't know.
Don't know what?
She feels bad.
-She feels a bit bad, right?
-Yeah.
-She feels bad.
-I think so.
It's because Theo's such a good guy.
-Exactly.
-So…
She's been wavering a lot
and feeling so confused,
but he keeps expressing to her
the same feelings he's had from the start.
So I think she genuinely
feels sorry about it.
-Does your head hurt?
-Yeah.
It's understandable.
I'm confused.
-You're confused?
-Yeah.
About what? Your feelings or…
Yeah.
We weren't given a lot of time,
so just do what you want.
For me…
it's always been you.
That doesn't mean
I want you to keep me in mind.
This is your life,
and this is your choice.
I like you, so of course…
if you choose me, I'd be so happy.
But I don't want
to put any pressure on you
or influence your decision like that.
You get what I mean?
Even if the outcome
isn't what I'd hoped for…
Yeah.
I'd obviously be sad.
I'd probably cry a little in the shower.
Damn it.
I'm kidding.
-I'm sure you know…
-Right.
But put your own thoughts,
satisfaction, and happiness first.
-Right.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Don't feel too pressured.
-Go with your gut.
-Yeah.
Yeah.
You never put pressure on me though.
-Always…
-Yeah?
I'm grateful to you the most.
Gosh, Theo is just…
He's too amazing to just move on from.
He's admirable.
-That's right.
-Yeah.
What?
-Theo.
-Switch.
What?
Theo, come out for a second.
Me? Not Si-an?
Go on a date, you two.
-The two of them are going to talk?
-I guess he wanted to chat with him.
How much did you
talk about with Si-an just now?
Well, she seemed to have
a lot on her mind.
Yeah.
-I told her to do what she wants.
-You did?
I said I didn't have any regrets anyway.
Si-an had a lot on her mind.
I know, right?
Well, I won't get into the details.
-You can just hear it from Si-an.
-Yeah.
I think she's taking this
more seriously than expected.
I really like that attitude.
Yeah.
So I thought maybe I should
-try my chances with Si-an too.
-Yeah.
-That's what I thought yesterday.
-Right.
I wanted to share this with you.
This whole time,
you've created a lot of connections
and had a lot of conversations with her.
-Yeah.
-Right?
That's why.
I think her feelings for you
are pretty strong.
-Yeah.
-But in any case…
-I'm just going to do what I want.
-You should.
I'm going to go full steam ahead,
like a real man.
I hope you'll do the same.
-I've been doing that.
-Yeah?
To be honest,
I've expressed my feelings
to her a lot from the very beginning.
When Si-an came into my heart,
I locked the door behind her
so no one else could come in.
But honestly, on the flip side,
Si-an can leave whenever she wants.
The door opens from the inside.
So in my opinion…
-It's her choice.
-Right.
The thing about people's feelings is
even if I give it my all here,
that doesn't mean she'll choose me.
You can do the same,
and she might not choose you either.
-She could even choose Jeong-su.
-Yeah.
In any case, let's both try our best.
Yeah, okay. We have to give it our all.
Let's do our best.
-We'll give it our best shot.
-Sounds good.
-They're both so cool.
-Yeah, seriously.
-Those two are so cool.
-Yeah.
-She stole the hearts of such great guys.
-They're amazing.
Si-an is one lucky girl.
-Exactly.
-She's the real winner.
Yeah.
This is like a fair and honorable battle
between two men.
That's what it feels like.
But two guys have never had
a conversation like this before.
-That's true.
-Right?
-Exactly.
-That's why it was more impressive.
They're both amazing.
Honestly, Si-an's so lucky.
But if Jeong-su gets involved here,
it'll become a love square.
I think it'll be tough
-for Jeong-su to find a way in.
-Yeah, in the current situation.
There's no room for him.
But you said Si-an likes Jeong-su.
I said she could waver. Things may change
depending on what Jeong-su does.
So if he shows up
with his bangs down again, she'll swoon?
Let's hope she doesn't do that.
With Si-an's feelings,
it's not over until it's over.
-Right.
-Yes.
-Not until the final decision.
Yes, I think so.
This is so complicated.
Is…
Is there any place you want to go to?
Where should we go?
-Where do you want to go?
-We can go anywhere.
-This spot in the shade…
-Paradise.
Paradise?
I lost more of my voice, right?
Yeah, I was going to say that.
-I like it here.
-Yeah.
-It's in the shade.
-Great.
How was it?
-How was it?
-Long time no see.
-Right?
-Doesn't a day here feel super long?
Yeah.
That's right.
-Yesterday was my first day on Inferno.
-Yeah.
I was bored.
-Everyone said they had a great time.
-Says who?
I think everyone was just pretending.
-So it wasn't fun?
-It wasn't for me.
Really?
How have you been?
Paradise…
Did you have fun? Was it different?
I had a good time.
That's what everyone always says.
Yesterday, I picked you
to go to Paradise with.
You didn't know, right?
Did you think I'd pick you?
I thought you'd pick Jeong-su.
Really? I actually picked you.
Honestly,
I don't think
my feelings will change much.
How many days are left now? Four? Three?
I've never expressed my feelings
so directly to anyone before.
He's confused.
-It's written all over his face.
-It's obvious.
Why is this so funny?
He's wavering.
When you talked with other guys,
there wasn't anyone else
you wanted to get to know?
Nope.
At this point, my feelings for you
will either go up or go down.
That's all there will be.
So if I get a chance to go to Paradise,
I'm going to pick you.
Keep that in mind.
But do tell me this.
Tell me if you don't want that.
But that's…
No, I want to go. I want to go with you.
That is what's different.
-That personality.
-For real.
-She has him all shaken up.
-Yeah.
It's something only Hae-lin could say.
No, I want to go. I want to go with you.
Yeah.
Feeling dizzy?
No, not at all.
We have to be open and honest.
-Yeah.
Anyways, that's how I feel.
Here you are.
Gosh, You-jin.
It's You-jin.
Here you are.
Hi.
I want to talk with Dong-ho too.
-Let's talk.
-You're so popular.
-After you two…
-I'm not popular.
Where do you want to wait?
Should I call you over?
-Should we do that?
-Yeah.
-I'll be resting in our room.
-I'll head over there.
Let me know after you talk.
See you later.
Yeah, You-jin needs to talk to him too.
-Right.
-I hope You-jin gets a chance as well.
She finally found the courage.
-Yes.
-Right.
What's the right thing to do?
I heard all of your honest thoughts,
so I should think it over
and let you know, right?
I'd appreciate that.
I'd be thankful, but…
No matter how you feel,
I don't think my mind will change.
Yeah, I'll definitely
let you know.
Okay. You must have a lot to think about.
-Thanks. Let's go.
-Yeah.
Are you going to see You-jin?
-I think I should.
-Yeah.
I'll be back.
-Nice outfit.
-What were you up to?
-Thanks.
-No, I mean…
What?
I meant Te-hwan's Paradise outfit.
Your Paradise outfit looks nice.
You look good too.
-What?
-I do?
-I…
-What?
He said, "Nice outfit."
So I thanked him,
but he was talking about Te-hwan.
-You look good too.
-Thanks.
Let's go talk.
How was it?
We haven't had a chance to talk,
and in the meantime,
you've been to Paradise twice.
-Right. Our timeline ended up like that.
-Yeah.
-Him and his darn timelines again.
-"Timeline."
-He's a numbers guy.
-Time is important to him.
I was really disappointed.
I tend to be pretty honest.
-So…
-Right, you are.
I'll be even more straightforward.
So…
Since I've waited this long,
I plan to try really hard
to win you over starting from today.
-But…
-Right.
But from your perspective,
if you're pretty certain
about your feelings, you could…
feel uncomfortable if I cross that line.
It could also be rude if I did that.
So that's what I'm going to do,
but if it gets too uncomfortable…
Honestly, it's not uncomfortable.
You're always nice and considerate.
-Right.
-But it makes me wonder.
Were my actions unclear and ambiguous,
so everyone was…
Did I do something wrong?
Not at all. We just have
our ideal types in mind.
And I haven't talked too in-depth
about this with A-rin,
but I briefly discussed it with Hae-lin.
She said her ideal type
in terms of personality
seemed to match up with you a lot.
Anyways, they've both been
to Paradise with you.
-You're right.
-I haven't had that chance.
-Right.
-Yeah.
You're right.
Right, they've already gone.
I think I'll need to quickly decide
so we can all have a peace of mind.
Really? I was secretly hoping
you wouldn't decide so quickly.
I secretly was hoping.
-Someone save me.
-Can't you decide
after going to Paradise with me?
I feel like I'm the only one
without any information.
So that's a bit disappointing.
If everything hasn't been settled yet
and you're still considering things…
If you decide right away
under these circumstances,
I think I'd be disappointed.
So I secretly hope
you don't make up your mind.
If one of the three winners
can take A-rin to Paradise,
I'd like to spend time alone with Dong-ho
on Inferno for a while without her around.
I think that's what I immediately thought.
"Can't someone take A-rin away for a bit?"
A quick decision means no chance for her.
-Right.
-Yes.
-She's not wrong.
-Right.
If he makes a decision now,
it means he's rejecting her.
They haven't connected in any way.
-You-jin expressed herself so well.
-Yes.
And Dong-ho didn't mean to mislead anyone.
You-jin had him in mind
but just couldn't express her feelings.
Dong-ho didn't even realize that.
Suddenly, he has three women
saying they like him.
He was flustered.
He thought, "Did I do something wrong?"
He thought, "Did I lead them on?"
But it's not that. He's just a good guy.
-Right.
That's why they all like him.
How are you feeling?
Dong-ho seems really busy right now.
There were women
who wanted to talk to him.
You-jin and the game changer
seemed to be leaning toward him.
They went to Paradise together, right?
He's so popular.
You just spent time
with the popular guy in Paradise then.
I've already had enough conversations.
At this point, I don't think it's right
to approach Jun-seo first.
I think now would be a good time
to give it a try though.
They're passing by.
Who is it?
No idea. I can't see.
Jun-seo…
All I can see is Jun-seo.
Is that Jeong-su next to him?
It can't be Theo.
-What?
-Why aren't you all talking?
Did you already have talks?
Yeah, I had some.
Really?
Come in.
What's going on?
Where are your sunglasses today?
You're wearing glasses instead.
Is that right?
How is it here, Min-seol?
-Here?
-Are you having fun? Yeah.
-Here on Inferno?
-Yeah.
It's fun.
-It is?
-Yeah.
I enjoyed watching the game today.
-You did?
-It was fun.
I looked pretty cool, right?
Jeez.
Yeah, it was cool.
Is Min-seol wearing a sock on her hand?
-Really?
-Could you replay that?
Jeez.
Yeah, it was cool.
-Really?
-It is a sock.
Is that really a sock?
-She has a sock on her hand.
-That's our youngest member.
-That's so cute.
-She's cute.
Gosh, not even a puppy could be this cute.
I'm Yuk Jun-seo.
-What?
-I'm Yuk Jun-seo.
Yuk, like numbers six, seven, eight, nine…
You know, I've never liked
the number six that much.
You think you'll get to go to Paradise?
Yeah.
-Really?
-Yeah.
It's all about confidence.
Are you done talking with everyone?
Not yet. I'm about to now.
Go on, then.
Come on, let's go.
Okay. Jeez.
Look how happy she is.
-She's so transparent.
-Yeah.
Min-seol said she'd stay here.
-But she's leaving after all.
-You're right.
-Gosh.
-Jeez.
She's like a little kid.
What?
What about me?
-It's the way you're smiling right now.
-Exactly.
-You were so down moments ago.
"Jeez!"
-Then, you put on lipstick.
-"Jeez!" Then, suddenly…
"This is kind of annoying."
I'll be back.
-Should we go to the back over there?
-Sure.
-Are you doing all right here?
-Totally.
-Really?
-I've adapted just fine.
You're always carrying
that bag around. It's so cute.
I look good with it too, right?
-Don't you think?
-Yeah. It's yours then.
I'll take that.
Thanks.
Are you still worried about me?
You think
I haven't been able to settle in?
A little bit.
I'm doing fine.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-It's just…
When we're hanging out,
I can tell what they're like.
I don't need to talk to someone
unless I'm curious about them.
Who are you curious about?
-My choices?
-Yeah.
The guys don't talk about this.
-Really?
-No, we don't talk.
I'm interested in you and Jong-hoon.
Jong-hoon?
So you're interested in him a bit?
Well…
I see.
The other person you want to
talk with is Jong-hoon?
No, not anymore.
So that's what you wanted to know.
Okay, I got it.
He asked me about Jong-hoon.
He asked what I thought of Jong-hoon.
Why did he want to know?
-What did you do yesterday?
-Yesterday?
I heard you drank whiskey.
We had dinner and drinks yesterday.
That's it.
-Really?
-Yeah.
We talked a little.
-You drank whiskey?
-Yeah.
-It was 80 proof.
-You promised to drink it with me.
It was whiskey.
But it wasn't Johnnie Walker.
-You didn't drink Johnnie Walker yet?
-No, it was something else.
-Honestly, I can't figure you out.
-Me?
We're headed towards the end,
but don't tell me.
Okay.
-Knowing would spoil things.
-True.
I guess everyone feels that way.
It must be nice to always go to Paradise.
-This will be your fourth time, right?
-Yeah.
Do you want to go to Paradise?
Of course, I do.
I've been saying that all along.
-Why?
-What?
Why?
It's fun, and you get more time
to talk and connect there than here.
-That's true.
-Yeah.
Okay, I got it.
Can I take this with me?
What on earth?
-That's all you wanted to talk about?
-Yeah.
You're no fun.
You… You only asked
what you wanted to know!
I mean, you…
What's with you? Fine, then.
Jun-seo?
I think he'll pick me.
He went with Si-an yesterday.
He wouldn't go with her again.
Shouldn't he go
one more time with me today?
If he doesn't end up picking me,
I'll be so embarrassed about this.
Si-an, where are you going?
Let's talk here.
And we're here.
Gosh.
Goodness.
It looks like your hair's curly again.
Yeah, I showered because I was so sweaty.
But I worked so hard to straighten it.
Right?
I didn't think they'd make us play
right at noon. We didn't even eat lunch.
It was impressive. I'll admit it.
-It was?
-Yeah, totally.
I admit it was cool.
Do you want to go again today?
-Do what you want.
-Yeah.
I will.
-I'm just asking.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Of course, I want to go.
Got it.
Jeez.
I'd…
Honestly, I'd like to go
with Jun-seo again.
I feel like something special
could happen if we go this time.
He asked Min-seol the same thing.
-Right.
-Yeah.
Whoever's not picked is bound to be upset,
whether it's Si-an or Min-seol.
With Min-seol, it was different.
He asked if she wanted to go
and just ended the conversation there.
That felt like he meant,
"Yeah, I'm taking you today."
But if he doesn't pick her, then…
It'd be awkward.
From her perspective, that would turn
Jun-seo into a bit of a jerk.
So I think he'll take Min-seol
with him to Paradise today.
But he had that conversation with Si-an.
She told him to do what he wants,
but she said she wants to go too.
If she didn't say that,
I think he'd pick Min-seol.
But Si-an was clear on that.
-Right.
-Exactly.
It feels like Jun-seo has no choice
but to pick Si-an now.
If Si-an was that clear
about wanting to go
but he ends up picking Min-seol,
Si-an might be a little shocked.
-Yes.
-Yeah.
But Jeong-su will probably take Si-an,
so she's destined to go
to Paradise anyway.
-True.
-It's a matter of who she'll go with.
Exactly.
I noticed earlier during the game,
you didn't look so good.
I was a bit worried.
Really?
I suddenly felt dizzy
and was a bit out of it.
We can't have you stay in the heat.
-But I'm okay.
-You should head to Paradise.
Gosh.
Are you going to pick me?
-Of course.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-I see.
"Of course."
-Of course.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-I see.
-Why?
-You don't want to go with someone else?
No. Did you think I would?
No, I didn't but…
I actually wanted to mention this.
Yeah.
Well…
-We just went to Paradise yesterday.
-Yeah.
-And don't take this the wrong way.
-Okay.
-But you got the chance to go again today.
-Right.
And the whole purpose
of going to Paradise is about…
-You know…
-Getting to know people?
-Yeah, it's honestly meant for us to…
-Right.
…get to know everyone a bit better.
Right.
So I was actually
going to bring this up today.
-Right. To not pick you?
-Earlier…
No, that's not it…
Is that the direct way to put it?
-Maybe you should go with someone else.
-With someone else?
Because that could help you see
if your feelings change.
Yeah.
Honestly, you never know, right?
-Really? You think so?
-Of course.
-You think they'll change?
-They could.
Or while you're there,
you could miss me so much
that I'd constantly be on your mind.
It could be a chance to figure that out.
Should I try that then?
Do whatever you'd like.
I'm just letting you know.
-It's just a suggestion.
-But…
What if I just choose you again?
Well, then…
I'd happily follow along.
-I see.
-Yeah.
I'd say, "Thank you"
and follow along.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Or you don't want to go?
No, that's not it.
-That isn't why at all.
-Okay.
-But I get it though.
-You do, right?
You haven't connected much
with anyone else.
-Right.
-The same goes for me.
We've only been talking to each other.
-And it's mostly been the two of us.
-True.
We don't have
many days left now until this ends.
I felt like if we let it end like this
without talking a lot with others,
it'd be disappointing.
-True.
-Yeah.
Is this a test?
How adorable.
This is why we thought he was so young.
-Exactly.
-He looks young too.
Is this a test?
-It's not a test.
-It's not?
You think it's a test?
How cute.
I thought it was a test.
-It wasn't.
-It wasn't?
-No.
-Okay, I get it.
But what if he actually goes
with someone else?
-She's encouraging him.
-Yes.
-What?
-It's with pure intentions.
-For real.
-She's trying to be considerate.
Isn't Ji-yeon being too relaxed
about Te-hwan?
No, I think she genuinely wants him
to get to know other people
without any ill intent.
-Because they went to Paradise yesterday.
-Yes.
But even though Ji-yeon said that,
if I were her,
I'd secretly hope deep down inside
that Te-hwan would still choose me.
-Right.
-But she doesn't want to pressure him.
-I'm so tired.
-Welcome back.
I'm so tired.
What if I can't go after all this?
What did you talk about? Is he taking you?
-To Paradise?
-Yeah.
With who?
-Jun-seo?
-Jun-seo.
He didn't say.
-Really?
We thought Jun-seo would tell you that.
That he'd take me?
-"Let's go. It's been a while."
-So, they had whiskey.
I asked him why he had whiskey without me.
And he likes Johnnie Walker.
He told me
he didn't have any Johnnie Walker.
So he said we should go
and have it next time.
Doesn't that mean he's taking you?
That's what he said,
but I still have no idea
what he'll actually do today.
Your choice might change
depending on who Jun-seo chooses.
It could.
I wonder who Jun-seo will pick.
I'm curious about his choice.
Right?
I think it'll be either Min-seol or Si-an.
But if Jun-seo picks Si-an,
who will Jeong-su choose?
-Jeong-su?
-Isn't it going to be Hae-lin?
The only connections he's had
are with Hae-lin and Hye-jin.
"Want to hang out with me again?"
-I think he'll pick Hae-lin.
-It won't be Hye-jin.
-Hae-lin?
-I agree.
-Hae-lin.
-I think it'll be Hae-lin.
Yes.
-I'm most curious about Jun-seo's choice.
-Exactly. It's important.
Now, we're going to match the couples
who will go on a date in Paradise.
The winners of the men's game
who earned dates in Paradise,
Yuk Jun-seo, Kim Jeong-su,
and Kim Te-hwan.
Please come outside.
-Have fun.
Thank you.
Go and enjoy yourself.
Let us know what kind
of good food you had tomorrow.
-Okay. I'll go and relax.
-Bye.
-See you later.
Yeah, see you tomorrow.
Let's go, first-place winner Yuk Jun-seo.
Let's go.
I wonder who he'll pick.
I put a lot of effort
into packing my bags.
But if I end up staying behind…
No, you're 100% going.
You think so?
I'm going to end up
alone in our room today!
We'll begin with first-place winner,
Yuk Jun-seo.
Please choose the person you'd like to
go on a date with in Paradise.
Lee Si-an,
who I went to Paradise with yesterday,
and Kim Min-seol
are the two people I'm torn between.
The person I'd like to go
to Paradise with is…
Yuk Jun-seo has selected…
I keep biting my nails.
I think it'll be Min-seol.
Min-seol. I think it'll be her.
-My heart is racing.
-It's Min-seol.
Have fun.
I think Min-seol will be the one going.
Yeah, Si-an went yesterday.
-Right.
-Yeah.
The person I'd like to go
to Paradise with is…
Is he going to double down?
Will he go with Si-an?
No way.
Yuk Jun-seo has selected…
The person I'd like to go
to Paradise with is…
Lee Si-an.
Let's go.
-We're going right away?
-Yeah.
All right.
I want to talk.
You two should go then.
NEXT EPISODE
I thought the sun was going to rise.
I almost went to bed.
This is really nerve-racking
and mentally exhausting.
I've wanted to go to Paradise with you.
What? Do you want to go today?
Let's go together.
You're so popular.
It makes me worried.
I've said everything I needed to say.
What's going on?
This is insane.
Hi.
Something's a little different.
Just a little bit.
What? Was he flirting?
But it's a bit a bit crooked… Hey.
-Hey, think it through before you act.
-Jun-seo.
Can't you treat me a bit more kindly?
I don't want you to feel pressured.
But I do want you to think of me.
It's been weighing on my mind.
You miss Si-an, don't you?
Hi, Si-an.
As I get to know Theo more,
I see how sincere he is.
Am I doing something wrong here?
This confusion I'm feeling…
I'm not going crazy, am I?
Subtitle translation by: Hye Min Eom