♫ The dusk awakens ♫
♫ The slumber of the whales ♫
♫ Swimming towards the galaxy ♫
♫ It docks at the blue shore of my heart ♫
♫ I hear the poems coming from afar ♫
♫ Happiness and sorrow come and go ♫
♫ As my memories dance along the clouds ♫
♫ I still remember ♫
♫ Please wait for me at the horizon ♫
♫ We'll watch the sunset together ♫
♫ Whose dream hasn't been beautiful ♫
♫ When have I ever been myself ♫
♫ Wait for me at the end of the daydream ♫
♫ Who has wandered within it ♫
♫ Life is nothing more than fantasy ♫
♫ I am still me ♫
[You Are Desire]
[Episode 26 We Are All By Your Side]
Fu Mingxiu.
Let's go.
Come on.
Mr. Fu.
When you gave me the gashapon before,
you said we could have a meal
and play with gashapon together.
Is that still valid?
It is.
Actually,
I asked Lin Yujing to ask you out for me.
We can climb mountains and have a meal.
Just be direct
I'll say it directly.
Mr. Fu.
I like you, so I want to chase you.
Are you okay?
I can do it myself.
You don't need to be shy. I'll help you down.
I'm not shy. I can do it myself.
Ruyi.
I've been texting you, but you never replied.
I thought you were still angry with me.
Why are you suddenly here?
- I--
- I don't mean you shouldn't come.
I mean,
if you have something, I can go to you.
I'm not angry.
I've been thinking about the things between us.
I need to say something to you in person.
You always came
to my school to find me.
Today it's my turn to come to find you.
I also want to see your usual life
and study environment.
And your experimental field
where you grow small tomatoes.
I'll show it to you.
Was it hot in the bus?
It's fine.
Over here.
Be careful.
I'm responsible for this place.
This is where you plant tomatoes?
Yes.
Can you plant other things here?
Yes, the soil has been fertilized.
You can plant whatever you want.
They are sunflower seeds.
I want
to plant them with you.
Okay, let's do it together.
Okay.
I'll dig the soil, and you plant the seeds.
Don't get your hands dirty.
It's okay.
I used to live in the countryside.
There was a large sunflower field
in the backyard.
I often took sunflower seeds
to eat.
- There's one last one.
- Okay.
Ruyi, I really shouldn't have lied
to you.
Look at these seedlings.
Although they are the same type,
because of different growing environments,
the fruits they produce are different.
We're the same.
We grew up in different places,
and our ways and thoughts are different.
This is normal
and hard to change.
I've been thinking a lot these days.
We can't remove these differences,
but,
can't we find a middle ground?
In that way, you're comfortable,
and I won't feel so awkward.
It might take a while to work out.
However,
I want to give it a try.
Deal.
Ruyi.
Don't worry.
I will take good care of these sunflowers
and you.
Shen Juan.
I'm done. You can come in.
Good night.
Can't sleep?
The sound of the waves is loud.
Morning.
Let's go.
To watch the sunrise.
Actually,
I never looked forward
to seeing the sunrise before.
I thought every day's sunrise was the same.
There's no difference.
Now I'm looking at you.
You have a grand dream.
It seems like
you're a little closer
to your dream day by day.
This feeling is particularly beautiful.
You know what?
After you talked with my mom,
it actually had a big impact on her.
She completely changed her view of you
and me.
All of a sudden, she let go of me.
Let me choose the path
I want to take.
I've been
looking forward to it.
But when it really happens,
I suddenly felt a bit empty inside,
because I don't know what to do
and what I want to be.
It seems like
I've never really thought about it.
Being confused is a stage
we must go through in life.
I will feel frustrated and bad,
But I won't give up like I used to.
Do you remember
what you said the first time you talked
to me about shooting?
No matter what happens,
go for what you love,
and strive for what you want.
Whatever the result is,
don't be afraid
or escape.
Now,
I want to repeat it to you.
Don't be scared.
I'll always be by your side.
♫ Please wait for me when the day breaks ♫
♫ Let's watch the fireflies together ♫
♫ Who's memory has been brushed by the breeze ♫
♫ You come to awaken me ♫
Just like the sunrise,
the night is just a process.
The sun
will always rise.
No matter what happens in the future,
I will make myself more determined and brave.
I will always be with you.
Handmade Workshop.
I drew it myself.
When I watched the competition before,
I noticed many contestants
had their own patterns on their guns,
but you didn't have.
So I've been wanting to make it with you
It's embed on your gun
to accompany you in every competition.
I tried my best,
but I still failed.
It's okay.
How is it?
You're quite amazing.
You made it better.
Let me polish it a bit.
Wait a minute.
I want to add something else.
Is it okay?
I'm a bit hungry.
What do you want to eat?
Let me think.
Shen Juan.
The school has figured things out.
Starting from tomorrow,
you can return to the team for training.
Thank you, Coach Lei.
What's wrong?
I can go back to the team for training.
Really?
See, your effort pays off.
Hurry! Hurry!
Shen Juan is vindicated
and is resuming training today.
You guys stand closer later,
and I'll hide behind you.
When he comes, I'll set off the firecracker
to celebrate for him.
Stop what you're doing.
He's already here.
Shen Juan, why did you come so early?
My surprise is wasted.
What surprise?
Well,
at least your surprise wasn't prepared in vain.
This is not a surprise at all.
It's a fright.
Don't regret missing
the provincial team's training this time.
Keep up the good work,
and there will be more opportunities
in the future.
Here. Hurry up!
Clean up the confetti over there.
Gather around, everyone.
The training starts now.
Mr. Fu, I like you. I want to pursue you.
Are you okay?
[University Student]
[Mr. Fu, how's your foot?]
[Is it still hurting?]
[I'm serious about what I said.]
[I hope you can…]
Are you free now?
Can we meet up?
Sure.
See you later.
Okay, bye.
What's up? Whose call is it?
Mr. Fu's.
That's good!
He took the initiative to contact you.
What's the situation between you two now?
I…
I confessed to him when
we climbed the mountain the other day.
You confessed?
That's so you.
So, how did it go? How did he react?
Did he agree?
He was very shocked.
And then,
he sprained his ankle.
He sprained his ankle?
Did you scare him by being too straightforward?
But I have to admire your progress.
With my respect!
I just blurted it out that day out of impulse.
He just asked me to meet up.
He probably wants to talk about this.
I'm not sure if he'll refuse
or agree.
Go for it!
I will.
You must be Shen Juan.
And you are…
I am Feng Li.
A friend of your uncle.
Sorry for my sudden visit.
I just returned from abroad.
I saw the report on
the Daydreamer Silverware Exhibition online.
So, I checked the information and came here.
I'm not only your uncle's friend,
but also his senior.
Although I'm only one year ahead of him,
I've always regarded him as a role model
in terms of artistic creation.
This bracelet is your uncle's work
that won the New Talent Design Award.
He was only a sophomore then.
And he was the youngest winner in history.
So, the school made an exception
and put his work on the school's magazine cover
which only features works of
well-known teachers.
To be honest,
seeing you organize an exhibition for him,
I'm really happy.
We share the same thoughts.
Qinghe's talent deserves
to be seen by more people.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Anyone who has seen his work
will definitely appreciate him.
I'm here for that reason too.
I hope you can authorize Qinghe's design
to my company,
Lifeng Jewelry.
I will not let your uncle's hard work
go to waste.
My company has been operating abroad for years.
Last year we held a brand exhibition in Europe,
which received a positive response
in the industry.
We want to seize this opportunity
to enter the domestic market.
We have sophisticated
industrial production equipment
and rich brand marketing experience.
We believe we can successfully
promote Qinghe's design.
If you're willing to cooperate,
I will treat your uncle's work with care.
Although he's gone forever,
his works deserve to be passed on
and let more people appreciate them.
Thank you so much
for appreciating my uncle's works,
but I can't cooperate with you.
[Feng Li]
Not only will we promote Qinghe Silverware,
but we will also offer you favorable terms.
It's not about the terms.
Look at this bracelet.
Every tiny detail has hidden patterns.
I can imagine
how much time my uncle spent
polishing and forging it
to make it shine like this.
My uncle's works are friends of time.
They cannot be replaced by industrial machines.
You don't have to worry about that.
If my production process
can't meet the requirements,
I wouldn't have come to you.
Rest assured.
I won't change a single bit of his design,
and will try my best to restore it.
But the spirit of my uncle's works
can't be restored.
He spent his whole life focusing on handmade,
giving each piece a unique meaning.
I don't want to go against his will.
Okay, then.
But I still hope you can reconsider.
Okay.
Mr. Huang,
that brat is too stubborn.
Let's proceed with our backup plan.
Mr. Fu,
you came here so early.
I'm used to arriving early.
Are you ready to accept my confession?
Gu,
based on your previous confession,
I collected some related information
and did some case analysis.
Here's the feasibility analysis of us dating.
First, here's a bar chart
showing our daily time distribution.
As shown in the chart,
your free time is mostly between
eleven to one in the afternoon,
four to five in the afternoon,
and after eight at night.
But usually at these times,
I'm in meetings, in court,
or working overtime.
So, our overlapping time is very little.
If there's no time,
we can make some time for each other.
Besides, true love isn't related to
having free time or not.
And this one.
In the next four years,
our life plans are
completely different.
Different stages of life will cause
our common topics to decrease.
And we might even have
conflict in values.
So your conclusion is
workers can only date workers,
while students can only date students.
Otherwise, their relationship
won't last long, right?
Do you have data to support your conclusion?
Sure. Look.
I did some case analysis.
Uh, these are the analysis of
the age difference and the success rate of
long-distance relationships. Look.
The age difference
with the highest success rate is
between three to five years.
On the contrary, the bigger the age difference,
the more likely
irreconcilable conflicts will arise.
You went to all this trouble
just to tell me that
we're not a good match?
Do you have other evidence?
I-I think, for now,
you should focus more on your studies.
And I'm not quite clear
about relationships,
so I can't make a decision rashly.
Otherwise, it would be irresponsible to you.
But you even made a slides.
You're quite serious.
Do you have anything else…
What's wrong?
Calm down. Wait for me at the office.
I'll be right over.
Lin Yujing needs me. Let's…
Let's talk about our matter some other time.
I'm leaving now.
This way, please.
Let me introduce myself.
I am Huang Yuming.
Do you have any questions about
the lawyer's letter that I sent you?
I can answer them.
Shouldn't you explain to me first?
What does this lawyer's letter mean?
The Galaxy Bird
is my master's work.
How did it become your client's
intellectual property?
Mr. Nie, don't rush.
Let's take it step by step.
Take a look at this.
Mr. Nie, is this Galaxy Bird silverware
a product of your online store?
You already know the answer.
On the Galaxy Bird's product details page,
the designer is written as
Luo Qinghe.
That is, your uncle.
Is that correct?
Yes.
Good.
Then please look at this document.
My client, Mr. Feng Li,
owns the intellectual property of
this Hanhaiji series design.
And according to the verification,
the Galaxy Bird of Mr. Nie's online store
is 95% similar
to my client's design.
So it has constituted patent infringement.
Mr. Shen,
you're the inheritor of Qinghe Silverware.
You also admitted that
the design of Galaxy Bird
comes from Luo Qinghe.
So we can confirm that
the plagiarism also comes from
the late designer Luo Qinghe.
What nonsense are you talking about?
I watched my master design
the Galaxy Bird with my own eyes.
How could it be plagiarism?
You must have stolen his design!
Mr. Nie,
only the evidence can determine
who is the real plagiarist,
not your memory.
I opened the online store.
I made those silverwares
and sold them.
It has nothing to do with Shen Juan.
Let him go. I'll talk to you.
Mr. Shen,
design is the soul of artwork.
And after such an incident,
my client is very angry.
Before I came, he instructed me that
I must pursue this matter and find a solution.
But during the process of
applying for the patent for Hanhaiji,
my uncle became a vegetable
due to a car accident.
Until his death, he never woke up.
Now, please tell me,
how could my uncle plagiarize
Mr. Feng, they…
It's okay. You may leave now.
I'll handle this.
Okay.
Come on. Sit.
I can explain this matter.
Before your uncle had that accident,
I had been to Qinghe Silverware
to visit your uncle.
That day, I was carrying my design album,
and I got a bit drunk.
I know Qinghe didn't mean to steal my design.
The deceased is gone.
I don't want to comment on this matter anymore.
You don't want to?
But haven't you said enough?
You're just distorting the fact
because my master
can't expose your lies anymore.
You said you visited my uncle?
When?
April 19th.
That was the last time I saw him.
You know what I want.
It was supposed to be a win-win situation.
But now, not only will others be involved,
your uncle's reputation will also be affected.
But as long as you change your mind,
we can still talk about cooperation.
I will not cooperate with you.
A person as despicable as you
will only tarnish my uncle's work.
One should not act on impulse.
Mr. Huang already showed you the evidence.
I'm in control.
With a little manipulation in public opinion,
even without a full lawsuit,
your uncle's reputation will be ruined.
I will give you two more days.
This is the last chance.
Mr. Feng,
I guess they won't agree so easily.
Should I release some news
to give them some pressure?
Yeah. Go ahead.
Okay.
Hello?
What's wrong?
It's only been a few years
and you already can't recognize me?
Feng Li!
Qinghe!
Come in!
You really haven't changed at all.
Let's have a drink.
Feng Li, I really can't drink,
I get drunk easily.
Qinghe?
You're so bad at this.
Come on. Let me help you.
Here. Sit still.
Don't fall.
Qinghe?
Shen Juan,
you'd better explain.
What is the cooperation
Feng Li mentioned earlier?
He plans to mass-produce
my uncle's design drafts.
He came to me for authorization before.
I did not agree.
So, he came up with another plan
to threaten me.
So,
he got this chance because
I sold the Galaxy Bird online.
You don't need to worry about this.
I will take responsibility for my actions.
I will explain it to them.
How?
Can't you see?
Feng Li is targeting me.
I will handle the rest.
Whether it's my uncle's reputation
or his design,
I will keep them intact.
Don't interfere.
Why?
Why should you bear
the consequences of my actions?
It's just like before.
I don't even have the right
to take responsibility on my own.
You just take over everything. Everything!
Nie Xinghe,
you don't understand my uncle at all.
If my uncle were still alive
and knew what you are like now,
he would be very disappointed.
I noticed you've changed.
You've become more cheerful.
You've become more easy-going.
And you're no longer alone.
I spotted you instantly in the crowd,
shining so brightly that you lit up everyone.
So, I won't allow any darkness to engulf you.
I won't let any bad guys harm you.
I will protect you.
♫ Love sprouts in my palm ♫
♫ Yet worried linger within my eyes ♫
♫ Our story hasn't ended ♫
♫ So where are we now ♫
♫ I want to hug you so badly ♫
♫ I want to become better with you ♫
♫ The youth we shared ♫
♫ Turned into a rainbow within my heart ♫
♫ I really want to warm you ♫
♫ I want to share with you ♫
♫ The beauty of the world ♫
♫ We promised ♫
♫ To never be apart ♫
♫ Do you want to hear me sing ♫
♫ The wind chime swaying in my heart ♫
♫ Is a wish ♫
♫ I secretly made for you ♫
♫ I want to plant ♫
♫ A red maple forest ♫
♫ To dye the whole mountain red ♫
♫ The sky after the rain ♫
♫ Was painted by our brilliant dreams ♫
♫ Time is a flower of dream ♫
♫ You've already collected it ♫
♫ When we all become better ♫
♫ We'll see the best of the world together ♫