♫ The dusk awakens ♫
♫ The slumber of the whales ♫
♫ Swimming towards the galaxy ♫
♫ It docks at the blue shore of my heart ♫
♫ I hear the poems coming from afar ♫
♫ Happiness and sorrow come and go ♫
♫ As my memories dance along the clouds ♫
♫ I still remember ♫
♫ Please wait for me at the horizon ♫
♫ We'll watch the sunset together ♫
♫ Whose dream hasn't been beautiful ♫
♫ When have I ever been myself ♫
♫ Wait for me at the end of the daydream ♫
♫ Who has wandered within it ♫
♫ Life is nothing more than fantasy ♫
♫ I am still me ♫
[You Are Desire]
[Episode 25 I Follow My Own Path]
After doing so many bad things,
you have the audacity to put this photo
on the table.
I understand now.
Shen Juan himself doesn't dare to face me,
so he found you
to stand up for him.
You're overthinking.
Shen Juan doesn't even know about this.
I came here
because we still have an old score to settle.
You sent the disciplinary notice
of Shen Juan to my mom, right?
What were you playing at?
I was just trying to help.
I kindly reminded your mom
to see clearly as soon as possible
the kind of person her daughter was dating
so that she would not be deceived
or see her own daughter sinking into misery.
Shen Juan is upright and innocent.
I know him best.
I don't need you to distort the truth.
As for you, you're like a rat in the sewer,
only capable of doing bad things
behind people's backs. How disgusting.
Shen Juan is upright and innocent.
Then who was the one who killed my master?
And who was the one who hit me?
I told everyone what he did.
What did I do wrong?
I grew up
with my uncle,
and he was the most important person to me.
Back in the day,
in order to rush
to see my shooting competition,
he had a car accident
and became a vegetable.
In the end, I found out that this accident
was related to a person.
So I lost control and hit him.
In other words, under extreme emotions,
you do have overreactions.
Yes.
I admit I didn't control my emotions well,
but it only happened once.
You're honest.
But how can you guarantee
it won't happen again?
After all, firearms are involved.
The risk is quite high.
I've overcome my negative emotions.
When my uncle passed away,
I didn't get angry
or feel rage
or despair.
It was because of someone
I'd met.
When I once gave up on myself,
she ignored my resistance
and pulled me out of my downfall.
It was she who showed me
there were still many people caring about me
and many things
worth cherishing.
So why did you leave the shooting team
and then return to it?
Because at that time I thought
it was my persistence in shooting
that caused my uncle's car accident.
I didn't have the face
to pick up the gun again.
But the person I just mentioned
let me know that in fact, my uncle
had always been supporting me
to continue shooting.
So I came back.
It's that simple?
Yes.
You should be clear about what you have done.
You're unable to face it,
so you want to blame everything on Shen Juan.
You suffer
and also drag Shen Juan down with you.
When I see you, I think of a saying,
hateful people
do indeed have pitiful aspects.
Pity me?
Pity Shen Juan first.
The person who was suspended
and expelled from the provincial team
is not me.
But in the end, Shen Juan deserved it.
People should not do wrong things.
If they do, they should pay the price.
That is correct.
If a person does something wrong,
they must bear the consequences.
May I ask if this is Mr. Nie Xinghe?
It's me.
Shooting itself
has nothing to do with dangerous violence.
On the contrary, it requires
a very stable psychological state.
If a person
is not stable or calm,
then they definitely can't hit the target.
If there's something wrong
with my mental health,
the rapid-fire team wouldn't give me a chance.
Rapid-fire is my dream,
and it's my promise to those who care about me.
Please give me one chance.
I've already wasted
the most precious four years.
I don't want to waste another minute or second.
I think this young man is not bad.
- What?
- After verification,
you indeed did not provide
trademark use authorization.
Please promptly submit the information,
or we will close your online store
within 48 hours.
You did it,
right?
So what?
Didn't you just say that?
After people make mistakes,
they have to bear the consequences.
Besides,
Shen Juan is the rightful heir of Luo Qinghe.
Without his permission,
what right do you have
to register the trademark?
This trademark was my master's.
How can you judge my relationship
with my master?
Then what right do you have
to meddle in my relationship with my mother?
Does Shen Juan know
what you're doing?
That's exactly what I intended.
Qinghe Silverware is my master's store.
What right do you have to deprive me
of reopening it?
For your shooting career,
you just shut down the store.
If I hadn't bought
the store,
my master's hard work
would have been long gone.
If my uncle was still alive,
would you dare to tell him what you've done?
His wish
wasn't that we inherited the silverware store
but that we pursued our dreams.
He was kind all his life.
He drew inspiration
from the beauty of the world.
But what you're doing now
is completely against his will.
You're not worthy of being his disciple,
using his designs,
let alone inheriting
the Qinghe Silverware trademark.
If you still consider yourself his disciple,
I advise you to get back on track.
Let's go.
After this incident,
Nie Xinghe would stop causing us trouble,
right?
The online store is closed,
and he'll have a lot of things to deal with.
I guess he'd calm down a bit during this time.
Go back.
What are you going to do about the suspension?
I'll wait for the school's notice.
I've said everything
that needs to be said at the meeting.
You've had it tough too,
having to take care of your mom
and also worrying about me.
Didn't we agree to face everything together?
My mom will be discharged soon.
I'll have some time.
Shall we go relax ourselves?
Okay.
[Inpatient Department]
I'll go with you.
You just wait here.
I'll put the stuff in the car
and come pick you up.
The car I ordered is downstairs.
I've visited the hotel
where your mom will stay,
and the place is good.
It's great to have you here.
- Let's go.
Mom, Mr. Cui has already booked
your ticket back to Huaicheng.
He will come to pick you up.
I know.
Stop tidying up and come here.
I want to talk to you.
I saw Shen Juan
at the hospital today.
I know the reason
my previous check-ups went so smoothly
was because he made a medical appointment early
and it helped a lot.
I used to
have a bad opinion of Shen Juan.
Unexpectedly,
he doesn't evade when faced with problems
and is so resolute.
Those comments about him
on the Internet are rumors,
mostly misunderstandings.
If you get to know him a bit more,
you'll actually find
he's a really good person.
Yes,
he's more responsible than Meng Weiguo.
I was at your age too
when I met Meng Weiguo.
At that time,
I was a naive freshman.
And
because I was shallow,
I was attracted by his appearance.
Back then, I brought Meng Weiguo
to meet your grandfather.
He didn't agree with us being together,
but I insisted.
I was silly.
I thought that for him,
even if I lost the whole world,
that was what love is.
Later, we got married.
I was extremely busy with work every day,
pressuring myself a lot.
I thought he would support me.
Unexpectedly,
he was totally lost in his fantasy
of being a writer.
He thought I was vulgar.
We couldn't communicate at all.
After getting married,
Meng Weiguo
never walked up to your grandfather
to say
he loved me
and would strive for our future.
But Shen Juan is different.
He came up to me,
saying he would give you a future.
The you in his eyes
and the you I know
are completely different.
He said that you had a lot of ideas,
and when faced with problems,
you always shouldered them yourself,
never asking for help.
That was the moment I realized
that you had grown up.
Yu.
I used to think
that you were still a child.
I was afraid that you'd be fooled,
so I arranged everything for you.
Now, I can finally rest assured.
I was overthinking.
You've grown up.
It's time for me to let go.
From now on,
I won't meddle in your affairs.
I hope
you can think carefully
about which path to take
in the future.
Mom,
I will think
about my future carefully.
This is a gift for the Guan family.
Thank Meng Weiguo for me.
I've settled my debts with him.
No matter how you get on with him,
it's up to you.
Mom,
can I give you a hug?
you're the most important person
in the world to me.
I will surely work hard in the future.
You take care of yourself.
You can argue with me
and scold me,
but,
I can't loss you.
Take care of yourself.
I'm leaving.
Go back.
When we're free,
we can have meals
and even open gashapon together.
You're back.
Lin Yujing.
I have something to ask you.
What is it?
Well,
what is your brother's favorite food?
As far as I know, he's not picky.
Does he have any hobbies?
He always works,
without particular hobbies.
Is he that boring?
Has he ever mentioned where he wants to go?
Gu Xia,
how much information are you trying
to get out of me for free?
Please.
For me?
Didn't you say when I want information,
I have to treat you well?
You have to make me happy.
After that, I can help you.
Okay, this beverage is for you.
I'll buy you nice snacks later.
Can you help me now?
Let me think about it.
- Fine.
- You're going to call him?
Right now?
It's answered.
Brother.
My mom went back to Huaicheng today.
Will you be at home tomorrow?
Can I see you at home?
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Bye.
Lin Yujing.
You did that on purpose.
Coming.
- Yujing.
- Aunt Guan.
Come in.
Give me your backpack.
Thank you.
Aunt Guan, this is a gift from my mom.
Thank you for helping to find the doctor,
and my brother also helped a lot.
I really appreciate it.
We're family.
No need of the formality.
Where's my dad?
He's cooking in the kitchen.
He used to just give orders,
but today he's cooking himself.
You should eat more later.
Brother.
Gu Xia let me say hello for her.
Alright,
but why do you give me that look?
Nothing.
I wonder what you're thinking.
What do you mean
by that?
If you have nothing to talk about,
you get some air here.
I have things to do.
No, I haven't finished yet.
If you want to ask Gu Xia out,
you have to seize the opportunity.
Now is a good time.
What do you mean?
Why would I ask her out?
Gu Xia is popular
at school.
If you don't seize the opportunity now,
there won't be one in the future.
What does it have to do with me?
When are you free lately?
Why?
You just did me a big favor
when my mom was ill.
I want to treat you to a meal.
I'm glad to hear that.
Okay, just let me know when you're free.
Deal.
Mingxiu, Yujing.
Dinner is ready.
Okay.
- Give it to me.
- You stay out of this.
You sit.
Mingxiu, your coffee is good.
You make us some coffee.
Okay.
Yujing, I'll go and get you some fruit.
- Thank you.
- You're so kind.
Dad,
I have something to tell you.
This room has been kept for you,
and nothing has been moved.
Dad,
thank you.
If it weren't for you finding Dr. He,
my mom's surgery
wouldn't have gone so smoothly.
Actually, I didn't do much.
Dr. He is a friend
of your Aunt Guan.
She helped me because of you.
My mom wanted me
to thank you on her behalf.
She never changes.
When thanking me,
she needs you to relay the message.
She also said
you two are even.
Dad,
shouldn't we
move on too?
By the way,
I opened a bank account for you.
The password is your birthday.
There are many expenses in college.
Rest assured, this is my secret money.
You still can't forgive me?
Well,
if there was anything I did wrong before,
I will apologize to you.
Take it.
Dad,
I'm not short of money now.
In fact,
I also did wrong in the past.
I had my issues.
I won't repeat them.
I promise I will come home more often.
Alright?
Yujing.
Coming.
If you want to eat anything,
tell me in advance.
I will cook for you.
Okay. Let's go.
Hello, my name is He Songnan.
I'm Xu Ruyi's boyfriend.
Well, let's not talk here.
Let's go in first.
- Okay.
- Sure.
We will go in first.
Okay.
I'm sorry to cost tonight.
Well,
this place looks expensive.
I'm nice to your roommates,
so if anything happens to you,
they can inform me.
And I get a discount at this restaurant.
Don't worry. It won't cost me much.
Well, alright.
Then let's split the bill.
Is that okay?
Okay, no problem.
Let's go in then.
Sure.
We had a great time today.
Thank you for the dinner.
You're welcome, and I should thank you
for taking care of Ruyi.
Don't worry.
We will take good care of Ruyi for you.
We won't disturb you anymore.
Bye.
Why did you pay the bill by yourself just now?
How much was it?
Only 355 for four people?
Right, it's not expensive.
I'll transfer money to you.
We agreed to split it.
No rush.
I'll see you every weekend from now on,
and you can treat me to a milk tea each time.
You can pay me back slowly.
Well, alright.
I have to go.
Okay.
He's so handsome. I think he's a good man.
She's back.
Ask her.
After our unanimous review,
your boyfriend has passed our test.
He's reliable and considerate.
He's very attentive to you.
And he's generous.
It's hard
to find such a good boyfriend.
The food was really delicious.
I've been wanting to try it.
It's too expensive.
After we ordered so many dishes,
your boyfriend didn't even frown.
He's really a good person.
That restaurant has a group discount.
If you want, we can eat again.
Group discount?
Impossible.
I've been following that restaurant.
There's no such group discount.
Hello.
May I ask how much the table ten
spent?
I just found out
that today's meal cost you 1355.
I'm sorry for costing you so much.
I'll transfer 500 to you first.
As for the rest of money,
I'll transfer it to you
when I get my part-time job wages.
Ruyi,
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to deceive you.
I didn't expect
this meal would cost you so much.
I chose this restaurant,
and tonight was my treat.
I'm your boyfriend. That's what I should do.
We agreed to split the bill before,
so you must accept my money.
Okay.
I know I shouldn't lie to her.
I apologized to her.
Even if she argues with me
or scolds me, that's okay.
But she apologized first.
What does it mean
for us to apologize to each other?
Why are you not speaking?
Whatever you want to say, just say it to me.
I'm listening.
I'm not worried to argue,
but I'm just afraid she gets silent.
She keeps everything in her heart.
I don't even know what she's thinking.
I'm telling you.
Since you like her
and want to be with her,
you have to put yourself in her shoes.
You two should try to understand each other.
Got it?
Come on.
I'm back.
What are you doing?
You want to hang out?
I want to hang out
with Shen Juan on the weekend.
This is your first time
hanging out together, right?
You should pick a fun place.
I know a restaurant
on top of a mountain outside the city.
I'll send you the location.
The scenery there is really good.
You can see the entire cityscape.
It's very romantic.
Did you receive it?
It's pretty romantic,
but I want to find a place
where you can shop and play.
A place to shop and play…
How about this one?
Nanfeng Island. I've been there before.
It's convenient to get there from Pucheng.
There's a really artistic street
full of craft workshops and pottery galleries.
Look, it's perfect for couples.
Looks nice.
We'll go here. Thanks for your recommendation.
Let me give you a surprise.
What surprise?
I got you snacks.
You grab the opportunity.
No problem.
Mr. Fu.
What a coincidence.
You're also here to climb the mountain?
Why are you here?
Are you waiting for someone?
It's already late.
Got stood up, huh?
Don't be silly.
I can't make it. I have something else to do.
This restaurant is hard to book.
You eat by yourself.
I don't mind if someone wants
to climb the mountain with me.
I'll climb alone.
Okay.
I'll follow behind you.
We've met now.
The rest is up to you.
Why didn't you
answer your brother's call just now?
A good helper knows
when to appear
and when not to.
I'm sorry.
There's a problem with our system.
The room you booked is already occupied,
and we have no other empty rooms.
The island is hosting a tourism festival,
so a lot of travelers is rushing in.
All the hotels on the island are full.
I'm really sorry.
So, should we go back?
However, there is a tent
on the beach.
If you don't mind,
I'll let you stay for free
and notify you when there's a room tomorrow.
Only one tent?
Lin Yujing didn't tell me
I have to climb the mountain for dinner?
It's okay. There's a good restaurant
on top of the mountain.
Lin Yujing
should have come with me.
Luckily, she didn't come today,
or, we wouldn't be able to make it.
You guys just lack exercise.
Look.
The old couple ahead
are climbing faster than you.
Mr. Fu.
I'm really tired.
Can't climb any more.
Then I'll hold you.
Fine.
My legs are about to break.
I won't be able to walk tomorrow.
You sure your legs are about to break?
Hi, do you want to buy a love lock?
It helps fulfill your wishes.
Lovers who hang love locks
will be together forever.
We are not a couple.
We're just climbing the mountain together.
I see.
You two can buy a lock together.
How much is it? I'll buy it.
100 yuan.
Done.
Thank you.
Just make one wish. It works.
It's not just for couples.
Write down your wish.
Aren't you going to hang one?
I haven't thought about what wish to make.
I'll hang it later.
The restaurant at the top
of the mountain is pretty good.
I'm too tired.
If I don't eat anything, I can't climb down.
I've made a reservation in that restaurant.
Thanks for your treat.
[Fu Mingxiu, Gu Xia]
I'll find another place to sleep tonight?
No, since we came out together,
let's do things together.
This tent has enough room for two people.
Let's go and play.
I used to love the night,
sitting alone quietly
and polishing the silver ornament.
I throw away worries in the past.
Now that I have you,
I prefer to see the light.
I take you to watch the sunrise,
seeing the sun rising from the sea.
It looks as shining
as our future.
♫ Love sprouts in my palm ♫
♫ Yet worried linger within my eyes ♫
♫ Our story hasn't ended ♫
♫ So where are we now ♫
♫ I want to hug you so badly ♫
♫ I want to become better with you ♫
♫ The youth we shared ♫
♫ Turned into a rainbow within my heart ♫
♫ I really want to warm you ♫
♫ I want to share with you ♫
♫ The beauty of the world ♫
♫ We promised ♫
♫ To never be apart ♫
♫ Do you want to hear me sing ♫
♫ The wind chime swaying in my heart ♫
♫ Is a wish ♫
♫ I secretly made for you ♫
♫ I want to plant ♫
♫ A red maple forest ♫
♫ To dye the whole mountain red ♫
♫ The sky after the rain ♫
♫ Was painted by our brilliant dreams ♫
♫ Time is a flower of dream ♫
♫ You've already collected it ♫
♫ When we all become better ♫
♫ We'll see the best of the world together ♫