♫ The dusk awakens ♫
♫ The slumber of the whales ♫
♫ Swimming towards the galaxy ♫
♫ It docks at the blue shore of my heart ♫
♫ I hear the poems coming from afar ♫
♫ Happiness and sorrow come and go ♫
♫ As my memories dance along the clouds ♫
♫ I still remember ♫
♫ Please wait for me at the horizon ♫
♫ We'll watch the sunset together ♫
♫ Whose dream hasn't been beautiful ♫
♫ When have I ever been myself ♫
♫ Wait for me at the end of the daydream ♫
♫ Who has wandered within it ♫
♫ Life is nothing more than fantasy ♫
♫ I am still me ♫
[You Are Desire]
[Episode 23 We Will Not Break Up]
Hello. I'm Shen Juan. I'm Lin--
I know who you are.
- You break up with her.
- I can't.
So, I hope
you can consider it
think more for her,
and accept her request.
Ms. Lin.
I've said all I wanted to say.
Hope you will be well soon.
Well,
I rushed back without eating anything.
I'm hungry.
Let's go grab some food.
Doesn't your leaving affect your training?
No problem.
I've asked for leave from Coach Lei.
Don't worry.
Everything will get better.
You're already doing great.
In fact,
I didn't tell you about my mom's illness
not just because you have a competition.
I've been used to doing things alone
since I was young.
I don't want to rely on
or be a burden to anyone.
But when my mom is sick,
I found out that everyone cares about
and takes care of me,
including my brother
and you.
So I think I should try
to share with you what's on my mind
and open my heart
slowly.
I understand.
It's okay.
Take your time.
Actually, at first,
when I heard about your mom's illness,
I didn't know what to do.
I rushed back in a panic.
I didn't expect
your mom's misunderstanding of me is deep.
All misunderstandings will be cleared up.
I won't break up with you.
We make a deal.
No matter what difficulties we encounter,
we will face them together.
Let's eat.
I understand
the pain of helplessness
after losing a loved one.
I've done everything I can.
I have no choice.
I can do anything for you.
I just want you to be healthy.
Because she loves you
and doesn't want to lose you.
My surgery…
When is it scheduled?
I'll go ask the doctor right now.
Didn't I tell you to go back for a rest?
Why did you buy so many things again?
I have experience with caregiving.
I bought something for your mom.
I have good news for you.
My mom agreed to the surgery.
You don't have to worry anymore.
Anyway, I can take good care of her.
Go back and train hard.
Alright.
You leave first.
I will watch you go.
I want
to see you leave.
I'm leaving then.
Shen Juan.
Keep it up.
See you.
Bye.
Mr. Fu.
The books you sent me are obscure.
I'm struggling with the reading.
Do you have any academic papers?
Academic papers?
You mean papers
that discuss legal issues in cyberspace
with case studies, analysis,
preferably with insights
on further improving
space management.
Yes, that's it.
I will have one after I finish writing for you.
That's not what I meant.
The point is,
the new semester is not far off.
I can barely get through your books,
but I won't have time to write afterwards.
I can't keep asking you questions
all the time.
You'll definitely find me dumb
and annoying.
How would you know without trying?
Okay, I'll start compiling questions now.
No.
Why haven't you gone back yet?
Coach Lei.
I didn't do the live ammunition training
this morning.
Gun control training,
I need to make up for it.
Have you looked at your recent shooting data?
Do you know your problem?
My first shot accuracy is too low,
which affects
the second shot,
and the third shot.
To improve the first shot accuracy,
only by specifically training your hands
and shoulders,
can your strength
be strong and stable enough.
I will send you an additional training plan,
but you must promise me not
to affect our regular training.
Okay.
Again.
Mr. Fu.
I've sent you the questions about my thesis.
Did you receive the file?
Yes.
You have too many questions.
I can't explain it clearly on the phone.
Why don't we talk about it in person?
Are you free now?
Sure.
Let's meet at the coffee shop
near the law firm.
Okay.
Not bad.
It's quite novel.
Why are you laughing?
What do you think?
Considering you sneakily filmed me
when I was drunk,
I'm already being very nice talking to you.
Yes, you're magnanimous.
I'm grateful.
The overall framework is okay,
but the order needs
to be changed.
Move the first sentence of the first chapter
to…
I'm just telling you the date
for my competition.
I know. It's the 18th, right?
This is your first competition
since returning to the field.
I will definitely be there.
I'll talk to Lin Yujing
about booking the tickets later.
Lin Yujing
has a little situation.
Okay.
I got it.
See you then.
What's wrong? Did anything happen to Shen Juan?
It's Lin Yujing.
Her mother is sick.
Gu Xia.
Xu Ruyi, you're here too.
- When did you know her mom is sick?
- I…
How come you all are here?
We came coincidentally.
Where is your mom?
I just sent her for a check-up.
Check-up? Is she going to have surgery?
Why didn't you tell us about this?
I found out
when I heard from the dormitory supervisor
that you were asking for leave
to stay out overnight.
Don't you consider us your friends?
You didn't even tell us about such a big thing.
It happened too fast.
I didn't mean to hide it from you.
I just didn't want to make you worry.
When is the surgery? Is it scheduled?
It's on the 18th.
I heard from He Songnan
that Shen Juan's competition is also
on the 18th.
I'll accompany you for your mom's surgery.
It's fine. My brother will be there that day.
And it's not good
to have too many people in the hospital.
Well,
don't bear everything on your own.
We're all here.
Let us know if anything happens.
Remember to tell us if anything happens.
We're all here for you.
Okay.
Ning Yuan, three points.
Shen Juan, three points.
Shen Juan and Ning Yuan go to overtime.
Ning Yuan, get ready.
Shen Juan, get ready.
Shen Juan, Ning Yuan, second round of overtime.
Be ready.
Shen Juan, get ready.
Shen Juan, three points.
Shen Juan eliminated.
Go on.
It's the last game
of this training session.
Everyone has improved.
This training session is effective.
I declare
this training session is over.
Tomorrow will be the National University Games.
Go back and have a good rest.
Rest up,
and do your best in tomorrow's game.
Dismissed.
- See you at the competition tomorrow.
- See you.
See you tomorrow.
Let's go.
Bye.
Keep it up.
See you at the competition tomorrow.
Alright.
Can we have a video call?
You've finished training?
You have a competition tomorrow.
Rest early.
Okay.
How's the surgery scheduled?
It's tomorrow.
Okay, I'll rush over
as soon as my competition ends.
My brother will accompany me.
You just focus on your competition.
Okay.
I will watch the live broadcast
of your competition.
Go for it, Juan.
Okay.
Good night.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome
to the third National University Games.
What's about to start
is the individual heats
for men's 25m rapid fire.
This is also the team competition
for this event.
Please welcome the athletes to enter the field.
The athletes are entering.
Right now,
let me introduce the rules of the game.
Two contestants will take turns
at the same shooting position,
shooting at five targets.
All single shooting scores are included
in the total score.
This preliminary consists of two rounds.
After two rounds,
the top six players
will enter the finals.
After the individual scores are added up,
the final team competition ranking
is determined.
Now, Jiangcheng University,
Yuzhong University,
and Pucheng University's shooting teams
have sent contestants
to fight for the team competition medals.
The athletes are ready.
The competition officially begins.
This is the procedure of the surgery.
You sign it to approve the surgery.
[In Operation]
Next up, Shen Juan.
Shen Juan.
It's your turn. Go ahead.
What happens now
is the men's 25-meter rapid fire heats,
which is also the team game for this event.
The group that's up now is the last
of the first stage.
Let's look forward to
the athletes' outstanding performance.
Attention.
Wang An ranks first. Li Xiang ranks second.
Sui Yu Li Xiang third. Ning Yuan ranks fourth.
Zhang Zhicheng ranks fifth.
Zheng Yu ranks sixth. Feng Xin ranks seventh.
Shen Juan ranks eighth.
Juan is in eighth place.
Is there still hope?
Don't worry. According to the rules,
there are two rounds in the preliminaries.
The top six in the final results
move on to the finals.
If Juan does well in the next round,
there should be no problem.
Among the last few athletes,
the one with the best chance
of making it to the finals
is Shen Juan from Pucheng University,
currently ranked seventh.
If he can score
above forty in this round,
he would surpass Zheng Yu,
who is in sixth place,
and meet his teammate Ning Yuan,
who ranks fourth,
in the finals.
Attention.
Shen Juan has scored forty-eight points.
Congratulations to Shen Juan
for making it to the finals.
This year, Pucheng University Shooting Team
has performed brilliantly.
Congratulations
to the Pucheng University Shooting Team
for winning the bronze medal for this event.
Congratulations
to the Jiangcheng University Shooting Team
for winning the gold medal.
Yuzhong University Shooting Team
won the silver medal.
As the men's 25-meter rapid fire preliminaries
have just been finished,
the top six athletes have emerged.
They are Wang An,
Li Xiang, Sui Yu,
Ning Yuan, Zhang Zhicheng and Shen Juan.
What will happen next
is the men's 25-meter rapid fire
individual event final.
Please welcome the six finalists.
The rules for the finals are different
from the qualifying rounds.
If an athlete shoot
at 9.7 rings or above,
it counts as a hit and scores one point.
Below 9.7 rings, it's considered a miss.
Zero points.
Nice to see you again.
Congratulations
on your team winning the bronze medal.
Thanks.
And congrats
on your team defending the championship.
In the final,
you must hang in there for a while.
It's no fun if you get eliminated too quickly.
Don't worry about me
but yourselves.
The six finalists
are now standing at their respective positions.
I announce
the men's 25-meter rapid fire
officially begins.
Many of the athletes
in the final are quite familiar to everyone.
Shen Juan, who is on position F,
might not be well-known to you.
He won a medal
at the National Youth Shooting Championship
four years ago.
Today, he returns to the competition field.
Let's look forward to
his performance.
The second round is going on.
Attention.
Dear audience,
the fourth group of competition
is about to begin.
Starting from this group,
the lowest-ranked
of the six finalists will be eliminated.
What does that mean?
From now on,
the elimination game starts.
The contestant
who ranks last will be eliminated.
Look how close the scores are now.
The rankings can change any minute.
So every round is very important.
Juan is currently in fifth place.
He must steady himself.
Firstly, congratulations to Zhang Zhicheng
from Yuzhong University Shooting Team
for achieving sixth place in this game.
The remaining five contestants on the field
will continue with the next round of the game.
It's a pity.
Ning Yuan made a mistake in this round,
only gaining two points,
and stopped at fifth place.
But in this game,
he has already
achieved his personal best score.
Let's look forward to his performance
in the future game.
Now there are four athletes on the field
to compete in the last round.
Which three athletes
are qualified
- for the top three spots in this game?
- Take a break.
Let us wait and see.
Attention.
The competition for third place
is very intense.
In this round,
Sui Yu ranked first.
Li Xiang ranked second.
Wang An and Shen Juan had a tie.
Did I see it wrong?
Juan stands a chance of winning a medal.
So, what happens in this tie situation?
Do both of them tie for third place?
In this case,
a tie-breaker round will be conducted,
which means the two people
with the same score will compete
until a winner is determined.
Only after that will the final match
between the first and second place be held.
Since Wang An
and Shen Juan have the same score,
a tie-breaker will be conducted next.
The first to shoot is Wang An.
Attention.
Wang An scored three points.
Now let's see
if Shen Juan can withstand the pressure.
Shen Juan also scored three points.
It's a tie again.
The second round of the tie-breaker
will be conducted next.
Attention.
Four points. Well done.
Now the pressure is back on Shen Juan.
The scores of Wang An
and Shen Juan are very close.
It's a breathtaking tie-breaker.
In this round,
Shen Juan must hit four out of five shots
to catch up with Wang An.
As long as Shen Juan hits all five shots,
he will secure a medal in this game.
He got five hits.
Congratulations to Shen Juan
for winning the tie-breaker
and advancing to the top three.
[In Operation]
- How did it go?
- The surgery went smoothly.
However, the patient needs to be in the ICU
for 24 hours of observation.
You can visit her later.
Thank you, doctor.
Thank you.
We finally get over it.
The third place goes
to Shen Juan from Pucheng University.
The second place goes
to Li Xiang from Yuzhong University.
The champion goes
to Sui Yu from Jiangcheng University.
Now let's present the awards
to the winning contestants.
Congratulations to all contestants
for achieving excellent results.
Alright, our award ceremony ends here.
Shen Juan.
You did well in the overtime match just now.
Looking forward to our next game.
There are still three years left in college.
We have plenty of time for that.
- I'm expecting it.
- Me too.
- Bye.
Come on. Let's take a group photo.
The surgery was successful.
[Inpatient Department]
♫ When a ray of light shines in my life ♫
♫ It lights up the direction
where my heart follows ♫
♫ We always have our doubts ♫
♫ But life always needs to set sail ♫
♫ When you sit beside me ♫
♫ Asking me where home is ♫
♫ I point to a star in the night sky ♫
♫ That's the way it guides ♫
♫ You are the weary bird in my palm ♫
♫ I can't bear to let you fly far away ♫
♫ I am the paper boat in your heart ♫
♫ And you are my only harbor ♫
Juan is capable of everything.
That means
I can loss many things
except Lin Yujing.
I can't do without this girl
who always stands behind me
but stands up for me without hesitation
when something happens.
She
is my whole world.
♫ Love sprouts in my palm ♫
♫ Yet worried linger within my eyes ♫
♫ Our story hasn't ended ♫
♫ So where are we now ♫
♫ I want to hug you so badly ♫
♫ I want to become better with you ♫
♫ The youth we shared ♫
♫ Turned into a rainbow within my heart ♫
♫ I really want to warm you ♫
♫ I want to share with you ♫
♫ The beauty of the world ♫
♫ We promised ♫
♫ To never be apart ♫
♫ Do you want to hear me sing ♫
♫ The wind chime swaying in my heart ♫
♫ Is a wish ♫
♫ I secretly made for you ♫
♫ I want to plant ♫
♫ A red maple forest ♫
♫ To dye the whole mountain red ♫
♫ The sky after the rain ♫
♫ Was painted by our brilliant dreams ♫
♫ Time is a flower of dream ♫
♫ You've already collected it ♫
♫ When we all become better ♫
♫ We'll see the best of the world together ♫