At this time, they should already be back.
Why did it have to be a woman?
Your Highness.
Why are you here, Your Highness?
No, I...
I was just passing by.
But... why... are you here?
What's with this look?
Oh, this?
This...
- Your Highness the Crown Prince!
- Your Highness.
- Moon Soo.
It's been a while, everyone.
How have you been—
Hyung-nim! It's been one month and five days, Your Highness.
I really, really missed you, Your Highness!
My hyung-nim!
Okay, hug me to your heart's content.
Aigoo, aigoo, Our Highness.
An undercover investigation? Human trafficking involving the Chinese?
Is that what's happening?
Yes. As you know, the country is a mess from the war and even the plagues.
The people's lives are tough so they sell their kids.
And those kids... are being sold to Qing Dynasty as well.
Right, the current world can put a price on a person.
But I didn't know they were being sold to Qing Dynasty as well.
If there is an illegal transaction by Qing people, we'll catch them for sure, Your Highness.
Is there anything I can help you with? It seems dangerous with just you guys.
No, not at all, Your Highness.
It is you who are walking on thin ice.
Right. You must stay out of this.
But the thing is, is this the only way?
Pardon me?
What I am saying...
Must she wear that sort of clothes?
Yeo Ji's clothes?
Ah, that looks uncomfortable.
But Yeo Ji is the only person who can speak the Qing language.
What? Uncomfortable?
I am fine, Your Highness. This is nothing.
- It feels alright?
- Yes.
- But... but that's not what I am saying now, is it?
- What?
It seems those two didn't understand what His Highness meant at all.
- What's does he mean?
- Why does he care what Yeo Ji wears?
No way...
No, that can't be. No, no.
What?
No. No matter how much I think about it, I don't think this is a good method.
I think we need to find a way, so she doesn't have to wear that sort of clothes.
- Pardon me?
- Why is that?
You are right. In order to keep an eye on Qing people,
we need to wear Japanese clothes and not Qing's clothes. So that's what you meant.
Right, that's what I meant.
Would Qing people have a secretive talk in the presence of other Qings?
So that's why you objected to Qing's women clothes.
These Japanese clothes will work better.
Of course, Your Highness. How did you come up with that bright idea?
I know, right?
I am flustered with myself for having come up with that idea.
Isn't it a bit strange?
Wow. Yeo Ji, you...
Don't I look awkward?
Do I look like a Japanese person?
Yes, totally.
Hey, you even look like a woman.
- Me?
- Yes.
Your Highness, do you think so, too?
Your Highness.
Do I look like a woman?
Your Highness, are you listening?
Please look at me. Your Highness.
Ah! That's right!
Of course, you are a woman. Are you a man?
Just be careful, I am saying. If you get hurt like before...
- Do you understand?
- Yeah? Yes...
Ah, you too, Moon Soo! Protect Yeo Ji well. Darn...
For some reason, doesn't he seem to be angry?
I know, right?
What does she mean whether she looks like a woman?
How... can she ask me things like that?
Do I need to go to the palace like this?
Alone, leaving them behind?
Oh, Hyung-nim! You came.
I want to check on the kid I brought yesterday.
- The doctor came by. He said she will be okay.
- Really?
Go Mi is guarding her, so don't worry about her.
When you say Go Mi, do you mean the girl who got kicked out from the prime minister's house?
Yes. She was dying from the beating when we took her in.
Okay.
But... what's with the clothes?
Ta-da! We are going to the new gisaeng house in Nakseonbang to gather information.
That place? I heard the boss came from the north.
Right. Whoever it is, he is pretty good at business.
I heard not only the nobles but Qings and Japanese are flocking there.
We'd get the intelligence.
Be cautious.
Don't make a useless scene.
Got it.
I heard she almost got sold to Qing.
Still, I think heaven helped her as it helped me.
Because she ended up here.
Your leg...
I got punished by the madam I used to serve.
I am not limping that badly.
Chae... Yoon Yeong.
The madam you used to serve
was that person?
- Again.
- I don't understand this.
She was the prime minister's concubine.
And right now, she's the mistress of Prince Milpoong Tan?
Do you know... my madam?
How do you know her?
A murder case of a noble family?
This is bothering me. Look into it further.
I will look into it.
I thought you would help my brother.
I am sorry. But with today's incident,
I'd think your brother understood his position and place.
Is that why you volunteered to be his teacher?
To isolate my brother?
I can't trust your brother, Your Majesty.
There is only a 6-year age gap between you and your brother.
What if he has a change of heart—
Are you saying he'd kill me?
Okay, I don't trust that kid either.
Of course, he has ambition, because the palace is a place where even castrated ambition re-grows.
How do I know, you ask? Because that's how it was with me.
That's how it was with me.
That's why I can't trust my brother's ambition either.
But at least I should give him a chance, give him the benefit of the doubt.
It's a murder case of a noble family, you said?
Yes, the police are investigating right now,
and they've asked for Saheonbu's collaboration.
So, about the inspector hazing,
you're going to come too, right? The new gisaeng house—
You guys go ahead. I need to wrap up the rest of the records.
Okay.
Here are the requested files from Saheonbu.
You've become the mayor of Hanseong  (capital)  now,
so why are you asking for Saheonbu's files?
You mean to say why am I interfering when I've lost my central position and was demoted?
I'll be on my way then.
As expected, you've become arrogant.
I'm a deputy inspector general, Your Excellency.
Coming and going each time you ask is troublesome.
There are always those who mistakenly think that tomorrow will be the same as today
when the time is changing even as we speak.
It must be that I know how to read the flow of time, too.
Otherwise, would I have been able to gain this position?
This case.
How the noblemen are being murdered.
I think this will lead me back to the royal court.
Will your thought be the same then?
What do you mean?
Do you know that I used to be the inspector general of Saheonbu?
It means that I am used to investigating cases.
Did you not notice after reading through the files?
This is not a simple case. They are homicides by an organization.
This is another world.
Which of these is the criminal?
- My Lord!
- My Lord! Have you come?
Here! This is the new gisaeng house!
I will specially kill you all here tonight.
He says he'll kill you all here tonight!
- Let's go.
- Come in.
Excuse me.  (in Japanese)
Hey, wait there a second.
Are you talking to me?  (in Japanese)
I've never seen your face before. Who are you?
I'm the owner here.
How could I not know you?
I am Asako.  (in Japanese)
I came here yesterday, so I wasn't able to greet you yet.  (in Japanese)
But a Japanese girl understands Korean?
I learned to entertain Joseon guests.  (in Japanese)
I understand a little bit.  (in Japanese)
Hey there, you have to host the guest here.  (in Japanese)
Then, I'll be going.  (in Japanese)
Her face is pretty so it seems that she'll be useful.
Hey! Hey, Do Ji Gwang!
Do Ji Gwang!
Come, come.
Hey, look at this ledger. Our gisaeng house is doing amazingly right now.
As you said, it's a really good thing that we decorated it to have a Chinese atmosphere.
Are you happy?
You're so happy that you must sleep really well.
Of course! Thanks to you, I'm able to stretch my legs and sleep deeply.
You fool. You're that happy?
He says he can sleep.
Why...
Why are you being like this?
He lost something yesterday, so he's not in a good mood.
Gosh, I thought it was something serious.
A man shouldn't be upset over such things.
I mean, during work, one mig—
Hey you f-ing bastard.
Do you know how people like you get ruined?
After you've been ripped off, you are able to sleep. That's why you get ruined.
Even after someone takes what belongs to you, you're able to stretch both legs!
I'll tell you one thing so listen carefully.
If you don't know when the back of your head is prickly,
then you'll be stabbed with a knife and die.
That's how it is here.
By bastards like them.
What happened to Goon Tae and the storyteller?
- It seems that they were found out while spying.
- Then...
They will definitely come to warn us.
Call everyone immediately and—
Auntie.
Goon Tae.
You f-ing bastards!
Okay... Attack!
- It'll be good to stop.
- Boss!
I think my sword will slice your neck before they get me.
Who are you?
Your clothes look quite fancy in this cave of beggars.
Shut up! Just who are you that—
Stop.
You can't cause trouble.
Okay, okay. We've acquainted ourselves of each other's faces, so should we stop here?
You're Dal Moon, huh?
Do you like my gift?
Remember well. If guys like these linger around my territory again,
then only their heads will return.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Hey.
Hyung-nim. Gae Dol was with him, Hyung-nim.
They're like wild animals.
They're crazy!
Move them quickly. Call the doctor.
Yes!
Who is he?
He's the owner of the new gisaeng house in Nakseonbang.
- These two went to check out what it's like—
- Wait.
New gisaeng house? The one even Qing and Japanese visitors frequent?
How did Your Highness know about that?
Your Highness. Your Highness! You can't do this.
Do Ji Gwang. It's that person's gisaeng house. That's where Yeo Ji and Moon Soo went.
However, we're looking for a Chinese. He is not related to this.
Even so, I cannot leave Moon Soo and Yeo Ji to such a dangerous place.
Boss!
This kid has something to tell you.
It's that person! That person is the one who was trafficking.
It's okay. What did you say?
The person who tried to sell me off to China.
The person with a scar on his face.
I clearly saw him.
Your Highness!
You're quite pretty.  (in Chinese)
How much would one night cost?  (in Chinese)
I'm fuming with anger. Go home.  (in Japanese)
What are you mumbling about?  (in Chinese)
- If you're drunk, just go home.
- My Lord.
Who are you?  (in Chinese)
Are you her lover?  (in Chinese)
He said something like who are you to step up. Right?
Yes, you jerk. I don't know what you said but I am!
"Qingren"? What are you going to do about it?
Get lost if you don't want to get beaten up.
What's so special about this gisaeng?  (in Chinese)
You fool.  (in Chinese)
Apologize? You're saying you apologize?
("Sha gua" = fool in Chinese, "sa gwa" = to apologize in Korean)
What was that just now?
If I wasn't quick enough, he would have been pummeled to death by you. It would have been pitiful.
Do you even know what he said that you acted that way?
Oh "qingren"? What is that?
Never mind. Did you learn anything?
Lower your voice.
No. How about you?
According to Inspector Yoon, he had information that said that
this is definitely the base for the traffickers to secretly act.
Maybe it's wrong information. It might be a trap.
Lord Yoon Hyeok said that it was information from his long-time friend who is at border control.
Just who are they!
I'll be back after using the restroom.
Okay.
Gosh, gosh.
Be careful.
But you guys can't go to the restroom! Drink on!
Your Highness!
Let's go together. I can't send you alone either.
Then look around near the rear door.
Be careful.
May I help you?  (in Japanese)
Excuse me.
Your Highness!
Your Highness, what are you doing here?
Where's Yeo Ji? Where is she right now?
Pardon?
Four days later at Gwangnaroo,  (in Chinese)
I'll send twenty young girls to you, okay?  (in Chinese)
It's not the Chinese.
The person you must find is not Chinese.
What do you mean, Your Highness?
Each head is worth 30 nyang.  (in Chinese)
I can't give it for any less, not even one nyang.  (in Chinese)
Be sure to bring the money. Understand?  (in Chinese)
That man is that owner from earlier.
What are you doing over here?
What is it?
This girl was secretly listening to the conversation.
Who is this?  (in Chinese)
You're that girl from earlier.
Where is she?
I'll go towards the garden in the back.
When you find Yeo Ji, you must flee first.
This is Do Ji Gwang's headquarters. You two won't be able to handle it.
Yes. You should be careful too, Your Highness.
I thought it was weird.
There is no way I wouldn't know a gisaeng here. Right?
Tell me. Who are you?
Who sent you?
Yeo Ji!
- Are you okay?
- My Lord.
Kill them. Kill them all!
Yeo Ji?
What are you doing?
You are... from earlier...
Yeo Ji, no!
Who are you? Tell me!
Let go! I said let go!
Who are you?
"Master-killer"?
You will kill your master? What does that mean...
Just kill me.
You're a girl?
Hey! Are you okay?
Hey!
Is anyone there?
Is no one here?
Hey!
Hey there. Come to your senses.
This...
What is this, Your Highness?
It's dangerous, Yeo Ji.
This is...
♫  You whom I love  ♫
♫  Become the moon light  ♫
Master-killer?  Did you just say the master-killer band?
You saw the culprit!
If you are not the culprit, that is!
We must locate her first.
If we cannot try his crime just because he's the crown prince, then we ought to discard these inspectors' robes!
You want the crown prince?
My family member has died, so how violently I will act...
If you want to set a new game, shouldn't you trust me?
Your Highness will become the culprit.
Your Highness, this time, it's your turn to trust us.
There are only three days. Your Highness must prove your own innocence
and reveal the truth about this case.
♫  So I would have to remember you even in my dreams  ♫