Through whom and where did you use it?
I don't care whether I die by poison or sword.
Do you think I'm scared?
What?
Hey you, listen carefully.
It's not because I'm scared of the sword.
I'm telling you because I'm so excited, okay?
What? It's poison without an antidote?
Yes, Your Highness.
Do Ji Gwang said that if Prince Milpoong used the poison, there won't be any antidote.
The crown prince, that jerk, found out that I went to the King's Physician's Office.
Tan.
Right?
So he forbade medicine, right?
How do you know that?
I... I told the crown prince to do that.
What?
I couldn't give my throne to the crown prince even if it meant my death.
His Majesty who screwed me over needed to be punished too.
What do I do about this? I can't be the only one who suffers.
Gosh, what do I do? Then!
I should use poison.
So I purposely left my trace at the King's Physician's Office,
so that everyone could notice that I'd been there.
Why, you ask?
Because it's obvious that the crown prince would throw a fit if I did that.
He would suspect me and stop the King's Physician's Office and forbid the medicine.
Then the crown prince will become the one who kills His Majesty.
I... knew about all of this.
Stop your bullshit.
The one who used poison is you.
You cannot place the guilt on the crown prince.
What about evidence?
Do you have any?
Should I return the favor as I have received it?
The evidence that you guys love so much...
The evidence that I used poison...
where is it?
How dare!
His Majesty will die soon.
With that poison, he might already be dead.
Then the crown prince will become the person who sinned against heaven, killing His Majesty by forbidding medicine.
Would a person like that safely become a king?
No way.
The throne I cannot have, Lee Geum cannot have it either.
Your Majesty!
- Your Majesty!
No...
No!
You're the same as the crown prince.
I... knew you wouldn't be able to either.
What about the prescription?
Were you able to prescribe medicine for His Majesty?
I apologize, Your Highness.
There is nothing more that we can do as human beings.
There is nothing we can do?
The King's Physician's Office said the same.
That there is nothing more they can do.
Are you saying that all these medical documents have no use?
How could we, with all of these doctors and medicine, not save His Majesty?
Your Highness, we are not out of methods yet.
There is a last method that we could try that, as far as I know, is dangerous but possible.
Dangerous but possible? What is it?
Inspector General! Tell me immediately.
What? What medicine are they trying to use? Chinese aconite?
Chinese aconite? Chinese aconite and ginseng?
Yes, Your Highness.
However, Chinese aconite is a poisonous medicine that is used for death penalty drink, isn't it?
It is.
However because of that strong toxicity,
the poison inside of the body could be removed.
There was definitely a case where a hopeless paraplegic patient
had Chinese aconite as a last resort to save his life.
And by using ginseng with Chinese aconite, you want to counter the poison.
That is right, Your Highness.
However, Chinese aconite's toxicity is already too strong on its own.
On top of that, the medicine that His Majesty has been drinking in the meantime
has black false hellebore, which is incompatible with ginseng.
Then are you saying we shouldn't do anything?
Who here can prescribe something
other than Chinese aconite and ginseng?
Serve him the medicine as we have discussed immediately.
Your Highness, if we use Chinese aconite and it becomes harmful,
- then Your Highness will face trouble, too!
- Don't you hear me?!
There is no time for delay. Order the prescription now!
Make the medicine as prescribed here.
What?
Ginseng and Chinese aconite?
Yes.
It's the last prescription that His Highness allowed.
Isn't this medicine that the medical community has shunned for a long time?
If this... goes wrong like this...
Everything is my responsibility, Your Highness.
If it goes wrong, I will take responsibility for the outcome.
No. You are wrong, Teacher.
The responsibility can be taken only by one who is suited for it.
It's what His Majesty told me.
I am the one who made this decision.
As His Majesty has done, I won't avoid my responsibility either.
I heard that His Majesty is deathly ill.
If His Majesty dies like this, what should we do?
This is how people's lives are.
You can never tell what will happen.
Did you look into it? How is it in the king's palace?
Is it this or that?
I'm a Saheonbu inspector. I need to enter the palace quickly.
Yes, go on in.
Inspector Park.
My Lord.
Are you coming back from Prince Milpoong's house of exile?
There is an urgent matter.
I have to tell the crown prince about what is going on behind the scenes immediately.
Just what is going on that you're like this?
Wi Byeong Joo didn't seem to know anything.
This is a trap.
This is a trap that Prince Milpoong laid to tie the crown prince and His Majesty.
You weren't followed, right?
That's absurd.
It's the half that I promised. It's half of Prince Milpoong's wealth.
You know that this is nothing compared to what I have done for you, right?
What I have planned will be carried out without any problems, right?
The crown prince is struggling to save him, but it won't matter,
because no medicine can ever counteract that poison.
I can finally take a breather now.
I want to drink tea, but do you have any teacups?
Tea?
It's refreshing chrysanthemum tea.
How about it? Will you drink some, too?
Moon Soo!
Your Highness.
What did you say just now? What do you mean that this is all
a scheme targeting not only His Majesty but also me?
He knew how you would react when you discovered that poison was used.
- Prince Milpoong was going for this.
- What?
Your Highness, even now you have to stop everything.
I apologize, but there is no way to save His Majesty.
Even if it's just you, you at least have to come out of this pit.
No, I can't.
Even if what Prince Milpoong said is true,
I have to do everything I can.
And what if even you get hurt in doing so?
Your Highness, I also don't want to be telling you this.
I don't want to tell you to become cowardly, but!
I also have to do everything
to protect you.
Moon Soo.
Your Highness! Your Highness the crown prince!
You have to go quickly, immediately.
Your Highness. Your Highness the Queen Dowager.
What about His Majesty? How is he?
Your Majesty, have you regained your senses?
Can you see me?
Can you hear me, Your Majesty?
Crown Prince.
Da-Dal Moon.
This must be the house of the King's Physician's Office's head nurse.
Yes.
As expected, you haven't given up anything.
You only pretended to have.
S-Stop. It's too late. You cannot stop me!
Was this what Prince Milpoong commanded?
To use poison to kill the king?
What good is that?
It's already over for Prince Milpoong!
With whose permission is it over?!
I haven't ended anything yet!
Yoon Bok Dan!
Come here! Is anyone outside? Is anyone there?
Tell Doctor Choi Seong Jo and Lee Gwang Jwa to come
so that they can feel His Majesty's pulse. Quickly!
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Majesty, please brace yourself.
You have to endure no matter what.
I will save you.
The ones who face their ends are the king and the crown prince.
The king will die.
The crown prince will be charged with that crime.
I've made it so that
they can't discover anything.
What?
What do you mean by that?
No way.
Yoon Bok Dan.
How could you...
Hey there, come to your senses.
Hey there!
Crown Prince.
Now...
stop trying your best.
It will be...
too difficult for me.
No, Your Majesty.
It is not so. You have opened your eyes.
You can recover.
Forgive me, Crown Prince.
Me, who took this position away from you.
Actually...
the throne that was yours...
Me... for taking it instead.
Your Majesty, please.
Do not say such words.
Right now, don't say anything.
And...
Geum...
Please, at least you...
for all of the people of this nation...
become a good king.
One I could not become.
One... I dreamt of.
That kind of a king.
No.
Your Majesty! Older Brother!
No. You can't.
You have to open your eyes. Please.
Your Majesty!
Your Highness, Your Highness, Your Highness!
You cannot cut your finger! It's dangerous for you as well!
Stand back. Let go of me!
Your Highness.
Your Majesty, please.
- You cannot pass away.
- Please...
Stop, Your Highness.
Older Brother!
Older Brother.
- Queen Dowager.
- His Majesty is now—
Your Majesty!
No, Your Majesty!
No, this cannot be.
Your Highness!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
Your Highness.
Your Majesty. Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
Everyone face His Majesty and mourn.
Bow down.
Bow again.
Has everyone gathered their will?
Yes.
Right now, the Soron court officials have?
Yes. It seems that they will come to the Queen Dowager's Palace soon.
My Lord, have you heard?
The Right State Councilor and a few other Soron court officials
are headed to the Queen Dowager's Palace!
The Queen Dowager's Palace? Why?!
Just what do you mean by that, Right State Councilor?!
I cannot ever allow it.
The preceding king has passed due to the crown prince's stubbornness and greed!
Stubbornness and greed?
The crown prince even cut his own finger
and tried to save His Majesty until the end!
No! If we had prescribed and given the medicine correctly,
we would not have had today's tragedy.
Your Highness!
Your Highness, the crown prince is here.
It's you, Crown Prince.
The reason why His Majesty passed
is all because of you.
You, who have done this,
do not have the right to become this nation's king.
♫  Since we met saying hello  ♫
♫  Should we break up while saying goodbye?  ♫
♫  Now the gentle and gentler wind hurts too  ♫
The remaining time until a new king ascends the throne after the predecessor king's death...
Six days are remaining.
Until then, the throne will be unoccupied.
This is the last time to address you as Your Highness.
Please become a sage king, Your Highness.
I have no thought of accepting your deal.
Being able to sacrifice even innocent ones,
that's another aspect of the king's position.
Please allow you to hold the coronation ceremony as soon as possible?
In the event a regrettable but inevitable incident breaks out in the palace,
how much military manpower can be mobilized to stop the crown prince's enthronement?
Whether to avoid this pain as a human being...
or gladly become the king and fight against all these humiliations.