The reason I have personally come to Saheonbu's jejwa hearing room today
is because I want to tell you that the new Joseon
needs to start here at Saheonbu.
This nation's Three Offices, and particularly Saheonbu,
have long been rotten to the core with evil customs and traditions.
Who of this nation would trust Saheonbu,
and who would believe in the fairness of Saheonbu?
Your Majesty, I am sorry but—
Stop!  I have not finished speaking.
However, I will not overlook Saheonbu's long history of corruption any longer.
This is for the sake of this country and all officials of Saheonbu.
As of today, from this place,
I proclaim to the whole world that I will abolish
the Ministry of the Interior's section chief system,
- Abolish...
- which has long held the appointment rights over Saheonbu,
and I will completely reform that system.
Section Chief of the Ministry of the Interior... who is in charge of Saheonbu's personnel?
Your Majesty, what do you mean?
Abolish the Ministry of the Interior's section chief system?
That is what I said.
From this moment on, I will abolish
the Section Chief of the Ministry of the Interior's right to select key government officials and to recommend his own successor,
and I will completely reform the personnel policies of the Three Offices including Saheonbu.
Prime Minister, announce my decree.
Until now, the Section Chief of Ministry of the Interior had the right to select personnel
of the Three Offices of Saheonbu  (Office of Inspector General) , Saganwon  (Office of Censors) , and Hongmoongwan  (Office of Special Advisors) .
This cannot be, Your Majesty.
This is an outrage!
- At the same time...
- Even if you are the king, you can't do this!
This is suppression of free press! This is oppression against Saheonbu! Oppression!
Please retract your decree!
Stop it! You are in His Majesty's presence!
His Majesty's royal command and its decree are being announced. Everyone stop!
- ...the corruption and evil...
- Your Majesty! Please retract your decree immediately!
- Your Majesty!
- Please stop, Your Majesty!
- Quiet!
- Please retract your decree!
- Stop this!
- Stop! You're in front of His Majesty!
- Please, Your Majesty!
You are in front of His Majesty!
...shall abolish the Section Chief of the Ministry of Interior's rights of appointment
and his right to recommend the succeeding section chief will also be reformed...
Your Majesty.
Saheonbu now will face the biggest turmoil it ever faced.
But it's the time we've been waiting for more than any other time.
Your Majesty, your grace is immeasurable.
Yes, please let us take care of Saheonbu now.
I leave it in your good hands.
Your Majesty. I think you should go to the palace quickly.
Prince Milpoong came into the palace and is causing a ruckus now.
What?
Lock this person up right now! Hurry!
Yes.
How dare you hold me?
Open up the way to the king's palace.
I will go to the king's palace, to the royal throne.
I am going to sit on the throne!
No...
I am the king.
I am the king, I said.
Prince Milpoong.
Your Majesty.
Lee Geum.
We are all living lives hanging off the edge of a cliff.
A slight push and we will plummet instantly.
Do you know what one realizes when that instance comes?
To lose power is akin to imminent death.
It's Prince Milpoong! Prince Milpoong walked into the palace on his own!
Protect the royal throne! Guards, surround the royal palace!
- Yes!
- Station yourself there!
- Queen Dowager.
- What's happening?
I hear Prince Milpoong came into the palace with a weapon.
- What?
- Something might happen so stay in your palace.
Lee Geum.
Prince Milpoong. How dare you...
- The rebels might be scheming something, so quickly move—
- Wait!
You need to hear me out.
I came to see you.
You should at least hear me out.
How dare you! Close that mouth of yours.
Truthfully,
I still don't really know
why it's you and not me.
Min Jin Heon, Sorons, and Namins...
Why do they all end up on your side?
The things I can't have,
why can you have them all?!
- What are you doing? Quickly, get this bast—
- Why!
Why did you come to the palace on your own?
Answer me, Prince Milpoong!
You could have run away, so why?
I came to die as the king.
I'll get caught as a fugitive anyway.
An end befitting a king...
Proudly...
to die.
Because that's the king.
Because that's what the king does!
You are afraid, aren't you?
Very much.
Yet, you came to die proudly as the king?
Okay. The scarier choice...
The harder choice...
If you could've made that in the first place,
perhaps the throne would've been yours.
What?
But you are too late and have been wrong.
You've done unforgivable evil deeds for far too long.
This time, I will definitely keep my promise to make you pay for your sins.
Without delay,
you'll pay the price with death.
-  Commandant of the Royal Guards!
- Yes.
Take him away!
Yes, Your Majesty.
No. I won't die.
I won't die by your hands.
Lee Geum!
Your Majesty!
Tan.
Prince Milpoong.
Okay.
You won. You did.
I...
lost.
I will wait for you from there,
so don't be too afraid to come.
I will be waiting... as your queen in the other world.
You must come... as king.
As king...
As the king...
My end...
Ultimately...
you become like this
in the end.
Tan...
Are you saying Prince Milpoong committed suicide?
That is what I heard.  His body was collected.
How could this be?
To put him up as Noron's puppet king, I brought him.
I needed a king whom I could control.
It was my misjudgment, Ha Gok  (Jo Tae Goo's pen name) .
I thought I lived my whole life for the court.
Why is the last thing left regret?
They say the regret never comes first. This feels so empty.
Well, perhaps a life without any regrets... isn't that even more terrifying and frightening?
Life is so fleeting and vacuous.
Even a person fawned on to become the next king exits like this.
He annoys me until the end.
Who the heck is he to take his own life
when he should be quartered to death?
He is no longer of this world.  What use is talking behind his back?
Soon, Lee In Jwa and Wi Byeong Joo will pass on as well at the execution ground, right?
Your Majesty, there are traitors still waiting to get their just desserts.
You must hand down their sentences.
April 1728. I, the king, hand down the sentences
against the traitors who, through a horrifying revolt,
murdered the people and caused chaos in the court.
The rebel head Lee In Jwa staged a rebellion and soaked this land with blood,
taking away countless lives of the people.
As such, his heinous crimes will be dealt with by capital punishment.
Moreover, Wi Byeong Joo, who murdered Inspector Han Jeong Seok
and joined the rebellion after escaping from his place of exile,
shall also be beheaded to pay for his egregious crimes.
Carry out the sentences against the criminals immediately.
Now, now, now, everyone, make haste.
Listening to my story is not important today.
Today is the day when the traitors' necks will be chopped off!
Let's see how well our executioner performs his death dance with our own two eyes.
Now, let's go!
- That's right!
- Heaven punish those bastards!
Lee In Jwa, this is all your fault.
- Because of your arrogance—
- Shut up.
As much as the grand aspiration you had in your heart, face your death with dignity.
Dignity?
What use is that when I am dying?  The world I wanted...
When Hyung-nim Jeong Seok held out his hand to you...
At that time, if you had chosen the human path rather than that of a beast,
you might have been standing here on the other side today.
Doesn't that occur to you?  I mean, in this world where Namins like you
get hired and get opportunities commensurate to their ability.
Yes, you are right.  But keep this in mind.
Do you think you would be different?
Someday, you will also be made to kneel down
on an execution ground just like me here.
Of course, that is a possibility, too.
But at least I will not tremble in fear like you,
because I won't have any regrets.
Start the criminals' execution.
You won't be able to do anything.
In the end, the powerful win.
The Norons are the masters of this world.
I'm advising you to side with them and choose to live.
How can I do that, Byeong Joo,
when the worlds we see are so far apart?
At that time, if you had chosen the human path rather than that of a beast,
you might have been standing here on the other side today.
Doesn't that occur to you?
Farewell, Bok Dan.
In your next life,
wanting nothing, regretting nothing,
be reborn as the silk-clad
Chae Yoon Yeong that you yearned for.
You've had a hard time.
You must have undergone a distressful time.
I thought you might need some solace.
Fear.
I, too, feel afraid.
As long as I sit on this seat,
times like this will come again,
when I must punish some and
put others to death.
Whether I will be right at every such occasion,
whether I can manage not to be wrong,
whether I will once again
qualify as a king, I mean.
Excuse me for my insolence, but if I may say this to you,
just the fact that you are asking that question
qualifies you to be the king.
At times, you might make wrong decisions.
However, you will not cease to ask yourself the same question,
and for that reason, you will always be able to find the right path again.
That is why people trust you and follow you.
And that is why I love you, Your Majesty.
Yeo Ji.
♫  You whom I love  ♫
♫  Become the moon light  ♫
♫  Shine on me again  ♫
♫  So that I cannot forget you, so I cannot erase you  ♫
♫  So I would have to remember you even in my dreams  ♫
♫  I break down inside of you  ♫
♫  I cannot erase  ♫
He is declaring war on us.
His Majesty turned the Saheonbu into an angry swarm of bees.
What does he mean by abolishing the Ministry of Interior's section chief system?
When he named Lee Gwang Jwa as the prime minister,
shouldn't you have expected that His Majesty would make this move?
- Pardon?
- Now, His Majesty has successfully put down even the rebellion.
Currently, even the popular sentiment favors His Majesty.
On your side, what cause is there for you to fight?
That is why we are saying you must come forward.
Why would I?  Didn't you guys tell me I don't deserve to be the Noron head?
There is no place for my servants to put the books down.
Will you make way?  Or you guys can help them.
Are the agendas for the regular audience session being finalized?
Yes, they are almost done.
Are you all ready?  Soon, the regular audience will be held.
It will be ready right away.
And His Majesty?
He stayed up all night in his office and went to sleep about an hour ago.
Again?
Then maybe we should put off the regular audience for a little bit...
What do you mean, put it off?
I can't have my reputation ruined for something like this.
Your Majesty.
Now, everyone, let us be on our way if you are finished preparing for the regular audience.
However, Your Majesty, how many days has it been already?
If you ruin your royal health this way...
What nonsense.
When a wolf hunts down its enemy,
he ought not to afford the prey a chance to catch its breath.
Here comes His Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Now, then, we shall hold this morning's regular audience.
Today, again, the issue under consideration is the abolishment of the Ministry of Interior's section chief system
in connection with the reorganization of the personnel policy of the Three Offices.
This is a joint petition to support the new personnel policy announced by His Majesty.
Many inspectors and high-ranking ministers who served in Saheonbu in the past
have already signed on.
Of course, I am well aware what a difficult decision it is.
However, if we truly want Saheonbu to change,
then shouldn't we be the ones to bear the burden first?
What are you sitting on the fence for?
If the Ministry of Interior's section chief system is repealed,
then we don't need to kiss up here and there but can simply do our jobs to the best of our abilities!
But you... Can it be you also signed on already?
Of course.  As for me, I have passionately longed for Saheonbu's change for a very long time.
I must follow the lead inspector's wish.
Look here, Inspector Joo.
Thank you so much.
Wait.
But I don't see Inspector Joo's name here.
What?
You are right.
There is a Joo Yeong Hoon, but no Joo Yeong Han.
How can that be?
This guy seriously!
Oh my. Wh-Why is it like this?
But I definitely wrote down my name as Joo Yeong Han,
but why is there a Joo Yeong Hoon?
Now, here.
Here. Write it again.
A-Again?
Of course.  It can be written again as many times as needed.
Is that how it is?
I worried for nothing.
Then, of course, I should.  Again.
Again...
- The brush is, though...
- Harrumph!
I will write it.
However, Your Majesty, the reason the appointment rights were given to the section chief of the Ministry of the Interior
to begin with was to prevent abuse by high-ranking ministers.
Because the system to prevent abuse itself got corrupted and turned bad,
I am suggesting its abolishment.
Then, how can you guarantee that the newly reformed system won't get corrupted again?
Detailed provisions were made to guard against that possibility.
Deputy Inspector General of Saheonbu, are you sure you have come to this meeting after studying those provisions?
Oh dear, has the morning regular audience session been dragging on for too long?
Two hours or so seems to have passed already.
That is right, Your Majesty.
I was excessive.  All of you must be tired from standing up,
and I failed to take that into consideration.
Your grace is immeasurable, Your Majesty.
Now, then, let's wrap up the regular audience here.
After a short recess of half an hour,
let us continue with our discussion in the afternoon seminar.
Yes, Your Majesty, we will do so.