Where have you seen these criminals as tenacious as snakes?
Step aside.
You habitually made such vicious and lawless comments
as "His Majesty is the real traitor for not begetting an heir."
I have never said such a thing!
Shut up.  There are witnesses who've heard you.
How can an impotent one be called a king?
Of course, in that sense His Majesty is the real traitor.
That's not all!
You carried out a detailed plan to assassinate the king.
Look clearly at this.  This is the poison we discovered at your houses.
You planned to carry out the treason and usurp the throne with this poison.
Even if you ask me a hundred times, I don't know about that.
For whose sake are you saying we plotted treason?
Of course, that must be the crown prince, because you intend to rebel and place the crown prince on the throne.
The head of the treasonous bunch is the crown prince!
- Until that name comes out, keep torturing them!
- Yes!
The apprehended traitors have not named the crown prince yet.
Isn't that because they know the moment they make the confession, they are dead.
However, they will not be able to last in the end.
W-We really didn't do it.
Left State Councilor!  This is a setup.
But information about how you two tried to kill
His Majesty when he was the crown prince is also there.
Th-That is...
Yes, we did talk about that briefly.
But it was just a passing remark, and it was for the sake of Noron.
If you really think about Noron, you shouldn't have provided the excuse.
I've been going against you, not knowing my proper place.
I am begging you like this.
If not me, at least please release my grandson.
He is the eldest son of my family.
I, too, ask you for this favor.  Please at least spare my son.
It really is not true that we tried to put the crown prince on the throne, Your Excellency.
- Left State Councilor.
- Your Excellency!
Look here, Left State Councilor.
- Left State Councilor.
- Your Highness.
What brings you here?
Is it strange that I should come to the State Tribunal when I am suspected of treason?
The ones who want to drag me down are you.
I guess voluntarily presenting myself can become a problem, too.
I am here to diligently respond to the State Prosecutors.
However, before that, I have something I'd like to discuss with you in private, Left State Councilor.
The crown prince personally before the State Prosecutors!
And he is having a private meeting with His Excellency Min Jin Heon?
Yes, what do you think is going on?
We were trying to be courteous to him until the involved ones confessed his name.
But why purposefully at this night...
You have always moved unexpectedly, but today, you are even more so than usual.
Why volunteer to come to the State Tribunal?  And on top of it, meet with me in private...
At this moment, who must be the most elated one?
Wouldn't it be you, Your Excellency, who always considered me a pain in the neck?
So, maybe, I was curious about your facial expression.
You are acting too debonaire at a moment like this.
It's only when you get bitten by a tiger for the first time that you feel fear.
If you get bitten a few more times,
it's natural to consider that fear as your life companion.
But now I've begun to think that I should beat down that animal
because I can't take it anymore.
Beat down the animal?
I know you are keeping a strange distance from this matter.
Why would it be?
What's the reason you don't jump on this golden opportunity to strike me down?
Isn't it because you know
that behind this dirty contemptible scheme is Prince Milpoong?
Just in case you board the same boat and end up suffering a miserable fate,
you must be taking precautions.
I am sorry but I do not really know what you are talking about.
You ought to listen to more of what I am saying, Left State Councilor.
Because here comes the real part of what I am trying to say.
In that case, what do you say you transfer boats for the time being?
Wu and Yue in the same boat.
How about cooperating with me to maneuver politics to our advantage?
With you, Your Highness?
Just like the people of Wu and Yue, who were enemies but shared the same boat during the Warring States Period,
we can assist each other for the common interest.
Isn't this the politics in which Your Excellency has a lot of expertise?
Wu and Yue in the same boat, you say.
It is surprising that you've come to the point of making such a suggestion to me.
But you are wrong, Your Highness.
In the world of my politics, this is the time for borrowing another's sword to eliminate the enemy.
I do not want you to succeed to the throne.
And now I am able to finish you off without putting in my own effort, why would I bother?
Why would I practice politics that are not my kind but yours?
At least, you are
a person who thinks about this country.
Isn't that so?  You'd rather kill me
than come at me through made-up treason, leading this country and court into turmoil.
Isn't that the kind of person you are, Min Jin Heon?
- Your Highness.
- That's why tonight, we can at least stand together, face to face,
because even if we have different paths to travel, we can share the same goals.
Because at least you are a person who understands this level of politics.
So what do you say?
Are you going to watch the throne going over to the uncontrollable Prince Milpoong,
or will you board my boat for the time being
and try to push me off that boat later?
What is it, Left State Councilor?  What did the crown prince want?
Until when do we just have to look on?
Grown up to this extent.  Crown Prince, you...
Your Highness!
What happened? Will Left State Councilor take your side?
It is a venture with a rare chance of succeeding.
Because, like Min Jin Heon said, now is his chance
to cut me off through the hands of others.
No, nobody can enter the crown prince's quarters.
I don't care.  Just let me go in.
I'm telling you, you can arrest me as a traitor too later.
Would that work?
Can I see His Highness if I do that?
Moon Soo!
Your Highness!  Your Highness...
Why are you here?
Don't you know this is not the right time for you to come looking for me?
No.  This is  the  moment that I should come looking for you.
Because I am your younger brother.
Tabloid sheet...
I've seen it too.
I heard that the capital was plastered with these things today.
And this is... Dal Moon's doing.
I don't know... what to say to you.
"The crown prince is the not the predecessor king's son."
"He is the seed of another, from outside the palace, by whom Water Maid Choi got impregnated."
Oh, you are here.
I've enjoyed seeing your skills.  They were as good as I heard.
Somehow, I will have to compete with a beggar now for a bigger pie.
Sit down.
Do you even eat off of the same table as a beggar now?
Just give me a cup of drink.
Sure.
However, like yours, my heart cannot simply blame him.
As usual, we simply have different responsibilities to shoulder.
Do not give up like this, Your Highness.
We got a clue as to how Wi Byeong Joo falsified the case file of Inspector Han Jeong Seok's death.
Somehow we'll uncover it
and try to invalidate Wi Byeong Joo's treason charge.
To be on my side at a time like this...
I guess you are not very talented with line choosing  (joining the side that will ultimately help one's career) , either.
A person has to live as he is born.
I will bid you good night now.
I will take these with me and burn them.
No, wait...
Wait a second, Moon Soo.
- P-pardon?
- I'd better take another look at these tabloid sheets.
Your Highness, they are full of vile words.  Why would you read such things...
The characters are different.
Here the "Choi" characters
and here the "Mil" characters...
What do you mean, Your Highness?
Can't you see?  These characters on the tabloid sheets.
On each sheet is written a different Chinese character.
Court Lady Ha!  Cho Hong!
What is the matter, Your Highness?
Summon Ja Dong now. Hurry!
Pardon?
Yes, I got it.
Each tabloid sheet has one different character.
There must be a reason to this,
to why Dal Moon, who is literate, wrote characters with wrong meanings.
"Can I offer you a piece of advice..."
Can I offer you a piece of advice as well?
Well, I guess you should just read the tabloid sheets posted all over the capital.
I don't see you coming up with a better solution.
That's what Dal Moon definitely said.
Tabloid sheets. Read tabloid sheets was what he said.
This is the payment for becoming my man.  Open it.
Put that away.  I didn't do it for money.
It wasn't for money?
Then, what is it that you want?
You couldn't possibly have worked without wanting anything in return?
How can that be?
I do want something... earnestly.
Okay, tell me.
Whatever it is.
They are here.
Wait here.
That thing you want, I will hear it out when I return.
The poison I gave you before, you can't use it haphazardly.
(in Chinese)
There is no antidote for it.
None, none.
(in Chinese)
What are they saying?
They say the poison you bought is a very strong one.
Okay, okay.
(in Chinese)
Good.
Hey, that rat bastard left behind keeps getting on my nerves.
Now, why don't you change this location?
Change?  Why?
Goon Tae.
Hurry back, Hyung-nim.  This is a trap.
That Do Ji Gwang rascal has already caught on.
- What?
- I believed that surely, surely you must have some other reason.
There is no way my hyung-nim would have betrayed the crown prince for no reason.
Aish, what are you waiting for?  Do Ji Gwang's underling has gone back.  Quickly!
What is it?
I'm positive.  Each sheet has one character with a different meaning.
Here, too.
Different "bi"s.
Here, "sook." The "sook" characters are different.
Bin Bi
Choi Sil Jin Sook Geum Mil Bi
What on earth does this mean?
Royal Concubine Lady Choi.
Truth.
Bi Geum Yi Mil?
Royal Concubine Lady Choi Truth Bi Geum Yi Mil.
The original meaning should be...
My mother's secret.
The truth that I am not the king's natural son.
However, if it is read using the other characters,
the meaning becomes...
Sook Bin Choi Sil...
Defeat someone and
the break "Choi" means...
That truth is...
That's right! Not Geum but Mil.
It signifies Prince Milpoong!
In that case, Your Highness, isn't this a secretive message that Dal Moon is sending you?
Dal Moon did not betray me.
It means he is doing something for me right now.
No one is going to confess? Okay.
Keep going. Keep going!
He was an inspector and then served as a section chief in the Ministry of Defense, but he lives in a shabby place like this?
I know, right?
Who are you?
Yes, it's correct. I wrote both of those death certificates.
Why did you write  two back then?
I remember that a Saheonbu inspector requested them.
By chance, was that inspector someone named Wi Byeong Joo?
The one who moved you to the Ministry of Defense
was Wi Byeong Joo who was the lead inspector back then?
I don't know the reason, but yes.
Afterward, you weren't able to meet him.
I had a problem at the Ministry of Defense, so I went to meet him.
But he ignored me, so I became like this.
Do you remember Inspector Han Jeong Seok whom you worked with back then?
Jeong Seok?
You mean him?
On the night that Inspector Han died, I know that you were on duty.
That night at that place, who else was there?
The rebels aren't yielding.
We have to call the crown prince to the Inquisition Hall and cross-examine him.
We can't. We haven't found any evidence that the crown prince is involved.
However, there is circumstantial evidence that the rebels met to try to poison the king!
Can you say that it is related to the crown prince?
If it actually happened, who would benefit the most?
It's certainly the crown prince.
Chief Censor, that kind of statement is dangerous.
Everyone except Deputy Minister of Taxation and Assistant Officer of Uigeumbu
will agree that we should bring the crown prince to the Inquisition Hall.
What do you think, Left State Councilor?
At least, you are a person who thinks about this country.
Isn't that so?
You'd rather kill me than come at me through made-up treason,
leading this country and court into turmoil.
Isn't that the kind of person you are, Min Jin Heon?
It's meaningless to stall for more time.
I also think that bringing the crown prince
to the Inquisition Hall is the right choice.
His Majesty will come.
He will interrogate the crown prince personally.
He should,
because he needs to clearly reveal the crown prince's crimes.
I didn't think you would sling your bow until the end.
This caused turmoil in our court.
I can't sit and watch.
In this troubled time,
there is nothing I can do for you,
so this is a small gift.
Your Highness, this is...
It's the late king's item.
How could you bring such a thing to me?
To whom else but the son would I give his father's possession?
It's rightfully yours, Crown Prince, so accept it.
That the bad rumor that is going around the streets is a cruel lie,
I know best of anyone.
So if this is a false accusation, Crown Prince,
confidently clear yourself from the charge and return to your palace.
Queen Dowager.
Crown Prince.
In the end, you are going to stand at the Inquisition Hall.
Will you give us space for a moment?
It seems that my persuasion did not work on you in the end.
What do you mean persuasion?
If persuasion works in politics,
then why would there always be the same bloodbath in court?
Politics is about revenge, Your Highness.
Blood calls to blood. It never ends.
A continuous cycle of revenge.
That's politics.
His Majesty is coming!
Your Highness, wait.
Hyung-nim! Hyung-nim!
I found him. I caught him.
Bring the criminals.
Crown Prince.
We are wronged.
We have never planned treason.
What are you doing? Make those criminals kneel right now!
Crown Prince, do you truly not have anything to say?
Answer me!
If you confess your crime here, then I will at least save your life.
Your grace is immeasurable;
however, I have never thought of treason
nor planned a rebellion.
I cannot confess to a crime I did not commit
by any means, Your Majesty.
Then there is no other way.
I will have to interrogate you myself.
Officers, start.
I will interrogate the criminals and the crown prince here.
I apologize, Your Majesty.
But may I say one thing before the royal interrogation?
Unfortunately, I cannot agree
to this royal interrogation today.
It is because the crown prince
is not guilty of any charges.
I have known this truth since a long time ago, Your Majesty.
♫  You whom I love  ♫
♫  Become the moon light  ♫