Was I a bit too much?
You were.  But will you be alright after only half an hour?
Of course.  Since I am the king, I can stay seated on the throne.
This is why it's nice to be the king.
How many days on earth has it been already?
Regular audience, good morning audience,
morning seminar, afternoon seminar, evening seminar...
how many times in a day mouthing "Ministry of the Interior's section chief" and "Saheonbu"...
I even lost my voice now.
But we must hang in there, Lord.
What His Majesty wants is to wear us out.
Then, you need to say something, too, don't you?
Are you all mute with your lips glued shut with honey?!!!
It's a joint petition signed by the incumbent and past inspectors of Saheonbu.
The names supporting the reform number several hundred.
Everyone was waiting with bated breath,
but in fact, there were a lot of people wishing for this moment.
I've heard that His Majesty, too, is trying very hard day and night.
Just maybe this time, I think Saheonbu might
realize the reform that's been long overdue.
It should be. It must be so.
Your Majesty, this is...
What do you mean by a public audience  (when the king openly communicates with the people) ?
Are you saying you will really hold this audience?
Yes.  A public audience.
I intend to leave the palace and listen to the people's stories.
- However, Your Majesty...
- Thus far, the rulers of this country
regarded the people only as the subjects of their rule
but never lent an ear to their stories.
They viewed the people only as objects on the other side,
who work and provide free labor and taxes.
I know what you are trying to say.
However, a king personally facing the public is not an easy task.
I've lived among the people way longer than the time I spent in the palace.
A king with lowly blood flowing through half of his veins.
What monarch would be able to handle this matter better than a king such as I?
- What is this about?
- What is it?
Public audience?  What on earth is this?
Hyung-nim, are you illiterate?
It's written right over here.
It says right here.
"The king will come out and listen to the people."
So I am asking why will the king listen to us?
- I know, right?
- Is it a good thing?
His Majesty will come out to the streets?
To listen to what the people say about the military service tax?
Yes, there is quite a hubbub in the capital.
The king listening to the people?  What earth-shattering event is this?
At this rate, am I going to lose my livelihood?
If His Majesty attracts all the people in the market, what am I to do?
It is such a confident unfaltering move, so like His Majesty.
Is the king of the palace  (gwol in Korean)
trying to become the king of the streets  (geori)  as well?
Exhausting one issue after another, now even matters relating to the land taxes and uniform taxation.
Why do we have to listen to the subjects about these matters?
That is what we are saying!
But the ones who pay the taxes are the people.
Isn't it a given that we should listen to them?
But what do they know?
They are just simpletons who farm.
Yes, we are just simpletons who farm.
But we know all that we should know about.
The ones who pay the military service taxes are us.
So if not us, who knows better about the system?
That is right.
Today's occasion is for the purpose of listening to the people's voices.
Regardless of the high and low of your class and status, anybody may speak.
Without hesitation, tell me all about your hardships.
Until this hour?  It's been four hours already.
It's still not over?
The debate between the commoners and noblemen grew to the point
where no end can be predicted.
Really?  How can this happen?
Please make haste.  The public audience session got drawn out so food to feed the people is needed.
Yes, we are doing our best, but we are short of helping hands.
Excuse me, where should I put this?
Palace Maid Cheon.
You can put it over there.
What is going on?  Why are you here?
I heard that they needed more help here.
Even though I am a terrible cook, I am a mighty girl.
I came to help even if it's just doing chores.
Oh dear!  I was wondering where you were all day long and look who is here.
Queen Dowager.
I should have known!  This kid, Palace Maid Cheon.
Every time, she's caught helping His Majesty, I hear?
No, Your Highness, that's what I intended but—
Court Lady Ha, now you can take this kid Yeo Ji to the king's palace.
I always take a back seat, and she puts His Majesty's needs before anyone else's.
So what use do I have of her?
If you can't get any more use out of her, should I?
N-No, Your Highness, that is really not what I intended.
I was just kidding.  How flustered you are.
From the beginning, I intended to send you
to His Majesty's side when the right time came.
- Pardon?
- I had told her about His Majesty's feelings toward you.
If not me, who would understand his needs?
Court Lady Ha.
By the way, the palace kitchen seems to be very busy.
Let's help out too.
The court lady and maids of the queen dowager's palace?
But I'm going to help, too.
You might not think it, but I was quite a good cook when I was still a young girl in my parents' house.
Now, let me see...
So the biggest burden comes down to military service tax?
That is correct, Your Majesty.
Other taxes can be paid if we farm to death,
but there has to be available manpower to farm!
How can he be so indefatigable inside and outside the palace?
It will soon be 11 PM.
It can't be that we have to pass the night standing on the street like this?
I see.  I will not fail to take that into consideration.
However, Your Majesty, this is impermissible and nonsensical.
What do you mean by reducing the people's military service tax by half
and asking the noblemen to supplement the deficiency?
Why is it impermissible and nonsensical
to suggest that the landowner pay taxes for the land he owns?
If all landowners pay 2  du's*  of rice  (* approx. 36 liters)  per 30 plots of rice paddies they own,
the deficiency, after reducing the military service tax, will be canceled out.
Is the military service tax really getting reduced by half?
So the landowners will get taxed instead?
- That is unacceptable!
- How can you tax the noble class?
That is not allowed, Your Majesty!
Preposterous!
Your Majesty, I am sorry to point this out, but this public audience is improper.
Right now, you are trying to piggyback onto the support of the people and implement an unlawful policy.
Piggybacking onto the support of the people?  Me?
Okay, let's say that's what I am doing.
- But why is that improper?
- Pardon?
How can the country exist without the people?
Shouldn't kings and ministers, of all people, keep in close contact with their people
and embrace their best interests through piggybacking or what not?
Therefore, I shall listen to the opinion of each and every subject.
Now, those of you who have gathered here, make up your own minds.
Those who agree to the new military service tax law shall head toward the South Gate
and those in disagreement shall head toward the North Gate.
You shall do so.
I will follow the majority rule.
Now, everyone, let your opinion be known.
What are you waiting for?  Soldiers, maintain order to facilitate the people's movements.
Yes.
Let's go!  Of course, we should head to the South Gate!
Right on!
The military service tax getting halved!  What a dream come true this is!
Let's hurry on!
Let's go!
Long live the king!
That hanging board reflects the king's edict he personally bestowed on the people!
What does it mean?
What is written there?
- Gyun Gong Ae Min Jeol Yong Chuk Ryeok.
- Huh?
Love the people with fair  taxation
and build strength with frugal spending.
Love the people through fair taxation?
Yes, that is right. That is precisely that is what our king said.
That's right!
I feel so frustrated!
I want to read what's written there myself.
What an illiterate you are.
At any rate, the military service tax will get halved, right?
That is right!
Long live the king!
♫ The paupers of the yesteryear have returned without dying.
♫ Here I come.
♫ The world goes around.
I have clearly seen it.
Really?  Really?  Here, here, have one of these.
Everyone, have one.
Here you go.
Here.
Here, here.
Keep on talking.
Did Magistrate Choi's servants really sneak out rice from the local government storage?
Are you doubting my vision right now?
No, I am not doubting...
But why do you keep talking down to me?
A pauper may forget about the hand that fed him,
but, as a rule, he cannot forget the hand that slapped him.
So will I be able to forget the hand that stole the rice or not?
That's right.  I saw it too.
Five-hundred sacks from Yangjoo and 300 sacks from Seobinggo...
So that Magistrate Choi jerk is
gobbling up the state grains one sack after another like one would with a string of dried persimmons.
In that case, would busting them today would be the right thing?
The taffy is really sweet.  Sweet.
Would you like to eat my taffy, too?
Somehow, your face is familiar.
But how long do I have to keep this up?
Just eat taffy.
("Eat taffy" can mean "fu*k you.")
Shoo!  Shoo!  Shoo!
Now, now, now, scoot over.
Jang Dal. Ah Bong.
Aigo, do you feel so wronged and aggrieved?
When Our Majesty insists on doing away with discrimination so much,
how can you pettily eliminate only yourself from the pauper disguise?
Thanks to the great boss I was assigned to,
this is the most mortifying disguise I ever had to wear in all my fifty years.
Hey, but look here. Think.
Even if I besmirch this milky toned face,
who would believe that it's the face of a pauper?
This is a strategy and tactic.
Huh?  Still, our strategy worked, right?
Here, Jang Dal, clink clink.
So when are you going to bust Magistrate Choi who stole the state grains?
Now that the alcohol has fully brewed, I should grind it up and down in one shot.
This is it, Your Majesty.
He's been keeping to this place lately.
Now I will omit the usual comment about how I am indebted to you.
I've heard that you will hold another public audience in a few days.
How many times has it been already?
Why?  Are you wary of me?
That I might encroach on your streets at this rate?
Just be satisfied with your palace.
I have already told you that I am the king of the streets.
Just look at this guy, daring to use the word "king" to the king's face.
In the past and now, you are really a beggar who grew up without manners.
I apologize.
Thank you.
Let's go.
It's been a while, Your Excellency.
All the way to this humble place...  Your grace is immeasurable, Your Majesty.
Unable to hear any word about you, I hired a private eye to look for you.
As you know, I have a very capable informer at my disposal.
You must be talking about that person, Dal Moon.
You've kept him by your side for such a long time.
That is what I want to do with you, too.
Why do you keep turning down the call of the court?
It is because I have carried out all my duties.
You have a lot of young and talented people around you, Your Majesty.
- However, Your Excellency—
- There was a time
in the past when I
spoke of Saheonbu's haechi in this place.
Haechi. I mean the legendary animal that can distinguish good and evil.
But do you know why that animal only exists in legends?
It's because, in reality, it's impossible to judge good and evil.
That is so, Your Majesty.
In reality, it's impossible to judge good and evil.
No matter how much one dreams about it.
Therefore, I gave up on that dream a long time ago.
At one time, I thought in reality only the victorious and defeated,
the winner and loser exist
and that losing power meant defeat
and imminent death.
Because I got weary fast and despaired.
When, in truth, life and politics are
all about making tedious progress
while dreaming that dream of impossibility.
Your Excellency.
Someday, the time might come for you too,
Your Majesty, to grow so weary and despairing.
For you too, a day when you might have to retreat.
All I can do is to wish, with all the loyalty in my heart,
that day will come for you ever so slowly, ever so tardily.
With you, I believe it will be possible, Your Majesty.
Because you are not alone.
Because you have friends who share your dream.
- Who the heck are you guys?
- Me?
Wait...
Here.
- Secret Royal Inspector!
- Park Moon Soo!
Crack down!
You know what I am about to say.
You are all dead!
Everyone, collect information for His Majesty's next project.
Get to the bottom of it.
- Yes, Hyung-nim.
- Yes.
Now, now, here we go!
Yes.
Therefore, on this road,
not getting weary too easily, not despairing—
Your Majesty.
Day in and day out, governing and studying...
and you even secretly inspect the people's lives every other day.
Isn't it hard for you?
To have it hard is the king's way.
What can I do about it?
Just consider it your beau's destiny.
What?
Your Majesty.
And I have to come out like this so I can hold your hand once in a while.
This is what you call killing two birds with one stone.
Still, you cannot do this here.  What if someone sees us?
What's wrong with this?  Who's here anyway?
Your Majesty.
Aigoo, curse this
slow-witted, silly old man.
Please continue on with what you've been doing.
No, Ja Dong!  What do you mean what I've been doing?
That is why I said no.
That is...
This bridge seems to be full of problems.  It seems to be in need of reinforcement.
Reinforcement?  Do you mean rebuild it?
This place sees a lot of traffic.
But it's rickety as if it will collapse any moment now.
But there are lower class people living under this bridge.
What happens to them if the bridge is rebuilt?
Then I should ask them about their opinion.
What they think about rebuilding the bridge.
What?  Right now, you mean?
- Your Majesty!  No, you can't!
- Your Majesty.
You can't go by yourself like that!
Please call the royal guards now.  Hurry.
Yes.
Your Majesty, it's dangerous. Let's go together.
May I ask you a question?  Is there any inconvenience in using that bridge?
Please let me ask you a question.  When you use that bridge...
Thank you to our channel manager:
Asiane
Thank you to our English moderators:
jadecloud88, myriam_7c
Thank you to our segmenters:
SignsofSerendipity (chief), pilar_velasquez, asiane, kitty100,
mxover, dasfl49, bjohnsonwong, sl3388, s14950, jazmineheart,
Thank you to our segmenters:
earsds, hana_860
Thank you to our English subbers:
Baritaggie, monstertop, sune1004, dramadramaok, asiane,
sl3388, bluewind, grrrcat, awesomeharry, cgwm808
Thank you to our English editors:
SignsofSerendipity (chief), baritaggie, joysprite
Therefore, on this road, may I
not get weary too easily or despair...
Because life and politics are
all about going forward
ever so gradually.
♫  Since we met saying hello  ♫
♫  Should we break up while saying goodbye?  ♫
♫  Now the gentle and gentler wind hurts too  ♫
♫  In the spirit we both loved  ♫
♫  The wind is saying we must let each other go  ♫
♫  That’s the story now told by the gentle wind  ♫
♫  A gentle wind blows  ♫
♫  I turn past the memory of what was read  ♫
♫  In the next story which is blank  ♫
♫  What should I be longing for?  ♫
♫  Since we met saying hello  ♫