What did you say?  The Saheonbu... in the palace?!
Something like that happened?
The reason I kept silent after witnessing all those events
was that the killer was a young girl.
If Saheonbu gets involved with this, the whole country like in the past...
Your Highness, even so—
I know!  The crown prince, not the king, cannot participate in government.
He must not do anything related to government.
Because all related matters fall into the king's jurisdiction,
if he does so, that is as good as coveting the king's authority.
If you want me to pay the price for this, I will gladly do so.
However, even so, the reason I acted this way
is that I wanted to know
why such a young girl had no choice but to commit a murder.
You wanted to know why?
Maybe it was because I couldn't help
the lowly blood running in my veins.
What hurt her so much!
For what reason did she have to hold that dagger in her hand!
Before making her pay for her crime,
I wanted to know that first.
Your Majesty!  There is big trouble.
Officials of the Saheonbu, rise.
I, the king, will not allow you to turn in your resignation letters.
In that case, please transfer the crown prince's case to Saheonbu, Your Majesty!
We cannot trust the investigation results from Uigeumbu that covers for the royal family!
- Inspector General!
- We have all come to an agreement.
If we cannot be guaranteed of a fair outcome of this case,
all of us will resign from our posts.
Please grant our request, Your Majesty!
Please grant our request!
You want the crown prince?
All right, will you be satisfied if I do so?
If I give you the crown prince?
Your Majesty!
Your Highness Queen Dowager, you are the only one who can save the crown prince right now!
Crown Princess Consort, wait until the results come out.  Right now...
Even if you are unfamiliar with the palace etiquette, how can you be so rude?
- You show off your ignorance this way?
- Excuse me?
Queen, you are one to talk.
Your Highness, I merely meant...
Your Highness, this is Court Lady Jeong.
Your Highness, an urgent development.
His Majesty just announced that he would give the crown prince's case to the Saheonbu.
What?  Back to them?!
Your Highness Queen Dowager!
Is this king's order for real?
That is so.  However, His Majesty said he would give you time.
Before giving Saheonbu the right to investigate this case,
that was the condition His Majesty attached.
Your Majesty!
Within that time, you must prove your own innocence
and reveal the truth behind the case, Your Highness,
because you will go in front of the Saheonbu's jejwacheong  (supreme tribunal).
Three days.  Three days' time.
Please take it back, Your Majesty.
This will be a burden on you as well.
One in ten thousand, if something goes wrong...
I, too, will have to bear the brunt of Saheonbu and Noron's attacks.
- Your Majesty!
- However, my brother said he would like to know.
He is trying to understand how the people feel before punishing them for their crimes.
If I am the king, Deputy Minister,
shouldn't I also know that?
Who did you say croaked? Jipyeong  (chief inspector, fourth highest official in Saheonbu) ? Who is Jipyeong?
What a sh*tty name that is!
It's not a name, but a job title belonging to Saheonbu.
Whatever the heck it is,
why did the son of a bitch have to get stabbed in someone else's gisaeng house
and cause a freaking mess for me?
Still, thanks to him, I think the Saheonbu's movement to investigate us stopped.
But, still, how about going into hiding for the time being?
Telling me to hide?  Hey.
I am Do Ji Gwang.
How can they keep barging in when the business is closed!
I don't know!  They want alcohol now!
I-I had n-no idea I'd meet you again, Your Highness...
I'll say. If you opened a gisaeng house in Hanyang  (capital) ...
Aigoo, please spare me!
you should have informed me
when you are my connection as well.
Excuse me?  D-D-Didn't you come to kill me?
My bad, my bad.
When everything was because of my karma, why would I kill you?
Here.  Let me pour you a cup.
Y-Y-Yes.
Which bastard is ordering me to open or close the gisaeng house?!
Is that you?  Your liver must be bloated  (means audacious) .
You even brought an outside wench to my gisaeng house.
This guy accrues bad karma with his mouth.
Sit down.  I will pour you a cup, too.
And what is this wench blabbering?
H-H-Hey, calm down.  This person is...
You f_king loser!
The bitch and bastard couple have accursed, freaking bloated livers.
Hurry and clear out of here, all you f**king bastards!
In the past, I would've gouged out your eyeballs by now.
"Abstain from taking life."
Thanks to that precept, you still have good use of your freaking eyeballs.
- Head Merchant!
- Stay put.
This freaking dude
is really something.
Put that down and talk.
I think you two share plenty in common.
Dear me, I'm sorry!
Were you scared a lot?  You're Do Ji Gwang, right?
Don't worry.  I am here to help you.
Saheonbu used the bridge-burning tactic  (to make soldiers more fierce by affording no retreat) .
So are you asking for my help now?
I am not here to ask for your help.
Procedurally, I came to request your cooperation.
You want to save your face and get practical gains too.  And you can't undo the arrogance you exhibited before.
This is Chief Inspector Oh's murder case file.
I request official cooperation from the Capital Bureau as well.
His Majesty says he will give you the crown prince in three days.
But why three days?
I think it's a move to gain time.
Not only to pacify Uigeumbu,
but also to give the crown prince more time.
You are pretty good.
What? Are you in the know?  By what you said a while ago...
Before that, you need to give me the information in your hand.
- That is—
- If you want to set a new game, shouldn't you trust me, Deputy Inspector General Wi?
If the crown prince is an uncomfortable presence for you, too.
Your Highness.
There are about ten posting stations in Hanyang and its outlying parts.
And in the past, the master-killer band secretly operated out of these posting stations as their bases.
But it's different this time.
We could not find anything suspicious at any of the posting stations.
Thank you.  Work hard.
Have you heard of the master-killers?
I am not sure.
That's not the only strange thing.
There was no trace of pillaging either.
Ordinarily, the master-killer band had pillage as one of their objectives.
And there is more, Your Highness.
There is a common, but incomprehensible thread connecting all noblemen murder cases of late.
Common but incomprehensible?
It wasn't just Chief Inspector Oh.
All the murdered noblemen were too drunk to even control their bodies at the time.
It means they were defenseless at the time.
However, even then, the killers could not deal a single mortal thrust to their victims.
That's perhaps why they tried numerous times...
Even until their own hands were wounded,
they had to muster all the strength they had.
That means...
Yes, it means the killers were weak individuals, Your Highness.
Not only that girl, but also other killers were perhaps...
little children perpetrating the acts.
Children?
Why?  How?
Hey, there, hurry up.  You have to go back.
Okay, I'm coming.
I will find their base.
Why don't you look for that girl together with lady damo, Your Highness?
Such a small hand.
What I saw that day.
Even if it is just to find out her story, we must locate her first.
But, Your Highness, about this dagger.
Are you sure this is the right one?
The one that you saw, I mean.
Since they say the smoke flue here is the problem, sweep it well.
If His Majesty catches a cold, that will be a huge problem.
If you want to earn even a coin, sweep it well.
Yes.
Gosh, so cold...
Children must have been summoned because of the problem with the heated floor of Your Majesty's bedroom.
On a cold day like this, it must be a hard labor.
I looked into this at Aekjeongseo.
However, the letter...
Probably the letter "Aek" was worn out.
And that's why even the Saheonbu did not catch on.
Where is this dagger used?
This Haeminseo is also a place where homeless children end up in.
Make sure not to skip a single temple where they give out alms to the poor and scan them all.
Yes, Hyung-nim.
What are you doing?
Too many places use the same type of dagger.  We can't find it at this rate.
How about asking for Uigeumbu's help?
By the way, who are those children?
They are children who clean the heated floor flue systems.
- They are not public slaves, but...
- Flue system?
Yes.
Can't be...
Black ash.
Lord, have you found out anything?
Nothing from Haeminseo.  How about you?
I think we'll have to check out the temples on the outskirts as well.
Lord, I'm afraid we can't ride that boat.
We can't?  Why not?
I don't know.  The boat is almost empty but they said no even to my offer of twice the fare.
There is another ferry dock over this hill.
Let's go and see.
- This way, Lord.
- Wait.
That boat. Something seems strange with it.
They are boarding only children.  Why?
Why refuse twice the fare
and board only children who seem penniless?
It was you, indeed.
Wait.  I am not trying to hurt you.
Let me go!  Let go of me!
I'm trying to help you!
Do you understand?
Why did you do that... I want to help you.
What do you mean you'll help me?
Yes, I saw you killing a nobleman.
I also saw that scary word "master-killer" etched on your body.
But before catching you and punishing you,
I wanted to find out the reason why you had no choice but to do that.
Do you understand?
So that I can help you.
Help me?
How can you, Lord?
You're a nobleman yourself.
You are of the same class.
So how can you help me when we came to this because of you people?
If it weren't for the rent money,
my older sister would not have been sold off to Qing.
Had the master given us just a bit more time,
my father would not have tried to sell me too.
Even if we had nothing to eat but the dirt,
I just wanted to live here.
Even if this is a lousy land,
I just wanted to live here with my family.
Getting sold off?  What do you mean?
Are you saying
someone tried to drag you off to the Qing Dynasty?
Who is there?
Your Highness, I think guards are coming.
- What do you want to do with this child?
- Hide now!
- Pardon?
- Before the guards get here, hurry.
What is it?
Your Highness, I am sorry.  We heard strange noises, so...
It was nothing.  So don't worry yourselves and go on your way now.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
We are hungry.
Wait just for a bit.
- We are hungry.
- Wait just for a bit.
This is the master-killer band's base?
Those children are killers?
How can this be?  How can something like this happen?
Who are you?
Oops, sorry, I didn't know you were there.
Don't you think you're too petty?
What did you say, bastard?  Petty?
Hey, are you done talking?
Lord Yoon Hyeok!
Please see me for a second.
I have something to tell you regarding the human trafficking case.
Hey, who do we have here?
If this isn't our newbie, Park Moon Soo?
- Please let go of this.
- Let go of this?
Hey, hey, see how cheeky our newbie is.
- At this rate, he'll punch me too!
- Yes.
Before I throw you one, unhand me now.
Hey, you, Park Moon Soo!  Do you want to die that bad?
Hey, bastard, you are a newbie.
The lowest-ranking officer that is even inferior to an animal.
If your sunbaes tell you to bark like a dog,
then the newbies ought to bark!
Ah... Newbie. That stupid hazing.
Fine, the dog bark.
Okay, I'll bark to your heart's content.
Do you know why the world is sh*tty?
People like dogs don't realize they are like dogs and
act like dogs while getting paid by the government.
The people are getting sold like dogs and dying like dogs,
yet you are trying to guard your own doggy food bowls
and just act freaking dogs!
You are exactly like trashy dogs, dog-shit!
Because of sons of bitches...
Did I bark enough for you?
Lord Yoon Hyeok, please come see me for a minute.
Oh, okay.
Hey, is he really crazy? Is he really insane?
Not sure. I don't think that is it, but it is better than barking.
Out of all the new inspectors,
I believe it was the most creative dog bark.
What did you say, bastard?
Let's go together.
So that's what the child said?
That instead of being sold, all she wanted was
to live in Joseon with her family?
The crimes of the children who committed murders
cannot be overlooked, Your Majesty.
However before that, please also redress this nation's evils
that caused the children to hold a knife.
I see... that this is the kind of place I'm sitting at, Crown Prince.
I, who couldn't even protect my people who are being sold,
am sitting in this warm room,
fixed by those small hands.
Deputy Minister of Taxation.
- Queen Dowager.
- It's been a while.
Is it okay to act as if we are close friends?
When I was young, I saw you often at my home.
I learned from your late father.
I heard that the crown prince is inside of the king's palace.
So how is the crown prince in your perspective?
- Pardon?
- You act as if you don't know.
You know what I am asking.
I'm not sure about what kind of person His Highness is yet.
However one thing, if we're talking about the ability to rule,
the kind of ability that this nation will need in the future,
he just might have it.
Are you sure? The crown prince insisted on it?
Yes!
Your Highness.
- Is it ready?
- Don't worry.
It will be taken care of soon.
I apologize for making you come all this way, Your Highness.
However, the law is law.
So the Saheonbu is only trying to do its duties completely.
That Saheonbu is fighting to keep the law,
I am more aware of it than anyone else.
Who that law is for is but another matter.
I'll take you to the Jejwa Hearing Room, Your Highness.
- Break down the door!
- Yes, Sir!
The crown prince has arrived.
We will follow this order.
You know how Saheonbu's hearing process goes, right? You've been here before.
What a nice walk-through. I'm thankful.
It seems a bit early for those words
if you think about the trouble you will go through soon.
Ah, do you remember what you've said before?
You said that when you learned what happens to those falling out of favor with the powerful,
you grew up.
- What?
- That's when I acted up, not knowing anything about this world.
But when I learned what happens to those falling out of favor with the powerful, I grew up.
It would have been nice if you'd truly had a revelation back then.
Then you wouldn't have acted rashly again.
- What are you doing?
- Come here!
Where's your boss?!
Hey!
What is this? Who are you all?!
Are you Do Ji Gwang?
Let's go obediently when we're using words.
You're under arrest for illegal human trafficking to the Qing.
No, wait!
- Your Excellency Min Jin Heon.
- Before you hold a jejwa hearing,
there is something you must see.
Min Jin Heon.
Bring the criminal.
How could the nation's Saheonbu treat their people this way?
That person is...
That child is...
How is that child...
♫  You whom I love  ♫
♫  Become the moon light  ♫
It's them! You must not lose a single one!
Are you going to say this is politics, too?
This is not politics but logic.
Help the crown prince, Your Highness.
Joseon is not the king's nation. It's the noblemen who govern the nation.
So are you saying we should abandon the crown prince?!
Does that mean you support the master-killer band, too, Your Majesty?
As requested by your council, dethrone me.
What are they doing not stopping the subjects?
They are all subjects stepping forward with their names on the line.
This is the real public opinion that nobody in the world can manipulate.
You will trust the people's opinion that can turn away in an instant as well...
Show them that you are still going strong as the crown prince.
♫  I become tears  ♫