Over here.
You didn't do anything suspicious, did you?
Of course not.
I was at the gisaeng house on purpose, all day before coming here.
What about the key to the armory?
Thanks. You know how horribly we've been treated as Namin.
If this plan succeeds, your position will be made in the central government, too.
Wi Byeong Joo, indeed you are...
You came right back. I was expecting you tomorrow.
The situation in the capital isn't good. So—
I heard the king has beaten the plague.
Ah, I heard your minions talking.
You need to control them.
The guys are uptight because they think the plan might not work.
It's nothing to worry about.
The guys are nervous before the mission.
Watch them carefully so they don't waver.
Yes, General.
Keep up with your impudence.
The one who needs me... is you after all.
Crazy bastards.
What's all this?
Check the capital's situation again.
Yes, General.
What is this?
This is the key to the armory at the Cheongju Government Office.
He's a hoobae  (junior)  from the same hometown, so it was easy to get him onboard.
Since we are both Namin, like us, he has a deep resentment for the government.
It was worthwhile to get you out.
I didn't know you would become useful like this.
However, I heard that the plan at the capital didn't go so well.
Why? Are you worried that the rebellion will fail?
Then why don't you leave now before it's too late?
No. Of course not.
Do you know how long we've been preparing for this?
We won't ever fail.
This mountain stronghold isn't the only one. Gyeongsang, Jeolla, Pyongan.
Once the rebellion starts,
fallen noblemen and subjects who are tired of being exploited
will all rise together.
Do you think that's the end? The capital and even inside the palace.
There isn't a place without our allies.
What is this?
Hey there. Is anyone here?
Damn it.
I said is anyone here?!
What is this sound?
General, outside right now...
What is going on?
You're doing a great job.
You say you're preparing a rebellion, yet you don't even know that a mouse has been poking around.
What have you been doing?!
What are you doing?
Find out who it is right away.
Yes, General.
He can't have gone far. Search the surrounding area thoroughly.
Yes!
- What are you doing? Hurry!
- Yes!
I'll be borrowing your horse.
Oh, no!
Hey!
If someone saw this mountain stronghold,
the rebellion plans have been discovered, no?
- General!
- Have you found him?
I apologize. It seems that we've lost him.
- If the person who disappeared heard any information—
- Stop.
I'm the one who will do the thinking.
- The rebellion plans are going to change.
- Okay.
Send my command to everyone right away. The rebellion will start sooner.
Firstly, tonight we will execute what we have been planning at the capital.
Yes, General.
Chief Royal Secretary, are you there?
Tell all of the Border Defense Council members to come by 3 PM.
Dal Moon! Dal Moon!
Is anyone inside? Dal Moon!
Lord Moon Soo, how are you here?
Is Dal Moon inside? I have something urgent for him.
Are you saying the rebels have infiltrated the capital and the palace?
The current police commissioner is one of them.
I saw and heard it myself at Cheongju.
We have to send word about the rebels' mountain stronghold
and their plans to His Majesty immediately.
Is anyone out there?
Ask the Left and Right State Councilors to come immediately!
Rebel armies?
Is that really true, Your Majesty?
Lee In Jwa from a fallen Namin noble family in the region of Cheongju.
None other than he enabled Wi Byeong Joo and Prince Milpoong to escape their places of exile.
And with Cheongju as his base, he is attempting a rebellion right now.
Moreover, there is intelligence that his spies have infiltrated even the palace and capital.
Spies inside the palace?  How is that possible?
That is why I have asked you two here.
I have a confidential favor to ask in order to expose them.
Here comes His Majesty!
But aren't they Lee Gwang Jwa and Jo Hyeon Myeong?
Everyone, be seated.
There is an urgent piece of intelligence so I need to discuss it with you.
These are the newly appointed Minister of Defense, Lee Gwang Jwa,
and Commander of the Five Supreme Military Headquarters, Jo Hyeon Myeong.
Those two are the minister of defense and commander of the supreme military headquarters?
But, Your Excellency, what is going on?
Did you know about this, Right State Councilor?
I don't know.
I just don't know what's going on.
Your Excellency, is it true that there are signs of treason?
It is still just a possibility,
but His Majesty seems to consider this plague episode the doing of traitors.
How disconcerting!
Anything else?  Are there other signs of the treason?  Do you have any information?
If there were, would I stay quiet?
So far, that's all I know.
Because of that, His Majesty called back his closest aides, Lee Gwang Jwa and Jo Hyeon Myeong, out of insecurity.
The king is getting close to the truth of the mysterious disease.
Fortunately, that is all he knows.
But he is also suspecting treason.
Speaking of which, a message from the mountain stronghold has just arrived.
Because of a small problem, the plan in regards to the capital has changed.
What?
You have not gone home yet, Police Commissioner?
I ran into the Royal Messenger of the Ministry of Defense,
so I was briefly discussing the worries over this situation.
You are working hard.
At times like these, your responsibility becomes even heavier.
Please do your best.
I will keep that in mind, Your Excellency.
Yes, Your Excellency.
Go on with your work.
Your Excellency.
Everyone, hurry!  We will evacuate the mountain stronghold now!
Yes!
Hurry, hurry, pack this up.
Have you delivered my commands to Gyeongsang, Jeolla, and Pyongan?
Yes, even the ones for the capital must have arrived by now.
- Check one more time.
- Yes.
We have to finish off the king in the capital before deploying the armies.
- Your Majesty.
- How is our plan progressing?
We are getting ready as you have commanded.
The Ministry of Defense and Five Supreme Military Headquarters will do all they can do.
However, there might be danger even from inside those organizations.
- Pay particular attention to security.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
Spies from the rebellious band have infiltrated even the palace.
How could this happen?
We must discover them all and catch them at all cost.
Just in case, make some soldiers tail the Deputy Ministers of Works and of Defense.
Excuse me?
Tell Lee Gwang Jwa, the newly appointed Minister of Defense,
that right after the Border Defense Council meeting, Police Commissioner Nam Gyeong Jin
secretly contacted Ministry of Defense Royal Messenger Lee Sa Cheol.
Yes, Your Excellency.
- My Lord.
- Are you ready?
Yes, we can roll out right now.
- Let's go!
- Yes.
Did a big case break out?  Why are you armed?
Hey, Ah Bong!  Why is the lead inspector acting like that?
- Aish, when I'm so preoccupied!
- Aish?!
You are getting in the way... sir.
G-Getting in the way... sir?
Hey!  You guys tend not to take me seriously lately.
I guess you guys are all busy.
- Inspector Park.
- My Lord.
How long has it been, My Lord?
What do you mean treason and espionage in the capital?
There is no time to elaborate.  Let's go for now.  We have to hurry.
Inspector Park, you must need this.
Get in line.  Everyone, check your weapons.
Is something up, Commandant of the Royal Guards?
There's intelligence about treason.  Spies are hiding in the palace.
What?  Spies?
You have to be extra vigilant to maintain palace security.
I am going to guard His Majesty.
Yes!  I will take my soldiers and guard the east part of the king's palace.
- Let's go!
- Yes!
Assemble all the police force right away.
Tonight, they must invade the palace and behead the king.
Yes, Lord.
- What is going on?
- Huh?
The movements of the royal guards seem unusual today.
What would we, palace maids, do with that knowledge anyway?  Let's go.
- Why are you guys still here?
- Pardon?
Haven't you received the order?
There is suspicious activity around Gwangheui Gate, so go there immediately!
- However—
- What are you waiting for?!
Just two remain here and the rest, move out!
I will take charge of guarding the king's palace.
Yes!
However, Lord, the commandant of royal guards told me not to, even for a second—
Lord!
Lord Police Commissioner!
Lord, we are in big trouble.
- The king seems to know about our involvement.
- What?
Lee Je Moon, a Royal Guard lieutenant, sent word.  We must come up with a way to deal with this quickly!
What are you doing?  Where do you think you are?
You will go head to head against the elite soldiers of the Ministry of Defense
with mere underlings of the Police Bureau?
Anyone who resists will be struck down without mercy.
Arrest Police Commissioner Nam Gyeong Jin and Ministry of Defense Royal Messenger Lee Sa Cheol.
Yes!
For now, we must escape and join the main force.
Main force my butt.
You are all finished.
It'll be better if you lay down that sword.
The front yard of the police station is already surrounded by the soldiers of the Ministry of Defense.
Strike!
Stop right there!
Who are you, wench?
Let her go right now!
Don't you hear me?  Now!
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
Are you alright, Yeo Ji?
Yes.  And you, Your Majesty?
Your humble servant, Minister of Defense Lee Gwang Jwa
and Inspectors Yoon Hyeok and Park Moon Soo
have received your royal command and arrested the traitorous bunch.
Your Majesty.
- Right State Councilor!
- Yes, how did it go?
Both Deputy Ministers of Works and Defense who had joined the rebellion were apprehended.
They are branches of the same Soron Faction.
To cut them out must have been a difficult decision, Ha Gok  (Jo Tae Goo's pen name) .
Rotten branches will kill the tree.
What we must safeguard are not the little branches, but a big tree called Joseon.
How big is the rebellious force led by Lee In Jwa?
I could not ascertain the exact number, but roughly they seemed more than several thousand.
Several thousand rebels?
More importantly, they are not all.
From Gyeongsang, Jeolla, and Pyongan Provinces, too,
they were going to rise up simultaneously.
As soon as I got your message,
Commander of Supreme Military Headquarters Jo Hyeon Myeong headed to Cheongju with the elite troops.
If they were caught unawares, soon—
Your Majesty!
Find out the detailed status now!
Yes.
- Minister of Defense!
- Your Majesty.
The situation got worse.
Commander of the Supreme Military Headquarters seems to have gotten there one step behind them.
This is...  This!
The Cheongju fortress has been seized.
It fell into the hands of the rebels in the end.
Your Majesty!
Lee In Jwa, in the end, he had to...
To this nation!
♫  Since we met saying hello  ♫
♫  Should we break up while saying goodbye?  ♫
♫  Now the gentle and gentler wind hurts too  ♫