- Out of the way!
- Aren't they the Saheonbu soldiers?
What on earth is going on?
Are they going to do it in the end?
- Aish.
- What on earth is going on?
This is the house of Yoon Gyeong Je, Rebel Lee In Jwa's father-in-law.
Any letter or object Lee In Jwa sent to him is fine.
Whatever the evidence, you must turn up something.
Yes.
What are you doing?
His Majesty definitely said nobody would be found guilty by association only.
Your son-in-law plotted treason,
and how is it possible that you are not guilty?
- Take the criminal into custody now!
- Yes!
What did you just say?
Saheonbu arrested Lee In Jwa's father-in-law?
Didn't I order not to find anyone guilty by association?
Your Majesty, Chief Censor and Chief Scholar are here.
- Your Majesty.
- Let them in.
Your Majesty.
I know what you are going to say.
Still, do I need to hear it?!
How about the court?  What is the situation like?
Right State Councillor.
Hand down His Majesty's next order right now.
Yes, Your Excellency.
- My Lord.
- Have you heard?  Right now in Saheonbu...
- Where is the lord inspector general?
Where are all the high-ranking Saheonbu officials?
Start interrogating Lee In Jwa's father-in-law and his family members right now.
The judicial rights rightfully belong to Saheonbu.
Irrespective of the king's orders, we shall do our job—
Irrespective of the king's orders?
If this is not treachery and treason, what is?
What are you doing?
What do you mean what I am doing?
I, too, am doing my job as a Saheonbu inspector.
I am simply trying to punish criminals who dare to
defy royal commands.
They are trying to drag Inspector Park out of their office?
You know I still network with the higher-ups.
The chief inspector was livid and ordered me to fetch soldiers.
- What?
- But I really didn't think that was right, so
I first came to the inspectors' room.
Lead Inspector, are you just going to watch this?
Now, let's go!  We should lend support to Inspector Park.
H-How about me?
My personality does not like putting myself forward!
Just why did I tattle on this?
Aish, did I get attached to them just because I've been mingling and conversing with them lately? No, no...
Has Saheonbu made its moves?
The interrogation will start soon.
Even with the royal command, what can they accomplish
when the judicial branch of this country insists on doing its job?
The court must be totally empty too.
Just tell him to try to govern with just the Namins.
He won't be able to last.  Impartial hiring not based on political affiliations...
Which monarch has won this battle so far?
Nobody was able to get it done.
Your Excellency!  Your Excellency Minister of the Interior!
What is it?
His Majesty seems to be determined to see this through to the bitter end.
He is really asking for it!
What are you saying?  What on earth happened?
I am sorry, Your Majesty, but what do you mean you are appointing me to be the prime minister?!
Exactly what the job titles say.  I am appointing you as prime minister
and Commander of Supreme Military Headquarters Jo Hyeon Myeong to the post of Saheonbu inspector general.
Your Majesty!
No!  That is unacceptable!
How can you entrust me, when I have so little experience, with such crucial duties?
I cannot carry out your order either!
Then, will you make me go on this path alone, Teacher?
Is it how it is?  Will you, too, leave me to fend for myself?
You know what I am trying to do here!
It's the path of Magnificent Harmony that this nation's court has never attained before!
Perhaps this may not be a royal command, but a shameless favor.
This hard path whose good end cannot be guaranteed,
please walk it with me.
- Have you heard?
- What?
The palace is in havoc because Namins were hired.
Look here.  Look here!
Let me ask you a question.  According to soldiers,
the king hired Namins and caused a whirlwind in the palace.
Is it true?
Gosh, what will a criminal do with that knowledge anyway?  Be quiet.
Please answer me.
Are Namins really being placed in key positions?
That is how it is!
For the sake of stability, His Majesty
is pushing hard to create opportunities for Namins.
But just look at what the high-ranking schmucks are doing.
Whether Noron or Soron, afraid that they might lose their turf war,
they are throwing royal commands or whatnot to the dogs!
I mean, did they even take on any sword fights because of the rebellion?
Those dirty old farts.  Step down for a bit!
- I lost my lifeblood-like eldest son in the Anseong Battle.
- Aigoo!
When they haven't even once held a sword in the battlefield,
what right do those scoundrels have to call for this or that?!
Agreed!
B-But the s-storyteller is me.
Hold on a sec.  Let me say something too.
Until when will those schmucks stir-fry, pan-fry, and only fight?
This is why only commoners get squeezed to death from battles and exploitation!
Yeah!  Here, here!  Well said!
Through and through, a hundred times, a thousand times right on.  Isn't that right?
They are saying only the truth.
Me too! I have something to say too!
Aigoo, gosh, well done. In fact they're doing better than I did, by golly.
The public sentiment deep down is to that extent?
Don't even make me start.  I couldn't even cut them off to throw in a word.
They must be venting as much as they've suffered.
Hasn't everyone seen enough political feuds in the court to be sick and tired of them?
This time, the public opinion will surely move as one.
Inform the palace of this fact now.
Yes.
Hyung-nim! Hyung-nim!
I've found the peddler's house.
It's this way.
Hyung-nim, this is the house.
Bok Dan!
Your Highness, we have to go quickly.
What are you doing?  Do you want to be caught?
Hurry, Your Highness.
It can't be... Prince Milpoong.
What is wrong?
Th-That is... The rest of the silver taels,
I'd like it if you gave them to me now.
- What?
- If you pass through here, it's the ferry dock.
The boat will be waiting, so I should take my leave here.
But look here, that's not what you promised.
What are you up to?
Wh-Wh-Why are you acting like this?
You were suspicious from early on when you kept glancing sideways.
Is the boat really there?
I'm asking whether you are trying to backstab us?!
When you're traitors, what?
Give it here.  Give me the silver taels!
- You bastard!  How dare a wretch like you—
- No!
Yoon Yeong, are you okay?
Is anyone there?
Isn't anyone here?
N-No!  D-Don't m-make noise, any noise.
Yoon Yeong.
Over there! Over there!
Excuse me, the traitors I reported are over there!
Yoon Yeong, you must stand up.
You have to come with me.
At least you said...
you'd make a lowly gisaeng like me your queen.
Still, not even once
did I embrace you with my whole heart.
I'm sorry.
No, no...
It's my fault, Yoon Yeong.
Don't be like this, Yoon Yeong.
I will wait for you from there,
so don't be too afraid to come.
I will be waiting... as your queen in the other world.
You must come... as king.
Yoon Yeong.
As king...
No.
Don't go without me, Yoon Yeong.
Don't abandon me.
At least you, don't abandon me.
Over there! Just over there will be Prince Milpoong!
Over there!  Over there are the traitors!
Prince Milpoong isn't here!  Find him!
Yes.
Bok Dan.
Despite it all,
I don't think I can bear to watch her die.
Bok Dan.
I'm Bok Dan.
You?
Dal...
Dal Moon.
Here...
Get up.
What are you doing here, you fool?
You didn't
live so heartlessly
to end up like this.
I didn't let you go
so you could leave like this.
No!
No.
That woman... ended up like that.
Head Merchant Dal Moon personally buried her body.
Dal Moon.
They are looking for Prince Milpoong everywhere, so...
I am sorry, Your Majesty, but an urgent message has just arrived from Saheonbu.
What discourtesy is this?
I said the high-ranking Saheonbu officials are to make way for me.
We cannot obey.
We, the Saheonbu high officials, cannot accept installment
of the newly appointed inspector general, who is unfit for the job.
Under pain of death, we will not pull back from this stance.
Are you saying you will disobey the royal command?
Those fellas, in the end...  What are you waiting for?
Summon soldiers now!
No, Inspector Park!
- Are you going to cause a disturbance here?
- Lord!
What do you think they are after?
It's an excuse that His Majesty is persecuting the Saheonbu.
So are you going to just watch this?
Even when they are obstructing the lord inspector general?
We must.  His Lordship is also enduring this humiliation.
Stop.
Oh my!
The Saheonbu high officials are blocking the inspector general from coming to work?
I am extremely sorry, Your Majesty.
Yet... what's the reason you helped me?
You think it's no use in the end.
Why?
That is...
the reason is, Your Majesty...
that is the most genuine form of politics.
Even if advancement is brief and in the end one has to retreat,
not getting weary, not despairing,
never letting go of the old hope till the end.
From there, the world, little by very little,
gets better, that's why.
Let's go on
not getting weary, not despairing,
even if in the end we have to retreat, that is.
His Majesty will go outside the palace.
All soldiers, take upmost care to guard him!
Yes.
Here comes His Majesty!
H-H-His Majesty.
What do we do next?
L-Look over there!
Here.
My Lord!
Your Majesty.
Saheonbu high officials, hold a jejwa hearing  (Saheonbu's supreme decision-making tribunal)  right this instant.
I have something to say personally in that meeting.
Here comes His Majesty!
Over here!
That's right.
I am the king.
I am. None other than I am the king!
The reason I have personally come to Saheonbu's jejwa hearing room today
is because I want to tell you that the new Joseon
needs to start here at Saheonbu.
This nation's Three Offices, and particularly Saheonbu,
have long been rotten to the core with evil customs and traditions.
Who of this nation would trust Saheonbu,
and who would believe in the fairness of Saheonbu?
Your Majesty, I am sorry but—
Stop! I have not finished speaking.
However, I will not overlook Saheonbu's long history of corruption any longer.
This is for the sake of this country and all officials of Saheonbu.
As of today, from this place,
I proclaim to the whole world that I will abolish
the Ministry of the Interior's section chief system,
which has long held the appointment rights over Saheonbu,
and I will completely reform that system.
♫  Since we met saying hello  ♫
♫  Should we break up while saying goodbye?  ♫
Carry out the sentences against the criminals immediately.
Since I am innocent, I will walk tall and go of my own accord.
Currently, even the popular sentiment favors His Majesty.
What cause is there for you to fight?
This time, I will definitely keep my promise to make you pay for your sins.
Well, perhaps a life without any regrets... isn't that even more terrifying and frightening?
I won't die by your hands.
- Lee Geum!
- Your Majesty!
I am the king.
♫  The wind is saying we must let each other go  ♫