This drama is fiction and the characters, names, institutions, events, organizations, and circumstances are not real.
Last Episode
What is that?
I'm trying to let you know about the nature of the Park So Yeong case.
The nature is that you cornered her too harshly and did something a lawyer should never do.
- That is why Park So Yeon—
- "That is why Park So Yeong died."
- Is that what you still think?
- No.
The one who killed Park So Yeong is Hong Seok Pal.
The one who killed Park So Yeong is not Hong Seok Pal.
It's TK Law Firm's Chairman Choi Tae Gook.
Park So Yeong's cell phones, Han Seong Beom/Lee In Su recordings...
Han Seong Beom, Lee In Su
With this, my brother...
father, Lee In Su, Han Seong Beom, Lee Si Hyeok, Han Dong Oh...
You'll be able to make them pay for their crimes.
The fact that you had a tough time because of Father and Hyeong...
I'm very sorry about that, Noona.
Disciplinary Action Subject.
What is your reason for claiming that Chairman Choi Tae Gook killed Park So Yeong?
I visited the hospital.
I'm pregnant.
Do you have evidence that it is my child?
I never saw you like that, but you're really acting like trash.
Park So Yeong was pregnant with Chairman Choi Tae Gook's child.
Create a scandal with An Gang Hoon. Something irrefutable.
You're telling me to do something like that while I'm pregnant?
You're the real trash.
I'll give you the money you want.
Get rid of the baby with that money and live quietly doing something else.
Chairman Choi Tae Gook ordered pregnant Park So Yeong
to create a scandal with Assemblyman An Gang Hoon
with the intention to remove the rival of Assemblyman Lee In Su.
Keep your promise,
or else, the fact that I'm pregnant with your child
and that you're the one who created An Gang Hoon's scandal...
I'll expose everything!
And Park So Yeong used her pregnancy and An Gang Hoon's scandal
to ask for a large sum of money.
What nonsense.
Commissioner, that is a one-sided argument.
It is slander.
Recent files
Since I was able to eliminate that bastard, An Gang Hoon, thanks to you,
I owe you a big debt, Chairman Choi.
Now, you just need to put on your wings and become President.
Of course, you need to put on your wings and fly.
Lee In Su, Choi Tae Gook, Han Seong Beom, we Three Musketeers.
All of us will fly together.
However, isn't this all just speculation?
Circumstantial and situational, speculation cannot be evidence.
According to the police investigation,
the person who murdered Park So Yeong is Hong Seok Pal
and Hong Seok Pal committed suicide from guilt.
Han Gi Taek, who assisted his suicide,
confessed everything and has been arrested.
So doesn't this mean that there is no evidence that Chairman Choi Tae Gook murdered Park So Yeong?
Isn't that right, Disciplinary Action Subject?
There is nothing. It's just her argument.
Please stop the disciplinary action subject from making absurd statements.
If you don't, this disciplinary committee will also be punished for violating the rules.
Beloved Son, Ha Seung Yoon
When Jae Yi left this world,
all the shameful moments I lived through unfolded in front of my eyes.
"Why did I live like that?"
"For what reason?"
"How should I go on living?"
For my child, who must be watching me from somewhere,
how to live from now on...
so that I won't be ashamed.
What happens next depends on your decision.
That's...
not something I can decide.
Check for yourself.
What Chairman thinks of you.
And then decide.
Chief Ha Il Gu
Attorney Oh,
I'll give you... everything that I possess.
So Yeong.
What did you come all the way here for?
You're always like that.
You're the one who called me and yet says, "What did you come all the way here for?"
Can't you just speak without any twisted meanings or feeling me out for once?
I warned you that it wouldn't be a good idea for you to come here.
I liked you because you were smart, but why are you disappointing me like this?
So you liked me?
I didn't like you at all.
How funny.
Why don't old geezers know their place?
They don't have any shame, either.
I told you.
I told you more than a dozen times!
I'll abort the child and leave this country if you give me money.
Do my words not sound like words to you?
Must you show your ugly true colors like this?
That's right.
So make a deposit.
Or else I'll jump off from here and die.
What are you doing?
If I die pregnant with your child,
it would be so entertaining, right?
Make a deposit!
Or else I'll jump off and die from the great TK Law Firm that you're so proud of!
All right, I understand.
I understand, so come down. All right?
Don't do anything dangerous.
Stop acting like you're worried all of a sudden and make the deposit first.
Five billion won.
You should at least give me that much.
Disciplinary Committee of Oh Su Jae: 2nd live broadcast
Material Witness Seat
I am TK Law Firm's Chief of Secretary, Ha Il Gu.
I was planning to dispose of the CCTV footage of Chairman Choi Tae Gook
pushing Park So Yeong,
but I held onto a separate copy, just in case
and recently handed it over to Attorney Oh Su Jae directly.
Resignation Letter
Chairman,
my son wrote me a letter before he died.
"Dad, please live comfortably now."
So you're saying to even go so far as to record a suicide note?
So do you have a body to put in my place?
You think I can't find one?
I made arrangements for the death of a younger friend of mine
I've known for a long time to follow your orders.
Drink that and be quiet.
I'll let you go tomorrow.
For real? Right?
Thank you!
I trusted you and followed your command
to hurt Kim Dong Gu and even let No Byeong Chool die.
If you do that, I'll take responsibility for the rest.
Don't worry about that part.
Upon seeing you dumping everything on me,
I was able to make a decision.
Of course, I will pay for my crimes.
From, Ha Il Gu.
- Father.
- Yes, Son.
The things that were in the secret space in your library,
I'm the one who handed them over to Noona.
What?
You did?
Why would you?
I'm sorry, Father.
Please stop all of this here.
What?
Do you know how I have lived?
You, my own son.
- You dare to—
- Father!
There's not a single moment of my life that I'm ashamed of.
I was always fierce and always did my best.
Father.
Please pay for your crimes.
Get out!
I never want to see you again.
Get the hell out now.
Assemblyman, ten years ago, the disciplinary action subject
made a deal regarding the trial she represented as a public defender.
Director Baek Jin Gi proposed to the disciplinary action subject,
that if she gave up the active defense of the Kim Dong Gu trial,
he would let her join the TK Law Firm and
and as a result, the disciplinary action subject was able to enter TK Law Firm.
She made a deal with something as sacred as a trial.
If that's true,
that's a violation of Paragraph 2 of Article 24 of the Attorney Act,
Breach of Concealment of Truth and Prohibition of Perjury.
This is an issue where heavy punishment can be imposed on the disciplinary action subject,
regardless of who killed Park So Yeong.
Isn't that right?
Well...
doesn't that reflect Chairman Choi's opinion?
That means Chairman Choi also took part in the deal.
That's not true. Father did not know about the deal at all.
It was between the disciplinary action subject and Director Baek Jin Gi.
Director Baek used Father's name
to better his own life and suggested the trade.
Disciplinary Action Subject.
Do you admit to these claims?
I admit to them.
Chair
I request that you call the defendant at the time,
Kim Dong Gu to the Material Witness Seat.
If the incident ten years ago is mentioned,
Gong Chan will come forth as Kim Dong Gu.
Have that in mind.
Gong Chan?
Gong Chan was Kim Dong Gu?
You didn't know?
That arrogant brat was Kim Dong Gu?
Catch up on your studies and conduct your investigation.
If that case is mentioned along with No Byeong Chool,
you will also be sweating since you put No Byung Chool in jail.
Are you going to let them see that you're sweating in the Chair's seat?
Kim Dong Gu?
Kim Dong Gu is here?
Let's call him over if he is here.
Hong Gi Pyo
We need to hear from the party concerned as well.
Kim Dong Gu.
Please proceed to the Material Witness Seat.
My name is Kim Dong Gu.
Ten years ago, I was forced to falsely confess
because of the abuse from the police and the prosecution.
No one was willing to listen to me
or believe my story.
Everyone tormented me so that I would say
that I was the culprit.
I knew then how much of hell it is
when no one listens to or believes you in this world.
And then...
I met a person who said she believed me.
That is the disciplinary action subject,
Attorney Oh Su Jae.
After I met her as my public defender,
I was able to plead not guilty.
But it was difficult to prove
that the false confession was because of the abuse from the police and prosecution.
The investigation room did not have a CCTV at the time
and the abusive acts toward me
were done in secret.
However, we found out that there were abusive acts at the time.
I was also the newbie detective of the team at the time.
At the time, Chief Kang Gil Ju ordered us to
get the confession from Kim Dong Gu,
saying he's the culprit by whatever means possible.
Chief Kang also had close relationship with the prosecution,
and the prosecutor in charge was Prosecutor Seo Joon Myeong.
That crazy bastard.
The reason why Kim Dong Gu was found guilty
was because his DNA and fingerprints were found on the knife.
We had his confession and his fingerprint as reinforcing evidence
which more than sufficed to prove him guilty!
However, the confession was falsely provided due to abusive acts
and doesn't qualify as evidence according to Section 309 of the Criminal Procedure Act.
Besides Kim Dong Gu's fingerprint,
two additional unknown fingerprints were found on the knife.
Since his confession was found to be false,
the unknown fingerprints' identities become more crucial.
Did you find out the owners of those two fingerprints?
We did.
Fingerprint 1 belongs to the late Jeon Na Jeong.
Fingerprint 2...
belongs to Chairman Choi Tae Gook.
- What is this?
- What does this mean?
This shows the possibility that Jeon Na Jeong
instinctively blocked the knife with her hands and
that Chairman Choi Tae Gook had stabbed and killed Jeon Na Jeong, who was still alive.
That's not true!
We killed Jeon Na Jeong.
Han Dong Oh, Lee Shi Hyeok, and I killed her.
We killed her!
CEO, please calm down.
Calm down.
Choi Ju Wan, Han Dong Oh, and Lee Si Hyeok.
Those three might have believed that they killed Jeon Na Jeong
up until now, but it is not true.
The three of you brought the girl here.
The three of you also killed her.
Is that right?
Is that right!
- Yes.
Get lost.
I'm really sorry father.
You listen to me right now.
If someone asks you about today,
your answer is "I don't know."
Only that one answer.
Nothing happened to you today, okay?
Do you understand?
Yes.
Yes, Father.
After arriving at the scene, Chairman Choi
sent Choi Ju Wan, Han Dong Oh, and Lee Si Hyeok home.
He noticed that Jeon Na Jeong who he assumed was dead was actually alive. And then he killed her.
Are you writing a novel right now?
These are mere speculations! You have no evidence!
I do have the evidence.
Chairman Choi Tae Gook's Chief of Secretary, Ha Il Gu.
The evidence is the video that he secretly recorded that night.
Chairman Choi killed Jeon Na Jeong with a knife that was in Chairman Han's house
and wiped the blood with a handkerchief that Ha Il Gu gave him.
Ha Il Gu kept that handkerchief until now and
gave it to us.
No...
The handkerchief has a particular print on it.
Disciplinary Committee of Oh Su Jae: 2nd live broadcast
You can see that the print matches the pattern on Chairman Choi's ring that he always wears.
Please proceed to the Material Witness Seat again, Ha Il Gu.
What relationship did you have with Chairman Choi at the time,
and how did you end up taking that hidden video?
Long before the incident,
I'd been doing the errands and
providing information for Chairman Choi while I was in a crime organization.
I had a bad feeling about how he called
me over to Chairman Han's house that night.
I filmed that video
out of fear that I might be used as a scapegoat for everything.
What did you do after?
Jeon Na Jeong, who was killed by Chairman,
was tied up with compression tape.
I took the tape off of her and
while I was abandoning the body at the construction site,
- Someone help!
- Kim Dong Gu came and found the body.
Please hel—
I had to frame him as the culprit.
I would like to offer Kim Dong Gu...
my sincerest apologies for what I did.
I'm sorry.
This is where you bastards trampled on
my daughter, Jeon Na Jeong, and Kim Dong Gu.
How foolish of you not to recognize the place even with the photo.
You'll pay for your shamelessness.
Yesterday, you all must have heard the name
Kang Eun Seo at the confirmation hearing of Candidate Baek.
On the day of Jeon Na Jeong's death,
the reason why the three men kidnapped Jeon Na Jeong
and dragged her to Chairman Han's house was because of Kang Eun Seo.
Kang Eun Seo, who was taken to Chairman Han's house,
lost her earring while running away from the house.
This is a picture of Kang Eun Seo's earring that I found at Chairman Han's house
which I had purchased.
Kang Eun Seo met the
part-timer Jeon Na Jeong while running away.
Jeon Na Jeong then put on her uniform on Kang Eun Seo.
This is Jeon Na Jeong's uniform that
Attorney Oh's team found.
This analysis result shows that the bloodstains
on the uniform were identified as Kang Eun Seo's.
Kang Eun Seo, who is the daughter of Candidate Baek and also my fiancée,
was kidnapped and violated by Choi Ju Wan, Han Dong Oh, and Lee Si Hyeok.
Jeon Na Jeong was also kidnapped by them.
And Lee In Su, Han Seong Beom, and Choi Tae Gook had conspired to cover their sons' crimes.
Also, shielding them from judgment were
the police, prosecution, court, and the press.
I hope that they all receive their proper consequences.
I offer my sincerest thanks to Attorney Oh Su Jae,
who stepped forward to reveal the truth, which is not an easy task.
"Thanks to Attorney Oh for Revealing the Truth"
Korean Bar Association
Choi Tae Gook, Han Seong Beom, Lee In Su
He forced the investigating agency to violate the victim's rights to make him falsely confess
and refused to accept it when we attempted to correct the false confession
at the trial, by turning it into an issue of trust.
The police, prosecution, and court
treated the trial like a theater play,
repeatedly shielded the organized crimes of those who mock judicial justice.
They willingly used the press to strengthen their fortress.
I also was surrounded by their influence not realizing how shameful my life was.
I confess those embarrassments and
no matter what kind of punishment that may fall on me, I'll willingly accept that decision.
Korean Bar Association | Attorney Disciplinary Committee
Since the chair and some of the committee members
were found to be involved in the mentioned incidents,
the current committee has lost the right to punish the disciplinary action subject.
Disciplinary Action Subject, Oh Su Jae
What the disciplinary action subject— No.
Attorney Oh has exposed
shall be followed up thoroughly by the investigating agency.
Also, as a fellow disciplinary committee member,
I confess that this disciplinary committee was highly flawed from the beginning.
The committee was formed due to Chairman Choi's influence in the legal field.
Some committee members' objections were not heard.
I apologize to Attorney Oh and the nation,
and offer my respect to Attorney Oh and her team for their lonely fight to
reveal the truth about the death of Park So Yeong and Hong Seok Pal as well as the incident from ten years ago.
Ajumma.
Dong Gu.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, Dong Gu.
Ajumma.
I'm sorry it was so late.
Not at all.
Thank you.
Hansu Bio has
made a false impression that the clinical trial of their new pipeline drug has been approved.
It was also found that they've committed deal-breaking acts such as accounting fraud
and money laundering through a paper company.
This violates the seller's statements and guarantees.
Thus, SP Partners reserves the sole right to cancel the agreement.
The down payment and the cancellation penalty shall be refunded to us.
Father.
Why?
Jeon Na Jeong.
Did you really kill her?
No, right?
Dong Oh, Si Hyeok, and I killed her, right?
And you just told Chief Ha to clean it up.
That's the truth, Father. Isn't it?
It was all for you.
What?
You're wrong, Father. That's...
That's not for me at all.
You know how sorry I was to you and how much I agonized.
That's why I followed your orders without complaint.
I broke up with Su Jae because you told me to and
also made it look like Seung Yeon gave birth to Jae Yi.
So I did all that.
I did everything!
Everything for that reason, Father!
It was revealed that Candidate Lee In Su and his son
were also involved in the matters discussed in Attorney Oh's disciplinary meeting.
Are they all true?
They are all true.
- What?
- What's happening now?
Are our sons' mistakes all taken care of?
You got rid of the body as well?
Yes, Sunbaenim.
We're on the same boat now.
Chairman Han, Inspector General Choi Tae Gook, and me, Lee In Su.
We're now hashing together toward our future.
Ten years ago, Assemblyman Lee In Su colluded with
Chairman Choi Tae Gook and Chairman Han Seong Beom to
cover up the crimes of his son, Lee Si Hyeok,
Chairman's son, Choi Ju Wan, and
Chairman Han's son, Han Dong Oh.
He also has a legal responsibility for the death of Park So Yeong and Hong Seok Pal.
As of today,
I resign from the spokeswoman position.
SP Partners claimed that they reserve the sole right to cancel the agreement
and ordered the refund of the down payment and the cancellation penalty.
Will Hansu Group accept that?
They probably should accept it, don't you think?
Chairman Han Seong Beom's money laundering operation through a paper company
deeply involves TK Law Firm Chairman Choi and Assemblyman Lee.
The issue of Hansu Bio's third-stage trial drug.
Hansu Bio Pipeline Drug Trial Stage Victims Documentation
It's true that they attempted to conceal the truth about the victims of trials,
and both Chairman Han and Managing Director Han are
deeply involved in the crimes that Attorney Oh exposed.
I apologize as Head of the Legal Department
and resign from the position as of today.
Su Jae, my last act was not bad, thanks to you.
We three should grab a drink together, Su Jae.
Kwang Jin Barber Shop
Hansu Group, TK Law Firm,
and SP Partners' acquisition are hot issues.
According to the agreement terms, Hansu Group and TK Law Firm
were found liable for an astronomical amount of money owed to SP Partners.
As such, both companies and their subsidiaries
are on the verge of bankruptcy as well.
That is not all.
Assemblyman Lee In Su, is no longer a candidate since
his candidacy was cancelled.
Assemblyman Lee, Chairman Han Seong Beom, Chairman Choi Tae Gook, and
their sons now need to be investigated.
Tomorrow morning, there will be an emergency arrest.
This is my last time contacting you.
TK Law Firm
Oh Su Jae, Partner Lawyer
Ta-da.
What are you thinking so hard about?
How should I live from now on?
What is a good life?
A proper life?
Whatever it is, do it freely.
Slowly.
As happily as possible.
It doesn't matter if you fail on the way.
What?
Since I'll be by your side no matter what.
In the world that's never fair,
where things have never been equal nor balanced,
the law must be applied to everyone fairly and equally.
You must do your due diligence to undertake the responsibility of this solemn duty.
Youngpyeong District Promotion Center Opening Ceremony
It was so close.
I was almost there.
Oh Su Jae
Yes, Chairman.
Hey!
You are the only one.
The only one who answers my call.
You seem drunk.
You should stop now, Chairman.
How would it have been if I hadn't raised you?
If I
had taken you in as my daughter-in-law,
how would it have been?
Would we have still ended up here?
But Su Jae,
I have always been fierce.
I did my best every moment.
No, Chairman.
You can't call that your best.
That was an act of evil.
No, it was not evil.
That was the best for my life.
That power protected me.
That's how I came up this far.
You should regret it.
You should be ashamed.
You should be humiliated.
That's...
what weak people
do.
I'm not... ashamed of my life.
Just one.
The only regret I have is...
letting you into my fence...
again.
Although you
stopped me this time.
Don't...
be mistaken... and think...
that you won.
Where are you right now?
You... did not...
beat me...
did not beat me...
Chairman. Hello? Chairman!
Is something wrong?
One second.
(T/N: Korean 119, emergency number same as US 911.)
TK Law Firm.
Chairman Choi is intoxicated and behaving abnormaly.
They're my position. All the positions at TK.
Are mine.
Intern, associate, partner, CEO.
Even the security guard and maintenance positions.
They're all my positions.
They're here!
Do you admit to the paper company money laundering?
How do you feel about the prosecution investigation?
Is the Hansu Bio clinical trial concealment true?
Where did the Hansu Group slush fund go?
I'm an honest person, you know.
See? I'm not making a show on a wheelchair and pretending to be sick like others.
I did do some bad things.
But the real bad guy is the dead Choi Tae Gook.
I'm sure he went to hell.
Hansu Group's slush fund. Where did it go?
It's a little late for me to say this, but beware who you befriend.
- Please answer!
- Wait!
- Assemblyman Lee In Su.
- Stop him!
What was that!
It's okay. Let him be.
It's fine. It's fine, everyone.
Don't worry. Everyone.
I'm okay.
I'll be forgiven by the people of this nation.
I'll be sure to come back alive!
- Hang in there!
- You're the best!
"Fair Country, New Country"
"Carry on, Lee In Su!"
Choi Tae Gook
Your Honor,
the defendant has committed a grave crime.
In 2008, after receiving a request from Chairman Geum Se Yeong of Geummyeong Savings Bank
to make a trial go in his favor,
he pressured his junior, who was the judge in charge
and received 200 million won from an illegal lender for introducing him to Chairman Geum.
However, Your Honor,
the defendant is sincerely regretful of his crimes and
had a difficult time taking care of
his daughter, who suffered from a mental disorder, as a result of being the victim of a crime.
He also strived to reveal the truth of the said crime.
Lastly, he donated the entirety of his assets to the
victims of the Geummyeong Savings Bank scheme.
His efforts to secure practical compensation for them.
Please take those facts into consideration.
Defendant. Do you have anything you'd like to say?
Defendant
I've been extending my pathetic life pitifully.
It was a shameful life, looking back.
Thanks to Attorney Oh Su Jae,
my daughter's resentment was relieved and the pile of evil acts was excavated.
Above all, thanks to Attorney Oh,
I can stand here today and
face the consequences of my crimes today.
Thank you.
Your Honor.
Please give me a severe sentence.
Anyone who commits a crime should be punished.
More than anything,
please show that a legal professional needs to be punished more heavily.
6 Months Later
Long time no see, Attorney Oh.
Father asked me to say hi to you for him.
Is he doing well?
Yes.
He said his heart is at ease.
I'm a bit worried because Eun Seo seems to be looking for him.
I came to make a suggestion.
I want to invest in your Central Law Office.
Why don't you build a large law firm properly?
And provide legal advice for my company as well.
Hansu Group is still being obnoxious about the agreement cancellation.
I'm grateful for the suggestion, but I'll have to turn it down.
I'm happy as I am now.
I'm curious about what makes you so happy.
Because you do really look happy.
The fact that every day is entirely mine.
That I move and decide with my own will.
That the results are also entirely mine.
Those things were more decent than I thought.
Whether the results are good or bad.
I rejoice in the good things, and if not,
just say, "So what?" curse and move on.
Or I don't.
Funny, right?
But I'm
content with myself living this way now.
I envy you.
Congratulations.
Legal Clinic Center Additional Recruitment.
At Legal Clinic Center,
we plan to provide class action lawsuit and legal advice
for victims of the Hansu Bio trial drug.
We ask for active participation from you, the students. /
Here she goes again.
Of course she's consistent.
Not even ten minutes left.
I will never send my client to jail.
This is the first and the last Practical Fundamentals for Lawyers class.
However,
there are things that you need to observe as a lawyer.
Just because you know the law a little, don't abuse the law to suit your taste or
abuse it for specific interests or for specific people.
The law needs to be fair and just for anyone and everyone.
Another one.
Every law has a loophole.
One of the lawyer's skills is to find that loophole and use it to your clients' advantage.
I also became the so-called "successful lawyer" with that tactic.
Nonetheless, standing before you,
I am not a successful lawyer.
My success involved many shameful moments.
Because I have lots of regrets and shame,
I plan to become a lawyer who's no longer like that.
A lawyer who isn't regarded as being anyone special.
Rather than the success itself,
think more about how you will proceed toward that success.
I hope you all contemplate that more fiercely.
Lastly, protect yourself in any situation.
Never let anyone control you and become a firmly rooted lawyer.
This semester is the same.
Lectures, once in a while.
What? Again?
- You don't mean...
- No way...
Your entire grade will be on verdict analysis, 100 percent.
One hundred percent?
There are some things that I promised the top student last semester.
Twenty million won, enough to cover one year's worth of tuition plus extra.
TK Law Firm intern lawyer employment.
Of these, the 20 million won plus extra was awarded last year.
You're here, right? The one who received my money?
- Who is it?
- Is it her?
Is it you?
I'm going to be an intern at your law office instead of an intern at the TK law firm, right?
Never mind if you don't like it.
What do you mean?
I'll be there for sure.
You can leave now if you don't like my way.
- This is nonsense.
- You should stay.
This is Legal Clinic Center's guest lawyer, Attorney Song Mi Rim.
Seek her help whenever
you have a question about the verdicts.
Since I know a thing or two about these,
your questions are welcome anytime.
There is no "20 million won plus extra " this semester.
- What?
- Then why am I here?
I'm broke.
Everyone, come up and take a copy each.
Had I known, I would've carried a prettier umbrella.
♫  And you say the place before we both liked it  ♫
Let's go.
♫  Passed the bedtime, you gave the halo away  ♫
♫  Try to be okay, be all right  ♫
♫  Cause I, I always break down when you cry  ♫
♫  What about us? We could have all  ♫
Why Her?
♫  Forget about that  ♫
♫  When I lose control, I wanna hold you back  ♫
♫  What about us?  ♫
♫  What about us us today?  ♫
Thank you to our channel manager: sarykawaii.
Why Her?