This drama is fiction and the characters, names, institutions, events, organizations, and circumstances are not real.
Then, think carefully.
How you'll take care of Park So Yeong.
Take care of what?
Why would I do that? Huh?
You know what you do best.
Burying people without anyone knowing.
Hey, Chief is asking for you.
First, I'll strategize...
I'll make sure you don't get an arrest warrant...
So...
So, you have to be honest with me.
I'm sorry.
Hong Seok Pal's video is so shocking.
I'm sorry, Attorney.
Mi Rim.
Attorney Oh, I'm not sure about this, to be honest.
I shouldn't be doubting you, but
you did tell Hong Seok Pal to kill Park So Yeong, right?
I could recognize your voice even in my sleep.
That's your voice on the recording.
Where you said "Bury Park So Yeong..." That part...
That's right.
Her devoted subordinate is doubtful.
You did say that, right... Attorney, Oh?
That's right. Admit it.
Mi Rim...
Hey, what's that?
What?
What's going on?
What did you say to her?
I dropped it and picked it up.
I asked what you said to her!
She told me to get lost! Why?
What did she say? Huh?
What did you whisper to her?
Who's all shaken up over a whisper?
What the hell is she saying?
Hey, do it right!
Episode 8
Chief Kang!
Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office
The right of prosecution and police investigation was reformed a long time ago.
How dare you tell me to turn the case over to you?
The police are still in the middle of the investigation.
We're already investigating Park So Yeong's death.
Since the police made a huge mistake of concluding her death
as a suicide when in fact was a murder.
This has nothing to do with that case!
No, it's not.
Hong Seok Pal even left a suicide video saying that he killed Park So Yeong.
This case should be investigated with Park So Yeong's murder case.
Of course, as for necessary investigation,
we'll make our request to the police.
But Chief...
Inside the guest ledger that Hong Seok Pal left behind, your name came up
like you were his best friend.
I'll request an additional investigation from you if necessary.
Establishing Law and Order
You can place the basket in an empty spot on the shelves,
and you can use the blanket underneath.
All right!
- Whoa!
- Hey, hey, hey...
Godori is the best!
(T/N: A winning move in Go-Stop game.)
- You like it, right?
- Let's go!
- Geez...
- Come on...
There!
Oh, I've seen her in the news.
Attorney Oh Su Jae!
You're her, right?
Wow, a powerful bitch joined us.
There!
It's not her?
It's really not Professor's voice?
"Bury Park So Yeong..." That one?
No.
She definitely said it wasn't her.
I didn't say the last part.
The last part isn't my voice. Find out about that.
How about other stuff?
"Think carefully about how you'll take care of Park So Yeong..." How about that one?
That was her.
She told me that she had said that on the phone with Hong Seok Pal.
Then out of the phone call, the beginning part is her voice and the last part is fake?
Why? Why only that part?
To fabricate a voice, you need several hours of voice data
and you have to give it to a specialist.
That's pretty cumbersome.
The charge of inciting murder...
"Take care" is somewhat vague...
They needed her to say "Bury her."
- Since that clearly means to kill her.
- Yeah.
He looked for ways to avoid the blame, even after making up his mind to die.
That guy is really...
Hong Seok Pal had come to the law firm before.
He said he had something to say about Park So Yeong.
He asked to meet with Chairman Choi.
Why would Hong Seok Pal...
He couldn't meet Chairman,
and he met Chief Ha briefly.
That was a week before he died.
We should trace back Hong Seok Pal's whereabouts for that week.
He had to have made up the fake voice
and had to prepare for a car explosion.
He must've been busy.
But why didn't you tell the police?
The fact that it's not Professor Oh's voice?
Is it that you couldn't do it or didn't want to do it?
Since Attorney Oh only told me in secret,
it means she doesn't trust anyone.
Not the police nor prosecutors. Not even the law firm.
Geez, this is crazy...
Attorney Oh Su Jae, charged with inciting murder and abetting suicide
Crazy trash reporters!
This is just the beginning.
They'll say worse things, and they'll become facts
and she'll be marked a culprit even before the trial.
Suspect
Die, you bastard!
Come on!
You killed her!
- You devil!
- Are you even human?
Suspect
It's hell.
We must find evidence that proves Professor's innocence as soon as possible.
We can't let her go through such hell.
We must save her.
When you visit her tomorrow, tell her not to worry
and that we'll rescue her for sure.
For inciting the murder of Park So Yeong
and abetting Hong Seok Pal's suicide,
the search and seizure of Attorney Oh Su Jae's office and residence have begun.
This case has been forwarded to the prosecution working on a relevant case.
The police are continuing to provide additional investigation efforts.
TK Law Firm
Assemblyman An Gang Hoon, who came up as the reason for
Attorney Oh inciting Park So Yeong's murder,
made his statement before he left for the United Kingdom.
That's right.
According to Assemblyman An Gang Hoon,
He said he's never even met Attorney Oh Su Jae in person.
According to Assemblyman An Gang Hoon
He's offended by the allegation of his involvement with deceased Park So Yeong.
And says that he has never even heard of the name Hong Seok Pal.
"Will take legal actions for misinformation"
If his name is mentioned again as relevant to this case,
he said he'll take legal action.
Assemblyman An Gang Hoon is firm on his stance.
Yes, Assemblyman An Gang Hoon...
All the documents are password-protected so it will take some time to open them.
But they're indeed Chief Han Gi Taek's files.
Good work.
And this is
from Police Chief Kang Gil Ju. He asked me to give it to you.
He said he found it while searching through Attorney Oh's home.
Police Chief Kang Gil Ju
Hey, Chief Kang.
Chairman, I went through the things we found during the search and seizure
and gave it a first look.
I didn't find much in them
except for the thing I gave Chief Ha.
I'm not sure if Attorney Oh was pregnant or not.
In any case, I sent it over to you, so you can look at it.
Okay, will do.
DNA Parentage Test Report
Combined Paternity Index: 661,085, Probability of Paternity 99.9998%
Probability of Paternity: No - Client 1 and Client 2 are not biologically related
Meeting Room
Why the long face?
How are the meals?
Did you get to eat something?
How did you sleep?
It was okay.
The pre-arrest interrogation was set for tomorrow afternoon.
And...
It's gone, huh?
Yes.
Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office
2001 Dispatched to Ministry of Justice, 2000 Seoul Eastern District Prosecutors' Office
2004, 2005 Seoul High Prosecutors' Office
Chairman Han, Assemblyman Lee, and you Chairman Choi...
These are footage of you enjoying yourselves in my bar.
I didn't make any copies. I swear it on my life.
I'm telling the truth!
And...
the trouble I've caused
sending you, Chairman Han, and Assemblyman Lee this footage
is because I was sad about being left out of the Yeongpyeong District project.
To be honest, I put my life on the line to be loyal to the three of you.
But it was so unfair, and I got so upset
You didn't think about the consequences of being so troublesome?
My apologies, Chairman!
I deserve to die, Chairman!
Assemblyman Lee is especially angry and says to get rid of you.
Chairman Han also agreed.
But I have no intention of doing that.
I like you, Hong Seok Pal.
Chairman, thank you!
Thank you!
Chief Ha will talk to you.
Do whatever he says.
Yes, sir! I'll never forget this for the rest of my life!
And I promise my loyalty to you going forward!
Loyalty!
Hostess bar villa footage
Don't try too hard. You've done enough.
I'll try harder.
I'll do my best all the way.
Gong Chan also told me to tell you that we'll get you out. Don't you worry.
So, just come out and start dating, two of you.
I already figured out that Chan is interested in you.
I said we'll get you out, Attorney Oh.
The forensics conducted their investigation.
But they said they didn't find much because everything was so burnt.
They suspect the fire got started by the charcoal briquette that was in the trunk.
The fire caught on the gasoline and butane gas and everything exploded.
Any trace of installing explosives?
What explosives? I said it started with charcoal briquettes.
He lit the charcoal briquette himself and put it in there.
This was definitely suicide.
But still, you're already sending the car to the junkyard?
The forensics went through everything
and Chief hates the sight of it. He wanted it out of there.
Traffic Information Collection System
Gosh, what do we do?
You know what you do best.
Burying people without anyone knowing.
Did you try to separate the voice only?
Yes, I did, but...
Why? It's not working?
You know, there is too much noise in the footage.
Look.
This, over here.
This is all the noise from the background creating interference.
Most critically, they played the cell phone recording while taping the video.
Stuff like this is too tough.
Good job. Please work on it a little more.
Sure, will do.
What the heck? You were so confident about figuring this out.
I didn't know it was like this.
But Hyung, it's a little creepy hearing it firsthand.
Hey, it's fake. Why be creeped out?
We don't know if it's fake or real.
It could be real.
She would never say that, man!
Don't talk about her like that.
I'm just saying we should keep various possibilities open.
So there's no other way?
It's not that there is no other way.
What is it?
Bring me the original file.
The original file of where the fake voice came from.
Hello!
Any explosives inside cars...
What are you talking about?
- Hello.
- Hi.
Excuse me, but do you also install explosives?
- What did you say?
- Install explosives...
Everyone said that installing explosives in cars was nonsense.
They treated us like complete idiots.
This is nuts.
Gosh, this place is too big.
How are we going to look through this place?
We wasted so much time because we lost him.
He couldn't have destroyed it in the meantime, right?
No way.
I'll look this way.
Okay.
Attorney Song, that way!
Gosh, you crazy punks!
What's the rush? Why junk it so fast?
What do we do?
I feel like the walls are closing in.
And we're running out of time.
I'm going crazy here! Really!
Regarding Attorney Oh Su Jae of TK Law Firm
being under suspicion of inciting murder and abetting suicide,
I'd like to express deep disappointment
and I'll point out three things in the following.
First of all, TK Law Firm has nothing to do with this case.
Secondly,
TK Law Firm and all the lawyers in the firm
will not get involved in this case investigation and trial.
Thirdly, we hope the truth of the case will be revealed.
Our position toward Attorney Oh Su Jae
will be determined accordingly in swift fashion.
That will be all.
TK Law Firm has officially announced that they will not get involved in this case.
The focus is on what position they'll take toward Attorney Oh Su Jae.
Next news.
SP Partners halted its acquisition of Hansu Bio altogether.
SP Partners said Hansu Group has been uncooperative during the inspection process
and has taken decisive action by halting the entire process.
Halting?
What do you mean they want to halt?
CEO Yoon Se Pil decided unilaterally.
We just found out through the news.
Hansu Group has not made any official statements.
Depending on the Hansu Group's cooperation on the inspection, SP Partners says
- they will decide whether to resume or not.
- Damn!
What does he mean by "cooperation during the inspection"?
What's he talking about?
That's all an excuse, Father.
They're making an issue out of the fact that Attorney Oh Su Jae is not around.
What?
Well,
there was a special line item that said the acquisition cannot proceed without Attorney Oh Su Jae.
So, you're saying you put this line item in the contract with your eyes wide open, right?
The Hansu Bio acquisition must be processed by TK Law Firm's Attorney Oh Su Jae...
I mean, I already reported it to you, Chairman...
You're out of your mind, asshole!
Get lost!
My apologies.
Get lost before I beat you up with a pork chop!
It must be crazy over there.
Chief Han Gi Taek is probably getting all the crap dumped on him.
When Su Jae put in that special line item,
she was way ahead of the game.
I'm sure she's way ahead of the game even inside the detention center.
Someone who had something to do with Park So Yeong.
Choi Tae Gook
Han Seong Beom
Lee In Su
Hong Seok Pal
On the night Park So Yeong died,
TK Law Firm
this person could've found out that Park So Yeong was headed to TK Law Firm.
Han Seong Beom, Lee In Su
Choi Tae Kook, Han Seong Beom, Lee In Su, Hong Seok Pal
On the night Hong Seok Pal died,
he knew I was meeting Hong Seok Pal.
This person knew how to drag me into it by using Hong Seok Pal.
Choi Tae Gook
I heard you got cut off...
from the company you were devoted to.
You're just book-smart.
The company you were loyal to abandoned you.
Looking good.
You should just go down while at it.
Utterly destroyed.
Gosh, too noisy!
Come on...
My goodness, look at your faces.
Here. Enjoy the food
so that your brains will work fast.
Okay?
We have so many smart people here. What's there to worry about?
You'll find your answer.
For now, eat.
Of course, I knew we could count on you, Hyeongnims.
- Thank you for this food.
- Oh, yeah.
I watched that video with Hyeong Chil.
We noticed something strange.
- The video?
- Yeah.
Hong Seok Pal's suicide note video.
What about it?
Well,
I noticed his finger,
and I think there's something there.
His finger?
You can't really see that well in the video.
But if you enlarge the snapshot of it...
Look at his finger.
What's that?
Okay, focus on his finger while watching the video.
It looks like he's repeating something.
Is it a hand signal?
Oh, the auction.
Right! You recognize it, right?
- Auction?
- Yes.
You used this hand signal at the fish market during the auction.
I see...
Il...
Gu...
Il Gu, Il Gu?
Il Gu?
Why, Hyeong? What's Il Gu?
Ha Il Gu.
Ha Il Gu?
Chief Ha?
I have everything including what Hong Seok Pal had kept to mess with us, Chairman.
Of course. I also have the USB.
Yes.
You should lower your voice, Chairman.
It's as simple as rescheduling the acquisition date.
The law firm CEO in charge of the acquisition is Choi Ju Wan,
not Oh Su Jae.
Who cares about that special line item?
That rookie Yoon Se Pil...
It depends on how you deal with him.
Yes.
Assemblyman Lee In Su
Yes, Assemblyman. Of course, I have it.
Whether I destroy it or sit on it,
I'll take care of it, Assemblyman.
The presidential election is right in front of you.
You have no time to worry about this.
Of course.
You should show that kind of attitude.
I'll hang up now.
They sure have messed around all this time.
The night of Park So Yeong's death.
Where were you when she died?
I drove the Chairman home
and I came back to take care of unfinished work.
While I was in my office working,
I got a call from the maintenance team.
that a woman fell to her death.
They said she looked like she had fallen from the rooftop garden.
So I went to the rooftop garden directly.
And?
No one was there.
Chief Ha never makes his moves alone.
Chief Ha...
and...
the person who can do anything using Chief Ha.
Oh Su Jeong.
We were in the same class in 12th grade.
You were number 27, and I was number 28.
The boy in the picture. Is he your son?
It's amazing that you remember me.
How could I not remember you?
I ranked number one in school, and you ranked last.
Gosh, such an annoying girl.
You're still rude as always.
- Why are you in here?
- Mind your own business.
Why the hell are you interrogating me?
You told someone to kill a person and helped him kill himself.
I didn't do it. Someone else did it.
Yes. Of course, that's how it is.
Every single person who ends up in here says that.
"I'm not the culprit. I'm innocent."
But not me.
I admit it.
I'm receiving punishment for my crime.
One thing that's unfair.
That the punishment is harsher than my crime.
I just think that's unfair.
I'm leaving today.
- What?
- I have my pre-arrest interrogation.
It's 50/50. But if it's dismissed, I'll be out.
You only have a few hours left in the same cell
with a successful lawyer.
Smart girls know how to read people, too.
So annoying.
Do you know that your nickname used to be Oh Jae Su?
(T/N: Means unlucky or annoying)
How can I not know?
You gave it to me.
Ministry of Justice
Let's go.
Defendant
Prosecution
When you were a public defender,
Seo Joon Myeong crushed you in Kim Dong Gu's case, right?
Is that your trauma for a lifetime?
Is that why you're paying it back this way?
Console your husband so he doesn't do anything stupid.
If you don't, you'll get to see
these pictures on the courthouse blog.
Defendant Oh Su Jae.
Why isn't your attorney here?
Your Honor, so that the interrogation is not delayed,
please exercise your authority and appoint a public defender.
Your Honor, pre-arrest interrogation
is where you confirm whether I need to be under arrest.
I will defend myself.
Defendant, there is no pre-arrest interrogation without an attorney.
Your Honor, I'm here!
I had to confirm something.
My apologies!
Prosecution, please begin.
That's how Attorney Oh Su Jae blackmailed me
and I had no choice
but to kill Park So Yeong.
Defendant Oh Su Jae incited Hong Seok Pal to kill Park So Yeong.
Defendant told Hong Seok Pal to "bury" Park So Yeong.
She clearly conveyed the message to kill her.
If he didn't, she blackmailed him saying that she'd expose his weakness.
Hong Seok Pal couldn't resist her blackmail and killed Park So Yeong.
He committed suicide, not being able to overcome his guilt.
Everything happened because of the defendant's incitement.
Defendant, please make your statement regarding the facts of the crime.
Your Honor, the charges against the defendant of inciting murder
and abetting suicide do not even make sense.
Are you denying the charges in their entirety?
I will not accept them.
Defendant, you cannot play the role of your own attorney.
Your Honor, there is something I need to say.
Unlike the forensics report,
I discovered that the crucial cause of Hong Seok Pal's car explosion lies elsewhere.
Your Honor, what the defense counsel is presenting does not apply to pre-arrest interrogation
but they should be dealt with in the criminal trial.
We're not determining whether she committed the crime or not here today.
We're determining the necessity of being in custody.
The defendant is TK Law Firm's partner attorney
and is skilled at destroying evidence.
She's exceptional at defending herself.
Therefore she should be tried in custody.
Please remind the defense counsel that we're here
to determine the necessity of being placed under custody.
Defense counsel,
you can say what you just said to the court at a later date during the trial.
Your Honor,
I'm speaking of problems with the critical evidence that placed the defendant here in the first place.
I found proof that the defendant's voice in the suicide note footage was fabricated.
You have proof that the voice was fabricated?
Yes, Your Honor.
I confirmed the evidence.
What type of evidence is it?
Is it in the list of evidence you submitted today?
It's on its way.
I confirmed the existence of the evidence over the phone.
The person with the evidence will arrive shortly.
Counsel, what do you think you're doing right now?
Your Honor, the defense counsel is playing with words and blurring the court's intent.
Your Honor, he brought us the crucial evidence.
Please allow me to submit it as evidence.
Your Honor, my apologies!
He ran off before I could confirm his identity.
Hurry up and let's get out!
Defense counsel, what are you doing in my courtroom?
Your Honor, the defense is out of order.
I don't know what the defense has brought in, but
the defense is more than capable of destroying the evidence
and the potential for her to run away is very high.
The police also tried to reach the defendant numerous times for investigation, but
they ultimately could not.
In the end, they had to arrest her without a warrant on the Seojoong University campus.
Detective Do Jin Myeong?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm Detective Do Jin Myeong from Central Police Station.
It's true.
Your Honor, I ask that you make a wise judgment
so that a fair investigation and trial are possible.
However, Your Honor... if you look at the request for the arrest warrant,
Hong Seok Pal's suicide note footage was a decisive factor in her arrest without a warrant.
If any part of it was fabricated, you must review it.
Also, if there is evidence of someone meddling in the car explosion,
it also means it was a murder, not suicide.
That issue must be determined in this court.
- The evidence not submitted in advance—
- Your Honor?
I'm sorry, but I must review it as a detective in charge.
The defense brought in some type of evidence,
and yet if you decide on her arrest without checking,
that really does not make sense.
Look!
If you took the case from us, you should have investigated properly
and asked us for additional assistance, but you didn't.
I already asked you if it was okay to junk the car,
and I also asked if you requested the forensics on the footage,
yet you said it was not necessary.
Why do you bring that up now!
Your Honor! Unnecessary evidence to determine whether or not to arrest—
Let's see it.
Pardon?
- Your Honor, we're here to—
- I know best why we're here in this place.
Counsel, present it if you'll indeed crack this case. If not, forget it.
To be honest, I think the nature of the defendant's crimes is heinous.
I believe the risk of destroying the evidence is extremely high.
I'm in the middle of considering the fact that she never answered any calls
from the detective on the case, meaning the risk of running away is quite high as well.
Defendant?
Yes.
How would you feel if you were in my shoes?
I would arrest myself.
Then think carefully.
How you'll take care of Park So Yeong.
Your Honor, if you look at the screen,
you can see the flow of the frequency is consistent.
Witness
This is Oh Su Jae's voice.
However, the second voice is different.
You know what you do best.
Burying people without anyone knowing.
Your Honor, over there. There, there.
If you look at the screen,
you can see that the frequency of this voice is broken up into pieces.
What does that mean?
This means it was manipulated from Oh Su Jae's voice data.
It means it's a fake of her voice.
Thank you.
Next is evidence showing that someone installed an explosive in Hong Seok Pal's vehicle.
Put an explosive?
In the car? Why would you want to do that?
We're filming a movie. An action movie.
Exploding cars, flying into pieces. Stuff like that.
My goodness. I can't believe the stuff I have to do.
But this is a bit difficult.
I'll compensate you enough, sir.
This man brought in Hong Seok Pal's car himself
and asked them to install explosives that he brought in.
In order to commit suicide, Hong Seok Pal asked someone
to install explosives.
He could've told someone, right?
You mean a person would tell someone else
to install explosives in his own car to commit suicide?
How can you be so sure that a person wouldn't?
Enough.
Please turn it on.
Chief Han Gi Taek of Hansu Group was asked by Hong Seok Pal
and helped install explosives in his car.
He also confessed his involvement in fabricating Attorney Oh Su Jae's voice in the suicide note video.
Chief Han Gi Taek?
Chief Han said Hong Seok Pal was tormented over his failed business and for murdering Park So Yeong.
He was extremely down on himself,
and that's how he came to aid in Hong Seok Pal's suicide.
The police plan to issue an arrest warrant
to investigate exactly how and in what way
Chief Han Gi Taek was able to aid in Hong Seok Pal's suicide.
What is your relationship to Hong Seok Pal?
Is it true you aided in Hong Seok Pal's suicide?
It's true.
How could this be, Hyeong.
Shack
He asked me to install explosives in his car, so he would die for sure.
I said no.
I told him to live no matter what.
But he said he was tormented from constantly thinking about how he killed Park So Yeong.
He said it was Attorney Oh Su Jae's fault
that he could no longer work for Hansu Construction.
Even record a suicide note?
So, do you have a body to put in there in my place?
You think I can't find one?
So, when the fire starts,
I'll sneak out of the car
and another body will be put in there?
That's right.
Hyeongnim,
I'll go to China and change my face completely.
I'll make up a new name
and I'll be back in two years.
You have to protect everything I own until then.
You have to do that for me.
- I got it.
- Hyeongnim.
I must survive.
My kids and my wife.
You know that they only have me to trust.
So trust Chairman Choi Tae Gook.
Both Assemblyman Lee and Chairman Han said to get rid of you.
But Chairman Choi is doing this because he alone is trying to save you, man.
Hey.
Because of...
Attorney Oh Su Jae at TK Law Firm,
I killed Park So Yeong.
The one who pushed
Park So Yeong from the rooftop of the TK Law Firm building
I will meet...
Attorney Oh Su Jae for the last time
and in front of her eyes,
I'll die.
I even installed explosives as you instructed, Chairman...
but you don't need to kill him...
Geez, if you just let him go out of the country...
Hong Seok Pal's hostess bar footage...
What do you think will happen if your family saw it?
You wouldn't want to lose 27 billion won and your family, too, right?
Chairman Choi Tae Gook
Hong Seok Pal had resentment toward Attorney Oh Su Jae for his failing business.
He said he wanted to take revenge against Attorney Oh Su Jae before he died.
That's why he lied and said Attorney Oh Su Jae told him to kill Park So Yeong.
Hong Seok Pal did kill Park So Yeong.
I'm apologetic to Attorney Oh Su Jae.
That crazy Han Gi Taek!
How could he aid in Hong Seok Pal's suicide?
This moron. He acts just like his father!
I can't believe I trusted him
and gave him a chance. That stupid idiot!
I know, Chairman.
I'm speechless myself. You must feel—
Hansu Bio and even Yeongpyeong District project!
Geez, there is so much to do!
Yes, well...
Please calm down—
I have to go!
Father, I really don't understand.
Why would Gi Taek hyeong get mixed up with someone like Hong Seok Pal?
I'm sure Hong Seok Pal held something over his head.
Pathetic bastard.
What could he possibly hold over his head?
I just don't get helping someone die
How is SP Partners reacting?
I'm meeting CEO Yoon Se Pil tomorrow.
"Oh Su Jae is in charge of the acquisition."
I can't believe he single-handedly halted the acquisition process by mentioning that line item.
That guy is really something else
Han Gi Taek turned himself in and Su Jae will be released once the charges are dropped.
Things will be different.
Yes. Since they halted on their own,
we'll have to put the pressure on and demand that they go twice as fast.
Oh, boy.
- Leave us for a moment.
- Yes, sir.
Ha Il Gu.
Ha Il Gu?
Chief Ha?
Mr. Goh/i&gt;
Mr. Go?
Yes.
Attorney Oh had asked you to do that?
I'll be right there, Mr. Go.
He found evidence of someone coming in with Hong Seok Pal's car to install explosives.
- I'll call you later.
- Okay.
Attorney Song, wait for me!
We've got the vehicle covered for now.
Who's Chief Ha Il Gu?
Chief Ha?
Chairman Choi's chief secretary? That Chief Ha?
Chan, come with me.
Let's find out where he is first.
Who cares where he's at?
We'll go right now and ask him to hand it over.
We'll ask him to hand over the original file for the fake voice in the suicide note footage.
Let's think and strategize first.
That should come first. Right?
Mister.
You're stalling. What are you trying to say?
And don't call me out like this anymore.
Choi Yoon Sang
Ajussi,
the collection of Noona's voice for the fake files...
I took it.
Tell my father.
The guy captured on the CCTV with me, Noona, and my team members...
If he promises not to hurt any of them,
tell Father I'll work for him.
I'm sorry, Ajussi.
You're my son.
My son shouldn't go up against me.
Okay?
Father,
let me be Su Jae Noona's intern.
I don't like you treating Noona harshly,
and I'm sure you'd be curious about what she's up to.
I'll help you and Noona in the middle.
I'm considering setting myself up to be a bat.
(T/N: Working under the shadows)
And then if you think I'm pretty good,
this TK Law Firm...
Give it to me.
I could be better than Hyeong.
You know
that I was always a better student than he.
Aiding and abetting suicide.
Worst case scenario, it's one year.
I'll let you get out on probation.
Turn yourself in
and exercise your right to remain silent.
The day you come out on probation,
your 27 billion won will become 40 billion won.
Forty billion won.
I'll dismiss the request for an arrest warrant for defendant Oh Su Jae.
Prosecution
Dr. Joon Hui was right, Attorney Oh.
Why?
Are you worried that Su Jae can't get out?
A long time ago, the number one ranked student in humanities in school was Oh Su Jae
and I was number one in science.
You know, people in those places find it tough to become friends.
But we became best friends as soon as we met.
Do you know why?
Crazy bitches connect with one another.
I guarantee it.
From now on, the ones who messed with the crazy bitches should be scared.
"Oh, I shouldn't have messed with Oh Su Jae."
"I was going to screw Oh Su Jae over, and now I'm screwed."
There'll be a moment when they realize that.
Eonni! It's dismissed!
What?
Hey!
Dismissed! Dismissed!
- Dismissed?
- It's dismissed!
Dismissed!
Dismissed! Dismissed! Dismissed!
Oh, yeah! Hooray, Attorney Song!
I knew you could do it!
We won!
Good job, Attorney Song!
Yoon Sang Hyeong
The phone is turned off. You'll be connected to the voicemail after the beep.
Tell me where the secretary's office is. I'll do it.
If they find out you did it, your father won't leave you alone.
That's why I have to do it.
So that everyone will be safe.
And you think I'd let you be cool all by yourself?
I want to look good to Noona, too.
I heard there's someone determined to purchase your stocks.
It means the acquisition is near.
Buy them.
Attorney Oh has been released.
It will move fast.
Hey, why don't you take a break from SNS until the acquisition is over?
Your rambling twice a day doesn't help the acquisition.
Why?
I enjoy looking at his SNS activity these days.
He posts raw chicken photos at 5 o'clock in the morning.
What the heck is "Good morning, chicken"?
But so many people press "Like."
He's got more than one million followers.
I was promoting the organic chicken that's sold in our shopping mall.
But something more entertaining than me
- came from Choi Ju Wan.
- First of all, TK Law Firm
has nothing to do with this case.
- Secondly, TK Law Firm and all the lawyers in the firm...
- Turn it off.
You know, you were so serious here.
I said turn it off, man!
Why are you butting in?
Who the hell are you to butt in!
My apologies, Managing Director. I'm sorry.
You're fired as of today.
You asshole..
Take it easy, man.
We're in public.
Do you want this all over the SNS you love so much?
So why did you have to provoke me and shit?
It's Han Gi Taek Hyeong's wife.
His wife must be in such a shock.
Still, that hyeong is pretty family-oriented.
In any case, you and I are both under his shadow all the same.
How do you think I was able to take 27 billion won?
It's all thanks to Chairman Choi Tae Gook.
I'll be loyal to him to death.
I truly trust him.
Han Gi Taek.
I guess he'll pay the cost of getting 27 billion won.
Chairman Choi Tae Gook
Yes.
How do you feel?
I feel pretty good, Chairman.
My eyes seem sharper and my hearing seems better.
It's not so bad.
That's good.
Yes.
It's all good.
Oh Su Jae
♫  What should I say  ♫
♫  My heart flutters as if I'm dreaming  ♫
♫  The star in my heart that keeps showing up  ♫
♫  It keeps haunting me  ♫
♫  I smile for no reason  ♫
♫  What I saw clearly  ♫
♫  Our future that is approaching  ♫
Had I known,
I would've had a nicer scarf on.
♫  I made a promise to myself since that day  ♫
♫  I like you so much that I'm overwhelmed  ♫
Come to my place.
This place isn't safe for you.
♫  You blossom so passionately inside my peaceful heart  ♫
♫  You came to me in this world  ♫
♫  What I had said then, I'll say it again  ♫
♫  I love you  ♫
I'm hungry.
♫  What I heard at last  ♫
♫  You saying to me that you like me, too  ♫
Why Her?
♫  I like you so much that I'm overwhelmed  ♫
♫  Oh, beautiful you  ♫
♫  You blossom so passionately inside my peaceful heart  ♫
Ta-da!
Professor is staying at your place?
Really?
Until the remodel of her building is finished.
Still, you're living in a student's house?
At a male student's place at that?
I moved into my father's house.
He wants to work as an intern under you.
I'll start next week, Attorney Oh.
As Chief Prosecutor Choi Tae Gook instructed ten years ago,
I took care of all the details for you.
Why do you hope for their destruction?
It started ten years ago.
Tell me what you want, Chairman Choi. What is it?
♫  When I'm with you  ♫
♫  I see a rainbow  ♫
♫  More beautiful than any given moment  ♫