=Vanished Name=
=Episode 17=
(I Know What Friendship Means)
Xiaoming, I told your mom everything.
Everything?
Everything.
You even told her
you're not the real Bai Shu?
Why did you have to tell her?
She can't keep a secret.
Shut it.
I can keep a secret.
How can you say that about your mom?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have mentioned that
in front of you.
I brought up sad memories for you.
It's okay.
I enjoy watching you two argue.
Are you crazy?
You like watching people fight?
If so, you deal with her.
I can't stand her.
Ms. Ren.
I really want to call you Mom.
Good, I have another good daughter.
I'm pretty lucky.
You're much better than the last one.
I wonder if this one can be returned.
But I can't call anyone else Mom.
I understand.
Look, she even wants to call you Mom.
You can't betray us.
You mustn't tell anyone
about us renting a place outside.
Watch that attitude.
Sweetie,
the market area is chaotic.
You can't live there.
Come home with me.
I'll go with you later
to pack up your things
and bring them to our home.
You're actually doing quite well.
Shut up. I'll settle with you later.
You and Xiaoming are good friends.
I know what friendship means.
Xiaofei, stop spinning the top.
Bai Shu.
Move your bedding out of your room.
From today on, you'll sleep on the sofa.
Xiaoming and Bai Shu
will sleep in your room.
Great! Bai Shu is staying with us!
Little thief, put everything you stole
back where it belongs.
Ms. Ren, are you not
making buns anymore?
Why is all the flour gone?
You know what? Those buns...
I used to live well.
I can't endure tiring work.
Making buns for a few days is enough.
How could I keep doing it?
I couldn't take it.
I can't do that, anyway. I quit.
What about earning money?
- You know what?
- Xiaoming.
Come to the market with me.
I'll cook some dishes tonight.
How much are you buying
that you need me to come?
Come on. Go with me.
Don't worry.
Leave everything here to me.
Alright, you stay.
Leave dirty clothes alone.
I'll wash them later.
If Xiaofei annoys you,
just smack him on the head.
Xiaofei and I get along just fine.
Go ahead.
Let me help you.
Don't tell Bai Shu about the bun thing.
You're not relying on her connections.
Why can't I tell her?
I know where those spoiled buns
came from now.
Where?
We offended someone and got framed.
Who?
Think about who you offended.
She locked Bai Shu up at home,
and you let her out.
So she hates you.
You mean Ge Wenjun framed you?
I swear my buns were definitely good.
Then where was the problem?
Think about it.
Right after you took Bai Shu out,
the spoiled bun thing happened.
I ran into Bai Shu's mom
at that same construction site.
I don't think it's a coincidence.
That's just too much.
Come on. Let's report it.
Report it? Do you have any proof?
We just have to take the loss.
Listen, you must not
tell Bai Shu about this.
If she finds out,
she won't stay with us anymore.
Aren't you afraid
Ge Wenjun will cause more trouble?
Yes, I am.
I'm deep in debt
and have no idea how to pay it back.
If something else happens,
I'll be helpless.
Then why did you take Bai Shu in?
I can't watch her living outside.
It's not safe for you two girls
to live in a market area.
If something bad happened,
her mom would surely kill me.
Now she's living comfortably
at our place.
Even if things get too tough,
her mom won't harshly blame us
when she comes to get Bai Shu.
I thought you were kind-hearted.
Turns out you have ulterior motives.
Are you kidding?
Today, I spent nearly 2,000 on you kids.
That was set aside to pay the fine.
Now, it's all gone.
Look, I have only 100 in my pocket.
If we don't figure something out,
our whole family won't survive.
By the way, I haven't asked you yet.
What's your relationship
with He Yuqiong?
What are you talking about?
You got the wrong idea.
Is there something between you two?
The place you rented and the mattress...
You're so annoying!
Listen up, Ren Xiaoming.
Look, if you start puppy love early,
I'll teach you a dear lesson.
Big white buns, one for each.
If they don't eat it,
that's their loss. Let's dig in!
Bai Shu, make yourself at home.
Grab whatever you want to eat.
Whatever you snag
into your bowl is yours.
Okay.
Let's start.
Thanks.
What? What are you doing?
Hey, what a good surprise with you here.
She can't finish it.
This is so much.
Have a bun?
You have this one.
Seriously? Nobody puts food in my bowl.
No.
No! Slow down!
Such a waste! It dropped on the table.
Ms. Ren, have some more.
Thank you for cooking, Ms. Ren.
Mom, eat more.
Eat more.
This is enough.
That's enough.
Ren Xiaoming.
Mr. Liu, it's me, Ge Wenjun.
Hello, Ms. Ge.
Rest assured,
I didn't let workers eat spoiled buns.
I drove that woman away.
She won't be coming back to the site.
Have you demanded compensation?
Compensation?
I understand what you mean.
She must pay compensation.
I'll handle this matter.
Good, we'll do it that way.
Feels so good.
Sleeping in a bed feels so good.
It's all thanks to you, Bai Shu.
Otherwise, I won't be sleeping in a bed.
Sleeping here feels really nice.
This is a real home.
So I'm your family now?
You wish.
Of course you are.
The moment to test the family
has arrived.
What?
Are you crazy?
What's wrong with you?
I farted.
You're crazy, Ren Xiaoming.
Anyway, I did as I wished.
Air this smell out. Come on.
Is this a biological attack?
Good for you.
It smells good.
What?
Why is the smell not gone?
I'm out of here.
No way.
We should endure the smell together.
Bai Shu.
Xiaoming, take this diary with you.
Go as far away as possible.
Don't come back.
Don't contact me anymore.
Hello, Liang Yi.
The second hearing starts tomorrow.
Have you arrived in Qingzhou?
Don't cancel on me again.
Don't worry.
I'm going to the airport.
See you then.
Don't be late.
Mom.
I have a hearing tomorrow.
I'm going to Qingzhou.
Why another hearing?
Why do you fight over the copyright?
Can't you give it up?
Also, I'm divorcing him.
Who filed for divorce first?
I'm asking you,
who initiated the divorce?
Tell me.
That doesn't matter.
I'm divorcing him, anyway.
Why does it have to turn out this way?
(In 2006, Qidaohezi)
Be careful.
Sir, this is practically brand new,
not even used for a full month.
That's not how you explain it.
Since you bought it, it's second-hand,
even if you haven't used it.
Please.
Alright.
The stove plus the steamer, 200 total.
Just 200?
I paid almost 1,000 for this stove.
You're not happy?
Don't sell then. Just keep them.
I'll move them back up.
Aren't you tired of moving them?
Fine, give me the money.
Okay, deal.
I'm telling you, it's a good offer.
More money, please.
Alright, take it.
Find me again if you sell stuff.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Mom, see if we got what we need.
Anything else?
Ms. Ren, why did they take the stove?
I won't need it to make buns.
It blocks the corridor.
But you can't get a good price
at this time.
That's not your concern.
It's cold. Let's go back home.
Let's go, Xiaofei.
Great, we need to pay so much in fines.
Didn't they explain it clearly just now?
Food poisoning,
plus you operated without a license.
You should be thankful
that they just fined you.
Thank heavens then.
What will happen
if I don't pay the fine?
If you don't pay the fine on time,
the court will
forcibly seize all your assets.
The court will
forcibly seize all my assets?
Is the house an asset?
Of course, it is!
Of course, definitely.
Chinese New Year is near.
If the house gets seized too,
we'll all be sleeping on the street.
How am I supposed
to get that much money?
Shouting won't help.
How about...?
How about what?
I have an idea.
What idea? Spit it out!
Let's sell Xiaofei.
In Southeast Asia...
What are you doing?
Why are you hitting me?
Stop!
Why are you provoking me?
I'm already at my wit's end!
Stop crying! Stop it!
Stop crying, sweetie.
Stop crying.
If only I'd known,
I shouldn't have used the house money
to pay the debt for Sun Jinfu.
There, there, stop crying.
Stop crying.
Stop any generous acts.
- Get lost.
What are you doing?
I can't live.
I'll hang myself there.
Are you serious?
You dare hang yourself?
You're scared to die.
I don't dare die.
I can beg on the streets.
You can't be a beggar
with that thin skin.
You...
- Don't follow me!
- Where are you going?
Go home and cook for Xiaofei.
Are you really going to beg?
Whatever.
Thanks.
Thank you! Come again!
Come take a look! Clearance sale.
Special price.
Excuse me, is this He Yuqiong's stall?
I'm his mom. And you?
I'm Ren Xiaoming's mom.
You're Xiaoming's mom?
Nice to meet you.
Xiaoming comes often.
Take a seat.
Come on.
Sit.
You never came to the parent meetings.
Or we'd have met sooner.
That's right.
Xiaoming is such a good girl.
I really like her.
If she becomes my daughter-in-law,
I'd be over the moon.
I'm here to ask you for money.
What?
He Yuqiong made a bet.
He ate three kilos of cake
and went into shock.
I happened to be there
and took him to the hospital.
His treatment cost nearly 2,000 yuan.
Here's the receipt. Please pay me back.
I told Ren Xiaoming
I'd pay this money back.
Why come to my mom?
He's fine now. I paid for his treatment.
How will you pay it back?
You'll spend your mom's money.
So I ask her for money.
Watch your attitude.
Listen, stop pestering my daughter.
She's at Yucai High School
and aiming for a prestigious university.
Your daughter is outstanding.
My son is good too.
How much do I owe you?
1,987.96 yuan.
Mom.
Here's 475. Take it for now.
I'll pay you back the rest
by the end of the month.
It's a small amount.
You gave her all you have?
How are we going
to pay the delivery guy?
Shut up.
You keep this money
and pay me back by the end of the month.
The receipt.
You...
Why didn't you tell me about it?
I didn't want to make you worry.
Your dad owes money outside,
and the creditors came to our home.
Now you're in debt too?
She came to our stall.
Mom, don't cry.
Are you driving me to death?
Mom, stop crying.
I'll definitely find a way
to pay back the money. It's okay.
Calm down.
(All mothers have their struggles.)
(If it weren't for the kids,)
(I wouldn't be able to do this.)
(Qidaohezi People's Hospital, 2023)
Yuxiu.
Grandma, you're so beautiful.
I love you.
Sweetie, come here.
Come closer.
Put your legs up.
On my legs.
Take a nap.
(Leaves)
Linden trees shed leaves in October.
How could they appear
inside a statue made in August?
It doesn't make sense.
(Qidaohezi cold wave in 2010)
Cold wave.
There was a cold wave.
(The golden period for solving a case
is 72 hours after it occurs.)
(All clues, like physical evidence,
fingerprints, DNA, and witnesses,)
(will gradually fade with time.)
(Old cases lacking solid clues
are like a veil of fog.)
(What we must do
is leave no stone unturned,)
(uncover the truth,
and pierce through the fog.)
What are you doing?
You scared me!
Why didn't you come alone
without telling me?
Could a cold wave make the linden trees
shed their leaves early?
There was a cold wave in August 2010.
All the leaves fell.
Haven't you read the novel?
If you had, you wouldn't be asking me.
Why do you keep telling me
to read the novel?
Listen, I want to help you.
Haven't you wanted to solve the case?
Can you be more specific?
No comment.
A friendly reminder, the diary
wasn't originally written this way.
Find the diary,
and you'll find the answers.
There's a cemetery on the outskirts.
The hill behind it is planted
with a foreigner's homesickness.
The homesickness
is called North American linden.
(Leaf, North American linden, cemetery)
Cemetery?
Rest Cemetery.
Captain Li,
how did you know it was Rest Cemetery?
Bai Shu worked at Rest Cemetery.
(Rest Cemetery)
So the novel is indeed connected
to this case.
Captain Li, I've read
the Leopard and Graveyard chapter.
First, the location...
Hold on.
The leopard died on the hill
behind a cemetery with linden leaves.
That matches our guess
about the primary crime scene.
Second, the time:
there was a cold wave in 2010.
That coincides with the renovation
of Qidian Middle School.
Finally, the cause of death.
In the novel, a branch was stuck
in the leopard's neck.
Our autopsy report
shows a broken cervical spine.
Neck, cervical spine.
Isn't that another coincidence?
It's like this novel is about our case.
So what?
You can't use a novel as evidence.
But Bai Shu said
the novel is based on a diary.
A diary can be used as evidence.
But Bai Shu said
the diary is in Ren Xiaoming's hands.
Ren Xiaoming denied having it.
So,
(Diary)
how can we prove it really exists?
When is the copyright hearing?
Tomorrow.
Would Ren Xiaoming
present the diary as evidence in court
to win the copyright hearing?
(The diary is the most direct evidence.)
(She will definitely present it.)
Yanzi.
Contact the Qingzhou court.
Once Ren Xiaoming presents the diary
in the court hearing,
they need to contact us.
Yes.
(This is
Qingzhou Intermediate People's Court.)
(This is the copyright case
of Ren Xiaoming and Liu Xiaoran.)
(Court is now in session.)
As Liu Xiaoran's wife and the defendant,
I can honestly say
(Representative Agent, Plaintiff)
that Liu Xiaoran, since 2021,
has been in a poor creative state.
(Defendant, Authorized Agent)
He completely stopped writing novels.
Also, the story of a TV series
he was involved in
was written by a ghostwriter
hired by his company.
So Liu Xiaoran plagiarized my work
after he lost his creative inspiration.
He admitted it himself.
It can be seen in the video call
between him and my mother.
Thank you.
Plaintiff Ren Xiaoming
is my wife,
who has lived with me for ten years.
To seek financial gain,
she disregarded the facts
and made baseless charges against me.
And before the trial,
she induced me to lie to her mother.
She wanted to save face
in front of her family.
I didn't guard against her
and fell into her trap.
I solemnly declare here
that the original concept
for the novel "Breathe" is mine.
I wrote it myself, word by word.
It has nothing to do with Ren Xiaoming.
(Qingzhou, 2014)
They recruited us back
and made me live here.
This is how they treat us.
This is what I am worth now.
Sorry.
I'm not Mao Dun and we aren't in Guilin.
You are still a junior lecturer now.
It's good to get a dorm like this.
What do you mean?
Are you mocking me?
My rank is low, and I don't deserve it?
I feel they disrespect me
and haven't given me what I deserve.
I'm a writer.
No bookshelf, no chair, nothing.
Just one desk.
The bed is for both of us.
There is something on the wall.
What is this?
I truly can't stand it.
Sooner or later, I will resign.
You know what? I know a guy
named Chen Junhang.
He told me
about a lucrative method nowadays.
It's writing articles on social media.
You first establish your persona.
It doesn't matter
if your articles are a bit subjective.
It's okay as long as people read it.
Just get clicks and traffic,
and you'll get money.
What do you say?
Xiaoran, it's been over a year
since we got married.
You've changed so much.
I...
You've become restless.
Restless?
Why do you suddenly
have so many negative feelings?
I chased you for years
and finally married you.
I have to make you happy.
I'm married. I have a home and you.
I want to make you happy.
I studied hard for so many years.
I definitely didn't come back for this.
Look.
Look over there.
Those people who used to praise me
are now hiding in some corner
and laughing at me.
All this is just temporary.
It will all get better.
I'm sorry, Xiaoming.
I vented a bit.
- I lost my composure.
- It's okay.
It's okay.
You're absolutely right.
It's all temporary.
Come on, Xiaoran.
Come on.
What do you think
our room is missing the most
right now?
What's missing?
Do you even need to ask?
Look, everything is missing!
Think about it.
What's missing?
What do you think is missing?
I don't know.
What's missing?
Curtains.
Could you come back
to my hometown with me?
Why?
It's my mom.
She is unhappy about us getting married.
She thinks I lied to her.
Aren't your parents curious
about me at all?
Hold on.
Actually,
as you know,
my parents
are intellectuals
who aren't very sociable.
They don't care much
about superficial ceremonies.
It's just a formality.
We won't live with them.
Okay.
We'll meet right here in Qingzhou.
I'll have my parents come over.
Your mom will come too.
This place is suitable.
We will have a meal together.
Okay.
Also,
although my family situation is decent,
my parents have taught me
that I need to make it on my own.
- And no material...
- I know.
You've told me a million times already.
The same with my family.
My mom won't help me either.
We'll rely on ourselves. Come on.
(Before the trial)
The video evidence
we submitted just doesn't hold up.
Liu Xiaoran submitted his writing drafts
from his computer.
Without stronger evidence,
we're definitely going to lose.
(The moment the diary comes out,
he loses for sure.)
I know what I want.
What?
Are you even listening to me?
Do you have any evidence or not?
No.
We're going to lose.
The evidence provided
by the plaintiff in this case
is insufficient
to prove the facts claimed.
The judgment is as follows.
- Dismiss
- (Strange.)
the plaintiff's claims.
(Why would she rather lose the lawsuit)
(than present the diary?)
She handed over the diary
we wrote together
to her husband for publication.
What diary?
How come I didn't know about it?
(Could it be
that she really doesn't have it?)
(Why does Bai Shu insist she does?)
(Which one of them is lying?)
I just told you to read the novel.
You must read it.
She doesn't have the final say.
She has to show evidence.
(What's going on
between Ren Xiaoming and Bai Shu?)
(Diary)
(Ren Xiaoming)
(Bai Shu)
(What roles do Ren Xiaoming
and Bai Shu play in this story?)
Ren Xiaoming.
Are you trying to use the trial
to prove the diary doesn't exist?
What are you up to?
Xiaoming.
Thank you
for not destroying me in court today.
It's okay.
I'll still get the copyright back.
Okay.
Well then,
thank you for not presenting the diary.
The diary?
What diary?
Didn't you say in court
that you typed your book word by word?
What diary?
Are you okay?
Good.
I'll go get you something to eat.
The copyright lawsuit is over.
Get ready.
For the divorce lawsuit.
Why?
Why do you insist on divorcing me?
We were fine before.
Why divorce me now?
For an apple,
the core goes bad first.
But from the outside,
it looks like a good apple.
Only when you bite into it
do you realize
the apple is rotten.
It's no good anymore.
The day you chose
to publish the new book,
the apple was bitten.
You bit the apple.
Be responsible.
Mr. Liu.
It's a good thing we don't have kids.
You...
Well,
neither of us is a good person.
To be parents, you have to learn
how to be decent people first.
Ma'am.
(Breathe)
Why are you sleeping here?
- I brought you breakfast.
- Captain Li.
I'll swap my porridge for your soy milk.
Since you don't eat it,
why did you buy it?
Alright, forget the breakfast.
Put it there.
Sit down.
Let's sort out the case details.
I had a new idea last night.
The Leopard and Graveyard chapter
is actually a murder case.
The one who died is the leopard.
The leopard is used
to conceal the victim's true identity.
Look at this line here.
That leopard appeared again.
What does this mean?
This shows that leopard appeared before.
So, if we think of it as a person,
that person must have appeared
in other chapters of this novel.
So, guys.
Let's start.
Time is tight.
One book per person.
We'll search chapter by chapter
and examine character by character.
We'll definitely find clues.
Read the novel?
Start.
Just do what she says.
(New message)
(Ren Xiaoming)
Hello?
Meng.
Can you do me a favor?
Go ahead. What favor?
I just sent you a string of numbers.
Could you send it to Bai Shu?
Why don't you send it yourself?
She blocked me.
How can I send it to her?
What do these numbers mean?
It's a secret communication code
between her and me.
How to decode it?
It's a secret. How can I tell you?
This isn't illegal, is it?
Will you guys arrest me?
Please do me a favor. I'm begging you.
Okay, I'll help you.
Alright, I'll treat you to a meal later.
Got it. Bye.
What did she send?
Copy it down.
101925,
371512,
661719,
362622,
530722,
300507,
051613.
613.
010621,
051215,
142608,
160915,
- 91...
- 160914,
082528,
060319.
That's all.
Ma'am, the master code?
The one often used in spy dramas.
Old Ghost, you decode them.
Without the master code,
it's useless to have these numbers.
Since she's playing
Cliff Walkers with us,
we'll just Let the Bullets Fly.
=Vanished Name=