=Vanished Name=
=Episode 12=
(Half A Sheet of Premium White Lambskin)
When she acted as the good Samaritan
by sending you to the exam,
did she think about me?
Did she ever pity me?
Was it my fault
that she was poor
and married a man who beat her?
Why blame me?
That was just her fate.
What gives you the right to question me?
You'll never admit you're wrong.
No matter how much you hurt others,
it's always their fault.
Since childhood, you've torn and smashed
my belongings whenever you pleased.
Because in your logic, I belong to you.
Everything I have is yours.
Whether it's your deceased daughter,
your husband who left you,
or me,
in your eyes,
we've never been whole people.
We're just possessions to you.
That includes everyone around me.
We all have to dance to your tune.
You'll pay for all the evil you've done.
That, I promise.
Don't forget
what I have in my hands.
You have no right to threaten me.
No right.
(Shabei County)
(Tubao Village)
(Mr. Liu)
Sir, I sent you my location.
Come pick me up later.
Thanks.
(Liang Yi)
My goodness, finally you're on.
Where have you been?
Everyone's looking for you.
Liu Xiaoran is frantic.
He has time to look for me?
Haven't the media been hounding him?
The media have been grilling Liu Xiaoran
about the copyright.
That's why he's looking for you.
And one creator claims
you're at the Thai-Myanmar border.
Thai-Myanmar border?
They even have photos as proof.
Since when
is the Thai-Myanmar border this cold?
My goodness, what are you doing
all the way out there?
Are you looking for Wen Yuxiu?
How did I just remember that now?
This is more important
than the court hearing, really.
I'm sorry.
Okay, the copyright lawsuit
is postponed until next week.
You must come back
no matter what, understand?
I promise.
One more thing.
Liu Xiaoran has also hired a lawyer
for the divorce.
His lawyer contacted me today.
They want to negotiate.
They mainly have two demands.
First, the divorce can't be made public.
Second,
the property division.
He thinks you want too much.
His attitude has been clear throughout.
He couldn't care less
about getting divorced.
What he cares about
is the real impact this has on him.
Liu Xiaoran's attitude isn't surprising.
After all, anyone in his position
would find it hard to accept.
Thinking about the past,
it must hurt
deep down, right?
I have no expectations of him.
Why would I feel hurt?
Alright.
Take care of yourself.
Don't worry. I'm hanging up now.
Bye-bye.
Where are you?
I called your home.
Your mom said you're not back.
Not in Northern Myanmar. Relax.
Northern Myanmar?
All eyes are on you right now.
What exactly is your game?
Why are you nervous?
Haven't you always been clever?
You even colluded with the publisher
to twist the truth.
What do you fear?
Xiaoming, come back.
Let's talk properly.
It's time to settle this.
Liu Xiaoran,
had you stopped publishing a month ago,
none of this would've happened.
Two weeks ago, by giving me
the copyright and pulling the book,
you could've saved it.
You chose neither.
To protect the reputation
you gained through deceit,
you drove me into a corner.
What?
I can't fight back?
Yes, I have other plans.
But we're opponents now,
so I won't tell you.
Bye.
(Liu Xiaoran)
(Rejected)
Tubao Village. We're here.
Travelers to Tubao Village, get off.
Everyone, wake up.
We're at Tubao Village.
- Get off now.
- Wait.
Right away.
Hurry up. Time to get off.
Anyone needing to get off, do it now.
What kind of technological era is this?
Lose a phone,
and we're back in the Stone Age.
Darn technology.
Ren Xiaoming? Xiaoming, get up.
How come you're lying here?
You can't lie here. Wake up.
Xiaoming, get up.
Get up quickly.
Feeling better now?
How come a young girl like you
wandered alone into this wilderness?
Luckily, I was coming down
the mountain hauling corn.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have met me.
Do you hear that?
Wolves are in the mountains.
You're lucky.
Due to the blizzard, the wolves stay in.
Where are you headed?
I can give you a ride.
I'm going to Tubao Village.
Which family are you from?
Why haven't I seen you before?
Are you from Tubao Village?
I'm looking for someone.
Who are you looking for?
The Hao family.
Who in the Hao family?
Hao Ying.
I am Hao Ying.
What do you want?
You're Mr. Hao?
What a coincidence.
What do you want?
I'm Ren Xiaoming,
a reporter for a travel magazine.
I'd like to do a feature on your village
as an authentic rural community.
How do you know about me?
My uncle.
He was the accountant
at your Qidaohezi Farm,
Zhao.
You know? Zhao.
It's okay if you don't recall him.
But he remembers you.
He said you're really amazing.
Back then, no matter
how sick the livestock was,
as long as it reached you,
you could save it.
Yes, right.
He knew I was coming
to your village for this feature
and thought since you live there,
maybe you could help me out.
Alright, someone from Qidaohezi
is like family.
Now that you've found me,
consider it like coming home.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Hold on tight.
Hao,
where'd you find such a beauty?
- A relative.
- So pretty.
She's come to visit me.
You're lucky.
Look.
Finding such a partner, huh?
Look at this beauty.
Impressive.
This is my relative.
We're here.
Get off.
My kid.
How old are you?
Ignore her,
that deaf and mute unlucky thing.
She's 17.
Don't fear.
It's chained.
Come inside. It's cold out.
Come on in.
Come inside, Ms. Ren.
Have some hot water.
Mr. Hao, where's your wife?
What?
You seem to be raising the kid alone.
Is your wife not here?
She's dead.
Been dead for years.
Dead?
Time of death was Day 1
of Chinese New Year, 2007.
The death certificate
was issued by the town clinic.
COD was postpartum hemorrhage.
(Medical Certificate of Death:
Wen Yuxiu)
Hello.
I need a card.
Please queue here.
Fill out your personal information here.
Yes, just fill this out.
(The Voyage of the Beagle)
(The Voyage of the Beagle.)
This book will tell you
how vast the world is
and how far one can travel.
Go out and see the world.
(Wen Yuxiu's Tomb)
(Ms. Zhou has passed away.
We'll never see her again.)
(Ren Xiaoming: Ms. Zhou has passed away.
We will never see her again)
Mr. Hao.
You bought the phone?
All settled.
Thanks for lending me money.
I'll pay you back later.
No rush.
Did you try street food
in town yesterday?
Wasteful thing. You fail at everything.
Wasteful thing.
Mr. Hao.
If you're free later,
could I ask you some questions?
What for?
I want to interview you.
Interview me?
What's there to interview me about?
You're very important.
Really?
Alright.
Let's go inside.
Do it inside.
Is there any place to stay
in the village?
Or you could make do at my place.
Are you sure?
No worries.
My daughter will keep you company.
I'll go to the village committee.
Stay here.
It's convenient for my interview.
- Makes sense.
- Right?
Thank you.
Don't go out at night.
I'll let the dog out at night. It bites.
What are you staring at?
Get to work.
She's narrow-minded.
Never seen a city person before.
Sorry for that.
Ms. Ren, you should rest.
Well, I'm off.
Got it.
I'll let the dog out. Stay inside.
Okay.
Come here.
First, feed the livestock later.
Then boil some water for Ms. Ren
to soak her feet. Got it?
Come out.
(Pechoin)
(Chinese Language Knowledge Dictionary)
(A Life Unfaced: Biography of Lu Xun)
(Small Dictionary of Chinese Idioms)
Wen's Shoe Shop.
It's okay. I can do it myself.
Can you hear me?
A little?
Don't be afraid. I won't hurt you.
Sleep here tonight. With me.
I won't tell him, okay?
Don't be scared.
(Take me away)
Come inside. Let's talk inside.
It's fine.
Alright, I won't pull you in.
I do want to take you away.
But if I take you out now,
if Hao Ying
catches you
and takes you back,
it'll be too risky.
He'll hit you harder
and yell at you more.
And if he reports to the police,
they'll still bring you back.
Understand?
Give me some time.
I will definitely get you
out of here safely.
Trust me.
(Do you know the way out?)
(I've been looking for it,)
(but can't find the way out.)
(Excellent)
(Bai Shu, this essay is well written.)
May you grow wings for your dreams
and become a tree traveling the world.
What are you doing?
Ms. Zhou died.
How?
Hemorrhage during childbirth.
Don't be too upset.
That place is remote
with poor medical conditions.
Such things happen.
If you hadn't reported her,
she wouldn't have left school.
If you hadn't told her husband,
she wouldn't have been taken back there
and even died.
If...
If she hadn't barged in that day,
we would've reconciled.
You wouldn't
have kept the memory
of me stopping you
from the high school entrance exam.
You wouldn't have run away
from me repeatedly.
You wouldn't have seen me as your enemy.
Death
is truly a simple thing.
Those who run away, those who are weak,
in the end, all choose death.
Living is pitiful.
Living is hard.
Then why don't you just die?
Do you hate me that much?
Because of her existence,
you see me as even more of an enemy.
(Shabei County, Dong Township)
Go back!
Sir, stop!
Can't stop. We're in a hurry.
Sit down. It's dangerous.
Still running?
Get up!
Move!
(I'm sorry.)
(I can't take you with me right now.)
(But I promise.)
(I promise, I will find a way)
(to rescue you fair and square.)
Ma'am.
Li Meng.
Come on.
Hurry.
Sit down.
What's so urgent
that you asked to meet me?
I want to tell you that
after I went back, I remembered
the last time
there was news of Wen Yuxiu
wasn't 2004.
It was 2007.
2007? Are you sure?
I'm sure. Xiaoming took
the gaokao exam that year.
I forgot the time
of her high school entrance exam.
But I remember her gaokao exam time.
On Day 1
of the Chinese New Year in 2007,
a strange phone number called.
Then, what did she say on the phone?
She didn't speak.
She was just breathing very rapidly.
Then how could you be sure
it was her calling?
The breathing.
I heard her breathing.
It was definitely her.
(Wasn't she dead?)
(How is that possible?)
The breathing.
(Last news from Wen Yuxiu, 2007,
Unknown number, No speech, Breathing)
That new book written by Liu Xiaoran,
Ren Xiaoming's husband,
is called 'Breathe.'
Is there a connection?
Hi.
Meiyan, you bought so many shoes?
Every pair I tried,
they said looked great.
- They do.
- They kept saying so.
We bought four or five pairs.
Yeah.
Can you wear them?
Of course. She likes them.
These aren't too many.
Not enough for a week's change.
Li is really good to you.
It's truly enviable.
Liu isn't bad either.
Thank you.
He has to buy me five pairs too.
Mom, what's wrong?
Got a stitch?
- I'm fine.
- I'll carry you.
I'm happy.
No need.
You take Xiaofei to get a haircut.
His hair is like grass.
Give it to me.
Okay.
I'm leaving now.
Okay, take care then.
She looks so happy.
Let's go.
You scared me. When did you get back?
Where's Xiaofei?
They went for a haircut.
Li bought me four pairs of shoes.
I forgot to tell you.
He has moved in to live with us.
He's now my live-in husband.
When are you and Xiaoran
coming back together?
Our whole family should meet formally.
Help me see which pair looks nice.
There are two flat pairs.
Take a look for me. You have good taste.
These two flat pairs.
Pick one pair for me.
See which one I should keep.
I'll return the other.
No need to spend so much. Help me pick.
This is bizarre. What's going on today?
Everyone's giving me shoes.
What brand are your shoes?
Wen's Shoe Shop.
Wen's Shoe Shop?
(Wen's Shoe Shop)
(You know how to make leather shoes?)
(Wen's Shoe Shop in Erdaohezi.)
(Then I want a pair of high-heels.)
(In white.)
Where did you find this pair of shoes?
These are mine.
These are for me.
Whose shoes are these?
Whose shoes?
These are my shoes.
She stitched these for me,
every stitch by hand.
I told her I saw on a calendar
a girl who looked nice wearing jeans
and white leather shoes.
And she really made them for me.
She also said white leather
was hard to find,
and she had to wait for leftover scraps
to piece together.
She had no money.
How did she get a whole piece
of white leather?
Who was she?
She was my Ms. Zhou.
Every time you yelled at me at home,
making me feel I couldn't stay,
I would go to her.
It was Ms. Zhou who gave me warmth
and hope.
Why didn't you tell me
that Ms. Zhou was Wen Yuxiu?
Tell me where she is.
While our family was happily
celebrating the New Year,
she was hemorrhaging alone
and died in a crude clinic.
(Wen Yuxiu's Tomb)
Why didn't you tell me back then
that Ms. Zhou was Wen Yuxiu?
If you had told me earlier,
she wouldn't have died.
I could have found her sooner.
Why borrow from her?
Why didn't you pay her back?
Do you know how important
that money was to her?
If she'd had that money,
she wouldn't have married that beast
or have died.
Why borrow from her?
Do you love money that much?
If she hadn't married that beast,
she wouldn't have died.
What were you thinking,
leaving her a will?
What were you thinking with this will?
What good is that money to her now?
She's already gone.
Ren Meiyan,
I used to think your little schemes
were because life was hard.
But now I see deep down,
you're just selfish,
and you only care about yourself.
Do you think the whole world owes you?
=Vanished Name=