=Vanished Name=
=Episode 5=
(Through Thick and Thin)
Xiaoming.
(2004, Qidaohezi)
Come out, Xiaoming.
Xiaoming, come out.
What's wrong?
- It's your brother.
- Where's the medicine?
Medicine.
Why would you move the medicine?
Xiaofei.
Take your medicine. Drink the water.
Lower your head. Swallow it.
Swallow it. Alright.
Good boy.
It's alright.
Swallow it.
Alright.
Xiaofei.
Good boy.
I am here.
Why would you move the medicine?
Freaked me out.
Xiaofei found the medicine once
and almost threw them all away.
So now it's my fault for moving it?
Of course, it is.
Why did he get sick?
Hadn't you been lazy, would he be sick?
You know very well
his disease is congenital.
But you insist on blaming me for it.
So can I say
that it's your karma?
My karma?
Here's your karma.
Where do you think
you're going at this hour?
Xiaoming.
Uncle Qian.
(Uncle Qian.)
(Where have you been?)
(I missed you.)
(Sweetie. Is the lollipop sweet?)
It's okay.
You must learn to praise things.
If you praise this lollipop,
it'll be sweet.
My mom never praises me.
Well, you should learn
to praise your mom first.
Once you praise her,
she'll start praising you, too.
Want it?
No.
You have it.
(Everything is my fault.)
(Am I really that terrible?)
Ren Xiaoming.
What are you doing here?
I...
Let's go.
Where are we going?
It's so late.
Why did you come to my place?
The night market just closed.
I came to see if you went to bed.
Any normal person would've gone to bed.
- I just want to tell you...
- Stop coming.
Some neighbors love to gossip.
Then tell me.
What did I do wrong?
You don't talk to me anymore.
You don't talk to me either.
You keep running away, buddy.
How do I talk to you?
What did you just call me?
Buddy.
Homie.
So we're not dating, right?
Are you crazy?
You idiot.
Who wants to date you?
You're not even a girl to me.
Y-You weren't trying to date me?
Then why did you give me that shirt?
The sleeves on your T-shirt were torn.
You never changed it.
We sell clothes. It was nothing.
Then,
why were you so awkward
when you gave me the shirt?
How was I awkward?
Hey. You couldn't even bend.
You shoved it at me and just ran off.
I hurt my back when helping my mom
move stock the day before.
I ran off because Zhang Fang
was waiting for me.
Then why did you give me tea eggs?
My mom cooked a whole pot.
They'd go bad.
Zhang Fang and the others all got one.
Everyone got one?
Why?
Even a tea egg makes you
feel privileged?
How love-starved is that?
Get lost.
I'm not love-starved.
No wonder you've been acting weird,
throwing brooms and changing seats.
It turns out you've cooked up
a whole romantic drama in just two days.
No wonder Ms. Zhou finds you talented.
You're so talented, you genius.
Why didn't you just say so earlier?
You scared me to death.
Buddies are the best,
through thick and thin.
Buddy,
can we talk somewhere else?
I'm freezing to death.
Let's go.
(2023, Qingzhou)
Help.
Anyone there?
Open the door. Is anyone there?
Xiaoming.
It's me.
Bai Shu.
Help.
Xiaoming.
Call an ambulance.
Mom,
if I died in that elevator,
what would you do?
What could I do?
Should I die with you?
I still have your brother to look after.
So you're saying
that you and Xiaofei
could live just fine?
What do you mean?
Do we have to die with you
to prove we love you?
Will you ever stop complaining
about being mistreated?
I'm not complaining.
I really hope you two will live well.
Stop being so cheesy.
What's up?
The good die young.
Don't you know how mean you are?
Mom.
I paid the fees.
The doctor said she needs
a little more observation.
But if nothing else comes up,
she can be discharged this afternoon.
I'm not your mom.
I'm her mom.
My daughter was out so late.
Where was she?
Was she robbed?
Hit by a car?
Did she fall into a manhole?
And you just told me,
"She went to her bestie"?
Thankfully, I kept calling her.
She's still alive
because I insisted on going back.
Ren Xiaoming has many faults.
She has a bad temper. She's stubborn.
You are her husband.
Your parents are highly educated.
I'm a folk person who speaks bluntly.
If you don't even care
about your wife's safety,
you're not a real man.
The elevator and the surveillance camera
were out of order?
I think it's your conscience
that's out of order.
Mom.
That's enough.
Go home.
No, I won't.
I'm staying with you.
Mom, you've been here the whole night.
That's nothing. In the hospitals,
I will stay all day and night
until the people are gone.
Mom, are you waiting for me to be gone?
Enough.
Mom.
We're in a hospital.
Just relax.
Go home and rest.
Don't be stubborn.
Talk to him properly.
I'll come in the afternoon.
Okay.
Take care.
See you, Mom.
(She may cause trouble sometimes.)
(But in the end,
I have to count on her.)
Xiaoming.
Mom is right.
It was my fault.
I was too careless.
This whole thing has me scared.
- I should have...
- My...
My...
Bag?
It's here.
It won't get lost.
The diary is there?
Mom just told you
to talk properly with me.
Fine.
I'm going ahead with the lawsuit.
And I want an open trial.
Alright.
Take your phone.
Talk to your bestie about the lawsuit.
Don't push me.
Captain Li.
Alright, guys.
Let's gather all the clues
we have on Zhou Yun.
I need to report to the higher-ups.
Captain Li.
I haven't found any leads
on Zhou Yun yet.
What do you mean?
Shun and I went to the school.
Zhou Yun left the school in 2004
and took her personal file with her.
In 2007...
Get some water. Sorry.
Shun, go ahead.
Alright.
The electronic records
became widespread
nationwide in 2007.
The Qidian Middle School
also entered the information
of the teachers and students
into the system in 2007.
So now, we can only
gather information on Zhou Yun
from people's testimony.
There are no paper records.
Her ID number?
- Nothing.
No ID number?
No.
No way.
Why not?
Zhou Yun
was hiding her personal information
on purpose.
Yue, tell them what we found.
Well...
Shun and I
went to see the retired teacher,
Wang Yulan.
We also asked some...
Enough, let me take over.
So,
we visited several former colleagues
who worked with Zhou Yun.
They all said Zhou Yun was very odd.
She never used a cellphone
(Hid her identity? ID card)
or socialized with anyone.
She poured almost all her energy
into her students.
She must have been an excellent teacher.
That's right.
Guess what's the weirdest?
What is it?
According to these teachers,
over all these years,
she somehow
never left a single photo behind.
(Why did she hide her identity,)
(Photos)
(not even leaving a photo behind?)
(Hid her identity?)
(Was she trying to hide something?)
(We must look into
every possible related aspect)
(and leave no stone unturned.)
Zhou Yun worked at Qidian Middle School
for so many years.
Theoretically,
she couldn't have been traceless.
This lead is crucial to our case.
Keep digging hard.
Get on it.
Got it.
No information?
Model worker.
Working overtime during the holiday?
Not taking a break?
Aren't you also busy?
I thought asking you out
might be awkward,
so I came
to bring you some coffee.
Here?
Are you sure?
I got a little out of line.
Sorry to disturb you, everyone.
How about this?
(In Memoriam)
Come out for some air.
The coffee is getting cold.
I'll wait outside.
Amazing view.
Seeing it every day,
death isn't so mysterious
or serious anymore.
It's just a routine matter
like eating or having coffee.
But for us police,
we can never treat death
as a routine matter.
Once we become numb to it,
we'll forget
the pain it brings to the living
and our responsibilities.
You're not here for work.
How did you know?
According to regulations,
investigations require
two or more officers to be present.
You even study
criminal investigation rules?
Pretty thorough.
My job gives me a lot of free time.
I learn a bit of everything.
By the way, have you ever fired a gun?
What kind of question is that?
"Have I fired a gun?"
That's my profession.
Have you fired a gun?
Yeah, I have.
There's a live-ammo
shooting club nearby.
I sometimes go there.
It's quite relaxing.
Are you bragging to me?
How are your scores?
Average.
9.6 at 100 meters.
Not bad.
That's actually pretty good
for an average person.
But mine is a ten.
I haven't lost to you in my profession.
Can I ask you something?
Go ahead.
Was Zhou Yun
your and Ren Xiaoming's
middle school homeroom teacher?
Yes.
(2004, Qidaohezi)
(She was nice to both of us)
(and often gave us books.)
Ms. Zhou.
Ren Xiaoming, come in.
How was it?
I got this, Ms. Zhou.
Finished the book?
Any thoughts?
I realized that a person's life is long,
filled with many experiences
and many people.
But in the end,
you don't even know how it ends.
That's what I wanted you to read.
Never label or define yourself.
As long as you want it,
life has infinite possibilities.
Understand?
Yeah.
I checked your grades.
(Academic record)
Stable performance in all subjects.
That means you have a solid foundation.
Would you like to give it a try
and aim for Yucai?
Yucai?
The city's top high school.
No, I won't make it.
Sit down. Don't be nervous. Come on.
If you can't, then who can?
Bai Shu.
I knew you'd say her.
But you're also excellent.
No, I'm not.
My mom says I can't do anything
or accomplish anything.
I'll never catch up to Bai Shu.
Don't make her your only benchmark.
See your own strengths.
Everyone has their own shining points.
Be more confident.
That's how you lead a brilliant life.
I have a book for you.
The Voyage of the Beagle.
This book will tell you
how vast the world is
and how far one can travel.
Go out and see the world.
(The Voyage of the Beagle)
Thank you, Ms. Zhou.
(No one ever told me I wasn't so bad.)
(No one said I had shining points.)
(Except for Ms. Zhou.)
(I never saw
how big the outside world was.)
(I only saw how small my world was.)
(In my world, there were
only potatoes at two-fifty per jin,)
(their ordinary counterparts,)
(animals to be butchered,
and their carcasses.)
(In my world, no one would ever leave.)
(Fate repeated itself for generations)
(in a spiral-shaped apartment building,
forming a cycle of life and death.)
(In my world,)
(time is usually divided)
(into time to make money
and time to rest)
(in order to make more money.)
(The vast universe exists)
(to highlight how small my home is,)
(so small it's like a speck of dust.)
(Dust has no nutrients.)
(I'm just inorganic matter
within that dust.)
(Inorganic matter doesn't grow.)
(Aiming for Yucai? What a joke.)
(Qidaohezi Qidian Middle School)
Cheap potatoes.
Do you know how amazing your world is?
Bai Shu?
Without this, the Mayan civilization
would be incomplete.
This pumpkin is great.
This golden grain
nourished countless civilizations.
Some say it came from outer space.
The corn is great.
You can't just get one.
Take two.
It's even better.
It's a miracle in agricultural history.
Its yield is so high
that other crops can't compete.
Many civilizations survived
because of it.
It's the root.
Take some more and don't starve.
You find them ordinary
because you see them every day
and forget
that they're as great as
those rare plants.
No life on Earth is simple.
Including you and me.
Why didn't you go home?
- Let's go.
- Hey.
You bought nothing after all that talk
about the Mayan civilization?
I just wanted to tell you
that your writing is beautiful.
You should show it to more people.
Let's go to Yucai.
Stop hesitating.
I won't make it.
You haven't tried, so how do you know?
Come on.
Join me.
Forget it.
Come on, let's try together.
Pinky swear, a hundred years,
no take-backs.
It's settled. Seal it.
Where are the slippers?
No need to change.
That won't do.
I came from outside.
We don't have so many rules. Come on in.
Come here.
Let me show you
my super-duper huge bedroom.
My sofa bed.
It's nice.
Have a seat.
A rat.
What's wrong?
There's a rat.
I heard it.
I heard...
A rat.
It was squeaking here.
That sound...
Where is it?
A rat.
We do have a big rat in our house.
Don't scare me.
Look how scared you are. You froze.
Let me show you
this universal super rat.
Ren Xiaofei, my little brother.
He hides in the wardrobe
whenever a stranger comes.
Come out now.
Come on.
Come out.
Hello, Bai Shu.
Hello there, Xiaofei.
I'm Bai Shu.
Nice to meet you.
This coil of yours
is wrong, isn't it?
Let me help you.
See?
Bai Shu is going to fix it for you.
Come out now.
Go ahead and play. I'll cook.
Try my cooking later.
Let me help you.
No need.
I finally got off work early.
This is...
This is Bai Shu, my classmate
and my best friend.
And mine.
And yours?
She is my...
Hello, Auntie.
Auntie, you're so pretty.
What did you say?
Young lady, you're also pretty
and have great taste.
You two are good friends?
All three of you?
Is dinner ready? Let's eat together.
Not yet.
I just got home
and haven't had time to cook.
Auntie, let me help her.
No need.
Sit down.
How can we let our guest cook?
All of you, sit down. I'll cook today.
Really?
Then I'm in for a treat, Auntie.
You're such a sweet talker.
Why are you so sweet?
What have they been feeding you?
Have fun.
Wait for the food.
Okay, Auntie.
Usually, I cook after I come home.
She eats whatever's ready.
The sun is rising from the west.
♪Summer blooms on the branches♪
♪Roses, roses, I love you♪
- ♪Roses, roses, carry deep affection♪
- Look how happy she is.
- She's even singing.
Wasn't it just one compliment
about her looks?
- She is pretty.
- ♪Roses, roses♪
- Prettier than you.
- ♪I love you♪
What? I'm telling the truth.
♪Holy light shines upon the earth♪
You two, hold on a second.
Wait.
Bai Shu, you try it first.
Okay, Auntie.
Oh my, Auntie.
It's amazing.
You're pretty and sing sweetly.
Your cooking is also amazing.
Stop laughing. Your gums are showing.
Have more.
Come often.
I will cook for you.
Bai Shu, do you like our home?
I love it.
Come every day if you want.
If you come, I'll be free.
We have tons of chores.
Washing clothes, cooking,
mopping, and cleaning the house.
No problem.
You...
Xiaoming, which one of you is older?
I was born in February, she in June.
You should call me big sister.
You two are also four months apart?
Yeah, why?
Look how smug you are.
All that extra time on Earth,
and you've got nothing to show for it.
Bai Shu, come often.
Come whenever you want.
I also like Bai Shu.
You barely say anything.
So talkative today?
Auntie.
I came to announce something.
What's so serious?
Xiaoming and I have decided
to aim for Yucai High School.
I didn't say that.
I didn't...
I know you're too shy to say it.
Why would I be shy?
It's not like that.
What is Yucai?
Yucai High School, the best in La City.
What? La City?
If she gets into Yucai,
she will have to go to La City?
Yeah, if we get in,
we will live in the dorms there.
Sun Jinfu is from La City, though.
Who is Sun Jinfu?
No idea.
Is this high school expensive?
Does it cost a lot of money?
Auntie, once we pass the exam
and get in,
tuition is the same
as regular high school.
Is the exam hard?
It's really hard.
That's good.
You really don't want me
to get in, do you?
If I get in,
no one will take care
of your precious son, huh?
I'm telling you.
I'll only be your maid
for three more months.
Then you're on your own.
Oh, please.
You talk like
you're guaranteed to get in.
Don't be so smug.
Leave yourself a way out.
Get me some rice.
Auntie.
Xiaoming will definitely make it.
Look at her.
So terrified.
If I didn't push her,
would she dare to try?
Reverse psychology.
Xiaofei.
Why are you crying?
Don't listen to your sister.
She won't get in.
If she got in, I would be a dog, okay?
Don't cry, my boy.
What if I do get in?
What do you want?
If I get in,
circle this table three times
and bark like a dog.
I...
Look how scared she is.
I'm awesome, huh?
Thank you.
I know you came to encourage me.
Not entirely.
I've wanted to visit for a long time.
Now you've seen it.
My whole family is crazy.
I really like your home and your mom.
My mom? Please.
I like your mom.
So gentle and so classy.
But you keep giving her attitude.
If I had a mom like yours,
I'd be over the moon.
She's not a good mom.
And you wouldn't want to be me.
See you tomorrow.
Bai Shu...
Did I say something wrong?
That's just the truth.
You're back. Wash your hands and eat.
I'm not hungry.
Not hungry?
It's fine.
Then don't eat.
I waited for you at the school gate
for two hours today.
I stood the whole time.
You know I have varicose veins
and can't stand for long.
Where were you those two hours?
I treat you so well.
I've given you everything.
But you?
I'm like that fish.
In your heart,
these are all garbage,
right?
You don't cherish them. You don't care.
You leave whenever you want
and refuse to eat.
You're hurting someone
who loves you most
and has raised you from childhood.
Aren't you ashamed?
Are you heartless?
Speak.
I told you to speak.
Why don't you talk?
Torturing me?
Torturing me.
I told you to apologize.
I-I'm sorry.
Say "Mom, I'm sorry."
I'm sorry.
"Mom, I'm sorry."
I told you to say "Mom, I'm sorry."
Say it!
I'm sorry.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Okay.
Wash your hands and eat.
Let's eat.
=Vanished Name=