(Pretty Boy)
(Episode 6)
Look at our life.
We roast wild game every day.
It's too comfortable, isn't it?
I think I've gained weight again.
Jiaoniang too.
It doesn't matter if you gain more weight.
It's best if we all gain a few more pounds.
When we walk down the street then,
it'll be like a group of Hu Jiao walking together. What a sight!
Since when did you start making witty remarks?
You're not being reasonable anymore?
You must have learned it all from Qing Cai, right?
You're right. He's just a troublemaker.
It's not right for you to say that.
You're insulting yourself by saying that.
And you're calling all of us trouble.
Then I guess I'm the troublemaker.
Who are you calling trouble?
I...
Han Aizhen.
How dare you bully my Jiaoniang!
I'll fight you!
You're not eating anymore?
It was a collateral damage.
You're done for. She's gone to get a kitchen knife.
I know it.
It can't be true, right?
Han Aizhen, just you wait.
Don't!
Come here!
You're really doing this?
Hu Jiao, give me that basin.
I'll help you avenge your Jiaoniang.
Hu Jiao.
Don't run!
Why are you three eating so much today?
I can't eat anymore.
I can't go on.
I can't eat anymore, I'm too tired.
I'm going to bed.
Take your time eating.
I'm off.
I'm full too.
I'm going for a walk.
Let's go for a walk too.
My back hurts from sitting.
Why do you have so many crossbow arrows here?
It looks like it's becoming an arsenal.
They're just for backup.
Who knows what might happen in the future?
You've just arrived here,
and you've already made this kind of cellar?
No, this
is formed by utilizing the natural terrain.
And,
it's just being used as a backup trap for now.
I admire your abilities.
I have many more abilities.
You'll discover them gradually.
Meeting you is like finding a treasure.
Who said you found anything?
Dream on.
Cover it up.
Let's go.
Speaking of which,
what do you think of today's competition?
I don't know martial arts,
so I can't tell.
But I think
your duel with Gan Pu was quite spectacular.
I'm just
feeling a bit uncomfortable, that's all.
Young Master Wang,
that Qing Cai has lost all face for you.
So pathetic.
And Hua Gu has been very depressed lately.
Young Master Wang,
you have
left a trail of broken hearts wherever you go, don't you?
Tea drinking is a refined activity.
Indeed, one must find the right company for it.
Look at him. He's trying to get rid of us.
Fine.
I know when I'm not wanted.
I'm leaving.
Who are you?
And who are you?
You don't need to know who we are.
But since we're already here,
our purposes might be the same.
Many people come here,
each with their own purpose.
Then I should kill you.
Wait.
Since I've already fallen into your hands,
I'll tell you
to avoid allies from killing each other.
If you're enemies,
I'll accept my fate.
Tell us the truth.
I'm here to rescue someone.
Aren't you here to kill?
No, to rescue.
Rescuing is my mission.
Our purposes are the same.
Which organization are you from?
We're just lone wolves,
not part of any organization.
We came here
just to help a friend.
You're friends with that person?
I don't know who you're referring to,
and I can't say.
But I won't ask which organization you're from.
I just need to know
if we have the same purpose.
If we can be allies,
then we'll have more strength.
Why should I trust you?
I didn't kill you just now. Isn't that enough?
You might not be able to kill me now.
You can try.
Fighting here would hurt us both, wouldn't it?
I can trust you for now.
Do you have any way
to break the barrier inside?
We passed through the outer formation of Mingyi Manor.
Our people have tried many methods.
If we don't make a big move,
there's no way to break the barrier inside.
What help can you offer?
What do you need?
Money.
We don't have that much money.
Breaking that barrier requires special tools.
We can do it,
but we don't have money to buy the materials.
How much do you need?
Ten taels of silver.
Just ten taels of silver?
People with connections are indeed different.
Do you have them?
No.
We have a contact in our town.
I can have him go to the royal city to get the money.
Why go to the royal city for just ten taels of silver?
We're not some local rich folks.
Who carries that much money around?
Wouldn't it be heavy?
How much money do you usually carry?
A few coins.
How long does it take to go to and from the royal city?
It takes about three days.
But we've already wasted several days.
I'll be uneasy if we waste another day.
How about we try to find a way from us disciples?
What do you mean?
Among the fellow disciples being trained this time,
there's one who eats a lot.
I saw her open her bundle one day,
and there was a lot of silver inside.
I can try.
I'll also arrange for someone from the town to get the money.
Alright.
Then for the next few days,
come here at this time every day to wait for us.
Okay.
Don't wait for us more than an hour each time.
I'm not sure if those two people
can gather enough money for us to buy the materials.
Let's go.
I think Han Aizhen might be
following us now.
She's definitely following us.
Which means
she doesn't fully trust us.
Even if she trusts us,
her superiors might not believe us.
Should we still include her in our future actions?
There are many hidden sentries there.
You can't handle them alone.
She's skilled in combat.
Understood.
Then we'll start with Hu Jiao tomorrow.
Let's go to town to make arrangements.
Alright.
It's perfect to let Han Aizhen lose our trail.
Why don't we
perform another "get lost" trick for her here?
It seems they can indeed pass through the grand formation.
I've woken them all up.
Boss, what did you call us for?
I heard you all had your first sales today.
Yeah, and I didn't throw up today.
My mom didn't roll around on the ground either.
What's going on?
We didn't sell anything today
when we were closing up.
Did your families give you trouble?
Our families didn't bother us.
They didn't give us any trouble.
Really?
Really.
My mom ended up eating everything.
She threw up several times, didn't she?
Are you okay?
Are you alright, Mom?
It's fine.
This woman has eaten too much.
Alright.
I've called you here today because I have a task for you.
Boss, we'll do
as you say.
Right.
Tomorrow, I'll bring a wealthy client here.
I want to
get all the money from her.
Tell us, what's the plan?
Have this poison ready for tomorrow.
Poison?
Boss, are you planning to poison someone in public?
That's so thrilling.
Come on, let's divide it up.
Tomorrow, add a small spoon of poison to each portion of food.
When they're about to die from the spiciness,
they'll devour your tangyuan.
Tomorrow, reduce the amount of tangyuan in each serving.
Just one tangyuan per bowl, with extra soup.
Why's that?
We're selling it as soup.
Boss,
are you sure one spoonful won't kill someone?
I've tried this dosage myself.
In my experience,
this amount is about right.
It'll be very spicy, but bearable.
What if I add two more spoonfuls?
They'd die.
Tomorrow, tell the people who come
if they want the regular one, it's the original price.
If they want the one with this poison,
the price is ten times higher.
Ten times?
Who would buy that?
Exactly!
This is specially prepared for the person
coming tomorrow.
You remember it?
Okay.
So if someone else comes and wants to eat this,
do we sell it to them?
Of course we sell it!
We don't sell it, right?
How are you even smarter than a pig?
Of course, I'm smarter than a pig!
Tell me.
Would Hu Jiao like the poison you mentioned?
Most likely.
What are the chances
those unreliable people of yours can pull this off?
They're all talented individuals.
Talented at relying on luck, I suppose.
No.
My luck
is always unpredictable.
I really admire your confidence.
Blindly optimistic.
Let's go.
You're back.
We're back.
It's quite warm.
Who lit the fire?
I did.
Did you two sneak off to take a bath?
Didn't you guys go take a bath too?
We did.
Don't even mention it.
We were interrupted halfway through.
What a buzzkill.
No way. I have to make up for it tomorrow.
Hey, why do you keep staring at me?
Is there a toad on my face?
You two went to take a bath together?
That's right.
And you took so long?
We just enjoy bathing.
It seems we're really not compatible.
We're already even.
Yet you're still so interested in me.
Han Aizhen,
you don't happen to like women, do you?
They say you only hurt the ones you love.
I...
I have absolutely no interest in women.
So you only like men, huh?
Did you two enjoy bathing together?
Doctor Gao,
I thought you always took the aloof approach.
Didn't expect you to make jokes like this.
I'm in a bad mood.
Do we have different senses of humor?
I don't think this even qualifies as a bad joke.
According to your way of thinking,
being in a bad mood is also an experience.
It should be interesting.
But it's also quite boring, isn't it?
It's a pity we don't have any alcohol.
Otherwise, I'd definitely have a good drink with you.
Gao Yin's way of thinking
is even more topsy-turvy than Qing Cai's.
It's indeed hard for ordinary people to understand you.
What's so topsy-turvy about having a drink?
So you're just an ordinary person.
That's why I like it.
I'm going to find some alcohol to drink tomorrow.
Qing Cai.
It's pretty normal for Hu Jiao to drink alcohol.
You're so delicate.
Who's delicate?
You are.
Don't judge a book by its cover.
I almost forgot.
Forgot what?
People always judge by appearances.
Who says they don't?
♫What kind of encounter♫
♫Sparks both tenderness and excitement?♫
♫I can see in your eyes♫
♫A vast and boundless sky♫
♫Brushing past in a sea of people♫
♫Waiting for time to glance back♫
♫If love shines like a shooting star♫
♫Who can truly hold it close?♫
♫The wandering I long endured♫
♫Once had someone by my side♫
♫The heartfelt moments in my memory♫
♫How to describe them with words?♫
♫I dare not reach out♫
♫Afraid to shatter the dream♫
You don't need to go to class today.
Liu Yiyi is not in a good mental state.
Should we go check on him?
He probably doesn't want to see you.
He must really dislike us now.
Then why doesn't he quit?
He's thinking about what to do.
He's a very persistent person.
Otherwise, he would have quit long ago.
Persist in what? Persist in thinking?
Wouldn't that mean he's been thinking over and over again,
and then thinking some more,
and just keeps thinking endlessly?
Mental illness
can only be overcome by himself.
Forget it. Let's not talk about this anymore.
What are you guys going to do later?
I'm going to the town.
I won't stay with you guys today.
I want to go to the town too.
The food at Mingyi Manor is too monotonous.
I'll go too.
Gao Yin, let's go together.
I'd like to go for a walk too.
Why don't we all go together?
Let's go.
Stop!
Why are you following us?
I'm going the same way.
The weather is quite nice today.
It's with gentle breeze and warm sunshine.
There's a clothing store over there.
Let's go take a look.
Sure.
Would you like to take a look at our fabrics, honored guests?
What color of clothes do you like?
Let's get you a new outfit.
Young Master Wang, what color do you think suits me?
I think you could try some
fresh and elegant colors.
Fresh and elegant?
What colors would be considered fresh and elegant?
There are two more boxes over there. Help me bring them here.
Alright!
For example, this moonlight white,
or light cyan.
You could try both.
Is he buying fabric for Gan Pu?
How can that be? I haven't given her anything yet.
They do look quite nice.
But usually I...
Isn't that all Gao Yin's style?
Do you want to transform Gan Pu into Gao Yin?
I didn't know that in Young Master Wang's heart,
you held such a high position.
Every time he sees a woman,
he uses you as the standard.
You're getting bolder and bolder.
Do you think I'm too mild-mannered
and have started taking advantage of me?
Aren't we close already?
I don't see you as an outsider.
I don't need your help.
Moreover,
aren't you afraid of making things worse?
Have you found anything you like?
Let's look around a bit more.
You don't understand women.
Women in love can sometimes be quite
fragile.
It's only been a few days,
yet you two seem quite close.
Young Master Wang,
you asked me what color I like.
Are you planning to buy fabric to make clothes for me?
Of course.
What are you talking about?
Young Master Wang,
are you buying fabric to make clothes for all of us?
That's so thoughtful of you!
I like red.
How can red be appropriate?
That's for wedding dresses.
Who wears that on a daily basis?
Why can't I wear it?
It's not like I'll ever get married anyway.
I can wear it every day.
Who said you can't get married?
Who was it? I'll settle the score with them.
Who? Who? Who?
I said it myself.
Who curses themselves like that?
There are so many men in this world.
Where are all these men in the world?
You mean Young Master Wang?
Isn't he the one you like?
How could I compete with you for him?
What's over there?
In this world,
Wang Yishao isn't the only man out there.
Who else?
Hong Hui?
Doesn't he like you?
How could I compete with you?
Why do you always try to steal men from Qing Cai?
There are only two men here,
and they're both connected to Qing Cai.
Who's connected to him?
Look, look.
I told you two were in sync.
If you ask me,
the two of them are a match made in heaven.
-Who’s matched with her?
-Who...
Miss, take a look.
How did we end up out here?
Weren't we supposed to look at fabrics?
I don't need that many new clothes either.
It's quite cumbersome to carry them around.
Why don't you buy some for Hu Jiao and the others?
Never mind, we're already out.
I'll fleece you next time.
Finding something to eat is more important right now.
Let's go. Let's go find some food.
Miss, look.
Look, over there.
Those people are laughing so awkwardly.
Let's go take a look.
Bro, what's this?
This is called Malatang.
Malatang? How much is this?
Vegetable dishes cost one wen, while meat dishes cost two wen.
What would you like?
I'll try one of each, vegetarian and meat.
Alright.
Finally, we're open for business.
Here, take it carefully.
Be careful, it's hot.
How is it?
The taste is quite good.
Is that so?
The key is, it's not spicy at all.
It's not spicy? That's okay.
I have spicier ones here.
Quickly, add some for me. I want to try it.
Well, um...
It seems...
If you want it spicier, you'll have to pay extra.
Right?
How much? Tell me.
How much was it again?
Ten wen for vegetarian, twenty wen for meat.
That's way too expensive!
Have you been blinded by greed?
I remember now.
I'm not selling anymore. Give it back to me.
Why won't you sell? Explain it to me clearly.
Who said we're not selling?
My Boss said we're not selling anymore.
Boss.
B... Boss.
We only sell to beautiful women.
Are you saying I'm not beautiful?
No, no, no.
It's like this.
Everyone's aesthetic is different.
In my eyes,
you're the most beautiful in the world.
You have good taste.
In that case...
Give me one with meat.
Sure thing!
Okay.
Here you go, take it carefully.
Be careful, it's hot.
Finally, we have our first order.
How is it?
It's amazing!
I've never had such amazing skewers before.
Really?
Then give me one too.
I won't sell to you.
Why not?
They...
Only sell to beautiful women.
No, no, no.
Those who come with beautiful women are also welcome.
Gentlemen, come this way.
I have grilled skewers over here.
Same recipe, same taste.
You can come and try them.
Boss said we have to sell.
What? I don't remember.
You're asking for a beating.
No, please!
I'll sell to you!
I'll sell! I will!
I know it already.
Why are you so excited?
You're shouting so loudly. Are you trying to sell yourself?
Idiot.
What an idiot.
This is way too spicy!
What is this? What's it called?
That's called "Poison."
-Yes.
-Poison! Poison!
"Poison" is good.
Poison is like tears that have been shed.
Endless longing, a heart-wrenching poison,
spills a lover's tears.
It seems the name "Poison" is still too fierce.
Lover's Tears.
Just now, this Young Master Wang
gave your "Poison" a new name.
It's called "Lover's Tears."
This name does sound better than "Poison."
Good, good, good.
So from now on, let's call it "Lover's Tears."
Good. Lover's Tears.
Alright. Come on.
Everyone, come buy my Lover's Tears!
Big sale!
Big sale! Lover's Tears!
Big sale?
Big sale!
How much discount?
Is there a discount?
A discount?
No discount. Big sale at original price!
Yes, yes.
Big sale at original price!
Give me ten portions.
You're looking to experience heartbreak, aren't you?
You really understand me.
We only live once. We can't waste our lives.
When it's time to feel something,
we should feel it to the fullest.
If it's not good, you don't have to pay!
Lover's Tears!
Big sale! Big sale!
Ten wen for vegetarian, twenty wen for meat.
If you want to eat skewers,
you'll have to share with me later.
I'm going to eat you all into poverty.
We'll definitely eat them into poverty.
But it's too spicy.
Does anyone have water? I need to drink water.
Are you also selling Lover's Tears?
I have tangyuan here.
Tangyuan can help with the spiciness.
I'll have a skewer too.
Six wen.
Here.
Thank you.
Six wen.
This is too spicy. Let me eat it.
I... I'll eat it.
Give me one.
I'll have another bite.
Gan Pu, I've finished eating.
Line up and move forward.
We have enough for everyone.
Gan Pu.
It's quite tasty.
Another bowl, please.
Come, try our skewers.
Come, get your grilled skewers!
Try this.
Skewers here!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
What's wrong with you?
Delicious food here!
If it's not tasty, it's free!
Take a look!
It's really delicious!
What is this? Why are they eating like that?
Young Master Wang gave it a new name.
Lover's Tears.
I was just teasing Hong Hui.
I didn't expect them to use it.
Then why are they crying?
You're so silly.
Listen to this name,
Lover's Tears.
Do you understand now?
Is it that exaggerated?
Give me one.
Alright!
This is practically poison!
You always see through to the truth of things.
I'm impressed.
It's actually quite tasty.
Is it that spicy? Look at you crying like that.
It's really spicy.
If you can't handle it, don't eat it.
I...
I'm eating it, I...
Are you kidding? Is it really that spicy?
You guys just won't stop, will you?
Quick, give me a bowl of tangyuan.
Here, here.
You pay for me.
Miss,
you're so beautiful
that you outshine all others.
Won't you have a skewer?
It's on me.
I'll give it for free too. Free!
For free!
Yes, this young lady,
a celestial beauty, unparalleled in the world.
I'll give it for free too.
Free, free, free!
Or is there any girl here,
who thinks she's prettier than her?
I'll give it all for free for her.
-Fair to all, regardless of age.
-I’m prettier than her.
I'm prettier than her.
Can I have it for free?
Your word alone doesn't count.
We need everyone to vote.
Right, right, right.
Ladies and gentlemen,
those with money, show your support with it,
those without, show your support in person.
If you think I'm prettier,
give me some applause!
It's up to you to keep me fed.
Alright.
If you think she's prettier, clap now.
Okay, okay, okay.
Can I eat for free now?
Alright.
Here, little one.
Where did this little girl come from?
She's made a monkey out of me.
Sir, I want one skewer too.
How many do you want?
Don't push. Come one by one.
Take it easy.
There's enough for everyone.
Here are the tangyuan.
The capable shoulder more work. You eat.
It's delicious.
I know.
Here.
Eat first, Han Aizhen, eat.
Take your time.
Take it.
We're still eating?
Come on, take it.
Everyone, don't push.
Hold it carefully.
Take your time.
On your way back,
you were scratching your head and ears,
looking just like a monkey.
those with money, show your support with it,
those without, show your support in person.
If you think I'm prettier,
give me a round of applause.
-You…
-What…
-You're even imitating now.
-What do you think?
Are you prettier or is she?
What do you think?
I think I'm prettier.
Don't run!
You... you...
Instead of hitting that kid, you hit me?
Boss.
Who told you to organize this beauty pageant?
It really wasn't me.
Jing started it. I had nothing to do with it.
You dare to hide?
No, Jing said
I wouldn't get beaten if I came here.
So you're not here for me to vent my anger on?
Why are you here then?
What am I here for?
Oh, right.
Here.
This is what we've managed to gather so far.
Jing told me to hurry over and give it to you first.
Ten taels of silver, so quickly?
Jing said as soon as I enter,
I should give you the silver,
and then I wouldn't get beaten.
Alright.
This is what they call making amends.
Next time, when you're all gathered,
I'll beat you all together.
If there's nothing else, go back and continue your business.
Okay, okay, okay.
Go on.
Quick, let me take a look.
There really are ten taels of silver.
Let's go. Let's go process it.
Let's go.
Come on, let's go.
Emergency! Get out of the way quickly!
Stop fooling around.
Young man,
why are you dressed up like a fairy today?
Dark Egg, you're joining in on this nonsense too?
Hurry and help me get the materials. I need to save my father.
That's quite a lot of materials.
Alright, I'll get on it right away.
Awesome!
No way.
What's wrong?
My stomach hurts.
Is that so?
Do you still want to eat the Lover's Tears?
I can't take it anymore.
It's okay, it's okay.
I'll help you.
Let's go quickly.
Don't eat it anymore in the future.
This is really a disaster.
It's not bad. It's delicious.
Go over there.
It's really delicious.
This is for the two beautiful ladies.
It's good, isn't it?
Give it to them.
Are you okay?
I can't even speak anymore. Let's go.
Take it easy.
♫A gentle breeze brushes past the bright moon♫
♫Your radiance spreads softly in the wind♫
♫Your quiet arrival♫
♫Tugs at my heartstrings♫
♫My heartbeat pauses at this very moment♫
♫Drizzling spring rain nourishes the soul♫
♫The sea of flowers in my heart blooms full of longing♫
♫No need for sweet words♫
♫Sharing simple moments♫
♫Our meeting no longer feels distant♫
♫A shooting star streaks across the sky♫
♫Wishes find their answer♫
♫I wish to pluck♫
♫The moon in the sky♫
♫Willing to change, all for you♫
♫Softly, softly whispering♫
♫You're by my side♫
♫Heart to heart, in unison♫
♫Forever intertwined♫
♫Memories swing gently like a hammock in my mind♫
♫Echoing between you and me, you and me♫
♫The sun rises, and the sun sets again♫
♫The moon wanes and then waxes again♫
It looks like we've saved a lot of materials.
I didn't expect the success rate to be so high this time.
We're really lucky.
Then we can store the extra materials here.
We might need them in the future.
Sounds good.
What's wrong?
I'm used to it.
I always did this when I was injured before.
My uncle told me when I was young,
if I don't suck out the poisoned blood,
it could be fatal in severe cases.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It's getting dark.
Let's come back another day.
Next time we come,
we can try making sleeve arrows.
Are those the crossbow arrows hidden in sleeves?
Yes.
That's a secret technique of our Mo Clan.
It's our exclusive technology.
These sleeve arrows
are much more powerful than ordinary sleeve arrows.
Since they're hidden in the sleeves,
they're highly concealed.
Unlike crossbows.
You know,
when we face opponents much stronger than us
in a fight,
sometimes we need to ambush them.
With these sleeve arrows,
even face to face with them,
they can hardly escape.
Okay.
Let's come back next time then.
Gan Pu.
♫What kind of encounter♫
You... You're like a tomboy.
♫Sparks both tenderness and excitement?♫
♫I can see in your eyes♫
You're the one who's like a fake woman.
If you don't know how to talk properly, then don't talk.
♫I can see in your eyes♫
♫A vast and boundless sky♫
What are you looking at?
♫Brushing past in a sea of people♫
Let's go.
♫Waiting for time to glance back♫
You know what?
Gao Yin's medicine is quite effective, isn't it?
Of course, it is.
Just look at who Gao Yin is.
Do you think
Qing Cai came back first?
Did she go somewhere to sulk?
Those people were really too much.
They harassed her on the street. She must feel very upset.
Why harass her and not us?
It's because she's flirting around.
It's... It's starting to hurt again.
Don't you think Qing Cai is quite charming?
Her? Please.
You're not a bit jealous of her, are you?
I just can't stand her.
A woman is blamed
even when she is harassed by men.
It's really unfair.
Well...
Agreed.
I just don't like her
timid and submissive attitude.
If I were harassed today,
I'd slap them right away.
That's right.
If it were me, I'd give them two slaps.
Right?
Exactly.
She's not like you two.
You...
We could take on twenty like you.
Stop walking.
It's too tiring.
Tell me.
Do you think Hu Jiao and the others might still be in town?
It's hard to say.
So you'll have to keep wearing this, won't you?
Actually, we could both just wear men's clothing.
We've only been out for half a day and you want to change clothes.
It's so easy to arouse suspicion.
Wang Yishao is not an ordinary person.
It seems you have a high opinion of him.
Indeed.
You see,
he is quite handsome and dashing.
And he's very considerate.
Most women
would find it hard to resist his charm.
That's true.
I've noticed Gao Yin has been quite close to you lately.
Do you think she might like you?
Who's close to her?
You are.
-Who's close to her?
-You are.
Who, who, who?
You, you, you.
In your opinion, Wang Yishao is so great.
Why did you choose me?
You don't understand.
Think about it.
Who is Wang Yishao?
He's a prince.
His status is noble,
right?
He's handsome too.
So many women like him.
I'm just a commoner.
How could I be worthy of him?
So, I definitely need to find someone
who's a bit dumber, a bit poorer,
and treats me better.
I'll just keep him as a pet for fun.