[Walk with You]
[Episode 18]
[The Truth]
Although I've regained my memory,
I have no martial arts skills left.
Given the current situation,
I can only return to Xie Yuheng's side.
Only by catching him off guard
can I avenge my father.
You can't even keep an eye on a person.
What use are you to me?
I'm willing to accept my punishment,
Your Highness.
Let it go.
Heng.
You may leave now.
Yes, Your Highness.
Where did you go?
Why didn't you tell me?
I was worried sick.
I wanted to have Qian's candied fruit,
but I couldn't find any maids,
so I went to buy it by myself.
Look, I brought some back for you too.
Yuheng.
Heng, who is he?
Even if she hasn't regained her memory,
we just met yesterday,
why she doesn't recognize me today?
Something's not right.
Ying.
Let's play a game, shall we?
What game?
He's the Seventh Prince, Xie Yian.
He just returned from the border
and hasn't met you.
He also doesn't know
you're the Chief Minister's daughter.
Let's pretend to be master and maid
and deceive him
and see how he reacts.
What do you think?
Okay.
He's the Seventh Prince,
you should bow quickly when seeing him.
Greetings, Your Highness.
This is...?
This is my newly recruited maid.
My name is Ying.
Ying?
You don't look like a maid,
but more like a young lady
from a wealthy family.
I'm flattered, Your Highness.
But I am indeed just a maid.
Just a mere maid,
yet you are so close
to the Crown Prince.
Have you forgotten
about your engagement
to Princess Furong, Yuheng?
If Father finds out
about this maid by your side,
what do you think he will think?
Thank you for the reminder.
I will explain everything
to him myself.
You needn't worry about me.
Heng,
does His Highness dislike me?
Is he going to send me away?
No one can send you away.
Don't bother with him.
Yian,
I have important matters to attend to.
You may leave the Eastern Palace now.
Sorry for not seeing you out.
Take care, Your Highness.
Alright.
You are cheeky indeed, Yian.
Of course. How else can I become
the leading playboy in the capital?
This maid seems rather special.
Her features resemble someone
I've seen before.
Yuheng, do you know who it is?
By chance, I saw
a portrait of Su Yingying, the daughter
of Chief Minister Su.
This maid looks exactly like her,
even sharing
the same "Ying" in her name.
Are you done talking?
Now, I'm in charge
of the Three Judicial Departments
and often review case files.
I even came across the case
about Chief Minister Su three years ago.
Ying, let's go.
Don't listen to his nonsense here.
Yian has a mischievous nature.
Don't mind him.
I don't mind at all.
I find what he said quite amusing.
He seems to have a way with words.
Of course,
you are still the best in the world.
By the way, Heng,
you work tirelessly
for the national affairs
every day.
You must be exhausted.
I'll prepare some hot water for you,
so you could relax and unwind.
Yuheng, let me join in.
Heng, I've prepared
the hot water for you.
Enjoy it with His Highness.
Thank you, Ying.
You may leave.
Okay.
Yuheng, what are you standing there for?
Come into the pool now.
The hot water provided by Ying
is so comfortable.
Su Tu said Xie Yuheng
is not of royal blood,
but members of the Xie Family
all have a plum blossom mark
on their bodies.
A simple check will reveal the truth.
You have a really good physique.
Lean yet muscular,
toned and strong.
He has a plum blossom mark.
He is from the Xie Family.
Could Su Tu be wrong?
You're not bad either.
Broad shoulders, narrow waist,
and fair skin.
How do you manage to maintain
such a physique
despite your busy schedule?
I often go horseback riding and hunting
when I have free time.
Then we must have
a hunting trip together in the future.
Sure.
By the way,
We'll have a competition.
Please go easy on me then.
Who's there?
Heng,
are you inside?
open the door.
Ying.
What's wrong?
I'm afraid of thunder.
Alright.
You are the best!
Yuheng.
I'm also afraid of thunder.
You are already a grownup,
yet you're still afraid of thunder?
I'm afraid of many things.
Thanks, Yuheng.
♪Lots of memories
fade into the distant past♪
♪The lonely swan goose
cries out in sorrow♪
♪Life passes by,
suddenly reaching the twilight years♪
♪The evening breeze hints at snow,
yet the boat doesn't cross the river♪
♪Peach blossoms fall in a sweet dream,
the moon remains unchanged♪
♪Having a jug of liquor
in the night rain, softly telling tales♪
♪No return on the road, no looking back♪
♪Good times also pass in vain♪
♪Trapped in the cycle of day and night♪
♪The candle by the west window
burns out, consuming this life♪
♪Ultimately, it's all in vain♪
♪Asking why, yearning for
the distant beloved through all seasons♪
♪A cup of soil,
alone in this vast world♪
♪See how time flies♪
♪With no company to be found♪