[Walk with You]
[Episode 13]
[The Deal]
You've got rid of evils for the people,
not only solving
the counterfeit banknote case
but also clearing my father's name.
I'm sending you this gift
as a mark of esteem.
You are welcome.
I invite you over this time
to inquire about an organization
related to the word "bird".
An organization
There is indeed an organization
matching that description.
However, it's an assassin organization,
targeting only high-ranking officials
and the wealthy.
High-ranking officials and the wealthy.
It seems to be Xie Yuheng after all.
Your Highness.
Are you referring to the Crown Prince?
I suspect the true mastermind
behind the counterfeit banknote case
is the Crown Prince,
because the Chief Minister Su
was investigating this case
before he died,
and the Crown Prince
has attached great importance to it,
often visiting the Archive
of the Three Judicial Departments
to check on the progress
of the investigation.
Wasn't the mastermind
the Left Vice Minister
of the Ministry of Revenue?
He's dead.
So,
I'm even more suspicious
that Xie Yuheng is the mastermind.
Your Highness,
His Majesty calls for your presence
in the palace.
Call for my presence in the palace?
Suying.
Furong.
Why are you here?
This is for you.
For... For me?
Thank you for saving me yesterday.
No worries. Thank you for your flowers.
Oh, I also made
some nourishing tea for you.
Suying.
I've brought back some delicious food
from the palace for you.
Father wanted to host
a birthday banquet for me,
but I declined.
Birthday banquet?
Is it your birthday soon?
Yes. It's coming up in a few days.
What gift are you going to give me?
What do you like?
I'll like whatever you give me.
Suying, I also want a gift.
You want one too?
But it's not your birthday.
Can't I celebrate it today?
Sure, you can celebrate it
any day you want.
Since the last failed arrest,
the Seventh Prince's mansion
has been heavily guarded.
It's difficult to plant spies.
We can only take it by storm.
Now is not the time to take it by storm.
Today is the Seventh Prince's birthday,
which is the perfect opportunity
to investigate
the identity of that maid.
I'll dispatch someone right away...
No need.
It might alert them.
Since the maid is in the mansion,
I'll personally go
and meet her to find it out.
You've solved the case
and today's your birthday.
It's truly two happy events
happening at the same time.
But why don't you
host a banquet at home
and invite guests over to celebrate?
I'm not familiar
with those social niceties
and the affairs of the imperial court.
I'll have to rely on you
to take care of me.
Come on.
By the way,
is there a new rule
in the Archive that anyone
other than His Majesty
can't enter
the Archive without permission?
Xie Yuheng. It is really him.
It's also Father's intention.
Yuheng,
if you want to access
the documents in the Archive,
just let me know.
I'll have someone send them to you.
Okay.
Cheers.
Give this to me. You can go now.
Yes.
Your Highness,
please enjoy this Golden Lotus Soup.
Didn't I tell you
not to serve this dish?
Can't you understand my words?
Bring another dish.
Go!
Yes.
Yuheng, where are you going?
You've finally come to visit me,
and I have a lot to say to you.
Yuheng, please.
Please.
Yuheng.
Ying.
Ying, I'm coming in.
What are you doing here?
I know you're angry.
Then why did you stop me?
You know that was the best chance
for me to kill him.
At present, we haven't got
solid evidence against Xie Yuheng
for falsely accusing
Chief Minister Su of treason,
nor have we confirmed him
as the mastermind
behind the counterfeit banknote case.
If you act hastily,
and if we fail,
it'll render all our efforts futile.
It's never too late
for a person to take revenge.
Until we find out
what he has been doing,
we must proceed cautiously
with patience.
What's this?
Between boundless water
and pulsating veins,
not a word
can be said.
♪Lots of memories
fade into the distant past♪
♪The lonely swan goose
cries out in sorrow♪
♪Life passes by,
suddenly reaching the twilight years♪
Fireflies.
The light of fireflies. Ying.
[*The two words have a similar sound.]
Is this the gift you want to give me?
Today,
I originally intended
to give you the gift.
♪Peach blossoms fall in a sweet dream,
the moon remains unchanged♪
I'm sorry.
You've suffered so much,
and I didn't pay attention
to your feelings at all.
I've realized my fault.
Will you forgive me?
♪Trapped in the cycle of day and night♪
♪The candle by the west window
burns out, consuming this life♪
♪Ultimately, it's all in vain♪
♪Asking why, yearning for
the distant beloved through all seasons♪
♪A cup of soil,
alone in this vast world♪
♪Sighing in the twilight years♪
♪Lots of memories
fade into the distant past♪
♪The lonely swan goose
cries out in sorrow♪
♪Life passes by,
suddenly reaching the twilight years♪
♪The evening breeze hints at snow,
yet the boat doesn't cross the river♪
♪Peach blossoms fall in a sweet dream,
the moon remains unchanged♪
♪Having a jug of liquor
in the night rain, softly telling tales♪
♪No return on the road, no looking back♪
♪Good times also pass in vain♪
♪Trapped in the cycle of day and night♪
♪The candle by the west window
burns out, consuming this life♪
♪Ultimately, it's all in vain♪
♪Asking why, yearning for
the distant beloved through all seasons♪
♪A cup of soil,
alone in this vast world♪
♪See how time flies♪
♪With no company to be found♪