Garlikowoo
Turning in Phoenix
Episode 10
I've sorted out the information you need.
Brother Yun, I have an idea.
A businessman from the mainland
suddenly came to Taiwan to join the gang.
It's a bit strange.
We need to be more natural
and be more careful.
Do you have a plan?
Brother Yun, don't mess with me.
According to your information,
Old Yu is used to his relationship with the gang
and is usually arrogant.
When I go to see him,
I just need to find some tea and change my file.
Then he'll think
I'm from the mainland and I don't have a backer.
He'll let the gang deal with him naturally.
Wait!
I'll go to the police station and sue you!
You're arrogant!
Go away!
Girl.
What?
Do you have cosmetics?
Yes.
Officer.
Report!
The report failed.
The average person is also arrogant.
I have to leave a impression
that I can't swallow.
And the witnesses
should come from the Five Lakes Alliance.
I'll cooperate with you then.
Here he is.
Come here.
Black Lotus Gang.
Brother,
I have a question.
Is there any other gang in Lin Anzhen?
There's also the Five Lakes Alliance.
I heard they've been recruiting people.
Five Lakes Alliance?
Young people
shouldn't be so arrogant.
The matter is settled.
Then we have to make things bigger.
But we can't be reluctant.
We have to be more natural.
For example,
if you happen to meet two younger brothers of Black Lotus Gang,
but you don't know that they are the Crown Prince,
and this Lin Ping He
goes to the same place every afternoon.
Are you going to beat him up?
If I can't do it,
I have to be more tough.
It's not enough to just know about Black Lotus Gang.
The Five Lakes Alliance also has to know.
It's best to spread the whole of Lin Anzhen.
ozone
You said that stance is less than 30 years old.
Don't you know that?
Pants, yellow, shorts and white shoes?
An accesory frame from Black Lotus Gang.
On the card that says it's a bananabrain.
You guys are both wearing fleece pants.
Let go!
Stay down!
I've changed recently.
Besides, I'm lucky.
Go inside, please.
Hurry up.
Please, I beg you.
I'll just hide and leave in a while.
Okay?
Please.
What?
You're a traitor.
Because of the accident of A'Pen and Wu,
the five-lake alliance is recruiting.
And you...
Just arrived at night.
The test of the five-lake alliance.
We're from the mainland.
Why are you afraid of the test?
Hi.
We met again.
God.
How dare you come here?
Don't talk like that.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm just afraid of you.
I'm afraid of you.
Don't talk like that, okay?
You're so fierce.
You're happy to see me.
I wish I could teach you a lesson.
You're so ungrateful.
You'll be ugly.
Thank you for your hard work.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm A'Pou, the leader of the five-lake alliance.
Thank you for your traditional and ideas.
And for your support.
Why does he sound like a tour guide?
The business of the five-lake alliance is the tourism industry.
Relax.
Don't be so nervous.
Get to know each other.
Relax.
First, please take off your clothes.
Take off our clothes?
Why?
Take off.
Okay.
Continue.
Do I have to take off everything?
I think so.
It's not real.
I'm a little embarrassed.
I'm done.
Can I marry you?
It's you.
I'm a poor boy.
I'm so embarrassed.
Next, we'll have the first test.
It's really a tour.
A whole snail.
How do you feel?
The traditional and the traditional.
It's one of the characteristics of the five-lake alliance.
Next, we'll take you to another project.
Is there anyone willing to try the first one?
You want to be the first one?
He wants to.
When did I...
You took off your clothes faster than you.
Are you not happy?
Give you a chance, right?
Come on, let's give him a round of applause.
Give him some encouragement.
Yeah.
You're the best.
Brother Dong Tian.
You're so generous.
We're friends.
Call me Brother Song.
Song.
What are you looking at?
Sit down.
You've been working so hard.
Let me do it.
Do you need to thank our owner in person?
Sure.
Can you tell which one is our owner?
Don't just look at it.
Talk to them.
No need.
They're not.
They're not?
You're the one.
Thank you.
This features 해
You can't just say it.
You don't have any sense of humor.
You hired him, right?
How can you tell?
There's no way.
I'm a natural.
You must have learned it somewhere.
You're a student of the school.
I'm a student of the physical education.
Physical education?
Do you still call it that?
No, it's just a sense of intuition.
It's very simple.
You can lie to people by talking.
People won't lie to people by their actions.
You can tell by observing them.
What did you learn in school?
Secret.
Chao, I'm sorry.
You've been eliminated.
I really can't do it.
It's okay, Chao.
If you can't do it, then next time.
If I can't do it next time, then next time.
Then next time.
Men are going to do it.
You're not going to do it.
I'm going to do it.
The world is changing.
You've tried your best.
There's nothing to regret.
What are you talking about?
I told you.
The five-tie alliance has rules.
Brothers can't fight.
I didn't fight.
We're not kids.
If you don't fight each other,
I can't do it.
Brother Xue, you mean
I can beat him now, right?
It's a good idea.
Brother Ming, Brother Shuang, you have to make a decision.
What do you mean?
Just pick one.
What's there to pick?
You're afraid of him, aren't you?
I'll tell you again.
Don't be afraid.
Be civilized.
I'll do whatever you want.
Don't mention my mom.
What do you want to do?
Come on.
Do you dare to bet?
Who loses today?
Tonight, let the other party
get up and climb out of this door.
Climb!
You're the best fighter in the Five Lakes Alliance.
You're going to fight against the two kings,
A Ming and Black Lotus.
You're going to fight against the two kings, A Ming and Black Lotus.
It's time to fight.
You can't be angry if you lose.
Come on, let's fight.
Pretend to pay for the game.
A Ming, face it.
It's expensive. Slow down.
I told you to fight.
I...
Don't be innocent.
Come on.
You're going to fight?
You're not going to hide?
I don't know how to hide.
You're very clever.
Don't come over.
Come on.
Don't hit me.
You're going to fight.
What the...
Do you know that?
Did the game end in a minute?
Are you sure?
You're shy, aren't you?
Get down.
I'm not kidding!
He's really a good player!
He's a good player!
He's so good!
Don't be so mean!
Xiu Pai!
You can't play like this!
Hey!
Ah!
Ming Ge!
Oh, shit!
Come on!
Ming, no matter what you say,
you have to break through!
How can you deal with it?
I'm sorry!
You're a real man!
From now on,
I won't play hard to get!
I want to be like you,
a real man!
Is it fair now?
Sure!
We'll fight to the end today!
Is this the star-like game between men?
It didn't count before.
From now on,
let's do it again!
Okay.
You don't believe me.
I can understand.
Then come on.
No.
I believe you this time.
Thank you for trusting me.
I'm very happy to fight with you.
Oh, my God!
What a touching scene!
The screen is getting bigger.
But don't get me wrong.
It's really a 100% real man's love!
But we're still rivals now.
Don't forget our bet.
You're right.
Don't be so serious when you're done.
I'll kill you!
The End
The end.
The battle at the local meeting finally has a result.
Brother Shuang used the despicable and despicable
to win the battle.
He always scolds me, Master Tang.
Just call me Brother Ah-qiu.
Brother Ah-qiu.
I'm a little confused now.
I'm smart and a little clever.
It's not a skill.
But you can cheat on the other person over and over again.
It's also a kind of wisdom.
Brother Ah-qiu has a taste.
Who?
Lu Qing!
Brother Ah-qiu!
Come and help me!
What are you doing?
Okay, let go.
What the hell are you talking about?
It's stimulating.
Xie Ying is still strong.
Brother Ah-qiu, stop pretending.
Get up.
What?
Let me introduce you.
This is our financial director, Brother Peng.
You recognized me as soon as I came in?
No.
I was also shocked when you first came in.
Then I saw you holding a gun for a long time and not shooting.
I felt very strange.
Then I took off your mask and I was sure.
Isn't this the big brother in my sauna room?
You're pretty smart.
So the sauna room is just a cushion.
The real test is in a dangerous situation.
Can you remember the previous appearance?
Right?
Brother Chuang, you're great.
Yingshuang, congratulations on joining the five-man alliance.
This is joining?
Ah-ming, I also welcome you to join the five-man alliance.
Me?
I...
Didn't I just lose?
Win or lose is a matter of common sense.
You can stand up when you're in danger.
You deserve the five-man alliance.
Brother Ming, I agree.
Not bad.
Brother Ming, I'm going to go to the bathroom.
I'll be back in a minute.
We were opponents just now.
We'll be brothers in the future.
Be more responsible.
You're so stubborn.
I said don't be so stubborn.
The End