Survivors
Does he dare to do that many people?
No.
Help me teach Uncle Han.
Now?
I have something to tell him.
Hurry up.
Okay.
I'll be right there.
I haven't come yet.
Uncle Han.
Brother He wants you to go.
Take care of him.
He.
So many people are waiting for you outside.
Tell me if you need anything.
Aren't you there?
Uncle Han.
Hi.
I'll be there right away.
Okay.
You're a man of your word.
Why are you so serious?
What are you talking about?
Tell me.
Actually, I've thought about it.
It's too dangerous to be a assistant.
This position...
doesn't have to be mine.
He.
You mean...
Uncle Han.
Why don't you be the assistant?
I...
I can do it.
We're family.
It's the same.
Ask me a condition.
Go ahead.
When I hug you,
I must hug you.
Of course.
But, He.
We need evidence to find the murderer.
We have to take our time.
Isn't it clear who the murderer is?
Tianhai Gate did it.
But there are so many people in Tianhai Gate.
It can't be the murderer.
Who did it?
Do we have to investigate it?
I'm not sure who did it.
But I've found the assistant.
Xia.
Tell me.
I can handle it.
You.
He.
You're kidding, right?
How could it be me?
What do you think?
Pan Tu.
He's here.
Let's go and check.
Be careful.
You.
I'll kill you.
You want to kill me?
Come on.
I'll kill you.
solo
XIN!
brotha
dero suitable
hide
de de da de de
da da de da
Fight!
Hi!
Go!
He's the first, but not the last!
I'll be back to be blind the day people beat me!
The last structure was taken down till now, right?
Yes.
Descendants of two Generally called Gods and Gods encountered in the case of Lin雪凌.
Now that you brought it up, why要走這條路?
Type it the same way, just similarly.
Let's go.
I'm going to see Bo Bo.
Do you know what fishing is?
What kind of fish?
It's a pity.
What is it?
If you want to fish, come here.
There's no fish here.
What do you mean?
You didn't watch the news?
Oh.
You mean the
city of the wild?
Fish?
I can't stand it.
People should be fine.
Tianhai Gate,
Daxia's coming,
high-end.
So that's why.
Yes.
I'll leave it to you.
Leave what to us?
The department approved it.
But the
change of the
rules.
It's troublesome.
There are people who don't know the rules.
Someone should come out and persuade them.
Like you to persuade Lin Yonglin?
According to your plan,
the future of this place
is different from now.
The old won't go, the new won't come.
If you five are willing to cooperate,
I'll help you.
What do you think?
What do you mean?
Why are you here today?
I'm sorry.
Business is not quick.
If you're not available today,
I can come tomorrow.
No need.
I'm available now.
Brother.
It's enough.
I'm sorry.
We don't want to
destroy the black-faced gang.
We just want the town
not to be too much disturbed by them.
So why are you saying
what you mean?
We are willing to help.
But there are conditions.
Is it?
What do you think?
That gun
is the gift I gave you.
What do you want in return?
Your father told you
what business
we were in?
Impossible.
I'm sorry.
Don't be so hasty.
Think about it.
Travel is the basic
of Lian'an town.
As you said,
we have to change our business
since the factory came.
Is it good?
The world is changing.
Changing a method
is not necessarily a bad thing.
We can't change the good.
Ask the people here.
As far as I know,
they
don't want to change.
We have some differences.
But it doesn't matter.
We are here to help.
Then I'll go first.
Goodbye.
Chen Tianshuang, right?
Am I that smart?
If you were the owner of the hall,
would you be so stubborn?
I can't
be your brother.
You said that
you would help me.
It's not hard to be a brother.
You are the brother
if you are gone.
Are you kidding me?
You have time to fish with me.
I'm sure of it.
You are not going to forgive me.
I'm going to be your brother.
How can you do that?
You should think it over.
Don't think that
you are the real brother
because of their brother.
So many people were there.
Only one person can help you.
The others are all the guests.
If you are good,
they will treat you as a brother.
If you are not good,
they will send you to Tianhai Gate.
What about you?
I'm your last life-saving straw.
You have no choice.
I have no choice.
Yes,
But you are the same.
You have no choice.
I have tried to help you.
But you don't know what you are doing.
No one can help you.
What can you do?
If you can do anything,
why are you hitting me?
So I am your last life-saving straw.
You can't only add price,
you have to lower the price.
You are crazy.
If you don't cooperate with me,
you will die when Tianhai Gate comes.
You will die.
Tianhai Gate.
I will do it.
Yes, I am crazy.
But you are not.
You can't beat me.
I can do anything.
Do you dare?
I got the news that
Jiajie is cooperating with Lin Pinghe.
So we have to act now.
What about Lin Pinghe?
Lin Pinghe has called Tianhai Gate.
Tell them to eliminate the murderer.
Otherwise, they will die.
Tianhai Gate hasn't responded yet.
Let them fight.
We just need to do something.
The fight and grudge in the gang
have nothing to do with us.
But if it involves Lin Anzhen,
it will be our fault.
What can Tianhai Gate do?
We saw Lin Yongning die in front of us.
Now Lin Pinghe has to act now.
I guess it won't be long before
the Black Lotus Gang is over.
Why do we have to be involved?
I always say
to protect Lin Anzhen.
To protect Lin Anzhen.
Actually, it's to protect
those I know and those I don't.
To be honest, I've been here for six years.
I care about them very much.
Do you understand what I mean?
You said so much.
You just want me to deal with Jiajie?
You finally heard it.
Say it.
How to act this play?
Very simple.
We have to cooperate.
We have to be careful.
What's the plan?
You told him the Five Lakes Alliance
would help him deal with the people around him.
But it's not convenient for people
to show up in public.
We need help.
We almost forgot the police.
I can help you with the next two steps.
But it's up to you
to gain his trust.
This is the hardest part.
When I saw you come back last time,
you were very excited.
It's a play.
So Jiajie is an old
playboy.
You have to do your best.
For Lin Anzhen's peace,
I have to sacrifice myself.
At least the shadow
still occupies the person.