Oops , I removed track as threshold
I heard you're going to the mall.
Are you so excited?
The people there are all the sugar-coated people.
Brother Xiu can't go.
He didn't ask anyone to pick you up.
What does that mean?
It means that you're his successor.
You're the one who came to the安政屋.
You just came for a long time.
You're super cool.
Why don't you react at all?
What reaction do you want?
I'm not going to the mall.
I'm not here.
You're the only one here.
What's the point of saying that?
You should be careful.
Don't offend anyone who shouldn't be offended.
Why are you so sentimental?
I need you to tell me.
Go home and see more.
Communicate with your dad.
Do you hear me?
Bullshit.
I have nothing to say to him.
Bullshit?
You can't even talk properly.
You're so cute.
Okay, okay.
I know.
Take care of yourself.
Help me clean up.
You can't fly anymore, right?
Do you think I'm feeding you
or did I find a pretty nurse to feed you?
What do you think?
Find me a prettier one.
Okay.
Brother Liu, thank you for taking care of me.
Why are you so sentimental?
You're not coming back?
What if?
There's no if.
I'm badly hurt this time.
Come back to me after you're done.
I mean,
what if I'm taken by the He family?
Why would I come to Anzhen?
I'll just go straight to heaven.
What if?
I've been thinking.
You're so close to Jiajie.
The world has changed.
You're a bad guy.
You can really eat goose meat.
Who's a bad guy?
Are you jealous of me?
I'm sure I'm jealous of you.
Yan Shuang,
be careful.
Wait for me.
Why are you back?
You're not going to say goodbye to my sister?
I'm not going.
I can't bear to leave.
I've sent her a message.
What did she say?
She didn't reply.
Look, she's angry.
I'll have to rely on you to comfort me.
Right?
Okay, I'm going in the car.
I'll talk to you later.
Why are you here?
You're rude to not say hello before you go out.
Why are you laughing?
I don't want to drink.
I'm sorry.
You're here to send me milk?
Yes.
I have to send it to someone else.
I'm leaving then.
Be careful on the road.
Okay.
Chief Zhang, Yingwu is in position.
The next step is the next one.
Okay, let's proceed.
Okay.
Chief Zhang.
Call me.
I'll just get it done.
Director Li.
Long time no see.
Huang Sixing.
Don't pretend to be happy in front of me.
You took the money from Haiji.
And were attacked by Li Li.
You're not going to get away with this.
You took the money from Haiji.
And were attacked by Li Li.
You think I don't know?
It's this face.
You never get angry.
Huang Sixing.
Do you think everyone will laugh at you?
Don't underestimate him.
He's very capable.
He laughs like this every day.
And he goes to lick the blood of the people above.
He's actually becoming a director step by step.
Director Li.
If you're not satisfied with me,
you can complain to me.
Complain to you?
If you want me to say,
you took the money from the black community.
I'm telling you today.
As long as I'm the director of the day,
you can't pass this project.
Then wait and see.
You bastard.
You can hit people.
He's too arrogant.
I gave him face, he didn't want it.
He wants to wait and see.
Director Huang, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Do you want to go to the hospital?
No, I have to pick up my daughter.
I'm too late.
Director Li is getting more and more out of control.
He usually scolds everywhere.
Now he dares to hit people.
I'll go back and complain to him.
Don't think too much.
Don't take it to heart.
You are too good-tempered
to be bullied.
It's okay. You go ahead.
Let's go.
How was it?
Did you like it?
I like it.
Okay.
Dad, can I eat fried chicken?
Fried chicken is a waste of food.
What about milk tea?
It's not healthy.
It's annoying.
Dad, I just got home from school.
I don't have to go all the way.
You said you were busy.
I have to go to school every day.
Because I like to be with Xixi.
Xixi, I'll call you back.
I'll be right there.
Yu Jie.
Yes, I need to get a temporary leave.
Please help me with it.
Dad, what order did you get?
I got a hand sanitizer.
I'll eat it next time.
Come on.
Cheers.
He's still pretending to be civilized.
He even said,
let's wait and see.
I slapped him.
I beat him up.
Good.
But he won't complain about you if you beat him up.
Complain about me?
He's not that brave.
You didn't see it.
I beat him up.
He climbed up from the ground.
He's full of blood.
He still laughs at me.
What is he?
He's a dog in my eyes.
A dog without a breath.
Let's see how I beat him up when we have a meeting tomorrow.
Okay.
Come on.
Let's drink.
Cheers.
Mom, I'm back.
Go in.
You'll be back soon.
Bye, dad.
Bye, Xixi.
Bye.
Come on.
Wash your hands.
You're not here this weekend?
Xixi's piano class this Saturday afternoon.
She's a new teacher.
See if it's suitable for her.
If it's not, then change it.
She has a great dance competition on Sunday.
Before the competition,
remind her not to care about winning or losing.
I promised her
to take her to a new restaurant.
I'll send you the address later.
I made it clear, right?
Do you want me to make you a note?
You've been too spoiled lately.
I can't even care about her.
I'm not spoiled.
I'm just being careful.
Do you think
you'll never leave me
if you don't care about me?
It's been so long.
Can you tell me now
why you're so wary
of your wife who grew up with you?
You don't want to tell me anything.
Why do you have so many secrets
in your heart?
You only tell me it's okay.
It's all in the past.
Yes, that's right.
I don't argue, I'm polite and gentle.
I think I'm the crazy one.
Even when I proposed to you,
you didn't even think of returning.
Keep your voice down.
Who will hear it?
Huang Zhi Xin.
You're a workaholic
and a good father.
But you know what?
You're the worst husband.
I'm sorry.
I've arranged
the cleaning.
Clean it.
I'm sorry.
The last one,
please vote for me
and keep your precious votes.
Thank you.
After the Wu Hong Alliance was established,
it became one of the earliest
sects in the southern part of Taiwan.
Since the late 90s,
the Wu Hong Alliance has been thriving.
It's almost the first sect in the southern part of Taiwan.
But the bigger the region,
the more trouble it has caused.
Fortunately, Yomi has become
the leader of the people.
But now he's retiring.
We'll see who will be
the successor of the Wu Hong Alliance.
Hello.
Welcome.
Long time no see.
Wait a minute.
Wow.
Brother Hai.
Brother Xiu has been talking about you.
Brother Qiang, long time no see.
Long time no see.
This one.
Mr. Gao is here.
Brother Qiang, you look good.
I'm good. I'm just as good as you.
Brother Hao.
Hello. Long time no see.
Where have you been?
Brother Hao.
Long time no see.
Brother Qiang.
I'm counting on you.
Brother Hao.
Brother Qiang, long time no see.
Okay, everyone sit.
It's okay to sit at home.
Brother Hao, you've grown up.
You've grown up.
Brother Mi.
Dad.
Sit.
I'm sorry.
It's been a long time since we've all been together.
It's been hard on you.
Yes.
Let me introduce you.
Today,
we have a guest.
The head of Tianhai Gate,
An Le.
An Le is waiting for you.