=Under the Sun=
=Episode 10=
Halo.
Yuze, it's me.
Ying Ying, why did you change your number?
My cell phone was lost,
I just changed to a new one.
Have you gotten off the fast train?
That's right, just dropped.
Uncle accompanied aunt
's toilet.
I'm guarding the suitcase.
Do you want to talk to them?
No need.
Surface.
There is something
what I want to convey to you.
You listen carefully.
What is it?
Like this...
Bos.
Correct.
The person is not in the office.
I took his cell phone from the drawer.
His cell phone was turned off.
Talk about it again after coming back.
OK, Boss.
Let's go.
Please pay 40 yuan.
I received 40 yuan.
The money is right, go ahead.
Thank You.
You're welcome.
Open the door!
Halo.
I'm right in front of their door.
The car is parked downstairs,
but there was no one in the house.
He had one student named Yu Chengbo.
Go to Nanzhou University,
and find this student.
Excuse me.
I came from out of town
to settle matters.
My identity was lost on the road,
can I stay here?
Do you remember your personal identification number?
I don't remember.
Wait a minute.
This is my teacher's identity,
I am a teacher at Nanzhou University.
Can this be used?
Can,
but can't make a receipt.
It doesn't matter, the important thing is that you can stay overnight.
Excuse me.
Over there.
Thank You.
Yu Chengbo,
Your lecturer is looking for you
under.
Okay.
(I offended very scary people.)
(Judging from the current situation, you might be involved. For your safety,)
(Tomorrow take permission and hide for a few days in your hometown.)
(Yes, Mrs. Ke.)
(Yu Chengbo)
Hello, what's wrong?
Miss Lecturer Ke.
Open the door.
Miss Lecturer Ke,
you really gave me a surprise.
Di... di mana Yu Chengbo?
What did you do to him?
What can I do to him?
He... he's just a student,
has nothing to do with this issue.
I...
I shouldn't have involved him.
He didn't know anything.
Really, let him go, will you?
If there's anything, just take it out on me,
let him go, okay?
Very clever,
exactly the same, yes.
Mrs. Ke, you are the first person
who dares to play tricks in front of me.
You came to the provincial capital for this?
Still want to report to the police?
No wonder you stay here.
The identity checks aren't strict, right?
It's like you want to play with me for life!
You came alone to deliver the letter,
still planning to report directly, huh?
Ke Ying,
You're also reckless, aren't you?
Honest,
your father, mother, and Yang Yuze,
where are you now?
I still haven't found it.
They don't stay overnight at all
at the booked hotel.
I've arranged everything.
You can't possibly find them.
Shen Shijie,
don't move
What do you want to do?
Are you sure this could electrocute me to death?
As long as you die,
I can just stop playing this crazy game of yours.
My family and friends
new there will be no problems.
What about Yu Chengbo?
You forget it very quickly.
Please!
I told you,
he has nothing to do
with this problem.
He rented a car for you,
buy you a cell phone,
this is already related to this problem!
If I die,
he must accompany me to die.
Shen Shijie,
you will go to hell.
Please!
You are too childish.
I just came back
from hell, you know, right?
I knew you would run.
However, I really didn't expect it,
you have guts
pulling me to death together.
Good,
we die together
Go to hell together.
Look, you're the one who's scared or I'm the one who's scared!
Let go, let him go.
Remember!
Your life is mine.
I didn't tell you to die,
you can't die!
You have to live well
in my hell.
Got it, right?
- Beat it until it dies. - Hit it to death!
(Nanzhou University; University Entry Directions)
(Mrs. Ke, don't look for me; Yu Chengbo)
(surface)
Halo.
Ying Ying.
How are you doing there?
Uncle and aunt were starting to get suspicious.
I can't lie to them anymore.
Ying Ying, did you hear?
Tell me, where are you now?
I'll look for you soon.
No need,
I am alright
I...
just returned from the provincial capital.
I've confirmed it,
Feng Xiaosheng dan Shen Shijie
there is no relationship whatsoever.
Previously it was just a misunderstanding.
I might...
suffered from temporary mental problems.
I'm going to see Doctor Tong.
Just calm down,
it's definitely okay,
I'll be home soon.
Good,
I'm waiting for you at home.
See you soon.
Don't look for me?
Only I know you are Shen Shijie.
Officer Chen probably already knows too.
So, you killed him.
Correct,
initially he didn't have to die.
You're the one who got him involved.
You didn't kill me,
not just to torture me.
Is there any other reason?
By killing me,
then no one knows
that you are Shen Shijie.
Shen Shijie
will be completely destroyed from this world.
Like a pile of mud.
Dry in the sun, it crumbles to dust.
Don't know where it will be swept away.
Maybe someone else knows too
your secret.
However, those people were impatient
erasing all traces of you being Shen Shijie.
They are very hopeful
you completely
menjadi Feng Xiaosheng.
You don't accept it.
Do not accept
live in this world
with other people's faces.
Even if you live prosperously,
but it's not your own life.
When you're new
changed identity to Feng Xiaosheng,
a criminal dares to die,
suddenly turned into a social elite,
powerful people.
You should also be proud,
ever happy,
but now you're not anymore.
Because...
you're just someone else's replacement,
a shadow,
a doll.
Minimize interacting with people
which is strange.
Don't forget your identity.
So, you need...
need one person to see you.
Seeing this successful person,
respected people these people.
Asking this person to prove...
in fact he is Shen Shijie.
What you said is right.
Indeed so.
Also you are the only one who still remembers Shen Shijie.
Correct.
Only I remember Shen Shijie.
So, how could he let me go.
The game will still continue,
I like this kind of beginning.
This life is very bleak,
So, you have to find fun for yourself.
True, or not?
Collect all the money I've spent in the past few years
to everyone.
I have an urgent need.
This money is very important to me.
My family's lives
is in here.
Look for friends you can rely on,
after the business is finished
You guys find a place to hide first.
Wait for the rumors to pass, then come back.
Just calm down,
I will not harm you.
Jie, you hide first,
wait until the rumors have passed, then come back.
Just listen to what your Second Uncle says.
Dao Jian.
You know clearly
where are Jie's places, right?
Of.
Watch closely.
Understand.
Later,
His territory will be yours.
Thank you, Second Uncle.
Kak Qiang.
Sis Wu.
You have now climbed to a high branch, yes.
In your eyes you no longer look at us,
your friends are downstairs, right?
Look at your character.
Am I that kind of person?
Follow people like Dao Jian,
sleep should not be too sleepy.
Don't wake up as soon as you wake up,
there are several body parts missing.
Kak Qiang.
These days, I don't follow Dao Jian,
Dao Jian menyuruhku ikut dengan Feng Xiaosheng.
Really?
Really.
What kind of tactic is this?
I... I'm confused too.
Maybe that day was a coincidence,
coincidental meeting.
Mr Feng told me to drive for him.
You're great too, kid.
The feet of this Money God alone
you can hug.
Nope.
Isn't he just second uncle's nephew?
What is great?
Second uncle,
Mr. Feng,
and Big Boss Feng in comparison,
it's the same as...
Anyway, the difference is very big.
Wu,
follow them well.
Maybe later Kak Qiang
still have to depend on you.
Don't, don't do that, Kak Qiang.
Don't talk like that.
I can't bear it.
Against you, against second uncle,
I will definitely be loyal,
it is impossible to betray.
Put a thousand.
Open it, okay?
This time open the big one.
Mr Bie, it's time.
Just that much,
no longer.
I tell you Mr Bie,
today I just moved money.
In nominal terms, you can just talk to second uncle.
(General Manager's Office)
Kak Qiang.
Be careful on the road, Sister Qiang.
Be careful on the way.
Paman Quan,
You're always very healthy, aren't you?
You...
bring a message to Meng.
Say.
My debt is paid off,
this is the last one.
Don't worry, I'll definitely tell you.
Take care, Uncle Quan.
How do you drive this?
Not so, Sister Qiang.
I was nervous when I saw those posts.
Whofire
you're so cowardly!
You're great, you're great.
Everyone shut up.
This is a big thing,
everyone be a little careful.
Kak Qiang,
what happened today?
We used to too
didn't spend that much money, right?
Have a second uncle,
I don't know why either
rush to get it back.
Second uncle also gave loans?
Ask less questions, live longer.
Okay.
Lately, they have been frequent
appeared in these places.
Every time
definitely bring a big bag,
copper.
There must be money in it.
Look, they're all nervous.
After putting the items in,
they started going around in circles
in the alley.
I was afraid of making them wary, after that I didn't follow them again.
Kapten Xiao,
next we...
Today got here first,
I still have business to go out for a while.
You archive it
these photos.
You guys have worked hard.
- Okay. - Okay.
All cash?
Not just cash,
there is gold too.
Then, where does the money go?
finally brought?
Dao Jian.
Dao Jian brought people
then take it.
Listen to what You Qiang said,
this is the money that second uncle spent.
Lately, he had been in a hurry to want her back.
He said there was an urgent need.
Here.
Okay.
When you come home, be a little careful.
Kapten Xiao, Kapten Xiao, Kapten Xiao.
What is it?
That...
next time when we meet
can you change places?
Why?
This place,
if seen by someone you know,
maybe it will be misunderstood.
This is for your security.
Next time, when we meet again,
call the receptionist directly,
give me your name then we'll talk directly.
Cape... Kapten Xiao.
Why else?
Try to see if it's possible or not,
I will remember this little door,
next time I will enter from this small door,
entering like this is also no problem, right?
You can, right?
Can't.
Why?
You still have to
entered from the front door mysteriously.
On what basis?
This is for your security.
Security?
Are you ready to go?
See you soon.
Bring this medicine.
Thank You.
(Male Reproductive Specialist)
Kapten Xiao.
This is a number plate
the goods car.
Check it immediately.
Especially you should pay attention to the alleys and fishing villages.
Captain Xiao, are you...
suspect they will
take the cash out?
Bring cash?
What era is it now?
Where possible to use
the old fashioned way
and risky like that?
The investigative team is already monitoring it
Feng family account.
Feng Meng wants to move large amounts of money,
but you can't go through the bank.
So, can only go back to the old way.
Find this car, keep a close eye on it.
Don't let them
take this money out.
Good.
Please come in.
This is your house?
That's right, please sit anywhere.
Here is hidden
a large crime family.
Investigate them,
means there will be risks
lose your life at any time.
Apart from that, there is still a terrible reality
what you have to face.
Did you forget
words I've said before?
This problem
I have to investigate until it's clear.
Good.
If you want to investigate the Feng family,
must start from the history of development
the two Feng family brothers.
Feng Meng.
Known as second uncle.
Haven't graduated from middle school yet,
has started to start a restaurant, recording studio,
karaoke,
and game studios.
Employ a group of subordinates
to keep an eye on the places.
Soon after,
he became a famous boss in his world.
Feng Yong.
Namely Big Boss Feng.
When young,
used to be a sports teacher.
The era of reform he led clashed
and have hurt other people.
1993,
starting a sand mine
and stone quarries.
In a short time,
he monopolizes
sand mines all over the city,
its assets amount to hundreds of millions of yuan.
When he already has capital,
his relationship with several offices
getting closer every day.
The Feng brothers' four business establishments and two mines,
is a traditional black business.
Using violence, accumulating wealth.
After that, it started to change.
Feng Yong holds both business and politics.
From the outside it looks clean,
at the same time also in control of the casino,
bars and high interest loans.
This situation
continues until...
Feng Xiaosheng took over the Feng Group.
Feng Xiaosheng?
I know him.
I once interviewed him.
He has his own understanding
on the economy and investment.
He is a very smart businessman.
Correct.
With connections and relationships
that Big Boss Feng had.
Coupled with Feng Xiaosheng's economic brain.
Feng family assets
increased more than tens of times.
In the country continue to give loans,
abroad continue to buy.
Spending billions of euros
to purchase the entire German new energy production process.
Then, spend tens of billions
to buy mines in South Africa, Brazil and Europe.
Most of the Feng family's property
flowing abroad.
Then, through various paths
collected into a personal account
Feng Xiaosheng di Swiss.
Are you the one investigating all this?
Not me.
My teacher.
They destroyed all their criminal evidence.
Meanwhile my teacher,
his career also ended then and there,
one leg is also paralyzed.
Since my teacher was hit by an accident,
no one dared to investigate them anymore.
Mr. Feng, you're okay, right?
Let go.
Don't play dead.
Mr. Feng,
I'm just your training companion,
You are too cruel.
This should count as a work injury, yes.
Give me more medical money.
You also have to treat me to a delicious meal to restore me.
Mr. Feng,
my blind attack earlier
Not bad, right?
Reasonable.
Your kick is also not bad.
Add another portion of bacon.
Please.
This guy looks a little familiar.
♪I'm sure, this time is a long journey with no return♪
♪Trying to listen to your faint warning♪
♪No problem, dilemma♪
♪Never believe in fate♪
♪Close your eyes Seeking inner peace♪
♪Can't cry, But have to laugh♪
♪Adrift between the Borders of good and evil♪
♪How many times have you woken up from a dream that contains you♪
♪Repeatedly convince yourself that you have to be strong♪
♪How much courage does it take♪
♪To change a little light♪
♪Don't ask about tomorrow♪
♪No regrets No revenge♪
♪How much courage does it take♪
♪To change a little light♪
♪Don't ask about forever♪
♪Menjaga di sisimu♪