=Under the Sun=
=Episode 5=
Two, three, four.
- Shake your hips. - Why are you so stiff?
You taught him.
Two, three.
Walk in style, shake your hips.
(Weizhen Temple) What is that?
One two.
Stylish.
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry.
Wu,
Why are you so unpunctual?
Did you secretly take orders
and deliver food again?
No, no, no.
Sis, I fell asleep.
Morning, Sis Qiang.
Our time is all very valuable.
I was wrong, Sis.
I'll change it.
What's this?
His cell phone rang again.
Do you want to take orders
and continue delivering food again?
No, no, no.
Message from group.
Your glasses are so worn out,
just let it go.
You still love me, huh?
Stop it.
Every day you are the one with the most problems.
Hurry up.
None of your business.
Go first.
Next time don't be late again.
Ready, Sis.
At the gambling place
there are bound to be people who win and lose,
In gambling places there are good and bad.
There are all kinds of people.
For this reason, we must be flexible in socializing,
treating people based on their status.
Knowledge here
a huge amount.
Fast!
Hurry, hurry!
The point is that this is difficult to explain.
This is our field
not black,
not white either,
but grey.
No need to fight and kill.
Safer than others.
Even if you get caught,
there won't be any big problems either.
However,
money must be saved.
So, the most important position is
the person who looks after the money.
As a person who looks after money,
you don't need to be able to fight and kill,
but your brain must be fast,
true, right?
Your legs also have to be able to run fast.
Plan a little!
Just by running fast,
can just take the money out,
then you can do your job well.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Fast!
Can't run anymore.
Twenty.
Had reached.
Kak Qiang,
I can't run anymore.
Each of you is one round short.
Quick, quick, quick.
Don't bullshit.
- Fast! - I I...
Enthusiasm.
This month it's your turn.
The bosses are all here.
You Qiang,
quickly add money for Mr. Xu.
I see it's almost finished.
Mr. Xu, how much do you want?
Just tell me the numbers.
Come on, quickly.
Add 10 for Mr. Xu.
Who chose this run-down place?
Next time you come here, don't look for me.
The feng shui is very bad.
What a shame.
My older brother,
this is just starting.
This... this is just a small problem like a hair on your body.
Fine, give me 300 thousand.
I'll let you pluck a feather.
Which one you want to remove is up to you.
You see.
If so, how dare I?
Come on, come on.
Stop it.
West wind. [*Mahyong pieces]
Eight bamboos. [*Mahjong pieces]
Did I tell you to daydream?
Dao Jian,
You've scared this kid.
If you're looking for death,
don't bring anyone else, okay?
You're afraid Dao Jian won't recognize it's you, huh?
Kak Qiang,
he kills... kills people.
Even though he killed your ancestors,
You also have to pretend as if nothing is wrong.
If you have the guts,
go in and kill him right now.
If you don't have the guts,
then pretend not to know anything.
Understand?
Wu, do you have to be this scared?
You just accidentally passed by and happened to catch a glimpse of him.
You also didn't kill that person.
Kak Qiang,
I think I... I don't really fit in
is in this field.
Let me go, will you?
I can go back and do whatever else.
I want to go deliver food.
Nonsense!
Wu.
Listen to me.
It's not that I don't want to let you go,
but if you leave now,
tomorrow someone will cut you off with a knife.
You believe it, don't you?
You just haven't told Dao Jian directly
that you saw him kill people.
Could it be that he let you go?
Listen to the words of Sister,
can't go
You can't go either.
Today my hands are really unlucky!
Today his luck is very good.
Not bad, not bad.
This brother in front is terrible.
Go first.
- Come again, yes. - Come again.
Be careful on the way.
Qiang.
Wu's background is peaceful, right?
It should be safe.
However, I don't know whether he was telling the truth or not.
Fine, lend me use it for a moment.
I'll be honest with you,
I was also asked by someone.
Don't let second uncle find out.
Lately it's not a lack of people,
lend me a moment.
Wu.
Brother Qiang, what's wrong?
I'm telling you, yeah.
Brother Dao Jian has been short of people recently.
You go help him for a few days.
Good.
Excited to the point of being stupid, huh?
I'll tell you, yeah.
You have to be more agile when working with the boss.
Work more, talk less.
If you dare trouble the boss,
I will skin you.
Kak Dao Jian.
Never mind, drive the car.
Liangzi, give him the car keys.
OK, Boss.
I'll just thank you later.
Miao Miao.
Sis.
Is there anything I need to do?
I've...already sorted everything out.
Sis.
My father is...
It's not just an ordinary car accident, right?
He must have offended someone
because investigating the case...
that's why he was killed.
Miao Miao, don't think carelessly.
Study well.
We will always be there for you.
Turn around, repeat.
Stop.
How far is this CCTV from the newsstand?
About 60 meters.
This is the only CCTV around here.
Installed by the owner of a shop.
Judging from this person's walking speed,
when he got to the pay phone
around the same time Inspector Chen received the call.
If it comes from this direction,
then there is only him.
Kapten Xiao.
If...
Looking for you.
Let's talk about it later.
Halo.
Who are you?
You said you witnessed it live?
Don't rush, say it slowly.
What really happened?
Itu Zhang Zhigao, Dao Jian.
He was the one who killed Officer Chen.
I can't tell you my identity.
However, it really was him.
What I said was very accurate.
Clicks enough investigating Dao Jian.
That time he was driving
a black car.
Dao Jian.
You guys investigate Dao Jian.
Zhang Zhigao.
Call from where?
Small stall on Huarong Street.
Call back.
Halo.
Who's calling?
Little boy!
Why are you running?
Hello. As soon as I called him he immediately ran.
What does he look like?
Wearing a hat
and masks.
His face was not clear.
His body is not short.
You're welcome, you're welcome.
Song Jingzhong.
- Hadir. - Xing Wei.
Di mana Xing Wei?
Xing Wei menemani Miao Miao.
Call him back.
Good.
You two monitor Zhang Zhigao.
Zhang Peng.
You go to Huarong Street.
Look around this shop
is there CCTV or not.
Then, around there,
pull all the recordings.
Good.
There's a task.
Miao Miao.
Kak Zhong.
Sis, you just work first.
Then be careful yourself, okay?
If there's a problem, call me, okay?
What is the problem? It's such a rush.
Accident problem.
Captain Xiao told us to monitor Dao Jian.
Was he the one who hit it?
Lower your voice.
Paman Xiao.
Miao Miao.
Have you finished cleaning up your father's things?
Do I need to send someone to take you home?
My father...
was he killed?
Who did you hear from?
You don't need to know who I heard from.
You just say it, is it true or not?
Was he killed by someone named Dao Jian?
Miao Miao,
you shouldn't be dealing with this.
Listen to me, go home.
Take good care of grandma.
Hello, Bureau Chief Liu.
I'm in the office.
OK, I'll be right there.
It's just right that I wanted to look for you to report this.
OK, I'll hang up the phone first.
Paman Xiao.
Listen to me, come home quickly.
Paman Xiao!
Boss, are you looking for me?
There are your men who kill the police.
Come back
and look for this person for me.
Kill the police?
Who killed?
Killing who?
Could it be Chen Jinyan?
That's not possible.
They don't have that guts.
Have guts or not,
Basically it's been done.
You investigate carefully.
Especially people
related to Shen Shijie.
Once you know who did it,
immediately told him to disappear.
Why is this linked to Shen Shijie again?
Wasn't he clearly dead long ago?
Do your research.
Take off and throw away the necklace on your neck.
This... this has been blessed by the monk.
That's to chain the dog.
Come on, Boss, let's have a toast.
Come on, Boss.
I toast you.
Come on, boss.
You eat too.
Don't just stay silent.
I'll keep getting it, come on.
(Mysterious Person)
Come on, come on, come on.
Then, I'll get some shrimp for you.
Okay.
Come on, come on, come on.
Everyone drank happily.
Drink happily, yes.
Halo.
Fine, fine, fine. Now do it straight away.
Eat a lot, yes.
Spend, spend, spend.
Spend, spend, I spend.
Caring for goldfish, huh?
How?
Spend, spend.
You, come with me.
The boss chose you.
Serve the boss well.
Irritating.
Nice, no?
Great, try it.
OK, the fitting room is here.
Please.
How?
That's all.
It doesn't matter.
Remembering some truths,
then began to reflect again on the meaning of life.
Finally realized
My own work is not finished.
People always think very deeply,
but the last will be restrained
by his own thoughts.
Restrained.
Chains, locks, handcuffs.
No need to stick to the literal meaning.
Translate to Chinese.
If said in Mandarin,
confined by his own thoughts.
Appropriate.
Hey, it's you,
let him rest for a while.
Come on, eat an orange.
Thank you, Auntie.
TO,
look how messy this kitchen is.
Young people today
can't do anything.
If there is no helper and food delivery,
I think I will definitely die of starvation.
Your aunt really likes to nag.
Just let him be.
Have you finished showering?
Where are your dirty clothes?
It's been thrown in the washing machine.
Why do you always
throw everything in the washing machine?
It is not machine washable.
Must be washed by hand.
Mother.
That's it.
I told you that the one who washes is also not clean.
Just me.
Bibi.
No need, no need.
You sit down quickly.
It'll be over in a moment.
Easy thing.
Mother,
Don't just come to my place and look for work.
I've hired a maid.
Hiring helpers?
The maid's job is to clean the house.
How nice would it be to tell him to wash it by hand?
Ying Ying.
Ying Ying,
Don't be annoyed because of your mother's nagging.
If you're his age,
I don't think you'll be any better than him.
Package.
Mine?
Please sign.
(Recipient; Miss Lecturer Ke)
(Sender; Feng)
Buy what?
Recipient, Mrs. Lecturer?
Surprise, secret.
What the hell? Very mysterious.
Halo.
Hello, I want to look for Mrs. Lecturer Ke.
What is it?
Telephone.
Hello, who is this?
Don't like the gift I gave?
Pak Chen, ya?
What business do you have to look for me?
Don't like the model
or the color?
How about I exchange it for you?
Mr. Feng,
today my parents are at my house.
I beg you...
Your pajamas are adorable.
Ying Ying, let me help you dry your hair.
What are you looking for?
What's wrong with him?
Bos.
What you sent is...
Your job is
brought a car to pick up and pick up this woman.
Understand.
Take care, yes.
Watch your mouth well,
don't talk much nonsense.
Good.
Make sure he changes his clothes into this.
Students,
today we will discuss about
America's tax rate reduction
in early 2018
and the trade war that started
in March 2018.
An increase in interest rates,
reducing tax rates and reducing balance sheets.
We can call it as
three pillars of American economic policy.
Keep raising interest rates
is the most powerful tool for
burst the property price bubble.
The effect
just like solving the problem from the root.
balance sheet decline,
in fact the effect is similar to
increase in interest rates.
In China,
the most direct impact is property prices.
A reduction in tax rates will instead
pressure the yuan to fall.
OK, now the problem arises.
What should we do?
It should lower property prices.
That's right, it should reduce property prices.
If property prices continue to rise,
it will lead to yuan depreciation,
there will be more funds flowing out.
Guaranteeing large-scale foreign loans in 2005-2006
divert funds,
causing the stock market to fall and the exchange rate to drop,
the consequences are fatal.
The government will definitely do more
control foreign investment.
To be more precise, it is
the government controls more tightly
investment in foreign assets
which is not supported by the state.
Actually, talking about anything is useless.
In the 80s,
US president, Reagan, lowered tax rates significantly.
It makes the Japanese economy
so go back 20 years,
even made the Soviet Union break up.
So, this time Trump lowered tax rates,
(Exit) the most affected
still us.
- Correct. - Correct
(Exit)
(Quick)
Good.
Then this question
will be
today's class quiz.
- Seriously. - Seriously.
Next, you guys
express your own views.
The number of words is not less than 2000.
After class, gather at Yu Chengbo,
then, take it to my office.
Everyone get started.
Here.
How to write it?
Teach me.
Can't.
I have urgent business, I have to go out.
You help me maintain class order.
Do you need help?
(If you don't fight, it won't hurt.)
No need, thanks.
Halo.
The item is in the bag.
Try opening it and taking a look.
You should already know what to do, right?
I'm still in the car.
Move the car over.
You're down.
Take off the jacket.
I want you to take off the jacket.
Well, call the person in.
Fine.
What about this girl?
He wakes up before 07:00.
(Read and Answer)
Then wash your hands and face quickly.
He arrived at school early.
Arrive soon.
These have been carefully selected for you.
You will definitely be satisfied.
Bos.
Good.
Mr. Zhang.
Come on, come in.
Halo, Rade, River.
(No Entry)
He didn't ask me to do any secret tasks.
The point is to pick up and pick up a girl.
Wu,
do you know who Dao Jian killed that day?
Don't know.
Who?
Police.
Deputy captain of the Criminal Police Team.
Dao Jian rupanya
colluding with the police.
I wonder who betrayed Sis Jie?
apparently that's him.
Wu, you're still listening, aren't you?
Ya, Kak Qiang.
I'm telling you,
Dao Jian called you there
because I want to test you.
He must still suspect that
You saw him kill the cop.
Got it, right?
Don't let that kid
even come back to bite us later.
Understand?
I already know.
Stay cool.
Sis, that's...
I'm menstruating,
I want to relax for a while.
Please don't tell anyone.
Thank you, Sis.
(No entry)
Boss, what's wrong?
Got a problem?
Weren't you asked to stand guard at the door?
Where did you run off to?
Boss, I have a stomach ache.
I went to the toilet.
Take the girl away.
What do you guys see?
Work!
That...
you're fine, right?
Go away.
Be careful.
Miss Ke. Miss Ke.
(Emergency Installation)
Dokter Zhang, ya?
How is he now?
Now this...
the patient was hit in the head,
chest, back, hands and feet.
There was a lot of bleeding all over his body.
Apart from that, during the inspection,
The patient is still vomiting blood
and dizzy.
Now it's still not certain
head injury,
or on internal organs.
Patients need to be hospitalized for observation for some time.
What is your relationship with the patient?
We are good friends.
How could he be injured?
He was robbed.
Have you reported the police?
♪I'm sure, this time is a long journey with no return♪
♪Trying to listen to your faint warning♪
♪No problem, dilemma♪
♪Never believe in fate♪
♪Close your eyes Seeking inner peace♪
♪Can't cry, But have to laugh♪s
♪Adrift between the Borders of good and evil♪
♪How many times have you woken up from a dream that contains you♪
♪Repeatedly convince yourself that you have to be strong♪
♪How much courage does it take♪
♪To change a little light♪
♪Don't ask about tomorrow♪
♪No regrets No revenge♪
♪How much courage does it take♪
♪To change a little light♪
♪Don't ask about forever♪
♪Menjaga di sisimu♪