=Under the Sun=
=Episode 31=
(Emergency Installation)
Grandma Chen
It is okay, right?
His mood just stabilized,
already asleep.
Does Ke Ying already know your identity?
Maybe you've already guessed a bit.
Today's problem
it's really confusing.
What did Miao Miao say?
What could he say?
He said he worked at the club,
don't know anything other than that.
this child,
makes me so angry I want to hit him!
Really good at making trouble!
That's it.
Who told Ke Ying?
People named Yu Chengbo,
teman Miao Miao,
is also a student in Ke Ying's class.
He couldn't contact Miao Miao,
then heard Feng Xiaosheng take Miao Miao away,
so panicked, he immediately contacted Ke Ying.
Halo.
Fine, I understand.
Ke Ying had returned to her house.
Judging from today's situation,
Ke Ying will be in danger.
You guys should send someone to protect him.
Don't worry, I'll arrange it.
Good.
Don't just intervene.
Today something so unlucky happened,
perhaps Feng Xiaosheng will also suspect you.
You should be more careful.
Besides that,
You don't need to worry too much about Ke Ying.
Currently Feng Xiaosheng
still didn't dare to do anything to Ke Ying.
Good.
Chairman of the Board of Directors.
This is the schedule for the next three days.
There were some clashes at times,
We have tried to coordinate.
Chairman of the Board of Directors, the coffee is ready.
There are still some special adjustments
which you have to decide for yourself.
Charity banquet tomorrow night,
the invitation was sent a month ago,
and continue to wait for your reply.
Just take this cup of coffee with you.
He's been on business lately, won't come.
The one surnamed Ke has brought the police
looking up to the club.
Interesting.
We haven't had time to do anything here yet,
they themselves were apparently divided.
It's like, God
still on our side.
How is he worthy of fighting you?
The difference is huge.
However, people who...
principled must take revenge,
he just let the woman go?
Meanwhile there has been no action taken.
Anyway, just reported it to the police.
That shouldn't be the case either.
Oh yes.
That person,
these two days,
quite close to Deputy Mayor Lian's daughter.
They really are
are you attracted to each other?
Nope
deliberately made for us to see, right?
Nope.
This matter was arranged very thoroughly.
Lian Lian was certain
it was done by his enemy.
Will not associate it with us.
Then, what about Ke Ying?
How was the response?
Strange.
He had no response at all,
don't even go to the company anymore,
have returned to work on campus.
Mr. Feng,
just had acupuncture,
Qi and blood are not yet stable,
Don't get too emotional, okay?
Fine.
Not emotional.
You are careful, yes.
Chairman of the Board of Directors.
According to you, is it necessary?
did something to that person surnamed Ke?
interview script,
I've handed it over to Secretary An.
I hope you can check it out
in the midst of your busyness.
So that no errors occur,
then said that I cheated you.
Heaven knows.
I just admire you,
there is no prejudice whatsoever.
Good.
Contact me anytime if there is a problem.
Really serious?
Until you forget the time.
Pretending not to be familiar with me.
That's enough, okay?
No need to think of ways to fool me anymore.
I've found out everything.
What do you already know?
Already know that
the relationship between you and Feng Xiaosheng is fake.
You don't love him at all.
You are forced by his power,
have no other choice,
So, surrender and submit to it.
That is it?
If not?
Lian Lian,
I've told you many times,
stay away from the Feng Group,
jauhi Feng Xiaosheng,
but you won't listen to me.
You insist on intervening,
will not be deterred before it is too late.
Because like this,
I will satisfy your curiosity.
Today I will tell you everything.
Correct.
Feng Xiaosheng and I are fake.
I don't love him at all.
I really hate it.
I really want to kill him.
Do you want to know why?
Because he is Shen Shijie.
Around March this year,
the robber who almost killed me,
Shen Shijie.
If that's true,
Why did you keep holding it in until now and only then tell me?
Why?
I don't believe it.
If that's true,
why don't you ask the police for help?
What are you really thinking?
You consider yourself
as a princess who was struck by disaster,
Want revenge yourself?
Or you have a conspiracy theory
and suspect the police?
Or
you have Stockholm syndrome,
You fell in love with the robber who almost killed you?
Actually, what is the reason?
Tell me.
Actually because of what?
Because I can't afford even the slightest risk.
Never mind my parents,
or Yang Yuze.
It can't be because of me,
let them get hurt or face danger again
the slightest bit,
even though the danger is just a threat.
I trust the police.
I believed them in the end
can definitely try Shen Shijie according to the law.
However, they need time to investigate cases.
There are still many limitations.
This time is really too long for me.
I'm scared,
So, I can't wait.
Shen Shijie is a madman,
as long as he is alive,
you don't know at all
what days and when he will do crazy things.
To my parents,
to Yang Yuze,
to my students,
to yourself...
I have no other choice.
What I can do...
just surrender myself,
mengacaukan Shen Shijie,
trick him,
paralyze him,
until finally I got conclusive proof.
Totally made him...
and others are tried according to law.
There really is too much going on here.
Maybe in a short time,
I can't tell you clearly.
Maybe I'm too paranoid,
It is my fault.
However, now I can only do
what do I think I should do.
When the time is right,
I will of course ask the police for help,
but now...
I just hope...
You can leave this troubled place.
A fugitive who has been declared dead,
changed his face to become the chairman of the Feng Group.
Journalist Lian,
Do you believe stories like this?
However, he already thought like this,
always wanting to expose my cover,
and sent me to prison.
Ridiculous, right?
What's even more ridiculous is
I've even fallen in love with him,
and is very obsessed with him.
So, you don't hesitate to use your own power
to make him leave Yang Yuze,
and stay by your side.
Actually,
I look more like a lunatic than Ke Ying, right?
It's about to start.
Come on, let's go down.
Audience,
Welcome to the charity appreciation dinner.
Sapphire, also known as the stone of destiny.
This symbolizes
loyalty,
purity,
honesty,
and hope.
Besides that,
also symbolizes love that will not fade.
This auction product
comes from a private collection in this city.
It consists of
12 pieces totaling 37.6 carats
Kashmir...
What about the necklace?
Like it, no?
Combined with 498 pieces...
I don't really understand.
The most important thing is
I can't afford it either.
The best products in jewelry.
The only request
the owner of this necklace to us is
to donate all proceeds from the auction
to the Nanzhou City Children's Orphanage.
Next, let's welcome,
who bid this sapphire necklace for 10 million,
Chairman of the Board of Directors of the Feng Group,
Tuan Feng Xiaosheng,
to give a speech on stage.
Thank you to all of you.
Donate this money to a children's orphanage,
I hope it can help the kids
left by their parents.
so that apart from food and clothing,
they can be like us too,
can chase their dreams,
and make their dreams come true.
Thank You.
I want to take advantage of this opportunity,
to give this necklace to a journalist who
Honest,
brave,
and fight on the front lines without fear.
Coincidentally he is also here today.
She is Miss Lian Lian.
I can't accept this necklace.
So many people are watching,
give me face.
Very beautiful.
(Feng Xiaosheng Bought a 10 million Necklace for His Fiancé's Best Friend)
(Sorry,)
(the number you dialed is currently inactive.)
It doesn't matter.
medical history,
and a diagnosis certificate has been obtained.
(Diagnosis Certificate)
(Treatment History)
Nice work.
What...
will this work?
Anyway have to try it.
So...
then I...
You go with me.
Thank you, Deputy Mayor Lian.
Get back to work.
Good.
Isn't this pretty good?
Don't you always say that women are unreliable?
So, I replaced it.
It should be according to your wishes.
Haphazard.
She is the daughter of Deputy Mayor Lian,
a good woman from a dignified family.
You don't have a problem why tease him?
The daughter of an official
and the son of a rich family is a perfect match.
You worry too much.
Blood pressure hasn't increased lately, right?
Take care of your health.
I guess you should date in your old age,
don't watch me every day
I'm different from Ruichi,
I don't mind
You find a stepmother for me.
You...
Halo.
Have you read the newspaper?
Already.
How do you feel?
Shen Shijie,
is it interesting for you to do this?
Interesting.
Very interesting.
If you want revenge on me,
just do it to me,
why do you want to harm other people?
Wretched?
Why do you use words like this?
Lian Lian is a very wonderful girl.
His personality is more cheerful than yours,
more open than you,
everyone is better than you.
Why can't I sincerely pursue it?
If you really sincerely want to pursue it,
why are you calling me now?
Because I'm happy.
I found a better girl than you.
I am happy,
I want to share with you.
Oh yes.
As a good friend of Lian Lian,
can you tell me about his hobbies?
Halo.
Why don't you speak?
Besides that,
namaku Feng Xiaosheng...
bukan Shen Shijie.
Ke Ying.
Ke Ying!
Sorry, Miss.
You still haven't paid.
That...
I'm sorry.
This way, please.
Officer Song, are you following me?
Mrs. Ke, I...
Thank you for your good intentions,
but I don't need it.
You don't need to protect me like this.
Jika Feng Xiaosheng sungguh adalah Shen Shijie,
then all this is logical.
Try saying it.
Shen Shijie is an escaped fugitive,
survive death with help from someone.
After plastic surgery,
kembali ke Nanzhou,
suddenly changed
became the chairman of the Feng Group's board of directors, Feng Xiaosheng.
For revenge,
torturing,
threatening the victim from cases 3-14,
namely Ke Ying, the first reporter.
After Ke Ying knew his identity,
immediately seek help from Inspector Chen.
At Ke Ying's request,
Inspector Chen went to see Feng Xiaosheng.
That day,
I went with Inspector Chen,
I'm waiting for him downstairs.
On the way home,
Inspector Chen held my hand for a long time,
and asked me to play the video of Feng Xiaosheng's speech.
Hold your hand?
Why hold your hand?
Don't know, he didn't say.
Xing Wei, you keep talking.
Inspector Chen went to see Feng Xiaosheng,
deliberately brought up Shen Shijie.
This made Feng Xiaosheng very scared.
So, he planned a car accident.
Dao Jian who acted,
engineer a car accident,
and killed Inspector Chen.
Dao Jian...
why did he listen to Feng Xiaosheng?
Maybe...
he wanted to hug Feng Xiaosheng's legs,
or there was a weakness in Feng Xiaosheng's hands.
Waktu itu, Dao Jian yang mengkhianati Shen Shijie.
Dao Jian dan Shen Shijie ini
working for second uncle,
they both are friends,
very understanding of each other.
Shen Shijie ini,
definitely knows many secrets of Dao Jian.
Not logical.
Look at it.
Dao Jian mengkhianati Shen Shijie,
jika Feng Xiaosheng adalah Shen Shijie,
then why didn't he take revenge on Dao Jian?
Got revenge,
isn't it after utilizing the Dao Jian,
then kill Dao Jian?
think about it,
Dao Jian hid so well,
even the second uncle couldn't find it,
but instead he was killed.
Who can kill him?
Who will kill him?
Is it second uncle?
Not second uncle.
Correct.
Even though it was the second uncle who killed him,
that's not necessary either
smashed his face and cut his hands.
I've got the money,
there is no revenge so great anymore.
The one who really had a grudge with Dao Jian was Shen Shijie.
The person who fell into the sea,
isn't his face also ruined?
There were three reasons Feng Xiaosheng killed Dao Jian.
The first is revenge.
The second is to seize money.
The third,
kill to silence him.
Dao Jian must have realized something
while helping Feng Xiaosheng.
Maybe you already know this Feng Xiaosheng is fake.
Actually,
dia adalah Shen Shijie.
Kapten Xiao,
what do you think?
Your logical reasoning is very strong,
but there is only one place where it is not suitable.
Where?
If
Feng Xiaosheng yang sekarang
adalah Shen Shijie,
Then, where was the real Feng Xiaosheng?
Besides that,
who was the dead Shen Shijie?
Feng Xiaosheng mati untuk Shen Shijie?
Impossible.
When Shen Shijie jumped into the abyss,
Feng Xiaosheng was giving a speech at the convention center.
Let's hurry from there, right?
Therefore, to investigate this case,
the most important part is finding
It was Shen Shijie who fell off the cliff that time.
If that person was not Shen Shijie,
then, who is that person?
Isn't that time to find
hair and fingerprint evidence
in Shen Shijie's hiding place,
and matched the DNA on the corpse?
Then, who exactly is this corpse?
This...
more mysterious than a novel.
I think it's impossible.
I even feel...
Ke Ying is possible
has a little problem with his brain.
Do you know there is a disease called
PTSD, post-traumatic stress disorder?
If it's serious, it's the same as a mental disorder.
felt like everyone wanted to hurt him,
perhaps there was a part of Feng Xiaosheng
who is a bit similar to Shen Shijie,
so, he felt Feng Xiaosheng
it was Shen Shijie who came back to take revenge on him.
Of course, Feng Xiaosheng was not a good person either,
Tapi dia pasti bukan Shen Shijie.
Do you still remember...
after the case occurred,
Ke Ying was very scared
Shen Shijie took revenge on him again.
Every time you meet us
I'll ask if you've been arrested yet,
have you been arrested yet?
How is Ke Ying?
Scolding me.
When we know we follow him,
he scolded me,
said he didn't need our protection.
If not,
I'll just come back
there are so many things on the team.
Sis Wu.
What are you doing here?
Look for me, okay?
Come on, come up for tea.
Sis Wu, Sis Wu.
Just forget it.
I didn't go up again so as not to embarrass you.
Wait,
what do you mean by this?
Got a problem?
What is it?
Say.
Do you have more money?
Can you lend me some money?
My mother was diagnosed with the disease,
now needs to be admitted for treatment.
Sis Qiang is also not there,
There is also no work at second uncle's place.
So, I...
How much?
I asked, how much do you want?
If you...
if you have more money,
can you lend me five thousand?
If you can't, two thousand is fine too.
If it's not enough, I'll borrow it from someone else.
Five thousand, I've transferred it.
Thank you, Sis Wu.
Why are you so reluctant?
Family health is more important than anything else.
Correct.
Lately, you're still like this?
If not, what else can I do?
You know, I can't do anything.
Back when I followed Sis Qiang,
can still eat.
Now we are eradicating the mafia,
also don't know where Kak Qiang went.
The second uncle has also stopped.
Have hands and feet, still so energetic,
can you still starve to death?
Sis Wu,
What if,
I'll just come with you?
Why follow me?
Don't I go to work seriously every day?
Do you know what my job used to be?
Bu Ke.
Hello, Mrs. Ke.
Grandma Chen, why did you come?
I came to visit you.
I should have gone to visit you.
You are...
It doesn't matter,
it's just that my legs have no strength.
The doctor said he could recover if treated.
Miao Miao,
you go to class.
I chatted with Mrs. Ke for a while.
I'll call you when I'm gone, okay?
Go quickly.
I will take good care of grandma.
In that case,
see you Bu Ke, see you Grandma.
Actually, I always wanted to visit you,
but don't know how to face you.
Your problem, Yu already told me.
Today I come,
first, would like to replace Miao Miao to thank you,
then want to tell you
You're overthinking.
I'm not that type of person
who cannot differentiate between right and wrong.
However...
Nothing however.
My son is a police officer.
There you are, he has to catch criminals.
There's no you, he also has to catch criminals.
This is his job,
also his responsibility.
About...
the people who killed my son for revenge,
or for fear that my son will investigate them,
those who killed him are the perpetrators,
not you, Mrs. Ke.
Who is guilty,
who is innocent,
I know clearly.
Thank you, Grandma Chen.
Yu Chengbo!
Stop!
Pretend you don't know me?
Familiar.
Then, why are you ignoring me?
Because there is nothing to talk to you about.
Are you the same as them?
I feel like I'm deliberately making a fuss,
and bother everyone?
Isn't that so?
It was to find the culprit, to avenge my father!
However, what was the result?
I know.
You are all on the side of Miss Lecturer Ke.
Grandma thinks I'm very unreasonable,
deliberately making a fuss.
Uncle Xiao felt like I was bothering him.
Even you...
Why me?
You like Miss Lecturer Ke.
So, you feel that whatever Mrs. Lecturer Ke is doing is right,
and whatever I did was wrong.
I really like Miss Lecturer Ke,
but not the kind of like you understand,
but respect,
amazed,
darling,
it is respect.
However, he is not just a lecturer to me,
but a lamp for me,
someone who guides me
When I feel insecure and sensitive because of poverty,
he was the one who told me to be a person you have to have a big heart,
must face everything about oneself bravely.
When I was slandered and framed by others,
only he is willing to trust me unconditionally,
reached out to help me.
Even this time,
when you found out you were taken away by Feng Xiaosheng,
also he...
who ignores their own safety
go save you.
He shouldn't have gone,
can pretend not to know,
can pretend to be helpless,
no matter what the bad guy does to you.
Miao Miao,
how can you treat others as fools?
No.
I...
I actually shouldn't scold you.
Wasn't I the same as you before?
I think I'm very smart.
Until now I just realized,
not how smart we are,
but we feel we are the most righteous.
I am wrong.
I know wrong.
I won't bother everyone anymore.
I won't feel right anymore.
I won't act smart anymore.
Senior Brother, I miss my father.
You feel...
Feng Xiaosheng adalah Shen Shijie?
Indeed he is.
He admitted it to me,
but I have no proof,
other people will think I'm crazy.
So,
do you have a plan?
I also do not know.
Just feel so awake,
suddenly hit by a big mountain,
towering,
and very big.
Can't get through,
and cannot be moved.
You can only hit yourself until your head bleeds, there is no other way.
Every time there seems to be a little hope,
I will be hit hard.
How about taking a step back?
Behind is the abyss,
if you take a step back,
will be shattered into pieces.
In that case, it can only go forward.
Even if you hit your head and bleed,
You also have to crash until there is a way out.
Deputy Mayor Lian
always very busy.
Want to meet
really not easy, yes.
If there's a problem, just say it straight away.
I won't beat around the bush any longer.
This time I'm looking for you for the problem of our two children.
I think you've seen the news too.
We are people who look up,
always tolerated these two children
create problems like this,
not a good thing.
Because they have this kind of intention,
better establish this relationship.
Don't hope.
Why?
You feel my family is not worthy of your daughter?
Feng Yong,
who are you?
What is the Feng family like?
Others don't know,
don't I know?
Don't mess with my daughter.
I tell you.
car factory problems,
- I still haven't calculated it with you. - Car factory?
What's wrong with the car factory?
Don't you understand yourself?
If it weren't for me to support you,
police station
I've been looking for you for a long time to understand the situation.
Can you still sit quietly here?
Understand the situation?
If so, we understand well.
This place,
who approved it?
Who also signed this subsidy?
My tens of millions,
fed to which dog?
Lian Zhiyun, Lian Zhiyun.
You think I'm the only one trapped and not free, huh?
You're the same way.
The investigation team came here not only to investigate the Feng family,
but also to reveal
big corrupt like you.
Both of us
have been tied together for a long time.
car factory,
if this rock falls, it won't just hit my feet.
Feng Yong...
you old fox!
Don't be angry.
Deputy Mayor Lian,
Anger is not good for your health.
Have you been checked for your illness?
Do I need to invite two experts for you?
Checking you well.
Don't get your diagnosis wrong again.
The leadership position requires you.
Don't...
go easy
Feng Yong,
don't put too much pressure on people.
I'm not pressuring you.
You want to let go,
I understand.
However, you must also give me space to retreat.
What does this have to do with my daughter?
Ada.
There are many relationships.
One, children's happiness.
Second,
can be considered giving
additional guarantee for both our families.
Win, yes, win together,
losing is also losing together.
Lian Lian.
Why did you come here too?
I even wanted to ask you.
What is this?
I also do not know.
Wouldn't it be known after entering?
Hurry here.
Why just stand there?
♪I'm sure, this time is a long journey with no return♪
♪Trying to listen to your faint warning♪
♪No problem, dilemma♪
♪Never believe in fate♪
♪Close your eyes Seeking inner peace♪
♪Can't cry, But have to laugh♪
♪Adrift between the Borders of good and evil♪
♪How many times have you woken up from a dream that contains you♪
♪Repeatedly convince yourself that you have to be strong♪
♪How much courage does it take♪
♪To change a little light♪
♪Don't ask about tomorrow♪
♪No regrets No revenge♪
♪How much courage does it take♪
♪To change a little light♪
♪Don't ask about forever♪
♪Menjaga di sisimu♪