Happy.
I finally got my revenge today.
Did something happen?
No.
It's not here.
I'm just in a good mood today.
I'll sign the engagement letter for you next time.
and set you free.
Let's go. Let's go.
Go! Go!
Your Highness! Your Highness!
General Mo.
Governor Shan, what brings you here so late at night?
We suspect that...
the princess is related to the injury of a snow robe.
Princess, do we have any evidence?
Shut up!
What evidence do you have? It's here. It's here.
This...
Magistrate Shan.
Although the princess was demoted,
she is still the seventh princess of Sheng Xuan State.
If you don't have evidence,
you can't bear the consequences.
because you can't bear the consequences?
You...
You are that pregnant woman.
It turns out to be a man.
Magistrate Shan, I'm totally sure that...
they did it.
They pretended to be pregnant and deceived me.
to attract my attention
and destroy my Snow Garment.
General Mo, what do you think we should do?
Is this why you're happy?
I didn't expect to be discovered so soon.
I'll take the responsibility.
It's just a piece of clothes.
At the crucial moment,
at the crucial moment.
That's right. It's just a piece of clothes.
That's right.
Mr Mo, this is not just a piece of clothes.
This is the civilization of Qingcheng.
Seijoh was famous for making clothes.
Later, it declined.
This is the only snow coat left.
Now the princess destroyed it.
If the Emperor breaks the law, it's the same as the commoners.
You must pay for it.
I'll pay for it. I'll pay for it. I'll pay for it.
Please help me.
Situ, calm down.
Calm down.
I will give you justice.
Although this is a princess,
we'll pay for it. Okay.
I’ll pay for it.
It’s not enough. The snow robe is worth 10,000 taels.
Are you done?
What are you talking about?
Magistrate Shan.
I'm going to sue her for extortion.
You're a good official who knows the law and the law.
Magistrate Shan.
I want to sue her for destroying the civilization of Qingcheng.
You're an upright official who upholds justice for the people, right?
Then you must help me.
Help me! Help me!
Come on. Come on.
Your Highness. Your Highness.
Miss Situ.
I am just
a lowly official.
There is no distinction between officials and officials.
You've been studying hard for ten years.
The gentlemen didn't teach
how to reason with women
Who can help me?
Are we going?
The princess was bullied.
I think it's our princess's fault.
That makes sense.
I'm struggling.
I did see your loyalty today.
I misunderstood you before.
You're a general.
You usually fight in wars.
there's no chance to be corrupted.
Then there's no money.
I'll take the responsibility.
Leave.
I won't implicate you.
Princess, what should you do next?
Why are you laughing?
I can find someone
to make her the same one.
Isn't that enough?
Besides, I should go to jail.
I should be the first princess
in Sheng Xuan State.
It's okay, princess. I'll go to jail with you.
You're an accomplice too. You can't escape.
Uncle, I'm so mad!
There's a stupid princess from Qingcheng County.
She went too far!
She not only bullied me,
but also broke my snow coat.
Will you do anything, uncle?
If you don't,
I can't look up anymore.
Calm down.
Uncle will make you look up
Dongsheng, how much longer?
You walk slower than the turtles in the palace.
Almost there, princess.
That's the mountain ahead.
I've asked around.
Uncle Erbai Li is on the mountain ahead.
He made the snow coat when he was young.
But it was flawed.
The Situ family was so shameless to go.
She didn't even give her a penny.
She was acting with me that day.
She cried so hard that I almost took it seriously.
She's really something.
She's not simple.
Don't mention her
Dongsheng.
We've been walking for so long.
There's no bird in this forest.
Could there be any bad guys?
Princess, don't talk nonsense.
Your mouth is glowing.
Don't talk nonsense.
It's like this. It's like this. It's like this.
What's that?
Listen to me
Dongsheng, put me down first.
Count to three before you open your eyes.
Footsteps.
Let's go! Let's go!
Oh, no!
Luckily I ran fast.
The bandits in this small place are quite imposing.
Dongsheng.
Take care of yourself.
Let me fight.
Come on, one-on-one.
Didn't we agree to fight one-on-one?
Stop!
Please don't hit my face.
You hit me so badly.
Shall we go up and help?
A hammer.
Our mission is to protect the princess.
You naughty girl.
Protect the princess. Yes.
Where is the princess?
Father.
Father, why haven't you come to me?
Snake.
Look at him. He's here.
Moli Chen Ziyou
Sheng Tao Tao Mo Na.
[Moli Chen Ziyou]
[Shan Yu Ci, Du Rong Yi]
[The peach blossoms.] [The peach blossoms.]
The sun rises. The sun shines.
Shan Yu Ci. Du Rong Yi.
Second Prince, Tong Huaizhou.
Noble Consort Wan, Qi Ning.
Situ Snow, Liu Xin Yu.
Princess of Jinshan, Xu Jiaman.
Aunt Wang, Zhao Hongwei.
Auntie Wang. Zhao Hongwei.
Ma Yi. Cheng Yi.
Ma Yi, Yang Yu Chun.
Zhang Yixing: Ma Yi. Zhang Yixing: Cheng Yi.
Li Zhenning: Hu Zhenning. Li Zhenning: Li Zhenning.
Old man Lu Chao
Jin He Qio
Old man 2 Chow Kaiping
Jin Qiran.
Two gold pieces, Qi Haoran.
Jin Junwen.
Three golden Joywen.
and the team actor, Zhang Honghao.
Wang Zhiguo.
Zhang Honghao from the team.
and the actors, Tang Jiaxiang.
and the actors, Wang Jinbiao.
and the actors, Hao Xinyu.
and Zhu Rui Xuan.
and the actors, Li Yang Zhou.
and Wu Qiuli.
and Li Yang Zhou.
and Wu Qiaoli.
and Li Siqing.
and Chen Jiahui.
and the actors, Li Siqing.
Actors in charge, Mou Zhendong.
Acting director, Li Xiaochao.
Special schedule.
Fanfan dance Wang Yinan
Steward Ma, Huang Fushuang.
Old lady of embroidery, Zhang Yan.
Jiang Guangxu, the swordsman.
Old lady of embroidery, Zhang Yanhua.
Swordsman Jiang Guangxu.
Sword client, Yuan Song.
Noble Consort eunuch, Li Junyu.
Emperor eunuch Ji Jili
Tang Yuyao, the sleeping minister.
Li Dongdong, envoy of Jin State.
Steward Ma, Huang Fushuang.
Sword client, Yuan Song.
Steward Ma. Huang Fu.
Knife. Jiang Guangxu.
Sword Customer, Ho Yuan Song
Knife Customer Jiang Guangxu
Dance girl Liu Ke.
Tang Shunhua.
Old Madam Wei Xinghong
Uncle Li of Erhu, Tan Shihui
Old Head, Ge Shi Tian.
Old man Ge Shi Tian
Zhuang, Han, Chen Zhi Wu.
The old lady with crutches, Zhang Dongying.
[The troublemaker, Li Long.]
The troublemaker, Li, Long.
The owner of Snow Garment Pavilion, Liu Qingquan.
Doctor Jia Andy Wang
Zhuang, Han, Yang Shenzhen
Mrs. Zheng, Ling, pregnant woman.
Yuan Li, the cleaning lady.
Yuan Li! Yuan Li!
Li Zichao, the owner of the Li Store.
Zhuang, Han, Wang Zibo.
Li Zichao, the owner of Liuli Store.
Zhuang, Han, Wang Shade.
Zhuang, Han, Wang Zibo.
Zhuang, Han, Lee Myung-gi.
Zhuang, Han, Wang Shade
Zhuang, Han, Li Minggi.
Ms. Ma. Ms. Lu Seol-rou.
Miss Zhang Jing
Zhuang, Han, Li.
Doctor Jia, Andy Wang.
Li Zichao, the owner of Liuli Store.
Wang Min An, a servant of the governor's mansion.
Flog Li Zichao.
Beggar, beggar, Li Faguang.
The magistrate's servant, Wang Min An.
Beg, beggar, Li Fa Guang.
Refugees Shao Zhikang
Refugees! Refugees!
Referee A
Zhang Yuhu.
Zhuang, Han, Yang Xingliang.
Dance, Han Xiao.
Li Jun.
Dance. Liu Jun.
Judge Li Jun.
Women’s Camp. Li’s Camp.
Dance, Liu Ke.
Women's men, Li's barracks,
Woman Gao Dan.
Lady Gao Dan
Bride makeup minister Wang Yue Feng
Tanghulu, Wang Guohua.
Female beggar, Qiu Mei Sun.
The owner of the steamed bun shop, Chen En Tao.
Fan Jianhua, the cleaner.
Pan Jian Hua
Old man Zhang
Old man Zhang Shufa
Old man Ge Shi Tian
Mr. Tang Shun Hua.
Old man Ge Shi Tian.
Old Madam. Zhang Shunhua.
Old Man Shun Hua.
Old Madam, Wei Xinghong.
Old lady, take down the cane.
Uncle Hu, Tan Shihui
Boss Robert
Uncle Erhu, Tan Shihui
Old Madam Xu Quanhong
Ms. Seo Kwon-hong! Ms. Seo Kwon-hong!
Here's the menu. It's here.
The production team.
The production team
Chief Planner, Xu Jiaman.
Editor-in-Chief Review, Xu Jiaman.
Editor-in-chief, Xu Jiaman.
Xu Jiaman from Shanning.
Producer Tong Huaizhou Li Feng
Chief Producer Qi Youning Xu Jiaman
Executive Producer Xu Jiandong
PR Director Wang Shensheng
Publicize Wu Heng Ruo Tan Yaqi
Mr. Lin Ken.
The circulation, Geng.
Screenwriter, Xu Jiaman.
The producer, Chen Hao.
The screenwriter, Xu Jiaman,
Director Chen Hao.
to make arrangements for Yang Piaqing.
Producer assistant Li Jiaxuan
She's in charge of Yang Piaqing.
Producer He Chongchong
Life Producer Guest Chen Yan
Foreign producer Fang Junqiang
Captain Hu Mingli
The director team
Li Liming.
Executive director Li Luhao
Mr. Baji
Executive Director Li
Mr. Baji.
Photographer team.
Guo Lei.
Photographer Ding Weihao
Photographer, Guo Lei.
Photographer Yang Yicheng.
Photographer assistant, Lu Yao.
Photographer assistant Chu Yingxu
Photographer assistant Zeng Xiangyu
Photographer assistant Ma Cheng
Camera Zeng Xiangyu
Lighting team.
Lighting instructor, Tian Bowen.
Lighting Daisuke Wang Yapeng.
Lighting assistant, Wang Yu Fan.
Lighting assistant Wang Yapeng.
Lighting assistant Yang Jinglong.
Lighting assistant, Wang Yufan.
Lighting assistant, Zhang Tian Qi.
Lighting assistant, Tang Jiaqi.
Lighting assistant Chen Yahui
The recording team
Come on. Come on.
Recording assistant, Zhang Bao Cai.
Recorder Zhang Jiahao
Recording assistant Zhang Bao Cai
Art team.
He Yuhui.
He Yuhui, art instructor.
Li Yiming, the prop team leader.
Li Yiming.
Props team leader, Li Yiming.
A prop for acting. Li Yiming.
Mr. Chen Dawei. Mr. Chen Dawei.
Chen Shencheng
ChengDawei, Head of Development.
Chen, Zhi, Zhu Lihui.
Chen, Xiang, Shi Qing Hua
Chen Qilin Liu Chunlin
Chen, set, Zuo Wentao.
Props on site, Li Chunming.
Chen Bao Ping.
Props on site, Tsuchihua.
The prop. Lee Chunming.
Li Chunming: Li Chunming. Li Chunming: Li Chunming.
The styling team.
The styling instructor, Tian Longfei.
The makeup team leader, Jin Guohua.
Makeup artist Zhang Qifei.
Makeup artist Sun Yiyi
Makeup artist Sun Gao Jie
Makeup artist Sun
Daisuke of the scene, Wang Shen Shen.
Mr. Wang.
Support from the scene, Wang Shen Shen.
Helper Wang, Xia,
We're here to help you.
[Costume Team Leader Zheng Jinmao]
Come on, let's go. Let's go.
Costume focuses on surprises. Costume focuses on surprises.
Costume assistant Ma Yongqiang.
Costume assistant Li Juan.
Li Zhenning: Look at the camera.
It's a team. It's a team. It's a team.
Let's go! Let's go!
The audition director, Li Xiaochao.
Actors and deputy directors, Sun Zhaogang.
Acting director Li Xiaochao.
Actors and actors. Mou Zhendong.
Actor, assistant director, Sun Zhaogang.
You're a good actor. You're a good actor.
The venue team.
He Chongchong, Zhou, Mi, Chen Jia Rui, Lei Xianfa.
He Chongchong, Zhou Jiarui, Chen Jiarui, Lei Xianxian.
Driver
Chen Yuehui Bao Jiangbin Li Zhenjie Dong Satellite Han Bing, Sun Weigang.
Fang Xiaohua, Ouyang Jun, Kong Weifang, journalist Cao Zhu Chunwei.
[Post production]
It's like this.
Seven-wei.
Senwei Culture Co., Ltd.
The project manager, Wang Simeng.
The post-production director, Zhou Xiaoqiao.
Editing instructor Zheng Shifei
The post-production producer, Alan Liu.
Cut. Zheng Shifei.
Video production.
Video technology manager, Liu Zhiming.
Video technology, Shin Eun-taek.
Li Ang, the screen producer.
DIT Li Ang.
Passenger Wei Heyun.
Personor Jing Mingrui.
Color maker, Jing Mingrui.
It's a special effect.
The light
WIGUANG
Weiguang Culture Co., Ltd.
of Weiguang Culture Co., Ltd.
Director of Production, Yan Qi.
Project Manager Liu Jialin.
Director Yan.
Visual effect, Yin Guimo.
"Yin Guimo". "Yin Guimo". "Yin Guimo". "Yin Guimo". "Yin Guimo". "Yin Guimo".
[Visual guidance: Yin Gui-mao] You're right.
Zhang Qianbang, you're the best. You're the best.
[Visual guidance: Xie Bing Han.] You're right.
Project producer Zhao Ziyan
Tie up Zhang Haitao Wang Ningkun
Lighting dyer Li Xueping Cao Shuai
Director Wang Xuya
Lighting dyeer, Li Xueping, Cao Shuai.
Guan Yang Hong.
Animation Director Yang Hongbin
Animator: Gu, Yu, Wang, Xu, Sun Rui. Pan Bo Guo.
The match master, Sun Xiaomeng, Yu Xiaochao.
Sun Xiaomeng
Special effects director Li Xu
Special effects expert, Jing Wei Ma.
Digital grapher, Bai, Yang.
Editor of UE5 Ding Ao.
Han Sheungheng, Lu Peng, Wang Zhen, and Yuan Yuan.
Gao Xinyi
Product company
Observatory Xinghe Film (Wuxi) Co., Ltd.
Big Wing Film.
Joint production company.
Leopardia Film (Wuxi) Co., Ltd.
[Wuxi Co., Ltd.]
Production company.
Zhejiang Strawberry Film Co., Ltd.
Big Wing Film (Dongyang) Co., Ltd.
Exclusive announcement.
[Xiamen Super Invincible Film and Media Co., Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd.]
Ming Xie Group.
[Hengdian Film Store]
[Hengdian Film Studies] [Video Studies]
You're here. I'm here. I'm here. I'm here.