Everyone,
The last game is coming.
and the real theme of this competition.
It's time to show your real talent.
Two days later, one representative will be selected
and put on their own works for the final show.
I believe everyone
Very good.
So,
The contents of the competition are innovative.
Okay.
Don't be stressed. Just stay calm.
If you want this texture,
you have to abandon the heavy embroidery.
Because once you embroider on this kind of gauze,
the original gauze will be damaged.
and run yarn.
Why don't we make other decorations
and sew them together.
It can greatly reduce the damage of the raw yarn.
Done.
Great work, Your Highness.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Thank you.
Go back and rest early.
Okay.
It's holiday these days.
Thank you, princess.
Thank you.
Take care.
Okay.
Bye. Bye.
You too
Dongsheng, close the door when you leave.
Don't worry, princess.
Let's go.
Do you think Father knows that I've grown up?
Will he take me back to the capital?
I miss him so much.
Of course.
I've written a letter to my father in the capital.
Tell him that our princess is the best.
Father will tell His Majesty
he's still waiting for a divorce.
How do you know it's Xiaoli?
What if it's Little Xiaotao?
I hate it.
I think she's going to steal something.
This is not our business.
Let's go.
Let's see what you can do tonight.
What happened?
It's all your fault. I didn't lock the door.
We worked so hard for so many days.
for nothing.
It's all your fault.
It's all for nothing.
What's wrong with you?
What's going on?
You can't even guard the door.
What should we do?
Be quiet.
You may leave.
I'll figure it out.
It's all your fault.
Taotao, clothes are not important.
You've succeeded, right?
Mo Li, don't talk.
It's not the end yet.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Here.
After the tense competition a few days ago,
it's finally time for everyone's attention.
Are you looking forward to it?
Look forward to it.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Okay.
Come on, show us.
Now, the representative of White Bear Gook is coming.
Their theme is peace.
Next, let's welcome Mr. Pi-kook.
OK.
Let's welcome the representative of Flying Kingdom.
Now let's welcome
Finally,
let's welcome the representative of Sheng Xuan.
Where is he?
Come out
Yeah
What's going on
No one's coming out.
Let's welcome the representative of Sheng Xuan.
Why hasn't he come out yet?
Why isn't he coming out?
What is he doing?
Yes.
Let's welcome the representative of Sheng Xuan.
to the stage.
Okay.
So pretty.
The princess is so pretty.
You have no idea
how dangerous the situation was.
That's right.
You didn't notice
how dangerous it was.
Yes.
I didn't have time
It's hopeless.
Unsolved.
But who am I?
I am the smartest princess
in Shengxuan State.
At that time, I was smart
I changed the broken jacket
into a pair of small wings.
So the clothes are more flexible.
Come on, Dongsheng.
Spiritual.
Let me show you.
It's so beautiful.
So pretty.
Nice
Such a rough fabric.
can win.
It looks like there's a little flaw.
So?
I asked them to turn off the lights.
and left a beam of strong light on me.
And with me,
I saw the princess
and carefree again,
I'm relieved.
Who could see the clothes clearly then?
I was looking for a prescription for her white hair.
Later,
to visit a miracle doctor.
It's a divine ceremony.
People who haven't seen it
It's a pity.
Great.
It's so nice. The princess is so beautiful.
Am I awesome?
Awesome.
Actors.
Actor watch.
Sheng Tao Tao, Mao Na,
Mo, Li, Chen Ziyou.
Shan Yu Ci, Du Rong Yi.
Peach hair.
Su Chen from Dongsheng.
Shan Yu Ci Du Rong Yi
Dongsheng Su Chen
Second Prince Tong Huaizhou.
Noble Consort Wan, Qi Ning.
Second Prince, Tong Huaizhou.
Prince Qi of Jinshan.
Princess of Jinshan, Xu Jiaman.
Aunt Wang, Zhao Hong Wei.
Ma Jia Cheng Yi.
Ma Yi Yang Yu Chun
Cheng Yi.
Adida Hu Jingyi.
Ma Yi, Yang Yu-chun.
Adida Hu Ching Yi.
Mr. Ma, Li Yu.
Lu Chao.
Zhou Qiping.
Jin He Qio
Third gold, Yao Junwen.
Two golden Qi Haoran.
Three, Jin, Yao Junwen.
Actor Wang Zhiguo.
and group actor, Zhang Honghao.
and the actors, Wang Zhiguo.
Tang Jiaxiang.
Wang Jinbiao
and a group actor, Wang Jinbiao.
Hao Xinyu.
Zhu Rui Xuan.
Li Yang Zhou, an actress in the group.
and Wu Qiuli.
and Li Siqing.
and Chen Jiahui.
Mou Zhendong.
Acting director, Li Xiaochao.
Special schedule.
Steward Ma, Huang Fushuang.
Fanfan dance Wang Yinan
Knife Guest Jiang Guangxu
Old lady of embroidery, Zhang Yanhua.
Swordsman Jiang Guangxu.
Sword client, Yuan Song.
Noble Consort eunuch, Li Junyu.
Emperor eunuch Ji Li
Noble Consort, eunuch, Jaydon.
Emperor eunuch Ji Jili
Tang Yuyao, the sleeping minister.
Li Dongdong, envoy of Jin State.
Steward Ma, Huang Fushuang.
Knife Customer Jiang Guangxu
Sword Customer, Ho Yuan Song.
Swordsman Jiang Guangxu.
Dance girl Liu Ke.
Old lady of embroidery, Zhang Yanhua.
Dance girl Liu Ke Yan.
Uncle Li, Gao Wenjun.
Old lady of embroidery, Zhang Yanhua.
Tang Shunhua.
Tang Shunhua
Wei Xinghong
Uncle Li Shihui
Old man Ge Shitian
Zhuang, Han, Chen Zhi Wu.
The old lady with crutches, Zhang Dongying.
The troublemaker, Li, Long.
Liu Qingquan, boss of Snow Garment Pavilion.
Doctor Jia, Andy Wang.
Liu Qingquan, boss of Snow Garment Pavilion
Zhuang, Han, Yang Shenzhen.
Doctor Jia Andy Wang
The pregnant lady, Zheng Linlin.
Yuan Li, the cleaner.
Li Zichao, the owner of Liuli Store.
Zhuang, Han, Wang Shade.
Zhuang, Han, Wang Zibo.
Zhuang, Han, Lee Myung-gi.
Jangang Han Wang Shade
Ms Ma, Lu Seol-rou.
Miss Zhang, Chen Jing.
Ms Ma, Lu Xue Rou.
Zhuang, Han, Bao, Li.
Miss Zhang, Chen Jing.
Li Zichao, the owner of Liuli Store.
Beggar, Li Faguang.
Wang Min An, servant of the governor.
Beg, Li Fa.
refugee Shao Zhikang.
Ranger Shaw Zhikang.
Judge A, Chen En Hong.
Contestant Zhang Dengkai.
Zhang Yuhu.
Contestant Zhang Tingkai.
Dance Han Xiao.
Judge Li Jun.
Women and men, Li Army Camp.
Dance Liu Ke.
Woman Gao Dan.
Wang Yue Feng, Minister of Bride Makeup.
Bride makeup minister Wang Yue Feng.
Tanghulu man, Wang Guohua.
Female beggar, Wo Mi-sun.
The owner of the steamed bun shop, Chen En Tao.
Paon Jianhua, the sweeper.
Old man Zhang Shufa.
Tang Shunhua.
Old man Ge Shi Tian.
Old Madam Zhang Minmin.
Tang Shunhua.
Old Madam Wei Xinghong.
Pregnant woman Zheng Ling.
Old Madam, Wei Xinghong.
The old lady with crutches, remove Dong-young.
Boss, Wang Guanbo.
Uncle Li of Erhu, Tan Shihui
Old Madam Xu Quanhong
[Staff Form]
Hello. Hello.
The staff list.
The production team.
Chief Planner, Xu Jiaman.
The Editor-in-Chief Review, Xu Jiaman.
Producer Tong Huaizhou Li Feng
Chief Producer Qi Youning Xu Jiaman
Producer Tong Huaizhou, Li Feng.
Executive Producer Xu Jiandong
PR Director Wang Shensheng
Promote Wu Heng Ruo Tan Yaqi.
PR Director Wang Sheng.
Publicize Wu Heng Ruo Tan Yaqi
Lin Ken.
The circulation, Geng.
Screenwriter, Xu Jiaman.
Producer Director Chen Hao
Production assistant Li Jiaxuan.
to arrange for Yang Piaqing.
Producer assistant Li Jiaxuan
Producer He Chong
Producer He Chongchong
Life Producer Chen, Yan Yuhui
Foreign producer Fang Junqiang
Life Producer Chen, Yan Yuhui.
Captain Hu Mingli
Director team.
The director team.
Director Li Liming.
Executive director Li Luhao
Mr. Baji.
Photography team.
Photographer Guo Lei.
Photographer group.
Photographer Ding Weihao.
Photographer, Guo Lei.
Photographer Ding Weihao
Photographer Yang Yicheng.
Photographer assistant, Li Lu Yao.
Photographer assistant Chu Yingxu
Photographer assistant Ma Cheng
[Photographer assistant Zeng Xiang Hua]
Lighting Team.
Lighting instructor, Tian Bowen.
Lighting team.
Lighting Daisuke Wang Yapeng.
Lighting instructor, Tian Bowen.
Lighting assistant, Wang Yu Fan.
Lighting assistant Wang Yapeng.
Lighting assistant Yang Jinglong.
Lighting assistant Wang Yufan.
Lighting assistant Zhang Tianqi.
Lighting assistant Yang Jinglong
Lighting assistant Tang Jiaqi
Lighting assistant Chen Yahui
The recording team.
Recording team.
Recorder Zhang Jiahao
Voice assistant Zhang Bao Cai.
Art team.
He Yuhui, art instructor.
The prop for the play, Li Yiming.
The prop team leader, Li Yiming.
Li Yiming.
Chen Dawei, the head of the decoration team.
Chen Shencheng
ChengDawei, Head of Development.
Chen, Xiang, Zhu Lihui.
Chen Shencheng
Chen, set, pay full
Chen setting Zhu Lihui
Chen, Xiang, Shi Qing Hua
Chen, Zhi, Zhi, Zhi, Fu.
Chen, set, Zuo Wentao.
The prop for the scene, Li Chunming.
Chen Bao Ping.
The prop at the scene, Li Tsui Hua.
Lee Chun-myung.
The prop for the scene, Lee Tsui-hwa.
The styling team.
The styling instructor, Tian Longfei.
The makeup team leader, Kim Guohua.
styling instructor, Tian Longfei.
The makeup team leader, Jin Guohua.
Makeup artist Zhang Qifei.
Makeup artist Sun Gao Jie
Makeup artist, Sun Yi.
Daisuke, Wang Shen Shen.
Mr. Wang.
The assistant at the scene, Li Minmin.
[Costume Team Leader Zheng Jinmao]
Costume main focus, Fo Hui Hui Chao.
Costume team leader, Zheng Jinmao.
Qu Hui Chao.
Costume assistant Ma Yongqiang.
Costume assistant, Li Juan.
Kwak Jin-young, the tailor.
The audition team.
Acting director, Li Xiaochao.
Actor assistant director Mou Zhendong
Actor assistant director Sun Zhaogang.
The venue team.
He Chongchong, Zhou, Mi, Chen Jia Rui, Lei Xianfa.
He Chongchong
Hu Mingli, Chen Wangqing Tang, Li Zhiming, Dong Jinwang, Chen Shencheng
Hu Mingli, Chen Wangqing, Tang Dazhong, Li Zhiming Dong Jinwang Chen Shencheng
Chen Yuehui Bao Jiangbin Li Zhenjie Dong Satellite Han Bing, Sun Weigang.
Fang Xiaohua, Ouyang Jun, Kong Weifang, journalist Cao Zhu Chunwei.
Post production.
Sanwei Culture Co., Ltd. Ltd.
The project manager, Wang Simeng.
The post-production director, Zhou Xiaoqiao.
Late production, Alan.
Editing instructor Zheng Shifei
Video production.
Video technical director, Liu Zhiming.
Video technology, Shin Eun-taek.
Production of subtitles Li Ang
DIT Li Ang.
Subtitles Producer Li Ang
Passenger Wei Heyun.
Color maker, Jing Mingrui.
Special effects production.
WIGUANG 19
Sun
WIGUANG
Weiguang Culture Co., Ltd.
Production Director Yan Qi.
Project Manager Liu Jialin.
Production Director Yan Qiqi.
Visual Director Yin Gui-mao
Visual Director Yin Gui Maomao
Visual guidance, Xie Bing Han.
technical director, Zhang Qianbana.
Visual Director Xie Bing Han.
technical director, Zhang Qianorange.
Project producer Zhao Ziyan.
The kidnapper Zhang Haitao Wang Ningkun
Asst Director Wang Xuya
Lighting dyeer Li Xueping Cao Shuai
Animation Director Yang Hongbin
Cartoon artist, Gu Yu, Wang Xu, Sun Rui. Guo Pan Bo.
The match player, Sun Xiaomeng, Yu Xiaochao.
Matchmaker Sun Xiaomeng Yu Chao
Special effects director Li Xu
Special effects engineer Ma Jingwei
Digital grapher, Bai, Yang.
Ding Ao, the editor of UE5.
Han Sheungheng, Lu Peng, Wang Zhen, and Yuan Yuan.
Gao Xinyi
Product company.
Oscar Xinghe Movie (Wuxi) Co., Ltd.
Big Wing Film.
Joint production company.
Wuxi Co., Ltd.
Leopardia Film (Wuxi) Co., Ltd.
Production company.
Production company?
Zhejiang Strawberry Film Co., Ltd.
Big Wing Film (Dongyang) Co., Ltd.
Exclusive announcement.
Xiamen SuperYingying Film and Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Ming Xie.
Hengdian Film and TV City.
Hengdian Film Studio.
[Hengdian Film Center]