She's here! She's here! She's here!
She's fine.
People grow up from reflection.
No one comes.
Maybe no one likes me.
So even Father doesn't like me anymore.
Liar.
We have a free dinner.
Yes.
I'm not lying.
Really?
Really.
Look how nice you are to me
Lady, please eat.
Here you go. Here you go. Here you go.
This...
Is it poisonous?
It's not poisonous. Don't worry.
You guys are so creepy.
I'm not eating.
I'll eat first.
Look.
Okay.
Let's eat. Let's eat. Let's eat.
I'll eat it.
Lady, have some fish.
Have some shrimp
Thank you.
Princess, you are so nice.
Me?
Of course.
You're pretty and kind.
and friendly.
I accept you.
From now on, I'll give you whatever I eat.
Look.
I knew you're the best princess I've ever seen.
You've seen other princesses?
Nonsense.
Don't talk nonsense.
Don't talk if you don't know how.
I've decided.
What have you decided?
Today is my birthday.
I hereby swear
I've decided to be the best princess.
and be loved by the people.
Okay.
Why should the people love you?
You've never been married, have you?
You deserve it.
You deserve to be single.
That's right.
No one wants him in the future.
Go on.
So I decided
I will open the cold palace myself.
First, opening a cold palace is not a small amount.
Second, we need a big house.
Do you have money?
Can you afford it?
No.
But you do.
I have. I...
Why are you always picking on the princess?
You keep discouraging her.
If there's no difficulty, just solve it?
Yeah.
You're short-mouthed.
I know a place that doesn't cost money.
Why not?
It's free. It's free?
Okay.
Let's start.
Here.
Put it over there.
Let's move this over.
Move that over there.
Come on, over there.
Let me help you.
The broom.
What are you doing?
I heard that the princess
will build a nursing home for us.
What is a nursing home?
A nursing home?
You want to make money again?
The tax isn't enough.
Are you trying to squeeze our Qingcheng Prefecture?
Money again?
I open a nursing home to benefit the people.
It's free.
She's so kind.
That's right.
How is that possible?
Of course.
Well said.
OK.
Thank you, princess.
Congratulations.
OK.
The nursing home is officially open today.
Okay.
It's still free.
Okay, please come in.
Please.
Thank you, princess.
Slow down.
Don't push.
What should we do?
Okay.
We can live here for free from now on.
We can live here for free.
Be careful.
Slowly.
The dishes are ready.
Mr Mo.
Can I help you?
What are you doing here?
Aren't there volunteers at the door?
She was hired.
Since you're leading the way to do good deeds,
how can Situ family be left behind?
Right, Mr Mo?
We need manpower in the nursing home.
Why don't you help me cut the vegetables?
Okay.
The weasel greets the chicken.
He's up to no good.
I cut my hand, Mr Mo.
It hurts so much.
You're bleeding.
I'll get you some medicine.
Watch the pot.
Tell me, what do you want this time?
Volunteer! Help!
You're only allowed to do good deeds.
I don't believe you.
When I opened a nursing home,
you were the strongest against it.
So what?
It's mainly because he's close to Mr Mo now.
He has a fiancee.
Fiancée?
You're not married yet.
I still have a chance.
Shameless!
You're shameless!
Princess, you...
It's about the ladies.
Let's leave the servants alone.
Princess, can you eat earlier?
Yes.
It's taking so long to eat
I'm hungry.
Let's eat
Dinner is ready
Eat mine first.
Eat mine first
Eat my cabbage first
My radish helps digestion
My cabbage can grow taller
My radish can also be beautified
My cabbage can lose weight
My radish can grow hair
Mine can also lose weight and live long.
Stop arguing.
Let's eat together.
How is it?
It's so spicy.
It tastes awful.
I want to go home.
It tastes worse than the food I want.
It tastes terrible.
This is terrible.
It's awful. How can I eat it?
She made it.
She made it. She made it.
You made it?
You did it.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I miss my mom.
How about
Let's try again.
Run!
Mr. Mo, you're sweating.
What is Situ Snow doing?
Why did she come to the nursing home to steal my thunder?
Princess.
It's obvious that she's stealing a man.
Steal a man?
Then I'm relieved.
That stinky ice doesn't like her.
Not necessarily.
I'm a rich girl from Seijoh.
I'm the rich and beautiful nose.
You are you
Actor watch.
Actor table.
Mo Li Chen Ziyou.
Sheng Tao Tao Tao Mo Na.
Shan Yu Ci, Du Rong Yi.
Sheng Tao Tao, Mao, Na Na.
Su Chen from Dongsheng.
Shan Yu Ci, Du Rong Yi.
Second Prince Tong Huaizhou.
Noble Consort Wan, Qi Ning.
Princess of Jinshan, Xu Jiaman.
Prince of Jinshan, Qi Zun.
Situ Snow, Liu Xin Yu.
Princess of Jinshan, Xu Jiaman.
Aunt Wang, Zhao Hongwei.
Aunt Wang, Zhao Hong Wei.
Cheng Yi.
Ma Yi, Yang Yu Chun.
Jia Cheng Yi.
Yang Yu Chun.
Governor Ma, Li Yu.
Old man, Lu Chao.
Big, Jin, He Qio.
Old man 2 Zhou Qiping
Big Jin He Qio
Third gold, Yao Junwen.
Two golden Qi Haoran.
Zhang Honghao,
Zhang Honghao.
Member, Wang Zhiguo.
and actor Zhang Honghao.
and the actors, Tang Jiaxiang.
I’m Wang Jinbiao, an actor.
Hao Xinyu.
and Zhu Rui Xuan.
and a group actor, Li Yang Zhou.
and Wu Qiuli.
and Li Yang Zhou.
and Li Siqing.
and Chen Jiahui.
Mou Zhendong.
Acting director, Li Xiaochao.
Special schedule.
Special schedule
Fanfan dance Wang Yinan
Steward Ma, Huang Fuchung.
Old lady of embroidery, Zhang Yan.
Knife Guest Jiang Guangxu
Old lady of embroidery, Zhang Yanhua.
Knife Customer Jiang Guangxu
Sword client, Yuan Song.
Noble Consort Eunuch Li Junyu
Emperor eunuch Ji Jili
Tang Yuyao, the sleeping minister.
Li Dongdong, envoy of Jin State.
Steward Ma, Huang Fushuang.
Sword client, Yuan Song.
Steward Ma, Huang Fu.
Knife Customer Jiang Guangxu
Sword Customer, Ho Yuan Song.
Swordsman Jiang Guangxu.
Dance girl Liu Ke Yan.
Uncle Li, Gao Wenjun.
Tang Shunhua.
Old Madam, Wei Xinghong.
Uncle Li of Erhu, Tan Shihui
Old Head, Ge Shitian.
The old lady with crutches, remove Dongying.
Old man Ge Shi Tian.
Zhuang, Han, Chen Zhi Wu.
The old lady with crutches, Zhang Dongying.
The troublemaker, Li Long.
Liu Qingquan, boss of Snow Garment Pavilion.
Doctor Jia Andy Wang
Zhuang, Han, Yang Shenzhen
The pregnant lady, Zheng, Ling.
The sweeper, Yuan, Li.
Yuan Li, the cleaner.
Li Zichao, the owner of the Li Store.
Zhuang, Han, Wang Zibo.
Li Zichao, the owner of Liuli Store.
Zhuang, Han, Wang Shade.
Zhuang, Han, Wang Zibo.
Zhuang, Han, Lee Myung-gi.
Zhuang, Han, Wang Shade.
Roh Seol-gi. He's here. He's here.
Lee Myeong-gi. Hello. Hello.
Miss Zhang Jing
Zhuang, Han, Li.
Doctor Jia, Andy Wang.
Li Zichao, the owner of Liuli Store.
Li Zichao.
Wang Min An.
Beggar, beggar, Li Faguang.
Wang Min An, servant of the governor.
refugee Shao Zhikang.
Ranger Shaw Zhikang
Judge A, Chen En Hong.
Contestant Zhang Dengkai.
Zhang Yuhu.
Dance, Han Xiao.
Judge Li Jun.
Dance Liu Ke.
Women and men, Li Army Camp.
Women's Men's Camp.
Woman Gao Dan.
Women, Gao, Dan.
Wang Yue Feng, Minister of Bride Makeup.
Tanghulu, Wang Guohua.
Female beggar, Qiu Mei Sun.
The owner of the steamed bun shop, Chen En Tao.
Paon Jianhua, the sweeper.
Paon Jianhua, the cleaning lady.
Old man Zhang Shufa.
Old man Ge Shi Tian.
Tang Shun Hua.
Old Madam, Wei Xinghong.
Pregnant woman, Zheng Ling.
The old lady with crutches shoved Dongying.
Uncle Li of Erhu, Tan Shihui
Boss Wang Gwanbo
Old Madam, Xu Quanhong.
[Old Madam Seo Kwon-hong]
Staff Form.
Hello. Hello.
The production team
Chief Planner, Xu Jiaman.
[Editor-in-Chief Review: Xu Jiaman]
Qi Ning, Xu Jiaman, Xu Jiaman.
Review. Xu Jiaman.
Producer Tong Huaizhou, Li Feng.
Chief Producer Qi Youning Xu Jiaman
Producer Tong Huaizhou Li Feng
Executive Producer Xu Jiandong
PR Director Wang Shensheng
Publicize Wu Heng Ruo Tan Yaqi
Mr. Lin Ken.
The circulation, Geng.
Mr. Xu Jiaman.
Chen Hao, director of production.
Screenwriter, Xu Jiaman.
Producer Chen Hao
to arrange for Yang Piaqing.
Producer assistant Li Jiaxuan
to make arrangements for Yang Piaqing.
Production assistant Li Jiaxuan
Live Producer He Chongchong
Life Producer Guest Chen Yan
Foreign producer Fang Junqiang
Captain Cherry Hu Mingli
Director team.
Director Li Liming.
Executive director, Li Luhao.
Mr. Baji
Executive Director Li
Mr. Bae. Mr. Jangwen.
Photographer team.
Photographer Guo Lei
Photographer Ding Weihao.
Photographer, Guo Lei.
Photographer Ding Weihao
Photographer Yang Yicheng.
Photographer assistant, Li Lu Yao.
Photographer assistant Chu Yingxu
[Photographer assistant Zeng Xiang Yu]
Ma Cheng, photographer assistant.
Camera assistant Zeng Xiang Hua.
Lighting Team.
Lighting instructor, Tian Bowen.
Lighting Daisuke Wang Ya Peng.
Lighting assistant, Wang Yu Fan.
Lighting assistant Wang Yapeng.
Lighting assistant Yang Jinglong.
Lighting assistant Wang Yufan.
Lighting assistant, Zhang Tian Qi.
Lighting assistant Tang Jiaqi
Lighting assistant Chen Yahui
The recording team.
Recorder Zhang Jiahao
Recording team.
Recording assistant Zhang Bao Cai
Recorder Zhang Jiahao.
Voice assistant Zhang Bao Cai.
Art team.
He Yuhui.
He Yuhui, art instructor.
The prop team leader, Li Yiming.
Li Yiming.
Li Yiming, a prop for the play.
Mr. Cheng Dawei, the head of decoration.
Chen Shencheng
Head of decoration, ChengDawei.
Chen, Zhi, Zhu Lihui.
Chen Zhi, Shi Qing Hua
Chen, Xiang, Liu Chunlin.
Chen, set, Zuo Wentao.
Chen, set, Zuo Wentao,
Chen, set, Cheng Bao Ping.
The prop for the scene, Li Chunming.
Chen Bao Ping.
The prop at the scene, Li Tsui Hua.
Lee Chun-myung.
Props on the scene, Tsuchihua.
The styling team.
The styling instructor, Tian Longfei.
The makeup team leader, Jin Guohua.
Makeup artist Zhang Qifei.
Makeup artist Sun Yiyi
Makeup artist Sun Gao Jie
Makeup artist Sun Yi.
Daisuke, Wang Shen Shen.
Helper Wang, Xia,
The assistant at the scene, Li Minmin.
[Costume Team Leader Zheng Jinmao]
Dai Hui Hui Chao is the main attire.
Costume assistant Ma Yongqiang.
Costume assistant Li Juan.
Kwak Jin-young.
The audition team.
The casting team.
The casting director, Li Xiaochao,
Actor assistant director, Sun Zhaogang.
Acting director Li Xiaochao.
Actor assistant director Mou Zhendong
Actor assistant director, Sun Zhaogang.
The venue team.
He Chongchong, Zhou, Mi, Chen Jia Rui, Lei Xianfa.
Driver.
Chen Yuehui Bao Jiangbin Li Zhenjie Dong Satellite Han Bing, Sun Weigang.
Fang Xiaohua, Ouyang Jun, Kong Weifang, journalist Cao Zhu Chunwei.
post-production.
It's like this.
Seven-wei.
Senwei Culture Co. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd.
Sanwei Culture Co., Ltd.
The project manager, Wang Simeng.
The post-production director, Zhou Xiaoqiao.
Editing Instructor Zheng Shifei
Late production, Alan Liu.
Li Ronghao: Cut. Li Ronghao: Cut. Li Ronghao: Cut. Li Ronghao: Cut. Li Ronghao: Cut.
Video production.
Video technical director, Liu Zhiming.
Video technology, Shin Eun-taek.
Production of subtitles, Li Ang.
DIT Li Ang.
Passenger Wei Heyun.
Personor, Jing Mingrui.
Color maker. Jing Mingrui.
Special effects production.
WIGUANG.
Weiguang Culture Co., Ltd.
of Weiguang Culture Co., Ltd.
Director of Production, Yan Qi.
Project Manager, Lau Jialin.
Production Director Yan Qiqi.
Visual Director Yin Gui Maomao.
Visual guidance, Xie Bing Han.
technical director, Zhang Qianorange.
Project producer Zhao Ziyan
Tinner Zhang Haitao Wang Ningkun
Lighting dyer Li Xueping Cao Shuai
Asst Director Wang Xuya
Lighting dyeer Li Xueping Cao Shuai
Guan Yang Hong.
Animation Director Yang Hongbin.
Animator, Gu, Yu, Wang, Xu, Sun Rui. Pan Bo Guo.
Animator: Gu, Yu, Wang, Xu, Sun Rui. Pan Bo Guo.
The match player, Sun Xiaomeng, Yu Xiaochao.
Matchmaker Sun Xiaomeng Yu Chao
Special effects director Li Xu
Special effects expert Ma Jingwei
Digital painter Bai Yang
Editor of UE5 Ding Ao
Han Shangheng, Lu Peng, Wang Zhen, and Yuan Yuan.
Han Sang Heng, Lu Peng, Wang Zhen, Bao Yuan Yuan.
Gao Xinyi
Product company.
Oscar Xinghe Movie (Wuxi) Co., Ltd.
Big Wing Film.
Joint production company.
[Wuxi Co., Ltd.]
Leopardia Film (Wuxi) Co., Ltd.
Production company.
Zhejiang Strawberry Film Co., Ltd.
Big Wing Film (Dongyang) Co., Ltd.
Exclusive announcement.
[Xiamen Super Yingying Film and Culture Co., Ltd.]
Xiamen SuperYingying Film and Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Ming Xie.
Hengdian Film and TV City.
Hengdian Film Studio
Hengdian Film Studio?