"Episode 12"
Hyejung wanted to take Hari with her.
Miss Min has tendered her resignation.
What am I going to do?
I think she really left.
Min Hari.
How can you leave me like this?
If you leave like this...
If you leave,
then what about me?
Kim Hyejin?
Hyejin, what are you doing here?
Hari!
You didn't leave yet!
You're not gone.
I'm relieved.
I'm so relieved.
How did you come here?
Hey! How can you leave without telling me?
Where are you going to go without me?
Don't go, Hari!
Who said anything about going anywhere?
Weren't you going to
follow your mom to Japan?
No.
I'm here to see my mom leave today.
See her off?
So you're not going with her?
Hey!
After how I've wronged you...
...do you really think I'd run away?
Did you think I'd leave
without telling you?
Then, you're really not leaving?
Of course not.
I'm so happy to hear that!
I thought you were going to leave!
Stop crying.
I'm not going to leave you.
How can I leave you behind?
I'm going to stay close to you...
...and apologise for the rest of my life.
Don't cry.
Did you make up with your mom?
Yes.
We spent time together,
and talked about a lot of things.
I couldn't understand
why she left me when I was a kid,
but I understand now.
Not as her daughter,
but as a woman.
That's good.
Such a relief.
But what happened to you?
Why did you tender your resignation,
and what happened to your phone?
And what about your
clothes and your shoes?
I've realized that I've made
such a foolish mistake,
because I'm still too childish.
My dad gave me my job,
and I've been buying whatever
I wanted with his credit card.
I've been living the easy life.
And I'm sick of all the superficial
guys I've been meeting with.
"Letter of Resignation"
And then...
I...
I went for something...
...that didn't belong to me.
Every time I saw your face,
I felt like crying.
I didn't know what to say or
how to say it,
so I ran away like...
a little child.
And...
I couldn't tell you
what I needed to tell you.
I'm sorry, Hyejin.
I'm really sorry.
Gosh.
I can't believe I did that to you.
I'm so very sorry.
We did narrow the gap,
but we are still second.
We only care about the results.
It's all worthless if we are
not on the top of the rank.
Don't forget that if you
don't make it this last time...
The Most Korea will be gone forever.
And it all depends on you.
So what do you plan to do now?
I'm going to give myself some time.
I'm trying to discover what
I can accomplish on my own.
I think they want you back at the hotel.
I'm never going there again.
From now on, I'm going to
do everything on my own.
Everything!
"Mr Ji"
I'm near your place. Can I see you?
I'm going to take a shower now.
Well, Hari?
I'm going to stop
by the convenience store.
-Should I go with you?
-No!
Take a shower. I'll be right back.
Okay.
Sungjoon.
Yes, Hyejin.
What brings you here at this hour?
Did you leave the office right now?
Wait, I need 10 seconds.
What are you doing?
Three, two, one...
Okay, I'll leave now.
Wait.
What?
I'm just here to see you.
I thought it would lift my spirits.
Are you okay?
You seem really tired.
Do you really have to work so hard
in order to make it to number one?
It's not something I can solve alone.
What do you mean by that?
When I accepted this mission...
I'm not simply aiming
to revive The Most Korea,
but I've accepted responsibility
for my teammates as well.
I'm sure some people will
survive even if The Most disappears...
...but some will be adversely affected.
Like the ones who still
lack experience and abilities.
It's all a part of my responsibility.
I have to take this seriously.
But it's difficult to do it alone.
If you really feel sorry for me...
you can always give me a hug.
I'm sure it'll cheer me up.
I'm being ridiculous again,
after I told you I wouldn't be.
I should get going.
Sleep well.
What the...
You're back?
What's that?
Why are you...
...in my house?
Oh, I took a shower.
I was feeling dirty.
I really like your shower!
The pizza is here!
I didn't order any.
I ordered it because I was hungry.
I didn't have dinner yet.
Hey...
Are you okay?
You seem startled.
I'm sorry.
I've developed some of the ideas
from the meeting, among others.
I've been home for the last two days...
...and my mind started flowing with ideas.
This is why I normally
stay away from these things.
Maybe I'm...
...a genius?
Have you decided to return?
Well, you went out of
your way to convince me.
So I've decided to stay.
This idea is underdeveloped...
...and it's too late
for this kind of article.
New Look's been working on
this idea for three months now.
What?
As for the cafe report,
try to expand beyond
the cafes here in Korea.
It may be interesting
to compare our coffee shops...
...with the ones found in Europe.
You can provide reference to
Woody Allen's "Midnight in Paris".
Look, I figured just as much.
And this...
Let's let Mr Kim Poongho
handle this one.
He's rather meticulous, so he's
good at analyzing this type of data.
For this, you can refer to Miss Cha's
article in last year's August issue.
It should be helpful.
Are you some sort of sage?
How are you keeping tabs on everything?
But what made you change your mind?
I thought you're
not that easy to convince.
I know, right?
I don't know what convinced me.
I think I'm starting to have fun again.
The threat of our magazine
closing down is giving me motivation.
I enjoy games where the odds
are stacked against me.
As you know, I'm a lunatic.
I won't give up without giving it a try...
...until the bitter end.
We still have a 50-to-50 chance.
I should get going.
If you dream about me,
handle it on your end.
That's ridiculous.
I'm sorry, I can't make it this time.
No, just something funny came up,
nothing special.
I missed you, too.
Let me call you back soon, all right?
Okay, bye.
I'm late, I'm late...
Wife, jacket!
Thank you!
I'm off now.
Oh, wait.
Are your eyebrows too dark?
There you go.
-Go, go, go!
-See you!
Oh right.
Well...
Have I ever told you that I love you?
Gosh.
I love you!
Have a good one!
And stop running!
Wife, make lots of money!
Jackson!
Mr Kim!
Want a taste?
Mr Kim, have you come back to us?
Maybe?
Come on, Jackson!
I thought you were gone for good!
I really thought you
went somewhere else!
I'm so relieved now!
Why are you so happy to see me?
You're making me emotional.
You look like a puppy
that's happy to see me.
♪ Wag your tail and bark for joy
Let's go, Coco.
Why haven't you been showing up
for work?
Why do you suppose that is?
Do I really have to tell you?
By any chance, was it because of me?
Do you really think
I almost quit my job because of you?
Because I told you how I feel about you,
and you rejected me?
My goodness... What's wrong with me?
Why would you quit your job because of me?
You're right.
It was because of you, Jackson.
What?
Ever since you kicked me to the curb...
I have a huge hole in my heart.
And work just wasn't that fun anymore.
Well, Mr Kim...
-About that day...
-But I'm fine now.
I'm starting to enjoy this again!
So what made you enjoy it again?
Hello.
So what made you return?
Who knows?
Oh, right.
Jackson, have you
ever heard of this quote?
"It's not over until it's over."
Sure, Yogi Berra said that.
You're a smart one, aren't you?
But what does that have
to do with anything?
It just crossed my mind.
It's not over until it's over.
Pretty inspirational, right?
What's he talking about?
Buongiorno!
Kim Shinhyuk!
Shinhyuk!
Oh, my!
-That lunatic.
-I'm back.
What happened?
Can you welcome me back
with a little less violence?
Seriously, where were you?
Things are going to get noisy
around here again.
How is the main interview coming along
for our 20th anniversary issue?
Well, we're trying to
get a hold of Leonard Kim, but...
Leonard Kim?
Are you talking about
the fashionista-turned-director...
...who recently won awards for his movies?
He's really hot these days.
But he's notorious
for avoiding interviews.
Do you think he'll work with us?
Well, Mr Ji.
I think we're over our heads here.
Maybe we should switch to Kim Shinae?
Why?
We can't give up now!
It's not like we have
a zero percent chance.
He's notoriously private,
so if we get a hold of him...
We'll have the perfect story.
If we're the first Asian magazine
to work with him...
Then we're bound to be
number one in domestic sales.
New Look was able to
land Hollywood stars...
So why is it impossible for us
to land Leonard Kim?
Am I right?
When did the two of them
start cooperating?
I don't know.
When did they grow close?
Yes, let's challenge
those guys at New Look.
It's our 20th anniversary issue,
so let's grab the top spot!
You seem awfully motivated.
Did something happen to you
while you were away?
Okay. We'll continue
to pursue Leonard Kim.
Wait, your nose is bleeding!
Your nose.
My goodness.
Blood!
Sit down, sit down.
Throw your head back.
No, no! Lower your head.
What are you saying?
You're supposed to throw your head back.
-You're supposed to lean forward!
-You're supposed to lean back!
-You don't know anything!
-What do you know about a nosebleed?
I'm okay!
I'm fine.
You have a show to attend
at Jeju Island tomorrow.
Are you going to be okay?
You seem a bit tired...
I'm okay. I'll take care of it.
You have to throw your head back.
He's been looking pale, too.
Didn't he get enough sleep?
Maybe he's not eating right.
Hyejin, what language is that?
Are you communicating with aliens?
Yes?
Oh...
ET go home.
Not amused?
I found it so funny.
Here's the meeting log.
Thank you, Kim Hyejin.
But are you okay?
You were bleeding earlier.
Yes, I'm fine.
You don't look so well.
I'm really okay.
What can I do to make you believe me?
Maybe I should lift my chair.
-Or maybe the desk?
-Okay, forget it.
You're fine, I get it.
I feel good.
Because you're worried about me.
Well, carry on, Mr Ji.
Mr Ji.
Burdock tea is supposed
to be good for nosebleeds.
I think it's better than coffee.
"Joonwoo"
After work, let's go to
that spicy noodle restaurant again.
I'm sorry, I'm not feeling well today.
Why? What's wrong?
-Are you okay?
-No, well...
My head hurts a little...
Why does your head hurt?
Maybe you're coming down with a cold?
Or the flu?
Do you have a fever?
Are you getting the chills?
Let me see.
Oh, my. Han Seol, maintain yourself!
Don't show any emotion!
No, it's not that bad.
Ahreum!
Hyejin.
Yes?
Can we postpone our meeting
concerning your article to tomorrow?
I need to meet with
the art team later today.
Okay, let me know
when you have spare time.
Sorry.
I nominate Mr Kim Shinhyuk for the task!
He's full of ideas,
and he's a great writer as well.
I'll help you out.
Kim Shinhyuk.
-Thanks.
-I know.
I'll leave it to you.
Well, I could wait until
you have the time...
Jackson, you're not uncomfortable
around me, are you?
Seriously?
No, of course not.
I've been giving you a hard time, so...
Okay, we'll let the coin decide.
Heads, I help you with your article.
And tails, we forget
the whole thing, okay?
No.
The general's face, so it's heads!
That's not heads, it's tails!
You told me that the general
was tails the last time!
It turns out you were right.
The general's face is heads.
I've checked with
the Korean Minting Corporation.
You've checked with
the Korean Minting Corporation?
Then we'll have our meeting in 10 minutes.
Was the number always tails?
He said it was heads the other day!
Is it heads or tails?
Did you really write this, Jackson?
You've got the basics down,
and you've got a great premise.
But take a look at this, Jackson.
If you can't hook your audience
with the very first line...
...you've already lost them.
For instance.
Now, compare these two articles.
The items are the same.
But which one stands out more?
This one, right?
Me, too. Why? Because I wrote it.
You want to be impactful
right off the bat.
Then your readers
will continue to read...
In order to write a killer article,
you have to constantly gather ideas.
Make a scrapbook of any
good articles you come across.
When you have writer's block,
you can refer to your scrapbook...
...and ideas will start
popping like soda pop.
Wow, I never knew you were
so good at this.
You're like a completely different person.
You've finally realized it?
So do you see me
in a different light now?
What?
I have to agree that there's nothing
more attractive than a capable man.
My professionalism probably
seems sexy to you.
Does it make your heart skip a beat?
No, well, Mr Kim.
I haven't shown you the real me yet.
And what kind of man I could be.
Remember I told you?
It's not over until it's over.
Well, Mr Kim.
I really, really like you...
Is that so?
I didn't know that you
really, really like me!
-What?
-Okay, I get it.
You really, really like me.
I see it now.
That's it.
Well, Mr Kim. Mr Kim!
Gosh.
That's not what I meant.
Han Seol.
Wait a second.
You do have a bit of a fever.
I wasn't sure, so I got you
several different medications.
This is for migraines,
this one's for the flu...
...and this is for a runny nose.
If you get a fever, take this.
Joonwoo, where were you?
Follow me, we're going to the agency.
Yes, ma'am.
You can't take medication
on an empty stomach...
...so be sure to eat something. Okay?
Don't get sick!
Make sure you eat something!
Kim Joonwoo.
Why do you have to be
so kind and lovable?
Why can't you be the chairman's son?
It's my lucky day!
Follow the ladder!
I got it, I got it!
Why can't they be quiet
so he can get some sleep?
Are you trying to fight us?
-What are you doing?
-What's the matter?
I'll pay for lunch today.
-Really?
-I really want to pay for lunch today.
Wow, jackpot!
I've already eaten,
so everyone go on without me.
Go on and enjoy your lunch.
What's with you?
What are you doing, my dear?
What?
Oh, my!
Your lipstick is smudged.
There you go.
You look very Most-esque again.
Thank you very much.
Ouch...
Jackson, you're here?
Why?
You want to have some fun together?
What's your idea of fun?
-Anything but this.
-What?
-Let's go.
-I have to deliver this to Poongho.
He can wait for another 30 minutes,
and it won't kill him.
Relax! Sometimes you need
to take a breather.
-Tea time!
-Oh, no.
I'll have an iced Americano.
Then I'll have an Americano, too.
Will your girlfriend have it iced as well?
What?
Well, I'm not his...
She's not my girlfriend.
Yet.
Let me get a slice of that cake, too.
-Sure.
-Mr Kim.
Well, Mr Kim.
I really do like you a lot.
There you go pouring your heart out again.
I already know that you really,
really like me.
Right?
Well...
How should I put this?
-So what I'm trying to say is...
-Is this why you like me?
Oh, my!
Just looking at me makes you smile.
No, what I'm trying to say is...
Wait, is this why you like me then?
My tooth! I've lost my tooth!
Mr Kim!
You're making me feel uncomfortable!
-You don't like me, Jackson?
-Of course not.
Why wouldn't I like you?
Then I've still got a chance.
Remember?
It's not over until it's over.
You'll eventually be mine, Jackson.
See you around.
Mr Kim! Mr Kim!
Why is he making me feel so bad?
"She Was Pretty"
You're back?
Come here and have a slice of pizza.
Hey, Kim Hye-rin,
what are you doing here?
Hari has some extra time now.
I wanted to talk to her
about this and that.
Oh! Is that Sungjoon calling you?
No, it's not!
Yes, Miss Cha.
I've already emailed that to you.
Yes, see you tomorrow.
I'm going to get changed
and join you for dinner!
Hari!
There's a guy following Hyejin around.
And do you want to know the funny thing?
She's playing hard to get!
Isn't it comedy?
He seems to be an old friend,
but he's either blind
or he's got low standards.
It's one or the other.
Hey my little sister, have your fill!
That way you'll grow nice and tall!
What are you doing?
He even came over
to our house the other day.
Hey! You're so cute!
You're so adorable!
You're just drop dead gorgeous,
aren't you?
Can you let go of me now?
It hurts!
Wife.
Come here.
Ta-da!
What's this?
Open it.
Gosh.
Why did you get me shoes
all of a sudden?
I promised to get you a pair.
So, do you like it?
It's so pretty...
But I don't think I can pull this off.
Why don't you change it
for one in your size?
I'll wear something more comfortable.
Hyejin, don't you know that
a good pair of shoes...
...can take you to a good place?
What?
Wear these shoes
and go somewhere great.
Don't think about anything,
and don't worry about anything.
Go wherever you please.
Wherever you want to go.
It'll feel uncomfortable at first,
and you may have trouble walking.
But you'll quickly get used to it.
Eventually, you'll get comfortable.
Hari, I like how things are now.
Hey, stop being ignorant.
Don't worry about me
and just go to Ji Sungjoon.
If you keep acting like this,
it'll make me feel uncomfortable!
I don't care if I remain
just friends with Sungjoon.
When I was pursuing Ji Sungjoon...
...all he could think about was you.
He's probably having
a hard time waiting for you.
I'm really okay.
I really am.
To be honest,
I wasn't really okay before.
But now...
It's for real.
I'm really okay.
So, Hyejin.
Just go.
And don't worry about anything else.
Okay?
I'm not going to pressure you.
Just don't run away from me.
You're just a girl I've grown to like.
Hey Princess, what are you doing?
Princess?
Waiting is harder...
...than I thought it would be.
I don't even have any water.
Hi, Princess.
Wait.
That scarf!
When did he stop by?
I'm not going to run away anymore.
Bye!
Wife, come here.
Hari.
I want to drop you off for the last time.
I'm going to drop you off
and then sell my car.
Thanks, see you later.
Good luck selling the car.
Okay.
Hyejin!
Yes?
Those shoes look great on you!
My Hyejin, you're so pretty!
You're the best!
Go, Hyejin!
Gosh.
It feels so good!
Good morning!
-Have you arrived?
-Good morning.
Is he here yet?
He hasn't arrived yet.
Mr Ji hasn't come to the office yet?
I need his confirmation on this.
Mr Ji and I had a meeting
with the art team this morning.
And he had another meeting afterward.
He left just moments ago.
Hyejin, thanks for lunch...
See you.
Anyone wants to go in
on a ladder for coffee?
Oh, thanks.
I'll see him at the office later.
Miss Cha, here are
the translations you asked.
-Oh, thank you.
-Sure.
Ta-da! The coffee has arrived!
-Coffee?
-Thank you.
I want iced coffee.
This one.
-Oh, take these.
-Thank you.
Oh! I ran into Photographer Kang
at the coffee shop.
He was in a meeting with Mr Ji.
Really?
What's this?
Didn't you put any sugar in mine?
Oh, I forgot.
Give it to me!
I'll go and get you some sugar!
You don't have to.
Aren't you Hyejin?
Oh.
Hello, Photographer Kang.
But where's Mr Ji?
Oh, did you want to see him?
Didn't you see him leave moments ago?
I guess I'll see him in the office later.
Yes, Mr Ji.
A car will be ready for you
at the airport in Jeju.
Will you be back on the 4 PM flight?
Then I suppose you'll be back
at the office after 6 PM.
Yes.
Yes, I'll see you later. Have a safe trip.
My goodness.
Hyejin, what are you doing?
Well...
No, it's nothing.
Right, he was heading
to Jeju Island today.
"Weather in Jeju Island"
I hope it doesn't rain when he gets there.
I wonder if he had something to eat.
Jackson, time for a meeting.
She's fallen asleep.
Jackson.
Can you look my way?
Hyejin, where are the documents
from Jungin Publishing?
Oh, Mr Ji wanted to look over those.
Really?
Can you take them for me?
-Sure.
-Thanks.
Jungin Publishing...
It'll end up sticking together!
Why do you need your mouth
to put on a bandage?
Wow, this movie looks amazing.
I want to see it now.
I want to see him.
Really? You want to see the movie, too?
Then you want to join the screening?
I'll be right back.
Hyejin, where are you going?
To a good place.
Yes, Miss Cha.
I've arrived earlier than expected.
I'll see you when I get back.
"Welcome, Ji Sungjoon"
Excuse me, are you okay?
Call an ambulance!
-Are you okay?
-Someone is unconscious here.
Are you okay?
Why isn't he arriving?
He's not getting his phone.
Oh, no.
So what happened?
We're fortunate
it wasn't something serious.
I know.
Of course he would faint
considering how much he's overworked.
Yes, okay.
Poongho, you take good care of him.
Bye.
Did someone faint?
Mr Ji.
I was shocked when I heard
from the hospital earlier.
He collapsed at the airport.
Why was he working so hard?
His body couldn't handle the stress.
Jackson.
Jackson, where are you going?
Taxi!
Jackson, get in.
I can't.
I have to go see Sungjoon right now.
I know, get in.
No, wait.
Go on inside.
Mr Kim.
It's okay, go on.
You're really worried about him right now.
I feel so bad for doing this to you.
You're such a nice person.
You've been so good to me.
I've always had a great time with you.
You're so very good to me...
Goodness, Jackson.
You're such a softy.
Okay, then.
Let's flip a coin one last time.
If it's heads,
you go without turning back...
...and if it's tails,
you'd better get ready.
Because I won't let you go.
Here we go.
Go, Jackson.
It's heads.
Mr Kim...
Thanks for...
...hesitating for me.
If you don't leave now,
I may change my mind.
"Ji Sungjoon, Male"
Wow, it's Kim Hyejin.
What brings you here?
Were you worried about me?
No.
I'm here to give you a hug.
"She Was Pretty"
Hyejin.
Yes?
Don't feel bad for me, and stop
making things weird between us!
You're so uncool.
It would've been nice if you met her...
...from the very beginning.
The two of them are holding hands!
I thought you only wanted
to see me for 10 seconds?
Hi.
From now on, we'll suffer together!
I won't leave you alone again.