"Episode 7"
What is this uncomfortable silence?
Wow, it's such a clear day!
Please close the window,
I prefer silence.
Yes. We'll go in silence.
Wow, these are cool sunglasses!
You're going to get smudges on them.
I know. We don't want any smudges.
I'll take over the wheel
at the next rest stop.
I'm not planning to make any stops.
I think we should
head directly there as well.
Do you think this is a vacation?
No.
I've got a lot of things on my mind,
so can we go quietly?
Sure.
I'm trying to be quiet,
but I'm having trouble controlling it.
What's this?
Why does he have to be so cold?
If you were going to be this way,
why did you give me the onion?
What?
Never mind.
Please carry on.
Please take a look at this...
-Hey!
-I've seen it already.
When is Kim Shinhyuk going to grow up?
Probably never.
No one gives a reaction
quite like Jackson.
Jackson...
Wow, this air is so fresh!
Why don't we fill ourselves with food
instead of air?
Okay.
-How do you do?
-Hello.
Would you like to order?
What would you like?
I'll have the vegetable bibimbap.
We'll have two tenderloin specials.
No, I want the vegetable.
Isn't that too expensive?
Do you have a problem with the price...
...when I'm the one who's paying?
You should really try our raw meat plate.
It's direct from the farm,
so the meat is really fresh.
We'll take an order of that, too.
Sure!
Two tenderloin specials
and one raw meat platter!
It's so expensive!
I think it's going to be too much.
I'm not going to ask you to pay,
so don't worry about it.
I already told you that it's on me.
Who left their wallet here like this?
They went together,
so it should be all right.
Maybe he left it here on purpose?
That's smart.
The meat that we bring in are fresh...
...and of top quality.
It practically melts in your mouth.
Is it done yet?
It's to die for!
My goodness.
Sorry about the grease.
Would you like an apron?
Aren't you going to wear one?
I don't care about my clothes.
Oh, right... My employee badge.
I don't want this to get dirty.
Are you dating the badge?
Why must you wear
that on a business trip?
This is my greatest possession.
Simply wearing it gives me strength.
I don't know
how I should interpret that scoff.
Oh, no.
That seems awfully provocative.
If you take it off,
you'll get grease on your clothes.
Let's eat.
What do you keep looking at?
Quit staring at me.
I'm sorry.
What the...
You've had a feast.
That will be 185 dollars.
Yes.
It's 185 dollars.
Sure.
185 dollars!
I already told you
that I'm paying for it.
Thank you for the meal!
That was the best meat I've ever tasted!
Well...
Let me borrow some...
What did you say? I couldn't hear
because of that motorcycle.
I left it back at the office,
my wallet.
Let me use your card
during the business trip.
Is there something wrong
with this machine?
You don't have enough balance.
You're short 40 dollars.
Really?
What should I do?
We can pay you when
the rest of our team gets here.
What?
So you can skip out on your tab?
We're not those kinds of people.
Then I can leave you with my ID.
My goodness. Unbelievable.
I'll leave this as collateral,
and when our people arrive,
we'll come back to pay you.
I won't put up with this!
I have a truckload of these!
These are worth a dollar!
Give me my 40 dollars.
This isn't worth a dollar.
This is part of
the 2015 FW Paris collection.
I don't care where it's from!
This won't do.
Honey, call the police.
We've got a problem here!
These people are crazy!
I can't believe they're ripping me off!
How far are you?
We're passing Daejeon now.
Daejeon?
Why are you in Daejeon when you're
supposed to head to Kangwon Province?
It's the opposite direction.
Oh, my, what am I going to do?
I thought it was
in the Kyungsang Province!
So it's Kangwon Province?
What am I going to do?
Yes, I'll turn the car around right away.
Why? Is something wrong?
We're supposed to be in Kangwon Province,
not Kyungsang.
I had no idea.
What?
How can you make that kind of mistake?
How long will it take us
to get there from here?
Call the police.
Wait, hold on.
I'll call my friend
and tell her to wire the money.
Why isn't she picking up?
She's not picking up?
Are you sure it's not on purpose?
Don't pull any funny business,
and give the phone to me when she does.
Okay.
Can you call someone
and ask them to send you some money?
I don't have anyone I can call.
Not a single person?
No one.
How can you not know a single person?
I'm going crazy!
That's Shinhyuk's phone.
I wonder where he is?
He's in a meeting with Photographer Kang.
Gosh.
Isn't Jackson supposed to be Hyejin?
Yes, Hyejin.
Hello?
Yes, hello!
Are you acquaintances with a Kim Hyejin?
Who is this?
Yes, Kim Hyejin needs to pay her tab...
...but her card has been declined.
Please send money
to her account for her tab.
Look here, Lady.
This is rather awkward.
How are you going to
make a living with that script?
Practise your pitch
and try again later, okay?
What a joke.
No one pick up Hyejin's calls.
Why, Ms Cha?
I can't believe that they're
phishing through cell phones now.
It was a voice phishing attempt
from Hyejin's number.
I can tell it's fake.
Really? Oh, my!
I'm getting the same call!
Don't pick it up, Ms Joo.
I'm not falling for this.
Beat it, you phisher!
Why isn't anyone picking up?
Gosh.
What should we do?
What else can you do?
You'll need to work off the rest.
Change into this. This is your uniform.
I don't know what you want us to do...
...but I'm not going to wear this.
Change into it.
Take a look.
This is my farm.
I want you to clean the cow manure,
40 dollars' worth.
What?
You want us to scoop cow poop?
How can you expect us to do that?
I'll call the police then.
Hello?
-Things are crazy over here!
-We'll scoop the poop!
If we don't, the police
will come here, so just do it!
But, I've got a weak stomach!
Why did you have to order the
tenderloin special and raw meat plate?
I can hear you.
And I'm sure you ate much
more than I did.
If I knew you were broke, I would've
settled for the vegetable bibimbap!
You ordered
an extra bowl of cold noodles!
If you didn't order that,
we'd be scooping five dollars less.
Why are you changing the story now?
You told me that I could order that!
Just get back to cleaning the poop.
If we stuck with the bibimbap,
we wouldn't be going through this.
Again, I can hear you.
Cow poop!
Cow poop.
Are you okay?
Do I look okay to you?
Gosh!
I can't do this!
The ma'am, the ma'am!
We should pick up the pace.
How much poop is 40 dollars' worth?
These are good.
They're plump and tasty.
Thank you for the food!
I'm going to eat all of it by myself.
You're eating it all again?
Of the countless things
we can eat in this world,
why are we eating this kind of meat?
You don't know
how great this tastes, do you?
-Try it, it's delicious.
-That's disgusting!
I feel like politely refusing.
Put aside your reservations,
and just try it once.
Disgusting.
-Open wide.
-This is wrong.
She really enjoyed
eating this disgusting thing.
Forget this!
-What are you doing?
-Lunatic.
Are you crazy?
It touched the fish cake!
I really wanted the fish cake!
You just want to eat everything yourself.
What are you doing?
Over there.
There?
Enjoy!
Come here, baby!
Dig in!
Eat a lot!
This is so much poop!
-This has to go up there!
-Stop, stop, stop.
A little more.
We're done.
Here.
I dragged it all the way here,
so you bring it back.
What?
Seriously?
Why don't we keep this experience
between us?
Why?
What's wrong with scooping cow poop?
Scooping poop because we
couldn't pay for the tab...
...is nothing to brag about.
Okay.
If it bothers you that much,
we'll keep it a secret.
You've finally worked enough
to pay your tab.
You can wash up over there.
Yes.
What?
My name badge!
Where did it go?
I had it just moments ago!
You lost your badge?
Yes. Where did I drop it?
So, why did you have to wear it
everywhere?
Forget it.
We don't have time,
so we'll need to wash up and get going.
I really need my company badge!
You can always have
another one issued to you.
Let's get going.
We've lost enough time already.
It may not be important to you,
but it's important to me.
I can't leave it buried
under a mound of poop.
After I wash, I'm leaving
in 20 minutes, no matter what!
Gosh...
Seriously. Where did it go?
My badge, my badge.
My badge.
My badge!
Where did you find it?
I found it on the ground.
Where on the ground?
I looked everywhere for it!
Are you sure you were
searching carefully?
I found it on the ground in plain view.
I'm so relieved.
Thank you very much.
I wouldn't kiss that.
-Let's go now.
-Okay.
Hey, young man!
What happened to the compost pile?
Did you dig through all of that manure?
Did you really dig through
all of that cow poop?
To find this for me?
What?
I already told you that
I found it on the ground.
These flies.
-Goodbye!
-Bye.
See you around.
Did they lose some gold?
This is my very first time.
First time working for a great company...
...and the first time
I've had my picture on anything.
While I was job hunting,
I used to envy people
who had work badges.
So every time I look at my badge...
...I'm thankful and it fills me with joy.
It reminds me that there's
a place for me in this company.
It's proof that
I'm a part of the company.
I'm taking this work badge thing
a bit too far, aren't I?
Yes, a bit too far.
But I do understand to a certain degree.
Everyone has a few things
that are precious...
...which seem worthless to others.
What kinds of things do you have?
The thing you shattered the other day.
What?
What's this? What are you doing here?
Oh, that.
Why the hand?
What are you doing right now?
What?
I'm asking you to repay me
for the shattered glass.
What?
My goodness.
Oh, you don't have the money right now.
Send it to me when we get back to Seoul.
My account number is 0820492...
Wait, wait.
What was after 08204?
You're too easy to take advantage of.
Haven't you ever heard of a joke before?
I'll pay you back!
What was after 04?
Well, it cost me 1,000 dollars.
Okay, I get the joke.
Do we have time to be doing this?
I told you that we're fine.
He told us to take our time.
Oh, my, this chair is dirty.
This one, too.
I think I'll have to sit next to you.
Let's eat and get out of here.
Okay.
We're not going anywhere.
First, I'll find the perfect moment
for the car to break down.
What's the matter with my car?
Why, why?
Oh, no, I think my car broke down!
It won't start?
No, it's not starting.
Do you have anything in here?
This isn't working.
Then, I act like I'm making
a call to the service centre.
Is this the service centre?
Our car broke down here.
We're in the countryside.
There are mountains here.
And I can see rice fields all around me.
There are also lots of foxtails.
The sky is beautiful here.
The sun will eventually go down.
Oh, my, Joonwoo. Look at the stars.
They're so pretty, aren't they?
As we stargaze together,
naturally we'll...
...kiss.
Then as of today, my boyfriend will be...
...Kim Joonwoo, the son
of the Jinsung Group's chairman.
And I'll be hitting the biggest
jackpot of my life!
Why aren't you eating?
Well, I am eating.
Wow, it's the ocean!
Right, we're here for work.
Oh, this is nice.
Oh, this is nice!
Let's look around.
Then I'd like to make
a phone call before we begin.
If the other two is going to be late,
we need money for dinner.
I'll need someone to wire us some money.
But you're really going to
pay me back, right?
Serious?
I'll sign a promissory note then.
My goodness.
You're pretty gullible yourself, Mr Ji.
I was only kidding.
Go ahead and make your call.
Yes, sir.
Yes, Hyejin.
Do you want to have dinner
with me later tonight?
Well...
How about at 8 PM in Kangwon Province?
Why Kangwon?
Oh, you're on a business trip,
aren't you?
Are you coming back tomorrow?
Sungjoon, I'm getting another call.
I'll call you back.
Yes, I'll call you
when I get back to Seoul.
Yes.
Hey, wife.
You weren't getting your phone all day.
I know.
I was involved in some labour earlier.
What are you talking about?
I'll tell you when I get back to Seoul.
Hari, I need to borrow some money.
What?
Why do I feel like you're phishing me?
We need money right now,
but I have no money in my account.
Yes, okay. I'll send it right away.
Oh, and I'll be back tomorrow.
I got caught up
with a business trip at work.
A business trip?
With whom?
Ji Sungjoon.
Just the two of you?
Well, as of now.
But our teammates are joining us
later tonight.
Oh, I see.
Thanks!
What? Yes.
Sure.
I think this belongs to you.
Ahreum, aren't you going home?
Go home? It's only 4 PM.
What?
It's only 4 PM?
It really is.
It's only 4:00.
I thought it was about seven.
Isn't time going so slow today?
Good. If you're not busy,
you can do this for me.
I'm going out for some fresh air.
Hey!
Why, that...
Are you sure that you know the way?
Why are we still in the countryside?
I know the way.
This is...
...a shortcut.
That's odd...
Hey, you're sweating.
-Are you okay?
-What?
I'm totally...
...not fine.
Oh, no.
I think something was wrong
with the fish I had earlier.
What am I going to do?
I need to use the restroom.
You have indigestion?
Bathroom.
Oh, no, I don't see
any bathrooms around here.
I can't hold it much longer.
I need a bathroom!
-This is crazy!
-What am I going to do?
Hey, hey! Isn't that a bathroom?
Where, where?
Yes, it is!
I thought I was going to die.
But...
Why did this have to happen
in front of Kim Joonwoo?
It's okay.
You can handle this, Seol.
What's this?
Why is this happening?
Han Seol, are you okay?
Hey, can you give me some tissue?
What?
I need tissue, tissue.
What? I can't hear you, speak louder.
Give me some tissue!
There's no tissue here!
Oh, tissue?
It's all over now!
No, it's okay.
You can handle this, Seol.
You can do it.
Are you okay?
It's only a natural
physiological phenomenon.
Let's go.
Since we're here,
I should use the restroom too.
It's okay, you can manage this, Seol.
You can't handle this!
This is so humiliating! It's all over!
Han Seol, are you okay?
That was the smell of compost.
Can't you see that
we're surrounded by it?
You've got to know that!
All right, let me help you get up.
That wasn't me, it was the compost!
Why? Does your leg hurt?
Yes.
You've sprained it really badly.
Do you think you can still drive?
No, I can't. You'll have to drive.
I don't have a license.
What?
Why isn't my little sister
getting her phone?
Yes, Kim Joonwoo.
How's the location hunt coming along?
It's an emergency.
We're barely halfway there,
and we're stranded.
What?
Han Seol sprained her leg,
so she can't drive.
And I don't have a license.
Hey, what about Jackson?
I mean, Hyejin.
She's gone ahead with the deputy chief.
Hey, hey.
Turn around. I've got the runs again.
Hey, let go of me!
-Hey, I've got to go.
-Hurry! Hurry!
Hey, Kim Joonwoo. Hey, you!
Wait.
Does that mean Jackson is alone with him?
This is an overnight business trip.
Mr Ji.
We can see the lighthouse from here,
so isn't this place perfect?
It's also perfect for our theme
of vacationing alone.
I guess so.
It's not bad.
Do you draft the plans yourself?
Yes, well whatever comes into my head.
That's really cool.
I'm thinking about monotone colours.
We want to portray the loneliness
while vacationing alone.
We should also include a lamp
and some letterheads on the table.
Letterheads?
Even if you come here alone...
...you'd want to write about it
and tell someone.
And sometimes you
feel like sending a letter...
...instead of making a phone call.
I'm sure the person would
rather be here at the ocean...
...with someone special.
So this person might
light a bonfire alone...
...drink some warm tea...
...and maybe take a few Polaroid pictures.
The person would probably
have a great time.
Because he wants to tell that special...
...someone that this is a great place...
...and that they should come together
next time.
Portraying letters and postcards
would change the theme...
...from loneliness to one of anticipation.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I think I took it too far again.
Like I know anything!
Come to think of it,
I've experienced that before.
Anticipating letters.
What are you going to do
with all that bread?
You're not going to eat
all these, are you?
What? You're going to cry?
Come on, cry!
Come on, come on.
When I moved overseas as a kid...
...I couldn't speak the language
and I had no friends.
But I had a friend who would
send me letters from Korea.
I wanted to tell her
that I was doing well...
...and that I was adjusting well.
I think she gave me the courage
to stay strong and survive.
Although, when the letters
stopped arriving...
...I was a bit heartbroken.
I see.
Anyway, I guess we'll end up
with a warmer feature article.
Good idea!
I should finish up the sketches.
Are there any better locations?
How do you do?
Your dog is so pretty! How old is he?
He's three years old.
-What's his name?
-His name is Professor.
So cute!
Bye now!
Bye.
Yes, Ms. Cha.
We've found a great location.
I'll send you some photos
I took with my phone.
All right!
Kim Hyejin.
Why don't we wrap things
up here and move on?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Is something on my face?
No.
It's just my first time.
Your first time for what?
It's the first time I heard you
call me by my name.
You were always like,
"Look here, Support".
I didn't always refer to you
as "Look here, Support"!
Look here, Support.
Hey, look here, Support.
Still, isn't that more appropriate
than Crazy Joon?
-How do you feel about that?
-Pardon?
That nickname is perfect for him,
Crazy Joon.
Look here, you Crazy Joon...
I wasn't the one who created
that nickname.
Let's go have some dinner.
Gosh.
How can you call me Crazy Joon?
You've got the wrong idea.
It wasn't me who referred to you as that.
You can always pay back
that 1,000 dollars.
What? That has nothing to do with this.
How can you call me Crazy Joon?
I told you, it wasn't me!
What are you doing?
I don't eat peas.
It doesn't taste very good
and it's all mushy.
I don't know why people eat it.
Why are you laughing?
You just reminded me of someone.
Oh, it's a Rubik's cube.
Oh, my. I solved it!
I solved it! I must be a genius.
You've only solved one side.
Let me see that. I'll solve it for you.
I only need 30 seconds.
Wow, you're fast!
It's not working.
What was that? This takes brains...
...but I guess you're
not some genius, either.
I'm good at anything that takes brains!
You know, the video game
where you stack blocks...
What was the name of that game?
-That, right?
-Yes, that! The name was...
-Tetris!
It takes me a tenth of a second
to drop each block.
I think so fast,
that you can hardly keep up.
And you've got
the wrong jingle for Tetris.
That's the main melody.
No, it's not! Tetris goes...
You're completely wrong.
You have a knack for arguing, Kim Hyejin.
You're wrong, I tell you!
Did you like girl groups?
Of course I did!
One, two, three!
-SES!
Which SES member?
-One, two, three.
Did you watch dramas?
Yes, I did.
What did you like to watch?
-Star in my Heart!
-That's amazing!
-My goodness.
-Looking here and there.
-Michael.
You have the same hairstyle.
If you are the same age as me,
I bet you know this very well.
-The one with pointy hair...
-I know.
I'm really sorry,
but we're closing for the night.
Oh, really?
Wow, look at the time.
We were here for a long time.
Yes.
-Should we get going?
-Yes, of course.
I'm so sorry.
Are you still sick?
No, I'm fine.
I think something
got caught in my throat.
I forgot to thank you for that.
Thank you for that day.
It's going to be okay.
It's okay.
Nothing's going to happen.
Yes, well.
My mother died...
...when I was 12.
She was in a car accident on a rainy day.
Mum.
Ever since that day,
I had a hard time driving in the rain.
I keep getting the feeling...
...that I'll be in the same
kind of accident.
I was doing fine for a while...
...but I don't know
what happened that day.
But why am I talking about this?
Was there whiskey in my dessert?
Wow!
I wish I could take half
of this back to Seoul.
I thought you had become
a completely different person.
I thought my gentle, pudgy
friend Sungjoon disappeared forever.
But you're still the same.
If I didn't hide from you like a fool,
we'd be laughing comfortably
together like right now.
And I'd be there for you
during your difficult times.
Sungjoon!
Today...
...I think I could come clean today.
That I'm your friend, Kim Hyejin.
I think I can tell you everything...
on a day like today.
Yes, Mr Ji.
I don't think she can drive right now.
Yes, I'm sorry.
I'll see you back at the company.
Yes, sir.
That was the smell of compost.
Can't you see that
we're surrounded by it?
You've got to know that!
Hey, hey.
Turn around. I've got the runs again...
She's kind of cute.
I'm done for! My life is over!
Ouch!
It's all over.
I'm done for.
I'm about to tell you something
that might surprise you.
Have you ever heard that...
...some memories
are best kept in the past.
And that memories are most beautiful
when they're reminisced?
I felt that way until recently.
But today...
...I realized
that it might not be the case.
Kim Hyejin,
what are you trying to tell me?
Mr Ji.
-To be honest...
-Hey, Sister!
You owe me sea snails!
I, Kim Hyejin, promise to grant
Kim Shinhyuk three favours!
See, you've made me a promise!
Are you trying to back out of our deal?
What sea snails?
Who comes all the way
to Kangwon Province for sea snails?
Me.
I'm kidding.
Joonwoo couldn't make it,
so I'm filling in for him.
I thought you might need help
hunting for a location.
I didn't know that you work so hard.
Let's go inside.
Since I just got here, we should
have a drink before we call it a night!
I don't drink.
Then go on ahead.
-We'll go after we've had a drink.
-What?
Let's go.
They have non-alcoholic beer these days.
Why did you come here?
Why do you think?
Let's go, Little Sister.
Hey, it's nice to be away from the city!
But since I came here in such a hurry...
...I didn't pack any underwear.
Do you have any underwear
that I can borrow?
Did you leave yours with me?
I'm not an underwear merchant...
...so stop talking
about underwear with me!
I've only brought my own.
Then do I have to wash mine and dry them?
I usually sleep in my underwear.
If I have to wash them,
where will that put me?
I'm so sorry.
Goodness.
Buy a pair at the convenience store.
You're definitely a brain.
Why didn't I think of that?
Hyejin, let me open that for you.
Since I'm your older brother.
This is how you open this.
Outside the company,
we've agreed to be siblings.
Right, Hyejin?
Oh, brother and sister?
That's not alcohol-free.
Kim Hyejin likes to be
friendly with everyone.
No, it's not like that...
Little Sister, wait a second.
There's something on your face.
There, it's gone.
I brought you a gift from Seoul.
A gift.
Yes! That's the reaction
I was waiting for!
Am I right?
Seriously!
I thought it was a real bug!
There was a mosquito buzzing around.
Mosquitoes in the fall?
Hey, that didn't feel so good.
You look really creepy.
What?
Greasy and creepy...
Hurry.
How does someone get drunk so quickly?
I can't tell whether he's drunk or not.
That was tiring.
Jackson, get me a cup of water.
Go and get it yourself.
If you can't handle a single drink,
why did you insist on drinking?
Aren't you going to get a cup
of water for your older brother?
Are you going to act petty like this?
Jackson, do you think I look creepy, too?
No, right?
I'll get you some water.
What's wrong with my face?
Tell me what?
What? What is it?
You startled me!
You're so good looking,
I'm always surprised to see you.
Hi.
Shall I look through the pictures?
There are a lot of great locations.
I missed you, my friend.
Hey, when did you get home?
-Late last night.
-I see.
Did anything happen
at your business trip?
Happen? Like what?
Was it awkward between
you and Ji Sungjoon?
I thought it would be.
But he's easy to get along
with outside of work.
I have to get going now.
It's the week of deadlines,
so it'll be hard to see each other.
Don't cry because I'm not here,
and don't wait up for me.
Okay.
Make sure that you feed yourself!
Hey, you're going to fall! Stop running!
Good morning, Kim Hyejin.
Oh, yes.
Good morning, Mr Ji.
-Good morning.
-How are you?
Hello.
Now, it's time for deadlines, so let's
all cooperate together and do well.
Yes, sir.
Let's do this!
-Let's do it!
-Go for it!
-What's wrong with Mr Ji?
-Is something wrong with him?
His new attitude is starting to scare me.
Hey, you're growing a beard!
Looks good on you.
Everyone, let's do this!
-Yes!
I think it's good, but it would be
better to take this bit out.
Is this the only thing
that needs editing?
-Yes.
-I understand.
Yes, Hyejin.
How was your business trip?
I couldn't get a hold of you.
Sorry, I've lost track of time.
Mr Ji, the photographs
for the movie segment...
Wait a moment.
I have deadlines to meet,
so I'm a bit busy now.
Sorry, I'll have to call you back.
Sungjoon, Sungjoon.
Thanks for lunch.
I'm so tired.
Hyejin.
Get me the box.
Yes, I understand.
It's finished!
I'm going to sleep until tomorrow.
The person who wakes me will die.
So stay away from me.
I need some sleep.
Have you arrived?
Good work everyone.
Hang in there a little longer.
Pardon?
The models for our anniversary edition
will be available this Thursday.
They're top models,
so we have to accommodate their schedules.
I'm going to lose it!
Come on now.
This is the final stretch,
so let's work hard and celebrate after.
I should quit this job.
I don't care about wealth
or honour anymore.
Yes.
What's going to be our makeup concept?
-Yes.
-Is that so? Yes.
Regarding the collaboration
with James Taylor...
Let's schedule it for this Thursday.
Yes.
Yes?
You have a delivery.
Thank you.
Well, Mr Ji.
After the photo shoot on Thursday,
will you have some time?
I can't pay you for the glass,
but I'd like to buy you dinner.
And there's something
I'd like to tell you.
All right then.
Jackson, what were you
talking to Mr Ji about?
I asked him if he had time
after the photo shoot on Thursday.
I plan to tell him everything then.
Really?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Oh, no.
Do I remind you
of your little sister again?
What?
Yes.
The more I look at you,
the more you start to resemble her.
The way you can eat anything,
and the way you look at me.
Go on and eat, Little Sister.
Yes.
That's hot!
Now, you're exactly like her.
Let's eat.
Big Brother, have some more noodles.
You don't have to do that.
How much do I owe you?
It'll be 20 dollars.
Wow, that's so cute!
Is that your dog?
Yes, that's her.
Coco.
My younger sister.
-Thank you, Aunt.
-Thank you.
-Good night.
-Bye.
Coco? Sister?
Little Sister?
Then are you comparing me to your dog?
A dog?
Yes, why?
I thought she was your sister!
Yes, my little sister.
She was a part of the family.
You didn't think she was human, did you?
You've had the wrong idea!
You're completely confused.
Why, you...
Are you making fun of me?
Come here!
What's the matter?
I never said she's human.
You want to get bitten by a woman
that looks like a dog?
Coco never bit anyone! Don't bite me!
Coco, my foot!
I'm going to bite your nose!
I didn't do anything,
so why are you overreacting?
You always joke around and tease me
and now you compare me to your dog?
Why did I give you more noodles?
About that...
I felt sorry for you because
I thought that your sister died!
I wanted to be good to you,
but this is going too far!
How can you do this to me?
Are you ignoring me like a dog now?
Yes, that's all you think I am, a dog.
That's why I said that.
Yes, let's hear your reason!
Why do you treat me like this? Why?
Jackson,
I think I have feelings for you.
What?
You told me that you're
coming clean with the chief editor.
But for some reason, it bothered me.
It bothers me to think that things
will go well between the two of you.
And I keep thinking about you.
I was wondering why I felt that way...
...and now I think I know.
I think I like you.
A lot.
Mr Kim.
What are you talking about?
I almost fell for it again!
Your ridiculous lies!
It's not a lie. I'm being sincere.
I really have feelings for you.
Yes, right!
I'm not talking to you anymore!
Seriously.
Really?
You can't do that to me!
I've really fallen for her!
I like her, even when she acts like that!
Jackson!
Hyejin.
Kim Hyejin!
How was the business trip?
The business trip?
It was rather odd this time around.
Do you know what I did there?
I scooped cow manure...
I don't think the timing is right.
We've just had dinner.
Why?
Was it fun?
No, I'll tell you about it next time.
Why, what is it?
We have an intern that shares your name.
She's our age,
but she remembers all of the arcade
jingles from back in the day.
She's like...
She was trying to imitate the song.
It was so funny.
Sungjoon.
Yes?
Can I ask you one thing?
What is it?
Are you meeting with me...
...because I'm your childhood friend?
What do you mean all of a sudden?
I want to...
...hear your answer.
I want to know how you feel about me.
And why...
...you're meeting with me.
Because I'm sure of my feelings.
Hyejin.
I'm warning you one last time.
You can't treat me like that, okay?
Okay, okay.
I'm sorry.
This is how I feel about you.
As a token of my apology...
Can you help me throw away
my shoe that doesn't fit?
Sungjoon thinks that someone
other than me is his first love.
I think I'm falling for him.
My avatar.
I shouldn't meet him.
What the...
What the what?
So, what's the token of your apology?
What do you keep looking at?
What's the matter?
I won't act in ways that
might make you concerned.
What is it that you want to tell me?
How much do you know
about your girlfriend?
I'll root for your love.
I'm sorry, Hyejin.
Please end this.
Pretending to be Kim Hyejin.
Then what are you?
I like her.
I like Kim Hyejin.
Who are you?
Who are you to keep
getting on my nerves?