畫 task
Quote
Inter一点
а
Ч Emir
With 자연
Is there a girl in the family who wants to find a boyfriend?
No, it's not a girl. It's a boy.
Yes, I remembered it wrong. He's a boy.
Does he have a boyfriend?
You're looking for a boyfriend for Mo?
Yes.
That boy is nice.
He has only one child.
He's kind and kind.
Their economic conditions are the best.
Really?
He must have a girlfriend.
She's kind and kind.
Is she your wife?
Yes, she is.
There is a girl in the family.
But she is a mute.
She is a distant relative.
She is very poor.
A few days ago, someone came to trouble her.
Actually, her husband is a nice person.
He's adopted her.
You can come to the west of this street.
They live in the west.
Her house is in the west?
Yes.
How much?
36 dollars.
Don't worry, 40 dollars.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
See you next time.
So, everything is done?
Yes.
Thank you.
Money money will always be
lighter.
Just kidding, they're not here.
And I had another lenses shot.
No one has named except my sister,
I was in the reconstruction,
you see?
Suddenly I seem the neighbor of the neighbor.
Knowing this's true,
I've inherited qualities from our family.
Really.
Too good…
Really!
Be careful,道具!
We will find the right location.
Twenty thousand?
Too much!
Mom!
We only have 20,000 Qing chinese shares.
We don't have much money.
I'll look for it.
Will we see the child immediately after we pay?
Are they liars?
What did you say?
Mom, I'm not a liar.
I'm not a liar.
We have photos.
Hurry up, send them to me.
I'll ask Lin Hao to send them to you.
We saw the photos.
And we asked in the town.
Someone saw Xiao Yangyu.
Mom, it can't be. It's fake.
I'll go to the hospital.
I'm going to see my relatives.
Mom.
Mom, you can't go to see your relatives.
They told us to inform you
that they are in danger.
You can't tell your relatives.
Mom, you're too much.
If you say too much, it may be bad for Xiao Yangyu.
Don't tell anyone.
Yes, mom.
If the police know,
you'll never see Xiao Yangyu again.
I know. I know.
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone.
I'll figure it out myself.
You have to listen to us.
I'll listen to you.
Okay, I'll hang up.
Honey.
Wait.
Hello.
We're from the police station in Lingshan.
Police officer.
What's up?
I heard that a girl from your family came here.
Yes, yes.
A relative came here for a few days.
She's gone.
A distant relative?
Yes.
She's gone?
She's from my wife's family.
She said she was poor.
She's been living here for a few days.
She's gone.
She's a distant relative?
Yes.
She's gone?
She's from my wife's family.
She's a poor girl.
She wants to find a job.
But she's a mute.
How can she find a job?
So she couldn't find one.
So my wife sent her back.
I'll go and check.
Go ahead.
What's her name?
She's a distant relative from my wife's family.
And she's not that close to me.
I don't know.
Who's this?
This is my son.
Mo Li.
Why are you so rude to say hello?
Go back to your room.
Stop playing.
Please don't get used to it.
I'm used to it.
There must be something wrong with them.
We need to find that mute girl.
She's the key to our problem.
I'll ask her next time.
Go and clean up the mess.
Okay.
I'll ask someone to keep an eye on it.
Hello, Yan Blockchain.
Ole.
relations
If you want to sell magicaries,
they understand.
When I was in college,
I had
a teacher who asked me
But you said I've changed since I was a kid.
What about Xiaoyu?
I wanted to draw her, but I realized that she's just a little bit blurry.
Xiaoxin, I often look after Xiaoguang.
She's probably a middle school student.
She's grown up.
She had big eyes when she was a kid.
Guess what? Her nose is like mine, but her mother is like mine.
Then my son must be like my mother.
I've been listening to you two for a long time.
I've been thinking, when she grows up, what will she be like?
She should be like my father.
But she's fatter than my father.
She was very greedy when she was a kid.
Her face was red.
Her nose has a black mole.
I wonder if she's still here after she grows up.
She should be.
I've only had this photo for so many years.
Nothing else.
I've been thinking, if one day Xiaoyu really stands in front of me,
will I be able to recognize her?
Yes, you will.
I'm sure you will.
Didn't Xiaosu say that there's a professor who said that
a person's heart is a reflection of the other person's.
I believe that.
I believe that too.
Okay.
Auntie, your house is a little older,
but it's going to be a new school.
I heard that there's a school for the famous.
You have to think it over before selling it.
Nobody lives in the house that has just been divided.
If you need money, sell it.
Let me tell you again.
This is a new school.
It's very popular.
If it's popular, then sell it.
The faster, the better.
How fast do you want it?
I want it all.
I want cash.
Then the price is...
It's a little bit less.
Can you sell it?
Some people have left their intentions.
Wait, I'll call and ask.
The price is as you said.
How much do you want?
Wait, I'll ask right now.
I have a client who can pay right away.
But the price may be reduced to 20,000.
Okay, okay.
It's good to sell it.
I'll ask.
Apply at the earliest.
If you give me two days, you'll get it.
Aren't you sharp?
Of course.
But I don't trust your lock.
You are right in front of vast public eyes.
Be done with it.
I'll dare to get it after.
I'll see to it.
I hate family only...
what if I see a dog outside my house?
What if my 2nd puppy is in danger?
Then I won't stand in the way.
Wish this could have happened in the past.
I think we haven't seen the child yet.
We should give them half of the money during the insurance period.
What do you think?
Yes, yes, it's safe.
Okay.
Wait a moment.
Give him the money.
Okay.
Happy and Xiao Hao found the little lamb girl.
It's not easy to see the child after giving him 200,000.
Aunt Lin, this is a scam.
Don't believe it.
We didn't find the little lamb girl.
I was thinking the same thing.
That's why I called you.
But I've already returned the money to Lin Hao.
What should I do?
Thank you.
Okay.
Come back.
What did you say?
I've already told you.
I've already asked the location.
Mr. Zhang, you drive.
I'll take you there.
Okay, okay, let's go.
Aunt Lin, don't worry.
I'll call Lin Hao.
Call him.
Send me Lin Hao's address first, okay?
Okay.
Cheng Rui.
Here.
The child is also in the third house.
Cheng Rui, let's go to the hospital.
Cheng Rui, let's go.
What are you doing?
I'm taking the child home.
What?
You go inside.
Can you take the child away from us at home?
Listen to me.
If you take the child away,
you can find a chance to take the child home.
Okay.
Mr. Lin, I'm not very comfortable here.
I'll go first.
Thank you.
Remember to find a chance.
Aunt Xia.
No, no, no.
Just us two.
Do you want to ask Mr. Deng?
What do you mean?
It's too late.
I'll go get milk for you.
Wait a minute, baby.
He's gone.
You drive the car.
I'll bring the child here now.
Go.
It's the doctor.
Honey.
Go, go, go.
Let go of the child.
Mom is taking you home.
Go home.
Let go of the child.
Mom.
I'll go to the hospital.
I see you.
No, I can't.
I'll put the car down.
The car is not parked.
Or I'll crash into the window.
What are you doing?
You idiot.
Let go of the child.
The car is not parked.
It's my child.
If you don't listen to me, I'll crash into you.
I'll go to the hospital.
I'll crash into you.
What are you doing?
You're a coward.
I'll let you run away.
What are you doing?
Let go of the child.
Don't be afraid.
I'll go to the hospital.
Open the door.
Don't be afraid, honey.
I'm coming.
Let go of the child.
What are you doing?
Don't be afraid, honey.
I'll go to the hospital.
Let me go.
I'm coming.
Let go of the child.
Open the door.
I got you.
Open it, honey.
Don't run.
Open the door, honey.
Open.
Let go of the child.
Open the door.
Don't run.
Go!
Go! Go!
Hello?
Director Deng is in trouble.
Lin Ao and Cai Xin took a child.
They just passed the North Station.
What?
Okay, I got it.
Okay, I'll be there soon.
Director, go to the North Station.
Don't move!
Don't come over!
Stop!
If you come over, I'll jump off!
Don't push yourself!
Don't try to take my child away!
Listen to me!
Put my child down first!
I'm not your child!
You're my child!
Don't move!
Don't push yourself!
If you die, I'll jump off!
Director, is Cai Xin really crazy?
She's not crazy.
She's going to be like this.
Don't push yourself!
What are you doing?
What's going on?
He's taking my child away!
No, honey!
This is it!
They...
This is the child they kidnapped!
This is my child!
You can't kill him!
This is not my child!
Do you know if this is your child?
No!
Look!
Did they take him?
They took your child!
Hold him!
What are you going to do?
Don't move!
Calm down, get up!
This is the emergency department!
They are up there. Come with me.
Let's go.
Huo, Huo, be careful.
Be careful.
What's going on?
This lady is very excited.
Master, master, please don't be excited.
Can you tell her?
Xiaoxiao, leave it to me.
Is this the kid's parents?
They are not parents.
Xiaoxiao, it's me.
Deng Yan, do you remember me?
Director, director, you are here.
Hurry, arrest them.
They are all criminals, they are all liars.
You are not allowed to arrest my child.
They are all criminals.
They have just admitted it.
Take her away.
Give it back.
Jiang Xin, they have already left.
Now no one is going to talk to you.
You believe me, okay?
Jiang Xin, I'm sorry.
We didn't find Xiaoyang Yu in time.
You found Xiaoyang Yu yourself.
We are the same.
We did something wrong.
Did you hear Xiaoyang Yu calling you?
Yes.
There is a mole behind her.
Mole?
I saw it.
The same position.
Okay, don't go forward.
If you go forward, Xiaoyang Yu will be in danger.
Think about it.
Xiaoyang Yu didn't see her mother for so long.
She is very sad.
If you hold the child and go one step forward,
the consequences will be unimaginable.
Think about the child.
How scared she is.
She is scared.
Dad, I can't hold her.
Why is she not crying?
Why is she crying?
Is she hungry?
Let me see.
She hasn't cried for a long time.
Xiaoxin, come here.
She is Xiaoyang Yu.
No one can take her away.
Xiaoxin.
Then you just look at me.
I just look at you.
I'll look at you and return you, okay?
Let me see.
Xiaoyang Yu.
Look, she is scared.
What's wrong, Xiaoyang Yu?
She is Xiaoyang Yu.
She was taken away by them.
She is crying.
She is looking at her mother.
What's wrong?
Take her to the DNA test.
It's okay.
She is safe.
Comrade police officer.
We have seen the photo.
It's really our child.
It's really.
We have also done a DNA test for the child.
She is not Xiaoyang Yu.
It's impossible.
You must have done it wrong.
You were cheated.
These people used the search and stay channels you posted.
They know the specific situation of Xiaoyang Yu.
And they found a child who looks like her.
The purpose is to cheat you.
During this time,
the people who provide you with clues,
the people who lead you,
even some of your passers-by,
they are all liars.
They were cheated.
Liars.
But don't worry.
The two Wang brothers who cheated you,
they have caught them.
But they have transferred the money to Zhao Zhilong.
Zhao Zhilong has not been found yet.
How much money did you give them?
200,000.
Don't worry about the money.
The colleagues of Qin Zhen will find out the situation.
We don't have money.
Xin Xin.
Don't say that.
I don't want to.
We don't have money.
Xin Xin.
No matter how much money we spend,
we have to find the child.
We have to find the child.
Director, you go first.
Dr. Mei is here.
Mom.
What's going on?
Why did you bring us here?
Didn't you say you found the child?
Where is Xiaoyang Yu?
It's all my fault.
Xiaoyang Yu.
Xin Xin.
Say something.
Where is the child?
It's all my fault.
Yan Yan.
What's going on?
Didn't I ask you to find them?
Why didn't you bring the child back?
Where is the child?
Mom.
We were cheated.
The child is not Xiaoyang Yu.
Mom.
It's all my fault.
I was too anxious.
I thought Xiaoyang Yu was found.
The child could really come back.
Our family could reunite.
How could this happen?
It's all my fault.
Mom.
After you came back to my family, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Xiaoyang Yu.
I'm the sinner of this family.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
Xiaoyang Yu's clue is broken again.
I was not used to it even though I came to Dalaben for so long.
That family is broken and broken.
They are sad and sad.
I always wanted to help them.
But now all the clues are scattered.
If only we could make a comprehensive database,
we could greatly improve our efficiency.
What is it?
I'll tell you.
We need to build a space in the server
to record all the information and data of Dalaben.
As long as we enter the keywords,
we can quickly find the clues and information we need.
Is it complicated?
It takes some time.
Can you do it?
Of course.
I'll show you.
Okay.
Director Deng.
Yes.
We've checked it.
The child is not from the third generation.
They were adopted by the legal procedure.
And the procedure was rejected.
It's a good news.
Otherwise, if we don't find the child,
we'll be in trouble again.
Okay.
You should rest early.
Yes.
Bye.
No rush?
Did you see that video?
The family was in a hurry to jump off the building.
All right.
Let me know if you have any news.
See you
You just joined the team.
I understand that you want to show your best.
But if a team needs time to grow,
you need to care about your colleagues.
Only then you can be a part of the team.
I told you to let go of your hands and feet.
I and the sales department will support you.
Okay?
Take care of your colleagues.
Okay, I got it.
Thank you for informing me.
Okay.
Which team is this?
Next.
They both got what they stay for.
Yes.
I want to ask, is 38 Bed Yin Jing Sheng?
He doesn't seem to be here.
Yes, it's him.
But he said he had something to do at home.
He said he had to go home first and come back later.
You...
Eat.
I'm so tired.
I'm hungry.
What are you eating?
Eat.
You eat it.
I'll eat it.
Yes, look.
Where is your chicken?
Jiang?
Jiangtai chicken?
Jiang chicken?
What are you doing here?
I'll just take it and go.
Master, where is Xiaoqi?
Xiaoqi, why are you here?
I just want to chat with you.
Okay.
What's up?
You've been having a hard time lately?
You're indeed a master.
You're so bright.
Actually,
I just want to say something to you.
I came here to work as a manager.
I found that you're a little different from what I thought before.
Your work and your work content
are much more complicated than I imagined.
What's wrong?
Are you stressed?
Director and Director Xiao
asked you to be the director.
They think you're a good person
and a good person.
I heard that you're in the hospital.
Are you in a good shape now?
Yes.
You're here.
What are you doing in this mysterious place?
I'm going to send you a meal.
Why are you so unwilling?
You only found out from the nurse when I came.
You've been busy these days,
but you're asking for help behind my back.
How come I didn't know that you're such a good person?
Where did you go?
I'm bored.
I'm going for a walk.
You should stay and watch your husband.
You can investigate him if you want.
Who's responsible for what happened to Zhenyao?
I know him.
He's a good person.
I know.
It's all an old habit.
As for Jiansheng,
his character and ability are all good.
He's a good person.
He's not a bad person.
You can find a paper and look it up.
He can definitely tell you the same.
It's a case.
You only care about cases, right?
Jiansheng,
you should think about yourself,
not me.
Hello?
Okay.
Oh, come on.
What are you laughing at?
You're making fun of me.
Who's making fun of you?
Where are you going?
According to Yin's age and experience,
you should leave the position of the head of the department.
You should let him be the head of the department,
not me.
Jiansheng is a retired soldier.
He only has a high school degree.
I've told him many times.
You should get a high school degree.
But he's just a kid.
He's a young man.
He's not a good person.
It's not easy to be a doctor.
When you're not here,
you always ask me about Lin Ran.
You know,
there are few clues in the past.
The environment is complicated.
The technology is poor.
It's not easy to find someone.
And the buyer's legal awareness is weak.
Their ignorance has led to the market
to keep flowing.
This requires that we must be strong
in order to control the people's will.
We must not give up.
You did a good job.
Xiaodeng, I'm telling you,
Jiansheng can't be idle in the hospital.
Let him rest for a few days.
Then call him back.
If there's a case,
he'll recover faster.
I see, Director Wang.
I'll go with you to play chess.
Let's go.
Go.
Hello, Officer Lu.
I want to ask you for a favor.
It's about the case of Yang Yu.
I...
38th floor,
turn off your phone and rest.
Don't you know what's going on with you?
You'll get a headache if you keep going on.
Okay, I know.
Rest.
Okay, okay, I'll be right there.
Right, right.
I'll go to you in person.
What are you doing?
Hello, I want to ask if there's a patient named Ying.
Yes, 38th floor.
38th floor, thank you.
Wait, you can't go in.
It's too late.
Yes, I know.
But the patient named Ying is a police officer.
So I want to visit him.
No.
Why?
It's too late.
Everyone is resting.
You can come tomorrow.
So strict.
Go.
It's not worth it.
Go, go, go.
먹어봐.
Okay, I got it.
I'll give you backs.
Uncle Ying.
The nurse didn't scold you?
I'm telling you, they didn't scold me.
Here, flowers.
I wanted to buy you a fruit.
But I thought you were diabetic.
How are you feeling now?
I'm fine. I'll be fine in a couple of days.
How's your team doing?
I'll be there soon.
How's the case with Yang Yu?
Any new leads?
Not yet.
But Jia Jia is looking for a cool guy.
He said he could help.
Are you sleeping, sir?
Director Deng, why are you here?
I came in the day and saw you weren't here.
So I came in the night.
I hope I didn't disturb you.
You're too kind.
I'll put it here.
Sit down.
Okay, come out.
You're so small, Director Deng.
I'm sorry.
Hello, Director Deng.
I'm afraid of nurses.
No, not that.
I'm afraid of breaking the rules.
You two talk.
I'm not here. You talk.
Master, did Han Zhiduan tell you to rest?
If we all listen to the doctor,
we'll fill the hospital with the police.
I'm fine.
I can't die of illness.
He's right.
What did he say?
He said you were checking the case.
He's right.
Since that's the case, let's talk.
What's the situation with Yang Yu's case?
We'll talk tomorrow.
The most important thing is to rest.
You can't be the only one.
Okay.
What's going on with him?
It's not a big deal.
He's just a man.
He's a man.
Han Liang, listen.
Listen to the doctor.
He needs to rest.
Director Xiao is worried about Yang Yu's case.
He has no clue.
He can't find Yang Yu.
He's not well.
So we need to hurry up.
You're a leader.
Wait, Director Xiao.
Director Xiao, Han Zhiduan, you want to see me?
Come on.
Sit down.
The public is interested in Yang Yu's case.
What's your opinion?
Recently, there are many cases of child abuse.
Yang Yu's case is also highly popular.
I think it's a very important opportunity for the public to join the anti-corruption movement.
The public is aware of the importance of anti-corruption.
And we have to take a serious action.
We can control these crimes.
Okay.
From the public to the public.
This is the
great idea.
You have the right to cooperate.
Okay, I understand.
I was two years old when my daughter was lost.
It's been 13 years and five months.
Her mother and I took her to the mall.
We had a little fight.
Nobody noticed.
She disappeared.
I ran away with my child.
I was crying and chasing after her.
Director Deng, as the director of the anti-corruption department of the Lingshan Public Security Bureau,
thank you for accepting our interview today.
The family of the victim was introduced to us.
The anti-corruption method can be said to be a good example.
Once it happens to every family, it's a huge disaster.
How should we prevent it?
If there is a case of child abuse, please don't panic.
You must call the police.
We will try to find the victim as soon as possible.
We hope that the parents of the lost children will not panic.
I want to ask him to draw a boy's portrait of you.
Maybe it will be your brother's after he grows up.
Okay. Thank you.
Be careful.
Think about it.
It's done.
Is this the database you mentioned?
It's done so quickly.
It's not that fast.
This is a demo version.
I've made all the information about the little girl
into a simple mini database.
Send this video to me.
Thank you.
The End