The next one is the most difficult one.
It's a very difficult one.
Then it's useless to hold the science too deep.
If it's too deep, I don't know what to make of it.
Did it work
The third background-
I'm going to the
Oh oh
I also get
We have solved three cases of human trafficking
These three cases are in Zhangjia Village
This is Hu Zihua
We solved three cases of human trafficking
Their family still lives in the village
Hu Zihua, don't be nervous
Aren't you the Baishi Dong in your village?
We are here today
Just want to find out some information
Twenty years ago
Have you seen a girl who is 16 or 17 years old in your village?
This is Zhang Hanzi's cousin
There is a beautiful mole in her eyebrows
This mole is quite good
Yes, this is her
Later, I went to find Zhang Hanzi
His door was locked
He and this girl are gone
Later, Zhang Hanzi returned to the village
But he was alone
I guess he didn't see her
So he ran away
Aunt, aunt
Be careful
You are here
Aunt, aunt
Sit down, sit down
Sit down
I'll get you some powder
No, I'll just sit down and leave
You are here
You are our great hero
I must get you some powder
Wait, it will be ready soon
You sit down, it will be ready soon
Be careful, aunt Zhang
Director Le, have some tea
Thank you
Come on, aunt Zhang
Come on
That's too much, I can't finish it
No, you can have more
Yanyan
You are our great hero
We really have to thank you
Just now, the people who came back from the trip
said they could come with us
Really?
Yes
We can stay in the small restaurant
and go to their place
I'm so happy to hear that
It's so noisy
Boss, give me a bowl of beef
I'll go to the restaurant
I'll do it
Come on, sit down
Come on, sit here
Director Cao
This is Zhang Hanzi, the famous Director Zhang
51 years old, married before
Now he is working in Shuanglin County
Give me a piece of the tissue
No
Oh
Did he put salt in the old spoon?
No
Almost forgot
Um
She threw up
Beef powder
It's not spicy to drink
You can have more
You can add spicy soup
I'm done.
You're done? That's great.
I'll have to make less next time.
Boss!
This is too salty.
This is too...
It's too salty?
How come?
Taste it yourself.
I'll make you another bowl right away.
I'm not eating it.
It's free.
I'll make you a bowl for free.
I won't eat the free ones.
Boss,
this situation of yours
is not the first time.
Forget it. I'm not eating it.
I'm leaving.
I'm sorry.
Boss,
take care.
This...
Seriously...
How come you're doing this?
It's okay, Auntie.
It's okay.
I'm old.
I'm really old.
Director Duan,
I want to tell you about
Auntie Zhang's situation.
It's just that she's been...
I don't know what's wrong with her.
She's been acting strange.
It's like this happened
several times today.
Yesterday,
when she was counting the bill,
she miscalculated a few points.
And yesterday,
when she was marinating the rock sugar and radish,
she forgot to put in the vinegar.
She was so confused.
Last night,
she was the last person to lock the door.
And she forgot to lock the door.
I came here this morning and saw the door was locked.
I was so scared.
What do you think I should do?
How about this?
I'll take Auntie Zhang to the hospital
and do another examination.
I'll go to the hospital and see if she's okay.
Okay.
I'll go with you.
I suggest you take Aunt Zhang to the hospital for a check-up.
Go to the hospital?
Is it that serious?
Not that serious.
But the old man is getting older.
We should do more tests
to see if there are any other changes in his body.
Don't worry.
Yes, you are right.
What are you doing in there?!
I'm not gonna cook at all!
If you die, you will kill me
Lead a household to a meal
With a 친구로 배 laptandy
You'll change the 2 blessings
I'll forget that you love you
I'll treat you with kindness
Like the love from Yuı
I'll remember, there's nocake
You know him?
Yes
Do you know him?
Isn't this Zhang Laohan?
Please go find him
He's in the bus. I'll go call him
Zhang Laohan
Assistant Zhang, right?
Do you know this person?
Yes
Where is he?
I've been looking for him for 20 years
What do you mean? Tell me the truth
20 years ago, I spent 1000 yuan to buy him
But he was cheated by someone
You're awake, sister
Don't be afraid
I'm your man
Let's have a meal
Don't shout
Okay?
Brother
Please let me go
Brother, you're a good man
I beg you
Please let me go
I bought it
I beg you
Let's have a meal
You'll starve to death if you buy it
Brother, I bought it
Help
I've said it
Don't shout
Help
Because I was a money-lender and a man
I regretted it when I broke up with her
She was so pretty
She was so young
How could I be with her?
I was thinking
If she smiled at me, how pretty she would be
Don't make a mess
Tell me the point
The point is, the seller said
As long as the time is long, she'll be obedient
But she didn't eat a bite
I'm sorry
Don't shout, okay?
What do you want to eat?
I'll cook whatever you want
I...
I can't let you go
I've bought you back as my wife
They can't return the money to me
I've borrowed all the money I could remember to buy you
But you didn't eat a bite
If you starve to death, I'll spend all my money
I'm sorry
I didn't mean to hit you
Eat something
If you don't eat, I...
I'll buy you a meal
That's a human disease
I spent money on it
What if I starve to death?
Where is she now?
I don't know
Xu Tanglong tricked her for 20 years
I can't find her
Who is Xu Tanglong?
A...
A... a seller
Hello
Come again
Brother Zhang
What did you buy today?
Did you get any new goods?
This one
This one is the best
You bought clothes and hairpins recently
Is there any good news?
No good news
What good news?
You bought a wife?
Yes
It seems to be true
Who told you?
No one
I guessed
Take a look
Is it really good?
Nothing good
Take a look
Let's go
I'm buying things
I'll send it to you later
Haven't you seen a woman?
No
Why are you so annoying?
Annoying?
I'm so annoying
Liu Shu, show me your hair
I don't see anything
It's almost done
It's not over yet
I have to go
You go
Bye
It's not over yet
Good, Zhang
This little girl looks so good
She wants to pay
I spent a lot of money
I see her like this
There is no air in it
I can't help it
Zhang
I have something to discuss with you
Say it
You can't do it
How about this
I'll give it to your dad
You give it to me
I spent more than a day to buy it
Why don't you know how to be a good person?
I'm helping you
Has he not eaten for a few days?
He has to go to the hospital
You can't get it
You have to go to jail
Such a big man died in your place
The police are looking for you
Why don't people in this village talk about you?
Think about it
OK
You don't want to, do you?
You can wait and be in jail
Wait a minute
So you sold Yangcaoyun to Xu Tenglong, right?
I'm afraid he'll starve to death
You're afraid he'll starve to death
Or you're afraid your money will go to waste?
I received 800 yuan
When I went to Xu Tenglong
He didn't admit it
He said I was a businessman
He said if I called the police, he would arrest me first
I was wronged
I was really wronged
Twenty years ago
Whether it's 800 or 1000
It's a lot of money
Can't you get married to someone with this money?
You have to do this illegal thing
I don't know it's illegal
Our village does it
You said no one would marry in our village
I ask you
Where is Xu Tenglong?
I don't know
When you sold him
You can find him
Now you can't find him
Do you know?
You ruined a girl's life
He was only sixteen years old
Director
Xu Tenglong is good at business
He works hard
He sells goods on the street
He made a lot of money
He has been living here since he moved from Wushun County
As far as we know
He lives alone now
No one around
Xu Tenglong
Tenglong, right?
We are from the Public Security Bureau
We want to investigate something with you
What's the situation?
You are talking here
You still want to talk inside?
Please come in
Lead the way
Please sit
I
Officer
What are you investigating me for?
Did you make a mistake?
You can ask around
I am a good servant of Fenggong Shouha
Do you know Yang Ziyun?
No
Where is Assistant Zhang?
Where is he?
I don't know him
He is from Zhang's Village in Wushun County
Think about it
Officer
I really don't know what you are talking about
What do you want to ask me today?
You really don't know him?
I really don't know him
I want to read something to you
My name is Zhang Zhongli
I am from Zhang's Village in Wushun County, Xinyang
I have confessed to the Public Security Bureau
and reported to Xu Tenglong
for selling his daughter
In October 1990
I bought a woman from a human trafficker
And half a month later
I sold her to Xu Tenglong
He used 800 yuan
to bury Yang Ziyun in my hands
Do you remember?
You mean that woman?
I was from that
Zhang, Zhang Laohan saved her
Zhang Laohan was starving to death
When I came here
she started eating as soon as I told her
Didn't you say you didn't know Zhang Zhongli?
How do you know her nickname is Zhang Laohan?
I just remembered it
The woman you bought is called Yang Ziyun
Where is she?
She was not here
She ran away
Ran away?
Explain it clearly
What's going on?
I really saved this woman from Zhang Laohan
I wanted to live a good life with her
But she didn't give birth
like a stone
I thought
it was not easy to make money at that time
If she can't give birth
I spent my money for nothing
Coincidentally
I have a business partner called Liang...
Liang...
Liang Wei, right, Liang Wei
He is really a man
I let him in
But he and that woman
I told him
I saw the green beans and it was right
I just followed the trend
and introduced it to him
How much did you sell?
Not much
I bought it for 20,000 yuan
You are good at business
Comrade Jin
You are wronging me
It's not a business
They are in love
I just signed a letter
At most, I will give it to the maid
Right?
Well, don't talk so much
Where is Liang Wei's family?
I only remember that place more than ten years ago
It's in...
Huangjiagou, Hongxi City
I don't know it now
Ok, go to the police station with us
We will call you now
We need to investigate
No, comrade police
I have made it clear
Why do you investigate me?
You are suspected of selling your daughter
Go
I...
I am wronged
You...
Translate by Alex
Aunt Zhang
I am back
Xiao Xing
So many things
You are welcome to come here tomorrow
And we still need to buy dumplings
Right
Have you bought dumplings?
Did you buy the dumplings?
Yes
See? Is it enough?
Yes, yes
It's so heavy. Put it on the back
I bought fruits and vegetables
One more thing
Xiaoxing
I forgot to tell you one more thing
That is
at the party
they all like the dumplings with the bean paste I made
I just bought them
You just asked me
My brain is
I'm going to cook now
I forget it when I have too much things
It's messy
Hello, Dr. Wang
I'm Luo Xiaoxing
Well
I want to ask
Did you get the test report from Aunt Zhang?
What a silly girl
She just fell asleep when she arrived at the reception
She didn't even eat dinner
Let her rest
We'll bring her some food later
Do you have chili?
No, it's just right
You know, Yang Taiyun
I've been looking for him for almost 20 years
I don't have many 20s in my life
He just got a little bit of a beauty
He's not selling it to other places
So I heard about it today
Yang Taiyun's case is really complicated now
If you can't stand it, tell me
I'll take a break from him first
I won't go back until I find Yang Taiyun
By the way
Han Che told me
He wants me to go back to Lingshan
I'll go back for a few days
If you need it, I'll come to you
Deputy Director Yin
Okay, I got it
Okay, don't worry
Don't worry
It's been a long night
It's too hard
Do you want to go to the nearby hotel and have a rest?
No, no
It's normal
Deputy Director Yin is now
suspicious of Yang Taiyun
I've been looking for this case for almost 20 years
You're old
You're still working so hard
You've been waiting for 20 years
You're almost there
Let's go for breakfast
No, no
You take a break first
How's the investigation going on here?
After receiving your call
We conducted an investigation overnight
We found Xu Teng's man called Liang Wei
And sent the photo to the Qingxi County
and the police
After Xu Teng's re-election
Liang Wei is the one who bought Yang Taiyun
nine years ago
Did you find Yang Taiyun?
It's too tight
We can only simply
investigate the information
Liang Wei's wife is Wen Su Juan
She's the same age as you said
Yang Taiyun
The time they got married
was exactly one year after Xu Teng's death
The time is also consistent
Wen Su Juan is not a local
We can't find any information
about her parents in the system
This is the certificate of Wen Su Juan
Please verify it
Is there any other information about Wen Su Juan?
Oh, right
When they got married
Wen Su Juan was pregnant
Soon after the marriage
she had a daughter
called Liang Xiaoyun
She had a child?
I'm sorry
Director Yu
This is Wen Su Juan's house
Is Wen Su Juan home?
She is Wen Su Juan?
Yes, it's her
Wen Su Juan
These two are the two who are in charge of the National Security Bureau
Director Yin and Officer Ai
They have some situations
I want to know about them
I'm sorry
Sorry
sorry
It's Đau Dinh
No, he's sharing with somebody
You'reoughs
I want to talk to him alone
Sure
We came to check some things with you.
Your real name shouldn't be Wen Su Juan,
but Yang Cai Yun, right?
My name is Wen Su Juan.
My name is not Yang Cai Yun.
Do you think this photo is you?
No.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Police officer, you really found the wrong person.
Your name is Yang Cai Yun.
On May 10, 1974,
in October 1990,
a man named Lao Huang Gou was kidnapped.
First, he was sold to Zhang Zhongli in Zhangjia Village in Wushun County.
Then he was sold to Xu Teng Long in Qingqu County by Zhang Zhongli.
Then he was sold to Liang Wei by Xu Teng Long,
who is your current husband.
Police officer,
my husband and I are in love.
Our child is already nine years old.
He's in grade two.
I really am not the person you want to find.
Please leave.
Mom.
This is your child?
Yes.
This is Xiaoyun.
Xiaoyun,
where is your father?
Dad went out to buy wine.
Xiaoyun, go and write your homework.
When you're done, I'll come back and talk to you.
Police officer, if there's nothing else,
I should go and cook.
Don't wait.
Let me tell you something.
Twenty years ago,
a girl was kidnapped.
I was the one who took over the case.
Unfortunately,
I haven't found this child for twenty years.
I remember that her parents
often came to our department
and complained to me.
They begged us to find the only daughter for them.
Later,
every time I went on a business trip,
I went to her parents' grave to see.
Her parents' graves are very cold.
Because their only daughter is missing,
no one was there to clean up their graves.
They have already...
Police officer,
your story is very touching.
But I'm really not Yang Xiaoyun.
Please go back if you don't have anything to say.
Xiaoyun, you can trust us.
We're here to help you.
If you have any questions,
you can tell us.
You don't have to be afraid.
I'm really not Yang Xiaoyun.
You really found the wrong person.
You guys go.
I'm sorry.
Mom, who are they?
Mom, what's wrong?
Mom, don't cry.
Liang Xiaoyun's parents have been bitterly disappointed
that he couldn't get a DNA test without going to the hospital.
If he insists that he is Wen Sujun
and not Yang Caiyun,
then we might not be able to take both of them.
Why don't you admit it?
Xiaoyun, where's your father?
Dad went to buy wine.
Xiaoyun, go write your homework.
Write homework to help dad come back.
I'll tell him.
I think it's because of the child.
Any mother wouldn't want her child's father
to be taken away by the police
and put in prison.
But I think the child might be
just a part of it.
Maybe there are other reasons
why he doesn't want to admit it.
We're also very worried about this.
You said that the two of you had a family affair.
So you're not going to tell us?
The villagers know about the two of you having a family affair.
They are very cruel.
They sent them to the hospital several times.
Then why didn't they call the police?
Wen Sujun himself
couldn't stand it.
He couldn't stand it anymore.
He went to our village committee.
But when we came up,
he was just a little bit upset.
It's nothing.
He said it himself.
What can we do?
If there are too many people in the village,
the villagers will not blame them.
They can't control the situation.
Yes.
Family violence
should be dealt with by the victim himself.
Did you threaten him?
Does he have any concerns?
Maybe.
We talked to him.
He also ate a few ice creams.
Wen Sujun, this time we'll deal with you.
Okay.
What did you do?
Nothing.
I just came to visit.
I asked if the police station was satisfied.
I said it was very satisfied.
I didn't have any objections.
Did he ask
what you were doing?
No.
The household register clearly states that
I am Wen Sujun.
I am free to love you.
I said it myself.
You know my temper.
Even if the police know I bought you,
you can't control it.
Once I'm out, I'll kill you.
I won't only kill you, I'll kill him too.
Xiaoyu is your biological daughter.
Dad.
Did the police support you?
Mom.
Dad.
I'll kill you.
Do you hear me?
Stop.
Give me the police.
Xiaoyu.
Come on.
I'm going to sleep.
Move.
Come on.
Let's go.
Sujun.
Yang Kanyun.
You can leave here now.
You don't have to worry about
the revenge of your parents.
He's suspected of domestic violence.
I'm here in this royal palace.
I'm leaving now.
Where else can I go?
Mom.
Are we going to lose our home?
You can go back to Linshan.
Your parents' grandparents are still here.
We'll connect with the local government.
They'll take care of you.
No.
If we go back, we'll be in trouble.
Yang Kanyun.
You're afraid you can't support this family alone, right?
No.
Don't worry.
And we'll be your team.
And many public welfare organizations
and love companies will come to help you.
This trouble will definitely pass.
Thank you.
You have to believe in yourself.
I can do it for Xiao Ying.
I can do it for myself.
I can do it.
This time,
you can finally go home.
I promise.
I can finally go home.
Let's go.
But the truth is in my heart
Finally, I became such a person
Every number is a memory of youth
For love, heartache, for the sake of the past, and this life
I'm determined to not look back
The time is over, let it go
There is always someone waiting for the future
Hugging this time, it will never change
Just like my heart, it will never be deep
The blue heart, it will never be deep