♪I can't help but feel a little happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little nervous♪
♪The Earth is turning because of you♪
♪Without you, the Earth stops♪
♪You are the rainbow that fills up
the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend
of the four-leaves clover♪
♪I dreamt of a white-horse carriage
and you becoming my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards the fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Am I the happiness you're looking for?♪
♪The deerlet inside me is lost♪
♪Holding your hand, let's count down to happiness♪
♪I can't help but be a little fragile♪
♪I can't help but feel a little gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who takes away
all of my loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 13=
Is that style
too modern?
No.
Although it appears to be
a bit run-down,
but it's actually not
one of those outdated cafes from decades ago.
A lot of people
come here
is purely because of
its good location.
If you place other cafes
at this location,
it'll achieve the same effect.
What we need to do
is to make everyone
have the desire to
come in and take a photo
after having one look at this cafe.
Although some designers
may despise this sort of thing,
this is the best method
for businessmen.
And it's the best way for this cafe to
integrate into its surroundings.
Industrial style or retro style
doesn't really suit this place.
Okay, I got it.
Mr. Gu, the exhibition hall project
is going very well.
I'll send you
our finalized proposal shortly.
Okay.
The owner of the cafe will
be here soon.
He must have been stuck in traffic.
I'm going down to take a walk.
Let me know when the owner is here.
Okay.
Penny for your thoughts?
You guys are done with the discussion?
Why didn't you come up and join us?
You guys were talking business.
Sister Man Lin also told me that
she would let me know
what you guys discussed.
Let's go.
We're here.
Here.
Sister Man Lin, this is your room.
Boss, your room is over here.
Let's see.
Here.
Boss, your room key.
I'm just next door.
Let me know if you need anything.
Okay.
This is a really nice room.
Hello, Boss.
Do you really need to be this polite?
We've only been apart for less than a minute.
That's true.
Boss,
I heard the hot springs here are pretty good.
You can soak in the hot springs at night
and look at the stars.
It's cloudy now.
I believe as long as you wait patiently,
you'll be able to see them.
Although this place doesn't
have the pollution or haze
from the city,
I should still advise you
you'd better check
the weather forecast
in the future.
But what if the weather forecast is wrong?
I shall still go to the hot springs,
or else I've come here for nothing.
Sister Wen Wen, what a coincidence.
Are you staying at this hotel too?
You're here to soak in hot springs too?
To relax for a bit.
My boss asked me to book a hotel,
so I booked this one.
Looks like we're quite like-minded.
We have similar tastes.
That's right.
This hotel
was designed by a Japanese designer.
And the hot springs here
are very well-known.
It's a top choice amongst
tourists in this area.
I see.
Come join me.
Okay.
Be careful.
Sister Wen Wen, have some.
I'm good. You can have it.
By the way, Sister Wen Wen,
are you a professional photographer?
I used to be a photo-journalist.
And then I worked as a part-time photographer
for National Geographic.
I only began working full-time these years.
But it's so rare to see female photographers.
You must have been to many places.
I've been to every place
you can think of.
Recently, my husband began to focus on
the domestic market.
So I followed him
and came back.
You got married at such a young age?
I won't say I'm still young.
I just got engaged this year.
I'm waiting for my photography exhibition
to finish
so that I can have my wedding at the end of this year.
How about you? What do you do for a living?
Me?
I'm currently working at
an architectural company.
An architectural designer?
No, no, no.
My dream is to be an architectural designer.
But for now, I'm just
an assistant to my boss.
Still in the process of learning.
Our boss is
a really, really good architectural designer.
He has won
a lot of international awards at a young age.
He's handsome and talented.
Anyway,
he's just so outstanding.
Super brilliant.
Such a boss...
Must be quite strict, right?
He used to always
pull a long face at first.
But now he smiles at me from time to time.
He's the kind of person who would look
super handsome when he smiles.
You like him?
How do you know?
I mean...
I mean, what made you
ask such a question?
Because you only answered my question
in one sentence, but
you spent the rest of the time praising him.
I just look up to him.
That's all.
I don't have feelings for him.
No feelings at all.
I'm not an employee of your company.
You don't need to be so nervous.
Is it very obvious?
Very obvious.
You're not someone
who can lie after all.
If it's so obvious,
what if my boss
could tell from long ago?
I just drank a little
and I am talking too much now.
(I'm done sorting out the proposal.)
(Do you want to come over and have a look?)
(Sure, you can send it to me.)
(The proposal is on my laptop.)
(How about I bring it over to you?)
(Never mind. I'll go over.)
You're right.
Since you and I
are just strangers,
I'm not afraid to tell you.
Actually, it's really hard for me
to not like him.
Although he appears to be
quite cold normally,
he's always the first one
to appear
when I need help.
And he does it very naturally,
as if
it was just a coincidence.
You'll never expect
that he did it intentionally.
He is someone
who shines so brightly
wherever he goes.
When you're talking about your boss,
you really did go on and on.
Looks like you're really into him.
We just met.
And I've talked a lot already.
I feel a bit embarrassed.
I didn't even ask you if you want to hear it.
It's okay.
I understand.
Sometimes,
it's easier to talk openly
to someone you don't really know.
You speak so highly
of this man,
even I want to get to know him.
I'll introduce him
to you later,
but
you must keep
what I told you tonight as a secret.
You don't need to. I was kidding.
It wouldn't really matter
whether I meet him or not.
One day
you'll learn
you can run out of curiosity.
Okay, I can't stay in any longer.
I'm feeling a little dizzy.
By the way,
I still want to remind you.
Be careful when you're falling in love
with your boss.
Be careful not to lose your love
and your job.
Got it.
I only admire him.
I have no other intentions.
I'm leaving.
I'll send you the photos later.
Okay.
See you.
Bye-bye.
Okay.
Then send it to me.
Who is it?
Gu Chuan.
Mr. Gu, the proposal is on my laptop.
I've left it on the table.
Please come in and get it.
Mr. Gu,
this proposal is quite urgent.
I suggest that you review it
while I amend it concurrently.
It's more efficient this way.
It's okay.
I can amend it myself
after I'm done reviewing it.
Mr. Gu,
I have a question to ask you.
What is it?
Were you so busy working on the proposal
this entire time in your room
that you didn't even leave yourself
any time to get changed?
What's wrong?
All these years,
I've never seen you
relax.
It's like you're constantly
preparing for war.
Mr. Gu,
you're already very exceptional.
You're a top-notch architectural designer
in our industry.
Do you have to be number one?
I have never
competed with anyone.
I'm just trying to
accomplish my own goals.
Apart from winning the Jin An Award,
do you have any other plans?
Acting mysterious.
Haven't I always been like this?
You've changed a lot recently.
You've become more bubbly
and you like to smile now.
Is it because of Jiang Xiao Ning?
Perhaps.
Looking at her
reminds me of myself
when I first got into the company.
I was about the same as her.
I was a fresh and inexperienced graduate,
running around
every day.
I seemed to have endless energy.
Chasing after you every day
with tons of questions.
Even messed up a lot of stuff.
But
it seems that I didn't
bring you that much joy.
You know that
I'm a pessimistic person.
I will always
prepare for the worst.
But Jiang Xiao Ning is the opposite of me.
I can feel an extremely strong
sense of optimism from her.
No matter how bad things get,
she can always turn it around.
For example,
I like to cut to the chase.
However,
she likes to enjoy the process.
I like living my life
according to my own plan,
realizing it step by step.
But she
is like an alarm
that won't stop going off.
And she makes everyone around her
extremely enthusiastic as well.
You could say that she's the opposite of me
in every way.
It's quite interesting.
Then do you like her?
In what way?
Romantically.
They came out.
The moon and stars are all out.
I don't think I'll fall in love
with anyone.
Okay, rest early.
I'll go back to review the proposal.
Jiang Xiao Ning, where did you go just now?
I went to soak in the hot springs
with a friend I just met.
Then the moon came out.
I'll head back first.
Boss, Sister Man Lin,
let me know if you need anything.
I'll head back as well.
Boss and Sister Man Lin
must be discussing work.
But if they were discussing work,
why would Sister Man Lin
wear such sexy sleepwear?
She's a born beauty,
while you're destined to be normal.
After waiting for so long,
the clouds have finally gone.
Why are you sighing
over there
when you've got what you wanted?
Boss,
you showed up out of nowhere.
It's you who was
too immersed in your own world.
Jiang Xiao Ning,
I think you're quite something.
A lot of things become miracles
the moment they encounter you.
You have to believe it to see it.
Indeed.
The moon is quite pretty.
I told you so.
Okay.
You've seen the moon.
Now you should go back and rest.
How about you, Boss?
I still need to work.
Su Man Lin just gave me
some proposal to read.
I need to check it through one more time.
Do you need my help?
The only thing you can help me with now
is to get inside and rest.
Goodnight, Boss.
Goodnight.
Was Boss giving me an explanation?
Was he? Was he?
Doesn't matter.
I'll take it as an explanation.
They really were discussing work.
Jiang Xiao Ning,
how could you misunderstand your boss?
Is there something wrong with your brain?
I'm working. Why are you here again?
I missed you, so I came to see you.
Didn't I tell you
that we should just be friends?
You did.
I'm giving you
these flowers as a friend.
Lilies.
So you will treat me as your mother now?
Thank you, friend.
Goodbye, friend.
I don't have much to do.
But I do.
What do you have to do?
Why should I tell you?
Zhao Yan.
What's going on?
Who is this?
My cousin.
Cousin?
Oh, your cousin.
Hello, cousin.
Hello.
Alright, I'll wait for you at the restaurant.
Okay.
Oh, by the way,
if you're free,
you can join us.
Who was that?
Why did you say I'm your cousin?
Your company doesn't allow
their employees to date?
Since you've already met him,
I'll tell you the truth then.
My boyfriend.
What did you mean by that?
I'm still too young.
Almost fell for it.
I don't believe you'll choose someone like that
to be your boyfriend.
Believe it or not. It's up to you.
I've already told you.
Don't think you can trick me into leaving
by using some
random person as an excuse.
I don't need to trick you.
Do you think I'm three?
You expect me to believe you're dating
a greasy middle-aged man like him?
Manager Wei.
You're here, Yan Yan.
Where's your cousin?
He was just dropping something off.
He left already.
Okay.
Close the door and sit.
Originally,
I planned on having your cousin join us.
Is he your boyfriend?
No.
It's not a big deal.
We're in the 21st century.
We're all adults.
It won't affect anything.
It won't.
Come on.
Are we really drinking at noon?
What's the matter?
I'll call the company
and tell them that
we're doing fieldwork together.
Then,
on this beautiful afternoon,
let's find a hotel
and enjoy our downtime together.
When it's time,
we'll "clock off" and head back to our own places.
No one will be affected.
Sir, you can't do this.
I apologize
for interrupting.
Is this your friend?
Cousin!
We know each other.
You can leave the room now.
I was looking for you.
Come on. Take a seat
Your appearance says that you're a boss.
How should I address you?
Here's to you.
It's just a name.
Call me brother-in-law.
Sister.
Brother-in-law.
Here's to you, brother-in-law.
Look at your cousin.
So polite and knows the ways of the world.
Cheers, cousin.
Cousin?
You're the cousin.
Your whole family is cousins!
Stop it, Xu Cheng Ran!
What are you doing?
Let go!
Stop!
Crazy.
Get up.
Manager Wei, are you alright?
Let's go.
Are you crazy!
I am.
I just wanted to test
if I'll be able to
act crazy for you this one time.
Are you done testing?
If you're done, just leave.
I just have one question.
Why did you pick someone like him
over me?
Because he's better than you.
I didn't see that.
You have to look deeply into his inner self.
My inner self is outstanding too.
The you right now is clearly not outstanding.
That's because
you said he's better than me.
You're just getting worse if you
keep acting like this.
Leave.
Stop embarrassing me.
♪You're the haze in my sky♪
♪A disaster for my clear blue sky♪
You're right.
I am insane
to embarrass myself
for a woman
with mental problems.
It's not worth it.
♪But who asked me to love♪
♪Who asked me to love♪
♪I love this bad guy♪
♪I want to rely on you♪
♪But who asked me to love♪
♪Who asked me to love♪
♪I have no idea♪
♪I won't let go♪
♪I adore you for no particular reason♪
♪This unreasonable love♪
♪I can't explain but just want to♪
♪mess around with you♪
♪Come on, let's hurt each other♪
♪If you dare to love, you have to
be ready to get hurt♪
♪We thank our fate♪
♪We all deserve it♪
♪But who asked me to love♪
♪Who lets me love♪
♪I have no idea♪
♪I won't let go♪
My Chuan,
where are you?
Chuan.
Next time, can you come find me
when you're sober?
I'm in so much pain.
Can you see?
See what?
My heart
is broken.
I see your moral integrity
has shattered into pieces.
You're not wrong.
But why did Yan Yan do that?
We have already
done everything.
Why did she change
her attitude all of a sudden?
Or,
she just wanted my body?
I really don't want to talk to you.
You're so gross.
Do whatever you want.
I'm going to sleep.
Don't leave. Chat with me.
I'm so sad that I want to die.
You're so sad that you want to die?
Then die.
I'm not going to stop you.
You're right.
I'll go die.
When he left me there
alone,
I was in shock.
The palms of my hands started to hurt.
I hope
he's not actually mad at me.
What should I do?
I'm just terrified
to build this relationship with him.
What are you scared of?
Have you watched this movie
called
"Memories of Matsuko"?
Nope.
I apologize
for being born as a human.
What are you talking about?
A quote from the movie.
The leading female character
grew up without her father's love.
She became this person
who desperately wanted to be
loved by others.
I don't want to be that kind of person.
I can live happily
by myself.
I don't need love.
In my opinion,
you really hurt him this time.
Do you not regret it?
You know.
I originally thought that
he's one of those playboys
who could cut things off easily.
I didn't expect him
to be this serious.
You're right.
It does not feel good
to act so carefully
and to be so afraid of
losing someone.
Xiao Ning,
I need to warn you.
Are you still going to
have this crush on your boss?
I'm afraid that you'll get hurt.
Sometimes,
it's good to keep a distance.
Should we keep a distance?
Why are you so quiet today?
I'm not, Boss.
I'm trying to focus on driving.
I still need to warn you.
You need to think it through
whether you still want to
have this crush on your boss.
Sometimes, keeping a distance
might be a good thing.
(We are indeed from two different worlds.)
Is this what you refer to as focusing on driving?
I'm sorry, Boss.
I'll drive slowly.
What did you do last night?
I
drank a little with Sister Yan Yan.
Are you sober now?
I'm sober.
Jiang Xiao Ning,
I hope that you can focus
when you're working.
Do you hear me?
Yes.
I'm sorry, Boss.
(Now, it looks like)
(they're from the same world.)
(Chen Wen Wen)
Sister Wen Wen,
I saw the pictures
you sent me.
It's wonderful.
How can I show my appreciation?
If you really want to thank me,
help me design my photography exhibition.
Me?
I would love to,
but I'm still an assistant.
I'm not qualified.
What about recommending
a professional designer to you?
Sure.
Help me set up an appointment
with a designer
and have them come over.
I'll send you the address.
Okay.
Come on in.
You sober?
Boss,
I'm not an alcoholic.
How can I not be sober
at this time?
So,
what is it?
Do you remember
the photographer
I told you about last time?
She's going to hold a photography exhibition
and she wants our company to help her design it.
Sure.
Just talk to Su Man Lin.
Why Sister Man Lin?
She's responsible for
all the arts-related projects
in the company,
including
that art gallery project
from before.
What?
Is there a problem?
No.
It's just
I spoke highly of you
in front of her.
I said you're extremely talented,
elegant, handsome.
Definitely a top-notch designer in the industry.
If you can't go,
I'm afraid that she'll be disappointed.
Go to Su Man Lin.
She can definitely handle it.
Okay.
I'll leave then.
(Transaction completed)
Hello?
Mr. Xu.
The money has been transferred.
I transferred the construction payment
from before to...
Alright.
I don't need the details,
as long as it has been done.
But the numbers on the book
are really different.
If someone checks it,
they'll know for sure.
I'm worried...
No need to worry.
Even if someone does check,
they'll never know it's you.
Besides,
I'm here, aren't I?
Understood.
Alright.
Don't overthink it.
Thank you for having so much faith in me.
Why are you still
so polite with me
after all these years?
Don't forget to
come here to have a meal with me
this weekend.
Yes.
Good.
Hi, Brother Xu.
Xiao Ning,
I'll go pick you up tonight.
Let's go watch a movie together.
I'm still at work.
Not sure about the plans for the evening yet.
Okay, I'll let you go then.
Alright, we'll talk later.
Let's go another time.
I'm hanging up.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
When did you start
reporting directly to Mr. Gu
about projects?
I... I didn't.
This photography exhibition project.
Didn't you go over my head
and report it to Mr. Gu directly?
I'm sorry, Sister Man Lin.
I didn't think it through.
Think more before you act next time.
Let's go.
Sister Wen Wen.
Sorry you had to wait.
No problem.
This is the Vice President
and Design Director,
Su Man Lin.
Sister Man Lin,
this is my friend.
A photographer, Chen Wen Wen.
Turning this space
into an exhibition hall
is a nice idea.
The view is unobstructed
and the space is large enough.
More importantly, the price is reasonable.
However,
it might be a little difficult to construct.
Transportation of materials will be
a problem too.
And we're not sure if
it'll take a long time
to receive approval.
That's not a problem.
I've got time.
I'm just thinking...
It'll be impossible for
the entire space to be used for the exhibition.
That's fine. Half will be enough.
Even half will be too much.
My advice is
to make a third into indoor space
and make the rest
into a resting area.
Then integrate some landscaping
into the exhibition area.
I don't think that's a good idea.
Landscaping...
The addition of garden design
will liven up the atmosphere
of this rooftop.
Otherwise,
this rooftop
will be no different from
other rooftops in the CBD.
(*Short for Central Business District)
But I prefer
this open and boundless feeling.
Let me put it this way.
The purpose of accepting smaller-scaled,
arts-related projects like this
is not to
make a profit,
but to accumulate work
to get nominated for awards.
So, I urge you
to trust our professional
artistic vision.
We will definitely help you
attract people's attention.
Alright.
Let me think about it.
Do you have
any similar design plans
I could refer to?
Of course.
Please come to our office tomorrow.
I can explain everything
to you in detail.
Sure.
I'll go take a look.
Xiao Ning,
let's have dinner together.
I'm not off work yet.
It's after
business hours already.
Why are you looking at me?
It's up to you.
When you've made your decision,
please let Jiang Xiao Ning contact me.
I'll leave first.
Sister Man Lin, take care.
Sorry, Sister Wen Wen,
I thought too highly of myself.
I thought I could let
Boss handle your project himself.
As long as my requirements can be met,
it doesn't matter who will be designing it.
But I feel like
your Vice President
doesn't like you much.
The reason Sister Man Lin
got angry could be
because I went over her head
and reported to Boss directly.
It was my fault.
You really think
she's angry because you went over her head?
What else?
You said so yourself.
No girl
would not like
someone as exceptional
as your boss.
Maybe she's mad because
you're too close to your boss?
Do you think so?
I'm just guessing.
Sister Wen Wen,
how could you know so much about relationships?
Sometimes,
a heart-breaking experience
will make you grow up.
So I envy you
for having someone you like so much.
Cherish it.
Don't wait until you miss it
to regret it.
I do want to cherish it,
but I don't even have the courage
to make a love confession.
How come?
Like one of my older sisters said,
Boss and I
grew up in different environments
We have different life experiences.
Not to mention our outlooks and horizons.
This is not
the Jiang Xiao Ning I know.
Being in love with someone.
You need to have trust first
and then the courage.
Aren’t you
a courageous person?
But you said yourself.
One has to be careful when falling
in love with their bosses?
Love always comes first.
Just eat first.
(If you're drinking again tonight,)
(don't come to pick me up tomorrow.)
(I told you I'm not an alcoholic.)
(I'm already getting ready for bed.)
(Good night, Boss.)
Sister Wen Wen.
Xiao Ning.
This way, please.
Okay.
(Chuan Design Studio)
This way.
(CHUAN DESIGN STUDIO)
Sister Wen Wen.
Boss.
Gu Chuan.
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Is it you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪