♪I can't help but feel a little happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little nervous♪
♪The Earth is turning because of you♪
♪Without you, the Earth stops♪
♪You are the rainbow that fills up the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend of the four-leaves clover♪
♪I dreamt of a white-horse carriage and you becoming my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards the fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Am I the happiness you're looking for?♪
♪The deerlet inside me is lost♪
♪Holding your hand, let's count down to happiness♪
♪I can't help but be a little fragile♪
♪I can't help but feel a little gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who takes away all loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 05=
Mr. Gu,
did my drawing
really bring you inspiration?
It did help.
I'm so happy!
To think that the flower I drew
could bring you inspiration.
Not only the flower you drew
but also your attitude towards life.
I didn't know
I could be of such use.
That's the highest praise
I could possibly receive.
But you suddenly
said so much to me,
I need some time to digest everything.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Mr. Gu.
From now on,
you can call me Boss.
Why?
Before...
That was before.
Didn't you say that
bosses
always have a straight face?
In the future, I hope
you'll constantly remind me
to not always have a straight face,
to be happier.
Yes, Boss.
Also...
Boss, please go on.
Your drawing is
really ugly.
I was just drawing casually.
The drawing is ugly, but it's the
thought that counts.
Boss.
Everyone,
we're officially signing the contract
for the resort project in two days.
Signing?
That means we've sealed the deal?
Yes.
Great!
I thought all that work was for nothing.
Mr. Gu,
doesn't
great news like this
deserve a celebration?
Yes, yes, yes!
Mr. Gu,
how about going out
and treating us to a feast?
♪Fireflies all around♪
Sure.
Man Lin,
decide on a place with everyone,
I'll pay.
Then you have to join us.
That's right, Mr. Gu.
Join us.
You've never gone out
with us together.
They're right.
Mr. Gu, join us.
I'll pass.
It'll be boring if you don't come.
Let's have fun together.
Yeah!
Come with us.
Come with us. Come with us.
Alright.
Those who don't come will be considered
as being absent from work.
Oh right, one more thing.
Wang Kai,
give Jiang Xiao Ning a desk.
A desk?
As of today,
Jiang Xiao Ning has officially passed
her probation period.
♪One, two, three, count with me♪
♪If the youth is precious, then cheers♪
♪Those passionate dreams, follow my command♪
Thank you, Boss!
Thanks, everyone!
♪Chase recklessly, long live the young♪
Give it your all.
Those who contribute to the company
will be rewarded.
♪You are the most perfect when full of vitality♪
Reward?
♪If the youth is precious, then cheers♪
Xiao Ning, congrats, congrats, congrats!
You're awesome.
What is the reward?
I...
I've never got one.
How should I know?
What reward?
What is the reward?
I don't know either.
♪You are the most perfect when full of vitality♪
It's rare for Mr. Gu to join us.
How about having him
say a few words?
No need to applaud.
I don't have anything to say.
Boss.
Make sure to enjoy yourselves tonight.
I'm happy
to have this meal together with everyone.
Come one, dig in.
This looks pretty good.
There...
There aren't any wet wipes around.
Waiter!
I'll go.
Xiao Ning,
get me an empty cup.
Xiao Ning.
Kai wants a wet wipe,
so do I. Thanks.
Wet wipe, wet wipe,
empty cup.
Anything else?
That's all.
Man Lin,
get a waiter.
We shouldn't let our people
run around doing errands.
Okay.
Xiao Ning,
we couldn't have gotten
this resort project done without you.
How about a toast
to that?
Thank you.
Thanks, everyone.
Thank you, thank you.
Xiao Ning,
I heard He Sheng gave you a hard time.
He's difficult to deal with.
Thanks for your hard work.
It's my job.
Thanks.
Cheers.
Xiao Ning,
shouldn't you say something
to Mr. Gu?
Thanks.
Qi Hong,
Mr. Gu never
clinks glasses with anyone.
Are you setting Xiao Ning up for trouble?
We are us,
Jiang Xiao Ning is Jiang Xiao Ning.
It's different.
Boss,
I'm really grateful to you and Man Lin.
Here's to you.
I don't drink.
It's okay, I'll drink.
She finished her drink.
Yeah.
One more thing.
I'd like to ask for your forgiveness.
What?
Could you stand up?
I was drinking for liquid courage.
All my words of gratitude
are expressed in this hug.
Thank you, Boss.
What is going on?
You called me here
to watch this?
Public confession, a hug filled with love?
Thank you, Man Lin,
thank you,
thank you.
Xiao Ning must be drunk.
She drank too much, too much.
Let's drink to the hug of love.
Cheers, cheers.
Cheers.
You and Jiang Xiao Ning.
Don't!
I know what you're thinking.
There is nothing between me and her.
You went to meet a big shot like Mr. Qin,
and you only brought her with you.
That has got to be the first time in years?
I just wanted her to know that
the problems from before
have nothing to do with her.
Chuan,
if you feel something, just go with it.
Your eyes say you're taking it seriously.
Everyone is enjoying themselves,
are you sure you want to leave now?
Yes, I'll leave first.
Alright.
Call a designated driver then.
I won't drop you off.
I'm going to drop Man Lin off later.
That old pervert He Sheng
has been after her for a while.
Now that he has been fired,
who knows what he'll do?
I'll drop Man Lin off,
just to make sure she's safe.
Alright, I'm leaving it to you.
Boss! Boss!
Boss!
I'll leave you to it.
Boss.
Wait for me,
I'll go get the car right now.
You drank.
You want to go to jail for drunk driving?
Boss.
I'm sorry,
I shouldn't have drunk.
I'm leaving now.
See you at the office tomorrow.
Bye-bye.
What about giving you a lift?
It's about to rain.
Boss, I'm pretty sober.
I'm not drunk.
I know which bus to take.
I'm not drunk, not drunk.
Alright.
Boss.
You're the boss.
I wouldn't have drunk if I had known.
Could've earned some extra money as a designated driver.
Even now, you're still
thinking about earning money.
You're really something.
Yes, Boss.
Boss,
you look
kind of handsome.
You really are drunk.
You smiled!
Yeah, you should smile more often.
You look like a mannequin when you don't smile.
Okay, okay, okay.
You're drunk,
so everything you say is right.
Not drunk.
We're here?
Okay.
Thank you for driving me home, Boss.
Are you sure you can get home by yourself alright
in this state?
I'll be fine.
Don't worry, Boss.
It's just through here.
You go home and rest.
Let me know when you get home.
Okay.
Bye, Boss.
You go first.
I'm going then.
Go home.
I'll be fine.
Bye, Boss.
Bye.
Kind of drunk.
Hopefully, I didn't do anything stupid.
No,
I can't go home like this.
Can't let Grandma smell
the alcohol.
Let me walk it off
before going home.
Zhao Yan.
Why are you here?
To discuss our collaboration
with Manager Wei
and to treat you to dinner.
I'm on a diet. I'm not eating.
Speak to Manager Wei directly
about the collaboration.
Stop resisting. You need a man.
Can you get a mirror
to look at yourself?
Whether or not I need a man
has nothing to do with you.
Let go of me.
Give me a chance,
and give yourself
a chance.
Let go, you filthy woman!
Cursing me out?
I should be okay now.
Boss?
Hey Jiang Xiao Ning,
are you home yet?
I... am...
home.
Don't worry, Boss.
I'm fine.
What's that sound?
It's nothing, Boss.
Jiang Xiao Ning,
tell me the truth.
Are you not home yet?
Boss,
I didn't lie to you on purpose.
I was scared that Grandma
would smell the alcohol on me.
I wanted to get some air
and get rid of the alcohol smell.
Hurry.
Boss,
I met someone even drunker than me.
Compared to him,
I'm considered sober.
Hi,
have some water.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
He Sheng?
Little Miss Designated Driver.
You… What are you doing!
It's really you.
What a coincidence.
I've been looking for you desperately
but to no avail.
Who knew you would
come to me.
Give me back my phone.
I don't know you.
You've drunk too much.
I've drunk too much?
Could I have found you if I didn't drink too much?
I...
Let me tell you, Little Miss Designated Driver.
You're really something.
You caused me to lose my job.
Now the company
wants to search my past records.
Today, I'll show you
who you can mess with
and who you should never mess with
in your lifetime.
Let go of me.
-You dare to hit me?
-What's wrong with you?
Let go of me.
Let's go.
(Jiang Xiao Ning)
Move it.
Mr. He.
-Let's go.
-What are you doing?
You'll find out soon enough.
Move it.
Let's go.
Let go of me.
Let go of you?
You wish.
Let go of me.
Move it.
Mr. He.
Mr. He, what are you doing! Mr. He!
What am I doing?
You'll find out soon.
What are you doing?
Mr. He.
Little Miss Designated Driver
What do you think you're doing?
Boss.
Gu,
I was worried I wouldn't be able to find you.
Stop...stop...
stop fighting!
Stop fighting, stop fighting! Stop...
Boss!
Stop fighting!
Stop, stop fighting!
To hell with you.
-I'm going to kill you.
-Boss!
Little Miss Designated Driver.
You shouldn't have messed with me.
♪When I'm looking at you, I feel like
I'm electrocuted♪
♪Take my hand don't let it go♪
♪I'll follow you to the end of the world♪
♪He and she♪
♪Round and round, losing ground♪
♪Wandering Earth♪
♪Fading, wiped out♪
♪Round and round♪
♪I'll go♪
Boss!
♪Where the heart leads♪
♪Who is that♪
Boss, where's your phone?
I'll call an ambulance for you.
Boss.
♪In my memory♪
Boss, wake up, Boss.
Boss, you can't die, Boss.
♪I can't sleep♪
Boss.
♪Pieces piece together our encounter♪
♪I am willing to admit♪
♪I belonged to you from that moment on♪
♪I'm still not giving up♪
♪Despite going off-course♪
♪The clips flashback to awake your
silhouette in the shadows♪
♪The light in your eyes shines more and
more clearly, like the light♪
Boss, you scared me.
If you had lost your life saving me,
I'd regret it for the rest of my life.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Boss.
I'm sorry, it's all my fault.
I'm sorry.
I'll take you to the hospital, okay?
I'm sorry, Boss.
Jiang Xiao Ning,
you talk too much.
I'm sorry, Boss.
I don't know what to do.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Xu!
-Mr. Xu!
- Xiao Ning.
-Boss.
-Chuan.
What happened?
How did this happen?
He Sheng drank too much.
He bumped into me and wanted to take revenge.
This piece of trash
dared to do something like that.
But thankfully,
Boss came to my rescue on time.
Chuan,
are you okay?
I'm fine.
Xiao Ning and I
will go to the hospital to get patched up first.
We'll leave He Sheng to you.
(Surgical department)
Boss,
where did you go?
Has your wound been bandaged?
Yes, it has.
That's good.
The doctor prescribed some medication.
I'll go and get it.
You can rest here for a while.
Okay.
Tell me, what exactly happened?
This guy's name is He Sheng.
He drank too much
and assaulted my friend.
I don't know what happened but
then he fainted.
I'm guessing
he has done too many bad things.
It's karma.
Check this person's records.
He was indeed electrocuted.
In this thunderstorm,
especially outside,
in an open area.
He got electrocuted.
The IV helped,
he'll wake up soon.
Thank you.
No worries.
Where's your friend?
Injured.
Receiving treatment now.
Miss Officer,
you need to ensure justice
is served to evil people like him.
Mind your manners.
Don't electrocute me.
Don't...
Sir.
Don't electrocute me.
Sir...
Sir.
Let me ask you,
what happened?
Police?
P… Police?
Officer.
I...
Officer,
let… let me tell you.
You need to believe me.
Everything I'm saying is true.
That person releases electricity.
That guy released electricity and
electrocuted me.
He electrocuted me twice.
I was scared to death. I'm telling you,
everything I'm saying is true.
It was so scary.
Sir,
do you remember how much you drank?
No,
I'm telling you, Officer,
listen to me.
Have you seen the comics about
Pikachu?
Let me tell you,
he's Pikachu.
He electrocuted me.
He...
Movies work too. The Flash.
He's the Flash.
Let go.
That's enough, He Sheng.
How much have you drunk?
You reek of alcohol.
You
assaulted someone
and now you're telling lies.
Lying to the police.
Just you wait,
you're going to be punished
to the full extent of the law.
He's lying.
Listen,
his friend Gu Chuan
is so scary.
Officer,
-you must…
-Stop being so loud!
This is a hospital.
Be quiet.
You're too much.
We've verified his identity.
His name is He Sheng.
He's involved in a financial crime case
and two sexual harassment cases.
He's on bail pending trial.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Oh no, oh no.
My head hurts, I feel awful.
I feel awful, I feel awful.
I don't know anything.
I'm telling you,
stop pretending.
How about this.
Watch over him.
When he's sober,
bring him to the station for questioning.
Okay.
You.
Get in touch with your friend.
We need to
verify the situation
with the other two witnesses.
They're here in this hospital.
Is this your friend's?
Yes.
Okay, let's go.
My head hurts.
Let me sleep a little longer, just a little longer.
I feel awful.
He Sheng had too much to drink.
I gave him a bottle of water to drink.
I didn't have time to react,
then he snatched my phone away.
He blamed me for causing him to lose his job
and dragged me off by force.
Luckily, Boss arrived just in time.
He even used the beer bottle to attack us.
My mind just went blank.
It was
raining heavily then.
The thunder was very loud.
There was a lot of lightning.
Then He Sheng fainted.
Boss and I both got injured.
And then,
we came to the hospital
to get our wounds treated.
So according to you,
he first obstructed you
at the entrance of your community.
Yes.
I think I more or less understand
the situation now.
Go back and rest well
tonight.
We'll search the
surveillance records at the entrance
of your community
to verify what you said.
As for He Sheng,
I'll wait until he's sober
to continue with my questioning.
We may reach out to you
for your assistance and cooperation
in the future.
I’ll definitely cooperate.
Even if they don't cooperate,
I'll make sure they cooperate.
Okay,
I'll be taking my leave.
Let me see you off.
It's okay, thank you.
I have the police car.
At least, let me walk you to the hospital entrance.
Boss,
are you okay?
You don't look too good.
Drive me home.
Not waiting for Mr. Xu?
Let's not wait.
Okay.
I already said you didn't have to see me off.
I insist.
Sorry that you had come here so late at night.
Plus, there are a lot of weirdos out there nowadays.
A pretty police officer like you
should be careful out there.
We may contact you
if we need anything else in the future.
Okay.
Also, ma'am,
that He Sheng
has always been a drunkard.
Lying is in his nature.
Make sure you're not
fooled by him.
Thank you for your reminder.
Goodbye.
Bye-bye.
Come out.
I'm telling you.
Growing up,
even my parents haven’t ever hit me.
You're too violent.
I'm telling you,
if the test results show that
something is wrong with me,
I'm so going to make you pay.
And
even if you had to hit me,
you didn't have to hit me so hard.
Let’s say you had to hit me this hard,
you didn't have to hit me on the face.
Listen,
if I don't get any women in the future...
No,
if my face is ruined,
what am I supposed to do?
Don't come near me.
A grown man whining and weeping like that,
what an embarrassment.
Wait, who are you?
What has this got to do with you?
My mouth is my own,
I can say what I want.
Is it your business?
Do you believe I'll hit you?
You want to hit me?
You can't even win a fight with her
and you want to fight me?
I wouldn't mind
compensating you for your injuries
along with this pretty lady.
But can your body...
Are you going to get tested for your injuries?
Yes.
Just you wait.
Do you still remember...
Boss,
be careful.
I'm fine.
You can go home now.
Are you sure?
But
I'm still worried about your condition.
How about I wait a while?
Okay, up to you.
But don't disturb me.
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The destined one♪
♪Guide me forward♪
Charging.
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Who is it♪
These two
didn't even tell me before leaving.
I'm hungry.
Buy me something to eat.
Then starve to death.
How about I use the money meant
to pay for your tests
for your funeral?
No, you...
What was wrong
with my taste?
How did I fall for you?
Looking at you,
who would want you?
Me.
You do have bad taste.
You don't even fancy
such a pretty lady.
Get your hand off me.
I'm helping you.
I don't need it.
Serves you right.
If you touch me again,
you'll end up like him.
And you,
are you going to get tested or not?
I don't have time to waste on you.
No, no, no.
-Not testing.
-Me!
I want an examination of my wounds.
Trying to pull a fast one?
No.
If it's not convenient for you today,
I'll make an appointment with you.
Let's add each other on WeChat.
Do you want to scan me or I scan you?
Do you want me to kick you?
Yes.
As long as it's something you're giving me,
I want it.
What's the situation?
Who called the police.
Officer.
Why is it you again?
Hello, Grandma.
Xiao Ning.
It's so late, why aren't you home yet?
I'm at the office, working on a project.
We were notified that we need to
work overtime last-minute.
Go to sleep,
don't wait up for me.
Burning the midnight oil is bad for your health.
Take care of your health.
Don't worry, Grandma.
Sleep early.
I'm hanging up.
Boss.
Boss, are you okay?
If there's anything,
call me anytime. I'm downstairs.
Take it easy.
So you're sure you want to settle?
Yes.
It wasn't me who called the police
in the first place.
What's the situation with you?
Officer,
as long as she's willing to compensate,
I can resolve matters peacefully.
Officer,
can I call the police for workplace
sexual harassment?
Zhao Yan,
don't push it, you!
I initially didn't want to
use public resources
and bring trouble to the police.
There was a reason why I hit you.
If we're really going to haggle over every ounce,
it's not certain who should be compensated.
Fine.
Since the police are here today.
Let's forget it.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, thank you.
Then I'll get going.
Take care.
Stay away from this person.
Stay safe.
How about I drive you home?
That won't be necessary.
Why are you smiling like that?
I'll never forget
what you did to me earlier.
You want revenge?
I'll take you on any time.
You seriously humiliated me,
but somehow, I kind of liked it.
Anyway, it's
a magical feeling.
I've never felt that way before.
I don't add strangers on WeChat.
You hit me.
It wouldn't hurt
to send me a red pocket.
This way, we can write off
whatever happened between us.
Plus,
after you add me,
you can delete me.
You hitting me is a fact.
A red pocket is not too much to ask for, right?
(Zhao Yan's red pocket)
(Delete contact)
Done.
Want me to hit you again?
Sure.
If you want to.
Weirdo.
Look,
now that
we're starting over,
shouldn't we
re-introduce ourselves?
Hello, Zhao Yan.
I'm Xu Cheng Ran.
How did you know my name?
I heard that person
call you by your name.
I'm not interested in getting to know you.
Don't follow me.
(The message is sent successfully but rejected
by the recipient.)
Charging complete.
♪Cicada chirping at the end of the street♪
♪Two sleeping cats♪
♪Coolness after the rain♪
♪Endless dreams ♪
♪Diana pink roses♪
♪Heartbeat like the green grass♪
♪Time passing by gently♪
♪Our eyes meet inadvertently♪
♪Do you feel it in your heart♪
♪Open the doors and windows of the new moon♪
♪Embrace the longing for pouring rain♪
♪You smile and say hello♪
(Dr. P, Mobile)
Hello?
Gu,
what happened?
I received a warning that says
your heart is discharging a high
amount of electricity.
It was an accident.
Doctor,
why did I lose consciousness
for around ten seconds?
Does it have to do with the discharge?
No, no, no.
That's a protective mechanism
in case of an overload.
When the mechanical heart
discharges too much electricity,
the system will take
around ten seconds to reboot
in order to protect the device.
Backup power will also be
activated simultaneously.
But you need to be careful.
The reboot is very dangerous.
If it takes too long to reboot,
brain hypoxia
will put your life in danger.
Okay,
I got it.
Gu,
are you in love?
No.
Gu,
before I resolve these issues,
make sure you keep
your emotions under control.
Falling in love
will cause excitement
and elevate your heart rate.
Your mechanical heart will discharge electricity
and malfunction.
Holding hands,
hugging,
kissing,
intimate physical contact...
Every single fluctuation in your
emotions will cause
fluctuations in your heart function.
So, falling in love
is a very dangerous thing for you.
Stop fighting!
Boss!
Gu, are you still there?
Gu?
I'm listening.
Don't be so pessimistic.
Give me some more time,
I'll find a solution.
A solution?
You've been saying that
for ten years.
Where is the solution?
I've heard enough.
I'm hanging up.
Gu!
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Is it you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪