♪I can't help but feel a little bit happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little bit nervous♪
♪The earth is spinning because of you♪
♪Without you, the earth will stop♪
♪You are the rainbow
that fills up the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend
of the four-leaves clover♪
♪I dreamt about white-horse carriage
and you became my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards the fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Are you the happiness that I'm looking for?♪
♪The doe inside me is lost♪
♪I'll hold your hand and
let's count down to our happiness♪
♪I can't help but be a little bit fragile♪
♪I can't help but be a little bit gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who took away
all of my loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 08=
(Jiang Xiao Ning)
(Operating Hours, Come on)
Mr. Gu, this is for you.
What is this?
A present.
Mr. Gu, I wish you good health and happiness.
Aunt.
Aunt, please hear me out first.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Have you forgotten?
You foolish girl.
Your father never took a single cent
from anyone.
Why could he embezzle
tens of millions of public funds?
That is all because of this
so-called good friend!
Your father.
My brother.
Would I not know what kind of
person he is?
Dead men tell no tales.
No.
How could he
be framed by such a person?
Do you understand?
It's already in the past.
Besides, Brother Xu has nothing to do with this.
I'm telling you I won't forget this.
I will never
move on from this.
We'll leave.
We are moving out right now.
Mom.
Let's go.
Please calm down.
You've only just recovered.
Grandma is getting on in years.
She couldn't stand being in distress.
I'll head back first.
I'll visit you another day.
You don't have to go.
It's us who should move out.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Are you leaving?
Aunt, aunt.
Mom.
Aunt!
Aunt.
When you were admitted to the hospital,
grandma forgot to turn off the stove
and almost burned the entire house down.
I don't have any money left
to compensate the landlord.
You should know that
the money used to pay your hospital bills
was borrowed from my company.
I can't afford
any agent fees or deposits anymore.
Xiao Ning,
you have to understand.
You know it too.
I can't talk about your father.
Whenever I do, I just get so angry.
I just couldn't help it.
I'm not blaming you.
Don't cry.
You poor thing.
All right.
I promise that
I will work hard
and make a lot of money.
When the house is fixed,
we will go back to our place.
Okay?
Get some rest with grandma.
I'll go and talk to Brother Xu.
Don't ever mention his name.
Xiao Ning.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, Brother Xu.
Brother Xu, please understand my aunt.
That's the way she is.
She's just harsh with her words.
She probably
still couldn't let go of the past.
I understand.
But we don't know
the truth behind it.
No matter what happened,
we still grew up together.
What happened between the last generation
stays with them.
It won't change us,
no matter the circumstances.
What about you?
Will you blame me
just like your aunt does?
I won't.
You're still Brother Tang Xu
that I know since little.
Besides, it doesn't hurt me
as much now.
It's as you said.
Being alive
is about moving forward.
I still have a lot of important things
to do.
I believe
my parents are watching me
from heaven.
If I'm sad,
they will be upset too.
I know
you're not involved.
But...
I understand.
Xiao Ning.
For you,
I will try my best to let her
change her mind about me.
I'm sorry, Brother Xu.
I never thought things
would end up like this.
When our house is fixed,
we'll move back immediately.
Thank you, Brother Xu.
I feel much refreshed after a bath.
Did I have a bad fall
just now?
Did you lose your memory?
Who am I?
Where am I?
But why is my phone
not ringing at all?
Why didn't Yan Yan look for me?
Why are you still working at this hour?
Don't push yourself so hard to earn money for me.
I'm very glad
but I care for you more.
What are you so invested in?
Doing my notes.
Whose notebook is this?
Mine.
Your notebook?
Such a girly notebook?
(Jiang Xiao Ning)
Jiang Xiao Ning?
You are annotating Jiang Xiao Ning's design?
You care for her this much?
She has huge potential.
She deserves some guidance.
I think you're getting old that
you are starting to like to preach.
Then do I have the potential?
You?
Forget about it.
No matter how you insult me,
even if you throw me
the nastiest remarks,
you can't extinguish
the burning curiosity in my heart.
Tell me.
Did you fall for Jiang Xiao Ning?
Yes.
She's ambitious and motivated.
Plus, she's optimistic and full of life.
If there is proper guidance,
she can be
a great architect in the future.
What I feel for her
is how an employer
likes his employee.
That's all.
That's all?
If that's the case,
you can't be the one
to return this notebook to her.
Why?
As her boss,
you annotated her design.
That's already a big favor.
To not let her misunderstand,
I will be the one
to return this notebook to her.
That's decided.
Chuan.
Thank you.
What for?
For giving me
a proper reason
to go to Yan Yan.
This will be my ultimate weapon
when she doesn't want to see me.
That would have to wait until
she's willing to see you.
Whether she wants to or not,
I'm going to see her.
(Jiang Xiao Ning)
Can you put on some clothes?
Do you not realize
you wear the same clothes every day?
It's either white, gray, or black.
I have zero desire
to wear your clothes.
Sure, then don't wear any.
Lend me some clothes.
Here is the
detailed business plan.
Mr. Xu, what do you think?
It's good.
Very good.
This operation plan
is done very well.
Thank you, Director Xu.
I never thought
you could work things out so quickly.
I'm not wrong about you.
Don't worry.
I will do better.
Oh, right.
Recently,
I have some funds.
Think of a way
to withdraw it through your company.
What's wrong?
Is it a big amount?
It's not.
I'll tell you
the details later.
Do you have any problems?
No, I don't.
Leave it to me.
You may go now.
Why are you here?
I called but you didn't answer.
So I thought I might drop by.
Are you coming in for work?
Yes.
But I have some documents to sort out.
Why don't you come in?
Okay.
Good morning, Jiang Xiao Ning.
Mr. Xu, I'm sorry.
I didn't know you are here.
I saw nothing.
It's fine.
You came at the right time.
Ask Yan Yan out for me again.
Mr. Xu.
Please don't make things difficult for me.
Sister Yan Yan
almost had me killed the last time.
What's with that death stare?
She's my assistant.
Look at you being protective of her.
Fine.
You don't have to help me.
I have my dignity.
I'll think of a way myself.
I'll give you two some time alone.
Bye.
Oh, right.
My notebook.
I think I left it here.
Did you see it?
He just took it.
Don't worry.
He'll return it to you.
No, what brings you here?
Did something happen to Xiao Xu?
No, Xiao Xu is fine.
Don't worry.
That's a relief.
I was wondering
why did you come all of a sudden.
You will be released
after a few days.
I might get too busy with work
to come and pick you up.
I had some free time today
so I came to visit.
Thank you.
Anyway...
Earlier on,
Xiao Xu came to see me.
He told me that
you have been good to him.
And that you trust him a lot
by entrusting him with the company.
He should be visiting you.
I told him.
No matter what,
you're still his father.
Thank you.
All these years,
I'm glad I have you.
Tang.
You're sounding like a stranger now.
We are friends.
We are like brothers.
What I promised you,
I will see it through.
I really do see Xiao Xu
as my own son.
Nice earrings.
It's matching
my outfit today.
Qi Hong.
Miss Su.
Where is Jiang Xiao Ning?
I think she went out.
You think?
Yes.
Wang Kai informed me
a few days ago
that Jiang Xiao Ning's
working hours and work tasks
will be arranged by Mr. Gu.
So she doesn't need to punch in.
Okay. Carry on with your work.
That was scary.
Boss.
Do you need my help?
No.
I'll wait for you then.
Okay.
What are you reading?
I'm doing my revision.
I'm about to sit
for my final examinations.
If I don't, I might not be able to graduate.
Boss.
Could I ask you some questions
when you are free?
Come here.
I don't really understand this.
There are many elements
that cannot be altered in architecture.
For instance, the shape factor of a building
should be lesser than
or equal to 0.4.
I'll show you.
Look.
This part here
plays a key role.
If you don't do it well,
it will affect...
Affect what?
Boss.
You talked a lot.
You must be thirsty.
♪Caught off-guard by our first encounter♪
I'll get you some water.
♪And the corner of your mouth is lifting♪
♪Heart pounding involuntarily, this phenomenon♪
♪Am I abnormal or are you shining♪
(What is going on?)
(My cheeks are burning.)
(This is bad.)
(Have I really caught feelings)
(for my boss?)
♪Hmm...♪
(Why would this happen?)
(There must be something wrong)
(with the mechanical heart.)
Boss, have some water.
It's fine. I'm not thirsty.
I'm not thirsty.
I'm sorry, Boss.
For wasting your time.
I'll clean up your table.
It's okay. I'll do it myself.
It's a blackout.
Boss.
It's...
It's not because of me, right?
It's got nothing to do with you.
It's just a short circuit.
It has always been this way.
It's always been this way?
But this residence
seems high-end.
I wonder why.
How about this?
I'll ask the management to come over
and have a look.
(Dr.P)
(Heart rate. One new notification.)
(Monitoring heart rate is rising.)
Are they doing something intense?
I just left and they can't hold themselves back.
But
will Chuan be okay?
I guess it's just me.
Come on in, please.
There's suddenly a blackout
for no reason.
Please take a look
to find out the problem.
The electrical panel is...
Where's him?
Do you mean the electrical panel?
I know where it is.
This unit often had blackouts.
I'll leave it to you guys. Thank you.
Often?
Boss.
Could it be that he got an electric shock
and passed out?
Boss, are you in there?
Boss.
Boss, are you there?
It's gorgeous.
What is this?
Don't touch it!
Boss.
Who let you in?
I'm sorry, Boss.
You didn't answer when I was calling for you.
I was worried that something had happened
so I went looking for you.
I never thought
I would have discovered your secret.
Wh... What secret?
In this very room,
you must have done...
live streaming sessions.
There's no way.
Where are the computers and video equipment?
Go out.
Boss.
Boss...
You're not allowed to enter this room
without my permission next time.
And...
I'm not an online streamer.
Then what's this room for?
This room...
This room is
a virtual reality gaming room.
It's like "Ready Player One".
I know that.
Boss,
you're always so stressed at work,
it's normal to take a break occasionally.
Boss,
are you afraid that someone
will say you're goofing around?
No,
there's a precedent
for the utilization of virtual reality
in the field of architectural design.
Are you
now conducting research into a spectacular design?
Something groundbreaking?
Impressive.
But rest assured.
As your assistant,
I'll surely help you
to keep it from others.
Okay?
Okay. Hurry up and head to the office now.
Leave now.
You wait a second. I'll go get the car.
Wait.
The weather is pretty good today.
I would like to go take a walk.
Is it okay?
It's not far.
But I already didn't go to work
in the morning,
If I'm not going to work in the afternoon...
As long as you're with me,
you've already started working.
Let's go.
Okay.
Last time she told me that she was at work,
then she asked me out here to meet.
Then her workplace
is probably around here.
As long as there's perseverance filled with love,
I'm certain that I'll get to see her.
How come only one minute has passed?
I feel that one year has passed instead.
Love is so torturing.
Why is the wind so strong?
My hair is such a mess.
What's wrong, Boss?
Let's go.
Go buy milk with me.
Okay.
Hello. Welcome.
(Pure milk)
Why are you picking so meticulously?
Many aren't able to grab the red packets
for food delivery,
so they're reluctant to order in.
For me, I'll take it to another lower level.
For even an item worth 5 yuan,
I also need to think it through.
Welcome to the world of the poor.
Boss,
I worked at a convenience store before.
The store manager usually
places the food that's expiring soon at the front.
So you take the one placed at the back,
it'll be fresher.
Even though it's expiring soon,
it still needs to be bought, right?
He's apparently a warm-hearted person,
why is his face always expressionless?
And this.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Chen Chen.
Why are you here?
The store that we worked together at before
had shut down,
then I was transferred here.
You...
How have you been?
I've got a
full-time job.
I'm with an architectural design company.
So impressive.
Then we should grab something to eat
when you're free.
Okay. Let's talk about it when I'm on my rest day.
Okay.
Wait.
These two are for you.
Thank you.
Then I'll leave first.
Bye-bye.
Remember we're going to eat together.
Is he someone you know?
We were in the same faculty in university.
The same faculty.
The most handsome guy in our university.
Lots of girls want to take pictures with him
just to post it on Weibo
and Moments to show off.
Him?
Let's go, Boss.
Let's take one more.
Come.
Is it that this dimwit is waiting for me?
(Meco Store)
Boss,
give me a second.
(The most handsome guy in our university.)
(Lots of girls want to take pictures with him)
(just to post it on Weibo)
(and Moments to show off.)
Boss,
you should try the cherry and berry drink of Meco's.
It tastes really good.
I've never drunk this kind of drink
which has no nutrition at all.
This fruit tea
contains real tea and fruit juice.
Fruit juice
can provide us with vitamins
and tea can help us to lose weight.
Just give it a try.
Only girls drink it.
I only drink milk and water.
Boss,
a tasty drink
will cheer you up.
Maybe this
tastes better than milk and water?
Just give it a try.
We came all the way here
just for it, right?
Just a sip.
Well, this drink...
Try it.
How is it?
It's so-so.
Is it?
Then give me back.
Give me back if you don't want to drink.
You... You said it's not good...
Boss,
do you feel better after drinking it?
Stop talking.
Doesn't it taste good?
Yan Yan.
(Cafe YELLOW Garden Restaurant)
It's such a coincidence.
Are you waiting for me?
I just arrived here not long ago.
I happened to pass by.
I happened to bump into you.
Bye.
Don't leave in a hurry.
I was in the wrong last time.
I shouldn't ask Jiang Xiao Ning
to deceive you and ask you out.
I promise I won't dare to do so anymore.
I won't lie to you anymore.
Did you tell a lie today?
I didn't.
Your nose is getting longer.
I saw that
you have been sitting here the whole day.
Wait.
You have been looking at me the whole day?
It's really touching.
Yan Yan,
I know that you have feelings for me.
I've never met someone
who is so thick-skinned.
Let me tell you.
I have no time to spout nonsense with you.
Leave me alone.
Don't follow me.
Women like speaking with a forked tongue.
When you asked me to leave you alone,
you were hoping that I could tag along instead.
Okay. Then you must follow closely.
Didn't you say that women like
speaking with a forked tongue?
You already ordered me to follow you,
I wouldn't dare to defy
the order of the queen.
Otherwise, I would be tortured.
Okay.
I think you truly wish to be tortured.
Let's go.
For the three-dimensional rendering
of the art gallery's design proposal,
it's basically the situation.
Mr. Gu,
if there's no issue
with the blueprint,
I'll submit the proposal.
Tomorrow is the day for the
submission of proposals.
We need to make haste.
Mr. Gu.
Then we'll submit this proposal.
That's it?
Okay.
(Yoga Room)
Are you all right?
I...
You must be kidding.
I'm completely fine.
Go and take your bath quickly.
You still need to go home.
How about you?
Me?
I...
I think the environment here is pretty good.
I'll go and get a membership card done later.
Go ahead.
After you.
I insist.
Okay.
Keep it up.
Be persistent.
(Is my aesthetic outdated?)
(Why is this guy handsome?)
What happened to you?
What's wrong?
Is it weird?
Why don't you stand up?
I'm tired of walking for 30 years.
Crawling once in a while gives me
a feeling of nostalgia.
What's wrong?
Where did you go?
If I'm to say I came back from the gym,
will you believe it?
If you said you went with Zhao Yan,
I would believe that.
Chuan,
you're truly the one who knows me well.
Seriously?
You really can't stand up?
I can.
Let me see if you can stand up now.
Come.
You've got no conscience at all.
That was fast.
Why did you
go to the gym out of the blue?
There are too many
young handsome guys at the gym.
I'm worried about
Yan Yan being alone.
Let me ask you something.
Do you think this look of mine now
is what young people like?
I always like it anyway.
As for whether young people would like it,
I have no idea then.
After all, I'm also an old man.
Moreover, I truly can't get hold
of the aesthetic of the youngsters nowadays.
Why did you ask me this question all of a sudden?
Could it be that someone
said you're not good-looking?
How could that be possible?
Nobody dares to say so.
I just wanted
to know your thoughts.
Chuan, don't worry.
You're still my true love.
I just keep Yan Yan company occasionally.
Don't be jealous.
OK. Alright.
Let me show you a photo.
Do you think...
Do you think this guy looks handsome?
Is he handsome?
Who is the girl beside him?
I'm asking you if this guy is handsome.
Pretty handsome.
Who is he?
What if he's compared with me?
Then you still look better.
Bosom buddy.
You're indeed my bosom buddy.
Be gentle.
But if you're compared with him,
your handsomeness seems to be a bit
outdated.
Outdated?
Where are you going, Chuan?
Don't you leave.
Carry me back to your room.
I really can't crawl back to my house.
You're staying the night here again?
Chuan.
Okay. Then you lie here.
It's quite suitable for you.
Chuan.
Don't be so unfeeling, okay?
You're handsome, okay?
You're not outdated, I am.
Chuan.
Boss, good morning.
Good morning.
What's wrong, Boss?
What is this?
It's a hairpin.
There's a hairpin in your pocket.
Maybe they gave it to me
as a gift when I bought milk yesterday.
Buy milk and get a free hairpin?
Hmm.
How could a hairpin be given with milk?
Come. I'll give it to you then.
Buy milk
and get a free hairpin?
It looks pretty good on me.
Thank you, Boss.
Hello, Ms. Cheng.
Is there anything?
I just want to know
if you can solve my problem.
I've discussed this with other designers
in a meeting.
The wall in front of your art gallery
is truly a conundrum.
If it's not demolished,
it'll affect the aesthetic appeal
of the entire design.
Chuan Design
is considered a top-notch studio in the industry.
And you can't even get the overhaul
of an art gallery done well?
We set high standards on design.
We don't want to change the proposal easily.
In fact, Ms. Cheng,
we're being responsible for you.
We don't wish
to show you
an unsatisfactory design.
Your biggest responsibility towards me
is to keep this wall for me.
Our company has changed a few designers
along the way.
We've also submitted more than ten proposals.
The problem is attributed to the wall.
Just be honest with me.
Is it that you can't handle that?
That's not the case.
We just hope that you...
I don't want to listen to this.
Chuan Design is so well-known.
My only requirement
is to keep this wall.
You can't even complete
the design of an art gallery.
How disappointing it is!
Ms. Cheng, don't be anxious.
Let's think it through again, okay?
I'll wait for your call then.
In fact, what I want to say is that
now he has finally
found a girl he likes.
A girl he likes?
Yes.
He even told us that
the girl is his assistant.
In fact,
he's my son.
I know him better than anyone.
He, himself might not even know
he's deeply in love with that girl.
Is she called
Jiang Xiao Ning?
Sister Man Lin.
Is this a newly bought hairpin?
It's a gift with the purchase of milk.
It looks pretty good on you.
There's a project for you to handle.
Me?
You're not confident?
Then forget about it.
No. I'm willing to accept it.
It's just that...
I'm not sure
if I can do it well.
But I'll try my utmost.
I can see that you're pretty hardworking.
You've always wanted
to try your hand at architectural design.
I'm giving you a chance this time
for you to get training.
It lies in your hands
whether you can do it well.
What's the project about?
It's very simple.
This is
the design project for an art gallery.
There is an old wall there and the client doesn't
want it to be demolished.
But if it's not demolished,
our design
won't be presented perfectly.
You
go and convince her to demolish the wall.
For the rest of the matters, do keep
your wits about you.
You need to play it by ear.
Okay. Thank you, Sister Man Lin.
You can do it.
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off guard♪
♪Sets foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Is it you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪