Get lost.
Kill them.
Yes, Mr. Napat.
Ouch!
Why are you here?
What are you doing here?
My dad and my brother
ordered me
to learn bedroom skills
and please you.
Do you like it,
huh?
Mr. Phisit.
There's no one else here.
Do you want to
sleep with me?
Hey!
Can you stop saying things
you don't mean?
I told you not to go
home, but you insisted.
Are you trying to
drive me mad?
(He's worried about me.)
(But does he mean it?)
I never understood why
you wanted to destroy
your brother.
But now,
I want to destroy him
even more than you do.
I even want to kill him.
(That won't do.)
(Mom is still
in their hands.)
No.
Don't kill him yet.
Make him suffer.
Take everything from him.
Destroy him completely.
Will you help me?
If it's for you,
I'll do anything.
But he serves
the governor.
Whoever hurts you
won't end well.
(It worked.)
Ouch!
(Napat,)
(I need you to see me
like this.)
(Only when
I'm at my worst)
(will you decide
to help me.)
Let go!
Whip him.
Here you go.
(Come on. Hit me.)
(The more you beat me,)
(the more Napat
will pity me.)