Can you take it off?
Of course.
Are you sure
you want me to?
(Should I trust him?)
(If he can remove it,)
(will he always
protect me?)
(Forget it.)
(With where we stand now,)
(it's not
the right time yet.)
I was kidding.
This bracelet
is a symbol
of my family.
How could I remove it?
I'll get going.
Is my skill that bad?
He always leaves
so coldly.
He didn't even hesitate.
Napat, the Phisit family's
notorious playboy.
The second son
of the family.
The current head
of the family is Lock.
He holds
absolute authority.
Nothing happens
without his approval.
He's mysterious and has
never appeared in public.
(Napat is second in
command in the family.)
(How much influence
does he have?)
(Can he be of use to me?)
Is that bracelet
a shackle?
Yes.
Can you take it off?
If you remove it
and pass the first test
I set for you,
I'll follow through
with the plan.
And you
will slowly become
the blade in my hand.