(Seven years ago)
I'll stay with you for a while.
How's it going Liu's matter?
When is the funeral?
The day after tomorrow.
His parents will come.
He was a good kid.
He was clever,
reliable,
and polite.
When he came to our house
for dinner last week,
I was talking about
finding him a girlfriend.
God is cruel.
Fortunately, he's not married.
If he had a wife and kids,
they'd be so desperate.
You always say
being a policeman
is not only your career
but also your dream.
I respect that.
But have you got what you deserve?
You've been a policeman for 10 years.
You stayed in the same position
for 7 years.
You get up so early
and go to bed so late
every day.
Feifei still hasn't
called you Dad.
Count the days.
How often do you come home?
Think about Tai.
You were classmates,
and you became policemen
in the same year.
He's a deputy director now.
Is it really worth it?
Tai is smart
and capable.
I'm not
as smart as him.
I need to work hard.
How much more effort do you need?
Liu was also hard-working,
and he was young,
but he died, right?
Do you know...?
Do you know I'm so worried about you?
I can't imagine.
If you were the one lying there,
I'd lose my husband,
and Feifei would lose her dad.
I have a bad temper,
and I often yell at you,
but... but at least you're alive,
and I can yell at you.
If you die,
I can only yell at your grave...
Stop.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I made you worry.
Since my father died,
I've been dealing with
the family business alone.
I'm tired.
I'm so tired.
Can you quit the job?
Can you come back to help me out?
I've been a policeman for 10 years.
I've never wanted to do anything else.
Xuan.
I've made up my mind.
I only want
to do one thing right in this life.
Please understand me, okay?
Are you afraid of gunshots?
If you're afraid,
stay away from it, okay?
=Black&White Forest=
=Episode 8=
(Tuan Island Market)
(Wen's Tuan Island Trading Co., Ltd.)
Aunt Chen,
have some water.
Don't worry.
I'll take Zhi back
safe and sound.
Wu.
Come here.
Bao is not here.
When you see them, don't start a fight.
You can accept any terms
except for
Tuan Island's
shares.
Okay.
Xi.
I think you're
the most educated man
in this team.
And you're handsome.
We're here
for one thing.
Release him.
Bao said he could be
responsible.
How much do you want?
Name the price.
Bao is so generous.
Bur Lao'er also said,
if you want the man,
give us the shares of Tuan Island.
Are you dreaming?
How dare you ask for the shares?
Stingy, stop bluffing.
We also talked to his mother.
If she wants her son,
give us the shares.
No other way.
Stop acting like
a disgusting lickspittle!
Listen, fight or die.
Do you want me to feed you to fish?
Retreat.
Calm down.
Let's go!
(Crispy Chicken)
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Try this.
I just had a meal.
I'm full. You can eat it.
How's it going?
After you left,
only an old man came,
and he left in a minute.
I don't think
the fried chicken is delicious.
Hello, Mr. Xing.
I'm on it. Don't worry.
Mr. Xing,
we spotted him.
He's heading north.
Follow him.
Seize the opportunity.
Mr. Zhou,
he said the suspect
was heading north.
- Chen.
- Yes, sir.
Cross Sanbao Street
and keep an eye on the exit.
Anyway, don't let him
out of your sight.
- Catch him at the right time.
- Yes, sir.
- Go.
- Okay.
You too.
(Crispy Chicken)
Tianyi,
a young boy
just bought a lot of chicken with cash.
I'll follow him.
Attention, attention.
The target has shown up.
Get him.
Hurry.
Who are you?
You don't know me.
Why are you arresting me?
What's wrong with you?
Captain Zhou,
I saw him at the birthday party
of Sun Changhai's uncle.
You've finished your work.
Get out.
(Sun Changhe)
Mr. Xing.
Take him to our car.
Go.
- Sir.
- Okay.
Where are you going?
See that van?
Go 50 meters and stop.
Can't you walk?
Or are you cheating on your wife?
My grandpa can live a long life
because he never minds
others' business.
- Okay.
- Hurry up.
Officers,
I've told you everything I know.
I've only been here for half a year.
I don't have friends.
Well,
my cousin asked me
to send something for him.
Okay?
That's all?
I'm asking you one last time.
Where is your cousin?
How should I know?
I'm just a delivery guy.
How can I know where my boss is?
If I do, I'll tell you.
No one wants to go to jail.
You know what to do.
Let him take it.
(Boss)
Hello.
Did you get it?
Yes.
Should I send it to
Liujiazhuang or Gaoheyan?
Gaoheyan.
Talk to you later.
Officers, I'll tell you everything.
Gaoheyan
is five kilometers north of Gaojiatun.
There's a river bank.
(Wen Binbin)
Mr. Xing, it's Bin.
I found him.
Come over.
(The Big Market)
Ten minutes ago,
the target headed north
via 203 Village Highway.
(203 Village Highway)
Keep me informed.
Thanks.
Chen, turn right at the next corner.
No problem.
(Emergency Room)
Mr. Xing, over here.
Bin.
Are you okay?
It's Tianyi.
What have you done?
Why did you get involved?
Don't you know the consequences?
Now you're talking about consequences.
If I had thought about it,
I wouldn't have let him
get away again and again.
Psycho.
If I had thought about it,
I wouldn't have let him escape
from Binjiang to Ninghai.
If I had thought about it,
I wouldn't have taken the risks
to drink with Gu Dadao
for clues.
You don't have to think about yourself,
but what about others?
If you had cared about others,
would your bro have been lying here?
What about Liu?
Why didn't you say this when
he took the bullet?
He was your bro, wasn't he?
Bin!
You've gone too far!
Mr. Xing.
It's not what he meant.
Put them on the phone.
Don't be angry.
Mr. Xing, Bin,
Ms. Wen wants to talk to you.
(Ms. Wen)
From now on, I'll participate in
every mission!
No one can stop me!
Hello.
(Na Fan, Xing Liang)
I heard your conversation.
However, I don't understand.
At this point,
aren't you supposed to work together
to get the bad guy?
Why are you arguing with each other?
I don't care
what grudge you have,
but don't embarrass me, okay?
From now on, I'll participate in
every mission.
No one can stop me.
I wasn't trying to stop you.
I know I can't.
Therefore,
Na Fan will follow you.
It can put my mind at ease.
Are you serious?
It's not appropriate.
Who's in charge?
I can't hear you.
(Na Fan, Xing Liang)
Hello.
Xuan,
it's not only inappropriate
but also fundamentally wrong.
Don't tell me it's not appropriate.
I know the rules.
But can you stop him?
Can I stop him?
Whether you like it or not,
he'll do it anyway.
It's safer for him to stay
with you than being alone, right?
How about this?
Tie him up and lock him.
I'm all for it.
Okay, I got it.
I'll think about it.
Hello.
Mr. Xing,
we lost him in the northern suburbs.
It's a T-junction
with no surveillance.
I don't know which way to go.
Bin,
I'm not trying to criticize you,
but you
really went too far.
How could you say that?
I'll talk to him.
(Emergency Room)
Fan.
You have to help me.
I'd love to,
but Mr. Xing doesn't agree.
You're right.
You don't have to go.
No way.
Didn't you hear Ms. Wen's words?
I'm not doing this alone
but going with the team.
I'm with Xing Liang.
Even if you don't trust me,
you have to trust him.
If anything happens,
he'll be my shield.
No, I can't do this.
Ms. Wen won't be happy.
Ms. Wen is worried about my safety.
Now that I'm safe,
she won't worry anymore,
right?
Besides,
Tianyi is seriously injured.
He needs you.
If you go with me,
won't you worry?
I'm so worried about him.
But Ms. Wen...
- I...
- Fan.
Sometimes,
it's okay to lie for the greater good.
Deal with Ms. Wen for me.
I'll work with the team
to arrest the criminal,
and you'll take care of Tianyi.
It's a win-win situation.
I know I can't stop you,
but
Mr. Xing needs to follow the rules.
Look,
I can stay,
but you
have to keep me informed.
In addition,
you have to protect yourself.
No problem. I swear
I'll keep you informed,
and I won't get hurt.
I'll arrest the criminal
and take care of our brother.
Our brother?
He's my brother.
It's the same.
He'll be my brother soon.
Bin,
I know you're capable,
but you need to be careful
with Sun Changhai.
How can I steal
Captain Xing's thunder?
Mr. Xing is here.
Mr. Xing.
Did you find him? Why did you stop?
Based on the analysis, Mr. Zhou thinks
he's heading to Da An Alliance.
There's a big forest.
It'll be hard to find him.
Both roads lead to Da An Alliance.
Which way should we go?
It's not Binjiang.
There are not many places
for him to take a break.
From here to Da An Alliance,
there are only two gas stations.
197 National Highway's
Pingling Town and Tumuji.
I don't think he'll go on
the highway at this point.
It must be Tumuji.
Fei Zai.
You're thinking like a policeman.
We need to think about it
from his point of view.
I'm sure he thinks
the best place to hide
is in plain sight.
Liu Yong.
Ask Mr. Zhou to contact
Pingling Town police station
and let them search the place.
(Xingyu Pier)
Dian Lao'er!
Don't be a coward!
Come out now!
What a scene.
Bao.
Are you going to rob me?
Did you take Zhi away from the casino?
What the hell?
I've told you a million times.
He cheated in our casino.
Well, we caught him in the act,
okay?
We can pay for that!
We don't want money.
We want shares.
Screw it!
What the hell? I've told you.
Listen,
let me repeat it.
You'll never
get the shares!
Then we have to follow the rules.
Cut off his arm!
Come on!
Don't waste time!
Tell me.
Sign a contract or fight?
Go to hell!
Let's die together!
Dian Lao'er,
stop being crazy.
Bao,
when did you become a coward?
Is the accountant
in charge now?
If we can't solve this today,
auntie,
I swear
I'll make you suffer.
I'll make sure
you have nightmares every night.
Okay?
Where is he?
- Son!
- Mom!
Help!
Zhi!
- Mom, help!
- Zhi!
Son!
Zhi! My son!
Mom!
Help!
My son!
Save my son!
Zhi!
You're...
You're making me look like a monster
who wants to destroy your family.
Auntie,
it's very simple.
You only need to sign the deal,
and it'll be over.
I'm begging you!
Please
let him go!
Please sign it!
- Mom!
- Please!
You can
cut my hands off!
Why would I do that?
He made a mistake.
His hands should be cut off.
Sign it.
Mom, help!
Help! Mom!
Bao!
Get up.
Get up!
Bao,
he's my only son.
You watched him grow up.
Maybe he's not a good son,
but I can't watch him die!
Will you listen to me?
I will. I will.
Give him the shares!
I don't blame you.
See?
Bao said yes.
- Come on. Sign it.
- Bao.
The shares...
Come on.
Just sign it.
Okay.
Money.
Son!
Auntie, get up.
Let's go. Come on.
Mom!
Bao,
didn't you say
I couldn't get the shares?
I did it.
Bao, take care!
(Qin Yuan Chun)
Mr. Xing, I'm Liu
from Pingling Town police station.
Hello, Liu.
Hello.
The suspect came here
at 3:00 a.m. this morning.
I think he's sleeping.
Mr. Li is keeping an eye on him.
He's waiting for you.
Attention, attention.
We've spotted the suspect.
Stay sharp and be prepared.
Come on. Hurry.
He's in Room 201.
Okay.
Don't move!
Stop!
Fei Zai!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Bin, be careful!
Stop!
Officer Wang.
He's in surgery,
but I think he'll be fine.
We'll interrogate him.
It's worth it.
I've told you
if you try,
wherever he goes,
you'll capture him.
Mr. Tai.
We've got him, but...
but the gun is still unclear.
Now that you've got him,
you'll get some information.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
We have seven days,
right?
I believe you.
I've prepared fine wine
for the celebration.
You have no idea
how terrifying it was.
Besides, he was hiding
in the dark.
It was so dangerous.
Then I saw a guy
fall in front of me.
Anyone would be scared.
But not me.
I've never been scared since I was born.
Then I picked up the gun and chased him.
Guess what?
I got that guy
in the end.
Right?
How... How's the food?
Not bad.
It's acceptable.
Are you hungry?
Of course, bro.
You didn't tell me.
- Come on.
- You didn't ask...
Come on.
You can only smell it.
The doctor has said
there's fluid in your stomach.
You're on
a liquid diet.
Come on. Have some water.
- No.
- Come on.
- Come on, let me help you.
Help yourself.
You've been talking too much.
Your mouth must be dry.
It's good.
Hey, can't you stop
making noises?
Fine.
It's good.
As a killer,
you must've made
many achievements, right?
No matter what you do,
it's hard to
make achievements
and be famous.
Don't you agree?
This guy...
What did he do?
Why were you so cruel?
Hey!
You hit me! Apologize now!
Am I wrong about this?
Are you wrong?
He didn't do it.
I did it.
Thank god.
I thought I wronged you.
But I'm so curious.
How did he
offend you?
Why did you do that for free?
He was rude.
He needed a lesson.
I heard
when you were a kid,
your mother wanted to leave your father,
so she left you
alone.
Mom.
Mom!
Then she died
in a car accident.
Your father was faithful.
He left you
and killed himself.
Dad!
You were only
five years old, right?
Losing loved ones is painful.
But you killed
other people's loved ones,
and it was also painful for them.
Right?
I don't know about them,
but I'm not in pain.
You got me.
I was unlucky.
Since I become a killer,
I've never expected to die of old age.
It's not because
he's pessimistic.
Normally, a killer
can't live as long
as your uncle.
Speaking of which,
it's not because
your uncle is capable.
We don't want to investigate him.
If we do,
do you think he'll get away?
Right?
Come at me.
My uncle has nothing to do with it.
We came for you.
Did you forget it?
Let me remind you.
A police gun is missing because of you.
If we can't find it,
none of us
can get away.
Where is the gun?
I threw it away.
Where and when did you throw it away?
Before I left Binjiang,
I left it at the cross-sea bridge.
Uncle Long is the middleman, right?
Haven't seen him.
I only know he's a tough guy.
I'm not sure about that,
but
he's smarter than you.
You... You can't get him.
Sun Changhai,
we came all the way from Binjiang.
Do you really think we're idiots?
It's okay.
You don't have to tell us
where the gun is.
Someone will tell us.
Okay.
Enough about the gun.
I have a question.
When we were chasing you in Hegu,
you could've escaped,
but you didn't shoot him.
Did someone tell you
not to hurt Wen Binbin?
♪The moon is surrounded by stars♪
♪I hide my regrets in the dark♪
♪You said don't go♪
♪Because that's where you belong♪
♪Wild winds blow across the land♪
♪Witnessing the hardships
we've been through♪
♪You said don't be afraid♪
♪Even though life is always hard♪
♪Looking back♪
♪My laughters and tears♪
♪You've seen them all♪
♪I've loved, got hurt, and made mistakes♪
♪Maybe it's in the past♪
♪Still remember♪
♪The promises I made♪
♪Dream about those years♪
♪Waking up feeling painful♪
♪On those lonely nights♪
♪I couldn't sleep♪
♪Praying for a good ending♪
♪All that's left♪
♪Is a sigh♪
♪How I wish♪
♪I could see you again♪