Don't play dumb here with me.
Let me confirm with you once more.
Are you sure Liang will be fine?
Your brother is handling it.
There's nothing I can't handle.
Don't worry.
In a few days,
he will be back home with you.
You can kiss and hug him then.
You brat.
What on earth did you do?
You didn't cause any trouble, did you?
I definitely didn't do anything.
Right now, I'm just
a law-abiding good citizen.
As for Xing Liang,
does he have the face
to make me risk my life for him?
Our friendship isn't worth it.
Enough.
The reason I'm telling you this
is I feel like you've been anxious
these past few days.
I want you to relax.
But
don't tell anyone else.
I don't want extra complications.
Got it.
Ms. Wen, the guests have arrived.
I'll go by myself.
How is Mr. Xing?
Ms. Wen's been really worried
these past few days.
I couldn't ask too much.
Anyway, it will all be over soon.
That's good.
I'm leaving.
By the way,
my sister said you like this perfume,
so I had someone buy it from France.
Give it a try.
=Black&White Forest=
=Episode 21=
This morning, Wen Binbin took Xing Jian.
Make sure to find him.
Got it.
Hello, what's wrong now?
Keep an eye on him.
Tomorrow, he's meeting
the DIC.
Don't lose him.
Don't worry.
Both Er'leng and I are watching him.
What could go wrong?
Bye, I'm hanging up.
Go. Go forward.
Where are you going?
Well.
Nothing.
I'm just tidying up because I'm bored.
Mr. Luo,
I've explained everything I need to.
You've also recorded the video.
When can I leave?
When I say you can go.
Well, can I at least call home?
This person is so annoying.
Why does he want everything?
He wants everything.
Should I just give him my life?
Annoying.
What did you just say?
Nothing.
Please, everyone, stay calm.
Please, residents,
evacuate the scene in an orderly manner.
Everyone, don't panic.
Please, residents,
evacuate the scene in an orderly manner.
Er'leng.
Where is he?
Go, go, go.
You all stay downstairs.
Fei Zai and the others
will be here soon.
Make sure to hold him there.
You didn't find him?
Smile.
Look.
He didn't lose any limbs.
He's perfectly safe.
I told you.
He's with me. Don't worry.
He won't get lost.
Making such a big commotion so late.
You really are something.
Of course.
I'm telling you, Yellow.
You really worked hard.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't be here tonight
enjoying the night view.
Wait, why are you blaming me?
Blame them.
Their house caught fire.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Look at how scared he is.
He's still recovering from the shock.
Earlier, there were too many people.
He tripped and almost got trampled
to death.
Luckily, he was quick-witted
and found a corner to hide in.
Otherwise,
he'd be hurt just like the others
over there.
Bin,
should we go somewhere else?
Everything's going smoothly.
(Surveillance 01, North to South)
(Surveillance 02, Elevator 1)
Don't move.
Take this call.
Mr. Xing,
as long as you cooperate,
you won't suffer.
Everything is ready.
Boss,
are you sure you want to do this?
Mr. Jiang is right.
We must chase down the fleeing enemy
with the last courage.
We can't sweat the details
when achieving great things.
To succeed,
we can't be soft-hearted.
Since we've done it, make it thorough.
Take care of the person
who wrote the letter.
Don't leave any hidden dangers.
OK.
(Siji International Hotel)
The leader only allowed you
to go in alone.
Relax.
Just repeat what you said
to the camera earlier.
Do you understand?
What I said in the video
is all a lie.
Those people outside threatened me
to do this.
Sirs, they threatened me.
What are you doing?
I knew I couldn't trust
someone like you.
Don't mess around.
Sirs, did you see that?
They're acting so arrogantly
in front of you all.
What else wouldn't they dare to do?
So what do you want to do?
I'm going to sue them.
I'm going to have them arrested.
Alright.
You're right.
You're arrested.
Choose.
Do you want to be dismembered
or bled out?
You're playing me.
Do you think
you're the only one who can act?
Bin,
should we go somewhere else?
I burned down your house.
How much is it? I'll pay you.
Such big talk.
If you're so rich, why rent my place?
Don't look down on me.
Get someone to give an estimate.
I'll pay immediately.
Okay, I'll find someone now.
You've got a great brain.
I'm glad we listened to you
and tested him first.
Otherwise, if he talked nonsense there,
we'd be screwed.
I was forced.
I had no choice.
I can't offend anyone.
Please, just spare me.
If it were up to me,
I'd just hand him over to Er'leng.
They'd handle it cleanly
and spare our worries.
No.
Give me one more chance, please.
I promise I'll be honest.
I'll never dare again.
Tell me what mistake you've made.
I...
Well,
I shouldn't have
been so greedy for money
and framed Xing Liang.
Then,
you gave me the chance
to correct my mistakes,
but I turned around and bit you.
In the end, it's all my fault.
Really, spare me.
I'll never dare again.
Please believe me.
Come over here.
Here's a chance to redeem yourself.
Do you want it?
I'll definitely come clean
and clear Xing Liang's name.
I'm not talking about that.
As for the rest,
I can't help.
Not necessarily.
(Jiahexin Hotel)
Speak.
I've done everything you asked me to.
We agreed on 500,000.
I want it now.
It's going to raise suspicion now.
Wait a bit.
I can't wait.
You're all fighting with Xing Liang.
You're all pushing me.
I've had enough.
Today, I must get the money.
Otherwise, I'll go to the police
and change my testimony.
If you don't give me
a way out,
I'll drag everyone down
with me.
You...
Wait for my news.
This guy.
He's acting pretty convincingly.
He's got the right attitude.
But it might not be just acting.
Right now, he's like a man
who's been caught in a bind,
full of anger.
He's mad.
How can he get mad?
If he weren't so greedy for money,
would all this have happened?
How do you know
he can contact the other side?
Last night,
they made such a commotion
but didn't take Xing Jian.
That means
they've got him under control.
Dealing with someone like Xing Jian
is all about money.
So, after everything,
they'll definitely contact each other.
Boss,
Bin has done
a great job, right?
Wait until we catch the guy
before we decide.
Don't act rashly.
Make sure before you act.
- Stop.
- Don't move.
Don't move, everyone.
- Get out.
- Don't move.
- Stop.
Hurry.
My brakes failed.
You almost killed him!
Don't get it wet these next few days.
I should've thought of this earlier.
If Xing Jian had died at this point,
not only would there be no proof,
but we'd be the prime suspects.
This is better than just paying
to silence them.
This was our oversight.
It's not really your fault.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
- Boss.
- How's it going?
The driver insists
that the brake system malfunctioned.
He refuses to admit
that anyone instructed him
to deliberately kill.
So, with our current evidence,
we can't do anything about him.
Though we didn't catch the mastermind,
at least we have his testimony.
Mr. Xing will be fine.
We didn't work in vain.
Let's go.
Let me help you.
No need.
Xing,
I'm telling you.
This is a new tea someone gave me.
Try it.
I haven't drunk it yet.
You're acting like you are
welcoming someone out of prison.
Good.
You can still joke.
It means you're optimistic.
Let me tell you.
Actually,
the organization has always believed
you're innocent.
But the process
still has to be followed.
Rest assured.
Everything
you used to have there
will stay the same.
I understand.
We're old now,
not some temperamental
college students.
Older comrades really think maturely.
But this matter
has really given us a wake-up call.
From now on,
in both work
and life,
we have to be careful.
A slight lapse
can give the enemy a chance.
This is also my fault
for not thinking it through.
But
it also exposed some problems.
Go ahead.
As the saying goes,
"Some people can only
be motivated by benefits."
You're just one of them,
right?
Let me finish.
Who am I?
I'm just a small fry, right?
Is it really worth
all this trouble
and careful planning?
Do you really think
this is just about me?
I'm glad you understand.
We're in the light,
and they're in the dark.
It's really hard to guard against.
But I have to remind you.
A wise man doesn't stand
under a dangerous wall.
Sometimes, some choices must be made.
What you're saying is nonsense.
We've tried every trick.
Don't you know
who's in charge of our family?
I know.
I've talked to Xuan on the phone.
I've given her a warning
about Tuan Island.
She's a smart person.
She should know what to do.
Alright, Tai Yongzheng.
No wonder you're the leader.
But from now on, stop calling her.
What's with all the phone calls?
Can you reason?
It was your wife who called me, okay?
You must've sent a message first.
Alright, alright.
Let me ask you.
What are you planning to do next?
Have you figured it out?
In my opinion,
all these things
are all aiming for one goal.
As long as we can open a gap,
all the problems will be resolved.
Who is the key?
The key is Chen Yiming.
As long as we can get him to talk,
we'll be able to see
the enemy hiding in the shadows.
(Outpatient and Emergency)
Bin.
What a coincidence.
Liu.
Well, my friend just had a baby.
I came to check on her.
Come on.
Chen and I have known each other
for a long time.
His wife had a baby.
I'm just here to see her.
It's normal, right?
Bin, the boss has instructed.
Unless Luo Jiahui agrees,
no one can see her.
- She has to agree?
- Right.
Let's go in and ask her.
She said on the first day
she wouldn't meet anyone
related to Bao Chenyan.
We're old friends, right?
I just need to ask her some questions.
I'll be out soon.
Please make an exception.
Liu,
when you first joined the police force,
who got you a desk and chair?
Now that I'm no longer there,
you don't even help me now?
Bin,
I really can't.
You...
Very dutiful.
Give her this for me then.
Alright.
You're back.
I remember someone saying
that he was well-respected
in the police force.
Turns out it was all just talk.
Bragging, huh?
Seriously,
I've noticed your colleagues
are hard to fool.
Except for that Fei Zai.
He's a bit brainless,
but I'd advise you to go easy on him.
(Medical Staff Only)
He will
get smarter if you keep fooling him.
Why the rush?
The show is just beginning.
The elevator just arrived.
Where are you going?
I'm going to see the child.
You don't need
to check up on the child every day.
The child is in the ICU
with special care.
You should focus on recovering.
Take care of yourself first.
If you're really worried,
I can go see the child every day
for you.
No need, thank you.
You're Bin's friend, right?
- Yes.
- I'm looking for him.
Do you know where he is?
He seems to have gone over there.
Over there, right?
I didn't bring my phone.
Can I borrow yours to call him?
- Can I borrow it?
- Luo Jiahui?
(Newborn Intensive Care Unit)
Hello?
Hello, Liu.
Where are you?
I brought you some food.
Luo Jiahui is missing.
What?
Don't worry.
Tell me everything.
I went to see the child with Luo Jiahui.
Halfway there, Bin's friend stopped me
and asked where Bin went.
Bin?
Did he come to the hospital?
He came to see Luo Jiahui,
but I didn't let him in.
Well.
Don't tell Mr. Xing
about this just yet.
You know clearly what Chen Yiming
has done.
Who told him to do this? Tell me.
Open the door!
Officer!
He took my child!
My child!
Wen Binbin, are you crazy?
Are you out of your mind?
Hurry up and return the child!
What child?
The child is in the ICU.
What do you want from me?
Take her away.
Let's go back to the ward.
(Newborn Intensive Care Unit)
Liu, take her back.
It's fine now?
Why were you so fierce just now?
I was just anxious.
So funny.
Hello?
I'll be back soon.
Your brother-in-law is fine now.
I'm going back to the station.
How do you know
he'll go back to the station first?
What if he goes home first?
I just know it.
If you don't believe me,
let's bet on a hotpot.
Anyway, if Xing Liang
dares to go back to the station
instead of home,
my sister will definitely get angry.
Our sister won't.
She's my sister.
Fine. Be careful later.
I'm not joking anymore. I'm leaving.
Come back.
I haven't finished talking.
Let me tell you.
After the fuss just now,
judging from her reaction,
I can be sure
Chen Yiming didn't tell the truth.
And Luo Jiahui
definitely knows something.
So what if she knows?
They're
a perfect couple.
Both of them refuse to talk.
We've interrogated
Chen Yiming so many times,
and he won't say anything.
As the old saying goes,
"Hit the snake at its weak point."
Since he's being so tough now,
just find something to scare him
to make him...
Scare him...
What do you mean?
Didn't you
break my watch once?
What were you most afraid of back then?
Why bring up something so old?
You were most afraid of seeing me.
Wait.
- Sis.
- Your brother-in-law is coming back.
Come home for dinner tonight.
I know.
It's no big deal.
Why get so worked up?
Alright, I got it.
I'll come back early.
Bin.
Think for yourself.
How is it, Xing?
No changes, right?
Yu and the others
always come here to clean up.
Look.
I'm almost a rare species now.
Mr. Xing.
What's going on?
Hold back your tears.
What's this all about?
Alright.
In half an hour,
let's have a meeting.
Let me see if you've been slacking off.
By the way,
you can get a good look at me.
Yes.
Go ahead.
Go get ready. Hurry.
Let's go.
How can you still focus on your phone?
I'm just checking the time.
Is Fei Zai reliable?
What time is it?
It's been almost 40 minutes.
- He hasn't been home.
- He'll be back soon.
Didn't you say he's out?
You made me cook dumplings so early.
Now they're almost cold.
Should I heat them up again?
He'll be here soon.
No need to change your shoes.
- I'm dirty.
- It's fine.
I'll wipe them later.
Let me see.
What happened?
I'm fine.
Nothing. I'm fine.
I'm back, right?
- Quick.
- Stop being so lovey-dovey.
The dumplings are getting cold.
Sit down.
- Try it.
- You made the dumplings?
I made them myself.
- Alright.
- Try them.
Eat more. You've lost weight.
That's not true.
These past few days, I've just been
eating and sleeping in there.
I think
I've gained weight.
It's so good in there, huh?
Why did you even bother coming back?
It's because of you at home.
Enough already.
You're making my goosebumps rise.
It's rare for me
to hear some nice words.
What does it matter to you?
Bin,
I've heard about it.
This matter
got cleared up so quickly
thanks to you.
Thank you.
No need.
Everyone helped.
This modesty doesn't suit you.
Bin has matured.
Before,
I always treated him like a child.
I underestimated him.
Binbin has definitely grown up.
You two stop.
You two should pull my ear
and scold me just like before.
I'll feel more comfortable.
Why are you so annoying?
Can't you tell that we're being sincere?
Your brother-in-law and I
were too strict with you before,
but that was really for your own good.
Don't be mad at us.
What are you talking about, sis?
Since I was little,
you've always spoiled me.
You always let me have my way.
But I wasn't good enough,
always causing you trouble.
Liang,
it was my fault before.
I caused a lot of trouble for you.
Cheers to you.
I also made some mistakes.
Family doesn't need to be so polite.
It's settled then.
May everyone
in the family
be safe and sound in the future.
Alright.
Cheers.
Thank you for telling me
about my wife and kid.
Thank you.
I've already said
everything I needed to.
If you ask me again,
I'll still say the same things.
There's nothing more to say.
(Detention Area II)
Boss, boss.
I have an idea.
Didn't you
break my watch once?
(Newborn Intensive Care Unit)
What were you most afraid of back then?
Why bring up something so old?
You were most afraid of seeing me.
(Belongs Room, Interrogation Room 2)
Face the wall.
Go inside.
Are you okay?
Are you alright?
What's wrong? Are you alright?
Does this need to be connected?
- Hello?
- I quit.
What?
How could this happen?
What exactly happened?
After he saw Bao Chenyan,
- his emotions...
- Wait.
Bao Chenyan?
Who allowed them to meet?
Mr. Xing,
this was my decision.
There hasn't been any new progress
with Chen Yiming,
so I thought maybe Bao Chenyan
could break through his defenses.
- Liu Yong.
- Mr. Xing.
I suggested it to Captain Liu.
Chen Yiming did this
when I was escorting him.
If you want to punish someone,
punish me alone.
Of course, I'll punish you.
I'll punish you alone.
What happened when they met?
They only looked from a distance.
They didn't talk.
I...
I didn't expect it.
Didn't expect it?
What did you expect?
You just want to get
what you want, right?
You didn't consider
any potential risks at all.
- Mr. Xing.
- Enough.
Handle the scene quickly.
I'm telling you.
Self-criticism reports for you two.
One year's bonus will be deducted.
The rest
depends on the bureau.
(Binbin)
You all go out.
After meeting you today,
Chen Yiming committed suicide.
Are you
suspecting me?
Chen Yiming's suicide
has something to do with you.
I'm saying
it's not you who wants him dead,
but for your sake,
he has to die.
I don't understand what you're saying.
When he was first brought in,
he didn't panic
like other suspects.
On the contrary,
he showed an unusual interest
in the Tuan Island bidding.
After learning the result
of the bidding,
he acted like a student
who knew the exam questions in advance.
Are you saying
he knew
the Tuan Island
bidding result in advance?
That's impossible.
Unless...
Unless he works for Qi Hanchen.
Every step he took
seemed to be carefully planned.
At the very beginning,
he refused to cooperate,
but later,
he admitted all the crimes.
But he kept avoiding mentioning
the mastermind behind it all
until you were arrested.
Then he insisted
you were the mastermind,
and he was just a coerced accomplice.
Of course,
everything he said
lacks solid evidence,
so it's hard to believe.
He clearly risked everything
to drag me down with him.
You police should handle cases
based on evidence.
After all that talk,
do you have evidence?
Bao Chenyan,
you're very familiar
with our police procedures.
But did you notice
today I didn't take a statement
from you?
So,
this is just a casual chat,
not a formal interrogation.
No need for evidence.
Right.
Let me correct your wording.
What I've said isn't a guess.
It's reasoning.
Fine, fine.
Then let me ask you.
Why did he want
to kill himself?
If
he hadn't committed suicide today,
I'd still find it hard to be sure
about my assumptions.
Actually,
he had predicted
your arrest.
And he was waiting for this moment
to identify you
and then commit suicide.
You mean
he was waiting
to meet me
and then die?
That doesn't make sense.
It doesn't make sense.
You know, my meeting with him today
was purely by chance.
He couldn't have foreseen it.
Are you saying he's an alien?
You're right.
He wouldn't know
when he'd meet you,
but what to do after meeting you
was all planned beforehand.
Someone wanted to use his life
to make the police believe
you, Bao Chenyan,
were the mastermind.
And
only after his death
could the real mastermind
remain safe.
Do you understand?
Big Eye Chen
has been my brother for years.
Every time there was a fight,
he fought hard.
I know
he just wanted to earn more money
to take care of his family.
Let me tell you.
The person who's manipulating him
must've gotten to his weak spot.
You'd better check it out.
How are his wife and child now?
As his boss,
do you really not know
about Chen Yiming and Luo Jiahui?
How would I know whom he's dating?
Our brotherhood was based on feelings.
I've never tried to control his family.
Besides,
I'm not that manipulative.
He didn't want to talk,
and I never asked.
Yesterday,
I also thought about it for a long time.
The mastermind behind this
wants to screw me so bad.
It must be
because I've blocked their way.
Think about it.
Right now,
Qi Hanchen stands to gain the most
from my imprisonment, right?
He's in direct competition with you,
so logically,
he's the biggest suspect.
But,
if we piece everything together,
this trap
must've started the moment
Bin lost his gun.
At that time, Qi Hanchen
wasn't even involved
in the Tuan Island project.
So, to suspect him
is really too far-fetched.
You're right.
I've been thinking about it too.
I've been in the underworld
for years,
and I've made plenty of enemies,
but not many of them
are smarter than me.
Could it be like this?
Dian Lao'er has always wanted
to snatch Tuan Island from me.
He knew
Bin and I were close,
so he wanted to destroy Bin's future.
That's why he took his gun.
He didn't finish the job
and teamed up with Qi Hanchen later.
The baton was passed to Qi Hanchen.
He kept going with the plan.
But Dian Lao'er is dead.
What you said can't be proven.
The Tuan Island project
is still up in the air,
so they must have more moves to make.
Xing Liang,
can you
let me out?
When will you release me?
You know Man and the others
are out there working their asses off.
I'm worried.
Why the hurry?
After our investigation is over,
we'll decide whether
you're released or not.
What's your attitude?
We're on good terms.
After so much talk just now,
you know I'm innocent,
so why are you locking me up?
Bao Chenyan,
I've already said it.
Today is just a casual chat,
not a formal interrogation.
Xing Liang!
Xing Liang, let's talk some more!
The moon is surrounded by stars
I hide my regrets in the dark
You said don't go
Because that's where you belong
Wild winds blow across the land
Witnessing the hardships
we've been through
You said don't be afraid
Even though life is always hard
Looking back
My laughters and tears
You've seen them all
I've loved, got hurt, and made mistakes
Maybe it's in the past
Still remember
The promises I made
Dream about those years
Waking up feeling painful
On those lonely nights
I couldn't sleep
Praying for a good ending
All that's left
Is a sigh
How I wish
I could see you again