Jiang,
(Sixteen years ago)
you've worked hard these years.
As your uncle, I should take care of you.
But finally, you took care of me.
I don't like hearing that.
You are being distant with me.
The family did not speak two words.
Isn't it?
Moreover,
thanks to your suggestions these years,
otherwise, with my brain...
Look at everything I have now.
Half of this big office
is mine,
and half is yours.
I should thank you.
Let's get to the point.
Do you want to make your company bigger
and make more money?
How could I not want to, right?
Why should I settle for this?
You know,
right?
Some matters of the company
cannot be put on the table.
This is exactly what I want to tell you.
To make the company go further,
these shady businesses of yours
need to be cleaned up.
Cleaned up?
I don't understand.
Any economic form
is imperfect
and the gray economy
is even more so.
The company has come this far.
It's time
to consider shifting these gray tones
towards positive colors.
Of course, you still have an advantage.
You are skilled
at walking the edge of laws and rules
to maximize development.
I still can't understand.
But it doesn't matter.
You can understand. That's enough.
I'll do whatever you say.
All right?
It's not that complicated.
From the perspective
of geography and economy in Binjiang,
you must break through the limitations
of industry and region
to develop and grow.
However,
the means
must not directly conflict
with the law.
I think I kind of understand now.
- Got it?
- Go on.
I have come up with an operational model.
I'll tell you once it matures.
There is only one ultimate goal,
to be a multinational corporation.
Multi what?
Multinational.
Oh my, multinational.
What's wrong? Don't you believe it?
No, no, no.
It's not that I don't disbelieve.
Uncle, you are indeed a cultured person.
You, you, you are bolder than I am.
So,
I want to go to South Korea and Japan.
In these two countries,
the gray economy has already taken shape.
I will evaluate the operation model.
After I return,
we will discuss how to implement it.
Ok.
Multinational.
While you are busy with it,
I will first take
over the Tuan Island Market.
Anyway, those guys are a bunch of lowlifes.
They won't listen unless they suffer it.
After they have been fully merged,
right,
perhaps they will know
who the boss of Binjiang is.
Wait a moment.
Merger
is an important form of development.
But we need to be cautious
about how to merge.
Simply fighting doesn't work.
I'll listen to you.
We don't fight.
We don't.
Hurry up and tell me when to leave.
When do you set off?
I've thought about it for a long time.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
How is it?
Are you satisfied now?
Take it.
I have enough money.
In case something happens,
you can still hold on with it.
Wait for my return.
=Black&White Forest=
=Episode 27=
I want a divorce.
Because of the matter of Lin Yisheng?
Xing Liang clearly knew everything
but just watched me jump into the pit,
without saying a word.
I can understand that it's his job.
Compared to Binbin,
work is more important.
Compared to family,
Compared to me,
work is still more important.
But now it's the hard-earned money
of so many merchants.
But look,
he still didn't change it.
So I...
I can't understand him right now.
I think his job, his ideal
should be
to protect his own little family first
before protecting everyone else.
But I...
I...
I can't...
I can't go on living like this.
I feel like I'm tired.
Come on.
You are really annoying.
But I think you
are right about Xing Liang.
Think about it.
On the matter of Lin Yisheng,
Xing Liang
deceived you.
What is behind this deception?
A rift has developed
between you, with no trust left.
So what is the next step?
That may lead to betrayal.
I think after betrayal occurs,
he may be likely to cheat.
Nonsense!
He can't...
Why did you...
What nonsense are you talking about?
Look at you.
I know you're trying to make me happy
and you're kidding me, but...
You're always been like this.
When it comes to the key issue,
you still protect him and care for him.
Xing Liang is the same.
He is a police officer.
He has no choice.
It's not that I don't understand.
I am just...
I have some emotions about this.
I don't know who to talk to.
Xing Liang
has kept quite a few things
to himself.
He is worried
that you and I are getting together,
and is afraid that you might get involved
in the case of the Tuan Island.
Do you know?
You two are actually the same.
I'm always the one who gets hurt.
Why do I feel you know him better than I do?
I don't know anything about him.
I can't stand him the most.
I have no choice.
I don't want to see you like this.
But now Tu Manjiang has run away.
If Lin Yisheng doesn't admit it,
what do you think I should do?
You have me.
Don't worry.
I have a way.
You can't cause trouble anymore.
You know,
I really want
to be a decent person.
Don't worry.
A decent person
must not do anything bad.
Don't cry anymore.
Come on, come on.
Go back.
Go back, go back, go back.
I have your word.
Don't worry.
Everything will be fine.
Xing Liang,
you really have good luck.
(Xinfuyuan Restaurant)
(Seafood Porridge BBQ Midnight Snacks)
(Wangwang Seafood)
Hey.
I guessed you'd be here.
You know I'm coming?
Excuse me.
Take a set of tableware.
Who else is coming?
Why not eat at home?
Why come outside?
Have you already eaten at home?
Here are your tableware.
Thank you.
You don't even want to eat at home,
but you make me eat at home.
Let me tell you,
I noticed that your sis and Xing Liang
had already entered a state of war.
It was very unsafe.
See if the food is enough.
Add whatever you want to eat.
So many dishes.
That's enough.
This dish, Tianyi and I...
What were you and my sister
talking about at the door?
It has nothing to do with you.
So it's about money.
What are you planning to get money?
Here's my advice.
There are two solutions
to this matter.
One is to catch Tu Manjiang
and force him to give the money back.
The other is to have the police
file a case in the name of financial crimes.
But for the benefits of the merchants,
two things need to be done simultaneously.
Don't just focus on eating.
Say something.
Say what?
You think it's just kids fighting,
if you can't win, tell the teacher.
I really can't deal with someone
as stubborn as you.
What era is it now, Bao?
I was originally thinking
if nothing happened
to Tianyi,
I would entrust
my brothers
and this territory
to him.
I'm still thinking...
I have great plans in mind.
I want you and Tianyi
to be buddies
for a lifetime.
Tianyi is already dead now.
(Tao)
Binbin,
did you bring any money?
Did you come out to eat without money?
You know it.
I usually
don't go out alone.
A large group of people are around me.
After all these years of eating together,
when have you ever seen me pay?
I'm being honest with you.
Being a big brother
is really pitiful.
No freedom.
Did you bring any money or not?
You've got me.
Just go.
Are you really angry?
What's wrong with you?
When you were little, I could touch you.
But now I can't even get close to you.
Your hands are oily.
Why touch my head?
You know
you are my heart,
- you are my liver.
- Get lost.
You are my heart.
You're my liver.
You are three-quarters of my life.
I found out about Lin Yisheng.
He used to have a mistress
who is a good friend of Fangfang.
Fangfang said
Lin Yisheng is getting ready to leave.
Where is he planning to go?
He said he wanted to go back.
Do you know when Fangfang
met her?
It's in the evening.
In the evening, huh?
Let's do this.
You asked Fangfang
to find a way
to get Lin Yisheng's current location.
Call me once you have the results.
Ok, leave it to me.
Ok, thank you.
Do you have a conscience
and want to settle the bill?
Ok, I'll be there right away.
Fangfang,
don't be afraid.
Make a call to your friend
and ask her where she is.
Hello? Lexin.
Lexin, where are you?
I have arrived at my place.
What's wrong?
You...
Fangfang, what's the matter?
Speak.
You are that friend of Fangfang, right?
What kind of potion did you give her?
After she met you today,
she insisted on going to Huqing.
(Lexin)
Listen up.
If she wants to leave,
that's impossible.
We are now in a society governed by law.
What you are doing is illegal.
I make the rules here.
Everyone has to follow the rules here.
Do you know who my man is?
If you dare to offend me,
you'll regret it.
I don't care who you are.
If you want to take her away, fine,
prepare 100,000 yuan to compensate me.
After I get the money,
I'll let you take Fangfang away.
Give me an account.
I'll transfer the money over.
I only want cash.
Cash on delivery.
Where are you?
I will take Fangfang over.
Lexin...
Lexin, save me, Lexin...
Fangfang, don't be afraid.
I am at Room 402, Xinsheng Hotel.
You'd better not try any tricks.
Lexin...
Lexin, save me.
- Bao.
- Speak.
I have found out.
She's at Room 402, Xinsheng Hotel.
I'll go there right now.
Get it.
Lin Yisheng,
you finally appear.
Xinsheng Hotel.
Let's go.
I know the owner of this hotel.
I just asked him about it.
There is only one person in the room.
Usually, Lin Yisheng
comes back late at night,
and he doesn't bring his subordinates.
Let's go up and have a look.
Who's there?
Lexin,
it's me.
I'm a police officer.
Please cooperate with me.
What
did he do wrong?
This matter involves confidentiality
and cannot be disclosed to you for now.
What time does he usually come back?
He called me
and said he would be back later.
It's just
around this time.
Fangfang,
is everything ok?
I'm fine.
Open the door.
I'm back.
- You're back.
- You took so long.
You took so long to open the door.
Let me tell you...
Pour some tea.
Pour me some tea.
Wake up.
Pour some tea.
Bao.
Sit.
Have a seat, Bao.
Bao.
Bao, Bao, Bao.
This is a society ruled by law, Bao.
Don't be impulsive.
You...
Bao, Bao...
From Bao's attitude, I think
he may take action against Lin Yisheng.
I was wondering if you could
file a case to investigate Lin Yisheng
under the name of a financial case.
At least put some pressure on him.
ECD is in charge of the financial cases.
Out unit can't interfere.
You wait a moment.
Let me make a contact.
Be sure to be safe.
Keep a close eye on Bao Chenyan
and make sure nothing goes wrong.
Contact me anytime if there's anything.
Got it.
Mr. Li,
it's me.
Sorry to bother you so late.
There is one thing like this.
Mr. Qi,
Bao has taken Lin Yisheng away.
This is a great opportunity.
You can cast the net now.
If everything goes smoothly,
the Tuan Island project
will be yours
tomorrow.
What do you want me to do?
You just need to send someone to force
the merchants to hand over their shops,
and then
let someone shift the blame
onto Bao Chenyan.
That's all.
When?
At that time,
I will call you.
Hello? Man.
What's the matter?
I found the person who sold out Changhe.
But they are very strong.
They are chasing me everywhere.
Send more strong people over here.
I pay 150,000 yuan per person.
After the matter is done,
I'll pay another 100,000 yuan.
I said they are two different matters.
I will go there in person.
Let's talk about it after it is done.
Ok.
Lao'er,
arrange ten strong people for me.
Bring the stuff
and go out with me
tomorrow morning.
Ok.
Go ahead.
Mr. Lin,
you might not understand me.
When I was young, my family was very poor.
It's different from your situation.
I had no toys back then.
The I placed a long nail
on the railway tracks.
Once the train passed,
it became a dart.
I have practiced for a long time.
- My skill is pretty good.
- No.
Don't...
I don't want darts.
Bao, don't joke around.
No, no.
Sorry to trouble you today
- and recall childhood with me.
- Bao.
Bao, I tell you the truth.
I...
I made an appointment with Tu Manjiang.
After things are settled,
we...
We will meet in Aocheng.
Where is the money?
Money...
...has been diverted to different accounts.
Once the money laundering is done,
it will be...
...consolidated into the overseas account.
I've already told you everything, Bao.
Bao, I've already told you.
What is the password for this phone?
I can't remember.
I remember.
616414.
Which phone number is your dad's?
The first one.
Dad,
help me, I am Lin.
Dad, help me.
Speak louder!
Save me, Dad.
Save me!
Save me...
Hello?
Mr. Lin.
Yeah, what you just heard
is your son's voice.
Your son is now in my hands.
You return the money
to its original account.
I assure you
that your son will live a long life.
It takes time to raise
such a large sum of money.
Give me five days.
Just three days.
If you delay for one hour,
your son will lose a part.
I assure you.
Is it him?
It's him.
Deal with him.
Bao!
Hurry up, hurry up.
Go.
Doctor!
Make way.
Er'leng.
Please wait outside.
(In rescue)
What happened?
It must be someone hired by the Lin family.
Who is the patient's family member?
I am his elder brother.
How's it going?
He has a comminuted fracture of the knee,
with nerves and blood vessels severed.
Surgery is the only option. Sign here.
Doctor, I...
I didn't hear clearly.
What kind of surgery?
Amputation can only be done through surgery.
There's no way.
The nerves and blood vessels are severed.
He is so good.
Why does he need to amputate?
Bao.
Can't we connect the blood vessels and nerves?
Is amputation really necessary?
Theoretically, they can be connected.
But his injuries are too severe.
The nerves cannot be connected.
If amputation is not done, he'll be in danger.
Sign it.
Bao.
Saving him is the priority.
Binbin.
Call the police.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter, anything is fine.
Call the police.
My people can't be hurt by them anymore.
Call the police. I need help.
Hurry up.
I'm on it.
(Public Security)
Stop right there.
Everyone, don't move.
Bao,
my situation...
Hello? Who is this?
Bao,
it's me.
How is Er'leng doing now?
Your own rules of the martial world
can't save him now, right?
Do you still have the face to say it?
The word 'rules'
coming out of your mouth
is just a joke.
Let me tell you,
you better hide yourself well
and don't let me find you.
Otherwise, I fear you won't be able
to pay back this debt of Er'leng.
You haven't repaid the blood debt you owe me.
I'll telling you,
the life of Er'leng
is not sufficient.
What I want is all of your lives.
Blood debt?
What do you mean?
Do you still remember Wild Jiang?
Wild Jiang?
You make it clear.
Who exactly are you?
Let me tell you,
Wild Jiang
is my nephew.
You caused my family to be shattered.
I will not let you go.
Wild Jiang committed murder and robbery,
and was caught by the police
and sentenced to death.
He deserved this.
Aren't you clear in your heart?
He was guilty.
What about my sis and her husband?
Were they guilty?
Weren't they innocent?
I have endured hardships for twelve years.
Finally, I come to this day.
I will let you know
who owes debts to whom
and who should pay with blood.
Hello?
Xing.
They all confessed.
These people come from Da An Alliance.
The leader is Sun Changhai's uncle.
His name is Zheng Haotian.
According to their statement,
they were summoned suddenly
by someone named Zhan Xiaoman.
Zhan Xiaoman?
Yes.
He shares the same name as Wild Jiang's uncle.
Do you think this is a coincidence or...
Mr. Xing,
this is the information
you asked me to investigate.
Tu Manjiang was known
as Zhuang Wentai by then.
According to his teachers and classmates,
Zhuang Wentai was very introverted.
He often went out alone.
He was only close
to someone named Zhan Xiaoman.
This is Zhan Xiaoman's information.
But this is quite strange.
Zhan Xiaoman disappeared later
and has been missing to this day.
(Household Registration Table)
The real name of Wild Jiang is Zeng Zhijiang.
Yes.
Do you still remember
his mother's name is Zhan Xiao...
- Zhan Xiaotu.
(Zhang Xiaotu)
(Zhan Xiaotu Zhan Xiaoman Zeng Zhijiang)
Tu Manjiang.
One character from each name.
Tu Manjiang
is actually Zhan Xiaoman.
Man...
...is the uncle of Wild Jiang.
He has done all these things
to take revenge on me.
I don't really understand.
Back then,
Wild Jiang kidnapped Binbin as a hostage
and demanded 10% of the shares
of the Tuan Island Market
from Mr. Wen,
along with the management rights.
I couldn't swallow my anger at that time.
I brought a few guys to Binjiang.
Later,
Wild Jiang's people
were arrested.
Wild Jiang was executed.
I thought this matter had been over.
I really didn't expect
there's still Man left.
It's really weird.
As the saying goes,
nephews resemble their uncles.
I truly didn't tell it.
When will you pay back the money
you owe us?
All our money has been invested
into the Make Money project.
We will pay you back
after we can withdraw it.
That means you have no money.
You signed it, right?
If you don't have money,
take the shop as collateral.
What are you doing?
Go out.
Our money has been scammed.
Now you are coming to collect our shops.
Are you still going to let us live?
Exactly.
Everyone,
it is like this.
On our mortgage contract,
it is clearly stated
in black and white.
If you can't pay this money back,
we can only take your shop as collateral.
You are always trying to scam our money.
Now you want to take over our shops.
Guys, we can't keep enduring this.
Let's drive them out together.
Get out, get out.
Get out.
- Out, out!
- Get out!
Get out!
Sir...
Tu Manjiang
is actually Zhan Xiaoman.
He called me today,
saying he wants to kill all of us
and repay blood debts with blood.
Zhan Xiaoman
is the younger brother of Zhan Xiaotu,
Wild Jiang's mother.
Although
they are uncle and nephew,
actually,
they are just three years apart.
Twelve years ago,
Zhan Xiaoman went abroad
and lost all contact later.
Now we know
that he had plastic surgery
while in South Korea,
transforming into his classmate
Zhang Wentai's appearance
and naturally assumed his identity.
After returning to the country,
he changed name to Tu Manjiang
and continued with the next phase.
So he started planning
twelve years ago, didn't he?
He is hiding too deep.
This game has been set up for twelve years.
What's going on? I'm busy now.
Just say it.
Hello? Bao.
Something happened at the market.
Hurry over here.
I'll go handle it.
Liu Yong, a fight occurred at the market.
Take people there.
Bao.
Who did this?
The leader is surnamed An.
He came over a few days ago.
Qi Hanchen.
What do you mean?
From a logical standpoint,
this is a case of life for a life.
Debt should be repaid.
From a legal perspective,
I was just using means
to protect my legal rights.
I will definitely pay you back the money.
But...
But your people hurt my people.
How should we deal with it?
Return the money first before we talk.
If you don't pay back the money,
even if you don't come to me,
I will have to look for you.
Bao, please let me go.
Sheng.
Sheng!
Mr. Lin,
look.
Your son is still alive.
Pay back the money
you scammed from me,
and also the medical expenses
for my injured brothers.
Bao, please let me go.
Five minutes.
Otherwise,
wait to collect your son's body.
Wait a moment.
I will transfer the money right now.
The money has been transferred.
I promise
I will never deceive you again.
Hope you can show mercy
to let him go.
(Zhan Xiaotu Zhan Xiaoman Tu Manjiang)
♪The moon is surrounded by stars♪
♪I hide my regrets in the dark♪
♪You said don't go♪
♪Because that's where you belong♪
♪Wild winds blow across the land♪
♪Witnessing the hardships
we've been through♪
♪You said don't be afraid♪
♪Even though life is always hard♪
♪Looking back♪
♪My laughters and tears♪
♪You've seen them all♪
♪I've loved, got hurt, and made mistakes♪
♪Maybe it's in the past♪
♪Still remember♪
♪The promises I made♪
♪Dream about those years♪
♪Waking up feeling painful♪
♪On those lonely nights♪
♪I couldn't sleep♪
♪Praying for a good ending♪
♪All that's left♪
♪Is a sigh♪
♪How I wish♪
♪I could see you again♪