Bin,
your return to the team
can't be made public
for now.
Comrade Wen Binbin,
your first task after returning
is to join the investigation
of the Tuan Island Special Task Force
as an undercover.
Report all matters
directly to me.
Okay.
I also want to remind you.
As an ordinary person,
it's normal to be influenced
by emotions,
but as a police officer,
if you act on emotions,
it will become a stumbling block
in your pursuit of the truth.
=Black&White Forest=
=Episode 23=
Bao,
let's steam for a bit
and then
take a bath.
After the bath,
the massage here is amazing.
I'll arrange it for you,
so you can relax.
You're really something.
I just nodded off for a second,
and you woke me up.
You were asleep?
Alright, we'll take a bath,
have dinner
at night,
and then
go to Tao's place
to relax for a bit.
I've been waiting for that, Bao.
While you were away,
we didn't even have a smile
on our faces.
Look, now that you're back,
we've got our energy back.
Right?
Yeah.
Why look at me?
Is something on your mind?
Are you crazy?
I didn't sleep well last night.
Now my head is killing me.
Did the police station reinstate you?
What nonsense are you saying
in broad daylight?
That's not right.
My sister went to bed
very early last night.
The only thing that could've kept you up
was either my sister
or the police station.
No, no, no.
You want to be reinstated
because of my sister.
So, the thing keeping you up
is still my sister,
you love-stricken fool.
If you keep talking nonsense,
I'll make sure you don't sleep tonight.
Didn't we find the gun, Binbin?
The station should've reinstated you
by now.
It's not that simple.
Xing Liang said
the case isn't closed yet,
so I still have to wait.
When these cops
couldn't find the gun,
you couldn't go back.
Then they found it,
but they said
they couldn't close the case.
Once the case is closed,
there'll definitely be another excuse.
What can I do?
It's up to them.
I have to wait.
Don't lie.
I'm going to take a dip.
I'll go with you, Bao.
Stay with him.
What do you think of Chen?
Bao valued him so much,
and now he's accusing Bao.
Do you think Chen did it?
I don't
think so.
Could it not be him?
I think it looks like him.
Yeah, that's right.
If you look at the appearance,
it really does look like him.
But I studied that guy
on the motorcycle.
His waist was bent very low.
I know Chen too well.
Forget it, forget it.
A lot of things have happened.
Can he wake up?
Hard to say.
Even if he wakes up,
he might just be a vegetable.
I just checked.
Luo Jiahui wasn't in her ward.
Is she discharged?
Don't mention Luo Jiahui.
The doctor said
she should stay in the hospital
for a few more days,
but she insisted on leaving.
I think
she's probably eager to make money.
You know, her child was
premature and weak.
There are many things
she needs money for.
But still,
every day she at least checks
on Chen Yiming and her kid.
Do you know where she works?
What are you going to do now?
What can I do in broad daylight?
Come on.
You scared the heck
out of her last time.
If I hadn't handled this,
do you think Mr. Xing
would've let you go?
Bin,
don't cause any more trouble, okay?
I'll apologize to her.
Okay?
(Fresh Coconut, Iced Green/Red Coconut)
(East City Specialty Store)
Hello?
Why is it you again?
Are you following me?
I went to your supermarket to find you,
but your colleague said you were out.
I was going to see you another time,
but I didn't expect
to run into you here.
What do you need from me?
The coercion didn't work,
so you've resorted to money?
I don't mean that.
I've known Chen for many years.
It's just a small gift.
If you still care
about the old friendship with Chen,
please don't bother me anymore.
Is it really Bao?
Boss,
I confirmed it with Mr. Wang.
The bid opening is set
for tomorrow at noon.
How's the situation over there?
They were just told.
Bao Chenyan's team
will definitely be flustered.
They'll probably apply for a delay.
That's childish.
Tuan Island is
the center and key
of this upgrade and renovation.
It has taken so long.
The government
can't afford any more delays.
This bid opening
will definitely yield results.
Have you arranged everything?
Yes, all set.
You aren't even qualified now.
Bao,
I wonder how you're going
to play this one.
(Wholesale, Liquor, Drinks, Ice Cream)
Sir.
Well.
Can I watch your
surveillance footage?
I just lost something on that street.
When I came back, it was gone.
Maybe I can track it down.
Sir.
Come on, sir.
Please help me out.
What do you need?
Two boxes of beer.
Five boxes of beer.
I'll take all of your beer
at the store today.
It's 2,000 in total.
Sir.
Two thousand.
I'll put it in your pocket.
So now,
can I check the surveillance footage?
The camera at the door
has been broken for a long time.
Give me my money back.
That's not going to happen.
Listen.
I have heart disease
and high blood pressure.
Are you trying to send me
to the hospital?
Do you have money?
Come on.
This...
In broad daylight,
you're robbing me.
A male,
about 1.75 meters tall,
weighing 75 kg.
He wears a black top,
black pants,
and black shoes.
Half an hour before you,
only one person passed by here.
Do you still want your money back?
(Qingyu Fusion Cuisine)
This should be it.
What's the plan for tonight?
Drink until we drop.
Hurry up.
What the heck? What's wrong with you?
You said you'd buy us drinks,
but you brought your own wine?
Help me pay for the car.
Why should I pay?
How stingy.
- Okay.
- Take the wine.
Coming.
How much is it, sir?
Two hundred.
I've really hit a bad streak.
I'm always helping you.
Where should we take the wine?
Let's move it inside to drink.
What else? Can we drink at the door?
Listen to me before we start.
I spent all my money on the wine.
I don't have any left.
What are you trying to say?
So you're treating us,
but I pay for the car
and the meal too?
I told you I'm buying drinks.
Just pay a little.
Don't be so stingy.
Well, I...
Do you agree?
Fine, I'm the unlucky one.
What a jerk.
I've been looking for you all afternoon.
Where did you go?
My stomach hurt.
My stomach hurt,
so I went to the hospital.
Let me help with the wine.
Can you handle it?
If you can't, keep resting.
No need, no need.
I'll just stay out of it.
I still need to pay.
I'm wondering if I have enough money.
The wine is almost all inside.
Let's head in first.
Go in. Stop standing there.
Got confused before drinking, huh?
You're not going in?
Then you stay here.
How could the company's qualifications
be in question?
This morning, Mr. Wang called,
saying that
the qualifications of our subsidiary
joint-venture construction company
will expire in three months,
and they aren't qualified.
Then I don't understand.
How did you submit
the application materials
back then?
Actually, I reminded them about this,
but later, with so much on my plate,
I forgot to double-check.
I thought they'd handled everything.
It's my fault.
I was careless.
This
is all my fault.
I didn't follow through.
Okay, okay.
There's no point
in saying that now.
What's important is
we need to think about what to do next.
We can only change
the construction company.
After I knew about it,
I immediately contacted
other qualified construction companies.
But they all clearly rejected us,
saying they have a cooperation agreement
with Benniu.
Ms. Wen.
Carry on with your work.
Zixuan.
I've contacted
every friend I could.
We're usually on good terms,
but today, they just
keep changing the subject.
Someone must be pressuring them.
The sudden notice of the bid opening
probably means someone from above
gave an order.
What do you mean
by "someone from above"?
It's Qi Hanchen.
Bao,
is it true that no matter what,
you won't let go
of the Tuan Island project?
Of course not.
Now, there's only one way left.
What is it?
Sorry.
I got delayed with something.
It's okay, Mr. Qi.
It's our last-minute invitation.
Waiting for you is expected.
Please take a seat.
What's the matter?
You know
why we wanted to see you.
Sorry, Ms. Wen.
I forgot to tell you.
Someone's waiting for me downstairs.
I might only have about ten minutes.
We can relax our previous conditions.
The stall fee will be adjusted based
on last year's performance
and won't fluctuate more than 3%.
Other details can be discussed further.
I just have one question.
Who holds the control?
Of course, it'll be us.
Everything else is negotiable.
Ms. Wen, did I hear it right?
I thought this time you guys
would show some sincerity,
but you surprised me again.
I'm leaving.
You gave us ten minutes.
Don't you want to hear
our backup plan?
A backup plan?
You can't get in.
No plan works.
The backup plan is
for this worst-case scenario.
Mr. Qi.
You must know me.
You've investigated me.
Yes, I know
all the tricks of a gang leader
and how violent it can get
in the underworld.
Today,
it's very rare
for me to brag.
Let me argue with you.
Actually,
the underworld isn't about violence.
What is the underworld?
The underworld
is all about personal connections.
A gang leader in this world
isn't just about fighting
and being ruthless.
It's about loyalty and responsibility.
Thirteen years ago,
I took two hammers,
with four brothers,
came here from the Central Plains,
and faced Wild Jiang head-on.
It took me over a year,
but I managed to plant my flag
and make my mark.
Before Wild Jiang died,
he insisted on seeing me.
He said, "Bao."
"I admire you. You're a real man."
"Losing to you is no shame,"
"but I have one request."
I said, "Go ahead."
He said,
"My brothers and I have"
"many relatives and friends
in Tuan Island."
"They're small vendors."
"They're honest and decent."
He hoped
I could let them go.
I said, "No problem."
"Don't worry."
After all these years,
I feel I am
just like Wild Jiang back then.
But I was far
from your level.
I was just nothing,
but you totally nailed it.
No.
You're a legend.
Do you know?
The money that we made,
including my brothers
the Tuan Island merchants,
and I,
might be the equivalent
of one chopstick of your dish
to you, Mr. Qi.
If you put down your chopsticks,
all of us can survive
and have food to eat.
I can burn incense for you
twice a month.
I can even kowtow.
But if you insist
on raising your chopsticks
to get the dish
for a bite,
then we're no longer able
to make ends meet.
You're forcing me
to go back to 13 years ago
and pick up a hammer to fight you.
Mr. Qi,
I'm really curious.
You're born wealthy.
Is it worth it to risk your life
to fight a worthless man like me?
- I can't drink.
- I...
I'm leaving.
Go then.
Be safe.
Okay, okay.
We're leaving. Let's go.
Er'leng.
Why are you two here?
I called you to sing earlier.
Why didn't you go?
It was too noisy.
We wanted some peace.
Let's sit for a while.
Okay.
Er'leng.
What were you doing
at 3 PM this afternoon?
I went to restock.
Restock?
I remember you said this afternoon
you had a stomach ache
and went to the hospital.
I'm such a fool.
I remembered it wrong.
I went to the hospital
because of my stomach ache.
I saw it.
You secretly met with Luo Jiahui.
What's the deal?
If you don't explain it today,
our brotherhood ends here.
You must've seen it wrong.
I didn't even see you.
How could you see me?
Did you make a mistake?
Er'leng,
Bao treats you well, right?
Why are you betraying him?
How could I betray Bao?
I dropped out of elementary school
and started following him.
The heavens can bear witness
to my loyalty to him
and to you all.
Then just tell me what you were doing
this afternoon
with Luo Jiahui.
What's wrong?
Speechless, huh?
Do you admit you're a traitor now?
Who is the traitor?
You...
Do you think I'm a traitor?
What else?
Do you think the same way?
How could I be?
It was Bao who sent me.
He told me to give Luo Jiahui
some money.
Bao told you to give Luo Jiahui money?
Do you know what Bao hates most?
Big Eye Chen caused him so much trouble,
and Luo Jiahui is Chen's wife.
Bao told you to give her money?
Who are you trying to fool?
I'm not fooling you.
I don't get it, either.
If I could figure it out,
he wouldn't have asked me to go.
it wouldn't be me.
I would've been you, okay?
I'm telling you.
You two grew up under my watch.
You can't look at me like this.
I can never
betray my brothers.
I can never be a traitor.
About this,
I'm only telling you both.
Don't tell anyone else.
Please, don't ruin my life. I beg you.
I hereby announce
the Tuan Island Trading Center
Renovation and Upgrade Project
will be jointly undertaken by Wen Group
and MorningStar Group.
Stop drinking.
You got it all over your face.
Today,
let me
say a few words.
Sure.
Today is a day for all to celebrate.
- Right?
- Right.
So,
just drink and take everyone else down.
I have one request:
Among all brothers,
we can't let anyone walk
out of this door
standing.
- Alright.
- Okay.
Cheers to Bao.
You can drink less.
I haven't seen everyone so happy
in a long time.
You know, this Tuan Island project
has had so many twists and turns,
but the outcome is good now.
It's been worth the hard work.
Yeah,
if it weren't for Qi causing trouble,
it could've been even better.
Bao,
we now hold 47%
of the shares,
just one percent less than them.
Plus, we have support
from the Tuan Island vendors
and the operational control.
This outcome is already great.
Think on the bright side.
Though Qi Hanchen's involved now,
the control is still in your hands.
Besides, there's also Mr. Lin's funds.
He won't cause any trouble.
Yeah.
You don't need to comfort me.
I really don't care about him.
He's just a pretty boy.
What bothers me is
his expression.
He's always putting on airs.
It's a bit annoying.
You're just used to hearing
your brothers
call you Bao all the time.
You're used to being the boss.
You can't stand others
bossing you around.
No.
He knows.
As long as they're right,
of course, I'll listen.
Besides, Zixuan,
after all these years,
when have I not listened
to you?
You may be willing to listen,
but I don't want to lecture you.
What's wrong?
What did I say wrong?
My task is done.
I should return the shares
of Tuan Island to you.
We agreed on it from the beginning.
I believe, under your management,
the people of Tuan Island
will have better lives.
Alright, you guys drink here.
It's too noisy.
I can't hear anything.
I'm leaving.
Sit for a while.
The driver is downstairs.
No need to see me off.
Binbin.
- Drink less. I'm leaving.
- Fruit.
- Ms. Wen, I'll see you off.
- Thanks.
(Siji International Hotel)
Thank you.
Boss.
What's our next move?
Gather the shares
from the Tuan Island vendors
as soon as possible.
Didn't Mr. Jiang
ask us to maintain
the current situation for now?
I never do anything without certainty.
Don't trust anyone.
We must take control
into our own hands.
Mr. Jiang.
Mr. Qi.
The Lin family's financial project
has been launched.
Everything will proceed as planned.
Mr. Jiang,
let me remind you.
We are just partners.
We will cooperate appropriately
to protect
our company's interests.
If there are any negative outcomes
in the future,
you should prepare a way out.
Of course.
No, no.
This way.
No.
Did you just pee?
Did you get it on your hand?
Did you wash your hands?
- Smell it.
- Go away.
- Go.
- Go ahead.
Stay steady, okay?
When we go in,
avoid drinking if you need to.
I won't avoid drinking.
(Puyan Dancing Hall)
Many guests are here.
Take care of them.
You just have to deal with it.
How much have you drunk?
Tao.
Bin, watch him closely.
I'm not drunk.
Chen. You're Chen from Xiyuehui.
See? Tao, I know her. I'm not drunk.
Tao.
Have a few girls to come
to have fun with us in our private room.
You're acting strange.
What's wrong?
Go call a few more girls.
Go.
Have a drink.
Keep drinking.
Just get him drunk.
Come on.
Come on, cheers.
Four fives.
Four fives? Four sixes.
Five sixes.
One.
Six.
Drink.
Good for you.
You really got me. I'm telling you.
You are...
You're from Xiyuehui, right?
I used to go there often.
I've never lost.
There's a girl
named Hui, right?
I can tell you haven't been there
for a long time.
She quit a long time ago.
Really?
Why?
She found a man to settle down with.
How did they meet?
Are you concerned about her?
I'm just curious.
I'll drink on my own, okay?
What happened?
Actually, I'm not too sure either.
We only found out about it
when she resigned.
She didn't usually talk
about her personal life.
At the time, we even said
she should bring the guy over
to meet us.
But she didn't appreciate it.
By the way, she used to say
she wanted to find a good man like Bao.
I wonder if she got her wish.
She knew Bao?
Of course.
I used to bring her here often.
(Birkin Paris)
Uncle Man.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I just drank too much.
I didn't notice
that you're quite popular
with the girls.
You drank so much.
That's not true.
It was all arranged by Bao.
It was a mess.
Bao was just worried about you
because you're so old
and still alone.
I'm not like Chen.
I don't like this kind of thing.
I don't like it.
Bao used to introduce
girlfriends to Chen?
He introduced
Chen's wife
to him, right?
You didn't know that?
Bao...
Liang,
I'd like to believe
that Bao is innocent.
But I promise you.
I will never show favoritism,
let alone cover for him.
Bao introduced Luo Jiahui
to Big Eye Chen.
Bao hiding this is indeed suspicious.
I've always thought
Qi Hanchen is the biggest suspect.
But
after the Tuan Island
investment conference,
he left.
If he really was
the mastermind,
he wouldn't have been willing
to settle for the current result.
Leaving at this time
could also be a tactic to mislead us,
letting us relax
before he makes a big move.
It's not impossible.
Actually, you also think
Bao isn't the person you're looking for.
Right?
Now, all the evidence
points to him as the biggest suspect.
But
from my years of understanding
and observation
about him,
he doesn't seem like the mastermind.
He's not clever enough.
(Seven months later)
(Marketing Center)
(Tuan Island Trading City,
New Trade and Hope)
Next, let's welcome the person
in charge of Tuan Island Trading City
to give a speech.
(Affordable Homes Witness Reunion)
Go up.
I can't speak. You go.
Just go say something.
Just chat with everyone.
It's the same.
Applause!
Good, good.
This should be where Mr. Bao
is standing,
but today, this bearded man
is shy.
Let me step in for Mr. Bao
and say a few words.
- Great.
Well.
Has everyone seen the blueprint
for the Tuan Island Trading Center?
- Yes.
Do you think it's good?
Good.
That's really good.
Originally, this location
was already very favorable,
with a lot of foot traffic.
Once the Trading Center is completed,
the environment
and infrastructure
will be much better
than before.
We will make
great improvements.
Here's another good news.
Thanks to Mr. Bao's
relentless efforts,
we've secured
favorable conditions
for the old merchants of Tuan Island.
What kind of preferential policies
are there?
Do you want to know?
Yes!
Let me tell you.
First,
we will give priority to relocating
the old merchants.
Second,
the stall prices
will also have discounted policies
for the old merchants.
Also...
Listen carefully.
The old merchants
have the right
to choose their store locations first.
- Is that good?
- Yes!
Let's thank Mr. Bao.
One, two, three.
Thank you, Mr. Bao.
Good, good.
If anyone has any other needs,
you can always come to me.
I promise
to do my best to meet
everyone's needs, okay?
Okay!
The upper floors here are livable.
There's a garden ahead,
great for a walk
or taking the kids out.
You can pick your storefront later.
Behind the building,
there's a parking lot.
It won't be chaotic,
with cars all over the yard.
The parking lot has several floors.
How much
do you think it will cost to move here?
Didn't Man just say?
The stall fee is discounted for us.
I know.
But you think about it.
To move to a new store,
apart from the stall fees
and renovation costs,
there are other expenses.
With all these little things adding up,
it's still a hefty amount.
Everyone,
please stop taking photos.
Listen to me for a moment.
We've looked at the upper floors, right?
There's also a lot
to check out downstairs.
Everyone, spread out,
walk around, and take a look.
If you have any thoughts or suggestions,
tell Mr. Man later.
- Okay.
Hui.
Come here.
Bao.
Your father is sick
and in the hospital.
I know.
How's he doing?
He's better now.
It's just an old problem.
He needs to rest properly.
Let me tell you.
You're moving to a new store,
and your father is in the hospital.
I know money's tight for you.
If it's really tough,
just let me know.
No need, no need.
Bao.
You have an appointment with Mr. Tian.
It's almost time. You should go.
What do you mean by "no need"?
If you have difficulties,
tell me.
After all these years,
you should know me.
No need to be polite.
Alright, go take a look.
Go back.
Bao,
the new market is on track now.
I'll keep an eye
on the construction site.
Aren't you tired
from coming here?
Yes, I am.
Let me tell you.
My body is really
not what it used to be.
Glad you know
you're not getting any younger,
yet you're still trying
to do everything yourself.
You need to learn to relax a bit.
Right, you're right.
I'll learn to relax.
With you here,
I have nothing to worry about.
Man,
I have to remind you.
Most of these people
here now
are our old neighbors
and old friends, right?
We've been together all these years
in the market.
They're moving to a new store now.
Their families
are all quite poor.
If they have any difficulties,
you need to show more care.
If you can help, help them out.
Bao, our funds are also tight.
Our funds are tight,
but are they tighter than theirs?
Has Lin's funds
been secured?
They're a big group.
There are a lot of regulations,
so
it might take some time.
I'll ask again later.
This matter
has to be rushed.
Don't worry.
I'm leaving now.
Bao, give me that hat.
Every time I wear this hat,
it messes up my hairstyle.
Man,
you're at the construction site
every day.
Be careful.
Alright.
I'm leaving now.
Bao.
Cheers to you, Bao.
Mr. Huang.
I'm counting on you
about the Tuan Island matter.
Sure.
Thanks, everyone.
It's always better to see it in person.
Good drinker.
Good drinker, good drinker.
I've never drunk with you.
I'll take this pot of wine.
Binbin,
I have a bottle of wine
in my car's trunk.
It's been there for over a year.
Bring it up.
I'll drink it with Mr. Huang.
I'll step out for a moment.
Mr. Huang.
Thanks.
Thanks, everyone.
- Come on.
I won't let Bao get drunk, alright?
Okay, I'm hanging up.
I'm going in now.
It's Tao again?
It sure is.
Even if she didn't call us,
we'd still take care of Bao.
What do you know?
Lately, Bao has had
too many social events.
Tao is worried those wild butterflies
will flock to him.
She's trying to get me to talk.
It's really not necessary.
It really is.
If Bao were like you,
reporting his schedule
every day without fail,
it wouldn't be necessary.
Has your sister mentioned it to you?
Does my sister need to mention it?
I'm not blind.
You're always on that phone,
complaining and complaining.
Do you think I'm complimenting you?
As a grown man,
can you be a little more reserved?
You're just a bit jealous of me.
You want someone
to report your schedule,
but you've got no one.
Do I even need that?
Hurry up and go in.
I saw that scene just now.
They're feeding Bao drinks.
Bao's about to collapse.
Why does Tu Manjiang keep arranging
these events for Bao?
I'll go get some alcohol deterrents.
Bao.
Let's go home, Bao.
Everyone's gone?
They're all gone.
Let him drink this deterrent.
Don't.
After all that wine,
he won't be able to handle this.
How about you help me lift him up?
Bao.
- Bao.
- Let's go home.
- One, two. Let's go.
Why are you... Come here.
Let's go.
Slow down.
Come on.
Hui...
Has the money
been delivered to Hui's house?
I went a couple of days ago, Bao,
but Hui refuses to take it.
He says he doesn't need the money.
Does he feel
ashamed to take it?
Based on his behavior,
I don't think he was lying.
Could it be that he borrowed money
from relatives and friends?
Last time, when his father was sick,
he borrowed money
from relatives and friends, right?
He said they're scared of him now.
Yeah.
Go...
Let's go to Hui's house.
Let's take Bao back.
We can go alone.
It's really strange.
He refused money from us.
Has he gone to borrow money
from loan sharks?
From his reaction just now,
I don't think he has.
He really doesn't want too much money.
Not everyone is like you,
with no shame or pride.
Can you speak properly?
Don't make personal attacks.
You're the last person qualified
to say that.
Who's always treating Uncle Man
in a weird, sarcastic way for no reason?
I'm not being weird.
Let me tell you.
If he doesn't provoke me,
I wouldn't even bother with him.
I know you don't like Uncle Man,
but don't go too far.
Just pretend a little.
I'm genuine.
I can't pretend.
Do you think
I'm being weird now?
Let me tell you.
One day,
he will make you all cry.
(Marketing Center)
- You bought it too?
- Yes.
(Choose "Make Money")
How much have you invested?
(Make Money: For Turnover and Savings)
(Marketing Center)
"Make Money".
We're really making money.
Make Money:
For turnover
and savings.
No interest.
Absolutely no tricks are involved.
We know that everyone is about
to move to a new store,
and money is a bit tight.
So this product
is designed to safeguard
our old neighbors.
- Good.
- For loans,
what procedures are required?
All you need to do is download our app
and follow the instructions.
Besides loans,
it seems you also have services
for savings.
How much is the interest?
Yeah.
The amount and the deposit term
will affect the interest rate.
Don't worry.
Our interest rate
is definitely higher
than similar products on the market.
Not bad, higher than market products.
(Choose "Make Money")
Not bad.
(To Enjoy Your Life)
Call them.
Is this thing reliable?
Yes.
A lot of people have used it.
Mr. Lin
is a partner introduced by Bao.
He's really reliable.
Okay, okay.
Buy more, buy more.
Let me take a look.
If anyone has any questions,
please go to the consultation desk
or the lobby for inquiries, okay?
Thank you, everyone.
Do you know
about the Make Money project?
They even hung banners
in front of the sales office.
You say you don't know about it?
I've been busy
with socializing recently.
I haven't been to the Tuan Island Market
in a long time.
You're saying
Mr. Lin Yisheng started
some kind of project?
I'll talk to you later.
That "Make Money"...
Mr. Lin.
Ms. Wen, what brings you here?
I've never been here before.
I was just passing by today.
I didn't expect
there would be a surprise.
Do you have time to chat?
Sure.
Mr. Lin,
does Bao know
about this Make Money project
you're doing?
This is something
I didn't plan out well.
I haven't had the chance
to tell Mr. Bao.
You haven't had the chance,
or you just didn't plan to tell him?
I'm doing this
not just to make money.
I really want to help the merchants
in Tuan Island.
Since we're partners,
it doesn't seem quite right
to make such a major decision
without informing us first.
Ms. Wen,
I'd like to apologize to you first.
But the Tuan Island project
is something I've been insisting on.
Only after convincing my family
did they reluctantly agree to invest.
But the condition is
I need to show some results first
before they'll confirm the investment.
So you're saying
you don't have the funds
for this investment now?
Don't worry.
As long as this project succeeds,
I'm sure my family
will approve the money.
What? Wait.
I don't quite understand
the relationship
between these two things.
Ms. Wen, don't worry.
Let me explain it to you.
We did a survey.
The occupancy rate
for the new market is low.
The key reason
is that the merchants
don't have enough money,
not that there's a lack of foot traffic.
This project
can precisely solve
the funding problems
of both new and old merchants.
When the market occupancy rate rises,
there will be more options
for attracting investment.
With more investment options,
the market will naturally profit.
Everyone will benefit.
This creates a virtuous cycle.
But if... I mean
if the merchants are stuck
with money issues,
then no one
will make a profit.
Has this project undergone
a risk assessment?
Every investment has risks.
Do you believe in investments
without risks?
Of course, our Guotai Group
specializes in financial services.
There's no problem with that.
I can not only guarantee
the safety of the funds,
but also help the merchants
in Tuan Island
get
the best deals.
(Marketing Center)
I've read the project proposal.
From the process perspective,
there's no problem.
The qualifications are also compliant.
But I just don't feel at ease.
Are you worried
something might be wrong
with Lin Yisheng?
That's not it.
I can't tell now.
I don't
understand accounts,
but I know people very well.
Don't worry.
If Lin Yisheng is honest,
that'd be perfect.
If he tries anything shady,
I'll make sure he suffers a lot.
Don't worry.
(Choose "Make Money" to Enjoy Your Life)
I knew this guy knew it long ago.
He's been colluding with outsiders
to scam the neighbors.
Such a traitor.
So many people are here.
Don't let anyone laugh at us.
I'm going to catch him now.
Let's see how he'll explain it.
Stay here.
Don't move.
Two handsome guys.
Drive.
(Birkin Paris Club)
Bao,
that ingrate has been deliberately
hiding things from you.
I wondered why he arranged
such a busy schedule for you.
It was just to buy time for them.
I'm aware
of this matter.
Over the years,
the company has developed so fast
thanks to Man's hard work.
Both of you know
how much effort he put
into the Tuan Island Market.
If
he hid this
from me,
then he's definitely hiding
more things from me.
Bao, look at this.
Photos don't prove much,
but he still never explained
why he went to Guanhai Tea House.
At that time,
I didn't have any substantial evidence,
and you weren't around.
The company was relying on Uncle Man,
so I didn't speak out.
But looking back,
his attitude since that day
has been somewhat strange.
The moon is surrounded by stars
I hide my regrets in the dark
You said don't go
Because that's where you belong
Wild winds blow across the land
Witnessing the hardships
we've been through
You said don't be afraid
Even though life is always hard
Looking back
My laughters and tears
You've seen them all
I've loved, got hurt, and made mistakes
Maybe it's in the past
Still remember
The promises I made
Dream about those years
Waking up feeling painful
On those lonely nights
I couldn't sleep
Praying for a good ending
All that's left
Is a sigh
How I wish
I could see you again