OH MY GHOST
Hey Na Bong. Hey!
What are you doing, Na Bong-sun?
How can you disappear like that after
saying that nonsense?
Are you,
by chance, playing a
'hidden camera' prank on me?
If that's what this is,
then it's really not fun for me.
Do you have a death wish or something?
What exactly are you doing, right now?
So you're saying you see ghosts.
Is that it?
Yes.
Every time I thought you were manic
you were possessed by a ghost?
Yes.
So, what you're saying is...
That ghost ...
That was inside you...
Or as people say, the ghost that
possessed you...
She is the one that I've been
spending time with.
Giving lessons to...
Having skinship with...
This is what you're saying, isn't it?
And you don't remember any of it, right?
Right.
Sounds plausible.
Why don't you just write a movie script?
You expect me to believe that?
Why don't you just say, 'I'm a ghost too.'
That'd be quite the twist.
It would be like 'The Sixth Sense.'
Why are you doing this to me? Why?
Why in the world are you doing this?
Have your feelings changed?
Are you trying to break up with me?
If that's what it is, then just say so.
Don't go on and on about this ghost
nonsense and drive me crazy.
It's not like that, Chef.
If that's not it, then what is it?
Everything I said is true. Really.
You know the ghost that possessed me?
She is the daughter of that little
restaurant owner.
I'm seriously going to go crazy.
OH MY GHOST EPISODE 13
YONGSAN POLICE STATION
(It was Shin Soon-ae for sure.)
Is something wrong?
If I can help, I will.
It's...
So...
Actually...
Never mind, it's nothing.
Your shoelaces are tied in a strange way.
Oh, this? You know Bong-sun from
the restaurant?
She tied them for me.
(She's been in Na Bong-sun's body,
all this time.)
Hello.
Oh, what's this? Officer Kang!
-You're back to work starting today?
-Yes.
-Are you feeling better?
-Yes, I'm a lot better now.
You must've all had a hard time,
taking on my share of the work.
What do you mean?
Sure, we couldn't take days off.
We worked late every day
and his nose bled.
We were so tired to death every day.
I'm so sorry.
I'll buy you both a meal sometime.
What kind of money would an
officer have? Huh?
Buy us meat, okay? Beef.
I'm just kidding.
She got prettier since she's
been sick, right?
Oh, you're right.
Relax, would you?
Don't overstrain yourself.
You got pretty.
That's right. Rest and don't do anything.
Don't even breathe.
No wait, you should breathe... Breathe.
Man, it's really boiling out... It's hot.
It's a hot summer, a hot summer.
When it's this hot out,
Chef-Bong couple probably can't do...
Stuff like this, right?
Are you going to talk or sweep?
Where are Chef and Bong anyway?
Does she think she can be late
now that she's dating Chef?
Hey, hey! What if Bong says to us...
'You lowly servants! You frivolous
peasants!' What do we do then?
-I'm sorry I'm late. I'm sorry.
-You're here.
What are you doing coming in now?
You're only 30 minutes late.
What?
A person ought to be late more often.
It makes them seem more human.
I just can't breathe when I'm next to
people who are always on time.
Bong, you shouldn't be like that.
Okay... Okay.
Why do you all have that look
on your face?
-It's nothing.
-You're the best.
What's with all the idle talk
in the morning?
We have many reservations so hurry.
-Yes, Chef!
-Jun.
-Yes?
Today's special is chicken pasta
using chicken breast.
-Marinate with pepper.
-Okay.
-Dong-chul.
-Yes?
You should cut them a bit thicker.
Yes, Chef.
-Woong.
-Yes?
We'll serve salmon raw today
so put them in the fridge.
Yes, Chef.
-And clean the scallops.
-Yes, Chef.
Yes, yes.
This is Heo Min-soo reporting from
the kitchen.
Sun Restaurant has its first
official couple.
It really is romantic and so sweet.
I can taste the sweetness in my mouth.
Yes, Bong.
What term do you use to call Chef?
'Honey,' 'baby,'
'husband'?
Bong Bo Roo Bong?
Yes, Bong is too embarrassed to answer.
Then I will take the mic to Chef.
When did you first start to see
Assistant Cook Na Bong-sun as a woman?
Number one, Bong who always dozed off
was sexy.
Wow.
Number two, Bong who said
'I'm sorry, I'm sorry'
and was all shriveled up and fearful.
And you wanted to protect her.
-Number three...
-Is this your playground?
Do I pay you to play?
-No.
-Go check on...
Go check on the dough for the noodles.
And go do your job.
Like I said, we have many reservations
today.
Yes, Chef.
Something is going on between them.
Something is off with Chef and Bong,
right?
There's tension there, isn't there?
It seems like they got into a big fight.
They were acting so cold to each other.
Yeah, they must have had a fight.
They weren't even making any eye contact.
I thought the kitchen became Siberia.
Why are you all so curious?
It's their personal life.
If you're not curious... Then get lost!
Gosh, seriously...
Maybe that's not it.
Maybe they went at it last night and now
they're just embarrassed in front of us.
What do you think? Right?
Their acting is awesome. We're at Cannes.
Are you saying they fooled us?
I don't think that's it.
I'm telling you they totally fought.
No, what I'm saying is right.
Our Bong... She is a very politically
savvy girl.
Her shriveled self suddenly turning into
a sassy girl is how she got Chef.
So that's why we have to keep
things friendly with Bong.
-Friendly Bong.
-Yes. Got it?
What the heck are you looking at?
I thought you weren't curious!
Officer Choi...
Why would Officer Choi do that?
To Na Bong-sun. Why?
Think carefully.
Does anything stand out?
When you possessed Na Bong-sun,
did anything happen with him?
When I possessed her?
Now that you mention it...
I went to see Officer Choi.
I asked him if he's sure about Shin
Soon-ae's suicide and to look into it.
And after that,
he tried to kill Na Bong-sun?
-Yes.
-If that's the case...
It means it has something to do with
your death.
You know there was something off
about Officer Choi from the start.
His fortune was different from
his current life.
His old picture and current picture were
weirdly different physiognomically.
And the gloomy look in his glare
when I met him.
Although it's not for sure, but maybe...
Maybe...
Officer Choi...
May be possessed by an evil spirit.
Evil spirit?
Once an evil spirit latches onto a person,
it doesn't leave and is like a parasite.
Between the evil spirit and
the person it possesses...
Over time, they can't be differentiated.
I'm getting a sense.
For now, warn Bong-sun or
whatever her name is to be careful.
Keep your eye on Officer Choi.
If he is an evil spirit,
he may be able to see you.
You must be very careful.
Okay.
Hey, it's right.
-It's really not.
-How much do you want to bet?
Hey...
-Bong. Miss Bong?
-Yes?
You... Tell us. Be honest.
You didn't have a fight with Chef, right?
It's because you two made
too much progress last night.
And you're embarrassed, right?
No... No. That's not it.
-It's not?
-No...
Then, did you guys really fight?
Yes...
By chance... Is Chef a pervert?
So last night he went 'eeeh' and
you went 'eee'?
He went 'eeeh' and you went 'eee'?
-Huh?
-Was it really like that?
You should talk about these things
with your seniors like us.
We won't tell Chef. Tell us what happened.
Go ahead. Tell us.
Na Bong-sun! Come out for a bit.
Come.
Chef, Bong is supposed to be in charge of
the dinner special salad.
Cancel dinner today.
You guys can clean up.
Chef, wait...
Our Chef just let go of his restaurant,
right?
I think so...
Wow, what is going on seriously?
This is huge.
It doesn't look like a trivial matter.
Based on Chef's mood.
I thought about it.
And I think you're seriously ill.
You seem to experience hallucinations.
You need to see a doctor.
If it's serious, get treatment.
If needed, get hospitalized.
I'll get you better, Na Bong-sun.
-I'm not... Manic depressive.
-How do you know? Are you a doctor?
Have you seen an insane person admitting
that they are insane?
-For now, let's go in. Get diagnosed.
-I...
I'm really, really, really not, Chef.
I know it's difficult to believe,
but you have to.
I lived like that for 28 years.
My grandma is a shaman.
I'm of that bloodline and
I can see ghosts with my eyes.
This is my reality.
You know, I...
I thought about dying many times,
but I endured and held on.
Chef, I'm really sorry.
Na Bong-sun.
Why? What's up now?
Na Bong-sun, listen to me carefully.
The time you almost
got into an accident...
Hey, Na Bong-sun!
Fine, let's say what
you're saying is true.
You are a unique person.
And you can see ghosts.
Okay, that's possible. Why?
Because there are many unexplainable
things in the world.
But, even so...
I refuse to believe that who I've seen
up to now isn't the real you.
That ghost or whatever...
I won't believe it until I see it with my
own two eyes. I can't believe it!
I told him everything.
Why?
What?
I didn't like it.
I don't like Chef getting confused
between you and me anymore.
What are you saying?
She's here.
The ghost I told you about before.
She's here right now.
What?
You're really not going to stop, are you?
Chef...
Don't talk to me.
My head is about to explode now.
You didn't know about it, right?
You didn't know since the ghost
possessed you on her own.
At first, I didn't know.
When I woke up, I had been possessed.
But after that,
I gave her permission.
Permission to possess me.
Why?
Why would you do that? Why?
I... Really... You...
I want to understand you like crazy.
But, I just can't right now.
There's something very strange
about this place.
Strange?
There's a mysterious mix of chill
and vitality in this place.
No, you can't!
Stop touching me, please!
Ah, ghost! Please! I can't hear you!
That's too left.
Right! Left!
-I think I'm going... Wait.
-Left. Right.
I thought you couldn't ride.
What? What do you mean?
I'm really good at riding bikes.
-Slowly, okay.
-I'm going!
-Let's go!
-Okay, okay. Slowly.
-Slow down.
-We're going!
Oh, hey, what's with all that drinking
with no food?
You'll get drunk at this rate, Chef.
When you get drunk and become sexy,
then I'd want to do it with you again.
Chef... You should eat something too.
Otherwise, you'll harm your stomach.
I'm going crazy.
Brother-in-law!
Oh, brother-in-law.
I was walking by and saw...
Are you drinking alone?
You should stop. I think you had enough.
I did? I drank a lot?
Why am I not getting drunk?
I really want to get drunk today.
I can't even get drunk.
Are things bad? With Bong-sun?
Bong-sun?
-Na Bong-sun?
-Yes, Bong-sun.
Do you...
Do you believe in ghosts?
What?
Do you believe that ghosts exist
in the world?
No, I never really thought about it.
Right.
It's not something most people would
think about.
What kind of absurdity is this?
Na Bong-sun is Na Bong-sun.
But, she's not Na Bong-sun.
So, Na Bong-sun is Shin Soon-ae.
KANG SUN-WOO
I was so stupid, Chef.
I thought if I could make you mine
like this...
I thought it would be okay.
Na Bong-sun...
Na Bong-sun!
Chef.
Why did you tell me?
Why did you...
If you were going to fool me,
why didn't you fool me till the end?
Why did you tell the truth now?
It would've been better for me not
to know.
You know?
I would've been better off thinking
you were manic depressive.
I couldn't...
Lie to you anymore, Chef.
Why!
Why couldn't you lie?
You did it just fine all this time.
Was it fun?
Here I was, unable to differentiate
whether it was you or a ghost.
Did you have fun watching me by chance?
No, Chef! It wasn't like that at all.
Gosh...
I'm going crazy, Na Bong-sun.
What do you mean, ghost?
Isn't this like those summer horror
specials on TV?
Who was it that I liked?
Did I like you or the ghost... Huh?
Why did you do this? Why?
Because I liked you.
Because I liked you so much.
I liked you so much from the moment
I first saw you.
I wanted to keep you by my side,
even if I had to resort to that.
I think I need some time. Go in and rest.
Sun-woo! What are you doing here
at this hour?
-I just came here to sleep.
-Hey, hey. hey.
What's going on?
Is something wrong with Bong-sook?
-Did you break up?
-It's not like that.
Mom, I'm going to rest.
Gosh, what's going on?
That kid is so charismatic.
He is my son,
but he looks good when he's like that.
No, no, no.
This isn't the time to think of that.
You can do it, Shin Soon-ae.
First, look into Officer Choi.
And tell Na Bong-sun about it.
You can do it!
CHEF KANG SUN-WOO
Where did she go?
I have to tell her about Officer Choi.
Her bags are gone too.
Did she, by chance...
Did Na Bong-sun leave?
No way.
Gosh, I'm going nuts.
-Jun.
-Yeah?
Where's the fried crab meat?
Bong said she'll put it in the fridge.
Is it not there?
Hey, hey. Call Bong, would you?
This is going too far.
Being late two days in a row.
Her phone is turned off.
Do you think she's not coming after
getting in a fight with Chef?
I doubt it.
Bong is not that irresponsible.
-Oh, Chef!
-Chef!
Why are you coming in from the front door?
I came from home. I'll get changed.
Chef, I'm not sure if you know this,
but Bong-sun isn't at work yet.
Na Bong-sun?
I was worried so I called,
but her phone is turned off.
She isn't someone who'd act this way.
Okay, I got it. Get to work.
Today's special is abalone pasta, right?
Get that out and prepare the abalone well.
-Yes, Chef.
What do you mean by that?
You think Bong-sun is gone?
It's starting to look that way.
We thought she was late or missing a day.
But, we checked her locker and
it was completely cleaned out.
Actually, things weren't good between her
and Chef yesterday.
I think that might be why.
That's crazy. Even still...
This is why dating in the workplace
is bad.
If a problem arises between the two,
one of the two has to leave.
Why? Because it's super uncomfortable!
Still, I don't think this is right.
There is never any boredom here.
It's one shocking thing after another.
So, Na Bong-sun is gone.
Then, that means she's not back in
that body.
Shin Soon-ae, where are you, ghost?
RESTAURANT
Oh, she opened her eyes. Dad, she's alive.
Are you okay now, Bong-sun?
Are you awake now?
How did I end up here?
I found you passed out when I went
for my morning exercise.
I considered calling the ambulance.
But, you didn't seem
completely unconscious.
Do you know how much of a scare I got
when my dad called me?
My legs were shaking from carrying
you here.
You're anemic, aren't you?
Look at that pale face.
It's got to be anemia.
I'm sorry. I've been such a burden.
Oh my, where do you think you're going
in this state?
-What?
-Huh?
Seeing that you have this bag,
you must have left your job.
Isn't that true?
Get better and then go. It's okay with us.
Oh no. I'll go stay with my grandma.
Do you think your grandma will be
happy to see you this way?
Well... Even if you go,
you should go when you're better.
You sure don't listen for such a
small thing.
What will you do if you faint again?
That's true. Just do as we say.
You've done so much for us too.
This is my daughter's old room.
It's an empty room,
so you can use it for a bit.
Okay.
Kyung-mo, let's leave so she can rest.
Why? I want to stay for a little longer.
Let's go! Come on.
-Rest comfortably.
-Thank you.
Come on.
What's got you so busy this morning, Dad?
Have you been well?
I'm a bit disturbed, Dad.
I'm disturbed because of Officer Choi.
And I'm disturbed because of Na Bong-sun.
This wasn't what I wanted to happen.
What's with the porridge anyway?
Is Kyung-mo sick?
He must've gotten drunk and sick again.
Gosh, that kid.
You have to cut off
his allowance to fix his habits... Huh?
What is it? Is Kyung-mo in my room?
Yes.
Oh!
Why are you so surprised?
-It's as if you've seen a ghost.
-What?
-No, that's not it.
-What are you doing here?
I brought you some egg porridge.
Even if you don't have an appetite,
you should eat to get your strength.
-Eat this.
-Thank you.
Thank you for the food, Mister.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
My dad has a lot of compassion.
What happened?
I went to the rooftop storage room and
I was worried when you weren't there.
It just worked out that way.
I had passed out and your father
spotted me.
What a relief.
Is it because of me, by chance?
That you left Sun Restaurant?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I didn't think it would go this far.
Honestly, I did resent you for a
little bit.
If you think about it, it's half my fault.
At least, I have memories with Chef.
That's something.
He's someone I couldn't even look
at before.
You're making me feel even sorrier...
By being so nice about it.
But, this isn't the time for us to feel
sorry and whatnot.
There's an urgent situation.
-What is it?
-You know that car that nearly hit you?
That was Officer Choi's doing.
Officer... Officer Choi?
Why would Officer Choi do that?
I don't know either. I have to find out.
You shouldn't be seen by him.
You should stay inside if you can.
I'll find out what I can and come back.
Okay.
-Na Bong-sun.
-Huh?
I'm thinking that my grudge isn't
a virgin grudge, after all.
Why would Officer Choi do such a thing?
Okay, these are the last orders.
Everyone, let's do it.
Yes, Chef!
Salmon salad and two Shrek pastas
at table four.
One steak and one Shrek pasta
at table six.
One vegetable bibimyun and
two bean pastas at table seven.
I'll do the vegetable and bean.
Min-soo, you do the Shrek pasta.
-Jun.
-Yes.
-You do the steak.
-Yes, Chef.
-Dong-chul, do the salad.
-Ji-woong, help Min-soo.
-Yes, Chef.
-We're on it, Chef.
-Hey, Cordon.
-Yes?
Forget the steak and work on the
intestines.
-Okay.
-Where did the lentils go?
Jun, did you use all the lentils?
Yes. Should I go get more?
-Keep working. I'll get it.
-Okay.
-Ji-woong.
-Yes, Chef.
Give table seven some more bread.
They finished it and
have been licking their fingers.
Bong left like that,
but Chef must not care at all.
He's more upbeat and full of charisma
than usual.
I'm grown fond of our Bong Bong.
So, I'm feeling betrayed, you know.
I'm feeling really let down by you, Chef.
The way I see things,
Chef is not okay at all.
That's the feeling I get.
What are you saying?
I've known Chef a long time.
The bigger the ordeal,
the more he pretends he's okay.
He has a habit of doing that.
He had that look in his eye... A sad look.
-Give that to me!
-Oh, what?
Are you going to get sick again and
take time off from holding this?
Gosh, now I feel like I'm back at work.
With you picking on me, Officer Han.
-I'll do it...
-Oh my!
Look at you.
You're so weak. How can you be an officer?
You're so worrisome.
How can we send you out anywhere?
She's been weak her whole life and
always wanted to be an officer.
She's become much healthier.
She always looked so pale because
of her anemia.
She's can't really walk well though.
(Keep your eye on Officer Choi.)
(If he is an evil spirit,
he may be able to see you.)
(You must be careful.)
Oh my... Here.
Thank you.
Oh, my legs... My legs.
She's weak, she's weak.
That makes me want to possess you.
YONGSAN POLICE STATION
Officer Choi.
-Yes?
-Do you have the digital camera?
-Oh, yes.
-Give me that, would you?
Wait.
-Here.
(-Oh, my diary.)
Your diary is in that cop's drawer?
Yes. And that drawer is locked with a key.
Now that I think about it,
it was odd then.
I said I'd take my diary.
But he insisted on keeping it.
That means there's something in there
that's incriminating.
Yeah, I wonder what it is.
Goodness, it's your diary!
-That's true.
-Just think about it.
You don't remember anything?
I don't know.
Suffering underwater...
And some strange music.
I just keep seeing images of that in
my head.
Okay, don't try too hard.
Just get that diary for now.
I think that's urgent.
Okay.
How do I get that thing?
This darn thing.
This isn't more than how much
baby chicks pee. It's so hot too.
You're hot? Should I help you cool down?
Huh?
You wench!
Do you like this too?
TODAY'S SPECIAL
Chef.
Good work guys. See you tomorrow.
The dog days of summer are over.
How about some ginseng chicken stew?
And if you drink some ginseng alcohol
your stamina, which was down here,
can rise up like this.
I think it will help us be
efficient workers, Chef!
-Are the dog days of summer already over?
-Yes.
I'm not really hungry.
You guys should eat something.
We always go together, so it's no fun.
Okay, Chef!
If you don't like ginseng chicken stew,
how about some beer?
Oh, what should I do?
I really want to drink with Chef today!
What's with you?
Let's go, Chef. I'll join in today too.
-Let's go!
-Go with us.
Kang Sun-woo, Kang Sun-woo!
-Okay, okay.
-Kang Sun-woo!
Cheers!
Let's drink!
What more is there to life?
We work until we sweat, drink beer,
eat this good food,
and be with each other as a family, right?
Yeah, it's great with just us guys.
Girls are just a pain.
Of course!
Yes, this is an old saying they say
in Italy... Italia.
When you're dealing with cows,
watch your front.
-With horses, watch your back.
-That's right.
When you're dealing with women,
watch out everywhere.
There's a saying like this.
What the heck? Is that some saying in
Jeolla-do?
Gosh, seriously?
The important point is that all women
are wicked people.
I don't need any of them.
I don't need them!
You startled me.
It's been confirmed. It's been confirmed.
Whoever betrays us and dates a girl...
I will take away all of your manhood.
-Goodness.
-Gosh.
Go on in.
Chef?
What?
About Bong-sun...
You're not going to give up on her, right?
-What?
-She's a good person, Bong.
She has a kind nature.
The Bong that I know...
From the first time she came in,
she's always been looking at you.
Whether she was washing dishes or
serving customers.
And even when she was on her break.
Her eyes were always looking for you,
Chef.
I respect you, Chef.
But if you let Bong go like this,
I think I'll be disappointed in you.
I know I'm overstepping my boundaries
when I say this.
I just want two people I like to be happy.
Officer Kang, what are you doing?
You haven't left work?
You shouldn't work too hard on your
first day.
Yes, I will go soon.
I must've had dinner too early.
I'm hungry again.
This punk... He eats and craps,
eats and craps.
Do some work, would you?
Should we order some pork hock?
It is a bit much, but at this hour...
There aren't many other places to order.
Don't bother doing that.
I'll stay here. Go out and eat, okay?
No, no. We should all stay together.
No, I have stuff to organize.
Go out and eat.
-Yeah?
-Yes.
-Should we?
-Yes, let's go.
Yes.
Will you be okay, Officer Kang?
You used to be scared alone.
What?
I should get over it now.
I am a police officer, after all.
Go on now. Okay.
-Work hard.
-Okay.
Bye.
-Where should we go?
-To Soon-ae's restaurant.
Not again.
What are you doing?
Officer Han.
Officer Kang, do you perhaps...
Have reason to be suspicious of
Officer Choi?
Tip?
Yes.
They told me that a tip came in regarding
Officer Choi.
Something regarding bribes and so on.
I can't give you specifics.
People at the top told me to look into it.
Is that so?
Officer Choi has several things that
seem off about him, doesn't he?
What do you mean?
Actually, I'm keeping my eye on
Officer Choi too.
-There's something suspicious.
-What do you mean by suspicious?
I'm not sure if you heard.
Recently, I got assaulted and mugged.
I was on my way back from restoring the
CCTV from Officer Choi's wife's accident.
As I passed out that day,
I thought I saw Officer Choi.
-On the scene that day?
-Yes.
In my opinion,
I think he's trying to
cover up for the criminal.
There must be some backdoor deal.
-How could something like that...
-That's what I'm saying.
For now, it's just my gut feeling.
Once I get the results, I'll be sure.
I've secured evidence that will determine
with certainty.
I just need to wait for the results.
Then, Officer Choi won't have anywhere
to turn.
Here is your meal.
I'm sorry, Mister.
You can't even close because of us.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I'm just selling you what I have.
Please, eat up.
You have to work all night.
-Yes.
-I'll be outside cleaning.
-Thank you.
-Please enjoy.
Officer Han said he'd be right back.
Where is he?
Why do you keep looking around anyway?
-Huh?
-Are you looking for someone?
-No, no. Let's eat.
-Okay.
(You shouldn't be seen by him.
You should stay inside if you can.)
STIR-FRIED RICE CAKE
That kid.
I guess she did study on her own.
CABBAGE
I saw this on Sunshine's blog.
BUCKWHEAT
(It was a hot summer night.)
(The buckwheat pancake I ate with him
was a privilege.)
(He said to me that those who cooked were
conductors of an orchestra in kitchen.)
(As I think about those wise words,
I will put up a buckwheat pancake recipe.)
(Think about what oil they used and
what they put in this dough.)
(What kind of seasoning they put in here.)
Think about this and don't just eat it.
Cooking is like being a conductor of
an orchestra in the kitchen, okay?
(If I perfect my understanding of
ingredients...)
(I am told that I can cook food to
my liking no matter where I go.)
(Try tasting all kinds of seasoning.)
(A cup of ginger tea will help get rid of
the after taste from your mouth.)
(Your recipes always contain a happiness
that one can feel through taste.)
(I'm a fan. Fighting.)
(Thank you very much.)
(Your comments are always a source of
strength for me.)
(It just so happens that I'm eating
the cabbage porridge right now.)
I think this person and I get each other,
emotionally.
I like you, Sunshine.
SUNSHINE
Resume... Resume.
RESUME
Kyunggi-do...
THANK YOU TO ALL THOSE WHO HAVE BEEN
READING 'YOU ARE MY SUNSHINE'
Yes?
What is this?
Can't you see? It's ice cream. Eat it.
My dad told me you didn't eat all day.
At least eat this and gain some strength.
I'm fine. I don't feel like it.
Why not, you wench!
You have to eat to live.
And why do you keep using honorifics
to me?
Are you trying to create a barrier
between us or what?
This is all because of Kang Sun-woo,
isn't it?
You left that place because of him.
Am I wrong?
You dumb girl.
If you threw me away and chose him,
you should, at least, be happy.
But, you got dumped like a moron.
You quit your job and can't even eat.
You dummy.
Why did you like someone like him?
A guest is coming.
Who could it be?
Hello, anyone home?
Hello there, is this the home of
Na Bong-sun's grandmother?
Yes, it is.
You're from Seoul.
You're someone who uses a knife.
Oh, yes.
Ah, I'm Bong-sun's work senior...
My name is Kang Sun-woo. Nice to meet you.
Oh! You chose a good career.
Your horoscope shows four positive 'yang'.
You should've been either an
artist or a soldier wielding a weapon.
It's not bad.
You're very compatible with my Bong-sun
who is all four 'yin'.
Oh, I see.
But, what brings you here?
Is something wrong with my Bong-sun?
No, that's not it.
I had some business nearby.
Bong-sun told me that her grandmother
lived around here.
I came to say hello.
Is that so?
Goodness, you sure have good manners.
-Please sit.
-Oh no, it's okay.
-I should...
-Oh, just sit down!
Unless you think it's filthy,
please just sit down.
Okay.
Well...
Bong-sun is doing very well.
She's such a deep person with integrity.
I know. I never worry about her.
She's always been so mature ever
since she was young.
She lost her parents when she was young.
She grew up without any peace
under a shaman grandma.
Yet, she would never complain.
She would prepare my meals every
morning and dinner.
And she would wait for me.
Goodness, she's got such a good heart.
It would have been so good...
If she didn't inherit my blood.
But since she was young,
she would see those ghosts.
She grew up so lonely without a
single friend.
Oh my...
I'm being so foolish,
in front of a guest at that.
Sit here for a moment.
I'm going to buy a bottle of soda.
-Oh no, Grandma.
-Just stay.
It's because I want to drink it.
I'm thirsty.
-Okay.
-Stay put.
(You must have been as lonely as I was,
Na Bong-sun.)
Hey, Kang Sun-woo. You're a total jerk.
-Oh, you...
-Yeah, it's me, you punk.
Wow, you look just fine.
You play around with an innocent girl and
kick her out.
You must be in great condition after that.
What are you talking about?
You want to know?
You really don't know what I'm talking
about, you awful punk!
Why did you do that to Na Bong-sun?
Why did you hurt that weak girl?
I...
I have never met anyone so bright and
positive besides my sister.
What did you do to her that she shriveled
up like that overnight?
She won't even eat one spoon of rice!
Are you even a human being?
How do you know that she isn't eating?
Because she's at our house, you jerk!
Be happy.
Yeah, Grandma.
What?
No, nothing's going on.
I'm doing well.
What?
Who dropped by?
-Who?
-Na Bong-sun!
-Gosh...
-Chef...
So, you've been alive?
Have you?
You only got this far when you ran off?
You purposely stayed here
so I'd come get you, didn't you?
-No, that's not it...
-I'm right.
Don't be mistaken, Na Bong.
I didn't run over here because
I've forgiven you for lying to me.
I was just so worried.
I'm holding you because my heart
told me to.
So, I'll just hold you a bit for now...
I'll stay like this for a moment.
I missed you.
Don't talk like a mosquito.
I can't hear you at all.
I said, I missed you a lot.
I missed you so much, Chef.
I thought about it and I'm sure of
one thing.
Even before, I...
Long before you were ever possessed...
I watched over you, thought about you,
and worried about you.
So, don't disappear from my sight again.
I'm going to go crazy with worry.
Chef.
You got that?
Yes.
OH MY GHOST
(I haven't done anything wrong,
but I feel like a bad guy.)
(It's not like I cheated.)
(I feel worried.
I'd rather we go together.)
(I'm never going to let go of this
hand again.)
(Looking at the circumstantial evidence,
it's almost definitely Officer Choi.)
Shouldn't we tell Chef now too?
(You know I rely on you a lot, don't you?)
About Eun-hee's hit-and-run case...
(She says Officer Choi could be involved.)
(What do you mean by that?)