OH MY GHOST
Seobinggo!
Hey, seriously...
-Today, I'm not letting you get away.
-Seobinggo!
Crap!
I just need today!
We'll be at this all night.
Taxi, taxi!
Stop, stop.
-Do you have a death wish?
-Pardon?
Do you know what time it is?
Would I make you wait like this?
I... I'm sorry, Chef.
You don't have a fever.
What's with you again?
Are you feeling depressed again?
You always say "I'm sorry" on repeat
when you're down.
No, it's not that...
Well yes, a little.
So, are you or aren't you?
Forget it.
Whatever the case, get in.
Whether it's a manic episode or
depression, we should eat something.
Okay.
By the way... Chef.
Yeah?
You know that show recording last time
and the thing with the flour?
-That worked out okay, right?
-Of course, it did.
Why? Did you want to gloat about it now?
That you're the one who fixed it?
No, that wasn't it at all.
Honestly, the bean powder was not bad
under the circumstances.
But if you put too much bean powder,
it can lose its moisture and fall apart.
That's where the saying
"bean powder household" comes from.
You should know that before you gloat.
Yes, I'll keep that in mind. Sorry, Chef.
-Okay, you keep that in mind.
-Yes, Chef.
Look up some directions on your
phone for me.
Search Hongjae-dong Buckwheat
Pancake House.
Yes, Chef.
Is she gone? She is, right?
Gosh, that Seobinggo is so good at
tracking people.
How the heck did she connect me
to Na Bong-sun?
I was nearly caught by her.
That gives me the chills. Whatever.
I caught you!
Seobinggo! Don't do this.
Don't get started with the sister crap.
-I don't like this.
-Shut up.
I'm so angry because of you!
-You're done for now.
-Okay, okay.
-Okay, okay... Ouch, that hurts.
-Come with me.
Do you know how much I spent on taxi
cabs because of you?
Goodness.
It hurts.
OH MY GHOST EPISODE 7
Food is not merely...
-Please enjoy.
-Yes, ma'am.
Food is not merely for consumption.
Just as much as music and art,
one should be conscious of it.
Do you know who said that?
-Chef?
-Wrong.
-I suppose you could think that.
-I'll do that.
It wasn't me. It was Leonardo Da Vinci.
Oh.
It means that you should eat food
in the same way you take in music and art.
Think about what oil they used.
What they put in this dough.
What kind of seasoning they put in here.
Think about this and don't just eat it.
Yes, Chef.
Cooking is like being a conductor
of an orchestra in the kitchen, okay?
Yes.
That conductor quote is something
I came up with. Surprising, right?
It gives you goosebumps, right?
It's very cool, Chef.
When have I not been cool? Eat.
How is it? Do you notice anything?
The texture is very crunchy.
Why do you think it's like that?
Is it corn starch?
If you use corn starch in this,
the dough would just get droopy.
The secret is... Onions.
Onions?
If you puree onions and mix it in,
it controls the moisture and it's crunchy.
You can think of onions acting as
the frying powder.
I see.
With food ingredients alone
you can make...
All sorts of textures without
creating them artificially.
Suppose you want it to be chewy.
Then, you would add potato.
And if you want something soft,
you can add milk to the flour.
You let someone like her take over
the sauce?
If you want to liven up the flavor,
you would add sesame oil.
-Are you going to zone out?
-No.
Right now, you're receiving
lessons that you can't pay for.
Yes, I know Chef. Thank you.
What would you add liven up the flavor?
-Sesame oil?
-That's right.
-Please eat.
-Okay.
Ah, this is nice.
Everything about this place is good,
but the parking is no good.
Can't you even look where you're going
when you're walking?
I'm sorry, Chef.
You need to work on your fitness.
You're always so weak.
The guys all call you "Bong, Bong"
and think they can get away with it.
-Why can't you say to them...
-Huh?
"I am not Bong. I am Na Bong-sun!"
Be confident.
Yes, Chef. I'll take note of that.
-Okay, let's go Bong.
-What... What?
I can do it, only me.
Yes, Chef.
That's so cool.
What's so great about that?
Don't you ever watch audition shows?
There are kids like that everywhere.
Hurry up. I'm tired.
Okay.
-Bong-sun.
-Yes!
-Get in.
-Seobinggo...
You're such a pain.
Please untie this for me.
It's only a matter of time until
I resolve my virgin grudge now.
What? You're kidding yourself.
It's not like blowing your nose.
It's not so easy for a ghost to
resolve their grudge.
That's not it. Just listen to me.
I've already prepared my meal.
It's game over once I dig my spoon
into it.
Goodness, what meal? How would you go
about finding a meal for yourself?
A meal...
You found a man of vitality?
Yes, I have!
It wasn't a coincidence that I entered
Na Bong-sun's body.
They say it's darkest under the lamp.
He was right under my nose.
You're not talking about that chef
at the restaurant, are you?
You noticed too, didn't you?
He turned out to be a man of vitality!
Goodness, no! No, you can't!
Why not?
His mom is my regular client.
I've become friends with her.
What's that got to do with me?
What ghost cares about that stuff when
they're resolving their grudge?
Even if he were your son,
I'd lay him flat out.
Son, what son? I'm a single woman!
And you can't touch her son.
You just can't!
Why not? It's not like he's your son.
Why are you protecting him?
That's not like you at all...
You must've taken a lot of money...
From his mother, huh?
How much did you get? How much?
What do you mean?
Just listen when I say that you can't.
Hey, I'll send you away,
so why don't you just leave?
It would be great if you could reach
a state of peace and go...
But, you can't do it on your own
so what can we do?
I prepared a nice table for your
memorial ritual for the dead.
A ritual for the dead?
No, I'm scared.
I heard it hurts and it's awful.
Everyone says it's very painful.
It's only for a moment.
You only need to endure it for
that moment.
No, I won't do it. I said I won't do it.
-Hey.
-I won't do it. I won't.
I refuse.
I ought to just cut you!
I don't usually eat late at night.
All this because of my employee.
I'm sorry, Chef.
You're sorry again?
I can't say anything around you.
Good night, Chef.
I don't know if I'll be
able to have a good night.
Who knows when you'll have a
manic episode and attack me.
-Sleep then.
-Yes, Chef.
Wait a minute...
Who hasn't played guitar back in the day?
I've played guitar a lot. I've played it
to the point where I'm sick of it.
Something like this.
Hey, Na Bong-sun. Hurry.
-Yes?
-Hurry up.
Wait, please.
Yes, Chef?
Look at the time.
Why do you sleep so much?
-I'm sorry.
-Chefs shouldn't sleep too much.
-You have to go to morning markets a lot.
-Okay.
-Hurry, let's work out.
-What, work out?
I told you yesterday.
You have fitness issues.
If you want to work in my kitchen,
you need to work on your fitness.
Look at me. Because I work out
all the time... See, my biceps.
That's really cool.
If you work hard, you'll get arm muscles
and be mentally healthy.
So, hurry up.
I don't really have exercise clothes...
Hold on a moment.
You can't ride a bike?
No, I can't.
What did you do when you were younger?
You didn't learn this?
Isn't this a fundamental thing?
I wanted to learn,
but I wasn't very athletic.
Well, what did you think I was renting
that extra bike for?
You should have said so
if you couldn't ride a bike.
It's not like you need a license or
anything like that.
Why can't you ride it?
Why can't you do this?
You're so good.
You're not letting go, right?
-Yes, I am.
-I'm going now.
If you go right, turn left and
if you go left, turn right.
Are you understanding me right now?
No!
You keep going left! Go to the right!
-Are you going to go up the stairs?
-I'm sorry.
-You have to go this way.
-Okay.
Wait.
Try again.
I'm trying to do well,
-but it's just not working out.
-I got you.
-Should we keep going?
-Yes, go left.
-Left where?
-That's too far left!
-Straight?
-In the middle, yes that's good.
To the right, okay.
-Left, right, right...
-Is this right? Wait...
-Ow!
-Are you okay?
Oh, my arm.
Teaching you is harder than
a cross-country trek on a bike.
Sorry, Chef.
Wait, I'm short 200 won.
You think we won't be able to drink any?
-Yeah, should we go?
-No.
No, there is a way.
Wow.
This is a growing experience of life.
This is a life tip.
You sure are learning a lot from me.
We're still short 100 won.
-100 won?
-Yeah.
We can share one can.
Here, 100 won.
-Have you done this before?
-No.
-It's your first time?
-Yes.
-It's really your first time?
-Yes, it is.
Since the teacher is quick,
the student is quick too.
I'm glad you are a quick learner.
-Here.
-Thank you.
Wow, looks good.
What is this? Where's my bike seat?
Hey!
What are you doing? Hey!
Stop right there!
-Oh, wait...
-Stop thief!
-Chef!
-Hey you!
-Hey!
-Chef!
Stop! Stop right there!
Oh my!
Darn it, he's fast.
Hey you!
Mister!
-Mister, wait.
-Hey, move!
-No, I can't, I can't, I can't...
-Just let go!
-Mister, I'm sorry.
-Let go of me.
If you're sorry, then let go of me.
Mister, I'm really sorry about this.
What is this? What's going on?
You jerk.
-My goodness!
-What did you do?
-I bit him.
-Good job.
-Get over here. Hurry up.
-What do you want?
Hey, you punk!
You stole all those bike seats and
now you're finally caught.
-Why you!
-Oh, you startled me.
Everyone's been having butt problems
because of you.
Get in there.
-Thanks, Chef.
-Oh no.
Hurry it up, punk.
How in the world did you catch him?
He's a chronic offender.
It wasn't me. It was Na Bong-sun.
What?
She couldn't overcome him with strength,
so she bit his leg. It was scary.
Oh no, Officer. I only bit lightly.
Whatever the case,
you did catch him by biting him.
I guess I did.
Thank you. He was such a pain to us.
I'll buy you a meal sometime.
Oh no, there's no need.
What did I say?
Now that you're exercising with me,
you have better muscles and grip.
The two of you... Exercise together?
Ah, well?
No, well...
She's not very fit,
so she's not good at holding fry pans.
-Ah...
-It's for training purposes.
-Hurry on in.
-Okay, bye, Sun-woo.
Goodbye.
-Bye, Bong-sun.
-Bye.
Have they left?
What's with the two of them?
Chef Kang is not the type to
exercise with his employees.
Yes, I know.
I know they're sometimes together
because of the TV show.
It's a bit unexpected.
A bit?
It's very unexpected.
It is, right?
I'll take one iced americano.
That's 4,300 won.
ROLL CAKE
Here.
Na Bong.
-Chef.
-Come eat this.
Oh no, I'm fine.
What do you mean?
You didn't eat breakfast.
Come grab a fork.
I really like this cake and
I don't usually share it with anyone.
I'm being generous today.
Okay.
How is it? Really good, isn't it?
Yes, it's tasty.
You're smiling a lot today.
-Excuse me?
-How nice is this, huh?
This is just right.
You're not going overboard or
shriveling up and saying sorry.
A person should have a neutral state
like this.
I really like you today, Na Bong-sun.
You even caught a thief today like, bam!
Look at you, you're so happy.
Sun-woo!
Hello.
Oh, So-hyung. What brings you by?
What do you mean? I came to see you.
-You said you liked americanos?
-Yeah.
Latte.
So, Bong-sun is staying in that
storage room?
Yeah, just until she finds a place.
She's already so weak as it is and
not feeling well.
The dormitory kicked her out,
so I felt bad for her.
What's with you?
I hear that you always keep your private
and public lives separated.
She's a part of this family.
I feel a little embarrassed to even
call that a room.
She just lays out a blanket in the
storage room and sleeps.
Did I say anything?
Why do you keep trying to explain?
It's getting suspicious.
What do you mean 'it's suspicious'?
Why are you here this morning anyway?
Just because, I was buying coffee nearby
and saw that cake you like.
I should just take it back.
-You were already eating it.
-No, don't.
Leave it. I'm grateful for it.
I eat bread for all three meals.
-Hello.
-Hi.
We'll step out for ten minutes, Chef.
-Yes, enjoy your conversation.
-Why? Where?
Stop going overboard.
We can step outside and exercise.
Or play hopscotch.
-We're interrupting something nice here.
-Be quiet!
-Go on in and prepare for the opening.
-Should we?
Enjoy.
I should get going.
I have to get to the station.
Okay.
I'll enjoy the cake.
You really are the best. Thanks.
-Oh yeah. I'll be going.
-Okay. Bye.
Bye.
So, that's the PD Lee I've heard about?
Ah, is this your first time seeing PD Lee?
It has been a while since she's been here.
She's super modern and trendy.
Is it because she's a Seoul woman?
Imagine if she were standing there
saying...
"Shoot" and "cut"...
I would be so excited.
You'd be excited by that?
Women need to have things like...
"Oh, honey"... A cuteness like that.
No, you're wrong.
There're too many of those women around.
A woman should be cool and modern.
I find career women sexy.
I think they'd lead well in bed at night.
Oh, stop it! I'm having fantasies
first thing in the morning.
Fantasizing is good. Fantasizing and...
Hey,
-you know fantasies?
-Yeah?
-For guys...
-Yes?
It's something all single guys or
lonely men need.
-That's true, that's true.
-Do you know what my favorite fantasy is?
-What is it?
-What?
You go over there.
What is it?
-What is it? What?
-Here...
Stay there, stay. Just a moment.
-Gosh, seriously!
-What are you doing?
-You pervert.
-Pervert!
-Get over here.
-I'm scared!
I don't want to do it.
I said I don't like it.
This is all for your own good.
-You don't have to do it for my own good.
-Come!
Just let me go up my own way.
Goodness, seriously!
Didn't I leave you be this whole time?
Did you resolve your grudge?
You exposed men to severe chills.
So okay.
Say you did find a man of vitality.
Did he say okay and just agree
to do it with you?
You only have months left.
What will you do when that time passes?
You want to become an evil spirit and
fight with me? Is that it?
I'm going to succeed. I will succeed.
It was going well for me.
Don't kid yourself, you wench.
Things aren't that simple and easy.
The world may seem chaotic and lawless
but there are more reasonable
people than not.
Come!
Dear Spirit!
All living things are fated to perish.
All things that are born disappear
after death.
But this pitiful soul has lost her way.
I'm afraid. I don't want to do this.
-Please.
-Spirit.
Sis...
A peaceful passage to heaven.
Be granted to this lost soul.
Please take pity!
I don't want this! I don't!
You're so happy.
Hey, PD Lee So-hyung.
You look great from the back.
Why are you acting up first thing in
the morning? Are you frustrated?
No, it's just habit.
When I see sexy women,
I just can't stop talking.
-Isn't this a talent too?
-Be careful.
You'll be sued for sexual harassment.
Oh my my. You're a little harsh today.
You're more charming like that.
Don't be that way.
Meet some guys while you look good.
I have a junior who's a great catch
and he's interested in you.
He's a single guy.
It's okay. I'll decline.
You're at your peak. You should date.
It's not because of Kang Sun-woo, is it?
Is something going on between you two?
Nothing's going on with us.
The crew members were talking about it.
They said the way Kang Sun-woo looked
at you wasn't ordinary.
I heard you two didn't look like
just friends.
No, we are really just friends.
Really?
Then, just do it.
My junior really is a good catch.
What do you think?
Should I go through with it?
I'll think about it.
Gosh, think about it?
Hey, hey, hey.
How about some crab stew and soju
after work today?
I found a great place today.
I have an allergy to crab.
-So itchy, itchy.
-Then, you can sit out.
-How about you?
-My mom suddenly said she's coming.
Your mom? Stop it, stop it.
Didn't your mom come up the day before?
Does your mom go back and forth
or do you have multiple moms?
Did you just say crabs?
-I did say crabs.
-Oh, I have to eat crabs.
My mom probably hasn't left yet.
Wait.
Are you going to keep lying like this?
Why I ought to just...
My knife got damaged because of you!
Isn't that Chef's knife?
It's mine. What are you saying?
I'm ruined. I'm ruined.
He's going to throw a fit.
Why did you use Chef's knife?
He hates it when people do that.
I didn't know it was his.
I just grabbed anything.
What should we do?
Darn it...
Hey, Bong Bong Bong.
You keep a lookout to see if Chef's
coming or not.
He's not coming yet.
Just keep looking.
He's... He's coming.
-Are the crabs fresh?
-Yes, Chef.
Get the dirt off it.
Yes.
What's my knife doing out here?
Did someone use it?
I sharpened it when I was doing mine.
Why the heck would you sharpen my knife?
-It's a bit short.
-There's no way, Chef.
It's about two millimeters short.
Bring me yours to compare, Min-soo.
Yes, Chef. Can you give me my knife?
Yes.
Why would you do something I didn't
even tell you to do?
Yes, So-hyung?
Gosh, this is brand new.
Why does he have such good eyes?
What is it? Is something up?
We finished editing the last episode
we filmed.
The cut we took between the takes
because of Bong-sun...
I merged them so it's not noticeable.
So don't worry.
What worry...
You called me to report that?
Yup.
And the talk regarding Bong-sun with
the Chief also went well.
(So don't be concerned.)
Okay, that's good.
Okay. Thank you.
-Talk to you later.
-Sun-woo!
Yeah?
You know that senior of mine you saw
at the studio last time?
He wants to set me up with one of his
juniors who's interested in me.
-Should I do it?
-He's setting you up?
Um, sure. Do it.
You've got nothing to lose by
meeting up with the guy.
-I should?
-Yes, you should.
You talk about it so easily.
You're saying I should, huh?
Okay, got it. I will.
(I can't die from old age without
even dating.)
(Okay, I'm hanging up now.)
Are you okay?
Does it sting a lot?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that to happen...
I think I was out of it for a moment then.
I got worked up because
I hated it so much.
It was an evil spirit.
What?
The spirit in your eyes at that moment...
That was an evil spirit.
Evil spirit?
It's been three years since your death...
You only have a few months left, right?
An evil spirit is slowly starting to
manifest in you.
And when you got all worked up,
it came out without your knowledge.
I don't know what's what.
What should I do with you?
Darn...
You want me to taste all of this?
Yes, I put them there for you to taste.
You only used them for cooking.
You never thought about what each
of these taste like, right?
-Yes.
-For example, salt...
Look at the salt. I laid it out here.
The taste is different depending on
region and company.
You have to know this precisely.
So that you can cook to perfection.
Okay.
Ah, salty.
Don't just think it's salty, dummy.
Roll your tongue around slowly.
Taste the saltiness, sweetness, and
bitterness.
And even the spiciness.
Try to find them all.
Salt has sweet taste?
Of course.
That's why we're doing this lesson.
-Go on and taste.
-Okay.
If you remember this taste precisely...
Then, you'll be able to know exactly
which salt to use while cooking.
Okay.
Olive oil is the same.
Try to figure out when the
oil was extracted.
Okay.
If you perfect your understanding of
ingredients...
No matter when and where you are,
you can make whatever you want.
Here.
What is this, Chef?
Ginger tea.
Drink this after tasting everything.
It'll make you feel better and refresh
your mouth, okay?
Yes.
-Okay.
-Yes, Chef.
I'll head in now.
-Taste it all.
-Okay.
I'm going to ask you about it tomorrow.
Good night, Chef.
-Bong-sun.
-Hello.
You're leaving now?
-Yes.
-It's late.
You must be patrolling.
I'm done. I'll head back and sign off now.
I see.
-Have you had dinner?
-No, not yet.
You must be hungry. Look at the time.
-I'll buy you a nighttime snack.
-What?
No, I'm fine.
Still, you should eat.
It's better than going home and
eating alone.
I just need to go back and
make a quick report.
You know that vendor at the intersection?
-Yes.
-You want to wait there?
See you soon.
Yes, okay...
Why isn't Na Bong-sun reading this?
How busy could she be?
She could be busy.
She's on TV and all that.
She's not even the main.
I thought she said
she'd exercise with you.
A person ought to keep their promises.
You don't play games with elders.
This won't do.
Gosh, she'll come when she comes.
You're the one who wants to see her, huh?
Why would I want to see her?
If she heard that, what would she think?
Hey!
Why aren't you picking up my calls?
Do you know how many times I called?
Me? I think you've got the wrong person.
What... What was that?
Dad, did she just totally ignore us?
What kind of person does that?
Wow, crazy. This is just crazy!
Wow, this is so wild, right Dad?
Is she crazy or something?
How could she...
Forget the phone thing.
Why did she pretend not to know us?
I suppose she could do that to me.
But, even to you?
It's a waste of electricity.
Turn off that light.
I'm sure she has her reasons.
What reasons could she possibly have?
Bullshit.
That's even too much
for playing hard-to-get.
Is she even doing that to her
future father-in-law?
Her acting was even spot on.
It was so natural.
You're right. The expression on her face
was as if she really didn't know us.
Right, you saw her facial expression?
Should we send her to Hollywood or what?
Gosh, I'm so annoyed!
Dad, should we have some soju?
Can you stay sober today?
Forget it, kid. Put it away.
Put it away?
You should order some more.
This seems too little for tent vendors.
Oh no, this is really more than
enough for me.
You really are strange, Bong-sun.
What? What is?
I felt this even before.
You seem like a different person
every time I see you.
You seem very introverted at times.
And at other times,
you seem like a tomboyish girl.
Is it a concept of yours?
No, no. It's nothing like that.
I often have mood swings like that.
And your memory comes and goes, as well?
Pardon?
Last time, you didn't remember
coming to the police station.
That's because I have a tendency to
easily forget things.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, you don't need to explain
yourself to me.
You must feel like you're being
interrogated by me.
No.
I'm just worried about you, Bong-sun.
When I met you early that morning,
you looked like you were in danger.
Like someone standing at the edge of
a cliff.
It didn't feel like it's
happening to a stranger.
I've had several moments like that
in my own life.
Well...
Actually...
Never mind. It's nothing.
Yes. It is nothing.
If you say it's nothing,
then it must be nothing.
-Please eat.
-Okay.
-Bon appetit.
-Yes, you too.
Why is she so quiet?
Is she sleeping already?
What is it?
(It's been a while since your mom called
and that's how you talk to me?)
("What is it?")
It's because it's so sudden,
I'm just taken aback.
Why? Is something going on?
(Yes, there is.)
(I'm sick.)
You're sick? Where?
Mom, are you okay?
You're here, Son? Come in, come in!
You came right on time.
What is this? I thought you were in bed.
Yesterday night, I took some medicine.
And I had a good night of rest and
now I'm all better.
My body has such good absorbing power.
It takes in alcohol
and medicine very well.
You lied about being sick.
-You lost weight. Are you dieting?
-My goodness.
-Sun-woo, you're here.
-You're here.
Yeah, I was fooled by Mom.
Her acting has really gotten quite good.
Be quiet and eat.
I worked so hard because you said
you were coming.
Go on and eat.
I put my care and effort into it.
It's not like it's something great.
You actually burned this?
You're driving me crazy.
It's hard to get toast wrong.
You're amazing.
What? It's not that burnt!
This is your career, so it's easy for you.
Making bean sprouts is harder than
getting my Ph.D.
Well, now...
Well, it's better than last time.
-Yeah, better than...
-Don't even bring up last time.
Sun-woo, when are you going on vacation
for your restaurant again?
I'm planning on next week. Why?
You know, this year...
You have to be careful of water too.
Oh right!
Do you wear that talisman underwear
that I got you early this year?
-You have to wear them. Let's see.
-Why would I? What are you doing?
Where do you think you're looking,
Professor Lee?
What's the big deal? I'm your mom.
-Gosh
-If it makes you feel better,
you can see mine.
-No, no! I don't want to.
-You can see them.
-Forget it! No.
-Now, let's see yours.
I'm not looking at yours. No!
-Something's very fishy here.
-I'm not going to look!
You're not wearing them, are you?
-What's wrong with you?
-You're not wearing them.
-Do you know how much they are?
-No, wait.
-Wait, hold on.
-They cost 200,000 won.
-Don't look.
-This is weird.
I don't even have food at home.
Where's all this food garbage coming from?
Seobinggo.
What?
Don't call my name. Just say it.
I'm too tired to respond.
If I stay here like this...
Will I really become an evil spirit?
Yes, you will.
What could you do about it?
I'm scared.
I'm scared of the memorial rites and
don't like that either.
But, I'm more scared of becoming an
evil spirit.
I didn't realize three years would pass
so soon.
If you had just listened and passed on
when I told you to
things wouldn't be so twisted like they
are now.
No kids turn out well
if they don't listen to elders.
Gosh, it hurts.
Maybe I need to sterilize this again.
Are you in pain?
Do you have any soju left?
Soju is best for sterilizing.
I know that too. Stop showing off.
Goodness.
I know I put some back here somewhere.
I have some left.
Is it here?
I know it's here. Where is it?
Gosh, I just keep forgetting where I
put my stuff.
Am I doing the right thing here?
I guess I developed some affection
for her, while hating on her.
I just don't know anymore.
Who cares about whose son he is?
Please, resolve your grudge...
You poor thing.
What's this situation here?
Even just yesterday, wasn't she having
a nice time with Chef?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
It's probably not what we thought.
If it were, is she crazy?
Why would she bring a guy here?
We don't know. It could be to provoke
jealousy.
Anyway, the mood is strange.
It seems like Chef is trying control
his facial expression.
Why is PD Lee hanging out with a
guy like that?
Even in my eyes, he's tacky.
He's just not at the level of our goddess.
Who does their hair like that these days?
Gosh...
What do you mean, goddess?
You can find women like that like
all over Kyungri-dan.
What Kyungri-dan?
Kyungri-dan, the street.
-You mean that really trendy street?
-Yeah.
Aren't you guys going to work?
-Yes, Chef.
-Yes, Chef. Sorry.
-Should I cook all the food?
-Sorry, Chef.
-Hey, Min-soo.
-Yes, Chef.
Take over. I'm going to the restroom.
-Oh, he's in a bad mood. He is.
-Yeah, he is.
-Going to the restroom?
-No, I'm waiting for you.
Huh?
What do you think of him?
Well, I don't really know.
He looks okay, like an honest guy.
Is that all?
Since he was introduced to you,
he probably has a good background.
You should keep meeting him.
It might not be so bad.
I should meet him, continuously?
As long as you're okay with it.
You can't tell with one date.
You really don't care at all, do you?
I'm suddenly really annoyed.
I'm the only one who does care.
Forget it. I don't know why
I'm acting like this.
Let's give it a rest.
Where should we have coffee?
-I know a great place...
-The thing is...
I'm really sorry.
I think I have to head back in.
What?
Sorry. I have editing left to do.
Thank you for today.
The meal was very good.
Then...
(You really don't care at all, do you?)
I'm suddenly really annoyed.
I'm the only one who does care.
I don't like the memorial ritual and
I hate becoming an evil spirit.
I'm going to resolve my grudge on my own
and then go up.
That's what I'll do.
-Hey, Na Bong-sun.
-Grandma!
Why are you so shocked?
Shouldn't you expect me by now?
This isn't what's important right now.
I have no time! I'm in a rush.
-What do you mean?
-I have no time for your permission.
-I'll go in now, okay.
-Are you crazy?
I have no more time.
I'm going to become an evil spirit.
Na Bong-sun!
-Hey!
-No!
Hey, you!
Will you take responsibility if I turn
into an evil spirit?
Why should I? I don't know anything
about evil spirits.
You can't say that.
You have a responsibility as a
resident of Seoul.
If you knew how awful some spirits were,
you wouldn't say that.
Wait now, I'm not technically a
Seoul resident.
I'm from Choongchun.
Yeah, we're all the same Koreans.
I don't know. I don't know.
Hey, Choongchun resident.
I don't know. I'm coming in.
No, you can't!
No!
Hey, stop!
Oh, stop running.
Get over here.
It's been a while since
I felt competitive.
I'm pretty athletic.
Grandma!
-Oh, is that Chef Kang?
-Don't look.
-What's he doing there?
-It's nothing.
Wait, you're not...
I'm not.
What's not?
Everything is not true.
Aw, you don't by chance...
I don't.
Really?
Since when?
Did you like him this whole time?
By yourself? One-sided?
You sure are something.
That's why you stuck around even
though you were picked on.
Yeah, I get it now.
Usually, I'm the expert in one-sided love.
Hey, Na Bong-sun.
This all works out.
Since things worked out this way,
let's mutually help each other.
Kang Sun-woo, that self-centered man...
I'll make him your man.
What do you mean by that?
With your personality,
you'll never be able to seduce Chef.
And I don't see Chef looking
your way first.
I'll get him for you, in your place.
-Why?
-What do you mean? I'm a virgin ghost.
In order to resolve my grudge,
I need a man of vitality.
Chef is that man of vitality.
So, I'll resolve my grudge and
leave this place.
You can be with Chef and
it'll be win-win for both of us.
Still, that's not...
What's wrong with that?
You're so frustrating!
Do you know who Chef Kang likes?
He likes PD Lee. Since very long ago.
PD Lee is single and it's only a matter
of time before they hook up.
One mistake, and Chef Kang can disappear.
No, we can't have that, no.
And I'm just saying this now...
But, isn't it because of me that
you're next to Chef Kang now?
You know what I'm like, don't you?
I'll stick to people, no matter what.
If you try ten times,
every guy can be won over.
Also, Chef has been taking care of you
a lot lately.
Still...
Still, that's not right.
I don't want Chef like that.
Why not?
Do you dislike that I'm resolving
my grudge using your body?
This is no time for you to be picky.
You have to make Chef Kang your man.
No, it's not right. What's wrong is wrong.
Na Bong-sun. Hey, Na...
Na Bong-sun.
Oh, crap.
If it were me, I'd say, "Yes I like."
And agree right away.
She is so subtly conservative!
I'm so hungry, I can't even pray long.
Gosh...
There's three left.
I have to last the week with this.
I'll eat half.
Gosh, why is she calling again?
I can't see her for now since
I sent that ghost to her son.
Yeah, it's me.
Honey, what are you doing?
Oh, I'm just doing nothing. Why?
I wanted to have pork ribs and soju.
(But, I didn't want to eat alone.)
Pork ribs.
But, what can I do?
I'm coming down with a cold.
I think I need to rest today.
Oh yeah? That's too bad.
I wanted to see you today.
(Okay. Take good care of yourself.
I'll call again soon.)
(-Bye.)
-Bye. Okay.
I'm so hungry, but I can't get
a free meal. This is just terrible.
Out of so many men, why does Kang Sun-woo
have to be the man of vitality?
Gosh, that cursed wench.
Is she working on her virgin grudge
or what?
Goodness,
there are no stars in the sky tonight.
You're right. It's really dark.
It's dark in my heart too.
If three years pass and I become
an evil spirit
I won't be able to recognize you dad.
What should I do?
So hot.
Will the fall season ever come?
That fall season scares me, dad.
How did I come to roam around here
when others got to go to the heavens?
Not like virginity is a huge grudge.
Now, tomatoes.
Try cutting out the stem ends first.
Yes, Chef.
Stop! Stop.
Tomatoes are soft.
If you hold the knife like that,
it'll go through the tomato.
And where would it hurt?
-Your left hand, right?
-Yes.
Here. Hold the knife.
-Don't hold the end.
-Okay.
In cases like this,
you need to hold the spine.
-Like this.
-Okay.
Hold my hand as if you're holding
the knife.
Go ahead. Hold it.
That's it. Hold still.
And then use your left hand
to turn the tomato.
-Okay?
-Okay.
If you know how to use the knife well,
that's 50% of cooking skills.
Okay, that'll be all for today.
-Clean up.
-Yes, Chef.
Go on in.
What's this?
So-hyung?
It's Kang Sun-woo.
Oh, okay, okay.
Hey... Did you have a lot to drink?
You drank with that guy till now?
Nope, I drank alone.
I was upset,
so I just had drinks by myself.
I'm just not in a good mood today.
For various reasons.
Woah, hey...
-You're quite drunk. I'll take you home.
-No, no.
Wait.
I didn't come here to ask you
to take me home.
Since I already embarrassed myself,
let me ask you one more question.
Are you really okay with it?
Even when I'm with some other man?
As for me, when you worry about
that nobody, kitchen assistant...
Just watching you being concerned
about her... Makes me get all jealous.
You are not like that?
You don't get like that at all?
Why are you like this all of a sudden,
So-hyung?
You're right.
That's what makes me upset.
Why am I like this all of a sudden?
But, let's just forget about me,
for a second.
What about you?
You don't see me as just a friend, right?
Right?
So-hyung...
I don't know why living is so difficult.
When I was alive, it was difficult.
And now when I'm dead, it's difficult.
What kind of life is this?
What is so difficult?
You even found a man of vitality.
No progress whatsoever since the kiss?
Oh, hey, you don't have much time left.
You should skip some bases
and just go for it.
You know, when guys are coming down
the stairs, if a girl jumps up to them...
They really fall for that.
It's all useless.
I can't possess the girl that
the man of vitality likes.
And the one I can potentially possess
resists saying I can never use her body.
So, are you giving up?
I don't know.
Maybe I should.
I really wanted to do it once.
Something so easy for others...
Why is it so hard for me?
-Even after I died...
-Hey...
Even when you're alive, you can't control
your life. What do you expect?
If it's too much to bear,
just ask Suhbingo to send you off.
It's better than being an evil spirit.
Memorial rite for the dead...
It'll probably hurt like heck, right?
Maybe as painful as urolithiasis?
Not sure. I heard that giving birth
is less painful.
It's nice to meet you all.
I'm Na Bong-sun.
Do you know who Chef Kang likes?
(He likes PD Lee. Since very long ago.)
(One mistake, and Chef Kang can disappear.
No we can't have that, no.)
Hey, ghost! I have something to say.
Why isn't she here when I look for her?
Hey!
I really need to talk to you.
Where did she go? Hey!
Hey, ghost!
Darn it. I don't know what to do...
Ascend through the rite for the dead,
or become an evil spirit...
Something will happen. Gosh, darn it!
What the...
It's Na Bong-sun!
I went around looking for you.
Me? You've been looking for me?
You... I've been looking for you
for a while.
I mean why? Didn't you shoot fires at me
and tell me to go away the other day?
I wonder why you came to see me,
Na Bong-sun, the most conservative ever?
I'll allow it. You taking over my body.
Huh?
You can possess me.
Make Chef Kang mine.
OH MY GHOST
I feel greed. For you, Chef.
-Fighting!
As a team-building event, I was
thinking we can go on a trip together...
Suddenly, attack!
(I don't think he should be allowed
to drink too much.)
If we are going to have something
between us.
It's out of our hands, right?
Catching the hit and run offender.
You should forget that incident.
I'm here for Eun-hee.
Why is another girl inside that girl?
What do you mean?
I have no idea what you're saying.
(The way you are setting boundaries
between us.)
(Is Bong-sun related?)