OH MY GHOST
It's so cold.
I'm all wet.
-What should I do...
-Hold on.
Oh, no. You're all wet.
I feel so bad. What should I do?
Oh, I'm such a klutz.
I think...
The water is all gone...
Now?
Oh, I'm... I'm sorry!
Hey, Na Bong-sun.
Na Bong!
It wasn't a mistake.
It wasn't a mistake this time.
Well, I...
I know...
I'm...
Acting strange and
I feel like I'm going a little crazy.
But, I'm being sincere.
What?
Don't you get it?
Kang Sun-woo...
Likes you.
I don't know when it started.
Whether it's from the very beginning or
when you suddenly changed
and latched onto me.
Or it could be yesterday or today...
I really don't know.
The one thing I know for sure is...
I keep wanting to see you.
And I feel nervous
if you're not next to me.
Gosh, I'm going to go nuts.
You're someone who's like my family.
So,
let's just go for it.
They're my feelings so who's to
say anything about it?
Well...
Well, say something.
Don't just stand there breathing.
If someone like me confesses to you,
shouldn't there be a reaction?
Ah, yeah.
Thank you, Chef.
What?
No, I mean...
What I meant was...
You're saying okay, right?
You're saying...
That you like me too?
Yes, Chef.
Why are you feeling so restless,
for no reason?
Get your head on straight, girl.
You're a ghost, not Na Bong-sun.
Let's get your head on straight.
Head, head, head...
Head...
Hey.
I'll do it.
-Don't move an inch and sit down.
-Okay.
I'll be done very soon.
Here we go...
That should do it.
Your hair is still wet.
Even though it's summer,
you can still catch a cold.
Here, face me.
-It's working, right?
-Yes.
I must be truly bewitched by you.
Seriously.
You're like a little chestnut.
You look like a puppy.
Look how happy you are. Gosh.
I am happy.
My goodness...
OH MY GHOST EPISODE 9
I wonder why he's calling?
Yes, Officer Yang.
Officer Han?
Yes.
Okay, I'll be right there. Okay.
What's that about Officer Han?
He was in an accident of some sort.
He's in the hospital.
-I'll be right back.
-Okay.
-Where are the car keys?
-Over there.
Oh my.
Wasn't Officer Han the lead on
Eun-hee's case? Your partner?
Yes. I'll be back, Mother-in-law.
-Go to bed first.
-Okay.
Oh my. What could it be?
A car accident?
I'm not sure.
I feel out of breath and
my heart's beating fast.
It must be bringing back past memories.
Are you all right?
I'll bring you some cold water.
No, I'm fine.
It's just that I saw Officer Han briefly
yesterday after work.
I hope it's nothing serious.
Officer Yang!
What's going on? Where's Officer Han?
He finished surgery and
they've put him in intensive care.
-He's not conscious yet.
-Is he seriously injured?
I don't know. The surgery went well.
But, he lost a lot of blood.
They need to watch him for a couple days.
What...
Just what was this about?
I just don't know.
Someone found him passed out bleeding
in a parking lot and called it in.
It looked like a mugging because his
phone and wallet were missing.
This guy was really prepared.
All the CCTV was gone too.
You're very startled, aren't you?
My heart is still thumping too.
Have you called his mother?
No, I didn't want to worry her,
so I called his older sister.
She should be here soon.
You did well. You did well.
Na Bong-sun, are you sleeping?
No, I'm not.
Sleep well.
Okay, you sleep well too, Chef.
Honestly, I don't know if I'll be able to.
Make sure to get a good night's rest
so that you're not tired tomorrow.
Okay.
Make sure to pull that blanket over
you properly.
If you don't cover your stomach,
you'll get a stomach ache.
Okay.
Dream of me in your sleep.
That's not an order. It's a suggestion.
I will, Chef.
-What are you doing?
-Oh my!
Oh, nothing. Just...
You're wondering what Chef's up to
after confessing his feelings to you?
You saw the whole thing?
Of course, I did.
It was me who made that happen
by laying the groundwork.
He just suddenly came at you.
I got annoyed and came out.
What's it like?
Getting a confession from the guy
you've been in a one-sided love with?
Huh?
It's nice, isn't it?
Yes.
But, I just can't believe it.
I keep wondering if it's a dream.
And I worry that it's not a dream too.
At least if it's a dream,
I can wake up and won't get hurt.
Gosh, why do you overthink things so much?
The obstacle is right in front
of you, Na Bong-sun.
Now is the time to overcome it.
I will resolve my grudge and
you make Mr. Kang your man.
Win-win.
-Win-win...
-Yeah.
We each need to advance toward our
own goals, okay?
Okay.
Trust me and follow me. We can do it.
What an awesome morning it is.
Chef's heart is already mine.
The real game will start today.
Should I start planning for the big event?
Oh, you're awake.
Yes, Chef. Did you sleep well?
Well, I...
Yeah, I slept very well.
Did you think I'd be all excited and
not be able to fall asleep?
You think I've been dating
for one or two days?
How tacky would that be?
Oh dear.
Your eyes look puffy.
My eyes?
-Did you not sleep?
-No, no I did.
Why don't you believe me?
Why are you laughing? Am I funny?
No, it's because I'm happy.
Don't be so happy like that. Okay?
You could get hurt.
By the way...
And I'm saying this for your own good,
don't be so obvious
in front of the others.
Of course. I do have control.
See you later.
Bye.
Hey, hey. hey.
What's Bong up to again, huh?
She's been following Chef around all
morning like a dog who needs to poop.
I know.
She must need something from Chef again.
Is it about another advance?
She's going too far.
It's not like Chef's a bank.
-I told you not to be so obvious.
-When was I?
They've been looking at us all morning.
Oh really?
I was doing my best not to be obvious.
People are being too sensitive.
-Why are you doing...
-Chef!
-Huh?
-Yes?
How much papillote should we make?
Well, probably not too much.
Let's just do ten.
-Yes, Chef.
-Ten...
CHEF KANG
CHEF, WHAT ARE OUR PLANS FOR TODAY?
-Ji-woong.
-Yes, Chef.
What was I going to say?
-You know the potatoes we ordered yesterday?
-Yes.
I prepped them all and
put them in the fridge.
For today's special, we'll use oven-baked
potatoes with sour cream...
And...
WHAT?
How many reservations do we have today?
We have 15 groups in total.
One group called in to cancel.
Jun, can you see how many
live seafood we have?
-Yes, Chef.
-Let's get ready.
Oh, Chef! I'm here.
What is it? Do we have to have a
secret conversation?
Really?
You're doing this on purpose, aren't you?
To watch me suffer.
No, it's just that today's our first day.
So, of course I'm curious about what our
plans are tonight.
I suppose we can go out to eat dinner
as part of our lesson.
That's it?
What do you mean, "that's it"?
Hey, do you know how many people in
Itaewon want cooking lessons from me?
You're making money. You're very lucky.
Still, this isn't right.
It's our only first day.
We should do something special.
For example... I'll give you an example...
Maybe an overnight trip.
You know those romantic trips.
Go on a train, see the ocean, eat some
delicious food...
-And then...
-And then what?
And then after doing this and that,
if there's nothing left to do...
We can go into a motel and take a nap.
I'm sure you'll really take a nap.
You think I don't know about your dark
thoughts.
Overnight trip? You're so ridiculous.
What's wrong with an overnight trip?
Na Bong-sun, listen carefully.
Regardless of your issues,
I can't be so liberal
when it comes to relations between
men and women.
I'm very, how do I put this...
Careful and thoughtful about this.
What use is any of that when it comes
to relationships between men and women?
Whatever the case, if you want to date me,
you have to match my tempo.
Here.
-What is this?
-Wait five minutes and come down.
Don't be so obvious and follow me
right away.
Ah, seriously!
A man of vitality shouldn't have
any issues.
I just don't have the time for this!
What is this? What am I supposed to do?
Gosh, darn it!
He's the man of vitality.
Hey, hey! Don't run!
-I didn't come to catch you.
-You didn't?
I was curious to see how it was going.
Oh, really?
-Look.
-You didn't bring this, did you?
No.
Goodness...
-Slow down and eat.
-Okay.
-Oh, my! Oh!
-Gosh, darn it!
Gosh, seriously.
Who told you to go at it like an elephant
that's been starving for months?
The triangle kimbap must be peeled
slowly and carefully.
You're too hasty.
Once it's in the stomach,
it all gets mixed together anyhow.
Goodness!
You must've been really hungry.
Have you run out of rice at home?
Why that mouth of yours!
This is all your fault, you know.
By the way, are you getting further with
that guy or what?
-The man of vitality?
-You're curious, huh?
What happened is...
Oh my, oh my...
That tickles. How dare you, to your elder.
What are you doing? What's with you!
Don't whisper like that.
Just tell me from over there.
Oh, how strange.
That man of vitality and I
have decided to date now.
We even kissed yesterday.
-Really?
-Yeah.
You wench. You've got some skills.
You've even touched lips now.
It's almost done now.
That's what I think.
My grudge will be resolved very soon.
Hey, when you ran away last time...
Did you know that I was pretending
not to know?
I thought maybe that was the case.
So, you have to resolve your grudge
and quickly leave.
If the Spirit finds out, I may never get
my powers back at all because of you.
Don't you worry!
I'm going to use this opportunity to
ascend to heaven.
Please, I'd like to rely on you.
What? This woman again?
Why does she keep calling me?
Yes, hello?
Actually, I had a dream last night.
Dream? What dream?
You know my Sun-woo?
There was a field of dead flowers.
He was walking through the field and
I called him, but he didn't answer me.
-Dead field of flowers?
-Yes.
What could that mean?
Can you tell me the meaning?
It's not a bad dream.
A lively field of flowers represents
something wicked.
For example, something like a
female con-artist.
But, if it's a dead flower field...
He's avoiding that bad thing.
Yeah? Is that it?
That's a relief.
I was worried for no reason.
I'm glad I saw you today.
Do you want to eat something else?
-No, no.
-Should we drink?
-Ma'am, please bring us some drinks.
-Okay.
Oh, Officer Choi! You came.
I was just in the restroom.
You must be very tired.
Oh, I'm not too bad.
They say his surgery went fine.
But, he's just not waking up.
I'm just dying of worry.
I can't bear to tell our mother.
Oh, Jin-goo.
Jin-goo, are you awake?
I'm going to go find the doctor.
Officer Han.
Officer Choi.
Are you okay? This is the hospital.
Yes.
About that day...
Do you remember anything?
No.
I remember heading out there.
But, I don't remember anything after that.
It's a huge relief that you're okay.
Your sister went to find the doctor.
Goodness, look at this sweat.
-Good job today.
-Yes.
Hey, you guys...
Oh right, I'm meeting some band guys
from my elementary school. I forgot.
-What's wrong with me?
-Why?
It's been acting up all day.
Is it enteritis or what?
What are you going to do?
Then, we better get going.
We should all rest for tomorrow.
Tomorrow? Is something happening tomorrow?
I didn't say that. I'm just saying,
let's go home today.
Go, go, go. I'll be going.
-Dress up nice tomorrow.
-Okay.
I'll be going.
Goodbye!
What's with him?
What's going on tomorrow?
I don't know.
But, I suddenly don't want to come
into work tomorrow.
Let's worry about tomorrow when
the time comes. Bye.
-Bye.
-We have to go too.
I'll be going too.
-Okay.
-Bye.
CHEF KANG
(Get ready. I'll see you in 20 minutes.)
(Okay! I'll see you later!)
What's with the heart?
So immature, Na Bong.
Yeah, I don't need an overnight trip
to do it with him.
I'll just look for an opportunity and
make my move.
Okay, then...
Should I get myself ready?
A girl is all about mascara.
This is good. I'll make myself up today.
So, you're the last step.
He won't know, he won't.
He didn't know last time either.
About the air freshener.
Why isn't she coming out?
Na Bong, are you ready?
Coming.
Tada!
How do I look?
I tried to make myself look nice
for our first date.
Why did you go so overboard?
How tacky of you.
Oh, it's tacky of me?
Then, did you think you'd look trendy?
Let's go. I'm hungry.
What are we going to eat?
Is it something tasty?
Would we eat something yucky?
Isn't the skirt... Kind of short?
Short? This? No, it's not short at all.
It is short.
Let's just go.
He sure is complaining a lot.
Wow, what's the occasion?
Bringing me to a place like this.
You always took me to some
hole-in-the-wall kind of places.
It's quite popular among young people.
So, are we like checking out your rival's
business right now?
Why don't you lower your voice?
No need to advertise that we're spying.
Your food is ready.
-Oh my, wow!
-Thank you.
That's Hanwoo steak with ginseng sauce.
It's a healthy dish that uses all
natural ingredients.
-Yes, we know.
-Thank you.
-Please enjoy.
Here, eat.
Just like there are trends in fashion,
there are trends in food, as well.
Being able to follow that
is a skill for a chef too.
How is it?
It's very good.
-It's good?
-Yes.
It really is. You try some too.
-More than my cooking?
-Come on now.
I didn't say that now.
What's with your foot?
It must be because my legs are so long.
It keeps touching you, Chef.
My legs are so long.
Let's just focus on eating and
not on anything else.
When was I thinking about anything else?
I suppose you must think that I'm thinking
about that 24 hours a day.
Chef, you must think that.
-It isn't true.
-Go over there.
Okay.
Gosh.
I'm just putting your belt on for you.
We have to drive safely.
What? It's not like I don't have hands.
There's no need.
Let's go!
Okay, let's go.
-Oh, you got something on you.
-What are you doing?
I think there's a stain here.
-What the!
-Right there, there.
-Where are you going?
-What do you think you're touching?
Where are you going?
What did I do?
I was just trying to get dirt off you.
I mean I'm driving and your hand
is on me suddenly. It's dangerous!
-If you keep this up...
-I'll get in trouble?
I truly want to experience being
in trouble.
My goodness...
You know if I put my mind to it,
you'll be shocked.
That's what I'm saying.
Why don't you let me get shocked?
Where are you going anyways?
We should go home.
We have to work tomorrow.
No! No way.
Today is our first day. We can't do that.
Uh, Chef, do you want to go for
some red bean shaved ice?
I know this place well. Didn't you say
you like red bean shaved ice?
Shaved ice?
What is this? Where is this place?
We're almost there. It's close.
There's a red bean shaved ice place in a
remote area like this? Maybe we're lost?
We're not. It is this way.
All you have to do is follow me, Chef.
-This is right.
-How odd.
How can there be a shaved ice place
around here?
Gosh, seriously.
I thought there was one near here.
Where?
Na Bong-sun, you.
Yes? What about me? What did I do?
I guess motels sell shaved ice these days?
Oh yeah, this really is a motel.
I wonder what happened.
But, this works out well.
My legs were starting to hurt.
Chef, maybe we can go in and rest a bit?
-A bit?
-Yes, just for a bit.
Just one hour.
-Can we? Chef?
-You really are too much.
Why? Oh, I know.
I'll just hold your hand and
lie next to you. Hm?
-Chef... My legs hurt.
-Let's go somewhere and talk.
Yes, talk, talk. In there.
-Come with me now.
-Can we talk in there?
-My legs hurt.
-Hurry. Come with me.
-Wait, wait. Hold on a minute.
-Sit.
-Sit down.
-Gosh, what?
My goodness...
I just wanted to rest a little.
What are you doing over there?
If you're going to sit, sit here?
Why do you like me?
-What are you talking about now?
-Do you like me or my body?
-What?
-Am I really talking about this?
Why am I saying these words? Gosh.
-Huh?
-Don't the girls usually say these things?
Usually girls do say those things,
but I'm not a typical girl.
What?
Why are you thinking so much?
I like you and I like your body.
And since I like you, I want to do it.
Is it that weird for a healthy man
and woman to do it?
-Is it?
-That's not the point I'm trying to make.
Then what?
-I am...
-Yes?
-At least when it comes to relationships,
-Yes.
I'm conservative.
And I think that's the right way to be.
Conservative?
I mean, for the relationship to
make progress
shouldn't we share our feelings
and go through the stages?
This is...
Is it right to meet someone and
immediately go all the way?
-Oh my.
-Like as if you were that liberal.
It's not about being liberal.
It's because I like you, Chef.
If you like me, then shouldn't
you be more prudent?
Am I some instant food?
I'm saying...
You should control your feelings better.
-And can we not do this?
-So frustrating.
For a woman, you have some bad habits.
What about being a woman? What?
A woman can't be like this?
Is there a law against it?
You're so ridiculous.
Your way of thinking is so outdated.
And if a woman tries this much, you
could at least try to go along with it.
I'm acting like this for a reason.
-Reason? What reason?
-Forget it!
-Never mind. Forget everything.
-Seriously.
You're the one who got all turned on
and kissed me in the kitchen!
You need to go through the stages?
Oh, okay, you need to go through
the stages? What should we do?
Should I be this far from you?
Is this enough?
-Is it acceptable?
-That's not what I mean.
-Why?
-Are you trying to be difficult?
No way. I'm just being obedient.
Why? Being obedient is a
problem for you now?
Then what do you want me to do?
Are you saying I should go or stay?
What are you telling me to do?
If you need time, every minute...
No, every ten minutes?
I can take a step like this?
Just tell me. A step every ten minutes?
Excuse me, Chef.
Did you just cover your ears?
Am I too loud for you?
-I guess mother-in-law is late.
-Yeah, she's at a meeting.
So Officer Han is okay?
We don't need to worry anymore?
Yes, I talked to him before.
He started eating.
He'll get discharged soon.
That's a relief.
What about the culprit? Any evidence?
Well, there are too many of these
crimes and culprits.
The world is a scary place.
I guess they are not even afraid.
The heavens will punish them
one of these days.
Oh my. Did you hurt yourself?
Oh, sorry.
I got annoyed for a moment.
It must have stung a lot.
Should I put some cream on it?
No, no, it's okay.
Let's finish drinking wine and
go for a walk. It's nice out.
It was nice to meet my school friends
before.
It reminded me of my college days.
Oh yeah? You were reminiscing, huh?
Yeah.
I didn't realize it then,
but I think those days were good times.
I didn't really have any worries.
Anyways, I noticed you don't really talk
about yourself much.
Your college days or your childhood days.
How was the orphanage?
I think there are many cases of kids
getting adopted.
Not me.
Not even once.
I'm back.
Mother, I need your signature stamp
on my report card.
Just do it yourself.
Oh, he's smiling. Oh my God.
He must recognize us.
Of course he knows.
We are his mom and dad. Right?
Oh my.
Where were you all this time?
Making us feel worried.
What do you think you're doing?
You evil punk.
You little punk. Go. Get out.
Get out! Get out of here!
Three years ago...
If I hadn't met you...
And I lost the will to live again...
What would've happened?
I probably wouldn't be here now, right?
Probably.
Please let me go.
Just let me die.
You told me then.
It's not up to us to decide whether
we live or die.
What did you mean by that?
Did you say it to provoke me?
Did I? I don't remember.
In any case, it was refreshing.
Since that day, I kept thinking about you.
I see...
Will this distance satisfy your
requirements?
Come on.
I assume this will do.
I shall now depart, sire.
Conservative and prudent, Chef Kang.
Please take good care of your body,
Your Majesty.
And I bid you a good night.
I shall now leave you, sir .
-Good night.
-Hey.
Why is she going so overboard?
Do you know my true feelings?
I can do it.
Kang Sun-woo, you can do it.
You can endure it, you can.
Is his 'thing' a national treasure or
something? I don't have time for this.
He sure doesn't look that way?
Why is he so old fashioned?
If you make eye contact,
you just go for it.
This isn't the Joseon era, right?
But, he's not wrong you know.
What Chef's saying...
Do you really want to take his side,
at a time like this?
Even if you like the man?
But, that's one of his attractions.
At first, he seems like a light person,
but he isn't at all.
He's very serious and
he takes a lot of responsibility.
You think that's attractive?
You're wearing rose-tinted glasses.
You don't find Chef attractive?
Well, it's not that he's not attractive...
I just don't think it's polite to play
hard-to-get too much.
That's all I'm saying.
Especially to a woman he likes.
Gosh, we're almost all the way there.
We're stuck right there at that spot.
(Is it good, stalker?)
It's Chef!
He must've felt bad about it,
seeing as how he's out and about.
Hey, don't go out there.
-Huh?
-You need to hold back with him.
If you keep going like this,
it's going to take too long.
Endure it, even if you want to see him.
I'll just open the door a crack.
-I'll just take a peek at his face.
-No, no. Don't do it.
You're eating well.
Is it good?
Oh my gosh,
-What the heck? You guys.
-What is it? Something online?
-It's Min-soo's birthday today.
-Min-soo?
Sous Chef, Sous Chef!
Look, I got a message.
It's Huh Min-soo's birthday today.
-Oh my God!
-Oh no!
No wonder! That's why he was going
on and on yesterday about today.
-Gosh...
-What should we do?
Do we have to throw him a birthday party?
That won't be enough for him.
He'll totally be expecting a present.
An expensive one, at that!
Hey.
-Let's pretend we don't know.
-What?
Okay, okay. Sounds good.
We'll all pretend we don't know.
This is for the best.
We won't be able to handle him.
He's here.
Hi, Sous Chef.
-Hi, Sous Chef.
-Hello!
Good morning!
Hey, hey.
It's so hot outside.
People who give birth in hot weather
like this are pretty amazing.
As well as post-natal care, right?
Hey, is there any seaweed left?
Let's have seaweed soup for lunch.
I feel like having that today.
If I gave them these many hints,
they should know.
Maybe they're already preparing something.
What is this?
Oh, how lame. Don't tell me
it's a surprise party.
What's going on? What's happening?
Hey, hey! I already figured it all out.
Stop it already.
Stop it and turn on the lights!
Turn on the lights.
-The electricity went out.
-Tada!
-What's this?
-What will we do if the electricity
goes out suddenly like that?
-Right.
-Shouldn't we look into it?
It's probably because it's summertime.
I think it goes out like that when the
system overloads.
It'll be a problem for us if it goes out
for a long time.
-What would we do with our fridge?
-Yeah.
Right, our fridge.
So, this was an electricity outage?
-Yes.
-I see.
Hey, you guys. Are you going to stand
around all morning? Huh!
Did you come to play?
You're not going to work?
We're not late yet.
You are late.
You know what...
All of you, meeting outside.
Meeting!
Put up your hands... Right up...
Why did you put your hands up like
that by yourself?
-Are you going to raise it like that?
-No.
Dong-chul, aren't you going to clean
your nails? Huh?
Have you been farming somewhere?
Look at all that dirt.
This isn't dirt. This is cleaner
I got on my hands.
You better shut that mouth of yours. Okay?
And you, when are you cutting your hair?
Are you 'Old Boy' or something?
Are you a hedgehog?
And you...
You... Yeah, you...
Yes, you punk!
You're a chef, not a model!
Make yourself shorter right now!
Go and get a bad haircut or
get plastic surgery to get ugly.
Lower your eyes!
Just looking at you annoys me, Bong!
We can't last the day, right?
I don't think I can.
He's like a rabid dog, totally crazy.
This is a pain. Can't we just toss him
something and say it's a gift?
Yeah, I suppose.
I ordered a pair of jeans online and
they came this morning.
They gave me a free belt
as a special gift.
Can't we just give him that?
-Look what we have.
-Wow, look.
You guys didn't have to.
Thank you.
Birthday beats.
Here you go.
Hey, it's not like I'm the only one
with a birthday.
We put our thought into it.
Oh, I just hate doing stuff like this
at work.
But, since you guys put so much thought
into it...
I should, at least, look at the present.
-Oh, it looks expensive.
-It smells like leather.
It looks really nice.
Is this an expensive brand?
This...
Is this fake?
What?
Just kidding!
-Gosh.
-Hey, this...
It's obviously leather!
-What's this made out of?
-Gosh...
It's cowhide.
Isn't this really expensive?
Maybe you guys spent too much.
Sous Chef, don't be like that.
You've been so good to us all this time.
-If you say that, we'll be upset.
-That's right.
We'll get really mad. We will.
Sorry. I'm sorry about before.
Okay, then...
Drinks on me after work, everyone.
-Okay, okay.
-I'm in!
What is it?
It's your birthday, Min-soo?
Yes, I'm embarrassed, but it is.
In this hot weather...
your mother must have suffered a lot.
Oh, then here. I don't have anything else.
-Treat everyone with this today...
-Oh no, Chef!
Well, how much?
Who asks that? Just use however much
you see fit.
-300,000 won?
-We have to go for second round too.
400,000 won?
Sure, go ahead.
I'm in! Yeah!
Can't you do the grocery shopping all
at once, Dad?
Why do you do little by little?
It's such a pain.
You have to do it daily
so that it's fresh.
You're a young man.
How hard could it be to hold that?
That's not the problem, Dad.
I have an image to uphold in society too.
If I walk around carrying green onions,
what would neighborhood people think?
This is why Na Bong-sun looks down
on me too.
Be quiet, kid.
Your sister went walking daily
to buy groceries
in the morning and evening.
She was the type to create work for
herself.
Wait for me, Dad.
I'm here.
Here's an apple that you like.
Eat lots.
How can a dead person eat?
What a waste.
That bad man.
Why did you do it?
You bad man.
Mister!
-Oh, Officer Choi.
-Hello.
What are you doing here?
I'm on my way home after buying groceries.
I'll drive you back. Please, get in.
Oh no, I can just walk back.
I'm headed there myself and you have bags.
Kyung-mo, the car's over there.
Let's go with him, Dad.
It's rude to refuse too much.
Thank you, Officer Choi.
-Goodness.
-Here, give it to me.
-I feel bad.
-It's no problem at all.
-Get in the car.
-Okay.
What is it?
You tie your shoelaces in a unique manner.
I tie my shoelaces like this.
If you tie it like this,
it doesn't come undone.
Mister, your shoelaces are tied
in a strange way.
Oh, this? You know Bong-sun from
the restaurant?
She tied it for me.
-Bong-sun?
-Yeah.
She said I could get hurt if it came
undone and tied it so tight.
She's a very bright young lady.
Ah, I see.
-Are you going to the party?
-Yes.
It would be nice if you came, Eun-hee.
It would nice to have a pretty woman
there.
All we have there is...
You're not my type either, Sous Chef.
(Thank goodness for that)
Please go and have fun for me,
on my behalf.
-Yes.
-You're headed out now?
-Yes, Chef.
Chef, you're not going?
If you don't have plans,
you should come too.
Me?
I'm sure he wouldn't come.
Our chef is a very conservative person.
We should just go on our own and have fun.
Yeah, you guys should just go.
That way, once the food runs out,
you can badmouth me.
Hey, what are you talking about Chef?
We'll be going now.
Chef, we're going now.
-Have fun.
-Thank you.
Okay,
in celebration of the birth
of our sous chef!
- Bravo!
This chicken is so good.
I'm going to eat a lot today.
Eat as much as you want.
It's on Kang Sun-woo's card.
What's the worry?
We'll never get to use his card again.
I'll use this card to make donations too.
Donate to me first. Order one more
chicken for each of us.
That's so cheap of you.
One chicken per person?
Ten chickens per person!
Ten chickens, it is!
Ma'am, more chicken please!
And beer please!
You know, I...
A mystic wet fog was formed.
-Another beer please!
-Aren't you listening to me?
Gosh...
-Okay, a mystic wet fog...
-You need to listen to this guy.
-Listen to me.
-I am listening.
A mystic wet fog was formed, okay?
There was a crane, a crane there
holding its leg up.
That was my mom's dream when she
was pregnant with me. A crane...
Crane, crane, crane.
Oh, it's a crane. A crane has appeared.
Here, crane. Eat this.
You can eat this too.
This is why he abuses people all the time.
(homonym for 'crane')
Hey now, Sous Chef was talking about
his cranes now.
Sous Chef,
this is his bad habit every
time he gets drunk.
Where's Bong-sun? Bong-sun's gone.
-Bong-sun?
-Crane, Bong-sun's gone.
Hello?
Do you not hear me?
Turn on the light.
Bong, what are you doing here?
Oh, Jun. Hi.
-Are you drunk?
-Why are you wearing that?
Oh, this... This thing?
My head was hurting, but this squeezed it.
It made it feel better. I like this thing.
This is so like you.
-Come here. Sit down.
-What?
-Oh, there was a chair.
-Sit here.
Jun, you're a guy
so you must know how men think and feel.
I suppose, why?
The thing is, listen carefully...
I have this friend, right?
My friend has this boyfriend, right?
My friend is a very liberal person,
so she just attacked him.
But, this boyfriend of hers is
totally rejecting her.
And he refuses to do it, that punk.
So, the thing that I'm curious about...
Do guys usually dislike it
when girls
suddenly come on too strong like that?
Do they?
Let's see... is your friend not so pretty?
It's not that she's not pretty.
But, she's not so pretty either,
in my opinion.
It's one of two things.
He doesn't want to because she's
not pretty.
Or he likes her so much that he's waiting
until there's more trust
in the relationship.
If it's the former,
he's just an ordinary guy.
If it's the latter,
he's a pretty good guy.
I just don't know.
This is really confusing!
Is it the former or the latter?
I don't know for certain.
I think it's the latter.
-You're sort of pretty.
-Gosh...
It's not about me. It's my friend...
It's my close friend.
Then, tell that friend to smarten up.
She'll regret it if she loses him.
By the way, you don't hold my hand
these days at all.
You must be cured of your
"lack of affection".
Oh, I'm not all cured yet.
Not yet... Gosh, I'm so confused!
HOW TO MAKE CABBAGE PORRIDGE
I wonder if she's busy.
There are no updates.
This is the only blog worth reading.
What's with everyone anyways?
They should keep things under control.
Aren't they coming into work tomorrow?
Gosh, they sure had a lot to drink.
They're going all out, aren't they?
-Let's go!
-Go, Dong-chul!
What are you two doing?
Stop!
Gosh, now.
This is enough, isn't it?
She should be home.
What's she doing with a bunch of guys?
Pal Pal Karaoke Room.
Now, they're digesting their food.
What's with her?
Does she want to be out with those guys
without me?
Huh?
Does she even think at all or what?
She's crazy. She really is.
It's two in the morning already.
What are they doing?
She's not doing this on purpose, is she?
To get revenge on me.
If she is, well...
Well, that is truly childish.
YONGSAN MOTEL
Motel?
Wait, Na Bong-sun? She really is crazy!
She's lost her mind!
Hey, Na Bong. Why are you doing this?
Have you gone nuts?
You're not picking up? You're not?
Min-soo, pick up. Pick up, you punk!
(-Hello, who is this?)
-Hey, Min-soo.
Where are you?
(I think it's a motel. Everyone's drunk.)
Is Na Bong-sun there too? Na Bong-sun?
(-Bong-sun?)
-Yeah.
(I think she's washing up.)
What? Washing up? Okay...
What's the room number?
Oh, gosh.
They even left the door unlocked.
Hey.
What's the problem?
Hey, Bong. Wake up.
-Oh, who's this?
-Wake up.
Chef, where have you been?
Be quiet.
-My goodness.
-It stinks.
Chef.
Be quiet.
Quiet.
This won't do.
Where are we going?
-Be very quiet.
-Okay.
He's so dirty.
Why doesn't he take his pants off
if he's sleeping?
Kang Sun-woo!
Gosh, he startled me.
-Ouch.
-Chef.
Not today!
Let's go home.
-Chef, one shot! Let's go.
-Pull yourself together.
Chef! Oh, Chef is here!
Chef, let's go for another drink.
-One shot!
-What do you mean, one shot?
-Stand up straight.
-Yes, straight!
-This isn't working.
-Uh, how strange...
The sky is spinning, Chef.
Drink more.
More, more.
-More.
-I'm so full.
-I can't anymore.
-You need to sober up.
Look at me now.
-Are you a bit sober now?
-Yes, it seems that way.
Gosh, really.
What were you thinking?
What kind of girl would fearlessly go into
a motel room with a bunch of guys?
Oh yes.
Unlike you, conservative Chef...
To a wild girl like me,
motels are like my home.
-Stop twisting things around.
-What's wrong with a motel?
It's just a room that's good for resting.
And if you were that worried,
you should've come along back then.
You're the one who told me not to.
You said something about being a
"conservative chef"...
This is the problem with me.
Do you think that really means I don't
want you to come?
If you're so smart,
why can't you figure out the meaning?
And why are you overreacting so much?
Those guys don't even see me as a woman.
Why aren't you a woman?
You're so much a woman,
it worries me to death.
Oh my.
You just don't know what men are
really like.
Men can change in an instant.
If you're careless, you can be in trouble.
Do you understand?
I would like for that trouble to happen.
Why you...
You know what? This won't do.
From now on, you stay right by my side.
Don't leave even for a moment.
I'm so nervous. I'm going to stick you
to me like a piece of gum.
When was it that you were telling me to
stay away from you?
Why do you keep going back and forth
like that?
I take back what I said earlier.
From now on,
you stick to me no matter what.
Okay.
I'm sticking to you.
Stick on you like this? Like gum?
I like this.
You told me to stay stuck on you, okay?
Come stick closer. More.
Yes, Chef.
-Chef, I'm curious about something...
-What?
Is it that you don't want to do it,
or are you just holding it in?
No comment.
Why no comment? I'm really curious.
Hm? Hm?
Well, what do you think...
Am I not a man?
What kind of question is that?
Why? Why aren't you walking?
Let's start like this.
And go slowly...
For a long, long time, Na Bong-sun.
OH MY GHOST
(I like Chef. A lot.)
(I think it's all thanks to you.)
This makes me feel strange.
(Do you know what is the most dangerous
to a ghost like you?)
Because I'm happy.
It's feelings.
That's what makes you get greedy.
Hey, can't you do it properly?
I'm sorry, Chef.
Of course, I can do it
with my eyes closed.
Why don't you hire someone?
Instead of suffering through it.
(Why are so many people curious about
Bong-sun these days?)
(Let's go on a trip.)
(I now want to go with you.
On an overnight trip.)