=Inherently Kind=
=Episode 7=
(Who Am I?)
After all these years,
I did not know her well.
It looks like
she really likes jewelry.
(Happy birthday.)
(Thank you.)
But why did she act so indifferent
at the birthday banquet?
This does not look like real jade.
(Yacang Tea House)
Yacang Tea House?
You're always
fiddling with your jewelry.
And you don't care about the family?
Mom.
Why are you so angry?
Just tell me what you want.
Our family doesn't support
useless people.
Today, you get this closet cleaned.
And clean all the jewelry.
Sure.
I was also planning to tidy up here.
At least you know your place!
Stay and supervise her!
No food until everything is clean!
Madam Gu.
You are so slow.
Do you even know how to do this?
If not this way, then how?
You have to...
How could you break
such an expensive jade?
You set me up on purpose!
We are even now, aren't we?
What do you mean?
You were the one who pushed me
last night, weren't you?
The scent on you
is exactly the same as hers.
Was last lesson not enough for you?
Madam Gu.
I...
I did not mean to.
You can continue working for him.
Or...
Be smarter.
Miss Gu,
for a counterfeit like this,
is it worth your time
coming here in person?
Didn't you sell
the genuine piece to me six months ago?
What do you mean now?
To be honest,
I had a car accident some time ago.
And I have forgotten many things.
I can't remember
any of the jewelry before,
so I wonder
if you could send me
our transaction records
for me to take a look.
Sure, I will send them to you.
From last December to this May,
(Jewelry List, Earrings and Necklaces)
you sold seven pieces of jewelry to me.
They are all here.
(Just as I thought.)
(This matches Gu Qingmei's diary.)
(Madam Gu, please have mercy on me!)
(These are all fakes!)
(They are worthless!)
(How do you know?)
(Last month, I overheard you)
(arguing with He Jinchuan by the pool.)
(You said)
(you were going to sell all the jewelry)
(and you still hadn't raised
the 30 million for him.)
(You were worried that people would
find out about the counterfeits.)
(He Jinchuan?)
(You mean)
(I sold all the jewelry)
(and gave the money to He Jinchuan?)
(Yes.)
(It was about some investment project.)
(Gu Qingmei, you fool!)
(All that money)
(was swindled by Jinchuan!)
(Transaction Date)
(Two pieces sold on May 20th.)
These two auction pieces,
you bought them on that same day?
Yes.
Right after the auction,
you rushed to close the deal
and demanded cash payment.
(I was already in hospital that time.)
(After Gu Qingmei sold the jewelry,)
(where did she go?)
Miss Gu,
are you okay?
I'm fine.
I just confirmed something.
Mrs. He.
I am so sorry.
The camera for the charity auction night
all malfunctioned.
So...
All the data was lost.
What a coincidence!
The footage on that day was lost.
Was it deleted on purpose?
Well...
So much time has passed.
As for that,
we really cannot confirm.
(Who was behind this?)
(Why did I become a substitute for her?)
(And who am I?)
(Mrs. He,)
(have trouble finding your seat?)
(Mrs. He?)
(Yes.)
Mrs. He?
We meet again.
You did a great job at the last banquet.
Not at all.
I am very happy to serve you.
Why do I get the feeling
that you seem afraid of me?
Was I not polite last time?
No, no.
You were a little strange last time.
Strange?
What's so strange about me?
The first time you came in,
you looked worried.
Then when you came in again,
you were all smiles.
I thought your emotional control
was quite impressive.
The second time...
I came in twice?
Yes.
Do you not remember?
Stop right there!
Why are you running?
I am sorry.
I should not have slandered
Meiyan International.
The information in the USB drive
was fake.
I made it all up.
USB drive?
Why would you make up that information?
I was forced to.
I worked in quality control
at Meiyan International for ten years.
Then I was suddenly fired last year.
I never received any compensation.
I was just pissed,
so I wanted to find something
to use against them.
Since it is fabricated,
then why did you give it to me?
I posted complaints
about Meiyan International online
and got to know
a journalist named Su Su.
I was planning to cause a scene
at the auction.
But then I was hunted.
I was also scared,
so I gave you the USB drive.
Who knew you'd turn out to be Mrs. He?
The one behind Meiyan International
turned out to be your husband.
(The one behind Meiyan International)
(turns out to be He Jinchen.)
Mrs. He, I was wrong!
Please forgive me!
Give me a chance!
I lost the USB drive last time.
I need another copy.
The USB drive...
Alright.
The USB drive is on my computer.
I will take you to get it.
Lead the way.
Continue searching for Gu Qingmei.
Bring her back alive,
or bring me a body.
Boss.
what about the one in the He family?
Leave her as Miss Gu for now.
Our source said
she went to see Tian Gang again.
But we don't know
whether she had the USB drive.
Tian Gang.
Go and take care of him!
As for that woman,
leave her alive.
I want her to be Gu Qingmei for now.
What are you looking at?
(These two car accidents)
(appear to be no accidents.)
(What's the secret)
(in that USB drive)
(that keeps them coming after me?)
I have handled him.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
By the way,
did you offend someone?
Why are people always after you?
I was just about to say.
Whenever something happens to me,
you are always there.
Did you arrange these rescues
to play the hero?
You are injured!
Are you not injured too?
Qingmei!
Come with me!
Didn't you see she is injured?
My wife
does not need your concern, Mr. Mu.
Aren't we going home?
Let's go.
Hello.
Check that car
and see if it has any connection
to the previous one.
Recently,
you have been getting a little close
to Mu Shaoze.
We are just business partners.
Business partners?
Do you need to be that close?
He was injured saving me.
What's wrong with me checking on him?
Besides,
I almost lost my life.
As my husband,
did you even care about me once?
Aren't you safe now?
If something really happened...
So I have to actually be in trouble
before you come mourn me?
Or are you unhappy that I did not die?
Why are you so sharp-tongued now?
You used to be so gentle and kind.
Kind?
If swallowing your pride
and never talking back is being kind,
then I have had enough!
I just wanted to remind you
not to get too close.
Are you jealous?
Mu Shaoze
is Jinxi's fiancé.
You'd better know your place!
Why?
Afraid I might cheat on you?
He is not that simple.
Maybe he is only getting close to you
because he's after Gu Corporation.
And what about you?
You're not interested in
Gu Corporation at all?
We're married.
Of course I'm on your side.
Sure.
Then I'll be counting on you, dear.
♪Time stole the proof of our love♪
♪Hidden in the moonlight,
lost in the clouds♪
♪Tangled glances and love fall together♪
♪Into a spiral of thoughts,
memories rewinding♪
♪Feelings both strange and familiar♪
♪I just know you're
where my heart belongs♪
♪Can't remember
when this flutter started♪
♪Or how it's supposed to end♪
♪Goodbye to the world rushing in♪
♪Let me hide in your eyes
and never leave♪
♪Feel the rhythm of your heartbeat♪
♪Every tomorrow seems worth the wait♪
♪Let me fill the emptiness of a century♪
♪As the wind brushes past your hem♪
♪All my hidden feelings come undone♪
♪Right as I confess my love♪