[Bright Time]
[Uncle forever.]
[Episode 20]
Hehe
Hahaha
Oh...
You're warming up, huh
Let me add some firewood
Hahaha
Hey
Isn't this laughing louder?
Hahaha
Hey
Oh no
Quite warm
Well
Xu Chao and Ruosi
have diarrhea
So I'm volunteered
to cover their shift
I can't leave you alone
Right?
The weather is really nice today
With moonlit and starry
It's quite foggy
Rarely such good weather
How about I sing a song for you?
I'll just sing that...
I won't listen
That works too
It's okay if you don't wanna listen
That's strange for singing at night
How about I tell you
a ghost story?
It must be coming from my stomach
I must have an upset stomach
It must be me...
Shut up
I need to go to the bathroom
How did you get in?
Hey
Why are you here?
If you keep talking, go stand outside
Just as I thought
You can't just leave me alone
It's so dark here
Cellphone
Flashlight
No
Isn't it more obvious like this?
It's fine
Convenience store, huh
Be quick
That's right
Just take this
Don't hide, I see both of you
Let's go, we still have time
Instant noodles, ham sausage
What?
Let's go
And instant noodles, ham sausage
What's wrong with you?
Lan Jinghui
Xiaohui
What about the instant noodles and ham sausage?
Forget it, let's just go for it
Stop
Which class are you from?
Don't run
You...
It's fine now
Pretty fast, huh
You...
You're pretty fast too
Of course
Where did you go?
Why so much nonsense?
Hurry up and eat
Are you gonna eat or not?
Or I'll throw it into the fire
I'll eat
They made up
Who's there?
Xiaohua
Instructor Wu
What are you doing here so late?
I'm on night duty, Instructor Wu
Alright
It's getting late
Go back and rest
Thank you, Instructor Wu
Wait
Contraband
Don't litter after eating
Okay
Thank you, Instructor Wu
She runs so fast
Thank you just now
Why are you thanking me?
Anyway, no matter what I do,
at most it proves
that I'm not a bad person
You're still angry
Why am I angry?
I'm just someone who does things for money
I was wrong
Actually, at first,
when I found out about this,
I was furious
You are my best friend
I just wanted to know
And I just need an answer
from you
An answer
I admit
that initially
it was because of your father
that I agreed to supervise you
Otherwise,
you were so arrogant
and annoying
at first
you always caused troubles
And you still wanted me
to approach you from the beginning,
to actively help you
Was I really that annoying?
Indeed
You were quite annoying
But,
as I gradually got to know you,
and understood you,
I realized what it means
to have a friend
You know what? Lan Jinghui
Although sometimes
you don't seem reliable
Sometimes you're quite foolish
You're always wholehearted
to friends
Whether it's Xiaohua, Ma Yiming,
or me,
you're always there for us
I used to be alone all the time
You slowly changed me
Well, as for you
either you don't speak,
or when you do,
it's always cheesy
Actually, I have had a question all along
I wanted to ask you something
What?
Why did you do that?
Earlier in the changing room
I'm just afraid of the dark
I'm afraid of the dark
Okay
Not just afraid of the dark
Maybe
I'm also afraid of enclosed spaces
I'm also afraid of the time
when a beam of light suddenly shines on me
Afraid of light?
When I was little,
my parents got divorced
At that time,
my mom insisted on taking me abroad
But I didn't wanna go
So, I made a pact with a friend
who I used to play with a lot back then
We agreed to hide together
until my mom left
So, does that mean
we'll never see each other again?
I don't wanna go
What if your mom insists on taking you?
What would you do?
I can hide
Hide?
Where?
But then, he betrayed me
He told all my little secrets
to the adults
So, you have to keep my secret
You can't tell anyone else
Let's pinky promise
Looking back, it was childish
I just
hid myself in an abandoned warehouse
behind the kindergarten
with no light
no food
no water
All I can remember is that...
I heard footsteps all around
Countless flashlights were shining in
And then?
And then, they found me
Then they took me back
Maybe...
subconsciously, it's been trying to tell me
to stay there
So, I'm still afraid
of enclosed spaces
and bright lights
Do you still remember that kid
who betrayed you back then?
I don't remember
I was too young, I forgot
And besides,
people like him
It's better not to remember
Maybe he didn't mean it that way
What?
Nothing
Wait
I've told you everything
No, it's not right
No, no
You have to tell me a secret
Now, right now, immediately
I I don't have any secrets
I don't believe it
Your expression doesn't look like
one without any secrets
There really isn't any
Did my dad already tell you
that you're not my uncle
Yes, I am
Do you know who he is?
Who is he?
He is...
He is your uncle
Uncle?
Go out
Get out
Ling Dong, what I just told you
Is it okay or not?
Mr. Lan
We are not related, right?
And also, the director said
that my sponsor is coming to see me
It must be you, right?
Can I ask
why sponsored me?
Well...
It's just...
This is a long story
Ling Dong, sit down and talk
Come here
Come here and have a seat
Actually
You and Uncle Lan
You don't have any relationship at all
But...
Uncle Lan and I
and Old Ling,
who's your dad
We three
have been friends for over ten years
With with my dad?
I won't go into details
Xiaoling
You know your mom quite well
She is quite strong-willed
She actually didn't wanna
accept our sponsorship
So, this matter
hasn't been told to you all along
I was afraid you would feel burdened
I came to find you
I just wanna...
Uncle Lan just wanna ask you...
to help Lan Jinghui more in his study
And of course,
as long as it doesn't affect
your studies
Indeed, Lan Jinghui is really
not doing well now
But actually,
he used to be a good kid
Why did he become like this now?
His mom and I
We really have a big responsibility
And now, it's a coincidence
You transferred here
You two are classmates now
and also desk mates
So I just
want you to help him more
in your free time
And besides
You have a different status now
As the uncle
Yes, you're his uncle
You can fully utilize this identity
When he doesn't listen to you
just let me know
Right?
He has to listen to you
If you can
help Lan Jinghui with his studies
Uncle Lan will feel relieved
He's kind
This counts as a promise
Look, what a good child
Thank you
Keep it up
What's wrong?
Ling Dong
You're too much...
Too much
Why didn't you tell me?
You...
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
It's nothing, my leg is numb
I'm fine, really
Are you silly?
Numb?
Still numb?
No, it's okay
Much better now
Nice view, huh
With a clear moon and few stars
Lan Jinghui
I've said it
I wanna be your uncle for life
I mean it
You wanna take advantage of me for life, huh
Dream on
Shouldn't it be the other way around?
You're annoying
You're pressing on me
Get off
No
The last time
Get off
Cheer up
Haven't you eaten?
Stay safe
I'm fine
Are you okay?
No one left behind
Left
Right
Left, right
Pay attention to arm swinging
No, wait
I think we should not move the arm
that much
Because if it's too big
it will affect the balance
and the speed
No...
Her body
is still a bit uncoordinated
She needs to swing her arms widely
to keep up with her pace
Right?
You have to do it like this
No, no, no
He's wrong
Listen to me
No, wait
You can't listen to him
You have to listen to me
You have to get used to your body
and follow your own feeling
No, why do you think
what you said
is more mature than mine?
I never felt
that my theory is more mature than yours
I just follow my heart
Follow your heart
You still have a heart?
Let's go
But I think, you know
you still need to approach it
rationally
You know what?
You can't just follow your heart
Humans are all emotional
Come on
Get ready
Go for it
Come on
Go for it, Ruosi
Are you ready?
Be careful, everyone
Come on
This time, our team
will definitely come in first
We will definitely win
Because he doesn't wanna lose
We'll win
You...
You
We will definitely win
Class 5
Pay attention to the techniques
during training
Stay safe
Get ready
Three
Two
One
Come on
One, two
Are they hurt?
I'll go check
Is everything alright?
Let them handle it themselves
They're used to being pampered
Let them suffer
They need to toughen up
On this matter,
I fully agree with Ms. Fang
How are you feeling?
Can you still go on?
My foot twisted
Can you still run?
Yes, of course
But...
Qingtian, we got first place
We were so close to winning
I promised you
that I would help you get first place
It's okay, Qingtian
Now,
I quite like second place too
We were just a little bit short
Just a little bit
Just a little bit and we would have won
We've practiced for so long
One, two
Come on
Slow down
One
Almost there
Come on
Come on, Xiaohua
One, two
Come on
Come on, Xiaohua
Two
Be careful
One, two
It's okay
Take it slow
One, two
Come on
Be careful
You guys are the best
Great job
It's my fault
We practiced for nothing
How can that be your fault?
As long as we cross the finish line,
it's a victory, right?
And look at him
who'd always get first place
He didn't say anything, right?
Isn't it the first place?
It's just a different kind of it
Actually, for me,
it's quite interesting
Listen
Our team is just too strong
We should give other teams a chance, right?
Brother Hui
Thank you
You're just picking up the leftovers
Qingtian
There's a bonfire party later
Let's go make a fire together
No, I'm not in the mood
You're still upset about
losing the race
I promised you first place
It's okay
Qingtian
Look
Where did you get this?
I just passed by the kitchen
Oh my god...
I didn't realize
you look so honest
Actually,
it was given by Auntie
But this is raw
So I asked you
to start the fire
Then I'll eat roasted sweet potatoes
Let's go
Come on
Run
Hurry
Be quick and nimble
Ma Yiming, hurry up
Be quick
Hurry up, be fast
Okay
Now let me tell you
the rules of the game
This's called "King's Game"
If you get the King card
you'll be very powerful
You can randomly designate
a combination of numbers
The King can specify
what this combination does
If this combination
cannot be completed
then you'll be punished with black garlic juice
So now...
Who got the King card?
Me
Brother Hui
Okay, then I choose...
10 of diamonds
and 8 of spades
I am 8 of spades
Who is 10 of diamonds?
Where is 10 of diamonds?
Who is it?
10 of diamonds
Who is 10 of diamonds?
Well...
This is just...
A duet of love songs
Sing
I accept the punishment
No, no, no
I cheated, let me do it
Did you go too far with this game?
Is it really that bad?
Well...
Come on, let's continue
Let's collect these cards first
Come on
Go back to our positions
Collect the cards
Come on
Come on, card please
Alright
Brother Hui
This black garlic juice
really tastes terrible
Who came up with such a punishment?
Luckily it's not Sister Meng drinking it
Sister Meng
Who allowed you to do this?
You deserve it
Sister Meng
Okay
So, in this round
who is the King?
It's me
Choose the number you wanna say
Jack of hearts
Carry her on your back
Run around our field
for a lap
Ma Yiming
Come on
Who is the new king this round?
Me
Quite active
Then, King
choose the numbers you wanna say
I choose the two of spades and...
The eight of spades
What do you want them to do?
I want them to hug
Embrace tightly
Okay, number 8
Step forward
Okay
Ling Dong
Okay, now the eight of spades
has already entered the field
Now, please welcome the two of spades
Two of spades
Is that a girl?
This is too exciting
Who is it?
Embrace in public
That's so awkward
Yeah
Two of spades
If you don't show up soon
I'll fold all my cards
Three
Two
It's me
Hug
Congratulations
I can't breathe
I can't even catch my breath
Here's a big one
Auntie, I want two ice creams
Two
Auntie
Auntie, I want six
Six
Yes, six
Thank you, Auntie
Auntie
I want that one
I want three ice creams
Three
Only two left
Two is fine
It's okay
Have a drumstick
You don't want vegetables
Here
What is it?
Why are there only two?
Where's yours?
I already ate it
I feel like I'm coming back to life
Is it delicious?
Take a bite
Once cold and once hot
Be careful of getting diarrhea