[Bright Time]
[Algo for passion]
[Episode 13]
Director
Come in
As for the basketball team members
who failed three subjects
can't play in the game
I'd like to ask for
another chance for them
Give us another chance, please
What's the reason?
The whole grade is the same
Are you that special?
I can vouch for them
Ling Dong, let me remind you
You'd better not
get involved in this
Director
As Lan Jinghui's uncle,
and also
the leader of the study group
I should be responsible
for his academic performance
So I guarantee
that in the final exam
Lan Jinghui's ranking
can improve by 100 places
Please give him a chance
100? Are you crazy?
I have confidence in you
That's right, 100 places
Lan Jinghui, do you know
that in our school, we're pretty much
in the intense competition
With your current grades
It's almost an impossible task
Director
Please give me this chance
I can do it
Ling Dong, can he do it?
Of course
It seems that in your basketball team
apart from Lan Jinghui,
there are a few others
who don't meet the requirements
The others are the same
Okay
I really wanna see your skills
Lan Jinghui
Show me this time
Go back to the classroom
Thank you, Director
Ling Dong
Homing pigeons secrete pigeon milk to feed their chicks
And baby chicks follow their mother hen
and scratch the ground for food with their claws
Which one
is directly related to pituitary function
The homing pigeon feeding its chicks
is because the pituitary gland secretes prolactin
While the baby chicks are just imitating behavior
Got it
Ling Dong, what about this?
Can chlorine gas react with elemental sulfur
to form sulfur chloride?
Yes, it can
Chlorine gas can directly react with most
non-metallic elements,
including sulfur
to form disulfur dichloride
When there is excess chlorine gas
sulfur dichloride can be formed
Good
Ling Dong, in today's physics class
I didn't quite understand
the universal gravitation
It's simple
I understand now
There is an attractive force
between two objects
This attractive force
is universally present in
all things in the universe
This is called universal gravitation
Ling Dong, is that correct?
Basically yes
In the future, for these simple questions
Don't bother him
Bother me
Isn't this Lan Jinghui?
You're all here
And none of you passed
What to do now...
You can't even pass the tests
How can you
play basketball against our class?
Shouldn't we all
develop comprehensively
Right?
Brother Peng, we didn't pass either
Ling Dong
Can you help me with this?
How do you solve this problem?
Which one?
This... The first one
That's it all for today's lesson
There's a lot of content
You should review it again
Dismissed
Stand up
Goodbye, teacher
Mr. Guo
I might have
some other things recently
I don't have time temporarily
to attend the physics competition class
Does your head teacher know?
Ms. Fang already knows
Okay then
I'll give you the materials
for this period of time
Take a careful look at it at home
Ask me if you have any questions
Thank you, teacher
Ling Dong
I wanna talk to you properly
Why?
Don't you think I don't know that?
Actually, I know
why you quit the competition class
I just want you
to tell me in person
I don't need to report everything
to you, President Chen
Don't call me President
Since you hang out
with Lan Jinghui
You don't value me
as the student council president
This will affect you
Do you know that?
Whether it affects me or not
Seems like it has nothing to do with you
It does matter
Let me tell you, Ling Dong
In the entire grade 11
only you and I
The two of us
can truly be
academic competitors
If you willingly degrade yourself
and give up your future
Don't blame me for being impolite
Alright, how about this?
How about a bet?
What kind of bet?
This semester's final exams
If I can let Lan Jinghui's score
advance by a hundred places
And you, advance by just one place
Ling Dong, you've gone too far
It's really too much, Ling Dong
This is just too much
Come on
Lower your center of gravity. Don't rush
Take a breath and then shoot
Alright
Got it
Come on
All objects are subject to a
constant and unchanging force
The initial velocity
is not in the same line
as this force
Therefore, the object's trajectory
is a parabola
What are you saying, Brother Hui?
I don't know
Parabola
A basketball in the air
is only affected by gravity
its magnitude and direction remain unchanged
And the initial velocity's direction
is not collinear with gravity
So, the basketball's
trajectory in the air
is a parabola
As long as you get the principles
your shooting accuracy will greatly improve
Classmate
I didn't expect
that you're so capable
These are the essences
verified by countless scientists
If we apply them
to practical situations
it will greatly help improve
shooting accuracy
Can it improve accuracy?
So tell me more about it
What is this?
The parabolic principle?
In the math class this afternoon,
it's about the quadratic functions
It includes
knowledge in this area
You better listen carefully
I know
Listen to me
Ling Dong
Since you have such rich
knowledge and expertise
Why not
become our assistant coach
Right?
You have the knowledge, I have the skills
Let's join forces
We'll be unbeatable, right?
Yes, exactly
No, wait
Don't go
Can't you at least just say yes or no?
Assistant coach
Because I'm the head coach
No, no, no...
How about this?
Head coach
You're the head coach, okay?
It's all up to you
Is that okay?
Then it's up to you
No, it's all up to me
Why are you leaving?
No
At least stay and teach us more
Right?
You're the head coach
You...
No, why are you in such a hurry?
Where can you go?
Today is your first day at work
And you're already laid off
No, just stay
Let's take a look
at this standard equation
Y squared equals 2P
Here's a graph for you
In the plane, there is a point F
and a straight line L
Points where their distances are equal
are called the trajectory of a parabola
So, the fixed point F
is called the focus of the parabola
Lan Jinghui
Do you have any questions?
No
Ms. Fang, I think
you explained it very well
As if you opened
the door to a new world
Okay, please sit down and continue listening
Class
I just wrote down
the formula for
the focus of the standard equation
Take a good look at it
Take some notes
Review the content of this lesson
when you go back home
You'd better read the text first
Then find this type of
comprehension
Pay attention
to this question
An electron is excited
from the ground state to the excited state
requiring 9 eV of energy
So,
what wavelength of light is needed for the transition?
So who's gonna
come up and solve this question?
Teacher, my name is Ling Dong
Ling Dong
Call Lan Jinghui
Teacher is calling you
Lan Jinghui
Come up and solve this question
Why, can't you solve it?
Like this formula,
ε = hv,
it can be used to calculate
the energy needed
for an electron to be excited
from the ground state to the excited state
ε = hv
Yes
Even Lan Jinghui knows how to solve it
Really?
No way
I don't know how to solve it
Lan Jinghui answered it correctly
You may go back
Light is also an electromagnetic wave
And electromagnetic waves
are composed of energy quanta
Each energy quantum
carries energy of Hv
This is Planck's hypothesis
Here, v represents frequency
And H...
Anyone wanna join
the cheerleading team?
Come here to sign up
Will she be the captain?
Is she good enough for it?
Xiaohua participated in the talent show
and she even won prizes
What's wrong with that?
Last time it was because of Ling Dong
I wanna sign up
So do I
Qingtian, so do I
No, you're a boy
Look at you
Then, count me in
But nobody asked you
I'm just afraid
that you're not good at it
Then our class will be embarrassed
Shushu knows ballet
with good body shape
But I'm not good at choreography
What should we do then?
Wait, I think of someone
She will definitely do it
Mengyu
I knew you would be here
I don't know why but...
recently, I just like to
come to the rooftop and daydream
Is there something?
The basketball competition
is about to begin
I wanna invite you
to join our cheerleading team
Why did you come to me?
Can you really trust me
to lead the team?
You know
Besides being tone-deaf
I'm not even good at dancing
What if we'll get laughed
by others
Do you really need me?
Being so indecisive
It's not the Xu Mengyu I know
Alright, I'll agree
But let's make it clear
If I join the cheerleading team
you'll have to listen to me
Music, costumes, dances
All need to be well-designed
Okay, it's a deal
It's a deal
Four, two, three, four
Five, six, seven, eight
Five, two, three, four
Six, two, three, four
Alright, everyone look at this problem
Given A is greater than 0
B is less than 0
And A is not equal to B
You're so considerate
Just have some drinks
Be quick
Here's yours
Thanks
Qingtian
Jia Letian
I don't know
Nope
Okay
Then let me explain it to you
Two, two, three, four
Xiaohua, that's not
the right movement
Shift your center of gravity back
Six, seven, eight
Two, two, three, four
Five, six, seven
Mr. Zhao
Ms. Fang, do you have time?
Yes, I do
Well, here's the thing
I have a small favor to ask
I want you to help
What's the matter with you, Ms. Fang?
Just tell me
Well, the basketball game
is coming up
So I was wondering if you could
spare some time
to give some guidance
to our Class 5
This is...
Is it difficult to handle?
Ms. Fang
Actually, it's not fair
If I only help Class 5,
without helping other classes,
it doesn't sound good
That's right
Forget it. I'll leave now
Take your time
Ms. Fang
I'll think of a way
Five, six, seven, eight
One, two, three, four
Two, two, three, four
Five, six, seven, eight
Three, two, three, four
Four, two, three, four
Five, six, seven, eight
Five, two
Are you finished practicing?
Finish and leave quickly
We need the space
Xiao Xiaohua
Just leave quickly
No way
What did you say?
We're already here first
And, my name is Xiao Xiaohua
Don't get the name wrong
You've been using the space for so long
Now it's our turn
Yes
This space is so big
Can't you just practice over there?
Why?
You've been using it for so long
And we're just here
What's so great about having more people?
You've practiced for so long
Yet you didn't do that good
Why occupy the space?
It's our turn now
Why don't you just stop it?
Are you bullying us?
Move aside
What are you doing?
They've been occupying the space all along
They won't let us use
What do you mean occupying?
It's our turn now
Then make them move
How do we make them?
Yes
This doesn't even belong to you
Say that again
So what?
Can you just shut up?
I told you to move aside
Brother Hui
Lan Jinghui
Apologize
What did you say?
I told you
to apologize to the girls in our class
What if I'll say no?
Lan Jinghui
I've had enough of you
Are you looking for a beating?
Come on
Enough
Stop arguing
Is there gonna be a fight?
What's going on?
Everyone, just calm down
Ms. Chai
They've been occupying the space
We also need to rehearse
What do you mean, occupying?
It's a public space
Alright, stop arguing
Let me ask you
Which class was using the space just now?
Our class
Teacher
It was originally ours to use
But...
Alright, fine
Since your class
has already used the space
then it's time for another class
to use it
We haven't finished practicing yet
Alright
Just calm down, okay?
Let's take turns using it, okay?
Students from class 8, hurry up
Hurry up and leave
No manners
Class 5, take a break for a while
Class 8, start training
Hurry up
Don't let it affect your mood
Class 8, let's train hard and cheer up
Why didn't you let me speak just now?
They've gone too far
Exactly
The most despicable one is Bi Peng
He's impolite
He even hit girls
If Ms. Chai isn't here
I'll definitely do something
Alright
Do you wanna be expelled?
If you don't want it,
then think about
how to win the competition
Ling Dong is right
We should now
win against Class 8
Then hold the trophy
and go to their class
Xiao Xiaohua
You're so much different
while talking now
Is it?
We'd better think about
how to win against Class 8
Easier said than done
They're the expected champion winner
Don't let others' spirit
reduce our own confidence
Every dog has its day
We need to be confident
Brother Hui is right
I should be holding
the championship trophy
and let them see
Ms. Chai is still with their side
Let's go
Nice shot
What's going on?
Defend!
I can't even do that
Amazing!
Ms. Fang
What are these things?
The basketball game
is about to start
I prepared props
for our cheerleading team
In my opinion,
all this preparation is unnecessary
It affects the students' attention
It affects their studies
I think
they should study seriously
when they need
Of course, when it's time to play,
we should enjoy ourselves
Anyway, you're still young
The students in our class
are very self-disciplined
I don't even need to worry about them at all
Some of them
handle cheerleading matters
Some of them win the game
I don't have to worry at all
I trust them completely
I'd say...
You shouldn't even
have appointed Lan Jinghui
as captain
He's such careless and foolish
How can he lead a team
How can he manage the teammates
Good
Ms. Fang
I'm talking to you
Why are you so distracted?
No, I'm not
Ms. Chai
Just now, I was thinking
why did you even say that?
I didn't mean anything else
I know
I'm not that experienced as you
I'm still young
But I have a different opinion
from you
First of all,
I don't think
Lan Jinghui is careless and foolish
Of course, I don't think
he's fooling around as captain
After all, you don't know him
What reason do you have
to say he's not capable?
Well
Why is it raining heavier?
I'm going back first
Lan Jinghui, go for it!
Come on
Class 5, let's go!
Class 5, we must win!
Class 1's overall strength
is average
But those tall players on the other team
are particularly difficult to defend
Especially their center
We need to pressurize him
Ma Yiming, Jian Zhiqiang
You two should cooperate
But try to minimize
get the ball
Keep him away from the penalty area
Xu Chao
We'll rely on you during the game
Everyone, relax
They're not that scary
Show the level of your usual training
That's okay
Don't worry
We weren't afraid to begin with
With Chen Jun's brilliance
Okay, come on
Class 5, let's get it
Come on
Three, two, one
Class 5, win
Come on
Come on, class 5
Class 5
Class 5, come on
Go, class 5
Brother Hui, take it
Good
Defend, Ma Yiming
Foul
Reasonable collision
Come on
Come on, Class 1
It's been three minutes since the start
No goals yet
Both teams are eager to win
If it continues like this
physical energy will be consumed quickly
Come on
With Ling Dong's shooting secret,
our shooting accuracy
will definitely improve greatly
X equals 2PX
P is greater than 0
F0 equals 1/2P
Y equals negative 1/2P
Let's try again
Coach
Who's the coach?
Lan Jinghui
Yes, Lan Jinghui
Coach
Coach, please don't leave
Teach us some more