[English subtitles are available]
[Begin Again]
[Episode 20]
I said I don't care.
Then I just don't care.
Cai Siyu.
Stop being delusional!
All right?
I made it clear to you.
I don't like you.
I've been using you
from the moment I met you.
That's because you're
the best choice.
A person like me
would never fall in love with you
and isn't worthy of your love.
I'm just an incompetent
and cowardly man
falling for
someone I can never love.
I can only end up running away.
Lu Yiyao.
I love you.
I really love you.
I'm not expecting
to be reciprocated
in this relationship actually.
I just hope that
when you feel lonely
and upset,
it can occur to you
that a girl like me
once loved you so deeply.
So that.
I may bring
you a little
warmness and encouragement.
That'd be
enough for me.
♫ Wanting to make a phone call ♫
♫ Asking how he's been ♫
Lu Yiyao.
Promise me
you won't have to be a person like this.
Don't be so stressed.
Be nice to yourself.
Because you'll be
alone in the future.
No one will love you
like I do.
♫ I love you forever ♫
♫ Love you forever ♫
♫ The person I love the most ♫
♫ I should have admitted long ago ♫
♫ I love you forever ♫
♫ Love you forever ♫
♫ The person I love the most ♫
♫ I should have admitted long ago ♫
The flower language of platycodon grandiflorus
is sincere and everlasting love.
It's quite suitable
in memory of our first date.
♫ It's all a destined arrangement ♫
♫ If I were like dust ♫
♫ I'd also be willing to fall into your heart ♫
♫ I love you forever ♫
The name of the dessert is.
'Let's Date'.
♫ Love you forever ♫
♫ You've given me immense warmth ♫
I'll try to
make you
like and love me a little more
every day.
Thus I'd be the one who once was
the leading lady temporarily
even if I fail.
♫ I just want to be by your side ♫
♫ I've never wanted to escape from the palm of your hand ♫
♫ Holding on to the past and present ♫
♫ And our future ♫
Miss Caramel Apple.
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
I'm a fan of yours.
Fan?
Yes.
I've been watching your live stream.
Every one of them.
And I've bought everything you recommended.
Really?
Thank you.
So what can I do for you?
Can I take a picture with you?
All right, yes.
Okay.
Anything else?
I almost forgot.
I prepared you a gift.
A gift?
Yes, yes.
I'm flattered.
Here you are.
A book?
Yes, this is my favorite book.
Hope you'll like it.
My fans are so cultured.
You read books.
Right,
how do you know
I live here?
Well…
I guessed
where this community is
by the room type in your stream.
You can do that?
So awesome.
Fate is the most important factor.
Yes, yeah. Fate.
Well.
If there's nothing else, see you next time?
See you.
-Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
He can find my house by watching my stream.
Forget it.
It's so good that
I have many fans.
[City Ballet]
Aunt.
Tang… Tangtang?
Shouldn't you be free today?
Aunt.
I'm not your aunt.
-Aunt.
-Don't call me that.
Don't come closer.
-Aunt.
-I'm not your aunt.
Don't call me that!
Aunt.
-Aunt.
-Stop it.
I'm not your aunt.
You're Ling Rui's aunt.
I'm really not your aunt.
-Since you're Ling Rui's aunt,
-Don't call me that!
you're my aunt too.
I don't want to threaten you
with canceling my membership.
Since I said it out loud now,
I can only
threaten you with this now.
Actually I just want you
to do me a favor.
Be my spy.
What?
Well.
What are you doing this for?
Because I am Lu Fangning's
one and only
rival
who is well-matched with her strength.
The number one candidate that.
Ling Rui should love.
Aunt.
Aunt, aunt, aunt.
You scared me.
Our diligent
Dr. Ling
has asked for so many days off.
Marital leave?
Personal leave.
I'll go to my hometown with Fangning
to visit the medical station there by the way.
It's this time again.
But it's okay.
Fangning will accompany you this time.
You can't stay there forever.
So both of you are also going
on a honeymoon?
What honeymoon?
What?
Take care of yourself.
Control yourself.
Don't go too far.
We're just going home to visit our relatives.
We won't have to do farm work.
Why should I take care of myself?
I will be on a holiday.
Kind of. I'm still working there anyways.
But you should work overtime as always.
Never be too kind to yourself.
Yes, Ms. Lu.
Don't be too kind to me too.
Call me if there's an emergency.
Unless it's at night.
I wonder if Ling Rui
likes the clothes Cai Siyu prepared
for me this time.
I don't care. I'll just change a style.
Which pajamas should I take?
This one is good.
No, no.
What am I thinking?
It's a serious business trip.
You…
Would you like some water?
No, thanks.
You've packed up your things?
Yes.
I quite look forward to it.
Me too.
Actually some things are not necessary.
The necessities are prepared well already there.
I've prepared the necessities well.
Me too.
-Let's go to sleep.
-Turn the light off.
I mean.
-It's time.
-Yeah.
It's late now.
Yeah, yeah.
I said it too simply just now.
Have… Have an early rest.
-Good night.
See you tomorrow.
-See you tomorrow.
Ling Rui.
Is this your hometown?
Yes.
Good.
Golden rice field.
Golden waves of barley.
Oh, rice fields.
They are not in season yet.
It doesn't matter.
It looks good this way, too.
Beautiful.
Well.
How about this?
Yes.
Where?
Here.
The color might have been edited.
But you can see the flowers.
You see here, and here.
The flowers look nice.
It's okay. It's okay.
We're not here
for sightseeing anyway.
We can photoshop the pictures anyway.
All right. Let's go.
But,
we seem to have got off the bus early.
Right.
We got off one stop earlier.
Let's wait for the next bus then.
There are only two scheduled buses here.
That was the last scheduled bus.
I'll call a taxi.
You can't get a taxi here.
But it's fine.
We can take a
free ride from the villagers.
Free ride.
That's nice.
I've never taken a
free ride in my life.
That's good.
Sir.
Yeah.
Can you give us a free ride?
Our destination is the village ahead.
All right, no problem.
Okay.
Sir.
Can you
put those two
down first?
What?
The two cuties.
The two sheep.
How about this?
I'll buy them, but I won't take them.
So you can tie them to the roadside.
And you can
pick them up later.
Are you insane?
You can name a price.
Double or triple is all fine.
No way. No way.
I won't take you.
You can walk there.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
It's okay, we can wait.
But Ling Rui,
we've been waiting for so long.
Ling Rui?
Are you Dr. Ling?
Yeah, that's me.
You know me?
Of course.
Come on, get on.
I'll put the goats down.
There is no need.
I'm sorry for what I said.
We'll sit here together.
Come on, get on.
-So cute.
-Let's go.
Are you okay?
Sit still, Dr. Ling.
Okay.
Let's go.
-It's okay.
Little White.
So cute.
You're so cute.
Hello.
Are you scared?
They seem to be more scared than I am.
It's okay.
You can touch them, here.
Be good, be good.
They are very gentle.
You can try it.
Why don't you feed it with this?
Little White.
Be good.
It's eating.
Here you are, Little Black.
Let's take a picture.
Okay.
Here we are.
You first.
Okay.
Be careful.
Watch out.
Thank you, sir.
It's okay.
Let me take it.
Dr. Ling.
We'll take our leave then.
-Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
I'll come to visit you in my spare time.
All right.
Take care, bye-bye.
You're welcome. You're welcome.
Bye-bye, Little Black and Little White.
Go ahead.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
So,
we're officially in your hometown now?
Yes.
But it looks as if
it's going to rain.
Never mind.
There is always sunny rain here.
Okay.
Let's go.
Careful.
Hello, is there anyone?
We want to stay here.
How many of you?
We have a booking.
Two rooms.
I want the best
rooms here.
Your suites.
There are not many rooms left.
Only a double room.
Don't look at him.
All couples live in one room here.
We started this year.
There wouldn't be a hotel for you
if you came earlier.
Let's go.
How about taking a look first?
This way.
Mediterranean Pastoral Suite.
Take a look.
Beautiful, isn't it? This is the best.
The sofa.
Pretty, isn't it?
The furniture here
was picked by me.
It's pirated.
What?
My mom bought them from a big supermarket.
It's expensive!
It's just some furniture, okay?
So meddlesome.
I'm not being meddlesome.
This is
the Inspiration Series
imported by our shopping mall in 2018.
I'll not tell you
the product number.
You won't understand anyway.
Little girl, where did you buy the sofa?
Tell me the address.
I'll go sue them.
Why are you so troublesome?
You're finding faults with me.
You want a discount?
We don't do that here.
You can leave if you're not satisfied.
Little girl.
She does not mean that.
You must be scared.
There is only one hotel here.
You'll have to sleep on the street if you don't like it here.
You rascal!
Why are you here?
I told you to stay at the counter.
What if Dr. Ling comes
and can't see us?
Sister Gu.
Ling Rui?
Why didn't you tell me
so I could go pick you up?
It's okay.
Come here.
You are Brother Ling Rui?
She must be Xiaoying.
Yes.
You were so little the last time I saw you.
Now you've grown so tall.
Brother Ling Rui.
I'll have the senior high school entrance exam next year.
Please enlighten my brain.
No way,
he is mine.
Who are you?
How can you be so rude?
Stay here.
Ling Rui, this is?
This is my wife.
Lu Fangning.
You bring your wife here?
Good, good.
Mrs. Ling.
If you don't like
the room,
I can change it for you.
And this, pirated.
I'm so embarrassed. I'll change it tomorrow.
I'll give you a new one.
Ling Rui, come to see this room.
Okay.
Knowing you're coming back,
I've prepared
the biggest room for you.
The bedsheet
and the quilt cover are new.
Thanks, Sister Gu.
Mrs. Ling, are you satisfied?
I'm quite satisfied.
Thanks, Sister Gu and Xiaoying.
That's great.
You can take a rest here.
We'll not bother you then.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-Um…
Brother Ling Rui, enlighten me.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
I'm wondering
what magic you've
cast on to the people here,
making them so
obsessed with you?
Aren't you tired after a day of the ride?
No.
It's nice to see
your childhood hometown.
This is actually
a normal town here.
Less prosperity and buzz
compared with big cities.
But every time
I come back,
I gain inner peace.
It's quite comfortable here.
-What are they selling?
-Crabs.
Miss, take a look at the crabs.
How about we buy some
for dinner tonight?
-Okay.
-Dr. Ling.
You don't have to buy.
I'll send you
some cooked ones tonight.
You live in Sister Gu's hotel, right?
It's okay, we can buy them ourselves.
No, I insist.
Just go.
Go have fun.
I'll send them to you tonight.
Thank you.
Never mind.
All right, you two go have fun.
Careful, Dr. Ling.
All right, thank you.
You're welcome.
You're such an idol here.
How can you be so adorable?
I just can't believe it.
What?
Let me have a try.
Ling Rui. I'm thirsty.
Dr. Ling.
Have some water.
Here you are. The water.
Uncle Liu.
It's okay.
We can buy it.
Hold this. Hold this.
Your wife is so pretty.
I need just one bottle.
Thank you, thank you.
Take it.
Thank you, Uncle Liu.
It's nothing.
Bye-bye.
Everyone here
looks up to you.
I don't believe that.
Will dogs even listen to you here?
-A dog!
-It's okay.
Dog!
Don't be afraid.
-It's okay, it's okay. Don't be scared.
-It's coming
It's coming, it's coming.
It's okay.
Sit down, sit down.
It's quite good. Are you going to come down?
No.
Then let's go.
Ling Rui, you're back?
Hello.
-You're back?
-Yes.
I'm back.
-Ling Rui.
-Hello, Sister Zhang.
-Ling Rui, you're back.
-Hi, Uncle Zhou.
Hello, Uncle Zhou.
Do you want sugar-coated haws?
You want sugar-coated haws?
No, no.
Ling Rui is back.
Hello, hello.
Your wife is pretty.
Hello, Dr. Ling.
Hello, hello.
[Flower Room]
Are you going to take a rest?
I'll go to see
if there is anything to eat.
No.
Be good.
No way.
I won't.
All right, you must first tell me
what the heck
have you done here?
Why is everyone
treating you so well?
They probably want to carry you up
and parade through the town.
Why are you smiling?
Before this, someone would send me
whatever I need.
Now it's just one question
and there's no answer?
Let me tell you.
Someone really came.
You can ask her.
All right.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Smell good?
Are they for me?
No.
All right, go ahead.
But after I tell you,
you should do me
a little favor.
You're even asking for something.
Sure.
Brother Ling Rui
was the first provincial top scholar
from our town.
My teachers always say
he is the pride of the town,
and an unprecedented
genius.
Yes.
That is true.
And,
Brother Ling Rui is extremely filial.
I heard that brother Ling Rui's mother,
Aunt Zhu,
once had depression.
It was brother Ling Rui
who took care of her.
But he still was able
to become the top scholar in the province.
Depression?
Yes.
He contacted a big hospital
and established a medical station in the town.
He helped many people cure their diseases.
And,
he comes here every year
to see the sick.
He is so awesome.
He indeed is.
I'm done.
Are you helping me or not?
Say it. What do you want?
Writing your homework is not okay.
Help me to secretly take
Brother Ling Rui's favorite thing
for me.
Maybe a pencil case
or a book.
I'll take it as my lucky charm.
I just might be in the top three
in next year's senior high school
entrance exam.
Usually,
I'm a clean freak.
But, show me your hand.
Brother Ling Rui likes
me the most.
No.
Wait.
Hey!
I don't want your hand.
Love you.
Well…
Ling Rui, if you feel
uncomfortable this way.
I'll go to another room.
It's okay.
It's fine.
We've been on a trip the whole day.
Very tired.
I have to go to the health center
tomorrow morning.
Why don't I sleep first?
Okay.
Good night.
Um…
Ling Rui.
Yes.
Are you really tired?
Actually…
I'm not that tired.
Me either.
Then…
How about we go ahead
and get prepared?
Prepare what?
Scented candle?
I didn't bring that.
Wine?
No wine.
How come I didn't prepare anything?
Actually,
there are somethings
we don't have to prepare for.
-Who is it?
Let me check it out.
Coming.
Who is it?
Surprise.
Dr. Ling.
Why is she here?
Yeah, why is she here?
Why?
Why is the insane woman
Tang Ping here?
How did she get here?
How did she know
we're here?
It might be…
Fate.
Why am I hearing her voice?
She… she is.
She is in the room next door.
Because of the poor sound insulation.
So she heard
everything that we said?
Lu Fangning,
the sound insulation is so bad.
I can hear clearly
whatever you do.
I'm changing my room.
Me too then.
I'll go to another hotel.
I've looked it up.
This is the only hotel in the town.
Fangning,
let's forget about it today.
No way, we can't.
Now that she's here today,
who knows what tricks
she will play tomorrow.
But,
there is no but.
Ling Rui, look at me.
♫ The vengeance of hell ♫
♫ boils in my heart. ♫
♫ The flame of ♫
♫ death and despair ♫
♫ surrounds me ♫
♫ If you do not ♫
♫ kill Sarastro to avenge me ♫
Fangning,
we don't have to force ourselves tonight.
♫ Disowned may you be forever ♫
♫ Abandoned may you be forever ♫
Morning.
Darling.
Eat more this morning, all right?
Where should we go shopping today?
I'm going too.
[Nanshanzhen Activity Center]
Tang Ping.
You'd better not
waste your time here.
Ling Rui will only
love me forever and ever.
What I care about is
my future
with Dr. Ling.
Now, I just need to assure
you two won't
do something bad.
Ms. Tang,
I remember that I
made it clear to you…
I'm sorry.
Keep your mouth shut now.
That's right.
I'll take care of this.
Tang Ping.
Do you still remember
Wei, Fanfan,
Han, Liangliang
and Dingding.
You've always been
defeated by me
for all these years.
How dare you mention them!
Lu Fangning, you bad girl!
Wait and see.
I'll make you suffer
tonight.
Pingping, let me explain.
Don't come closer.
You accepted my gift.
I'm just too fond of you.
And you said in your live streams
that you want people to follow you more
and like you more.
I don't mean it like that.
No.
Let's take a picture then.
Or I can take a picture of you.
Stop following me.
I'll call the police if you come closer.
Pingping.
Then see you next time.
What should I do?
Tell my dad?
No.
My dad is going to kill him.
This one.
This one is just a freeloader!
And this one?
This one only knows who to lick my shoes!
Shall I go to Lu Fangning for help?
What's wrong?
Why are you shouting here?
Because you will only scold me.
What are you saying?
What's wrong?
I…
That means,
you don't know his name,
contact way
and any useful information?
No.
How about his picture,
video, or voice recording?
No.
How about your brain? Do you have a brain?
I really thought he was my fan.
Fan?
What kind of fan is he?
Shows up in front of you again and again
and waits at your door.
He's not a fan.
He's a freak.
A stalker, you know that?
What do you practice in
the judo gym normally?
You only know how to take pictures.
See?
You can't beat him now.
And you can't outrun him.
You don't even have a brain.
Stop it.
I'm already scared.
What should I do now?
I can only ask you for help
after thinking about it again and again.
Lu Fangning,
help me.
I'm done.
I'm screwed.
I'm doomed.
You'd better disappear.
You shut up.
Be quiet for a while.
I'll go if you don't shut up.
I'm leaving.
Didn't your dad teach you
when you were little?
If something bad happens,
go to the police.
The police?
Listen carefully.
Okay, I understand.
All right, I know.
Where did she go?
Fangning.
I'm done with my work.
Let's go eat.
Wait a second.
Maybe later. Later.
She refused to dine with me?
Is she really upset?
What are you looking for?
You need my help?
You…
I can't let Ling Rui
meddle in this kind of thing.
You can't do it.
Rest assured.
I can take care of it on my own.
I'll look for you later.
See you at night.
I can't do it?
She'll take care of it on her own?
It's about your honor as a man.
How come you don't have any strength as a man?
Was it because of last night?
Is she despising me?
I didn't see him.
Are we really doing this?
How else can we
lure the stalker out?
Come on.