[English subtitles are available]
[Begin Again]
[Episode 21]
There's still no one.
Be patient and wait.
Why is there still no one?
Tang Pingping,
can you be more natural?
Be quiet.
Don't be like a thief.
No matter what happens
later on,
you must take him
to the designated location I told you.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I scared you again.
It's okay.
I'm sorry that
I embarrassed you today.
You aren't angry, are you?
Why would I?
Didn't I say that
we'll meet again?
Don't worry.
I'm still your big fan.
That's good then.
By the way,
these are for you to eat.
Do you like them?
For me?
Yes.
Thank you!
Aiyah.
Aiyo.
What are you doing?
I...
It hurts.
You took candid shots!
Pervert!
What can a few photos indicate?
I did nothing.
You did nothing?
Do you see it?
The CCTV is there.
The police will tell you
whether you did it or not.
I'm in the wrong.
It's my first time.
Please let me off the hook.
Right now,
you should be thankful
as you can be corrected
before making a huge mistake.
I'm still a student.
If I'm caught by police,
my life is over.
My future is gone.
This society always welcomes
the one who has turned over a new leaf.
It hurts.
Not bad.
Aren't you just
going to show others
by dressing like this?
You finally said this.
It's a modern era now.
You still said something like this.
Let me tell you.
Wearing a skirt
is for my own happiness,
but not for others to see.
How is it?
Well said.
You praised me?
Lu Fangning,
praise me again.
What you just said
was taught by me.
So you know what?
Your greatest strength
is that you know to learn from me.
I don't need to learn from you.
Then you use your own words
to scold him again.
Scold him.
I need to see
whether he's willing to be scolded by me.
Stop there!
Who are you again?
Don't move.
Dr. Ling.
Ling Rui?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Hit.
What are you doing?
Hold on.
Hit now.
Hit.
You pervert!
I'm beating you to death.
Pervert!
Scumbag!
Vile pervert!
I'm beating you to death.
Here you are.
Drop dead!
Pervert.
Pervert!
Make sure you hit on him.
I'm hitting you to death.
Scumbag!
-Drop dead!
-Help!
We finally caught that pervert red-handed.
Lu Fangning.
You're so smart.
He really is a habitual offender.
Darling.
You were so impressive just now.
That was because I heard before that...
Forget it.
I got it wrong.
It's great that you're fine.
Why would I be hurt?
But if
something happens to you,
I'll be worried to death.
You don't even know that
the hands of a surgeon
are very precious.
I used feet just now.
Yes, you're so smart and amazing!
Lu Fangning,
why are you so pretentious now?
You can surely
beat him just now.
Honey,
you said before that
you could handle it.
Did you refer to this?
For this matter,
I can do it for you.
Okay.
I still have to go to the medical room.
There's still something to deal with.
We're going to separate again.
What should I do?
I'll miss you.
We'll see each other later.
Come back early then.
I'll make a move now.
See you tonight.
Missing you!
Lu Fangning.
You've changed.
I'm better than who I was before.
Why are you following me?
I'm scared of being alone.
Then go home and look for your dad.
I won't.
Lu Fangning.
Go to the bar with me tonight.
No, I don't want to.
Do keep me company.
It shouldn't be a big problem.
But it'd be better for you
to go to a big hospital to check tomorrow.
Try not to move with the wound
tonight.
Thank you, Dr. Ling.
You're welcome.
Dr. Ling,
we took you so long for this.
We're really sorry.
You haven't eaten yet, right?
I'll go and make the arrangement.
There's no need.
I...
My wife is still waiting for me.
I understand.
Well,
thank you then.
We'll make a move first.
Okay.
Thank you.
-Thank you, Dr. Ling. Thank you.
-Okay.
Thank you.
Remember not to move with the wound.
Okay.
Slow down.
Tang Ping.
Tang Pingping.
You've fallen asleep?
You...
What are you doing?
What's wrong with her?
She was scared today,
so perhaps she's feeling sad.
But she can even be drunk like this
by drinking this wine.
She really can't drink.
Tang Ping.
Don't move.
Let's go out.
Let's leave.
Is she okay?
Aiyah.
She's okay.
Look. She's okay.
Look at me.
When Tang Ping was conscious during the day,
she was looking and staring at you
with bad intentions.
Who knows whether she'll take advantage of you
when she's drunk?
I can't let
my cutest Ling Rui
be taken advantage of by her.
You're also very cute.
Then do you want
to give me some rewards
for being so cute?
What rewards?
It's the lobby at the back.
It's crowded.
It's fine.
Come over.
Come here.
What are you two doing?
What are you doing?
Why did you come out?
Fangning,
where did you go?
Why did you leave
without saying anything?
I thought you'd never come back.
What nonsense are you spouting now?
What happened to you?
Are you drunk?
Why are you crying?
-Tang Ping.
-You're nasty.
I'm nasty?
You've been nasty since your childhood.
You clearly know that
since my childhood, I've always wanted
to be good friends with you.
Why have you been bullying me since my childhood?
You hate me, so I also hate you.
Do you know that
I really envy you?
You've been doing so well
in everything,
and everyone likes you.
But I can't do anything well,
and I've always been cheated.
Tang Ping.
Look at me.
Enough said.
What are you doing?
You drank too much?
Moreover,
why do you want to compare yourself with me?
Aren't you courting yourself humiliation?
I'm
such a great person,
right?
Okay, stop spouting nonsense.
By the way,
when I scolded that vile pervert
today,
I just imagined
myself like you.
So handsome!
I found out
for the first time that
cursing is such a cool thing.
I feel that it's so handsome.
I really like you so much,
Lu Fangning.
Enough said.
I actually
don't hate you either.
Tang Ping.
That's enough.
None of you men
is good.
But you
are considered not bad.
You...
Tang Ping.
You're drunk.
Enough said.
Stop making trouble.
Go in and sleep.
You're drunk.
Lu Fangning.
I
love you.
Tang Ping.
Tang Pingping.
Think about it. I'm Lu Fangning.
Who have I served since my childhood?
She vomited, and I had to coax her to sleep.
That was awful.
Look.
She's like a pig.
I'm really unsatisfied.
Our romantic night
was ruined by this fool.
You're not allowed to leave me.
She needs you the most
right now.
I have to
temporarily lend you to her.
But I'm not willing to be lent.
It can't be helped.
I'm just too lovely.
Right.
You're indeed too lovely.
So sometimes
it's also quite troublesome.
But
you only love me.
Right.
Fine.
I'll stay with her tonight.
It's just that
before lending myself to her,
I want her to get
a little punishment.
What punishment?
Come here.
Come and sit here.
Why?
Darling.
This is not that proper.
Just one kiss.
I don't allow that in front of me.
This is really not that good.
Yes.
Whose room is this?
Aiyah!
None of you men
is good.
Lu Fangning.
I
love you.
I must be crazy.
What did I say to Lu Fangning?
How can I meet her next time?
I want to go home.
Going home.
[Greenhouse]
Miss Tang.
You're awake.
I...
Ready to leave?
Ling Rui,
why is my apple...
You're awake.
Do you want to have an apple?
I...
I'm not eating.
-You don't like it?
-Don't come over.
Don't come over.
What's wrong?
It's that
I'm already full
from your PDA.
I don't have to eat this apple then.
This apple
is really not well peeled.
Honey.
It's too dramatic.
Well,
I'm not acting.
I was just being nice, asking
if you want to have breakfast?
What are you doing?
You stupid...
Silly girl.
Silly yet cute.
When you are outside alone
next time,
don't drink so much alcohol.
How dangerous it is for a little girl.
Okay.
You're...
Planning to leave?
You don't plan to continue
ruining my romantic time?
Aiyah.
After going back this time,
I want to live a good life,
work hard,
and make money properly.
Hopefully
when you see me next time,
you'll scold me less.
Or
shall we take you to the station?
There's no need.
I'm fine. Don't bother.
Dr. Ling.
-Something happened.
-What happened?
Hurry up and go to the medical station
to take a look.
Several students fought
and they're injured.
Okay, I got it.
I'll go over at once.
Okay, hurry up.
Fangning.
I'm fine.
Patients matter. Hurry up and go.
Okay.
I'm sorry, Miss Tang.
How about I let Xiaoying take you there?
It's okay.
I have Lu Fangning to see me off.
Okay, I'll leave first. Fangning.
-I'm leaving.
-Bye-bye.
Xiaoying.
Come and see Sister Tang Ping off.
Let go of me.
So annoying.
Go down the stairs slowly, Xiaoying.
You're so warmhearted.
What's the matter? Why are you shy?
Aiyah, don't be shy.
What's wrong?
Don't walk hand in hand with me.
Why?
Haven't we reconciled?
You don't hate me anymore, right?
That's enough.
Okay.
Stop teasing you.
I'll wait for you.
Why will you wait for me?
Didn't you say that
you're seeing me next time?
Goodbye.
See you next time.
Then
I'm leaving.
You can go now.
Leave now.
Leave now. What are you doing?
Bye-bye.
We must see each other again.
Goodbye.
Bye-bye!
Go now.
-Bye-bye!
Brother Ling Rui's wife,
is this sister
just like you,
who also likes Brother Ling Rui very much?
What nonsense are you spouting?
But I think that
although she likes you so much,
she'd been messing around
between you and Ling Rui.
But it's obvious that
you only fancy Ling Rui.
After all,
Brother Ling Rui is so great.
Indeed.
As you can see,
I'm really quite lovely.
But
I only have Ling Rui in my heart.
Of course, Ling Rui is also very good.
But sister,
you don't have to be sad.
Why would I be sad?
In fact,
Brother Ling Rui
has had someone whom he's been into for a long time.
I know. It's me.
No.
It was really a long time ago.
I heard from my mother that Brother Ling Rui
has been into that girl
since high school.
Sister-in-law,
have you and Ling Rui
known each other for that long?
Well,
it's not that long.
Right?
I heard that
Brother Ling Rui
has been keeping a coin.
It was given by the one
whom he's into.
This is a gift for you.
A coin?
With the motif
of an amusement park on it?
How did you know?
Because that's mine.
But didn't you say that
you and Brother Ling Rui
haven't known each other for that long?
You're a little kid.
Why do you have so many questions?
If you keep asking me,
I won't help you
to get Brother Ling Rui's
lucky item.
Really?
Sister-in-law,
do you really want to give it to me?
Sister-in-law, you're so nice.
Here is the place
where Ling Rui used to go to school.
The person he's into
should be his classmate.
Senior, I'm into you.
No. Thank you.
[Books bring eternal benefits to me]
Is your hand hurt?
Let me see.
Don't move.
Why did you fight?
He laughed at me.
They all laughed at me.
They said I picked up food
and clothes for a living.
Saying that I was a beggar,
picking up what others didn't want.
Are you then?
Of course not.
Why were you angry then?
My family is poor.
Even the tuition fee is paid by the teacher.
We share the same clothes.
Finally, I got new clothes,
which were left unwanted by my classmate.
I have to go to school every day,
wearing old clothes that others don't want.
What a shame.
I still have to go to the teacher in the afternoon
to take the lunch that others don't want.
They must be mocking me
in their hearts.
They must be laughing at me.
Forget it, how can you understand?
I understand.
I also had
the experience of wearing
classmates' old clothes to school.
I also had
the experience
of standing in the corridor
and having bread given by the teacher.
I had experienced all of these.
So what?
You're smart.
You had excellent results.
So I have to study hard
to be like you.
Did you mean so?
What I want to say
is that I can understand your feeling.
Yes.
When I was in school,
my results were pretty good.
So maybe
I had to go to the podium frequently
to express my gratitude in public.
I need to thank
and bow.
To thank classmates and teachers for their help,
although some of them
didn't deserve it.
Didn't you have self-esteem?
Compared to self-esteem,
I have something more important.
I'm not asking you to abandon self-esteem
by telling you this.
I want you to keep it well instead.
If you're feeling angry
towards others due to this,
that's really giving up on yourself
and giving up dignity.
I'm not as strong as you.
I'm not strong, too.
I'll also be angry.
I'll also lose control.
Really?
Correct.
I'm just an ordinary person, too.
But fortunately,
at that time,
I met someone.
That person
once confessed her love
in front of me.
Although the way her using a coin
as a token of love
was childish,
it's been warming me up.
It's just like
a person who is about to drown
managing to grab a floating board.
She saved me.
And now,
I also hope to be your floating board.
Floating board?
I thought that it was me.
It's the coin again.
I didn't expect that this coin
is so important to him.
It's lucky that
I always carry it with me.
Forget it.
I'll reluctantly inherit you.
Where's the coin?
I'm doomed.
Drop dead!
Pervert!
Let's swap. Okay.
It's not a game coin.
Whose coin is this?
[Nanshan Town Medical Center]
Come and get some sugar-coated haws.
I lost it again.
I really don't share an affinity
with this coin?
I even don't mind inheriting you.
You still dislike me?
Hey.
The school has always had a tradition.
The lower and upper grades
have to learn in a pair.
Hello, my name is Ling Rui.
What's your name?
The White Queen of the Golden Forest.
Just call me Queen.
Hello, Queen.
Teacher Xu asked me
to come and help you with your homework.
No. I can't and I won't.
These inferior questions
don't fit my vibe at all.
I'll first write out
the thought processes of ​​answering the questions for you.
You...
You didn't say not to read.
Then I don't want to do homework here.
Where are you going to do it?
My territory.
Which place is it?
Forget it, come with me.
Let's go and play the next one.
Which one to play?
That one.
Let's play it after you've finished your homework.
I'll do it later.
You do it first.
Work on this.
With the level of Queen,
half an hour should be enough.
I'm done.
Less than half an hour.
Let's go.
Pack my schoolbag for me.
Look at me.
Let's continue doing it.
Come again if you like it.
Let's eat cotton candy.
I'm not eating.
You haven't finished your homework yet.
I treat you.
Nanny,
get me two cotton candies.
Okay.
Keep the change.
-Here.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Let's go and do homework.
Be careful.
I'm done.
Little teacher,
don't you want to play?
I'm not playing.
Boring.
Hold the cotton candies properly.
It's the Queen's ride.
I'm coming.
Nanny,
can I borrow your camera?
Sure.
But I have no money.
You bought cotton candies
and paid me more than they cost
just now.
Just take it.
Remember to give it back to Nanny.
Do you know how to use it?
Yes, I do.
Good.
Thank you.
Be careful.
Little teacher,
show me my photos.
Am I pretty?
Am I?
-Am I?
-Yes.
You're actually quite good-looking.
You'll be my subject from now on.
Call me when anything happens.
I'm The White Queen of the Golden Forest,
Ningning.
The kid behind.
Yes, higher.
One, two, three.
Here's one photo.
Sit properly.
Let's take one more photo.
Hello.
I'm sorry.
I can't teach you anymore in the future.
Hello,
this is the city hospital.
You lost our photo
just like that.
When you came to me,
my dad just passed away.
His surgery
was delayed again and again.
I thought it must be because
we were poor.
So I could only witness
his situation
getting worse.
At last,
I almost broke down.
Little teacher.
Finally, I found you.
What's wrong with you?
Is someone bullying you?
I'll teach him a lesson.
I'm the queen.
No one here is going to play with you.
What happened to you?
Tell me.
My family is rich.
My dad said that
in this world,
money can solve all the problems.
Look. I have money.
I'm giving you all of my money.
I don't want it.
What do you want?
I only have money.
What should I do?
How can I help you?
I can give you whatever you need.
You...
Why are you so kind to me?
Because you played with me in the amusement park
and looked at me laughing.
You have a great smile.
I don't want to see you like this.
I want you to laugh, too.
For this one,
I accepted it.
You can regard the money accepted
as the deposit.
I'll earn more money
when I grow up,
and I'll marry you, okay?
The White Queen of the Golden Forest.
Little teacher.
Long time no see.
Unfortunately,
I lost
your marriage deposit.
Why is it with you?
All things that are lost
will be found.
It's like the fate
between us.
Fangning.
In your past,
I may not be special.
But you're very important
to me in my life.
It's you
who prevented me from
being in excruciating pain.
You made me realize
that someone would help me.
that I wasn't
a weak person,
and I could also bring hope to others.
If it was without you,
I might have done something
that I may regret later.
Afterward
I heard from Professor Luo
that for my dad's illness,
there was basically no chance for surgery.
It's them who tried their best
to extend his lifespan again and again.
So
I made up my mind to study medicine,
trying to overcome
this medical difficulty.
So that's why
you want to study abroad
so eagerly.
So it's because of this.
I thought
that I agreed with your marriage contract
was because I was grateful towards you.
But afterward, I found out
that I'd do only you
such a favor
in my life.