[English subtitles are available]
[Begin Again]
[Episode 09]
Have you
ever been in love?
I...
Yes, I think.
That's good.
A girl with experience
like you
should listen carefully to
every word I say,
and do a proper analysis
for me.
I have a friend
who really needs a child.
So, she found a guy
whom she likes very much,
and got married.
But after they got married,
they have never slept on the same bed.
My friend has tried
many times
but to no avail.
Do you think the problem lies
with my friend or the man?
Oh, so that's
why you married Dr. Ling.
So you...
I'm talking about my friend.
Yes, your friend.
Yes.
Never mind.
I don't think you know how
to solve it. Go back to work.
Ms. Lu.
This is actually very simple.
Just let your friend show
all of her charm.
She's your friend,
so she must be someone like you.
No one could resist
a girl like you.
I know that.
But I...
I mean, my friend has tried that.
It didn't work.
She has tried it?
Really?
Why didn't it work?
It didn't work, even you...
It's clear that this man
has a noble personality.
He's not an ordinary man
who could be attracted by simple beauty.
Ms. Lu,
your friend really has good taste.
About this situation,
my idol has said that
to lure an adult,
we need to stop being human.
There are three methods.
You could be a cat,
or a tiger,
or a dog who got wet in the rain.
I didn't say that.
It's not you.
She's my idol
from the entertainment industry.
You have good taste in picking your idols.
But,
how exactly to apply this?
It's a bit difficult
to actually do that.
But the advice from my other idol
in another industry
might suit you...
-your friend better.
-A very good friend of mine.
The CEO's Personal Treasure.
The CEO's Dear Wife.
Rich Family's Contract,
the CEO Falls For Me.
Because their identities
are similar to that of your friend.
Your friend could find some inspiration
from these books.
For example,
how to show her charm.
As long as she could let
the noble man feel
0.01% of her charm.
It won't be a problem for her
to take him down.
You can think of someone close to you,
for example,
Director Lu.
How did a handsome man like him
get attracted by
his fiancee?
Are you asking me about
Simon and his fiancee?
No, I'm just curious.
Why do you care about this?
Qin Yujiang,
the heiress of Jiang Cheng Group.
Smart, independent, and elegant.
She is different from me.
Different from you either.
Impressive ex-girlfriend.
You guys are so boring.
They broke up so many years ago.
You guys are still curious about this.
Please don't show up again.
Thank you for all this.
You're off work now.
Great.
Good luck, Ms. Lu.
I'll triple your overtime pay.
Thank you, Ms. Lu!
[My neighbor is CEO]
[The flirtatious evil CEO]
This is
so easy.
[Shenzhen Huiren Hospital]
[Emergency]
[We protect you with science]
It's a woman.
She is much cooler than you.
Let's go.
Wait a second.
It was all good.
How did it become like this?
[Doctor's Office]
[General Surgeon's Office]
Dear me.
It's so loud.
What kind of hospital is this?
-A healthy man...
-Yeah.
-He is dead after being treated by you.
-The operation
took Dr. Ling six hours.
It was successful.
But no one expected complications.
Stop it.
What should I do?
Are you...
Are you all unqualified doctors?
Are you?
How did you become doctor?
Give me back my brother.
They're swearing at Ling Rui.
Give me back my husband!
Don't you know
this is part of
a surgeon's job scope?
You can't go in now.
You'll only make it worse
if you go in now.
I don't care.
Ling Rui didn't do anything wrong.
How could I just watch my husband
being scolded by them?
Yeah, I understand.
I'm more worried than you.
I wanted to go in a long time ago.
Then, why are you still standing here?
Let's go.
No, wait.
Listen to me, please.
If we go in now,
this matter could not be solved either.
How about this?
Wait here for a while.
When Ling Rui walks out,
you can talk to him.
He still needs to
do a ward round later.
He is in trouble right now.
And he still has to keep working
and do a ward round?
What kind of operation did you do?
Tell me.
How did the complications happen?
Ma'am,
the operation was successful.
Your husband died of complications,
which has nothing to do with Dr. Ling.
Nothing to do with him?
He was talking to me
before he went into the operating theater.
How could you say this?
Give my husband
back to me.
Give him back to us.
I want my husband back.
My husband.
Get some rest
later.
I'll take your shift
for this afternoon.
Ling Rui.
Why are you here?
Are you available this afternoon?
If you are free,
follow me somewhere.
[Haunted Castle]
Your client is here?
Yeah.
I'm busy at the hospital.
I don't have time to
play with you here.
Where are you going?
You can't go anywhere.
You're mine today.
So you have to come with me.
Just tell me
what do you want to play?
Haunted houses, pirate ships,
and bumper cars.
I allow you to play each one of them once.
Let's go.
Let's take a ride on the merry-go-round.
Why?
Because you were staring at it
for more than three seconds.
Although it's a bit surprising,
but I'm okay with that.
-I don't want to go.
-Let's go.
[Bumpers Car]
[Please keep a safe distance]
How many of you?
How many seats do you have?
Twenty.
[Coupon]
I'll take all the seats.
Are you
paying for the 20 guests behind you?
No, just him.
How is this?
I booked all the seats for you.
Are you happy?
Pick whichever you like.
Ride on it if you like it.
Mom,
I want to ride too.
Let them come too.
Or I won't go either.
Why didn't you say that earlier?
Alright, as long as you're happy.
-This way.
-Let them all in.
-Come on.
I'm not going.
-Why?
-I'll get motion sickness.
You go ahead.
Go ahead.
Come, this way.
One, two, three, four.
-Take this one, this white horse.
-Five, six.
This one is big. Ride on it.
Seven.
I want the white horse.
Eight.
This way.
White.
Don't fall.
Hold tight.
♫ Your arrival in my world ♫
Ling Rui. Look over here.
Hey, there.
Girl, lower your head.
Ling Rui.
My "husband charming"
is so cute.
♫ I can only be sure
that you are the only one ♫
♫ I'm not afraid to walk in
a sea of ​​people ♫
♫ Because I really love you ♫
♫ My dear, I have three hearts for you ♫
♫ Listen to this carefully,
this shall not be done half-heartedly ♫
♫ You must love
and give with all your heart ♫
♫ I'll love you well ♫
♫ When I speak of love,
I mean it wholeheartedly ♫
♫ To prove that you'll always
be my one and only ♫
♫ From now on, my heartbeat, pulse,
and breath ♫
♫ exist only for you ♫
♫ My dear, I have three hearts for you ♫
♫ Listen to this carefully,
this shall not be done half-heartedly ♫
♫ You must love
and give with all your heart ♫
♫ I'll love you well ♫
♫ When I speak of love,
I mean it wholeheartedly ♫
♫ To prove that you'll always
be my one and only ♫
Do you come here often?
How shall I put it?
I used to come here often
when I was young,
but seldom these years.
How about you?
Every kid has a special feeling
about amusement parks.
No matter how old we are,
amusement park could always
stimulate our adrenaline
to make us feel happy,
and bring us comfort.
Are you trying to comfort me?
How about I buy you cotton candy?
Granny, I want two cotton candies.
Take it by yourself.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-How much is this?
Five yuan for each.
Here.
I don't have enough change.
No need for change, granny.
-Thank you.
[Cotton candy]
Ling Rui.
What are you doing?
Silly.
Can't you see
what I'm doing?
Sister,
what are those two people doing?
It's so embarrassing. Let's go.
What do you know, kids?
I really can't tell.
What did you say?
I even got my palms red,
and I still failed?
We went around all day,
and this is the only thing
we brought back.
When we come here again,
we have to bring all the toys
on that wall back home.
What's wrong with you today?
You're a bit weird.
Weird?
Actually,
I saw
what you were like in the hospital.
I want to tell you that,
don't take it too personally.
This is not your fault.
Really.
You're already a very good doctor.
But no matter how good the doctor is,
he cannot bring back
all of his patients' lives.
Thank you.
I'm fine.
Medicine
is just relativity,
never a promise.
As a surgeon,
I might face
this kind of thing every day.
I've got used to it already.
It's not that easy.
If you can get used to it,
you're not the Ling Rui
that I know anymore.
Are you comforting me?
What else?
You know, I had Gao Erfan
spend a lot of time
booking this whole place today.
Isn't this amazing?
When I was young,
I liked coming here
every time I felt down.
This is very comforting.
A lot of time?
You prepared this in advance?
Never mind all that.
Time is precious.
Where do you want to go next?
I've tried so hard to
get you half a day off.
Half a day off?
Director Luo told me
to take a rest.
That's because of you?
I apologize. I'm sorry.
But,
I saw that
you weren't feeling good today.
So I want you to have some rest.
I've already asked them.
You don't have any
important appointments today.
-So I thought...
-First of all,
it's my call
whether I have
important appointments.
Secondly,
it's a waste of
medical resources
to change a doctor's schedule.
Lastly,
I would like you not to
intervene in my job and my life
too much in the future.
Am I not part of your life?
You are.
But...
But what?
But we...
We're just bonded by a contract.
A contract?
It's just a contract?
You think I like
to watch you riding on
some merry-go-round
and play bumper cars with you
like an idiot?
I even acted like
the CEOs in the novels,
called you silly,
and put my hand on a tree,
hurting my own palms.
Even the kids were laughing at me.
I did all these just
to make you happy.
You're doing this just
to achieve your own goal.
What goal?
I don't want to talk about it.
I want to have a baby, right?
What's up?
Why are you embarrassed to
say that out loud?
I just want a baby.
Say something.
Alright.
Let me ask you a question.
Do you love me?
Does it
matter whether I love you
or not?
I think this is something
that has to do with love.
I hope you can understand
and respect me.
Aren't we married?
Lu Fangning, you really want
a baby that much, huh?
Yes, I do.
Okay.
I'll give you what you want.
Let's give it a shot.
But you must not
run away this time.
Deal.
I won't run away.
Didn't you do everything
to get this?
I think
we can do it
step by step.
What's up?
Are you scared?
Scared?
My hair was stuck.
Just give me a second.
One second, okay?
Lu Fangning, haven't you been waiting
for this day to come?
What are you waiting for? Get inside.
It's the first time.
It's normal to be a bit nervous.
About what?
Just close your eyes
and you'll have a baby.
But I was so frivolous
in front of him.
If he finds out
I have no experience,
isn't that embarrassing?
You don't need to care about that.
When this story got out,
how would Cai Siyu think of you?
Once Tang Ping knows,
she is gonna jump to the sky.
You were just bragging
with that girl at the front desk.
Have you forgotten?
If you went out alone,
what would she think of you?
If you go out alone now,
it'll be more embarrassing.
Lu Fangning, don't you want a baby?
Don't be scared, go inside.
You're right.
Wait, wait.
Hold on, hold on.
Why do we still need to wait some more?
We've waited long enough.
You just want a baby, don't you?
I knew you are afraid.
Honey,
I'll be up in a minute.
Ms. Lu,
How's your charm working?
Ling Rui,
you're a beast.
This will not do.
Is there anything more exciting?
Is this not exciting enough?
It doesn't make any sense.
Is Dr. Ling unwilling?
It's not that.
The problem is with me.
How is the problem
with you, Ms. Lu?
Can you?
Of course,
I can't.
Ms. Lu,
you have a serious problem
which could not be solved
by the books.
So what am I supposed to do?
How about
asking for help from someone else?
If I could find someone else,
why did I ask you?
If you don't ask someone else,
how do you know for sure
it's your problem?
Well, who am I gonna talk to?
Ms. Lu.
I didn't know you had important business.
Well, I'll come back later.
What are you doing here?
Ms. Qin of Jiang Cheng Group
will be here soon.
[LM Deer Sing Group]
Yujiang.
Ms. Qin of Jiang Cheng Group.
Who is that?
This is Ms. Qin of Jiang Cheng Group?
Director Lu's ex...
fiancee?
She's so tall,
yet she's wearing high heels.
That must be expensive.
Perfect figure, pretty face.
And her presence
is almost like that of Ms. Lu.
Qin Yujiang, and Cai Siyu.
Only our names are similar.
It's god's will.
I heard you just got back today,
and you came here
right after you got off the plane.
You're so hardworking.
Not as good as you.
You're running Deer Sing alone.
You even used your marriage
as a marketing stunt.
I hadn't come back in time,
or I would have witnessed it.
This time you've come to us
for the production lines.
It must be
for Infinity, I presume.
Yujiang,
you really know a lot
about our Deer Sing.
You're an important client of Jiang Cheng.
Knowing about the Deer Sing
means we're taking you seriously.
I will be responsible
and follow up on
this production line in person.
Isn't that a little
unnecessary?
You're so busy.
Why do you have to do everything yourself?
If I don't do this,
how could we show that
we value Deer Sing?
I know that Lu Yiyao is back.
Now he is chiefly in charge of
your product development.
I'll talk to him.
I know Infinity
the best.
Talk to me. It's more direct.
Lu Fangning.
I won't talk to you.
I only talk to Lu Yiyao.
[Qin Yujiang]
Never mind.
If you don't want to see her,
just forget it.
No problem.
She won't make a fuss
out of nothing.
I'll do it.
Uncle.
Why did you break up
with her back then?
Why did you suddenly
decide to go abroad?
All these years,
neither Qin Yujiang
nor you have mentioned anything.
I'm not being nosy.
I only care about you.
If you really don't want to talk about it,
I can understand.
We...
We just found that
we weren't suitable for each other.
You were together for two years,
and right when you were
about to get married,
you found that you were not compatible
with each other?
Sometimes,
it only takes one moment to
realize that.
Okay, I give up.
Relationships are so confusing.
Let alone someone else's.
But if it's truly
like you said,
Qin Yujiang is not sentimental,
that will be good.
The main product of Infinity
this time is
so special.
If we can't get
Jiang Cheng's support,
I'm gonna have a headache.
I won't let that happen.
I'll take care of everything for you.
Alright, don't worry.
I've made a contingency plan.
I just
don't want things
to come to that.
I've already contacted
Ms. Qin's office
for many times.
She's either in a meeting,
or out of the office.
I suspect
they don't even want to work with us.
Give me the card.
Hi, I'm the director of
the Business Development Department
from Deer Sing Group, Lu Yiyao,
May I speak to Ms. Qin, please?
Hi. I'm so sorry.
Ms. Qin is out of the office currently.
Can I help you with anything?
May I take down your message?
I'll let her know when she gets back.
No, thanks.
Can't reach her, right?
I'll keep trying.
You'll have to reach her someday.
I don't believe Ms. Qin
could just disappear.
If you approve, director,
I'm gonna go to her company
and wait for her.
Director,
you and Ms. Qin have known each other
for years.
Don't you have her personal phone number?
She didn't pick up the calls
in the office.
Perhaps she'll answer her private calls.
This is business.
If she doesn't answer a business call,
she definitely won't answer private calls.
Stupid.
Hello.
It's me.
Lu Yiyao.
Director Lu.
I've been waiting for your call.
I'd like to meet you sometime.
And we could talk about
the cooperation between
Deer Sing and Jiang Cheng.
Okay.
Let's meet over lunch.
By the way,
I have one request.
Name it.
How romantic.
Isn't this Director Lu?
I never thought
he'd do something like this.
Look, so handsome.
Who's so lucky? He's so handsome.
Who's so lucky?
I'm so jealous.
Learn from him, okay?
Flowers?
We're about to get into
the main storyline?
But,
why is he standing in the lobby
with two bouquets of flowers?
That's lovely.
I'm embarrassed.
How do you feel?
Standing in the lobby alone
with two bouquets of flowers,
isn't it good?
As long as you are happy.
However,
I don't like
this kind of flower anymore.
The colors are too boring.
It doesn't really go with me now.
Well, then,
what kind of flowers does Ms. Qin like?
I'll buy it next time.
Of course, you will.
Siyu, why you are still here?
Don't look at me. Just go.
Now, may I take Ms. Qin
for a meal now?
Of course.
Please.
Throw it away.
It's all right. Go eat.
Okay, bye.
What a waste.
Threw away such perfect flowers.
And the trash can downstairs
could only take dry waste.
I've done my bit
to keep our company clean.
That's basically the same as
you bought me flowers.
Cai Siyu,
who bought you flowers?
Come on.
Didn't you go downstairs for lunch?
Did you go to buy flowers instead?
I just picked it up.
I see.
Who is so rich
to put such a bunch of flowers there
waiting for you to pick it up.
How was I supposed to know that?
Director Lu bought it.
Well, he's certainly rich.
You wouldn't admire Director Lu,
would you?
I...
Really?
-You...
-Alright, I admire him.
I admit that.
What? Can't I?
Of course, you can.
You're not the first one
and you won't be the last.
Don't take
hopeless things so seriously, okay?
Bye.
I'm just gonna be the last one.
For dessert,
we have mango pudding
and chocolate mousse.
Which one do you prefer?
Mango pudding for two.
Alright, please give me a moment.
I know you like
mango pudding.
Yujiang,
Deer Sing needs
Jiang Cheng's production line.
These two companies
have been doing well together.
But, it has been a long time
and you still haven't signed the contract.
I want to know
what else do you want?
I'll move forward with the partnership.
-Okay.
-But,
you don't like
things you can get easily.
Besides this meal,
shouldn't you have something else
to offer?
The prices we set couldn't be changed.
Deer Sing can make certain compromises
to Jiang Cheng.
As soon as you come up with a plan,
we'll consider taking it.
We do need some new plans.
I understand that Jiang Cheng
hasn't got big projects
in recent years.
Deer Sing can ensure that
in the next few years,
you'll have a steady start-up rate.
A partnership like this
is a rare opportunity for you.
-Enjoy it.
-Thank you.
For you,
I'm just a business partner?
I think
we're still friends.
You think?
Lu Yiyao, you've always thought
that you know me well.
There's so much
you don't know about me.
You don't know that
I never like mango pudding.
You don't know that I like flowers,
but I don't like your attitude
when you send me flowers.
You don't know where I am,
whether I'm busy or hungry.
You never care.
You were just following
your standards
and playing the perfect fiance.
Weren't you?
Excuse me, Director Lu.
I have an appointment today
with Golden Horse Furniture.
Mr. Zhang's called me many times.
If I don't go, he'll feel offended.
We all don't want
to offend anyone in business.
Yujiang.
I'll give it to you
whatever you want.
I don't want our relationship
to affect the cooperation
between Deer Sing and Jiang Cheng.
Infinity
is important to Fangning.
After all these years,
you still care about her so much.
I'm sorry.
Let's call off the engagement.
As long as you wish,
you could use any excuse
to tell the public.
I'm sorry.
The number you dialed is
busy now.
Sorry.
The number you dialed is
busy now.
Sorry.
The number you dialed is
busy now.
Please try again later.
Clean up the room.
Lu Yiyao and I
will cancel our engagement.
Lu Yiyao.
Why do you think
I can handle all of this?
Why should I have to
be decent and sensible?
It's unfair.
You're the only one who's calm.
Fangning.
Let's have dinner tonight.
Bring your husband along.
I didn't make it
to your wedding.
Think of it as a celebration.
Okay, see you tonight.