What's hidden in this room?
He never lets me near it usually.
This...
This is his master?
I really
do look exactly like her.
Yaoyang.
What...
What just happened?
[Immortal Beyond Dust]
[Episode 16]
I can't find the Shadow Moon Pendant.
The fiendish aura of Xieyun
will soon be detected
by the immortal sects.
I need to think of another way
to suppress the fiendish aura.
[Soul-Mixing Pill]
The Soul-Mixing Pill
can suppress the fiendish aura.
Refining it requires
nurturing the Soul-Mixing Herb
with the power of one's spirit.
What are you three standing here for?
Come taste my cooking.
- No, thanks.
I'm not here for your ingredients.
I just came to tell you
not to make dinner for me tonight.
You're not eating?
I don't have an appetite today.
I won't eat.
What?
You're not eating either?
What's going on?
None of them are eating?
Yaoyang.
Yuxun.
I've started fasting
for cultivation recently.
I won't eat.
Just so you know,
you don't need to
make food for me for the next few days.
Alright.
Something must have happened last night.
I missed all the fun.
Why do you have the curtain drawn
in broad daylight?
I...
I'm copying the mantra.
Can you leave?
Alright.
It's hard for a girl to bring it up.
I'd better go ask Little Fox.
Did you have a fight?
No.
Then why is the vibe so strange?
You still haven't answered me.
At this rate,
when will they ever fall in love?
Wan'er is waiting for me.
No way.
Looks like I'll have to step in.
Little Fox,
I already know.
There's something up
with the three of you.
How do you know?
I'm a one-of-a-kind mushroom
from ancient times.
A little calculation
and I know everything.
Forget it.
I can't think of anything else.
Anyway,
I can see right
through your little situation.
I think love between a man and woman
should be mutual.
You can't force it.
Did Miss Ruoxi
reject you?
She didn't say it outright,
but I can feel that she...
She's a girl!
What matters most to a girl?
Reserve.
How could a girl
just say she likes you out loud?
If the one she loves isn't me,
I can't save her.
When did Miss Ruoxi
reject you?
I think
she likes you.
Really?
After I gave her that book
"Neither Red nor Green",
wasn't she pretty eager
to learn from you?
How can you miss
such an obvious hint?
What hint?
What does making her love me
have to do with that book?
Do I really have to spell it out?
It's...
You two have to...
You know,
that.
That.
You still don't get it?
Let me be straight with you.
Ruoxi was formed
from a wisp of Bai Xiyin's remnant soul.
She was born with an incomplete nature.
Only through dual cultivation
with the one she loves
can she become whole
and restore her soul.
What did you say?
Dual cultivation...?
Why are you only telling me this now?
How was I supposed to know
you'd be so clueless?
Usually, when two people are in love,
that kind of thing
just happens naturally.
But
I think her heart belongs to Yaoyang,
not me.
He's not an option.
Why not?
I said he's not an option,
and that's it.
Anyway, you need to act fast.
Otherwise,
Miss Ruoxi's life might be in danger.
How much time do I have?
Less than a month.
But dual...
That kind of thing
requires mutual consent even more.
How could it be forced?
Miss Ruoxi was born
with an incomplete nature.
How could she understand romantic love?
You need to
take the lead on this.
You should really read that book
"Neither Red nor Green".
I'll lend you a hand
when it counts.
I made you this soup with the finest
worry-dispelling herbs.
How can you drink it now?
I don't have
an appetite anyway.
This soup is meant to ease your worries.
I
have no worries!
Your worries
are written all over your face.
Is it because of that man?
Has he been
cold to you lately,
and you're
feeling a bit resentful?
I knew it!
That's not it at all!
Maybe he's been distant
for his own reasons.
This is exactly when
you shouldn't give up.
If you two miss your chance now,
you might regret it
for the rest of your life.
So serious?
Of course.
I had a friend.
She fell deeply in love with a man.
But because of some misunderstandings,
they ended up apart.
In the end,
they were separated forever.
So hard.
I can't think of anything else.
So,
maybe
I've been too harsh on Yaoyang?
What if
the person he likes
is someone similar to me,
but not me?
What then?
Everyone has a past.
You can't cling to the past forever.
That only hurts each other.
If you go on like this,
you'll end up like my friend,
filled with lifelong regret.
Actually,
come to think of it,
he's usually
quite good to me.
Maybe
I really am being
too stubborn?
Romantic love
is an art.
It's just that you haven't learned
the skills of courtship yet.
So you've gone astray.
What skills?
Don't tell me you haven't read
that book I gave you.
Every time
I show that book
to Tu Jing,
his face turns bright red.
He even avoids me.
So...
I could tell right away
it wasn't going anywhere.
Listen,
some men
like women to be forward,
while others
prefer them reserved.
Men can change.
Today
you might like this type,
tomorrow
you might be drawn to another.
So
you really need to be observant.
That's the way
to capture a man's heart.
Sounds
complicated.
Put simply,
do the opposite.
When he says "no",
it means "yes".
When he says "yes",
well,
it still means "yes".
Do you get it?
So
which is it,
"no" or "yes"?
Little Fox, a grown man,
can't swallow his pride.
I guess I'll have to let Miss Ruoxi
take the lead.
Alright,
come with me to a place.
Once we get there,
you'll know what to do.
What place?
You'll know when we get there.
But I'm telling you,
this stays between us.
You absolutely can't tell those two.
Okay.
Let's make a pinky swear.
Pinky swear.
I promise I won't tell anyone.
[Yingchun Pavilion]
We're here.
Sir,
is this your first time here?
Let's go.
Come on, Xiaotaohong.
Sir, please come in.
Sir.
I'll wait for you upstairs.
What is this place?
These women
are masters of romance.
They excel at capturing a man's heart.
You'll need to
pay close attention and learn.
I
think I'll just head back.
You're already here.
You need to learn a trick or two
before you go.
Let's go.
Come on.
Ruhua.
I'm leaving this to you.
Sure. No problem.
Pay close attention.
I'll come check on you later.
Where are you going?
Xiaotaohong, here I come!
Come on.
Learn from me.
First,
your gaze at a man
has to be captivating.
Start
by looking him straight in the eyes.
Then lower your head.
Put on a shy expression.
Men love this look the most.
That looks like
you're rolling your eyes.
Head.
Lower your head a bit.
Alright,
let me teach you another pose.
Did you learn it?
This seems simple.
Let me try.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
- I'll be gentle.
- It's fine.
Let me give it a try.
Like this.
Like this?
Pretty close.
You drink wine
like this.
Let me try.
Like this?
This...
Yes, that's it.
Just like that.
But...
But what?
Your makeup isn't quite right.
I need to redo it for you.
Miss Ruhua's skills are truly excellent.
You look like a completely new person!
This...
Does it really look good?
You wouldn't understand.
Men love this.
This outfit is too uncomfortable.
I'd rather change out of it.
A man and a woman
alone in a room.
Plus this love-inducing incense.
They'll definitely
cross that final line
Will it be enough?
That should do it.
♪What is flickering?♪
♪Shining, delicate, and bright♪
♪Like a trace of bitterness in a smile♪
♪What is falling?♪
♪Clean, precise, and light♪
♪Like enduring too many farewells♪
♪When petals drift down♪
♪When the rain falls all around♪
♪I gaze into your eyes♪
♪Beyond the dunes♪
♪No end in sight♪
♪I am like a mayfly♪
♪I won't ask what the future holds♪
♪Nor will I run away♪
♪Through all seasons by my side♪
♪Searching for sparks in the dust♪
♪What is flickering?♪
♪Shining, delicate, and bright♪
♪Like a trace of bitterness in a smile♪
♪What is falling?♪
♪Clean, precise, and light♪
♪Like enduring too many farewells♪
♪When petals drift down♪
♪When the rain falls all around♪
♪I gaze into your eyes♪