May you rest in peace.
What are you on about?
Do I look dead to you?
Please take this opportunity
to reflect on your life.
Hey.
Are you making fun of me?
Just you wait
until I get back up.
I sure hope you get back up.
Don't touch me. Just leave, will you?
You crazy bastard!
How many times have I told you
not to ride your motorcycle drunk?
Apparently, a fall like this
would have killed your average man,
but I came out relatively unscathed
because I broke the fall by rolling.
Filming's meant to start on Monday!
Per the contract, you owe us for damages.
Just push filming back a few days.
Broken bones always heal fast
in my family.
I just need a few days, okay?
The doctor said 12 weeks for recovery!
Everything in life happens for a reason.
Just shoot it later.
Much later.
She's right.
Just shoot it later. Much later.
You're out, dimwit.
We'll be filming as planned,
so stay on schedule, okay?
What are you on about?
Your lead actor's injured.
Yeah, what are you on about?
Don't overthink this.
The plan was to film what we can
while editing the script.
Hey, didn't you hear me?
How do you plan to shoot a film
without the lead?
Use a stand-in for the whole thing?
Yeah, how?
That would be ludicrous.
I am the heart and soul of Madame Aema.
Will you quit butting in?
And why would you be the heart and soul
of Madame Aema, you crazy bastard?
What? "Crazy bastard"?
You crazy bitch.
Think you're the heart and soul
of Madame Aema?
It ain't you either, crazy bitch!
You're just a crazy bitch,
you crazy bitch!
This can be easily resolved
by finding a new actor.
We just need to focus and stay on course.
Got that?
President Ku.
Since it's come to all this,
why don't you just
drop me from the film too?
Look, Ms. Jeong Hee-ran.
Why do you keep putting your hands on me?
Could you please try
to keep things professional?
You dare
use force on an actress?
You crazy…
You're no actress, you crazy bitch!
You're just a crazy bitch,
you crazy bitch!
He's right! You're just a crazy bitch,
Shut the hell up, you crazy bastards!
COMPLETE BED REST
Just shut the hell up, all of you!
You're all driving me crazy!
Focus? You want me to focus right now?
Did you say we'll film as planned?
I wrote the lines and did everything
as the actor asked,
only for him to break every bone
in his body right before the shoot.
The government's riding me
to revise the script,
breathing down my neck
and making me take out the sausage!
The producer wants more breasts,
but we can't actually show any breasts,
so they're meant to be subtly bare.
What am I meant to…
What even is this?
What is it?
What do you want from me?
AEMA
FILMING CREW
MADAME AEMA
PRODUCTION VEHICLE
-Nice!
-My, that's refreshing.
Feels great.
That's nice.
Thirty-six counts
of inappropriate subject matter.
Salaciousness, obscenity, degeneracy…
Fuck.
AEMA CHOOSES HERSELF
TO SEEK INDEPENDENCE
WITH ERIKA'S INFLUENCE
We're finally filming tomorrow.
How do you feel?
Why did you cast me for this role?
I don't know.
I guess the thought just came to me
the moment I first saw you.
"Oh…"
"She's the one."
Because of my breasts?
When I was little…
I was the only girl in our hometown
to hit puberty.
My breasts were constantly
the talk of the town.
"They're bigger today."
"They're smaller today."
Everywhere I went, I always slumped over
and looked down at my feet.
Getting so much attention
for my breasts made me feel guilty.
Who knows why I felt that way?
I don't care
if you cast me for my breasts.
Let's be honest.
Breasts like these deserve
some screen time.
And it's about time
these breasts did me some good.
We can't bare your breasts anymore.
The government won't allow it.
Then how are we going to film
those scenes?
Well…
it's like this.
We can't actually show your breasts,
but we'll be subtly alluding
to your breasts
so that it's no different
from actually showing your…
I'm still working on it.
I'm okay with that.
No matter what happens, I believe in you.
So whatever you come up with,
I'll be okay with it.
I'll do whatever you say.
All right!
Thank you for getting here.
Now go back.
What?
Drop this off at the Ministry of Culture
and Public Information tomorrow.
It's urgent, so no detours.
But…
MADAME AEMA FINAL DRAFT
SHINSUNG PICTURES
"On this day,
the day of the Horse and Snake,
in the year of the White Rooster,
I, Kwak In-u,
director of the film Madame Aema,
shall make this plea."
"Please watch over
our entire cast and filming crew
for the entire duration of filming,
and let our film, Madame Aema,
be showered with love from the public
until the very day it leaves theaters."
"Please ensure
a smooth and peaceful production."
"Spirits of the heaven and earth,
please accept our offerings."
Fire!
Stomp it out.
-Hurry.
-Ung-bae, get over here.
Coming!
-Put it down here.
-Wouldn't it obscure the shot?
-Bring it here.
-I'll move that, sorry.
-What a view.
-Let's get going.
All right. Let's move it.
Let's go.
Hey, move it.
Here's the new script.
Memorize it. You've got 15 minutes.
Sorry? But…
There are a lot of changes,
so make sure you've checked them.
New script.
We'll be shooting in 15 minutes.
Scene 135, take one.
And go!
Erika.
Aema… are you out of your mind?
Have you forgotten what your husband
did to you all these years?
How could you even consider
going back to him?
You're forgetting about
the thing that matters most.
I'm talking about
you.
Are you really going to give up
on your life as a woman?
-Answer me.
-Answer her.
Answer me, Aema.
Say something!
I may be
a woman,
but I'm sorry, Erika.
Before anything else,
I'm the woman of a man.
I'm his…
his…
Wife! You're his wife, damn it!
Reshoot the part she just butchered.
I'm going to continue.
Get a grip.
By letting a man
control your life like that,
you've made a mockery of me.
Not just me,
but all of us.
Erika…
Cut!
Come on, what the hell was that?
You don't know your lines,
and your delivery was flat!
I'm sorry.
I haven't gotten used to my lines yet.
No, that's not it.
This isn't about
getting used to your lines.
You need to embody Aema and speak as her.
Am I good to go?
Yes, you were great, Hee-ran.
It seems she's nervous,
today being her first day and all.
Isn't today everyone's first day here?
Like I said,
she simply doesn't have
what it takes to make it big.
Use a stand-in.
What's a stand-in?
A replacement.
A replacement for whom?
Aema, are you out of your mind?
Have you forgotten what your husband
did to you all these years?
How could you even consider
going back to him?
You're forgetting about
the thing that matters most.
I'm talking about you!
You are really
going to give up on your life
as a woman?
Answer me. Answer me, Aema.
-Answer me, Aema.
-Answer her.
I said answer me.
What's this? What are we going for here?
I have no idea. Only Mr. Paul knows.
So you're telling me
this is what Mr. Paul wants?
If you're here to see Hee-ran,
you can't right now.
I said no, didn't I?
Oh, come on…
You really can't.
You really shouldn't go there.
You really shouldn't go up there.
You can't!
Didn't I say not to let just anyone up?
He did stop me.
I forced my way through.
You don't like me, do you, Hee-ran?
It can't be helped. I can deal with that.
But you must have had
a first day on set too.
For me, that was today.
I'm not any good yet,
but I'm trying my best.
Because I want to get good.
That's the problem.
The misguided notion
that hard work will make you good.
It's not like acting
is the New Village Movement.
When an actor tries too hard…
it's tacky.
Then again,
I guess that would suit you better.
Fucking bitch.
Head to the market now
and buy a fresh ginseng gift set.
FILM MODIFICATION DECLARATION
-The fattest, most expensive one.
-Okay.
Go.
MINISTRY OF CULTURE AND PUBLIC INFORMATION
Your cigarette.
You'll make it smell like smoke.
Let's see.
Like this…
Let's emphasize those curves.
It's Madame Aema.
All right.
Aema's here for acupuncture treatment.
The blind acupuncturist
starts treating her.
While undergoing treatment,
Aema feels a strange pleasure
along with the pain.
Erika.
Erika?
You, Erika,
immerse yourself in those sensations
with Aema as you watch it all unfold.
Did everyone get that?
-Let's go.
-Okay.
I should feel it too?
But I'm taking notes.
Okay, in that case,
just feel it on the inside.
Let's focus on the rehearsal!
All right. Ready?
Go!
Hey, Aema shouldn't be lying
like a corpse!
Savor every poke.
Savor it?
Don't look at me.
You squirm in pleasure.
You're getting all turned on.
Why are you actually turned on?
What do you think?
The breasts are staring a little too hard.
Can't we just put a bra on her?
Who wears a bra while they're getting
acupuncture? Should we flip her around?
Then it would seem like
we're trying to hide them.
That's true.
Don't you need to be
face down for acupuncture?
You don't needle chests.
Why not?
You can needle your chest if it hurts.
Hang on a minute.
Would showing one breast
also be a violation?
Maybe it's okay
as long as we don't expose both.
Didn't they say how many breasts
we're allowed to show?
What do you mean, how many breasts?
It's just no nipples.
Right.
So not a single nipple?
Okay, now give me ecstasy.
All right, love it.
Now pain, then elation!
Now, pain!
Okay, now ecstasy!
But I already did ecstasy.
Now let's go to Erika. Erika!
Erika.
Hee-ran.
Is something bothering you?
I just don't get this situation.
What do you mean?
Why is she getting so turned on
by acupuncture?
What is she, some acupuncture fetishist?
The scene is meant to show that pain
and pleasure are actually the same thing.
What are you talking about?
How is pain the same as pleasure?
You know what? Forget it.
It's not like I'm the one acting it out.
"Erika observes Aema
and shares her pain and pleasure."
Why am I feeling anything?
"Erika licks her lips with her tongue."
"She starts getting turned on."
Why am I getting turned on?
Why am I sitting around like an idiot,
watching, feeling, and getting turned on?
How am I meant to play this?
I got the idea from ero guro nansensu.
Stuff that's erotic and grotesque
but also nonsensical.
Like a blend of sweet,
salty, spicy, and sour.
The yin, yang,
and five elements of sex are--
Director.
You can't convince me, can you?
Hee-ran.
This scene
will be iconic
and come to represent Madame Aema.
Those are your aspirations.
I asked you how I should play this.
Please don't change the subject.
Do you know how torturous it is
for actors to play a role they don't buy?
Director.
We'll shoot this scene
when you're ready to convince me.
Yeong-bae, start the car.
Script, wallet, handkerchief…
Oh, the script.
Wait.
How can you just walk out like this?
If you hate both me and this film,
why are you even shooting it?
How bold of you.
Are films just a paycheck to you?
You're a real bitch, you know that?
Fine.
Keep working hard.
Tacky or not,
it suits you as you are right now.
Trust in the director,
trust in the script,
and keep doing your best.
But there will come a time
when, no matter how hard you try,
you just won't buy it.
A time when even the director fails
to convince you.
What will you do then?
Will you keep giving it your all
even when you don't buy it?
What will you even work hard at
when none of it makes sense to you?
Quit whining and ask yourself
what it is you're demanding of me.
And,
since you know I'm a bitch now,
stop these clumsy attempts
to look like you're a bitch.
Before I truly…
beat the shit out of you.
Let's wrap things up and head out.
I'll give you the new schedule
when it's ready.
Okay.
-Coming through.
-Good work, everyone.
-We need to tear this whole part down.
-Let's hurry up.
Director.
Listen,
I'm giving this film everything I've got.
I need you to know what that means.
In return…
you need to make me believe in you.
I'll be going now.
MADAME AEMA
SHIN JU-AE
IF I'M GOING TO BE A BITCH, MIGHT AS WELL
BE A BADASS BITCH LIKE JEONG HEE-RAN
You came, Aema.
Aema?
Seriously!
I told you to take off your underwear.
Any underwear marks
will keep us waiting all night.
I'm sorry.
It just felt weird
going commando by myself.
I try not to take my underwear off
when I'm outside.
Ever since I was little,
I've been rather sensitive
to cold temperatures.
Make a fist for me.
Okay.
That's your genitalia.
Including your scrotum, okay?
Genitalia, including the scrotum.
Hand me your fist.
Do this.
Then, taking your size into account,
trim the parts that stick out like this
with scissors.
But don't cut against your skin,
or it's another all-nighter.
Wrap it around properly,
separating the scrotum from the body.
Especially down here.
That part's out of view,
so stick it down well or it'll come off.
You can do it yourself, right?
I guess you might have a hard time
managing by yourself.
Hey, I heard you wanted to see me.
Have you found a workaround?
What?
A way to subtly allude to my breasts
that's no different to actually showing…
Oh, that?
I've been discussing it
with the director of photography.
I've given it some thought, and…
what if it rains?
Rain?
Out of nowhere?
When it rains,
you get wet.
And what if we scrap everything else
so I'm just wearing this?
What? Just this?
When it rains,
you get wet.
It would be no different
to actually showing them.
Rain.
Assistant director. I need my AD!
Rain! I want rain!
Rain! Assistant director! Hey!
Back up.
Hold on. Wait!
-Rehearsal, go!
-A close-up of the face.
Let's see it from this side.
Lower your legs, you idiot.
As for you, stiffen your back.
Stay still.
The emotions are what matter here.
Emotions. The emotions.
Focus on the face.
-The face…
-Okay?
-We're all set, right? Okay.
-The face.
-We need more there.
-Do we have to keep going?
Keep going at it. Harder.
Don't look at me.
Lights! They're blinding me.
That's enough lightning.
-Save it for later.
-Yes. Sorry.
This scene is
what Aema's always dreamed of.
It's the moment she finally frees her body
from the shackles of the morals
that have bound her up until this point.
What matters most here is the orgasm.
How do you express an orgasm?
Don't you know what an orgasm is?
It's a burning sensation that shoots up
from the pit of your stomach,
travels up your spine, and makes you…
Right, and how am I
supposed to express that?
Are you still a virgin, Ju-ae?
Have you done it, Director?
How is that relevant?
You asked me first.
I've had instances
where my partner was trying their best,
and I felt as though
I should repay them somehow.
What do you do when that happens?
I hold my breath.
Your breath?
All right, ready!
Rolling.
Go!
Yun-ho.
Aema.
You came.
Now.
Oh God! Wait up!
Oh man, this is bad!
You idiot!
I didn't even call cut!
Are you out of your mind?
My apologies.
The cover fell off my privates.
Sorry.
He got hard.
Oh, to be young.
How was it? Was it any good?
It was amazing.
There sure are a lot of magpies
in this neighborhood.
What?
I've just noticed
a lot of magpies around.
Oh, magpies.
Magpies are
great.
I don't know what love is yet
You're the only one that I trust
Excuse me.
We're shooting a film here,
so thank you for not parking here.
Hey.
Yes?
We're here to see the director.
Is he in the middle of a shoot?
That's right, sir.
Then tell him to wrap it up
and get over here.
Sorry, sir. Could you repeat that?
Is this nutter for real?
You need some help understanding?
No, sir!
Get a load of that dumbass.
Hey, stop.
Cut! I mean…
Stop! Stop filming!
What the hell do you mean?
Who stopped the shoot?
They're from the ministry.
-The Ministry of Culture?
-I think so.
Get Seok on the phone.
-They were from the ministry, sir.
-Yeah?
-They had a ministry car and badges.
-What?
-Ministry suits.
-Were they actually ministry folk?
-The heck is going on?
Not at all.
If you would put in a call for us,
that would really help.
In that case, I'll give them a call.
-Thank you, sir.
-Sure.
I'll treat you
to something nice and fancy soon.
Thank you!
Hey, you're right on time. Take a seat.
The ministry sent people last night.
Apparently, they shut down the shoot
because we didn't make
the adjustments they demanded.
We did as they asked, okay?
We did everything they wanted
and expressed our gratitude.
The thing is,
no matter how much I reflect,
I can't tell what the problem was.
Could you look into it for me?
If filming is shut down for good,
Shinsung Pictures is as good as bust.
Help us out, will you?
What a life you've lived.
So the '70s were the golden days
of your life, President Ku.
Things are different now, aren't they?
Younger audiences are losing interest
in domestic films,
and every household has a color TV now.
People are forgetting about the perks
of going to the cinema to watch films.
Man, you must really be feeling the heat.
You film industry folk.
Such a shame, when we government men
should be looking out for you.
President Ku.
Where do you think
the '88 Olympics will be held?
Come on.
They're announcing it today.
Everyone seems so certain
that the honor will go to Seoul.
Thanks to that,
I've been working my ass off as of late.
A grand banquet
has been scheduled out of the blue.
The higher-ups are saying
we need some fresh meat this time.
That's easier said than done.
We all know the game.
Where can I find a fresh haul
when everything's already been tried?
Am I supposed to snatch people
off the streets?
I'm just kidding, by the way.
Of course Seoul's going to win
the Olympics bid.
God knows the Republic of Korea
has broken its back to host the Olympics.
Hard work always pays off.
It's as good as ours,
which is why we should prepare in advance.
If we just had the chance,
we filmmakers would love
to deliver our congratulations.
A while ago,
we held a huge press conference
for Madame Aema. Did you see it?
Did I
see it?
I've discovered a new actress.
Shin Ju-ae.
She may be a rookie,
but she's so dependable
that I felt confident casting her
as the lead in Madame Aema.
Highly dependable.
Well, she must be busy filming right now.
That's right.
Filming's on hold, isn't it?
Voting is underway to decide
the host city of the '88 Olympics…
Are you sure you submitted the documents
and script like I told you to?
Of course we did.
Why would we leave anything out?
And I slid them a little something.
Has it been announced?
Just give it some time, okay?
Did you skim some off the top?
You did, didn't you?
You skimmed some off the top
of the money we gave you.
Do you take me for some thug?
You fucking thief!
What the fuck are you going to do
about the shoot?
I did as told. What more do you want?
You're raising your voice at me?
You fucking snake!
-Are you kidding me?
-Wanna see me crack this bottle?
-You're cracking nothing!
-You fucker!
-Bring me soju!
-Did they just say Seoul?
I'll gut you from your fucking tongue
down to your belly
and brew snake wine out of you.
-You goddamn snake, you!
-The Olympics host city…
Seoul.
'88 OLYMPICS HOST CITY ANNOUNCEMENT
…will be Seoul.
The Olympics.
Hey.
They say that once we host the Olympics,
the Republic of Korea's GDP
will skyrocket.
And we will become
a fucking developed country.
What's GDP anyways?
I feel like this is my fault.
What do you mean?
I shouldn't have crossed
the ginseng's legs.
Maybe that jinxed us.
What are you even talking about?
Forget all that!
Go over there.
You're sober, aren't you?
Head across the street to Yangji Café.
Mr. Ku said he'd be there.
Grab him a meal if he hasn't eaten
and drive him around.
Ju-ae will be with him.
Welcome.
What are you talking about?
Like I said,
you've got great inherent moxie.
All right.
Let me break things down for you.
The grand banquet
is a great celebration held
by the most powerful people in the nation.
Not just anyone gets to go,
so it's a great honor
for a rookie like you just to be invited.
You've got nothing to lose.
It's to celebrate hosting the Olympics,
so it's going to be one happy party.
Besides,
one could argue
that as the lead of our film,
you're responsible for its success.
You get me, right?
For you to live, the film must live.
The fate of the film and your own
lies squarely in your hands. Got that?
GREAT FORTUNE WILL COME
IF YOU WORK WITH YOUR SENIOR
That's an awfully elegant way
of begging me to save your skin.
What?
Why should I bear all the responsibility
when you never shared any authority?
You're the boss. I simply work for you.
You need to take the coward's way out
but want to save face.
Pick one and stick to it.
Okay.
I guess I was euphemizing
to soften the blow.
You've got squat.
No authority, no nothing.
Just go.
Forget about it.
That's not your job.
You're not seriously
thinking about going?
Ju-ae.
He says I just need to impress
some higher-ups and drink with them.
It's no big deal.
So you're going?
You're seriously gonna go?
Is this an easy choice for you?
How can you come to a conclusion
so quickly?
You know what an opportunity
this film is for me
and why I'd do anything to protect it,
even if I have to get my hands dirty.
Should I go home and wither to death
working in yet another kitchen?
Would that be right?
I have no idea
what lies ahead of me.
I only know
that I don't want to give in or back down.
That's all I know right now.
Take them off.
Don't make me repeat myself.
Everything.
Come in.
From the moment
you step inside,
the things you see,
the things you hear,
the things you smell,
and whatever you may be put through
go with you to your grave.
If you so much as speak of,
hint at,
or even whisper to yourself
about what may happen today,
you're a dead woman.
And it won't just end with your death.
Everyone around you will die as well.
WRITTEN OATH
I AGREE NOT TO SPEAK ABOUT…
OCTOBER 1, 1981
UNDERSIGNED SHIN JU-AE
Now then,
from this moment on,
smile.
The morning rain pitter-patters on my face
Choo, choo, the sound of its horn lingers
As the early train goes on its way
But I still love him so
Where should my heart go now?
THIS SHOW IS A WORK OF FICTION
INSPIRED BY THE PEOPLE INVOLVED
IN MAKING THE 1982 FILM "MADAME AEMA"
ALL CHARACTERS AND STORYLINES
HAVE BEEN CREATED
SOLELY FOR DRAMATIC STORYTELLING PURPOSES
Subtitle translation by: Jimin Choi