[sensual music playing]
That was fun.
You enjoying yourself?
Why, you must be over the moon right now.
Since everything's been going your way,
hasn't it?
Every year, for the last ten or so,
hundreds of you come here
dreaming of becoming Jeong Hee-ran,
the next "it" girl, right?
They all fail.
I'm not going anywhere, honey.
Hundreds of girls
fade back into obscurity.
You must think you're special.
I'll tell you now that you're not.
You'll fail and go back to being a nobody
without ever even knowing the reasons why.
Look at me.
I'm Jeong Hee-ran.
I don't care how desperate you are.
You'll never be me, so don't even bother.
[footsteps retreating]
[Hee-ran] You can leave now.
Hey.
I said you can leave.
[Ju-ae sniffs]
Sure, I'll leave.
I'd like the opinions
of the other judges before I go though.
DIRECTOR KWAK IN-U
[loud clapping]
There's that "it" factor!
What you said earlier. Hmm?
That girl's got some spunk in 'er!
One thing's for certain,
this lovely little lady's
our hot new siren of the silver screen!
- [chuckles]
- [scoffs]
[thumps table]
I spent the past few weeks…
searching everywhere for this woman.
And even if you were to kick her out now,
well, I-- I'd do it all over.
I'd just find her and bring her back.
[disco music playing]
You're all morons. [scoffs]
Yeah! Ooh, lookin' good!
Hey! Get over here, Director.
Get in the picture!
- This'll be in the history books.
- Right. Great.
Over here, c'mon.
- All right, everyone.
- [Gi] All right, let's go. The final shot!
Big toothy smiles!
And say, "Madame Aema"!
Madame Aemaaaaaa!
[music intensifies]
AEMA
[music fades]
[Gi] As you're under contract
with the studio,
you'll live in places like this
from now on.
It's more fitting.
You're a star now.
Be sure to remember that.
[water stops]
Are there, uh, any open positions?
LET US LIVE LIKE HUMAN BEINGS!
LABORERS DESERVE RESPECT TOO
WE ARE NOT MACHINES!
LET'S MAKE A NATION FOR THE WORKERS
OUR DEMANDS
1. REASONABLE WORK HOURS
[Ju-ae] Geun-ha.
[whimsical music playing]
- [Geun-ha squeals softly]
- [laughs]
I signed a contract. They even got me
an apartment, so it's "official" official.
You should work with these guys.
I asked them, and they said
the head of production needs an assistant.
What about the girls?
They'll still be stuck there.
Chungmuro's a place
full of fuckin' snakes,
and… I can't do this on my own.
They say it's a new era.
And that means
new beginnings for both of us.
Geun-ha…
I'm heading into war here.
[lighter pings, ignites]
- [Hee-ran] The early termination fee.
- [lighter clicks]
[exhales] It's even more
than our initial agreement.
- [scoffs]
- So let's part ways.
End on good terms.
You're incredibly predictable,
you know that?
I already broke things off once
because it's what you wanted.
Ms. Jeong Hee-ran,
it's unfortunate that
business transactions would be useless
if there weren't any penalties
for the other party breaking the rules.
It's how the law works.
So, if you still wanna break things off,
then the early termination fee
is just gonna be the start, baby.
You think a termination fee would be
enough for me to walk away? Uh-uh.
Don't pick a fight with me.
Unless you want me to bleed you dry.
[sighs] You got one project left.
So just ride it out!
You can even close your eyes if you want,
like a good little girl.
And once that's done,
I'll dump you like you want, 'kay? C'mon!
[thoughtful piano music playing]
All right.
Let's just get one thing straight here.
Audiences turn up by the millions
to see my films in theaters.
I've won more awards
and accolades than I can count.
And every month,
I'm shooting a new commercial.
[Jung-ho gasps softly]
[moans shakily]
Am I making myself clear?
I'm adored by millions of viewers.
They can't get enough.
So, whatever happens,
I won't be the one that they turn on.
It'll be you.
Mm-hmm!
[music ends]
You, um,
the quiet type?
Yeah.
Great.
You start in the morning.
Huh?
Just remember this.
Everything you see and experience
from now on is top secret.
That's my only condition.
You don't get a salary.
But what you will make
is pretty dang good. Eh?
[poignant music playing]
SEOUL TEXTILE COMPANY
YEONG-JA'S HEYDAYS
[woman 1] Take care of yourself.
Stay safe out there.
- [woman 2] Don't skip any meals.
- [woman 3] You know our off days, right?
[woman 4] Don't go!
Let me give you my card.
Just give me a call if you need any help.
DEMOCRATIC PEOPLE'S VOICE
REPORTER YANG SEOK-WON
Don't forget about our fight over here.
You hear me?
And you…
go fight yours.
We'll fight together, 'kay?
- [woman 1] Have a safe trip, Ju-ae!
- [woman 2] Take care of yourself!
- [woman 3] Come by to visit, okay?
- [woman 4 cries]
[Geun-ha scoffs softly]
Here we are. Right up there, you see that?
It's on the third floor.
I bet you have
a pretty decent view from there.
Wow, you've made it.
SHINSUNG PICTURES
PRESIDENT KU JUNG-HO
MADAME AEMA
WRITTEN AND DIRECTED BY KWAK IN-U
[alarm beeping]
[grunting]
Mm.
Eh?
Wha-- what the…
what the hell is this shit?!
[beeping continues]
[sighs] It's a little early for this,
don't you think? Huh?
Mi-na! Get me outta here!
All this is nighttime stuff. I gotta go.
[Mi-na scoffs]
You bastard. Did you seriously forget?
- Whaa?!
- Someone needs a little reminder, huh?
- I'm an actor.
- [sighs]
- And you're dating me.
- Ah, s…
I know Aema needs a new lead,
so how come I didn't get an audition?!
You're a fucking asshole, you know that?
You disgusting son of a whore!
Mi-na!
- Look, nobody is right for everything.
- [erotic music playing]
But one day,
the right role is gonna come along.
[scoffs] You're so full of shit.
Oo--
Whoa-- Uh-- Hey, now!
- Mr. Ku Jung-ho…
- [moans nervously]
…did you think shacking up
with a 20-year-old aspiring actress,
brand-new to the city,
would come with no strings attached?
- [growls]
- [chuckles uncomfortably]
[laughs]
Ah, I get it, I get it!
Uh, fine. Go ahead, then.
- Uh!
- All done!
Huh?! [gasps]
- [laughs]
- What the hell?!
Ow!
Hey!
- Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! All right!
- [giggling]
What the hell is going on?
This is blackmail, honey.
- What?!
- Now, if you keep neglecting me…
That little photo?
I'll have it blown up and posted
in the busiest areas of the city.
- [sighs] This isn't happening.
- Here!
- Listen!
- Just like that!
- Say cheese!
- Cut it out, you crazy bitch!
- [laughing]
- I said let it go!
[Mi-na] Oh my God!
Uncuff me, goddammit!
- Peekaboo!
- No, what are you doing?! [grunts]
[music intensifies]
Untie me, damn it! I'm warning you!
Don't you dare! Pull it back up!
You tricky little fucker!
- [music intensifies]
- Go!
Go!
[Yeong-bae quavering] Noonaaaa!
[moans]
Noona!
I finally got it!
- [music stops]
- Yeah?
That's right!
- [whimpers]
- What?
Ah.
[papers rustling]
What you wanted from Kwon Do-il.
His screenplay! [panting]
PREDATION NIGHT
[optimistic music playing]
MADAME AEMA
[music fades]
You already read through it all?
B-- but how?
It's only been, like, three minutes.
Why is Aema tying a guy up
and using a whip all of a sudden?
It's from that Japanese smut
you've been watching. That hentai?
What man doesn't wanna be dominated
by a gorgeous lady?
You and Mi-na have never done
any domination role-play?
[Jung-ho inhales]
[sighs] I'm havin' a day,
so don't make me repeat myself.
Just go vanilla, got it?
Pants and panties off, then pecker out,
puts it in there, dong-dong-dong,
he comes, okay?
Are you kidding me right now?
The whole point was to showcase
sexual desire from a woman's perspective.
Then let her come too! I don't care!
Oh, and also,
three titty scenes are gone.
Explain that to me.
Yeah, I went over this with you before.
- There's a subtle way to--
- Subtle?
Yeah, screw that. Hey.
The audience wants sex,
so shove your subtlety you know where.
You wanna be subtle after casting a girl
with a rack made by the gods?
Are you crazy?
You'll see once you finally get
a taste of the money.
Flash a pair of breasts once
and you can afford a car.
A new house from the second pair.
And a third pair
will change your whole world.
Go back to the old one.
This one is trash.
Things are goin' great. Don't fuck it up.
[door slams]
DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
[Jung-ho] Of course!
You call the shots, Mr. Choi,
and I'll follow.
I'm on my way.
PRESIDENT'S OFFICE
I'm the director here!
It's ridiculous for you to ask
that I direct a project
I don't even believe in!
I had a vision for both Hee-ran
and Ju-ae's parts, all right?
'Cause I am the director here,
and you can bet that I know
how it should be, okay?
So enough!
I refuse to let you step
all over my vision!
Aema's mine to direct, is it not?
[breathes shakily]
You actually sound like a real director.
Hmm?
I believe in you.
Why else would I let you
direct the project?
The real situation here
is you don't believe in your producer.
If a little feedback is so difficult,
you're gonna have to find
a new project to work on.
[In-u sighs]
And Aema will find a new director.
A shame.
[gentle music playing]
PREDATION NIGHT
[phone ringing]
[Yeong-bae] Noona,
word is Director Kwon is headed
to his villa to revise the script.
The address is…
[music fades]
Not many people know of this place.
So, uh, how'd you find me here?
Director… I, uh,
need to apologize to you.
It's wrong, I know. But I…
I got my hands on your new screenplay.
What?
When I read your work…
[breathes shakily]
I don't even know.
I just had to come speak with you.
Please use me to help tell this story.
You won't be disappointed.
Well, to be honest,
I'm still rewriting it.
And besides that,
I'm not quite ready
to bring on anyone just yet.
I don't intend to pressure your process.
I can wait.
Just let me know
when you're ready, Director.
Didn't you announce recently
that for all projects moving forward,
you're no longer doing nudity?
I'm sure you know that
since you've read the script,
but this project isn't shying away
from nudity.
Let me be clear.
When I asked for you to use me, Director,
I meant it.
Use every inch however you want to.
When I was 20,
I began my career in this industry,
entirely focused on
increasing my celebrity rather than craft.
I became famous
without exercising my skill.
In my career…
I have experienced incredible success.
I never chose roles for the art.
I chose fame and celebrity status,
anything for the publicity.
Never before
have I felt this desperate
to play a part in any film, you know?
[sobs]
[Do-il sighs]
[music becomes apprehensive]
[Do-il] After an eternity
staring into the flickering embers…
[woman sighs]
…she slowly sits up.
Heavy rain drumming against her window.
[thunder cracks]
In fact, a vicious storm rages outside.
Yeah, that's good.
We see a close-up of her drenched feet
walking along the carpet.
SEEMINGLY DETERMINED,
SHE WALKS UP THE STAIRS
She ascends the stairs…
THE SOUND OF HER BEATING HEART
ENCROACHES LIKE A SHADOW
…and the closer she gets to the door,
the more I'm overcome
with increasing dread.
RIGHT OUTSIDE THE DOOR…
She's here.
Right outside that door.
[gasps] Ms. Su-jeong.
- [Su-jeong sobs]
- This…
is a story of love.
[both moan]
Ms. Su-jeong, we can't do this. No!
[gasps shakily]
Can you feel it? The beat of my heart?
When I asked you to use me…
I meant it.
Use every inch however you want to.
[Do-il] Her hands are cold.
[moaning]
Meanwhile, her heart is on fire.
A story of deep love and desperation.
Ms. Su-jeong. Don't!
[Su-jeong groans]
[Do-il] I fell in love first, but I…
was also the first to betray her.
[sobbing]
[panting]
[sighs]
[music fades]
As I said before,
this is a story of love.
[ethereal music playing]
The story of predation night,
fueled by desire,
marked the end of that love.
PREDATION NIGHT
[sighs softly]
THE END
[music fades]
[sighs]
Oh. So, listen, President Ku, I was…
[sighs softly]
I've reconsidered!
We just need to show her boobs, right?
If I do that, we can honor my screenplay?
Sure!
As long as it gets you horn-ay!
[woman 1] Young people these days.
- Disgusting!
- [woman 2] Goodness me.
- [woman 1] Ugh!
- He must not be right in the head.
[In-u sighs]
SHINSUNG PICTURES
- It's so nice to see you, Director.
- [man] Oh, hello.
[Jung-ho] Director!
Forgive me for not reaching out sooner.
It's been quite a while!
Long time no see, my friend.
Have a seat.
So, uh, how've you been, Director?
[elevator music plays in café]
Let's do a film together.
Wha-- [chuckling]
Yo! Ooooh!
PREDATION NIGHT
REVISED DRAFT
Oh, wow! Predation Night, huh?
I'm so humbled.
For real, though,
what an incredible honor.
Well, I guess you must think
I'm a half-decent producer now
if you're entrusting me
with a precious script of yours.
Do not misunderstand.
- Eh?
- What I want is Hee-ran.
Ah! [laughs]
She is still under contract
with your company.
Ah, well, you'd be right.
She's still all mine.
If I want her, you come as a package deal.
It's unfortunate.
Ah, well, no matter why you're here,
like I said,
I'm honored to be a part of it at all.
[sighs]
[erotic music playing]
PREDATION NIGHT
REVISED DRAFT
Director, what do you think about
making the budget bigger?
'Cause, as you know,
a bigger budget is a bigger picture.
Let me make some calls and arrange that.
What do you say?
Increasing the budget
will raise the stakes.
Let's just keep things as they are.
Director.
You and I both know Hee-ran is talented.
But would you ever consider
someone new instead?
And why would I bring on
an unknown talent?
I mean, c'mon. Can't you picture it?
Envision a fresh young face
breathing new life into your film.
Our audiences crave newness
and the unexpected.
And what's more,
she might even end up
serving as some kind of muse for you.
Sounds like you had
someone in mind already.
[Jung-ho] Mm-mm.
Well, since you mention it,
when I read it,
an actress did immediately jump to mind
that'd be absolutely perfect.
I told her to drop by and say hello.
I mean, the girl is already in the area.
What do you think, huh?
[chirpy music playing]
[man] 'Scuse me, miss.
Okay, good.
All right, looking great.
You look beautiful.
Okay! Gimme nostalgia.
Good. Incredible.
This time, give me a wistful look.
You have a story. All sorts of stories.
Your dreams are a balloon about to burst.
What's over there? Oh yeah.
HEE-RAN
CODE RED!
[man] Yes, yellow. Yellow.
You're just crazy for yellow.
Well! You are a vision!
Isn't she just adorable?
[laughing] This is Hwang Mi-na.
[Mi-na] Oh, can you get me
something to drink?
I'm so thirsty.
What do ya want?
A soda.
Hey! Can we get one soda?
So you're sleeping together, aren't you?
- What?
Yeah. I thought so.
I don't know if it's love necessarily.
But you're definitely sleeping together.
- [Jung-ho sighs]
- [Do-il] So…
[Mi-na scoffs]
…you want me to cast the broad you screw
instead of Jeong Hee-ran in the role?
This one here.
She's an up-and-coming actress
I discovered.
So treat her with some respect, Director.
I tell you I'm casting Jeong Hee-ran,
and so you decide to manipulate me
into casting your girlfriend?
What the hell's wrong with you?
All these years in the business
and you're still
just as utterly full of shit.
I'm the goddamn president of Shinsung,
Director. Come on now! [laughs]
And you there.
Miss Mi-na, wasn't it?
Look at you. You're barely 20 years old.
Why sleep with this asshole?
Did he say he'd make you a star?
Yeah.
I guess I'm just
a gullible dumb little bitch
so desperate that she had to resort
to grabbing a producer's cock!
Whoa, hey, take it easy! What the hell
are you doing? He's the director.
- That's not how you talk to him.
- Piece of shit.
- You should be taking my side here!
- Shut the hell up for once, okay?
Can you do that for me? Huh?
I see
you're still acting like a little shit.
Are you ever gonna grow up and get a grip?
Act your age!
Can't you use your head for once,
and stop thinking with your cock?
All right, enough!
How are you so insulting?
We can't act like teenagers.
We're a producer and director
meeting with each other.
Let's keep it professional here.
Well, I don't think
you have a leg to stand on.
You started this, asshole!
If there's anybody here who's responsible
for this shitshow, it's you, old man!
- What?
- You gotta come to your senses, Director.
C'mon, man, you're over 60!
You gotta lose that edgy auteur shtick!
What the hell did you say?!
You little punk!
- I dare you to say…
- Auteur!
[dramatic music playing]
Did you just hit me?
Why, you…
- I'll kill you, you bastard!
- Goddammit!
- [both groan]
- [Mi-na squeals]
[Jung-ho] Oh yeah! How you like that?!
Mi-na! Don't try to hold me back!
- Why would I hold you back, dumbass?
- [Do-il] That's right, princess.
[Jung-ho] Oh, for the love of…
You just had to learn the hard way!
You play with the bull,
you're gonna get the horns, old man!
[glass shattering]
[rhythmic thumping]
- [music fades]
- [Jung-ho and Do-il groaning]
[Yeong-bae] Noona! O-- o-- over here.
[off-the-hook phone beeping]
[Jung-ho] Uh, had enough yet, eh?
[Jung-ho and Do-il groaning]
[Jung-ho] Ouchie.
[weakly] Oh, my mouth. Fuck me.
Ah, what?
- [dish clatters]
- [Do-il] Damn it.
[zesty pop music playing]
LUCKY SEOUL
Whoo!
What's up, Kwak? Why the long face?
Do you think I'd be happier
if I switched to your job?
What?
How long does it take
to get as good as you?
You won't, buddy.
It's not a thing you learn.
You're born with it.
I'm kidding, man.
I learned everything
while playing a bartender in Lucky Seoul.
Sure, the film bombed, but, uh,
I got a fan base 'cause of it, so…
[laughing heartily]
One sec. Mwah!
[women screaming]
Director Kwak, you heard of this?
Undoing one button is nice.
Two is a tease.
Three, we're getting saucy.
And the fourth unbuttoned?
That's just hot!
[women screaming]
[shouting] About the film!
For Aema, we're…
[screaming continues]
Aema…
Aema just got done.
- I mean, the casting process.
- Uh-huh, right.
So I wanted to let you know
that production's about to start.
- So I'll have Seok--
- Whoo!
I'll be reaching out soon
to you through Seok!
- Yeah, he'll call!
- Mmm.
Mmm.
The girl needs a makeover.
We're gonna make her a star.
[jaunty music playing]
[man grumbles]
[grumbles]
Hmm.
[footsteps approaching]
[man grunts]
- Hmm!
- Who is that?
Some rookie actress
who just signed with Shinsung Pictures.
I've never seen her before.
- [Paul inhales deeply]
- Hmm.
[grunts]
[footsteps retreating]
We've done it.
[whimsical music playing]
[man] Ah.
Those are for Ms. Jeong Hee-ran.
You see, Mr. Goh always designs
custom outfits exclusively for her.
[fabric rips]
[music fades]
Testing, testing, one, two…
MADAME AEMA
PRODUCTION PRESS CONFERENCE
What is the total opposite of passion?
Anyone know?
Nothing?
How 'bout you go home
and ask your wives! [laughing]
Anyway… since I've received so much love
for my passion-filled acting
these last 20 years or so, I,
Heo Hyeok, would like to return the favor
with a love letter to the fans.
- Rest assured…
- [tense music fades in]
…Heo Hyeok, the stallion,
will grab the reins
and lead Aema to success.
Without further ado,
I'd like to hand the mic over
to the only goddess I worship,
more beautiful than a thousand sunsets.
Ms. Hee-ran?
Your turn.
[Hee-ran scoffs softly]
[music intensifies]
[man 1] All right, uh,
can you give us a "Madame Aema, hooray"?
[Jung-ho] Madame Aema!
- Hooray!
[man 2] Smile, Ms. Jeong Hee-ran.
Great. Looking great.
- [Hyeok laughing]
- [man 3] Ms. Shin Ju-ae!
- [bone crunches]
- [subdued squeal] Argh!
- [man 3] Ms. Shin Ju-ae!
- You psycho.
- [man 4] Back up a bit.
- [man 1] Smile, please.
- [Hyeok chuckles]
- [man 1] Everyone, look this way!
- What's your problem, crazy bitch?
- [man 1] Right over here. Right over here.
Now just the women alone.
Can we get the two of them?
[Hyeok muttering under breath]
[Ju-ae] You were great up--
[music ends]
[gasps]
- [footsteps retreating]
- [tense music playing]
[Hee-ran sighs loudly]
[inhales deeply]
[scoffs]
You know, dear,
my intention was
not to talk to you all day today.
What is this?
I can't believe what I'm seeing.
Paul most definitely made that dress.
He'd never design a silhouette
so vulgar and cheap.
So I guess this was your doing?
Why?
Are you so desperate for fame
that you feel compelled
to flash your tits around everywhere?
Your breasts need that much attention?
You can't be that crass.
Or are you perhaps worried
that your promiscuity will be overlooked?
It's not like that.
The look, I wasn't pulling it off.
And this here to you is pulling it off?
Paul Goh is a national treasure, okay?
Does your tiny brain comprehend
how disrespectful this is to his work?
I didn't mean to disrespect his work.
I'm very sorry.
But showing some cleavage
doesn't make me a slut.
[door opens]
[man] Good work out there.
You heading straight back?
Let's go outside.
[footsteps retreating]
[door bangs]
[music intensifies]
[Yeong-bae grunts]
[chuckles smugly]
Ah, that little bitch.
[Gi vocalizing]
[thumps chassis]
Was it you?
Huh?
Why did you take that bitch
to get a Paul Goh outfit?
Oh, uh, you mean Ju-ae?
Yeah, it was the president's idea.
Tell me, is your head inside your ass?
You should be doing
whatever's best for this cast and crew.
Do you think that girl's on my level?
That little bitch-ass can't remotely
pull off the same kinda outfit, you idiot!
Understood.
That little bumpkin went and destroyed
a one-of-a kind Paul Goh dress
'cause you decided to put her in something
extremely out of her league!
[Gi clears throat]
[Hyeok howling]
[energetic music playing]
Yeehaw!
- [Yeong-bae] Whoa!
- Oh my--
[Hyeok laughing hysterically]
[laughter continues]
[motorcycle retreats]
I swear to God!
- Am I the only one who isn't insane?
- [whimpering]
I was staring at Jeong Hee-ran.
She looked pretty hot.
[upbeat dance music playing]
What's new?
She is a babe.
And an asshole.
Yeah, that's what makes her so hot.
- [chuckling] Whoa! Hey there!
- [music stops]
Ms. Performer!
Ah, that's a bummer.
That hurts me.
Oh, come on, you don't recognize me?
I used to be a regular!
♪ Oh, here's to lasting… ♪
Huh? Huh?
[sniggering]
I knew you were too good
to waste away as a backup dancer.
And, hey, I was right. What do you know?!
[mystical ping]
You and I are gonna be great friends.
Congrats on the role.
Aema be seeing ya.
Huh? Oh? Ohhh!
- [laughs]
- [Ju-ae sighs]
Is he, uh… is he your boyfriend?
♪ Oh, here's to lasting Aema! ♪
[tense music playing]
♪ Oh, here's to a happy madame! ♪
[Geun-ha] Who was that fucker?
♪ Oh, here's to a good life ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
YEONBANG SPORTS
ENTERTAINMENT DEPT. LEAD, LEE JAE-GEON
MADAME AEMA
PRODUCTION PRESS CONFERENCE
ROOKIE ACTRESS TO STRIP DOWN FOR ROLE
[Paul scoffs] What on earth?
Why'd she butcher my outfit?
I'm not sure. I guess it's a means
of self-expression for her?
[Paul inhales, exhales impatiently]
[classical music playing in background]
[Paul groans]
[Paul] Hmm.
- Hmm.
They sense weakness. A horse
has to respect you before letting you on.
You have to show dominance.
'Cause otherwise,
if you show hesitation of any kind,
it'll throw you right outta the saddle.
I won't dominate another creature.
We have enough of that in the world.
What name does he go by?
Thunder.
[subdued piano music playing]
Thunder and I have got it from here on.
Huh? But you've never ridden before.
Yeah.
It's the first time we're meeting though.
We need to get to know each other.
Don't we?
Is that yummy, Thunder?
Isn't sharing a good meal together
a great bonding experience?
It's like we're a family.
[music becomes energetic]
[Ju-ae squealing joyfully]
Hello! [laughing]
Go, Thunder!
Faster! Go, Thunder!
Whoo! Giddyup!
Giddyup!
[In-u] What's this?
This is them butchering our script
before we even started filming.
That's what this is, Director.
We need to sign a memorandum
agreeing to their edits
before they let us begin,
so get over here.
For fuck's sake, treating us
like we're a couple of students.
[In-u] "Upon reviewing
your script submission of Madame Aema,
we have concluded the following problems
must be attended to."
[mischievous music playing]
INAPPROPRIATE SUBJECT MATTER
FOUND IN SCRIPT, TOTAL 36
[In-u] They want us to fix 36 things?!
I told them that we'll send
the revised version later.
Since filming's starting soon. [spits]
So we can at least get
the okay'd scenes outta the way.
We can't just film scenes
without the whole script being done.
They just punched 36 gaping holes
into our movie.
- It's like Swiss cheese now.
- [blows, spits]
[In-u sighs]
And here I thought this new government
wanted to try to foster
the new film industry.
So much for
"Screen, sex, and sports," huh?
These guys are no different
from the last. [sighs]
Argh! Goddammit!
God, you just had to shoot down
the revised script and-- Arghhh!
- [sighs]
- Take a good hard look.
Most of their issues
are with the scenes you wrote, wise guy.
[sighs]
[quirky electronic music playing]
Wha-- what's wrong with the sausage?
- I-- Do you think a sausage is "vulgar"?
- [sighs]
Are they, what--
afraid she'll shove it somewhere? Huh?!
Ah, and this?
Why do they want-- What about the horse?
'Cause Lady Aema just keeps horses.
That's her name, okay?
C'mon, she loves ponies,
but it's not sexual, right?
If that's obscene, then what's next?
While we're at it, let's ban bald heads
'cause they look like… the head of a cock.
Yeah. "Wear a hat!"
"Hey! There's children in here!"
The hell's wrong with these people?!
Are she, the horse, and the sausage
gonna bang in some perverted three-way?
I think they might be onto something.
I mean, horse cocks are pretty massive.
Oh Jesus Christ!
Don't tell me you're also on their side!
I'm on your side.
I'm just tryna make some sense
of it all up here, okay?
What should we do? Hold a censorship rally
against the government?
They'd lock us up, man!
You're not the only one that's mad.
Trust me, you can't be angrier than me.
Huh? I mean, look at this last one.
"Women's breasts are not to be exposed
in the naked flesh."
We can't film any titties! Titties, man!
[shakily] "No exposure of the chest,
'cause women's breasts are prohibited."
[document slams]
[In-u chuckling]
[laughs] Hm-hm-hm! Nuh-uh-uh!
[chuckles] Mm-mm.
Oh no! [laughs hysterically]
The tits!
I have to unleash them now. Let them out!
Oh yeah! In fact, we'll just
whip all of them out in every scene, yes!
Yes, yes! Change your whole life.
Don't you start with me again. 'Kay?
You and I
are in the same predicament here.
Try to look on the bright side.
You wanted something subtle, yeah?
Now you're free to make it
as subtle as you like.
Yeah, you know, uh,
you just… gotta be discrete about it.
You can't be showing the tits entirely,
but what you can do
is to suggest the boobies beneath.
Under the shirt or something, y'know? Huh?
[laughing maniacally]
[grunting rhythmically]
[guffawing]
[jaunty music playing]
[In-u growls]
Titties this, titties that!
You and your titties!
This shit happened because you turned
my script into a giant tit-fest!
Are you happy now?!
I'm done!
[wearily] I really… can't work like this.
Just find yourself a new director.
[music fades]
[In-u sobbing]
[door opens]
[door closes]
BACCHUS
They can take everything else from me
except the title.
[exhales]
[classical guitar music playing]
[In-u] Okay…
Madame Aema will be reborn.
This "ma" means horse, right?
We'll change it.
Instead of this, we can do…
No, that has nothing to do with the film.
Okay, um, how about this, then?
I like this interpretation
of the "ma" character.
Aema. "She who loves and swears a lot."
So it's basically,
the "I Love You, Fuck You" Madame.
"I Love You, Fuck You" Madame.
That's good.
[In-u] That's awful. [sighs]
Then what about…
You…
[ethereal electronic music playing]
[Jung-ho groans]
Uh…
So that's the character "ma"
as in "ma-rijuana."
And "ae" like "to love."
Uh… uh--
You thinking what I'm thinking?
"Ae-marijuana."
"Ae-ma" for short.
Madame Weed?
Yep, I guess so.
[Jung-ho sighs]
[In-u] At least, this way,
we still get to keep our title, right?
MADAME AEMA
♪ Ba badum ba! ♪
[vocalizing drunkenly]
Jeez.
♪ Ba-ba badah baaa! ♪
♪ Badum bada baaaa! ♪
[engine starts]
All right. [cackles]
[phone ringing]
[Yeong-bae] Noona!
D-- don't hang up! Don't hang up!
We have a situation! It's really bad!
[phone ringing]
Ah, come on, noona! Why'd you hang up?
I said it was really bad!
If someone isn't gravely injured or dead,
I'm gonna kill you.
Heo Hyeok drove his motorcycle
into an oncoming vehicle last night
and flew 50 yards!
God, and filming's just about to start!
I don't know, noona,
at this rate, Madame Aema
might not be able to start production!
[vibrant disco music playing]
[music fades]
[gentle music playing]
[upbeat electronic music playing]
THIS SHOW IS A WORK OF FICTION
INSPIRED BY THE PEOPLE INVOLVED
IN MAKING THE 1982 FILM "MADAME AEMA"
ALL CHARACTERS AND STORYLINES
HAVE BEEN CREATED
SOLELY FOR DRAMATIC STORYTELLING PURPOSES
[music fades]