OUR UNWRITTEN SEOUL
Are you sure about this?
Once you walk out that door…
we won't be on the same team.
You know I don't play fair, right?
It won't be easy
getting into a decent firm.
I don't speak kindly about someone
who turned their back on me.
- I'll find somewhere to work.
- That's not the issue.
You're not the kind of person
who'll take any job.
What matters to you is where you go.
From college to law firms,
you think that your affiliations
define your worth, don't you?
Only two of the top three
law firms are left.
How far down
are you willing to go after that?
If it's not up to your standards,
I bet you'd rather
change careers entirely.
I'm curious to see…
how far…
you are willing to fall.
I'll help you.
That whistleblowing case
you never got to finish.
I'll help you with it.
Who asked for your help?
I told you. That's all behind me.
I was still with the firm then,
so I couldn't take the case myself.
Now I can handle the lawsuit
or whatever else needs to be done.
Look…
I said I'm fine.
And wait. You quit?
Why'd you suddenly leave?
Why not?
That's not the only law firm in the world.
I can go anywhere.
No, somewhere even better.
That's what I'll do.
I will.
Are… you drunk?
No.
I'm more clear-headed than ever,
and I don't regret my decision.
- I'm going to help you.
- I said I don't need help.
I'm still going to help.
I'll do whatever it takes.
I have to.
Every animal has
its own way of surviving.
Mi-ji has missed
nearly two months of school.
If she's sick,
she should submit a doctor's note.
She's barely meeting
the attendance requirement.
If this keeps up, she won't graduate.
- Lee Da-yeon.
- Here.
- Yu Mi-ji.
- Present.
When sensing danger or predators,
chameleons change their appearance
to fool their enemies.
CONSENT LIST
Doesn't Mi-ji get
some kind of terminal leave?
- Pardon?
- Unless she joined the army,
how can she be gone this long?
She went to Seoul. To a relative's house.
What kind of relative lets someone stay
for over a year?
- There you go.
- Okay. Thanks.
- Bye.
- All right. Take care.
Some animals, like pheasants,
just tuck their heads to blend in.
By the way, is Mi-ji still not back yet?
It's been two years since she left!
Has she moved out for good?
Moved out?
Didn't she go to Seoul
to get her leg fixed?
- What the heck!
- Octopuses and squids…
- Are you out of your mind?
- …release ink to escape danger.
And humans,
when in crisis,
often behave in ways
no other animal does.
Gosh, it's tough cooking
all three meals at home every day.
No deliveries, no eating out…
It's not good to eat out all the time.
It's cheaper and healthier to eat at home.
Did you get garlic?
Wait. Did I buy garlic?
EPISODE 4
MY NEMESIS
New York? Or London?
Man!
New York?
London?
Choosing between
the London and New York branch?
- No.
- Don't get up.
You deserve it.
You already set up a meeting
with the landowner of Rosa Restaurant.
Yes, it's set for Friday afternoon.
I had high hopes,
and you really delivered.
Our Ms. Yu exceeded our expectations,
don't you think?
Well…
She hasn't agreed to sell yet.
All we have is a meeting scheduled.
Securing a meeting with someone
who refused to speak to us is impressive.
Hey, everyone!
Let's give Ms. Yu a round of applause
for her hard work.
It's fine. Stay seated.
Thank you.
Don't worry too much, Mr. Choi.
I will make sure our team
gets the credit, not her.
No way. We need to go bigger.
Invite the General Affairs Team.
And keep emphasizing,
"Ms. Yu made this meeting happen."
- Sorry?
- Get her under the spotlight now.
So when things go wrong,
all the attention's on her.
You know how landowners are.
They say they will turn up
and then ghost you at the last minute.
Still, if by some miracle
Mi-rae pulls off the land acquisition--
- Mr. Shin.
- Yes.
Who's leading the new HQ building project?
Lead Specialist Park…
So, even if Mi-rae pulls it off,
she'll end up backing out.
Sir, you are ten steps ahead.
I'm learning so much from you.
Lead Specialist Park?
Ghost me?
No way.
No.
Please, that can't be true.
Is she really ghosting me?
Ma'am, please. That can't be true.
Please, ma'am. Don't do this to me.
Ms. Ro-sa.
Ma'am.
Gosh, a leak out of nowhere?
This is terrible.
Are you here to keep me put
before the meeting?
What? No!
I was just heading home and…
How long should I say
you'll be closed for?
Until the day after tomorrow…
No.
Make it three days.
Gosh, three days?
Does it really take that long
to fix a leak?
I also need a new fridge.
Jeez.
The old one was ancient,
so they don't make parts for it anymore.
It short-circuited and burned.
Where will you go to buy one?
I can come with you.
Doesn't your company give you any work?
I am working right now.
TEMPORARILY CLOSED
If you're done
checking up on me, take this.
- Just put it in a pot and let it boil.
- Yes!
I finally get a single portion takeout?
Thank you.
No need to pay.
I'm giving it to you
so it doesn't go to waste.
And give this to that guy.
Ho-su, Ho-se, or whatever it was.
You mean Lee Ho-su?
He's getting ginseng chicken soup?
He must be feeling anxious
because he quit his job.
He should at least eat well.
Drop it off and check in on him.
Don't worry.
He probably even makes
a to-do list on his days off.
People like him can end up
like deflated balloons
when faced with such hardship.
Really? Ho-su?
- Come in.
- Okay.
- Want something to drink?
- Just water.
What's that?
It's ginseng chicken soup.
Ms. Ro-sa told me to bring it to you.
You haven't eaten, right? Have some.
- It's fine. I'll eat later.
- Have some now.
It won't taste good
once it's been in the fridge.
- I'll eat it later. I promise.
- Oh no!
Gosh.
- Sorry, let me get that.
- No, you get out of the way.
I'll clean it up.
You grabbed that with your bare hands?
Sit over there. I'll take care of it.
Last time I saw you,
you were all fired up about helping me.
Why do you seem so down now?
Are you sick?
I'm just tired from switching jobs.
Switching jobs?
You just quit a few days ago.
When do you start at the new place?
I've been rejected
everywhere I've applied so far.
You must have been in too much of a hurry.
But hey, it's good! You've never
really taken a break before, right?
Now you can!
Go travel or enjoy your hobbies.
I don't have a hobby.
It doesn't have to be anything big.
Just something you usually enjoy.
What do you do when you're not working?
I sleep…
or do chores.
No, not those.
What do you do for fun?
Like TV or games.
There has to be something you enjoy.
Not really.
What were you doing before I came over?
- Thinking.
- About what?
Everything.
Things I've been too busy to think about.
Things I didn't want to think about.
That won't do. Let's go.
Here it is.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
- Oh. How much is this?
- Gosh, you picked a fancy yarn.
It's 30,000 won. What are you making?
- Wrap it once, then pull through.
- Okay.
- Through here?
- Yes.
- Let me.
- Wait. Didn't I hook one?
I told you to hook two.
Wrap it once.
Then pull it through.
Ta-da!
- I see.
- Now it's a circle.
If you keep doing this,
you'll end up with a scrubber.
So, what's on your mind right now?
Nothing, really.
That's the power of crochet.
It gives your mind a break.
They say your brain waves while crocheting
are similar to those when you meditate.
It's basically meditation with your hands.
There. Go on.
Being unemployed is a fight
against your own mind and the clock.
When everyone else is working
and you're home alone,
you think too much.
And the more you think,
the more you lose track of time.
You wonder if the clock's broken,
but before you know it,
the whole day's gone.
That's true.
And 99% of those thoughts are useless.
Thinking about the past
only brings regret,
and thinking about the future
only brings anxiety.
So whenever you start overthinking,
just crochet.
Just get through the day,
one stitch at a time.
If you just hang in there,
something new will come along.
And even if it doesn't,
at least you'll have yourself a scrubber.
How would you know?
You've never been unemployed.
Hey!
I spent years on the civil service exam.
And you can't call yourself…
unemployed.
You're just a lawyer who's between jobs.
If you find a firm, that's great.
If not, just open an office.
There's no need to be down.
What if I end up being useless?
I wanted to join a better firm
and prove that I made the right choice.
But now that I'm out,
I think the firm I quit
was the best I could ever achieve.
It feels like
there's nowhere to go but down.
So I'm scared to take the next step.
Ho-su.
You're still you.
You're not any worse,
you haven't disappeared,
and you haven't gone downhill.
You just quit a job.
You're okay.
Why…
are you being so nice to me?
What?
Mi-rae, you're the last person
to try and comfort others.
So what? You don't like it?
No, it's just…
- You seem different from usual.
- There you go again.
You think you know me so well?
What have you thought of me all this time?
Gosh.
Oh.
- You dropped a stitch.
- What do I do?
- Undo the whole thing?
- No, there's no need.
Just go back to where you got lost.
Give it to me.
I let my guard down.
Why do I end up being myself around him?
Pay attention.
Hook it in.
- Not bad.
- Are you buying that?
You startled me.
Didn't you say you'd rather
throw out your back than look silly?
It's for my partner, not for me.
Buy two.
They seem better than farming seat pads.
Se-jin, are you getting those?
Didn't you say you'd rather
throw out your back than look silly?
Cut it out. Don't tease him.
It's not for him. It's for Yu Candy.
I see. Still, I'd never heard
that Mi-ji had two butts until today.
People have two butt cheeks,
with one on each…
Forget it.
Come on. Just get them.
You've got the money.
Buy three or four for her.
And you know what?
Since working with you, Mi-ji's been
closed off and looking down again.
I hope she doesn't disappear
like she did before.
Gosh. Take that back, now!
I take that back.
Why do you keep saying
she'll disappear or run away?
What did I do to her?
Il-lam isn't saying
that you did something.
He's just concerned
since Mi-ji has disappeared before.
What do you mean, disappeared?
Did she go missing?
Who knows whether she was missing
or if she ran away.
She was gone for two or three years
and then came back.
And her whole family clammed up
and never explained what happened.
They say she was in Seoul.
But it was her twin who went to Seoul.
She has a twin?
I guess she just keeps quiet
and picks strawberries all day.
Hurry up and check out.
Never.
What?
- Jeez.
- Come on.
Well, it's comfortable.
Right?
I could tell just by looking at it.
Why did you just get one for me?
I just prefer picking the classic way.
I'm a bit old-school, you know.
- Seoul?
- Yes.
They say you have a twin in Seoul.
Are you identical or fraternal?
Identical.
So you look exactly the same? That's wild.
What does your twin do?
Do you have any siblings?
Me?
No, I'm an only child.
Where in Seoul is your twin--
Have you ever lived in Seoul?
Me?
I moved to Seoul after college.
Well, technically I didn't graduate
because I started working.
I used work as an excuse
because I didn't want to write my thesis…
Wait, what? I got sidetracked.
Min-hee, you lived
in Seoul for a bit, right?
- Me?
- Yes. Didn't you?
Some say you were in Seoul,
and others say you were hospitalized.
They said you were gone
for two or three years.
Military service
isn't even that long these days.
- What were you doing in Seoul--
- By the way,
how far are you picking today?
- Me?
- Yes.
I don't want to overdo it,
so up to this row.
Okay. I'll do that side, then.
Where have you been interviewing?
Never mind.
You probably got rejected everywhere.
Why did you quit so suddenly?
You could've just transferred
to another team.
Is it true?
The rumor about your fistfight
with Attorney Lee Chung-gu?
Is that why you wanted to meet me,
to ask if we really had a fistfight?
That's part of it, I guess.
Anyway, listen.
You're not failing these interviews
because of your abilities,
so don't rush things.
Just wait until things blow over.
By the way, what are you doing?
I crochet whenever I have
a lot on my mind.
Do you want a scrubber?
Oh my.
You must have had a lot on your mind.
Who taught you how to crochet?
Just a friend.
Why are you making that face again?
Is the friend a girl?
Or a guy?
Or a girl who's basically a guy?
She's an old classmate.
- Nothing's going on between us.
- Okay.
There's nothing between you two,
but you keep thinking about her
before bed.
When you see her,
your feelings are all over the place,
and you end up doing whatever she wants.
Maybe she's changed,
or something's off with you.
Do you know what you call
this neuropsychiatric symptom?
What is it?
Having a thing.
You should go now.
I'm glad to see you doing well.
I'll head off with some scrubbers.
One's for me.
This one's cute.
And one is for Ms. Min Ye-rin,
since her crush sailed away.
Take care.
I'm off.
You said you were up for anything, right?
Come to Sindang Station, Exit 1,
in an hour.
KITCHEN FURNITURE STREET
Ho-su?
Ms. Ro-sa.
What brings you here at this time of day?
The person
you are trying to reach is not available.
She's not answering.
She's unbelievable.
Making a busy guy
come all the way out here…
If you're talking about me, I'm not busy.
- I'm unemployed now.
- Still.
A lawyer shouldn't be dragged
into petty errands like this.
It's fine, really.
- I don't have much to do anyway.
- Just go home.
You're just wasting time by coming here.
- Go on, now.
- The thing is…
I have too much time these days.
As much as I enjoy crocheting at home,
helping you is so much better.
- It's been forever.
- Look at you all dolled up!
The Sinsong Girls' High Queen
hasn't changed.
18TH GRADUATING CLASS REUNION
What do you mean, "dolled up"?
I just threw on whatever I could grab.
Gosh, you're still the queen of Sinsong.
Queen Ok-hui, okay?
Stop it.
How'd you manage to come on a weekday?
Did the vice principal
give you permission?
What permission?
There's no school. It's Foundation Day.
- Okay.
- I see.
Bun-hong hasn't changed a bit.
People would think
that you're the vice principal
and she's the lunch lady.
What's a lunch lady supposed to look like?
- Oh…
- Come on.
Then I'll ask Ho-su to look into that too.
There must be a lawyer
specializing in insurance at the firm.
So did Bun-hong come here for the reunion
or to give legal advice?
She finds all sorts of ways
to brag about her kid.
Ok-hui!
Did you come because it's Foundation Day?
Yes, I'm here, ma'am.
What are you doing?
The vice principal wants you
to assist her.
- Hurry up.
- Go away.
- What is it? Why?
- Just go.
What's with her today?
- Move. I'm going to the restroom.
- Don't push me.
Let's have fun today.
I'm counting on you.
You two sat together? What about me?
- How have you been?
- Mi-kyung!
- So nice to see you.
- My goodness.
- You've been well, right?
- Of course.
Jjan, jjan, I won't cry anymore
Goodbye, farewell, my love
Jjan, jjan!
Now, next up…
Let's find out just how loved
the Sinsong ladies really are.
The first person to hear "I love you"
over the phone wins!
Excuse me. Attention please.
Isn't this kind of unfair
for widows like us?
- Not at all.
- Come on!
It's totally unfair.
What do you mean? I am a beloved woman.
It doesn't have to be your husband.
That's right. Anyone's fine.
It could be your kids
or the guy next door. Whoever!
All right.
As long as you hear "I love you,"
you're good.
If you hear "I love you," you win.
I'll take ten seconds off
for the first challenger.
- Who wants to go?
- Here, here!
Let's hear Bun-hong
call her famous lawyer son!
No, what's with you?
Come on. Didn't you say
you're a beloved woman?
Or were you thinking
of someone other than your son?
Whoever it is,
let's have Vice Principal Yeom Bun-hong
give it a try!
Beloved Yeom Bun-hong!
Yeom Bun-hong!
Ma'am, this one's the best.
Strong compressor,
9-watt fan motor, indirect cooling,
and all stainless steel.
Don't you have direct cooling models?
These days, everyone uses fridges
with indirect cooling.
They're frost-free, so it's convenient.
But I heard at another store
that for places that use up
ingredients daily,
direct cooling is better.
Price aside,
don't frost-free refrigerators
use more electricity too?
Ma'am, your son is very thorough.
You must feel reassured
to have a son like him.
I'll show you the direct cooling ones.
Right this way, ma'am.
Oh my.
This way, ma'am.
MOM
Hello?
Ho-su, where are you?
I hope I didn't call
while you were working.
Oh…
I'm actually with a client right now. Why?
Ho-su, you know you're the only person
I love in this world, right?
- What?
- I just feel like I never say it enough.
Is there anything
you've wanted to say to me
but haven't been able to?
MY SON
What do you mean?
Hey.
This could take a while.
You know, things you've kept to yourself.
Things you thought about saying
but couldn't.
Something you've buried deep
in your heart.
You know, like "I…"
"I…"
I quit my job.
What?
I left the law firm.
When?
Why didn't you tell me?
Excuse me, sir!
I can take care of my own issues,
so please don't worry.
This one is good.
- It's been over a minute.
- Okay, Ho-su.
I'll call you again later.
How long was that? How many seconds?
Two minutes and 32 seconds.
Sorry, you failed!
That's too bad.
Who's next?
Did you wipe with your hands or something?
Your skin's going to peel.
Oh my.
I know. I wasted too much water.
Sometimes it feels like
they're someone else's kid.
They act like they raised themselves.
They don't even remember
who changed their dirty diapers
and who'd tell them,
"Don't worry. I'll take care of it"
Hey, just take it as the price
of raising a brilliant kid.
Better than having one
who can't take care of herself.
We're leaving in five minutes.
The child you gave birth to
doesn't feel like yours?
I don't think I can relate.
It's funny how you act so cold
to your real one.
- Pardon?
- To your real mom, I mean.
I overheard, and it sounded like
you just told her that you'd quit.
She…
worries about me a lot.
Letting your parents worry a little
is part of being a good son.
To me,
being a good son means
moving on and letting her have her life.
Who am I to judge
a parent-child relationship
based on something I just overheard?
Sorry about earlier.
For lying and saying you were my client
when you were right there with me.
Instead of lying,
why don't we make it a reality?
What do you mean?
Pardon?
So you're saying that
starting now, he's officially your…
Legal representative.
I'll go to the meeting
since I already promised I would.
But from now on, handle all those
annoying issues through your friend.
- Ms. Ro-sa.
- Oh, and here.
- What's all this?
- The documents I need before the meeting.
What?
We should at least know
the company's terms for negotiations.
Send me the purchase proposal
and the business plan first,
- and if possible…
- Hey.
Why are you making this a big deal?
We're friends.
Work is work, and friends are friends.
Send them by Monday.
- I'll head out first.
- I'll finish up and head home too.
- Good work today.
- Thanks.
WONGEUN LAW FIRM
Hey!
I gave you work because I felt bad.
How could you give me more work?
It's not me.
Your company did
an unacceptably sloppy job.
Jeez.
Let me take this call.
Hey, Ji-yun.
Hi, Ho-su.
Thanks to you, the interview went well.
It's all because of you.
You even made the reservation for me.
Are you at the office?
If you are, I thought I'd stop by
for a quick chat.
I quit the firm.
You quit?
- Just like that?
- Yes, it just happened.
This weekend?
Is the reunion you mentioned this weekend?
What reunion?
Okay.
Did you tell Mi-rae?
No, I didn't tell her on purpose.
What do you mean by "on purpose"?
I guess you don't know,
but Mi-rae doesn't really socialize
since giving up on the civil service exam.
Everyone knows how hard she worked.
It must be hard for her
to have people see how she is now.
What's wrong with how she is now?
I don't mean she's in a bad place.
From her perspective,
she probably feels like she settled.
I think she feels awkward
about meeting everyone.
Ji-yun, I appreciate the thought,
but I'll be there too.
What?
I'll bring Ho-su with me. See you there.
What was that? Are you going?
Of course I am.
They're painting me as a social recluse
who failed the civil service exam.
But you don't have to…
Why would you take me?
And you…
Come looking sharp.
Otherwise,
they'll gossip about you forever.
Get your hair done too.
What's with you?
Since when do you care about that stuff?
If you don't want to go, then don't.
Why give them the satisfaction?
If I don't go,
they'll say whatever they want.
"Mi-rae this" and "Mi-rae that."
I'm not letting that happen.
I'm going, no matter what.
What's up with her?
FALL RISK
BED REST ONLY
I wondered where that went.
Did you wash it?
Yes, I did.
Grandma kept looking for it.
It gets pretty chilly at night these days.
I see.
Mi-ji.
It's about time
you gave Grandma a haircut.
Okay… What?
Me?
You've always done it yourself.
Time to reopen "Mi-ji's salon,"
don't you think?
That's right.
At this pace, they'll turn
into gray-haired witches.
I'll see… what I can do.
How did Grandma's skills
skip her daughter
and land on her granddaughter?
That's amazing.
They say talent skips a generation.
Is your sister good with hair too?
No, she's not really good with her hands.
It's not about skill.
She just doesn't care.
There's always one in every family.
They think giving money is enough
and wash their hands of everything else.
She's probably just busy making money.
Kids like Mi-ji are rare.
Still, she hasn't shown her face once
since I've been here.
Grandma's going to forget her face.
How could she forget?
- She looks just like Mi-ji.
- Good point.
Here, have these while you work.
- Wow.
- They're still a bit tart.
But they'll wake you up!
- Thank you.
- Please, try some.
By the way, ma'am,
have you had a chance to check
this month's payment?
What about it?
Well…
Some things haven't been paid for yet.
The caregiver fee and the meals.
That can't be right.
Wasn't it transferred under "Yu Mi-rae"?
There's nothing on record
for this month yet.
Oh dear.
Maybe she forgot because she's so busy.
I'll look into it.
What the…
So what happens to Mi-ji now?
What do you mean? She's done for.
HNU is off the table for her.
Life really is unpredictable.
- What's she going to do now?
- What else?
She should marry Gyeong-gu.
That's not so bad.
- Come on!
- It's possible.
Like in a romance comic!
It's not like one of them is settling.
That's harsh!
Elementary school sweethearts
getting married.
- This is pure romance.
- Seriously.
Yesterday is over.
Tomorrow is yet to come. Today is.…
Mi-ji?
Or is it Mi-rae?
Mi-rae.
Long time no see, Mi-rae.
Choi Seung-hyeon! Choi Seung-hyeon!
Does he ever pass the ball?
That's insane. He's on fire!
- Seriously, what's the secret?
- Hey there!
He looks amazing.
Take a guess.
Is she Mi-ji or Mi-rae?
Mi-rae's here.
Come on, Ji-yun. What a buzzkill.
It's Mi-rae.
It's been ages. We never get to see you.
It's been crazy at the office.
Right, you work at the KFMC.
No wonder you're so busy.
Still, you should've shown up
for weddings and stuff.
You missed
our wedding invitation gathering.
Are you two getting married?
Come on, we've got a two-year-old.
Ji-yun, you didn't tell Mi-rae about us?
I did tell her.
I told you. You probably forgot.
If you ask me, Mi-rae's the only one
who traveled through time.
Let's sit. Have we ordered yet?
Yes, all done.
What's the best thing on the menu?
It really has been a while.
HOW TO CUT GRANDMA'S HAIR
Oh my. This is driving me crazy.
Seriously, what do I do?
I feel so hopeless.
What is it? What's wrong?
Is something going on with Mi-rae?
What do you mean?
I mean, even if she never calls,
she always pays
the hospital bills right on time.
Do you think she's having money problems?
I'll cover it this time.
Goodness, with what money?
I've been working on the farm.
I'll pay you in cash.
Don't waste your money.
Just save it.
I make more per hour than Mi-rae.
I'll save what's left--
Jeez!
Just save it.
Is it okay to use Mi-rae's money, then?
You think you and Mi-rae are the same?
What's so different?
What do you think? I mean…
Cheers!
Remember when Seung-hyeon
did the speech at graduation?
Girls from other schools and lower grades
were bawling their eyes out.
Stop. That's ancient history.
Seriously.
Ho-su, you made it.
Hey, Ho-su!
Long time no see.
- You're looking good.
- So handsome.
He is.
You're late.
I heard you're a lawyer now.
He's the only lawyer
from our class, right?
That's wild.
I've never met a real lawyer before.
Where did you do your military service?
Do lawyers get assigned
to special roles like army doctors?
I'm not sure.
I was exempt.
Shoot. Sorry, I forgot.
Wow, you're blessed, man.
Ho-su, can I get your business card?
- Gosh.
- Okay.
I don't have…
- You know Wongeun Law Firm, right?
- Yes.
- Ho-su was there until recently.
- Wongeun?
Isn't that the top firm in Korea?
What's up with you two?
Since when have you two kept in touch?
Gosh!
Ho-su and Mi-rae…
I always knew you two would do well.
Come on.
They were the top two in the whole school.
We all knew it.
Turns out Duson High
has some pretty successful alumni.
A lawyer,
and a public corporation employee.
I honestly thought Seung-hyeon
would be the most successful.
Hey.
He's way too good-looking
to just be a store clerk.
I thought he'd be
a TV personality or something.
He's not just a clerk. He's a manager.
I know.
Sorry, she's drunk.
Cut her some slack.
She used to be your fan club president.
Thanks for seeing me in such a good light.
But Mi-ji was
the most likely to succeed, right?
- That's true.
- I know.
What's she doing these days
after quitting track and field?
I saw her in Duson-ri the other day.
She was moving some stuff at the mart.
- What?
- My mom said she's a janitor.
Wait, a janitor?
What do you mean? She's done for.
HNU is off the table for her.
- She should marry Gyeong-gu.
- That's harsh!
Like in a romance comic!
It's not like one of them is settling.
Seriously.
Don't ask me.
Her twin is sitting next to you.
Fair point.
Mi-rae, how's Mi-ji doing?
Why would you ask that?
Mi-rae, you must have it so hard.
Why are we talking…
…behind her back?
Ho-su still goes from zero
to a hundred in no time.
Just like the old days.
But he's right.
Mi-rae's right here too.
Is your wedding
really happening this time?
- Of course!
- Definitely.
You said that last time,
but it didn't happen.
- This time we have to do it.
- Really?
- You better come.
- I will.
Ho-su! You should come to the wedding too.
Okay. It's a bit late, but congrats.
Yes, congratulations.
- Bye.
- See you.
Ho-su, are you leaving?
- I'll join you then.
- Hey, traitor!
You got us all together.
You're staying till the end.
Bye. I'll call you.
Who's up for karaoke?
Mi-rae.
I just realized I don't have your number.
Okay.
- Here.
- Thank you.
I'll contact you before the wedding.
If you're going, then let's go together.
All right.
Would you like to come with us?
Do you want me to?
I'll get going.
- You two take care.
- Okay.
How are you getting home?
No idea.
Are you mad?
Why would I be?
How should I know?
You've barely said a word,
and you don't seem so happy.
What's there to be happy about?
It wasn't exactly a fun gathering.
Then why did you even come?
No, seriously.
You're not the type to show up
just because I asked you to.
Why did you come?
Me?
- I've already told you.
- Right.
You said you hate it
when people gossip about you.
Then why were you so quiet earlier?
What?
You can't stand people talking about you
behind your back,
but you're fine with them
talking about Mi-ji right in front of you?
I'll get going.
Hello.
Why weren't you answering your phone?
Sorry, I was out, so I didn't notice.
What's up?
You've been paid, right?
I forgot to mention the hospital bill.
I texted you my bank account info.
Transfer the money
and keep the rest for yourself.
No thanks. It's your paycheck.
You're the one who went to work.
Anyway, come down on Friday.
Grandma needs a haircut.
Oh…
Can't it be another day?
Mom's not coming home on Friday night.
You should come when she's not around.
Any other day works for me.
I have something on Friday.
Something? Like what?
Well…
There's this really important meeting
at work.
I have to be there.
Just come down.
They don't need me anyway.
Still, I should do what the company asks…
Do what? I told you to just sit tight.
Come on.
I can't just sit there and do nothing.
Gosh.
I'll make time and come later.
You're unbelievable.
So work comes before Grandma now?
- That's a stretch.
- What is?
It's what you always said to me.
It's not the same for me.
And I'm not doing this for myself.
- It's all for you--
- What's so different?
I wasn't doing it for myself either.
Anyway, I really can't make it on Friday.
What am I supposed to…
Should I tell Mom
to change her plans for you?
What's with the attitude?
Forget it.
I'll handle the haircut
and everything else.
Just send the money.
Is it that much of a burden
to take care of Grandma for me?
If it is, then don't do it!
That's what you always told me.
Is it as easy as you thought,
just sending money from Seoul?
- What?
- Transfer the money now.
Hey.
CALL ENDED
She's freaking mean.
NICE SEEING YOU
SEE YOU AT THE WEDDING!
Just sip at your own pace.
Thanks.
Are you mad?
What's there to be happy about?
It wasn't exactly a fun gathering.
Then why did you even come?
When you see her,
your feelings are all over the place,
and you end up doing whatever she wants.
Do you know what you call this
neuropsychiatric symptom?
I've finally cleared out
all of last year's produce!
What's all this?
Some boxes and shipping labels.
- For you to send out.
- Oh.
I don't have anyone to send them to.
You haven't sent any to Seoul yet.
Send some to your twin
to share with her friends.
She has no one
to share them with in Seoul.
That can't be right.
Strawberries aren't a big deal here,
but in Seoul, you have to pay for them.
Even if I send these, they'll just spoil.
There's no one to share them with.
How can there be no one?
Seoul is not a deserted island.
She only cares about herself.
Only her problems matter,
and only her struggles count.
That's why she has no one.
Still, she can have some strawberries.
Do whatever you want. They're yours.
PARCEL SHIPPING FORM
RECIPIENT ADDRESS
Mi-ji.
Hello.
Is your mom home?
She said she's staying over
at a friend's tonight.
I never seem to catch your mom
at the right time.
I wanted to talk to her.
What's with all these strawberries?
I got them from work. Would you like some?
They're organic, but they're a bit tart.
You're right.
The tart, ugly ones like these
are perfect for jam.
Mi-ji, do you want to make
strawberry jam with me?
Sorry?
For God's sake.
The person
you are trying to reach is not available.
- Please try again later.
- She's not answering.
Still setting up? Where is the landowner?
She should be on her way,
but I can't reach her.
You can't reach her?
Is she ghosting you or something?
I'll ask her representative
who was supposed to come.
- Hello.
- You're on your way, right?
And you're with Ms. Ro-sa?
No, we agreed to meet at your office.
What?
When was the last time
you spoke with her?
We spoke last night.
I haven't called her today.
Did she say anything unusual last night?
She just said, "See you at the meeting."
Why? Is she not answering?
Should I go to her place?
No, it's fine.
Just come to the office for now.
Once I finish setting up the meeting room…
Wait, never mind.
I'll just go there myself.
I'll do it.
Pardon?
I'll finish getting things ready here.
You go check on her.
- Oh…
- What's going on?
Oh… Nothing. I'll go.
Mi-rae.
Then I'll leave it to you. Thank you.
Ma'am!
Are you home?
If she's not home,
where could she possibly be?
Ms. Ro-sa!
Ma'am?
Oh my goodness.
Oh gosh.
Grandma!
- Ms. Ro-sa!
- Gosh.
I thought I was going to
starve to death here all alone.
It's just a minor sprain in my back.
Call 911.
Hey. What's going on?
What's wrong?
Stay with me, okay?
Ma'am?
Ho-su? Here!
Over here!
- Go get a plastic bag!
- Ma'am!
- Put a bag over her mouth.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Go get a bag. Hurry!
Stay with me!
Mi-rae, here!
What's going on?
Calm down and breathe.
Attention, patients
and guardians in the emergency room…
Any word on the CT scan?
Is it her brain?
There's nothing serious on the scan.
Just a minor back injury.
They'll keep an eye on her
until tomorrow, just to be safe.
Are you okay?
Still not feeling well?
It almost happened again.
If it weren't for you, Ho-su…
Mi-ji, open the door.
Open up.
Yu Mi-ji!
I can't take this anymore.
Let's settle this
once and for all today.
Get up.
I said, "Get up."
Why did you cut the phone line?
Get up.
You're not even going to
show your face anymore?
Get up!
Do you want to see me go crazy?
Come on, I said get up!
You…
How long are you going to keep this up?
You won't go outside,
you don't see anyone,
and now you've cut the phone line too?
You call this a home? It's a prison cell.
Get up. Come on.
Let's go out.
It's been three years!
You've done enough, and I've had enough!
Just because you can't run anymore,
your life is over?
How long are you going to waste your life
stuck in the past?
Are you going to hide forever?
What are you going to do with yourself?
Since when do you care?
What?
Since when do you ever care about me?
You don't give a damn what happens to me.
Mi-ji.
It's true, isn't it?
You never paid any attention to me
before I started running.
I can't run anymore.
So just go back to worrying about Mi-rae,
like you always have.
Do you hear yourself right now?
To you, I've always been Mi-rae's add-on.
So keep ignoring me like you always have.
I'm just sitting here, dead quiet.
So please leave me alone!
So you're saying
all of this is my fault now?
How far back are you going to trace this?
What's next?
Will you blame me for giving birth to you?
Yes, why did you even have me?
You could've just had Mi-rae.
You think so too, don't you?
You brat!
Did you really just say that?
I can't believe you.
How could you break
your mother's heart like that?
- What are you doing?
- How could you do this?
- You can't… Get up and come out.
- Calm down.
- Come out!
- Stop! Come out!
- Let go.
- Stay out of here.
Are you insane?
Why are you going after her like that?
If she won't come out,
maybe I have to make her!
Give it time.
You think this is something you can force?
Jeez.
This is all your fault!
You coddled her too much
and turned her into a recluse.
You were never like this with me as a kid,
so why do you baby my kid and spoil her?
Gosh.
Mi-ji.
Grandma's coming in.
Why are you sitting like that?
It must be suffocating.
Look at me.
Come on.
No.
No?
Then don't.
Oh, my little cocoon.
How big of a butterfly
are you trying to become?
No.
I'm not going to become anything.
That's fine too.
As long as you stay healthy, eat well,
and keep Grandma company, that's enough.
I have enough money to take care of you.
I mean it.
Grandma.
There might be something wrong with me.
I regret everything and worry so much…
that I can't do anything.
What's there to regret and worry about?
Yesterday is over.
Tomorrow is yet to come.
I don't know.
I know I should get out of here…
but I don't want to go back
to being nothing again.
I know that's the only place
I can go back to…
but it feels so pathetic,
and I'm sick of it.
I have all this life ahead of me,
and I feel completely lost.
Grandma.
I feel like trash.
If a deer runs away from a lion,
does that make it trash?
If a hermit crab hides
in fear of being eaten,
is it a coward?
They're all just trying to survive.
You're hiding to survive too.
No matter how pathetic or messy it looks,
anything you do to survive is brave.
Grandma.
It's okay, my dear.
Let's brush it off and get back up.
Grandma.
Grandma?
Why aren't you answering me?
Grand…
Grandma!
Grandma, are you okay?
Please wake up! Grandma!
Where's the phone?
The phone.
Oh no, Grandma!
Hang in there, Grandma. Please, please…
Grandma…
Come on!
Someone, please help.
Please help!
Help me.
Save my grandma!
Please save my grandma.
Hello?
Anyone home?
Anyone?
Please, save her!
I talked to your team leader.
We'll reschedule
after Ms. Ro-sa is discharged.
What was that earlier?
You were having trouble breathing.
Is that your heart again? Or…
Thank you.
For what?
For everything.
The meeting, and Ms. Ro-sa.
If it weren't for you,
everything would've gone wrong.
I only went because you told me about her.
Don't worry too much about Ms. Ro-sa.
The doctor said we made it just in time.
We got here before it was too late.
Would it have been
the same for my grandma?
The day she collapsed…
If someone other than Mi-ji
had been with her,
would things have turned out better?
I think so.
Even the hospital said so.
That we should've gotten there sooner.
If it hadn't been for Mi-ji,
Grandma might not be bedridden
like she is now.
How is that…
Mi-ji's fault?
Then whose fault is it?
She's always like that.
It's not enough that she's miserable.
She drags everyone else down with her.
Mi-rae.
You know what I hate the most?
That she keeps on living like that.
While Grandma's lying there
because of her,
she still laughs, eats, and goes out
like she didn't do anything.
Then I guess
my dad died because of me.
What?
The day he died…
I insisted we go out.
I didn't want to go on any other day,
and I didn't want to go with Mom.
I wanted it to be just us two.
I got my way in the end.
And the car ended up totaled.
A drunk driver crashed into us.
Dad died, and I survived.
If I hadn't insisted that day,
he might still be alive.
That's…
That's not your fault.
It's the drunk driver's fault.
Then why would you
say stuff like that about Mi-ji?
You tell me it's not my fault,
yet you're so harsh with her.
Just like no one was to blame
for what happened today,
what happened to your grandma
isn't on Mi-ji either.
- I guess.
- You guess? It's the truth.
How is any of that Mi-ji's fault?
Okay, I get it--
No. Be clear about it.
It wasn't Mi-ji's fault.
You know, jam tastes best
when the strawberries are a bit tart.
If they're too sweet, they're not as good.
You've been working hard
on the farm, right?
I wouldn't say hard…
I see.
Things don't always feel right
in the beginning.
If you start with something super sweet
and try something sweet and tangy,
all you can taste is the tang.
But life's funny, you know?
Just like strawberries.
Even if it feels too sour right now,
the tart ones make the best jam.
Did you get it?
I'm using strawberries
as a metaphor for life.
Yes.
Oh, you did?
Can you stir this for a bit?
You're looking at that photo again?
Sorry?
Be honest. This is Mi-rae, right?
No, it's not.
Come on.
Even I can recognize Mi-rae at that age.
She always had that look.
What look?
Like she was holding it all in.
Trying to hide her soft side.
She may look sullen on the outside,
but kids as thoughtful
and kind as her are rare.
She's not that kind.
What do you mean?
Of course she is.
She was nice enough to cut her hair short
just so her sister could graduate.
Mi-ji, don't be like that.
No one cares more about family
than Mi-rae.
For so long,
I was harder on myself than anyone else,
just for being me.
Even deer and hermit crabs
do everything they can to survive.
So why do humans…
SENDER: YU MI-JI
RECIPIENT: YU MI-RAE
Why do I end up attacking myself
in the moments
I most need to protect myself?
It wasn't until I lived as someone else
that I realized my worst enemy was myself.
Now I know, but so what?
What difference does it make?
Why are you defending Mi-ji?
You're not even that close.
Because I like her.
What?
You already know.
Mi-ji is my first love.
Knowing doesn't mean
I can change anything.
YU MI-JI
Is this team in charge
of the new HQ project?
Ms. Yu, prepare the project report
by next week.
- What?
- If you can't, then say so.
- The penalty will be all yours too.
- Can you help me?
- Did you receive this?
- Mi-ji, that's not fair.
I hear you're dating the farm owner.
Is that just a false rumor?
Does my response even matter?
Hey, Ho-su!
Let's keep this strictly professional.
I'm Ms. Kim Ro-sa's
legal representative, Lee Ho-su.
Are you going
to keep treating me like this?
Why are you curious about that?
Subtitle translation by Soya Back