Hello, Mr. Li.
What's with the report?
It's totally different from what I took back.
My baby
He needs one too.
Who are you?
Don't tell me
your baby
has something to do with Mr. Li?
My baby
is Mr. Li's husband.
Gu Nanshan.
What?
You don't believe me?
I did a DNA test.
Right, Mr. Li?
I'm here today
to give me
and my child
with my child.
Enough.
This company has become a market.
What do you think?
or get a divorce.
or resign.
and give the company an explanation.
Uncle Lu.
You asked for it so quickly.
People might think
you had a plan.
Ran.
Don't provoke me.
I watched you grow up.
After your father passed away,
I don't want anything to happen to you.
I will be fine.
Everyone.
Three days.
I'll give you an answer.
If you can't,
I will leave the board.
Mr. Li, this is the schedule you asked me to check.
They never appear in the same place
at the same time.
How could this child be his?
There must be something wrong.
Is this Woo-Eon Hospital?
I want to see President Chai.
Thank you.
Uncle Chai.
I'm Youran.
I want to ask you a favor.
Gu Nanshan.
Leave Li Youran immediately.
When will this end?
It'll end when it's time.
I quit.
I... He really quit, okay?
Okay.
Here's your choice question.
One is a woman we met by chance,
and the other is your beloved father.
Whose life is more important?
Think carefully and tell me the answer.
You're at home.
Explain this.
What do you mean?
He's not your child.
Why did you admit it?
I wasn't sure.
I slept with her seven months ago.
The test report says whatever it says.
Yes.
It's clearly written on the schedule.
Last year,
you and her
at the same time.
How did you sleep?
Are you done?
I'm tired enough.
Is it fun?
Let's get a divorce if you feel uncomfortable.
Do you know
can't be decided.
Can you be content?
You're lucky enough.
Besides,
our marriage is a contract.
It's none of your business
It's none of your business.
I've had enough of this.
Let's stop here.
Let's break up, okay?
Feels good.
You married me not because of love.
You've achieved your goal.
I'm useless.
Let's part nicely.
According to the DNA test report,
Gu Nanshan is not related to that child.
The schedule list shows
he has never met that woman.
So Gu Nanshan was framed?
We'll believe you.
Who knows if you're protecting Gu Nanshan?
If you don't believe me,
you can verify it yourself.
I have to say something here.
it's true that I married Gu Nanshan.
So I got the company's decision-making power.
is also a fact.
I don't want others
to make trouble
behind my back.
This will not change anything
nothing will change.
What about the report?
It's totally different from what I took back.
The hospital made a mistake.
Anything else?
The invitation to the charity auction
to attend the charity auction with Gu Nanshan.
It can break the gossip
between you two.
He can't come.
What happened
has caused a serious impact on the Li family.
If she shows up alone in front of the media,
it will bring her more trouble.
Like this.
hurt her.
Hello, Miss Li.
Tonight's charity auction
should be held by the couple.
I don't know why you're the only one here.
My husband has something to do today.
It's said that you and him are already
about the divorce?
Where did you hear that?
Honey.
Why are you so careless?
I left my bracelet in the car.
Why are you here?
Give back
you left behind.
Mr. Gu,
Have you admitted your affair?
Did you break up
have broken up?
Your question is ridiculous.
My relationship with my wife
with my wife.
The rumors you mentioned
are just groundless rumors.
My wife and I
and will keep the possibility of
by law.
Today's theme is Charity Night.
Please don't ask
please stop asking.
Don't delay the guests coming in.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Didn't you say
we'll part ways
and never see each other again?
I'm sorry.
I always said
I wanted poems and faraway places
to cover up
the so-called loneliness.
But after knowing you,
I realized
true freedom
is love.
I just realized
the poem and distance I wanted
is right in front of me.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
Actually,
I have a feeling.
I thought you'd come back to me.
Why?
I don't know.
But you're back.
Right?
I'm back.
Mr. Lu.
Gu Nanshan doesn't play by the book at all.
What should we do next?
Forget it.
Use your strength.
We'll see.
This scene
according to our script.
Understand?