♪The moon is shining above
the broken bridge, and the lake ripples♪
♪My heart in a whirl,
with all sorts of feelings♪
♪Clouds encircle the green hills,
and people are in distress♪
♪To help all beings, to be chivalrous♪
♪I wish to ride the wind♪
♪It's never been done♪
♪At this perfect moment,
you wish to exchange♪
♪A thousand of reincarnations
for a lifetime of love♪
♪Watching the fireworks
and the full moon♪
♪With affectionate gaze♪
♪Accumulating lifetimes
of destiny to be with me♪
[Different Princess]
[Episode 10]
Master.
Something bad happened.
What happened?
Your Highness.
Liu Xiang died in the East Office.
Your Highness, you are here.
What happened?
Around one hour ago,
I heard
Miss Liu screaming inside.
I rushed in
and found her
dead.
Where's the culprit?
There's no culprit.
No culprit?
Did she commit suicide?
Well...
It's not a suicide.
You'll know once you see her.
Open the door.
Yes, Your Highness.
What are these?
These Adamantine Talismans
are sent from Prince Qi Residence tonight.
They say that Prince Qi
is terror-stricken today.
So, he needs something
to suppress the demonic aura.
I didn't think
that a few talismans would
hurt anyone.
So, I asked someone to paste these on.
I know how to cook some medicinal dishes
that can help you get accustomed
to the climate here.
If you don't mind,
I can cook them for you.
Becoming the best chef in Shengjing
is my dream.
Come back.
Do you want to ruin the crime scene?
Liu Xiang
was such a kind girl.
She had a passion for life.
And she was loyal.
There was even a spark
between her and Ji Feng.
She could have had
a blessed future.
But everything
has been destroyed by Ji Chu.
Both her hands and legs are tied.
She couldn't have committed suicide.
What is that?
This Vajra Weapon
is from Prince Qi Residence too.
It is said to be blessed
and can be used to defeat evil.
Are there any other exits in the prison?
Your Highness.
This prison is known as the Steel Box.
It's specially built
for unusual criminals.
There's only one exit.
The door, windows and walls
are crafted from special materials.
The walls are unbreakable.
So, you are saying
that this cell is a closed room.
So, it was impossible for someone
to sneak past the guards,
kill Liu Xiang
and escape without notice.
Yes. It was impossible.
So,
who killed Liu Xiang?
Well...
I have no idea at all.
You were usually very talkative.
What's wrong with you today?
What do you want me to say?
Tell me
who killed Liu Xiang.
You don't need me
to tell you who killed her.
Why not?
You spoke so eloquently
at the East Office court
for Ji Yun
that day, right?
What's wrong?
Are you being quiet because
this case has nothing to do with Ji Yun?
It has nothing to do
with the crown prince.
Today,
with the exalted Prince Lv here,
I
don't dare to speak too much.
When will the coroner be here?
I already sent someone
to get the coroner.
I think he'll be here soon.
Go away.
You demon.
- You demon.
- Feng.
Feng.
Mother.
Feng, don't be scared.
Don't be scared.
You are fine.
I don't want to marry her.
It's okay.
- You are fine.
- I don't want it.
I don't want to marry a demon.
I want to break off the engagement.
Okay.
Don't be scared.
I won't let you
marry a demon.
I'll come up with a solution.
Mother.
Is there really a demon in this world?
It doesn't matter
if there's a demon or not.
I'll protect you.
Mother.
Sometimes, I'll dream
about Imperial Consort Xian.
Is she a demon?
Of course
she is.
But our uncle
killed her with an arrow.
She...
Will she...
Will she seek revenge from me?
Feng.
Don't worry.
Even if she comes back,
she'll come for me and your uncle.
It has nothing to do with you.
But I don't want to be like this.
Why can't we
get along with everyone?
Why can't we get along with everyone?
Why?
Maybe
this is the tragedy
of being born into the royal family.
Although we live a life of luxury
and get to enjoy
unattainable privilege,
we walk on a tightrope every day.
Your Highness, it's time to go.
Okay.
Feng.
Feng, don't be scared.
I'll handle everything.
I have to go back now.
Don't be afraid.
This is not a locked-room murder.
Ji Chu must have sent someone here
to kill Liu Xiang
through a secret passage.
A sharp instrument pierced her chest
and ruptured her cardiac artery
that caused her to die
from excessive bleeding.
Her time of death was around
two hours ago.
Why did she suddenly transform
during the engagement banquet
and return to her normal self
upon her return
to the East Office?
Usually, it happens
under the influence
of special medication
to cause a temporary change
in the color of the pupils
or temporary hair growth.
After the medicine wears off,
that person will return to normal.
But...
But what?
He's such a fox.
You are the one
who poisoned Liu Xiang.
Stop acting like you are innocent.
There's nothing wrong
with Miss Liu's blood.
And I don't detect
any poison in her blood.
It means that she was not
under the influence
of that type of medication.
How is that possible?
In my novel,
the poison is detected right away.
And it proves
the existence of Demon Poison.
Why has the script changed?
Calm down, Miss Qing.
Yes. We can't rush this.
I wonder what Ji Chu
is plotting this time.
I heard about a rumor.
What rumor is it?
It's said that this Vajra Weapon
from Zhendao Temple
is highly accurate.
As soon as it detects
the presence of a demon,
it will kill that demon.
So, I'm thinking
that maybe Liu Xiang
is really a demon.
That's why she was killed
by the Vajra Weapon.
Do you believe
that there's a demon in this world?
Nothing is too strange
in this huge world.
It's not impossible.
So, based on your theory,
Prince Qi killed Liu Xiang.
I wouldn't dare make that assumption.
A locked room
where no one can enter.
But the Vajra Weapon from Prince Qi
stabbed through
the chest of the deceased.
Doesn't it mean
that Prince Qi is the culprit?
Li Yi.
I'm here, Your Highness.
Go to the Liu family
and inform them that Liu Xiang is dead.
Also, tell them that Prince Qi
is the main suspect.
Yes, Your Highness.
So, Ji Chu
is trying to target
the Wei family behind Ji Feng.
Send the body to the mortuary
and guard it well.
Do not let anyone go near it.
Yes, Your Highness.
Are you going to leave,
Princess Consort?
No wonder Qing knows Prince Lv
so well.
So, she's the Princess Consort.
Your Highness.
I want to spend some time
at Miss Lin's house.
Miss Lin.
You'll take me in, right?
I'm afraid I'll have to get
His Highness's permission to do that.
I have my own freedom.
He can't dictate where I go.
You don't have my permission.
Princess Consort.
You better go back with His Highness.
Now, Ji Chu has confirmed
that I am Hua Qingge.
If I go back with him,
I'll be walking right into a trap.
Do you see that?
The brat who barged
into the dance room last time
is the Princess Consort.
That Princess Consort
is the thief who barged
into the dance room?
Keep it down.
- Stop talking.
- Keep it down.
Xiao Yan.
Yes, Your Highness.
Ask the three guards
who are on duty tonight
to come and see me separately.
Yes, Your Highness.
You have been invited by His Highness.
Roger that.
Are we going or not?
Of course we are going.
Do you want to get beheaded
and have your skull made
into a wine glass for Prince Lv?
After Liu Xiang was sent
to the East Office tonight,
you were on duty, right?
Yes.
Commander Chang led me
and another guard,
Wang Junior, to guard the place.
During that time,
who went into Liu Xiang's cell?
The first person who went there
was Xiu, a maid from Liu Residence.
Xiu.
Your Highness.
She said that she was
Miss Liu's personal maid
from Liu Residence.
And she brought a box of pastries
just for Miss Liu.
I am Miss Liu's
personal maid, Xiu.
This is the identity tablet
from Liu Residence.
No chatting.
You have 15 minutes.
I understand.
Did Liu Xiang eat the food?
I don't know.
But I think she ate it.
Why do you say that?
First,
I heard Xiu
asking Miss Liu
to eat the pastries.
Second,
it was nighttime.
The time when people often get hungry.
Why starve yourself
when you have something to eat?
Besides, those pastries
were Miss Liu's favorites.
Come with it.
Roger that.
Does Ji Chu suspect that no Demon Poison
was detected because Liu Xiang
ate the pastries
brought by Xiu?
Do you think
Liu Xiang ate the food or not?
I don't understand what you mean.
It's just a plate of pastries.
Is it that important
whether she ate it or not?
You are acting dumb to me.
I wouldn't dare.
You are the one who's acting dumb.
You sent someone to poison Liu Xiang,
kill her
and frame Ji Feng for it.
Now, you are pretending
to investigate the case.
That's not logical at all.
Looks like you have
a lot of resentment toward me.
That's not true.
All I feel toward you
are awe, veneration and fear.
What do you
fear about me?
Your Highness.
Please have mercy on me.
What did you do?
Please spare my life.
Don't behead me and
turn my skull into a wine glass.
If you don't want me
to behead you,
you better tell me the truth now.
I'll tell you.
I'll tell you everything.
I'm the only son
in my family.
It...
I've finally become
a guard at the East Office.
I can't just die like this.
I don't want to die
with some missing body parts.
Do you think Liu Xiang ate the food?
Well...
I'm not sure.
What do you mean?
Your Highness.
I heard
Xiu
asking Miss Liu to eat the food.
But Miss Liu
didn't say anything at all.
Could it be
that Liu Xiang was already
dead at that time?
No.
Miss Liu was still alive at that time.
Because not long after that,
Prince Qi Residence sent someone
to deliver the talismans
and the Vajra Weapon.
I was
the one who went in
to paste on the talismans.
She's just asleep.
How long did you take
to paste on the talismans?
Around
fifteen minutes.
And Liu Xiang didn't wake up at all
during that time?
Yes.
When I saw
that Miss Liu was sleeping,
I was careful
not to wake her.
You can leave now.
Thank you for sparing my life.
I'll bring Manager Chang in.
Xiao Yan.
Is there a rumor going on
about me having a habit
of beheading others
and turning their skulls
into wine glasses?
It's just a rumor
saying that you loved
doing that in Nanjing
and that you stopped collecting
skull glasses after returning to Liang.
After all, you are a citizen of Liang.
You have more mercy
toward your own people.
Bring Chang Xun in.
Yes, Your Highness.
Are you afraid of me
because of the rumor?
You have a reputation,
how can I not be afraid?
But you grew up in Fuyu.
You've never been to Nanjing.
And you had never visited
Liang before this.
How do you know
about this rumor?
I...
I know that even if I tell you about it,
you won't believe me.
But I'm really
not your Princess Consort.
At least
I'm not the Hua Qingge
that you think I am.
Your Highness.
I re-read the dossier
on Princess Hua Qingge from Fuyu.
There's a record
that she has been learning
martial arts since she was young.
It means that she didn't lie
in the Grand Hall today.
Greetings, Your Highness.
When Liu Xiang died,
you were the first
to enter the cell, right?
Yes.
What did you see?
I was guarding
the cell door at that time.
Then, I heard a scream
coming from Miss Liu's cell.
So, I went in.
The room was pitch black.
I was on my guard.
Then, Wang lit the candle
and we found Miss Liu's body.
Before you entered the cell,
you heard Liu Xiang
saying the phrase "Stay away", right?
Yes.
That's why
I barged into the cell.
When I noticed
that the room was pitch black,
I didn't dare to go forward recklessly.
I drew out my sword to defend myself
in case there was
anyone else in the cell.
But you said
that the cell is a locked room
without
any secret door or passage.
So, how did that person
appear out of thin air?
It's something
that confuses me as well.
So, my guess is,
maybe Miss Liu
was hallucinating due to
the demonic influence
and was killed by the Vajra Weapon.
You can leave now.
Yes, Your Highness.
I'll take my leave now.
Let's go back tonight.
We'll enter the palace tomorrow
to meet His Majesty.
Xiang!
Xiang.
I will seek justice for you.
My Xiang.
Who is it?
Gongge.
It's you.
Why are you here so late at night?
His Highness asked me
to deliver something to you.
Does he want to treat me
to some pastries?
There are too few of them.
Something has changed.
His Highness wants you
to check these pastries for him.
[Liu Residence]
This tonic porridge needs
more time to cook.
I'll let it simmer on slow fire
and it'll be ready after the banquet.
Xiang, it's late already.
It's time for you to depart.
Father,
I'm paying attention to the time.
Xiu, let's go and get changed.
Xiang.
What are you
going to surprise me with?
You'll know later.
These are my new recipes.
Give them a taste.
You are indeed
my extraordinary daughter.
Xiang.
Are you sure you don't blame me
for arranging this marriage for you?
Are you willing to marry Prince Qi?
Yes, I do.
By marrying Prince Qi,
I can learn from
the top chef in Prince Qi Residence
and have the best cooking skills
in this world.
Then, I'll cook for you.
Xiang.
Getting married
is different from cooking.
They are two different things.
I understand.
Although Prince Qi
is lacking in both
learning and practical ability,
he's not a bad person.
I won't get bullied
if I marry him.
Xiang.
This is my fault.
I shouldn't have
dragged you into this.
Who is it?
Master, it's Liu Er.
Come in.
Master.
I've sent out someone
to be our informant.
Xiu went to the East Office
to deliver some pastries to Miss Liu.
But she's not back yet.
Go.
Go and collect more information for me.
Yes, Master.
[Xuanze Hall]
Your Majesty,
Prince Lv is here.
[Xuanze Hall]
Your Highness.
His Highness has entered the palace.
He's not here.
It's okay.
I'm not here
to visit Chu.
I'm here
to visit my sister-in-law.
You are here to visit Qing?
I mean the Princess Consort.
Why?
Mister Song.
Are you sure you want to ask
about the things between ladies?
The Princess Consort
is staying at Anxiang Hall.
Let me lead the way.
It's okay.
I'll go to the pavilion over there.
You can ask her to meet me there.
Yes, Your Highness.
I'll relay the message to her now.
Your Highness.
You know that the player
of the white stones
hasn't been visiting
Prince Lv Residence lately.
Why are you looking for him here?
I'm not here to look for him.
I just
love the scenery at the pavilion.
And I can pay Qing a visit
while I enjoy the scenery.
Your Highness.
Long time no see.
♪Walk idly in the shadow of
falling flowers with floral note♪
♪Separated by death and life,
we can only meet♪
♪In dreams♪
♪Propose a toast to the moon,
I have no one to talk to♪
♪Hate to forget you♪
♪And walk away willingly♪
♪Putting on make-up
at the dressing table♪
♪Who are you with now?♪
♪Why should I be upset?♪
♪You're never my destiny♪
♪My heart just flutters unknowingly♪
♪I can't help being in love with you♪
♪Love is an absurdity♪
♪That repeats the illusion♪
♪I'm still yearning♪
♪Love eventually gets me lost♪
♪Saddened by the fading of love♪
♪I'm left with a dream♪
♪Why do I still wish♪
♪I could spend
the rest of my life with you?♪
♪Putting on make-up
at the dressing table♪
♪Who are you with now?♪
♪Why should I be upset?♪
♪You're never my destiny♪
♪My heart just flutters unknowingly♪
♪I can't help being in love with you♪
♪Love is an absurdity♪
♪That repeats the illusion♪
♪I'm still yearning♪
♪Love eventually gets me lost♪
♪Saddened by the fading of love♪
♪I'm left with a dream♪
♪Why do I still wish♪
♪I could spend
the rest of my life with you?♪