♪The moon is shining above
the broken bridge, and the lake ripples♪
♪My heart in a whirl,
with all sorts of feelings♪
♪Clouds encircle the green hills,
and people are in distress♪
♪To help all beings, to be chivalrous♪
♪I wish to ride the wind♪
♪It's never been done♪
♪At this perfect moment,
you wish to exchange♪
♪A thousand of reincarnations
for a lifetime of love♪
♪Watching the fireworks
and the full moon♪
♪With affectionate gaze♪
♪Accumulating lifetimes
of destiny to be with me♪
[Different Princess]
[Episode 11]
Your Highness.
Long time no see.
Wait,
I think I smell an aroma.
It's a kind of rare herb
called Butterfly Jiegeng.
What is it, Your Highness?
It's not a long time no see.
We just met yesterday.
Did we?
Now that you've used
Butterfly Jiegeng,
you must have taken
the antidote beforehand.
Why is your memory worse than mine?
It seems that you have already noticed.
No wonder you wanted to
smell my scent.
Your scent
is a mixture
of bitterness and freshness.
It's exactly the same as what I smelled
in the palace yesterday.
So,
we must have met
yesterday.
Don't you want to ask me
why I erased your memory?
I won't ask.
Why?
As long as we see each other,
I'm satisfied.
I don't need to get to the bottom of it.
Besides,
since you and Chu are close friends,
I'll respect your little secret.
You are indeed wise and perceptive,
more so than the rumors.
Since I won't pry into your secrets.
Then,
can you
tell me one thing?
What is it?
What's your name?
Where can I find you?
Actually,
we can be friends.
I won't interfere with your business.
I'm Gongye Qi
from Mystic Medicine House.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Gongye Qi.
Oh, so you're that weird old man
with amazing medical skills.
What are you laughing at?
Nothing.
Every time you
hear my identity,
you always say the same thing.
Yesterday,
you told me your name,
and I said the same thing?
Later when Her Highness
is done,
let her find me.
Okay.
Let's go.
[Xuanze Hall]
Your Majesty, taste this.
I've made you some lotus seed congee.
A wonderful engagement banquet,
has become such a mess.
How can I still eat?
This is
all my fault.
Who would have thought
that Liu Xiang would...
Yesterday
Feng had such a huge shock
and still hasn't recovered yet.
Feng is still sick?
Your Majesty.
When Feng was little,
he saw Imperial Consort Xian
with his own eyes.
I'm afraid
he won't be well for a while.
Let him rest.
I'll let him know.
Prince Lv.
I've asked you to investigate
the case of Liu Xiang.
But you said in your report
that Liu Xiang was killed
by the Vajra Weapon
sent by Prince Qi,
and that he's the murderer.
I didn't expect you to be so hasty.
Father,
it's true based on
what we've found so far.
However,
there are still doubts about it.
How do you dare to submit the report
when there are still doubts?
While there are doubts,
Prince Qi
must have something to do with it.
Prince Lv, you're really out of line.
Feng has been protecting and loving you
since you were a child.
How dare you accuse him?
Feng is
already so sick now.
How can he do any harm?
You are wrong.
Even if Ji Feng can't do it,
what about the Wei family behind him?
Can't they do it too?
You!
You're blaspheming!
Am I a blasphemer?
I think you know the best.
A demonic Liu Xiang is dead.
How much would you benefit from it,
do you need me to
list them all for you?
You!
Your Majesty,
Feng would never
do such a thing.
It's Prince Lv.
Liu Xiang has been
in his custody.
He's the one who made the mistake,
and did all the things.
He framed Feng.
Enough.
You're arguing in front of me,
what a shame.
I'm sorry.
I heard
that Ji Yun is in the palace today.
Go call him.
Okay.
Mother.
Why I don't see Wan'er?
Lately, she's been going out every day.
She left early in the morning.
It's hard to keep a grown girl.
Don't worry, Mother.
She's smart,
I'm sure she'll take care of herself.
She has always had a sense of propriety,
I'm not worried about her.
The one I'm worried about
is you.
Mother,
I don't know what I've done
to make you worry.
This is outrageous.
It's a disgrace
to the Your Highness' reputation.
How can he do this?
Please tell me, Mother.
There is no crown princess yet
in East Palace.
What do you have in mind?
Mother,
I have no plans to marry yet.
You are the crown prince.
Marriage is an important matter
for the fate of the nation.
It must not be a child's play.
For this, you should listen to
my decision.
Okay.
Your Highness,
Eunuch Li is here.
Crown Prince.
Your Highness,,
His Majesty
wants to see the crown prince
at the Xuanze Hall.
Go.
I'll leave for now.
Your Highness,,
I heard that Miss Liu last night,
Had an accident at the East Office.
This East Office
is a real place of trouble.
Prince Qi's wife-to-be, Liu Xiang,
was murdered last night
at the East Office's jail.
They created an illusion of evil.
This is ridiculous.
I order you and Prince Lv,
to investigate this case together.
We must find out the truth
as soon as possible.
Noted.
Go on.
I'll leave now.
[Xuanze Hall]
Chu.
Actually you don't believe
that it's Feng
sent people to kill Liu Xiang.
Why did you submit that report?
It's Ji Feng or Imperial Consort Wei,
does it make a difference?
[Xuanze Hall]
Chu.
No matter what,
we're all family.
Feng and Wan'er
wish we could go back
to the way we were
when we were children.
Even if we can't
at least I hope
you and us
won't have too much separation.
Your Highness.
Unless you can bring
the dead back to life.
Otherwise you
and I will never cross paths again
Your Highness.
Prince Lv has spoken
out of turn many times.
Why do you have to be so tolerant?
After all, it was us who
abandoned him.
[Prince Lv Residence]
Gongye Qi is just a wicked man
like Ji Chu.
[Anxiang Hall]
I don't want him
to be with Wan'er.
But what I saw just now
was too beautiful.
I can't bear to separate them.
Don't think so much.
Let's think about
what we're going to do next.
Qing.
Your Highness.
I'm here.
Your Highness, you've done talking.
Chu is back,
they are in discussion,
so I came to find you.
So, tell me.
Tell what?
Why do you like
Gongye Qi?
Is it that obvious?
I think he's special.
What's so special about him?
Being ruthless?
Or being wicked?
In my eyes,
he carries sunshine, flowers,
the bitter scent of medicine,
secrets,
and a desire to be free.
All of that made him special.
He's unlike anyone else
I've ever met.
But different doesn't always mean good.
I know
he was in the Grand Hall yesterday.
I think
that Miss Liu's demonisation
has something to do with Chu and him.
But I don't want to give up so easily.
Whether it's Chu or him.
What if
he hurts you?
He won't.
My third brother,
although his face is cold,
but he has never hurt me.
I don't think he will either.
A woman in love
can't be woken up.
Your Highness.
Can you do me a favour?
What kind of favour?
As long as you don't hurt anyone else,
I'll try to help you.
I want to leave Prince Lv Residence.
I can't help you
on this.
There's something wrong with the snack.
You're right.
Inside the snack,
there's indeed a drug
that can suppress the demonic poison.
This is the antidote.
It can make the poison
in Liu Xiang's body
re-emerge.
Alright.
What's the situation in the palace?
For Liu Xiang's case,
His Majesty has brought
in the crown prince.
It seems this is the result
of testing His Majesty.
His Majesty wants to use him
to ease our relationship
with the Wei family.
This is delusional.
Now that we've confirmed Qing
is indeed Hua Qingge,
why are you still keeping her?
Because she looks
like Hua Qingge,
but also not at the same time.
Just because she knows
what you're thinking,
you're keeping
such a dangerous person with you.
I keep her around,
on the one hand, to find out
her true identity.
On the other hand,
Ji Yun
seems to be treating her differently.
Keeping her in hand,
it's the same
as grabbing Ji Yun's weak spot.
Chu,
I hope you believe in
what you're saying.
Of course, I do.
If that's the case,
I have nothing more to say.
But you need to know that
on the road to revenge,
any leniency
will result
in immeasurable consequences.
Goodbye.
What about you?
I don't want you to hurt Wan'er.
Then keep your sister under control.
Keep her away from me.
Qing,
you made such a scene
at the banquet,
that even Mother testified for you,
If you leave suddenly,
what circumstance are you
placing the others in?
I know.
Running away just like that
is a bit ungrateful.
But I'm a small-timer,
whether I leave here
or die here,
no one really cares.
You are now
the princess of Fuyu, Hua Qingge.
You're also Liang's Princess Consort Lv.
But you know
I'm not at all
the princess of Fuyu, Hua Qingge.
If this got exposed,
Ji Chu is a man of honor,
he'll be fine.
But my life would be in danger.
Your Highness,
I just want to live.
I'll have to discuss
this with Chu.
No, you can't tell Ji Chu.
If you tell him
I'll die.
Why are you so afraid of Chu?
No one in this world is
not afraid of him.
How about this?
I can put you
in the Jingzhi Library,
but I have a condition.
It is
if there's a palace banquet
or an occasion that requires
the presence of Princess Consort Lv.
You must attend
as that identity.
I promise you.
But, Qing,
we can't hide this from Chu.
I know.
But Your Highness,
since you've decided to help me,
are we
good friends now?
Of course.
From now on,
can I call you Wan'er?
Of course not.
Her Highness is honorable,
her name is not to be blasphemed.
Of course, she can.
It's just a name,
I have always been indifferent to these.
Wan'er.
As long as you're firm and have my back,
I'm sure Ji Chu won't dare to
do anything to me.
After all, in my novel,
Ji Chu's only love
is his sister.
Actually,
Even if you stay in Prince Lv Residence,
I can still
protect you.
But I still have to go.
You want to leave Prince Lv Residence?
You just said you'd take care of me,
why are you so scared now?
Where are you going?
Your Highness.
I'm not the real
Princess Consort Lv.
I've been a servant girl for so long.
You must be tired of it.
Why don't you just kick me
out of the Residence?
Are you going to find Ji Yun?
Sort of.
My future is for sure
bound to Ji Yun and Lin Xiyao
because I need to protect them both.
So,
you approached me,
and the things you did
are all to help Ji Yun?
Yes.
I thought you already knew that.
I've always stood by Ji Yun.
Why?
Do I still need to explain?
Who would want to stay
with a cold and perverted
murderer
who has no boundaries.
This is human,
we all want to avoid harm.
Before you question others,
don't you ask yourself
what have you done?
So,
in your heart,
Ji Yun is a kind
and warm existence.
For sure.
He's everyone's dream guy.
And yours too?
Of course,
am I not human?
Anyway, since we've talked about it.
I can't stay
in Prince Lv Residence anymore.
You can kill me if you want.
Chu.
Although I don't know why you
fought with Qing like that,
I think you've misunderstood.
Misunderstood what?
She wants to leave
the Prince Lv Residence,
not because she wants to find Ji Yun,
is because she wants to go
to Jingzhi Library.
I'll go and settle down first.
Is she telling the truth?
Yes, Your Highness.
Do you want me to follow her?
No need if she's going
to Jingzhi Library.
Okay.
[Jingzhi Library]
Hold it.
Okay.
Please come again next time.
Let me know when you have new books.
Sure.
Take care.
Master, you're back.
Your brother has been here
waiting for a long time.
Ji Yun?
Ji Yun.
Your Highness.
Why are you here?
Mother complained to me today,
that Her Highness has been
running around a lot.
She was worried.
So she asked me to come and take a look.
Yun, let's talk inside.
What's going on?
There's nothing wrong
with the blood color,
and there's no toxicity.
Why has it turned blue now?
I can't tell what kind of poison it is.
It's better to go
to the Mystic Medicine House,
and ask Gongge.
What?
Are you investigating
the Liu Xiang case too?
Right.
Liu Xiang is the future
Princess Consort Qi.
She can't die in vain.
That's why Father asked me to help Chu,
to investigate together.
How is it in vain?
It's clearly Ji Chu who did it.
Qing,
how do you know
it's Chu?
Just think of it as my intuition.
In this case,
I think
it's not Chu who did it.
What do you mean?
I went to the East Office
and found the case file of Liu Xiang.
There is something suspicious.
It's not that snack, is it?
Chu
has already sent someone
to investigate that snack.
It indeed has a problem.
Other than that,
what else is there to suspect?
The time of death
is suspicious too.
It's demonic poison.
After being poisoned,
it causes changes in the body.
Like a monster.
So there is such a drug
in this world.
I've only read about similar
descriptions in books.
I didn't think it existed.
But
why when I
first did the autopsy,
I didn't find it?
All things are mutually exclusive.
In this world,
there are poisons
that can demonize people,
and certainly there are drugs
that can hide them too.
It's easy to understand.
Thank you for the lesson.
These two guards today
are not the same as last night.
Where are the guards from yesterday?
To answer Your Highness,
they've changed shifts to rest.
Open the cell.
I need to check some more clues.
- Yes, Your Highness.
Go get Chang Xun
and the two guards from last night.
Yes.
Those who entered
this chamber last night,
one of them
must be the murderer.
Then the one who is most suspected
is Chang Xun,
who first arrived at the scene.
According to the testimony.
Chang Xun was the first
to enter the cell.
But it was dark inside,
he didn't dare to enter
until the two guards
arrived in time.
They lit the candles.
Then only the three of them
found the body
of Liu Xiang.
The testimonies of the three
were surprisingly consistent.
There are no gaps in their testimonies.
There's always a candle burning.
Why were the candles out
when they arrived?
Also,
who put out the candles?
What if Liu Xiang put it out?
That doesn't make sense.
Then who could have inserted
the Vajra Weapon accurately
into Liu Xiang's heart
in the dark?
Your Highness,
Wang Senior and Wang Junior
have been taken by Prince Lv.
Commander Chang is on leave
due to illness.
Alright.
You can leave.
Yes, Your Highness.
What if it was Chang Xun who
blew out the candles?
If it was him, it doesn't seem like
there's enough time to commit the crime.
You can't tell without practice.
How about this?
Let's run through the
process of the case.
Sure.
I'm Liu Xiang.
You're Chang Xun.
The two guards outside
are Wang Senior and Wang Junior.
Yes.
Stay back.
No.
Even if Chang Xun had killed
Liu Xiang in the dark,
he'd still be caught red-handed.
There's not enough time.
Right.
What if Chang Xun
killed Liu Xiang first,
and then put out the candles?
Let's do it again.
♪Walk idly in the shadow of
falling flowers with floral note♪
♪Separated by death and life,
we can only meet♪
♪In dreams♪
♪Propose a toast to the moon,
I have no one to talk to♪
♪Hate to forget you♪
♪And walk away willingly♪
♪Putting on make-up
at the dressing table♪
♪Who are you with now?♪
♪Why should I be upset?♪
♪You're never my destiny♪
♪My heart just flutters unknowingly♪
♪I can't help being in love with you♪
♪Love is an absurdity♪
♪That repeats the illusion♪
♪I'm still yearning♪
♪Love eventually gets me lost♪
♪Saddened by the fading of love♪
♪I'm left with a dream♪
♪Why do I still wish♪
♪I could spend
the rest of my life with you?♪
♪Putting on make-up
at the dressing table♪
♪Who are you with now?♪
♪Why should I be upset?♪
♪You're never my destiny♪
♪My heart just flutters unknowingly♪
♪I can't help being in love with you♪
♪Love is an absurdity♪
♪That repeats the illusion♪
♪I'm still yearning♪
♪Love eventually gets me lost♪
♪Saddened by the fading of love♪
♪I'm left with a dream♪
♪Why do I still wish♪
♪I could spend
the rest of my life with you?♪