♪The moon is shining above
the broken bridge, and the lake ripples♪
♪My heart in a whirl,
with all sorts of feelings♪
♪Clouds encircle the green hills,
and people are in distress♪
♪To help all beings, to be chivalrous♪
♪I wish to ride the wind♪
♪It's never been done♪
♪At this perfect moment,
you wish to exchange♪
♪A thousand of reincarnations
for a lifetime of love♪
♪Watching the fireworks
and the full moon♪
♪With affectionate gaze♪
♪Accumulating lifetimes
of destiny to be with me♪
[Different Princess]
[Episode 16]
Manager Wang,
the new blind maid is here.
Come closer
and let me have a look.
Quick.
Sir.
Sir, please spare me.
I'm sorry I bumped into you.
I deserve to die.
No.
I can't die yet.
Alright.
If you see something you shouldn't,
if you have any ill intentions,
you'll be killed.
I can't see even if I want to.
This place is heavily guarded.
According to the mark left by Qing,
she should have entered here.
Qing said that we can find
Prince Qi in this way,
which means Prince Qi is here too.
Qing has always been perceptive.
And this place is guarded
by private soldiers.
It's very convincing.
But Qing is alone in there.
I'm worried about her.
I'll ask Fang Cheng
to come and help us.
But
before that,
we must rescue
Feng and Qing as soon as possible
and then see if
there are any other breakthroughs.
Let's go.
It's good that you can't see,
so you'll live a long life.
You'd fit right in here.
Change her into something clean.
You'll work here
as a personal attendant from now on.
Ji Yun, Yao,
when are you coming to save me?
It's so scary in here.
Why did you come out early?
What's wrong with your pulse rate?
I told you
not to get upset
when taking a medicinal bath.
I'm fine.
We've come this far in our plan.
You're not
going soft, are you?
Of course not.
You can't drink cold tea.
I spent a lot of precious herbs on you
getting you in better health
when you were a kid.
You're such a nag.
Have some hot tea.
Xiao Yan came
to report
that the crown prince and Miss Lin
have gone to
the weapons camp to investigate.
I'd like to see
what the crown prince can find out.
Qing...
You're not easy to disguise
with your fair face.
And so are you.
This is the Wei family's
secret camp.
Imperial Consort Wei
would never have expected
that the precious son
she's looking for
is right under their noses.
The more dangerous a place is,
the safer it is.
Ji Chu is so mean.
Remember,
when it's done, leave no one alive.
Is that the order of His Highness?
It is both the order of me
and His Highness.
No way.
I've got to find Ji Feng
and get him out of here.
We can't let Ji Chu
go further down the path of
fratricide.
Hurry up.
Stop there!
Where are you going?
You're not allowed to
wander around here.
I'm going to the toilet.
Go ahead.
Get back here quickly.
Quick.
Hurry up.
Put it over there.
I'll see who dares to slack off again.
Get to work.
You two, move these out of here.
What are you doing here?
Hurry up. Come on.
Hurry up.
Quick.
Mister,
I...
Aren't you the blind girl?
Yes.
I got lost by accident.
Where is the toilet?
Over there.
Over there?
Come here.
Yes.
Take her to the toilet.
Here comes a blind girl.
How troublesome. Let's go.
Hurry up.
Get to work. Do you have a death wish?
Come on.
Those guys over there, don't be lazy.
This place is actually
a camp for making weapons.
Who has the audacity to do this?
The missing people in the city
must have become
undeclared laborers here.
I've worked on
undeclared labor cases.
They are often tortured
in inhuman ways.
Sometimes to the point of death.
I wonder how Qing
and Prince Qi are doing.
Not only do we need to find them
as soon as possible,
but we also need to find out
who's behind this weapons camp.
Okay.
You two, hurry up.
We're waiting for you. Hurry up!
You're still dragging your feet, huh?
Let's play it by ear.
Do you have a death wish?
Hurry up.
Come on.
Hurry up. I'm talking about you.
Hurry up.
Get to work. Do you have a death wish?
Quick.
Those guys over there, don't be lazy.
That's not enough.
You'll have to get
another load of water.
Sir,
can we take a break
before we get back to work?
You look like strangers.
Why haven't I seen you before?
We're new.
New?
Are you in the same batch
as the blind girl?
Yes.
Where is she now?
She and I are from the same hometown.
We can look after each other here.
She's working under Manager Wang.
Manager Wang?
Looks like a secret letter.
I wonder what it's about.
It's none of my business anyway.
It's my life that matters.
[Send someone immediately to...]
[Prince Lv Residence]
Your Highness,
the Wei family has taken action.
A team of spies has entered the city.
Good.
Stick to the plan.
Yes, Your Highness.
This is the Wei family's weaponry.
Is it possible that this weapon camp
belongs to the Wei family?
The iron is of very poor quality.
It's an inferior weapon.
If all of Liang's soldiers
use such inferior weapons
to fight,
there will be a lot of
innocent casualties.
Such greed can't be tolerated.
Your Highness,
Aren't the weapons of the Liang army
always
supplied by the government?
Why would there be a private production?
It's all about profit.
They're making inferior weapons
to replace official ones.
The profits are huge.
Every year, large sums of military funds
go into
their own pockets.
Ordinary people can't do it,
but with the Wei family's power,
it's possible.
Who are you? What are you doing here?
Sirs,
we accidentally
got wet carrying water,
so we're drying our clothes by the fire.
I hope you can make it easier for us.
Don't you know
we're not allowed to enter
the foundry at night?
Sirs, here's the thing.
We're new.
We don't know a lot of the rules yet.
Please forgive us.
If that's the case,
you two are coming with me
to the supervisor's office
to receive your punishment.
Come on.
Let's go.
Yes.
I can't believe it's you.
Chu sent you to rescue me, right?
Silly boy,
can I say
it's all the work of your third brother?
Fine.
Brotherly harmony is the way to go.
Yes.
Prince Lv sent me here.
He always speaks with forked tongue.
You know that.
I know.
It's all my fault.
In the past, as an elder brother,
I didn't treat him well
and I let him suffer.
I've learned a lot
from my ordeal this time.
Congratulations,
you've finally matured.
Has Chu surrounded this place
with his men?
Let's send a signal
to level this place
and arrest
these crooks.
Arrest them all.
Your Highness,
you're really overthinking this time.
Now...
Now,
I'm the only one who got in.
How are we going to get out of here?
I don't want
to be here a moment longer.
Don't worry.
I've got a plan.
I've been asking around.
They take these
swill buckets out every day at 1 AM.
If we hide in two of them,
we'll make it out.
You want me to go into the swill bucket?
No.
It's a disgrace.
So you mean you're
not leaving?
Where have
you two been?
I've been looking for you
for a long time.
Chen,
are they your men?
Yes, they're new.
They're slow in their work.
Come with me.
There's still a lot of work.
Alright, get back to your work.
You'll be punished severely
the next time
you wander around.
All right.
Let's go.
No way.
I can't stand it.
If this goes on,
we'll be caught for sure.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
I'll help you out.
How?
Your Highness, I'm sorry.
But we staying alive
is all that matters.
You two,
go to the back kitchen of the restaurant
and pull a few buckets of swill.
Those laborers
will have to
live on that swill tomorrow.
Yes, we'll get going now.
It's the crown prince.
That's great.
Thank God for that.
My plan is perfect now.
Your Highness,
we've been looking
into this for so long,
we're just going to give up now?
Let's find a place
to dump the swill wagon.
Come on, get on the wagon first.
There seems to be
someone in the bucket.
We should be out of the camp soon.
Victory is in sight.
There are people in the buckets.
It's you.
No.
Save your strength
and come back for us.
Don't move.
You'll never see the light of day
working for the Wei family,
let alone achieve great things.
The Wei family has lost its power.
A wise man submits circumstances.
If you want to live,
Prince Lv will spare your lives.
If you want to die,
I'll fulfill your wish.
I failed to save you,
and I've put my own life
on the line.
Why am I so unfortunate?
How dare you say that?
You have a lot of nerve, huh?
How dare you attack me?
If it wasn't for saving you,
I wouldn't be here
suffering for nothing.
Now,
I can't even use my escape skills.
[Wanshou Hall]
Duke,
why did you enter Xuanze Hall
when you weren't summoned?
Your Majesty,
I've found out
the whereabouts of Prince Qi.
Where's Prince Qi?
Your Majesty,
Prince Qi is currently imprisoned
in Wei Zhao's secret camp.
Wei Zhao is Feng's uncle.
Why would he imprison Feng?
Your Majesty,
Wei Zhao is holding Prince Qi hostage
with the intention of rebelling.
Audacious!
Your Majesty, please calm down.
I have solid evidence that Wei Zhao
is making private weapons
and training his own soldiers.
The crown prince is now investigating
in the Wei family's weapons camp.
The crown prince is there too?
Your Majesty, please make a decision
as soon as possible
to save two princes from danger.
Your Highness,
all of the spies
sent by the Wei family
have been taken under control.
Duke has also
gained His Majesty's trust.
Your Highness,
shall we immediately conduct a siege?
Be patient.
Let's wait for a little longer.
How much longer do we have to wait?
Till the terrified man
struggles.
What did you say?
The teams of spies
we sent out have all gone missing?
How reckless!
You're too reckless.
Why are you here?
Sister,
have you ever thought
about the consequences
of deploying men behind my back?
I couldn't care less!
I must find Feng
immediately!
You...
Feng's disappearance is strange,
and now, all our spies
have disappeared.
We must have
fallen into a trap.
Well,
what should we do now?
I've given orders
to make sure
no one enters or leaves the camp.
Sister,
don't act rashly again.
I'm going back to the camp
to erase all traces.
You... You mean...
Destroy all evidence
and leave no witness alive.
I have one more thing to report.
The crown prince and Miss Lin
have found evidence
of the Wei family's
illicit weaponry at the weapons camp.
The crown prince is really
swift at what he does.
Besides,
in order to save Prince Qi,
Miss Qing's captured as well.
Qing?
Why is she involved in this?
Wherever there's trouble,
there she is.
That's good, too.
From now on,
no one
will be able to spoil our plans.
Order Duke to lead the troops
to surround the camp.
I'll go first.
Ji Chu,
you should know
that if you take action in advance,
we may not be able
to get rid of the Wei family.
Are you going to disregard
our revenge plan for a woman?
Qing is my woman.
No one can hurt her.
Calm down.
Is it worth
destroying our years of planning
for a woman?
You know Qing is my wife.
So what?
She was supposed to die!
Say no more.
I know what I'm doing.
Ji Chu!
Gongge.
Chu,
for her,
you hurt me
regardless of our brotherhood.
A bit higher.
A little bit higher.
Will you hurry up?
If I hadn't hurt my foot,
I wouldn't need you.
It's such a huge disgrace.
I've
never been stepped on.
Cut the crap.
Give me the red beans.
Red beans.
Everyone is equal before death.
We need to find a way
to get out of here.
Oh, no.
My foot's really broken this time.
Are you okay?
I'm still alive.
Who are you?
This is a restricted area.
You can't enter.
I'm from the kitchen
to deliver preserved fruit
to Manager Wang.
Leave the preserved fruit here.
You can go now.
It's good. Let's have one more.
Miss Lin,
why do you
carry laxatives around?
It's required for my job.
I've got a few more drugs here
in case we need them.
Even though the preserved fruit
was coated with laxatives,
how could you be sure
they'd eat it?
I wasn't sure.
Seeing how hard they work,
so I just gave it a shot.
♪Walk idly in the shadow of
falling flowers with floral note♪
♪Separated by death and life,
we can only meet♪
♪In dreams♪
♪Propose a toast to the moon,
I have no one to talk to♪
♪Hate to forget you♪
♪And walk away willingly♪
♪Putting on make-up
at the dressing table♪
♪Who are you with now?♪
♪Why should I be upset?♪
♪You're never my destiny♪
♪My heart just flutters unknowingly♪
♪I can't help being in love with you♪
♪Love is an absurdity♪
♪That repeats the illusion♪
♪I'm still yearning♪
♪Love eventually gets me lost♪
♪Saddened by the fading of love♪
♪I'm left with a dream♪
♪Why do I still wish♪
♪I could spend
the rest of my life with you?♪
♪Putting on make-up
at the dressing table♪
♪Who are you with now?♪
♪Why should I be upset?♪
♪You're never my destiny♪
♪My heart just flutters unknowingly♪
♪I can't help being in love with you♪
♪Love is an absurdity♪
♪That repeats the illusion♪
♪I'm still yearning♪
♪Love eventually gets me lost♪
♪Saddened by the fading of love♪
♪I'm left with a dream♪
♪Why do I still wish♪
♪I could spend
the rest of my life with you?♪