Timing and Subtitles brought by Room No. 9 Volunteer Team @ Viki
[ Room No. 9 ]
[ March 14, 2108, White Day ]
- Hi, you're here.
- You like it?
It's so simple.
Do I seem too materialistic?
Minimalism, minimum life.
I'm not good with those concepts.
You didn't show her what I picked out during lunchtime.
I'm sorry. I didn't know it was for her.
We can engrave on this.
I was thinking, "Veritas." What do you think?
I was getting bored waiting for you.
So pretty!
Totally my taste!
It's too thin to put an engraving on it.
This one looks perfect this way.
[ Birthday ]
Cheongdamdong, 99-11.
This one.
- A set of matching rings?
- Yeah, matching rings.
- You got a problem with that?
- Oh, no.
Not at all. I'll be back.
Engrave a word on it. "Veritas."
Berry? As in strawberry?
Strawberry-like love?
Veritas.
I loved Ki Yoo Jin.
The fact that he's a company hospital doctor.
Amazing good looks that suck in all the gazes of women.
More than that...
the title that he's the
one and only brother of Chairman Ki San of HSC Group.
That was so precious and lovely to me.
Big Unnie.
Where did you get this?
- What is it?
- Wow, a matching ring!
Ki Yoo Jin...
was a compensation for my dark past.
He was a shining brooch with a 10 carat diamond on my bosom.
Veritas...
It's a Latin word.
Truth, trust, faith.
It's not the type of common trust people always bring up.
It's an absolute truth between two people
and absolute trust.
Veritas is the very first necessity and
perfection for love.
You realize how precious they are to you
only after having lost it and lived through it.
While I lived as Hae Yi...
I guess I didn't truly love him.
Only in this old and sad body,
I realize I truly love Yoo Jin.
[ Room No. 9 ]
[ Episode 7 ]
Thank you for the Seochodong incident.
At the resort...
What are you doing?
That's a lot of stitches.
When did you get hurt?
That's pretty bad.
At the resort last time. Right?
- Let go.
- It's a sharp cut. Glass?
- I said let go!
- How did you get this cut!
If you know how I got hurt...
Are you allowed to question just anyone like a suspect if you're a detective?
So...
you just have to tell me how and where you got hurt.
Two days ago at home.
I hurt myself grieving for the director.
I broke my wine glass while drinking.
Which hospital? The name.
Why are you being so obsessive about this?
Are you interested in me?
I'm worried for you. So what?
Is it that hard to tell me the name of the hospital?
I don't know why you're doing this, but
I told everything I need to say at the reference witness questioning.
I heard he's your friend.
If you're curious, ask Detective Park.
If you want to know more, bring me a warrant or subpoena.
Lee Sang Hee of the NFS!
Are you connected to him jumping off a hotel?
How will you explain the bruises on your legs that I saw in Park Chul Soon's room?
I'm pretty clumsy.
I fall easily.
Two days ago at home.
I broke my wine glass while drinking.
Change the date of her getting the stitches to 30th instead of 24th?
Yeah.
Fabricating medical record is illegal.
You think changing the medical record would do it?
If Oh Bong Sam thinks you're the suspect...
you won't get out of this easily.
Right. It would be just putting a band-aid on a wound.
You came because you believe that I'm Eulji Hae Yi, right?
I'll relay the message to the Chairman.
Chairman.
I heard Detective Oh Bong Sam is asking Attorney Eulji about Director Ma's death.
I'll toss it over to the Chief Prosecutor.
Just let it be until she's on absolute edge.
The golden time is when you've got your neck snatched by the hunting dog.
Whether I'd rescue Eulji Hae Yi
or throw her into a sewer.
Yes.
Oh, my! Oh! Big Unnie!
Unnie! Unnie! Unnie!
If you're so tormented like this, you can stop now.
Killing and dying. Paying back for what I got...
That's not the only way to take revenge.
Oh Bong Sam. What will you do about him?
Didn't you hate being in prison?
You want to go back there having finally escaped it after 34 years?
For murder?
Let's run out of the country.
I think that'd be good.
Right.
I think I should go.
Oh. Right. Thailand?
Canada? Australia? Where? Just say it.
Pack first?
Not decide on destination first?
True. Who cares how we go about it?
Geez...
You should pack up the safe first.
Huh?
You must love that feather thing.
The Seongbukdong Madam wanted that one.
It's a limited edition with only 50 in existence.
This is the only one in the country.
Don't you look fancy?
Hello, Madam.
It's rude to look fancier than the madam of the house.
It's pretty.
I'll accept it wholeheartedly.
My friend's daughter is getting married in the fall.
Thanks.
You were like this last time.
Did you fall for me, dear?
The Chairman...
loves you very much, huh?
Well, if you're a wife of a conglomerate owner,
everyone thinks you give up being a woman but live for money.
It's not true.
I live for love.
Dear.
The Chairman and I are still so passionate.
Excuse me for a moment.
Sure.
I'll take you to the powder foom.
No, it's okay.
I already know.
Unnie, he's coming up right now.
Unnie, why don't you answer me?
My lady, you're still so girly.
I'm having tea with Hae Yi.
Have a seat, Honey.
Did you get caught?
Should I come in?
- Attorney Eunji?
- Yeah, she's in the powder room.
It's not easy overstaying your welcome as a guest.
She's gutsy. I like her.
Chicago University...
I heard Chicago is similar to here.
[ Summer of 1984 ]
It must be so hot to study there.
You know...
ramie fiber undershirt with sleeves.
Ten.
Ten underwears.
50 ramen.
Beef ramen for nutrition.
Okay.
Is that all?
Oh, gochujang! Parilla leaves and canned food.
Prepare everything and ship them to San.
You know the dorm address to Chicago University, right?
Unnie!
Attorney! I almost died.
I was wondering if you got caught, did something happen, should I go in...
Did you find the recorder?
I think I was wrong.
- I was scared with nothing to show for!
- No.
I think I remember...
something I had forgotten.
What happened to the real Ki San of Chicago University?
I don't know that far into it.
Chu Young Bae is living as Ki San.
So, doesn't that mean the real Ki San is dead logically speaking?
Could be or not.
Unexpected things could always happen.
Either he went missing or got into an accident in the States.
I'm 99% certain about this.
If he's dead, the important thing would be how and why he died.
And we must find that out.
[ 1984, Director Bong Sa Dal ]
[ December 27, 1984, Study Dorm in Shinlimdong ]
- Hye Sun.
- Oppa!
Geez, girl. Seriously.
This is for dinner and...
this is your breakfast.
How about this one?
Your late night snack.
Really?
Catching criminals by the day and studying for the bar by the night.
Could you survive that?
The cause of death is exhaust poisoning supposedly, but his cervical spine is broken.
He's only been dead for four hours, but the livor mortis is at its peak.
On top of that the livor mortis shows mobility.
Did the corpse get up and dance around or something?
All the evidence point to Jang Hwa Sa's innocence.
You got into a law school at a top-notch school, yet you took a break and took a police exam.
Is it to support your sister?
None of your business.
I'm considering having you as my brother-in-law.
Wow, she's a good cook.
Delicious.
Have your sister become San Hae Corporation's madam.
I'm thinking of putting her in a place of envy of all women.
[ Personal Information: Kam Mi Ran ]
What's this crap?
She's a secretary Attorney Eulji recently hired.
Director Park, how are you handling your job...
that trash like this is on the Chairman's table?
May I ask for...
a favor, Hyungnim?
[ Law Firm Damjang ]
I'm sorry, but would you please park it in the basement parking?
This is the director's spot.
I guess it's my spot starting today then.
Take care of it.
Attorney Eul!
Gosh! You're so hurried. Is there a fire in the building or something?
Close to having a fire.
We have a new director.
A new director...
Who is it?
Not one of the senior partners.
He's an outsider.
[ December 28, 1984, Jongwoon Police Station ]
There's always someone who tells different stories with one mouth.
They all admit that they're the culprit in here.
They put fingerprint stamp.
But once they're at the Prosecutors' Office,
they always change their story in court.
How do you think I handle trash who screw with me?
Rip their mouth.
Rip!
Whole wheat, right?
Did you find anything on Butterfly Sleep Hospital?
The identity of the woman who died giving birth?
Let me eat first.
We even feed suspects before we start our questioning.
Lots of onions on whole wheat bread, right?
Yes.
Should I put one more sauce for you? It'd be good.
No, thank you.
I did find something.
Someone who knows about the hospital very well.
Who is it?
Here.
Choi Young Hee.
She worked as a nurse practitioner in Joongbu Hospital in 1987.
- She's currently serving her sentence.
- Serving her sentence?
She made and sold some diet pills mixing in psychotropic medicine.
And someone died.
So, she's currently at Cheongwon Prison
helping out at the dispensary running small errands.
This woman...
Don't put on a show.
Take your baton and get to work.
Please reinstate me to homicide division.
All this...
Is it relevant to the NFS report you obtained illegally?
I can't tell you that right now.
Can't you just trust me, Hyungnim?
I know you like me.
I have my wife whom I love much more than Oh Bong Sam.
See, see, see?
For me to take care of you too is a bit, you know...
Even if I can't be back here...
I'll never give up on this case.
This is as far as our friendship goes, man!
How dare you, punk! Stop right there, man!
Where should I line up...
I'll stand in front of you.
Wait, does a part-timer need a meeting, too?
Intern or part-timer, isn't it same difference?
Besides, I'm a special hire, not a part-timer.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're actually part-timer.
A part-timer with a gold trim around her.
The high-handed part-timer!
Did you just find out?
Geez, geez, geez! Seriously!
What in the world?
Are we in a night club or something?
- Yes. - This is Geum Ja Young from the secretary's office.
He'd like to meet with you exactly at half past the hour.
Attorney Eulji is here.
Is my presence here uncomfortable for you?
I was a bit surprised.
Your fast appointment and...
instead of your installation ceremony on your first day,
you're meeting with the employees.
I guess so.
They say eyes are a window to our souls.
We need to sit close like this to open up.
I met you in this office for the first time over Chan Sung's case.
It was memorable.
Your eyes were sparkling.
Filled with your ambition to succeed.
Your eyes have changed a lot.
People do change.
I see.
What is your strategy for the second day in court for my nephew?
[ Cheongwon, Ki Se Woong's villa ]
Chairman.
I'm So Young Cheol. It's my honor!
There still are guys like him these days.
Have a seat.
Your great beauty sure has dwindled.
Cut the bull****.
You came because you believe I'm Eungi Hae Yi.
I'll get to the point.
That woman Jang Hwa Sa...
Is she crazy or normal?
I asked you about our rebuttal strategy.
Not yet...
Not yet?
This is the strategy for now.
Remember it.
Not just yet...
the original file 0977 was submitted to the court.
We can't confirm the validity of the analysis.
Now that Lee Sang Hee who produced the document is dead,
the Prosecution has lost its witness.
Even if the court...
is suspicious of the file 0978 analysis,
they have no other option but to use file 0978 analysis as the evidence.
They bribed Lee Sang Hee, right?
Yes.
If Lee Sang Hee had testified,
you'd have to give up your attorney title.
His suicide is Godsent for you.
It's fortunate for Chan Sung as well.
True.
I'll personally check Chan Sung's case myself and receive reports.
Go ahead.
Prove that you're Eulji Hae Yi.
05422207189719.
Six junior and senior partners share that account.
- I think that's enough.
- Yes.
Inmate 122 definitely had DID.
[ DID: Dissociative identity disorder ]
Are you saying she's normal then?
Well...
for me to view this as a simple case of DID...
she seems a bit different.
Different?
I didn't expect her to deny our visit.
What should we do?
Yes, I got it, Chief.
Dr. Ki Yoo Jin, you can go in alone.
- What the heck?
- Please wait out here.
It's not a cafe here. Coming and going on their whim.
If Jang's case is closed, that's it.
Please go in.
[ Examination Room ]
Dr. Ki!
You just turned down a visit.
- But you look happy to see me.
- Well...
now we can be alone.
What could be the reason you're here...
to see me?
I want to know about the Butterfly Sleep Hospital.
My goodness!
Who knew that a 30 year old "Butterfly" would make me money.
My husband's bank account.
After you deposit,
I'll tell you everything about the "Butterfly."
Come back after your deposit.
- I'll do it right now.
- What?
It's a great world these days.
And I'm the one only one
rotting away in this great world.
I deposited your amount.
Then run a full test on this.
[ Full Lab: Comprehensive blood test ]
- You can ask Hyeom Yeo hospital for this.
- Geez.
It'll cost money. I'd have to pay for it.
Plus, San Hae Hospital is better.
I'll mail you the results.
Please tell me about Butterfly Sleep Obstetrics Center.
Deposit first, delivery second.
Delivery?
I mean, okay.
Dr. Ki,
here's a preview.
Aigoo, you look so disgusted.
December 24, 1984.
The meteorite ruined the hospital.
[ Butterfly Sleep Obstetrics Medical Center ]
I know that part.
Then what about the foreigner who died giving birth?
She was a foreigner?
She didn't understand Korean at all
and even had an English name.
What was her name?
If you're curious...
Father.
Where did you and Mom first meet?
Do you...
believe in miracles, mysteries...
whatever you want to call it...
which occur outside of...
human logic?
I don't believe them.
Especially Attorney Eulji being Jang Hwa Sa.
[Viki Ver]
tvN E07 'Room No. 9'
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Morgan Kim.
She died in the Ki Chan Sung accident.
Since they lost the civil lawsuit,
her compensation was tiny due to her foreigner status.
That's how SHC handles things.
But that compensation was donated per her will.
She had a will? Before she died?
She's an adoptee who never married.
Foreigners tend to make wills beforehand.
She donated everything she had to Chicago University as scholarship.
I see.
Give me the file.
Chicago University.
[ University of Chicago ]
That's her.
My baby's a genius, a genius.
What does it say?
Ask the smart attorney to read English. Why ask me?
"My dear friend Esther."
"I'm on my way to see you..."
"after 34 years."
You didn't bring me coffee.
I was craving for it.
CEO Ki San attended Chicago University, right?
And Morgan Kim was a faculty member.
CEO Ki San and Morgan Kim attended school together.
But then...
she was hit by her classmate's son's car and died.
Is this not an accident...
but a murder?
Was it really Ki Chan Sung?
What's the reason?
What's the use for an attorney to know all that?
Your job is to focus on...
getting a "not guilty" verdict at the trial.
Was bribing Lee Sang Hee to make it a "faulty brake hose"
done to cover up a murder?
How should I know that?
You're talking nonsense.
Guard, I'm done.
You knew the truth!
- Guard!
- Two people died.
Morgan Kim and Seo Eun Young!
Do attorneys only work for money?
Were you defending wealth and not the people?
Whomever and whichever crime, even murder?
Is this what you've been doing?
If you don't win Ki Chan Sung's case,
you'll be charged with Ma Hyun Cheol's murder.
Therefore...
don't mess around with my body.
Don't put my body in danger!
That body...
isn't yours...
but mine.
Focus on Ki Chan Sung's trial. Nothing else.
The visit's over per the inmate's request.
How could the police not know about this?
Because they thought it was an accident.
Everything's tangled up.
Gosh, so complicated.
I can see clearly now.
Ki Chan Sung's car accident.
NFS' Lee Sang Hee.
Morgan Kim from Chicago University.
Seo Eun Young was an innocent bystander,
and my mom getting hurt...
All these are connected.
What?
Chu Young Bae.
People who found out or suspected that
Ki San is Chu Young Bae are all dead.
I'm getting the chills.
Then what should we do next?
The real Ki San and Esther.
When we find their trail, we'll complete this puzzle.
Do attorneys only work for money?
Were you defending wealth and not the people?
Whomever and whichever crime, even murder?
Is this what you've been doing?
- Unnie!
- What's wrong?
Unnie!
I told you to bring a summons.
I don't think our relationship requires such things.
Just what is your relationship with her?
She made me sugar water.
We got dusty together.
We recited poetry.
I carried her on my back in the rain.
Can't we grab some soju without a summons?
When I lived in Yeongdo,
I was close with a neighbor hyung.
He was a prodigy who got into Canada's Toronto University at age 15.
He was our town's superhero, like Batman.
What are you trying to say?
It's a drinking story, just listen.
He came to visit Yeongdo during his vacation.
He saw his old friends and
ate spicy rice cakes with fishcake.
He was having a ball.
There's this narrow stairwell in Yeongdo.
While he was fooling around with his friend there,
he accidentally...
pushed his friend and...
the friend ended up dying.
I'm sure he was scared.
"Oh, my life is over."
"I'm leaving in a few days. I'll hide this."
So he threw his dead friend into the sea.
And...
what happened next?
While running away from the police car...
he suffered an accident.
That hyung had a lot to lose.
People with a lot to lose make foolish decisions.
Thanks for the genius hyung story...
but it's too heavy for a drinking story.
The investigation's over.
Don't bring up Director Ma again.
I want to help you.
You had your reasons and circumstances.
I'm not here to harass you, but to help you!
Does he have any evidence?
What did you talk about?
About his childhood neighborhood hyung.
- Hey!
- Whoa!
Dr. Park, you're immature.
- Coffee?
- Had some already.
The blood test you requested.
What's ♪122?
That's what the vial's label said.
Attorney Bang, please come in.
Fighting!
Bang Sang Soo.
Chundang Gwangju Songjong.
4th group and an intern for the past 11 months.
Yes, correct.
You still live at Silimdong study dorms.
Why don't you get a loan?
If you're an attorney intern,
you can easily pull up to 10 million won.
Why not do that and move?
There's always a possibility of getting fired.
I also lived at Silimdong hills area.
It seems that Attorney Eul's more distracted
after the Hyojadong case than before.
Jang Hwa Sa's re-trial?
She ignores us and is always
always only with Ms. Kam.
That's the reason she'd ignore us for.
Jang Hwa Sa.
- Bang Sang Soo.
- Yes?
Starting today...
why don't you be my ringer finger?
What?
Director, I can't be your lover.
After I become a full time, I'll be married.
From a ring finger to a right arm...
then the shoulder.
Am I being promoted to full-time?
You're very naive.
From now on, report everything to me.
Especially about Attorney Eulji...
even her personal life.
I'll be your personal security cam.
Is it my turn now?
You're a special hire.
Part-time.
What happened?
I waited for two days and didn't see the Director.
That's good.
There's no point in clashing.
Let's search entry records from 34 years ago.
Where can we find that? It's old.
According to Han unni,
the foreigner entry records start from 1961.
Search the entry records for Esther.
Esther.
Is it for certain?
It's not a common name.
Esther.
A pregnant woman wouldn't have come alone.
I'm sure someone dropped her off.
Would you remember who?
Esther.
A pregnant woman wouldn't have come alone.
I'm sure someone dropped her off.
Would you remember who?
[ December 24: If you have any info about "Esther"
who died after giving birth, please contact me. ]
As if she was abandoned...
no one came to see her afterward.
No one came to see the baby,
and no one came for the deceased lady.
I heard she became a "Jane Doe."
A "Jane Doe."
Then what about the baby?
The ALP is 287.
[ ALP: Alkaline Phosphatase ]
The GGT is 115?
[ GGT: Gamma Glutamyl Transpeptidase ]
It's more than double the norm, right?
According the blood test, it's the big intestine or the gall.
As a doctor, I'll recommend...
a thorough examination at the hospital.
Please help me.
I gave you money and ran your blood test.
Regarding ♪122, speak to your warden.
- But Doctor...
- Instead of taking care of yourself,
why bother with ♪122?
This is important to me but...
others may find it insignificant.
I owe Big Unnie my life.
You're a doctor.
You can't discriminate patients.
If we had a needle, we could prick her finger.
Should we call the doctor?
That would be the quickest.
♪122!
It's an upset stomach. Not my first time.
I haven't eaten since breakfast.
It's a good thing. You can relax on a
bed and everything.
And feel a man's touch.
Well, maybe not literally.
Okay. Let's lean back now.
Since you insist,
go right ahead!
Her ALP and GGT are extremely high.
Running her blood test was...
wrong in itself, don't you think?
Okay, we're rolling your shirt up.
Let's start with the ultrasound.
- Put the gel on her.
- Okay.
No.
I won't do it.
I won't.
You don't have to, if you don't want.
But...
if I must...
I'll ask Dr. So.
I want to as well, but...
Do you want this or not?
Geez, Unnie.
Stop it and just lie down.
Okay? Come on.
Here, lie back.
- Take off her necklace and etc.
- Okay.
Breath in and...
hold it in.
Don't move or turn your head.
What's wrong with me?
Aside from diabetes.
This isn't my area of expertise.
So you must consent to few things.
Since you're in prison, you must
agree to not hold me responsible for these results.
You sound so cold.
You weren't like this before.
Don't act like you know me.
Chan Sung,
I'll get you a...
"not guilty" verdict for this trial.
After the verdict,
leave the country.
Why are you sending me away?
I'm on vacation but no where to go.
When you leave this time...
I want you to stay there for 10 to 15 years or so.
College, grad school and PhD...
then our New York Headquarters.
Checkmate!
Game over.
You haven't answered me yet.
Why do you want to send me away?
What's the reason?
So you can learn a lot...
in a bigger world.
I'll hold down the fort for 15 years.
For you, of course.
- You'll miss me too much.
- I'm sure I will.
Dad.
Yes?
I love you.
Aigoo, seriously.
Why all choked up?
Huh?
Chan Sung.
Well...
there's something...
I really want to protect is this world.
It's not my company, but...
it's you, Chan Sung.
My son.
Aigoo, just don't get sick.
The blood test indicates that her ALP is 287 and GGT is 115.
There's an unidentified mass near the long intestine
[ Mass: A tumor ]
Her liver sugar rates are very high.
I don't think it's gallstone.
She needs a CT in her stomach area.
And let's check her CA19-9, too.
Did they get it fixed?
Take off your uniform and come downstairs.
You're back on Team 3 now.
Seriously?
Wow, yeah! Yeah!
- Officer Oh!
- Welcome back.
Thank you, thank you.
- Hyung! - You punk! Fighting!
- Fighting!
- Good seeing you.
- Welcome back.
- Happy to have you back.
- Thank you.
- Follow me.
- Good thing you're back.
- Hey, hey, I'll be back.
- Okay.
- See you later!
- You should buy us dinner!
I'll get started.
You must have your reasons for continuing with the
Ma Hyun Cheol case.
If it's nonsense, I'll kill you.
Of course, Hyungnim. It's it's nonsense, please kill me.
This is a day before the incident, at 6:02 p.m.
That's Ma Hyun Cheol and...
Please go in, Doctor.
Please excuse me.
It's too simple. Do I look materialistic?
Minimalism and minimal life. It's not for me.
Didn't you show her what I picked out during lunch?
Oops, I'm sorry.
I didn't know it was her.
We can engrave them.
I was thinking of "Veritas."
It's not a common faith.
It's an absolute and unshakable faith.
"Veritas" is...
the first essential condition of love and
also completes love.
You won't believe me but...
I'm...
I can't believe it either.
But I 'm...
Hae Yi.
I'm Eulji Hae Yi.
Hae Yi?
Are you...
really Hae Yi?
Timing and Subtitles brought by Room No. 9 Volunteer Team @ Viki
[ Room No. 9 ]
I'll make sure Chu Young Bae cries tears of blood.
Whether I take ♪122 off the premises or not...
why do you care about it?
She has stomach cancer in it's final stages.
She has three months left to live.
I hope she doesn't get suspension of sentence.
How could you pretend to be Hae Yi?
You must do as I say.
You mustn't make a mistake.
Jang Hwa Sa, please give Hae Yi back.
- A Damjang attorney's been kidnapped?
- Yes, it's true!
Someone could die here!
Hello?
Ma Hyun Cheol's nemesis could be the kidnapper.
I found the way to switch you back.
♪ I am praying, I am praying ♪