Timing and Subtitles brought by Room No. 9 Volunteer Team @ Viki
[ Room No. 9 ]
[ Episode 9 ]
Gel.
[ Jang Hwa Sa - F/62 ]
Team Leader, let's check last week's footage.
Hey punk, let me go home.
52 hours.
Don't you know the 52-hour law?
Let's at least check on him!
Disregarding the procedure again.
Hey punk, what about the Chief's permission?
- Geez, Team Leader.
- Slow down a little.
How do you expect others to keep up if you sprint alone?
[ Lee Sang Hee ]
Lee Sang Hee.
Ki Chan Sung's case witness is dead.
Ma Hyun Cheol.
Ki Chan Sung's case law firm director is dead. Eulji Hae Yi.
Ki Chan Sung's case attorney.
Everything points back to Ki Chan Sung.
Even Eulji Hae Yi points back to that punk.
Aren't I right?
Okay.
I'll be right out.
Please return...
that body back to Hae Yi.
Yoo Jin.
I...
still have...
something to take care of.
Having three months left means...
that within 90 days, Hae Yi...
can die anytime...
today or tomorrow.
I'll give it back.
After I finish my business...
I'll give it back to Hae Yi.
Please. Please, please.
The way we both look right now...
might be God's will.
If this is God's will...
then change with me instead.
Exchange Hae Yi's body for mine.
[ Paddles ]
[ Defib On ]
CEO.
Yeah.
It's been a while since you said you'd be down.
No, no. Let's go.
Yoo Jin.
He was looking for ice and towels,
so I said we didn't have any. Those are personal supplies.
So where did he go?
Must I know that, too?
An outside doctor doing this at
- another hospital...
- Okay, okay.
If you can't get Ki Chan Sung acquitted,
you'll be charged for Ma Hyun Cheol's murder.
The number you dialed is not in service.
What was Bang Sang Soo's number?
Thank you.
Are you listening to me?
Tomorrow's Chan Sung's trial, yet...
it looks like you have a lot of free time.
I heard Jang Hwa Sa was dying, so...
I'll stop the car for a moment.
Since this was before the opening...
I thought the security cams were off for the VIP clients.
I guess you have a naive side.
This clip can't be given to Detective Oh Bong Sam, right?
Whether it gets disposed is up to you.
If you can't get my son acquitted as promised,
you'll be standing in that courtroom instead...
for murder.
I know.
But CEO,
why were you at the hospital?
Must you know why?
It would look strange to anyone.
I went to see the inmate who killed my half-brother.
I heard she was dying, so...
I wanted to see her face.
Where the heck did she go?
I'm more curious about her whereabouts!
Tomorrow's the trial. Does it make sense that she's MIA?
- Of course, it doesn't make sense.
- Oh, my!
Director's about to flip out right now!
Bang Sang Soo, why are you worried about Director?
Bring the Prosecutor's strategy docs. I'll review them again.
And bring me all materials from the first trial.
- Yes.
- Understood.
What happened?
I was dying of anxiety.
Until Oh Bong Sam called and said he had your purse,
I thought you were arrested.
- Kang Mi Ran...
- Unnie, you got your wish.
We found it.
It'll be possible to see...
Ki Chang Sung getting cuffed in front of Ki San.
This means the game's over, right?
What are you talking about?
How could you just leave...
You're Hae Yi, right?
You're Hae Yi, aren't you?
You were changed back, right?
It was successful, right?
If my son's not acquitted, you'll be standing in that courtroom instead...
for murder.
It'll be possible to see...
Ki Chang Sung getting cuffed in front of Ki San.
This means the game's over, right?
I'm very sorry.
But that's not possible.
That's not possible.
Me, Hae Yi, Jang Hwa Sa, and the defibrillator.
If I was really Hae Yi,
wouldn't we be hugging and shedding tears of joy?
Why is Ki San's brother so serious?
Finish your story about Ki Chan Sung.
I found a clip of Morgan Kim going over to...
Ki San's house.
Where is it? Give it to me.
At home.
- What is it? - Director's asking for you.
Okay.
Han Yeon Hee, go to Jo Eun Police Dept. and get my bag...
from Detective Oh Bong Sam.
Are you sure they're in a relationship?
For a long time, now.
My guess is that they went somewhere yesterday
and got into an argument.
I mean, how can this be when the second trial's tomorrow?
Is there a problem?
Not a problem, exactly.
But it's an unexpected "two-shot."
Bang Sang Soo.
Why aren't you leaving?
Okay.
What are you doing?
It must be hard for a bat.
Should I join this side? Or that side?
Plotting, collaborating, alienating people.
Not everyone can do this.
What is he saying?
You being absent before Chan Sung's trial.
How should I take this?
I'm not sure how I should take it.
Anyone can have an 80% victory rate,
if you're talented or work harder than others.
For a 90% victory rate, politics are necessary.
You need your firm's support.
It's at times like this when partners can shine.
But...
I'm 100% victory rate, Eulji Hae Yi.
So?
It's a good thing that you were a Busan Prosecutor, right?
If you were in Seoul, you would've had to watch me stomp on your hoobaes and...
it would've been upsetting.
I see.
There's a saying for times like this.
"Just sit back and enjoy the ride."
"Enjoy the show and eat the rice cakes?"
I hope the rice cake you're making...
is tasty.
Attorney Eulji asked you to come and get this?
Of course. Why else would I come?
It wasn't a lost item, so you don't need any forms, right?
I'm losing my mind.
Did she put on a show to mock me?
- Kidnap?
- Yes.
- You said she was kidnapped.
Murder, threats, kidnapping. What a joke. Aigoo.
I'm confused, too.
Geez.
Ddaeng Chil's asking for a payment.
She worked hard. Shouldn't we give her some?
I don't have any money.
What do you mean?
Your monthly salary's over 90 million won.
What will you do with everything in the safe?
The money and the jewels.
Give me a cut and Ddaeng Chil, too.
Hey!
Unnie, it's all yours now.
Eulji Hae Yi is you and you're Eulji Hae Yi.
Okay. Play it.
Wait.
Pause right there.
Doesn't she deserve a payment for this?
Yes, I'll pay.
A lot.
You guys are truly amazing.
You must have a lot on your mind.
When the sun comes up...
it'll be Chan Sung's second trial.
You should be by Chan Sung's side, too.
He has you, Hyungnim.
There's someone else I need to take care of.
What are you doing?
I'll scrub your back.
Aren't you leaving?
You'd asked me to bathe together to conserve water.
I have a lot on my mind because of the trial.
Hey.
Everything we've investigated so far...
Can you print them out for me?
Now?
Yeah.
It's nice to dry my hair like this instead of with a fan.
It's refreshing.
The outside world is a good place.
And even better if you have money.
Judge, Prosecutor, they're all professionals. You sure you can do this trial?
Why?
You don't think I can?
Whoa, you're so confident! You really look like Eulji Hae Yi.
This is what we've investigated.
They're here!
CEO, do you still think your son is innocent?
Hey, Lawyer.
You'll be relieved after the trial.
- CEO, what are your thoughts?
- CEO, please answer the question.
I am a father believing in his son's innocence.
Let's go.
Of course, he's not guilty.
The first trial already gave us this verdict.
Lately, it's been difficult for the rich and the powerful.
The underdogs are no joke.
This is a...
case of underdogs taking aim at the conglomerates,
and the Prosecutors walking on eggshells.
This is just a happening.
Case number 2017-1865.
Let's begin the second trial for the Hyojadong pedestrian murder case.
Witness, during the first trial...
you stated you didn't notice anything strange about the vehicle, while in the car.
Is this correct?
Yes, that's correct.
To go to Hyojadong from the defendant's home in Seongbukdong,
you pass by Seoul's famous S-shaped Yeonsu road.
It's approximately 1.2 km downhill.
You went down this road on the day of the incident?
Yes, that's correct.
Whoa, s***!
What? What is it?
What?
There are multiple symptoms of a faulty brake hose.
The brakes slip or pulsate,
poor break response,
or there's sounds of air deflating.
These symptoms escalate when going downhill.
Why didn't the witness feel any of this?
Witness?
Do you know the term "butler friend"?
"Butler friend."
I know that term very well.
From Elementary school until now...
I've heard it more than enough times.
Perhaps the witness couldn't feel any of this
because there weren't any issues with the brakes?
I rest my case.
Attorney, please state your defense.
Witness.
Does the defendant like K-pop girl groups?
What?
You said you're his butler friend.
Everyone here heard it, "butler friend."
No, he doesn't.
Chan Sung's not interested in girl or boy groups.
Oh, what a shame.
Idol groups are Korea's pride and joy.
Then let's forget the idol groups.
What song was playing in the car that day?
It was "So What" by Serious.
The car's audio system is better than any clubs.
The speakers are by Ground Zero Corp.
The sound system was meant to mimic a nightclub.
They're in their 20's.
When the brakes were pressed, the car would've shook.
But if you're blasting music on that system,
it'd be impossible to feel any symptoms.
The reason why the witness couldn't feel any issues.
Need I say more?
Your attention please.
SHC Group's CEO Ki San will now make a toast.
After the sentencing trial a week from now,
Chan Sung will finally be...
returning to school.
Tickets have been purchased. One-way, of course.
Let's celebrate our victory in advance.
Here's to Chan Sung!
Cheers!
Go and greet everyone.
Why the long face?
At the last party...
Director Ma was here.
The void is so big.
He died in a grotesque way,
but who doesn't die?
You'll be maintaining your victory rate.
Congratulations!
Aigoo! Aigoo. I'm sorry.
My apologies.
I got too excited.
Attorney Eulji, you were amazing today.
Perfect.
CEO, I'd like to discuss my victory compensation.
You certainly don't hesitate.
Victory compensation is good.
Isn't victory compensation the best money to spend?
This...
Where did you...
Who did you get this from?
Continue watching.
This...
Where did you...
Who did you get this from?
Continue watching.
Kitty.
Chang Sung must like cats.
Meow, meow. Here kitty.
He's calling a cat, right?
What is it that you want?
Debt relief.
My lifeline which you're holding.
Please destroy the original footage from the resort.
And the copies as well.
I will.
Now I have nothing to do with Director Ma's death.
CEO, your mission of the...
formal sentencing trial remains, but I already won the case.
I'll throw this in as a bonus.
I'll ask you one more time.
Where did you get this?
It's my rule to not expose the source.
CEO, you owe me a bonus, too.
Senior Partner.
Director Ma promised me when he was alive.
[Viki Ver]
tvN E09 'Room No. 9'
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
You're so excited.
Much congrats.
Thank you.
So...
were you playing around with me?
Huh?
Riding behind me and holding on for dear life.
Inviting me to eat chicken soup with Jang Hwa Sa's mother.
Was it all a joke?
Detective Oh Bong Sam, you must've liked me.
So unexpected.
How can you fall for someone so fast?
What?
Wow, geez.
Were you messing with me the whole time?
Because I suspected you of Ma Hyun Cheol's murder?
Or because of Ki Chan Sung?
I have nothing to do with Ma Hyun Cheol.
If you have evidence, get a formal warrant from Hyeseungpo police.
And as for Ki Chan Sung's case...
I have no reason to use my charms on you.
You wench!
Then why did you confuse me?
I knew you were old-fashioned, but you're also clingy.
I have a boyfriend.
She had a blast in my body. She even dated...
What's the association here?
It makes no sense at all.
Kim Jong Soo.
Bong Sa Dal.
Ki San. Ki San's wife.
Gosh, I really don't know.
At least I managed to escape from Ki San's palm.
I don't care.
Mm, delicious.
It's so crunchy.
Why is my life so amusing?
As per her will, we donated her entire assets
to Chicago University.
Chicago University?
She was a faculty member.
Morgan Kim.
She's a classmate who attended at the same time you.
Your friend.
I'll throw this in as a bonus.
Find out who she is and
what relation is with Morgan Kim.
Okay.
[ Wooil General Hospital ]
It looks like a semi-coma.
It's been six days already.
The mystery of human body.
There's not much we can do to extend one's life.
We have to wait and see.
Good morning.
I'll take back...
my belongings.
Why is a patient so strong?
What's the date today?
Ki Chan Sung's trial.
Why worry about that when you're ill?
It's okay. I put them in their place.
Only the sentencing trial is left.
Not guilty. Bam, bam, bam.
Do me a favor.
I won't be doing you any favors.
Call Professor Kang for me.
You're clever.
Stay of execution?
You've used up your inmate financial aid.
You'll be miserable outside.
I think it's best that you spend your final days here.
Oh, are you still fixated on your goal?
To see Ki Chan Sung...
handcuffed in front of Ki San?
How do you know about that?
Just because.
By coincidence...
I just know.
Hae Yi.
Are you okay?
Let me take a look.
I have no doubt.
You're Hae Yi, right?
Noona, it's you, right?
I had no choice because of Chan Sung's trial.
I had to figure out Jang Hwa Sa's doing and make it right.
Eulji Hae Yi, seriously?
I thought it was the wrong defibrillator, and...
I was so...
Yoo Jin, I'm sorry I couldn't tell you right away.
I missed the chance to tell you I'm Hae Yi.
Thank you.
Thank you, Noona...
for coming back.
[ Senior Partner Eulji Hae Yi ]
♪ Congratulations ♪
♪ Congratulations on becoming senior partner ♪
- Congratulations!
- Yay!
That's right.
The time I spent as Jang Hwa Sa was much needed.
I was full of conceit, and...
God forced me to reflect on myself...
and I learned humility while there.
Therefore...
I realized that my life is beautiful.
And that my rightful success...
was very precious, indeed.
Like a light reflecting off the river...
I realized that...
I must enjoy my youth and everything else...
through Jang Hwa Sa's frail life.
Unnie, we have to talk.
What's wrong with you lately?
They say that "late wind" is scarier, is that it?
I don't mind you forgetting about your revenge
and enjoying life as Eulji Hae Yi, but...
I'll take things slow. Slowly.
Look at me.
I'm still young and have a lot of time.
You must've suffered, right?
Go and take a break.
It's better if you go far, overseas.
Unnie!
Thank you, thank you.
Of course, you must be discharged.
Let's get the documents from her doctor.
- I'll submit a trial request tomorrow.
- But I...
must get out soon.
We have to submit documents, receive internal approval,
and they come out for a field check.
It'll take some time to process...
I've witnessed an inmate...
get a stay of execution in two days.
Oh, that's a special case.
No, I'm not wearing a respirator
nor barely hanging on by a thread.
But since I'm not hanging on by a thread...
that's why I must leave now.
Before I die...
there's something...
I must take care of.
♪122.
I'm not sure if it'll fit.
It doesn't seem appropriate for you.
This isn't a market.
There's no other way.
What I received back...
wasn't clothing...
but time which had halted.
Not a coat with holes from age...
but my past life with...
un-mendable holes.
And the echoes which were left from...
a "fake love."
I was...
sent here to die, but...
I didn't die.
But I'm...
walking towards the looming death...
waiting for me outside.
I lost Eulji Hae Yi's body...
which was a God given chance.
But there's still one thing...
left for me to do.
When death comes for me...
Chu Young Bae...
you're coming with me...
to that very place.
Jang Hwa Sa!
- Watch out for the table.
- Okay.
Throw it all out.
Kimchi, seasonings, barley tea.
Don't leave anything.
I'll have the fridge emptied.
Throw the mattress away.
Throw the mattress away?
Throw the sheets away, too.
Yes, understood.
How about here?
It's fine.
I'll take care of this room.
It'd be best to call a different company.
- You can leave now.
- Yes, Attorney.
Aigoo, really.
Who knew we'd come to a tofu place.
These days...
even tofu is fancy.
Well then...
Since the stay of execution was so sudden, I couldn't find you a place to stay.
A motel's too sketchy, so...
how about staying next door to my office for now?
You've done more than enough for me.
Just go with him.
It's not his money. He's being generous with donations.
So please don't feel burdened.
I heard from your daughter that...
you went through a lot because of me.
What can I say, but...
I'm very sorry and grateful.
It's okay.
It's alright.
Everything was my choice.
Isn't that life?
Don't turn down my offer and come with me.
I didn't come out so I can ask you to take care of me.
Because I have something to do.
Before I die...
there's something I must do.
Secretary Kam.
Your fashion is, hahaha!
Are you skipping work and going on your honeymoon?
Vacation. Bali.
Massage. Travel.
Massage? You're lucky.
The sentencing trial isn't over yet.
I'm not a full-timer. I'm Attorney Eulji's personal secretary.
Hey, who is this?
Aren't you Hee?
Hee!
Do you know regretful I am and how long I've been looking for you?
I'm sorry.
You weren't asking for Kim Joong Bae's diamond,
but just a tiny little jewel.
Hey, what is Hee?
- Do you know this grandpa?
- How would I know him?
Grandpa, your eyes must be bad.
I'm not Hee, I'm Kam Mi Ran.
No, no. I'm positive you're my Hee.
And I'm your Hoon.
I'll buy you everything. Everything you want.
Red, blue diamonds, I'll buy you all of them.
Why this grandpa...
You must have Alzheimer's instead. I said, I'm Kam Mi Ran.
Do you see that over there?
The top law firm in our country.
I'm a secretary there.
Attorney, let's go. I'll buy you some meat.
But I'm sure she's Hee.
I asked them to heat this up.
So...
I'm...
a bat, a bat.
A bat?
What else can I do?
An underdog must get on the right side.
Being on the right side determines one's life.
You're a disgrace.
Not 80 years...
not 100 years...
but he says he'll live to be 120 years old...
what am I going to do for a living?
Huh?
There's a surplus of lawyers in this world.
Let me ask you something.
Go ahead or don't...
I'm...
have to stand in Kim Jong Soo's line...
or the one who hit a solo homerun ball...
and saved Ki Chan Sung, Attorney Eul?
Of course, it's our attorney.
Of course...
She made senior partner.
She's going to marry Sir Ki...
Yes, she will.
Reply with sincerity.
Will you?
I did reply with sincerity.
Hey...
if you look here...
haha!
Well, a chili pepper...
Why is a chili pepper in here?
Walk straight!
Walk, walk.
I'm so tired.
Why does a Damjang attorney
live in a study room?
Seriously.
Geez! Seriously!
Get up, get up!
I said, get up!
Where's your home?
I have to pee.
Just lay down!
My goodness...
You're so pitiful...
You reek of pity...
[ If you want to become a full-time employee, stand behind Kim Jong Soo. ]
[ Attorney Eulji and Ki Yoo Jin are 100% going to break up. ]
If you want to become a full-time employee, stand behind Kim Jong Soo.
Attorney Eulji and Ki Yoo Jin are 100% going to break up.
We're closed.
Ddaeng Chil.
What b**** is bringing up my past?
Unnie!
I must be dreaming.
I can't believe I'm seeing my Big Unnie here! Unnie!
Umm...
let's exchange greetings later.
Where is Pal Pal?
I can't get a hold of her.
I heard she's going on a trip.
She got a bonus and vacation time.
We were heading out on vacation, too.
Ddaeng Chil...
don't listen to anyone...
except for me.
Can you do that?
Of course.
By any chance...
the footage you found of Morgan Kim...
do you have it?
It was absolutely daebak.
We found it in a car black box.
Where is it?
Pal Pal unni probably gave it to the attorney.
Unnie?
Unnie!
Unnie, are you okay?
I can recover the footage on my computer.
The salad is ready.
Potato!
Is this a decalcomania or deja vu?
This is exactly what I did for your birthday.
That's when things started to go sour
so let's go back to that day and make things right.
How is it?
It's really buttery.
It must be fattening.
But... it's really good.
I have to lose weight.
Jang Hwa Sa ate everything carbs and everything in sight
so my body's a mess.
- What do I do?
- It's okay.
Is it good?
Eat up.
I know you're going to start dieting tomorrow.
I'm being careful not to swallow the ring.
Do you think my imagination is lacking?
Do you think it's Kang Mi Ran or Pal Pal?
Yoo Jin!
You have one wild imagination.
Noona!
Why are you scaring me?
Why are you making my heart drop?
Are you upset?
Don't be mad.
I didn't think this through.
I'll explain everything.
Why he sent this to me...
I didn't get to hear why from Director Ma...
but I learned about a lot of things.
I saw my mother's face...
You met your mom?
Let's talk about that later.
Noona, it must be a bad memory for you.
No, it's not.
It was a time of reflection for me.
I've waited too long, Hae Yi.
If he figures it out, I continue on...
If he doesn't...
then I'll stop right there.
Director Ma passed away.
Who sent this?
What are they trying to do?
Yoo Jin...
I'm getting goosebumps...
Defendant Ki Chan Sung,
drove into the intersection and killed two people.
He also injured two others.
However,
the accident was due to uncontrollable circumstances
and the vehicle's maintenance was performed by a third party.
Considering that the defendant did his part to maintain the vehicle in working condition
I sentence the following.
Judge, wait a minute!
This incident wasn't an accident.
This was pre-meditated to kill Morgan Kim!
What?
I have evidence.
You can't submit new evidence during a trial!
Timing and Subtitles brought by Room No. 9 Volunteer Team @ Viki
[ Room No. 9 ]
That's impossible!
How dare you do that to my son!
CEO, are you going to represent him without me?
How can you bring Jang Hwa Sa to my home?
Jang Hwa Sa knows information that is important to me.
Why do you have this picture?
What's the reason you had to do that to Ki Chan Sung?
Doctor Ki, I feel like I'll remember something when I see you.
When did you find out I was alive?
Chu Young Bae!
Eulji Hae Yi.
You're the one who died then.
It was you!
How did you become Ki San?
How are you living as Ki San?
You're under arrest for the murder of Ma Hyun Cheol.
It's not me. I said it's not me. It's not me!
♪ Cry, I can cry ♪