(Missing Crown Prince)
(SUHO)
(Hong Ye Ji)
(Myung Se Bin)
(Kim Ju Hun)
(Kim Min Kyu)
(Missing Crown Prince)
(All characters, locations, organizations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are historically irrelevant and fictitious.)
(Production guidelines were strictly followed...)
(when filming with children and animals.)
Do you wish to be a mother who gets her own son killed?
I told you to shut your mouth!
I killed her.
Because of me, you can no longer clear your name.
Now, you can no longer save Father...
or take down the traitors.
So, why...
Why are you not saying anything?
Ask me why I did such a thing.
Yell at me and call me insane!
Your selfish brother dragged you into this mess for his own sake.
Let go. Let go of me!
- It is okay. - Let go...
Dosung.
It is all right.
Gun.
- The royal taster is... - About the royal taster.
I killed her.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
No, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, please open your eyes.
- Your Majesty! - Calm down.
Soo Ryeon took medicine, not poison.
She will wake up in less than four hours.
Court Lady Kim, I will leave her in your hands. I must get going.
Please take good care...
of my dear Soo Ryeon.
No, you cannot leave.
What are you doing?
The royal taster is dead.
I do not know the details yet,
but one of the guards at the prison saw her,
stabbed and covered in blood.
So please...
I cannot miss the morning assembly today,
so once Soo Ryeon wakes up,
come to the Royal Office. Do you understand?
Your Majesty.
(Episode 13)
Where is the letter?
I was about to head over to the Crown Prince's Palace.
There is no need. Hand it over.
- Did you read it? - I was worried about Myung Yoon.
I wanted to understand what was going on to save Lady Myung Yoon.
Take my life, my lord.
I heard the royal taster was found dead.
Did you know?
Did you hear...
who did it?
It was the deposed Crown Prince.
The deposed Crown Prince.
Am I...
wrong?
Your father...
was a loyal vassal.
His Royal Highness the Crown Prince is entering.
I heard on my way here...
that the Queen Dowager might be late.
We will have to wait a few moments.
- Yes, Your Royal Highness. - Yes, Your Royal Highness.
Why did she ask to see me?
She said she had something to ask you.
Go inside.
Is the Crown Prince all right?
Are you trying to add fuel to the fire?
I am sure you heard everything, hiding here.
He is not all right at all.
Happy now?
I am aware...
that my father framed His Royal Highness for high treason.
However, I do not know why my father did such a thing,
so I cannot find a way to help him even though I truly want to.
It is shameless of me to ask you this, but tell me the reason.
What are you, the cat worried about the mouse?
Or do you feel responsible...
because your father caused all this mess?
Gosh.
What is the reason...
my father is trying to get the Crown Prince killed?
Your father...
did something horrendously heinous.
His Royal Highness happened to see it.
So to cover up his heinous sin,
your father tried to murder His Royal Highness, but it failed,
That is why he poisoned His Majesty.
What was the thing my father tried to cover up?
The thing His Royal Highness saw.
If you are that curious, go and ask your father...
No.
There is no way he will tell you.
If you truly wish to know, ask those in the Queen Dowager's Palace.
Does it mean the Queen Dowager knows everything too?
They say, in the palace,
even the walls have ears.
Keep a close eye on her so that she does not leave this room.
Yes, sir.
Not just her leaving the room.
Make sure no one enters the room either.
Especially those from the Queen Dowager's Palace.
If you truly wish to know, ask those in the Queen Dowager's Palace.
You may put your worries to rest for the time being,
so relax and focus on taking care of your health first.
It is true that we cannot trust Yoon Yi Kyum,
but until Prince Dosung officially becomes Crown Prince,
we will just have to...
keep a close watch on Jang Hyun Mok and the Crown Prince.
How could you do this?
How could you try to leave me behind, all alone?
Did you want to see me...
live on as if I was already dead?
- Soo Ryeon. - Leave.
At the moment, I cannot even stand the sight of you.
- Soo Ryeon. - I told you to leave.
I am sorry.
I am... It is all my fault, Soo Ryeon.
Did you believe that I could go on living without you?
Had it never occurred to you...
that I would take my own life to follow you if you died?
Soo Ryeon.
I suppose the medicine still has not worn off completely.
I shall administer acupuncture on you.
Your Highness, let me ask you first.
The royal taster was found dead last night,
and I heard...
it was the deposed Crown Prince who killed her.
Is it true?
- About that... - Yes.
I did it.
He truly killed the royal taster?
Was there something she knew about...
that you did not want her to tell others?
Is that why you took her life, to silence her?
You are out of line.
Are you interrogating His Royal Highness now?
No, I am not.
Anyone would agree with me.
If he were not involved in the plan to poison His Majesty,
he would have no reason to kill her...
when he was the one who captured her.
- Am I wrong? - Do not go off on a tangent!
I heard His Majesty collapsed...
upon eating the dried yellow corvina the Crown Prince had sent.
If that is true,
the royal taster should have died right there and then.
The fact that she did not die that day...
serves as proof that His Royal Highness...
had nothing to do with how His Majesty collapsed.
That is correct.
When His Majesty collapsed,
His Royal Highness was not even in the palace.
Are you admitting your guilt?
At that time, I was outside...
the palace walls.
Are you pleading guilty or not?
I was outside the palace walls.
However,
the deposed Crown Prince has admitted to committing treason.
I suggest you go over the reports once again unless you are blind.
He has never once admitted to doing such a thing.
But as you are aware, he has never once denied it either.
All right.
He is right here.
I will ask you once again.
If you are not guilty of treason,
why...
did you not deny it?
Look.
- Even now... - All right, ministers.
That is enough!
That woman is already dead. It is pointless...
to discuss her death now.
You all know there is a more important matter we must discuss.
What? What could be more important than this?
We must decide...
which one of the two deserves the official Crown Prince title.
Do not tell me...
you are planning to let both of them stay in the Crown Prince's Palace!
- Gun. - Now is not the time yet.
The Queen Dowager is not feeling well today.
She says you are all dismissed.
(Miryeong: Not feeling well due to illness)
Was it Prince Dosung?
Or was it the Queen?
Who is it that you are trying to protect?
Please tell me.
I must know why you are doing this to come up with a plan.
I did it.
It has nothing to do with the Queen's Palace.
If that were the case,
Yoon Yi Kyum, the former Left State Councillor,
would not stay quiet.
(Wonimdaesin: A former senior or junior 1st rank court official)
I bet he is staying quiet...
because he is afraid that...
you might change your mind and reveal the truth.
Your Royal Highness.
I owe you an apology, Grandfather.
Do not be too concerned.
Gun will make sure nothing will happen to you, Mother.
However, I cannot dump it all on him again.
You know how he is.
He is wise,
so I am sure he has a plan.
I truly cannot dump it on him again.
Mother, please!
By keeping this up,
you will only make things more difficult for Gun.
So...
please trust him...
and wait.
- Mother! - I did it,
so I should be the one getting punished.
I will bring in your lunch.
- Lady Myung Yoon. - Let her know.
Her Majesty is...
I am Myung Yoon, the Inspector General's daughter.
I must speak with you. Please allow me to enter for a moment.
Lady Myung Yoon.
Was this why?
Was this the reason...
you tried to kill the Crown Prince?
Lady Myung Yoon.
What are you doing?
Hurry. Go after her.
Right now, she will not want to hear anything I say.
- Sang Rok. - After some time has passed,
I will have a talk with her,
so do not worry.
I understand Myung Yoon is a righteous, brave girl,
this will be too much for her to handle.
So why are you doing this?
Why must you have him killed? I do not understand.
I never asked...
for your understanding.
So, think of me as your mother.
My father was poisoned,
and my brother was framed for it.
Was this why?
Was this the reason...
you tried to kill the Crown Prince?
My lady.
Lady Myung Yoon...
Even so, I doubt she went straight to the Queen Dowager's...
Lady Myung Yoon.
Please kill me, Your Royal Highness.
Please take my life.
Take my life.
I suggest you two talk inside.
What you saw...
I saw it too.
My lady.
- Queen Dowager and your father... - How could they...
do such a thing to you...
and to His Majesty?
- My lady. - What should I do now?
Knowing what they have done to you...
Even brutes would never do what they did to you.
How will I carry the burden of their sins?
My lady.
Please look at me.
I am...
not in love with someone's daughter.
You are simply...
the first woman I have ever loved.
So I ask you...
to please remember me...
as a man who loved you,
not as the Crown Prince.
Where is Myung Yoon?
Why are you looking for her here?
You took her from Yanghwadang yesterday.
That was not me. The person who took her...
was the Crown Prince.
Did he hide it from you as well?
When I visited him last night,
he was with Myung Yoon.
Tell the Crown Prince to hand over Myung Yoon.
Why should I do that?
Your Highness, you and Myung Yoon will get married.
So, you must find her before rumours spread.
You must hurry.
Then I will trust that you will find her, Your Highness.
Are you Moo Baek?
Where does her mother's maternal family live?
Her mother's uncle lives in Buyeo.
Do you think...
you can take Lady Myung Yoon there without your master finding out?
I ought to obey Lady Myung Yoon's orders.
If she wishes to go home...
If she returns home and stays with your master,
they will both end up...
being punished for treason eventually.
Keep your head down!
How dare you...
"Treason?" That is preposterous.
Lady Myung Yoon did nothing wrong.
But her father committed high treason.
Seeing how you will not ask another question,
I am certain you already know what your master did.
Even better if her mother's maternal family does not live there.
Can you take her to a place where no one knows her...
and keep her safe?
I already told you.
I must obey her and follow her wishes.
Even if...
it gets her killed?
No matter what happens,
I will protect her.
Even if it goes against your master's wishes?
Would you still be able to protect her?
The person I ought to risk my life to protect...
is Lady Myung Yoon,
no one else.
Did he hide it from you as well?
When I visited him last night,
he was with Myung Yoon.
I have informed the Royal Kitchen, so they will soon bring our drinks.
People will constantly knock on these doors,
so let us drink in your room.
Where is Gun?
How did you find me here?
His Royal Highness is looking for you. I was on my way...
to fetch you.
I need to talk to you. It is about Lady Myung Yoon.
She is...
at Buyong Pavilion now.
Choi Sang Rok dropped by earlier.
Was he looking for her?
Yes.
The truth is,
Choi Sang Rok...
came into my chamber with a dagger to kill me last night.
Choi Sang Rok did such a thing?
Are you not hurt?
I wanted to wait until I calmed down a bit,
but this happened.
I am sorry.
No, do not be sorry. I am relieved that you are okay.
But earlier...
Never mind.
What do you plan to do now?
What if...
Father's condition worsens drastically overnight?
We ought to torture Choi Sang Rok...
to find out what we can use as an antidote.
Do you think he will surrender and give us that information?
Before returning to the palace,
I met the Training General and the Royal Guard Commander in secret...
and made sure to obtain their promise.
As soon as I let them know,
they will come barging in with their soldiers.
- Then Lady Myung Yoon is also... - That is correct.
She will be hurt too.
Then we must make sure...
she leaves the palace as soon as possible.
Gun, the wind is still chilly.
I cannot believe you made her wait here.
I had no choice.
Her priority is to avoid those who might harm her, not the wind.
Are you all right?
Yes.
- Let us go to the East Palace. - Your Royal Highness.
My brother and I thought long and hard...
and arrived at the conclusion that it is the safest place now,
so please listen to us.
We will make sure you can leave the palace tonight.
No, I...
If you decide not to leave,
I will stay here too.
Then...
I shall also stay here to protect you, Gun.
She is not in the East Palace? Then where did she go?
She could not have left the palace yet,
so she must be somewhere inside the palace.
"Somewhere inside the palace?"
She must still be in shock. What if something bad happens to her...
while wandering around in her current state?
We must hurry up and find her before that happens.
Yes, she must be very hurt emotionally.
However, neither the Crown Prince nor Prince Dosung...
will hurt Myung Yoon,
so she will be safe.
As for Prince Dosung,
I understand he will not hurt Myung Yoon for he fancies her.
How could you be so certain that the Crown Prince would not hurt her?
I have confirmed that the Crown Prince...
also feels the same way about Myung Yoon.
- Then... - Yes.
Since this has already happened,
I believe it is better that they leave the palace with Myung Yoon.
That is why I am not intervening,
so do not be concerned.
Understood.
Then what do you think we should do with the Crown Prince?
I suggest you issue a royal decree.
(Bimanggi: A royal decree)
A royal decree?
Get some rest.
I am stepping out for a quick talk with Dosung.
Sure.
Will you be all right alone?
Yes.
Gap Seok is guarding the room outside, so relax and...
I am okay now.
Please do not worry about me. Get going.
That man, Moo Baek. Can we trust him?
We have to trust him.
At the moment, we have no choice.
Well understood.
Then I will take her...
to that location.
- You will take her there? - Yes.
There are more eyes watching you than me,
so I believe that would be better.
Then do me a favour and take her there safely.
A favour? Please.
After all, we nearly got married.
Of course, I should do it.
It will be a tough journey.
If you leave on an empty stomach, you may faint.
I was worried, so I prepared this meal.
Force yourself to have some food.
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
You should eat too.
It is all pointless.
I will never see her again anyway.
Whatever happens,
why would it matter?
Did you draw this?
Yes.
My mother's maternal family lives near a village called Saleogae.
Every spring,
you can see apricot blossoms in full bloom.
I suddenly remembered that scenery, so I drew this.
So, these fluttering petals are all apricot flowers?
It actually looks much more beautiful in real life.
But I cannot draw too well.
They look like peach blossoms or snow.
I certainly would not call this a great painting.
But I am not a painter, am I?
Who is this man?
Who do you think it is?
He is good-looking.
You must have drawn a handsome nobleman.
Could he be someone you have feelings for?
(I will remember you forever.)
"I will..."
"forever remember you."
(I will remember you forever.)
I will remember you forever.
Though I do not know who she is, she has well-defined features.
You must have drawn a beautiful lady.
Could she be someone...
Your Royal Highness has feelings for?
Until the petals that fall...
make a mountain of their own,
(Until the petals that fall...)
(make a mountain of their own, )
I will remember you forever.
(I will remember you forever.)
(Baek Gu)
"Baek Gu?"
I wish...
I was Baek Gu.
I wish you were Baek Gu.
Had I been Baek Gu,
I would not have had to leave like this.
I would have been able...
to stay by His Royal Highness's side.
(Baek Gu)
Had you been Baek Gu,
I would have stopped you from leaving.
I would have...
had you stay by my side.
(Until the petals that fall make a mountain of their own, )
(I will remember you forever.)
Please...
be well, Your Royal Highness.
You should also...
stay safe.
Eat well,
and sleep well.
It is how I feel about you.
(Until the petals that fall make a mountain of their own, )
(I will remember you forever.)
Are you all right?
Let us take a short break.
My apologies.
Did something happen...
at the Queen Dowager's quarters during the day?
I witnessed what...
the Crown Prince had seen.
I am leaving...
as I cannot defy His Royal Highness's wishes.
However, how could I...
dare to think of surviving?
If only...
I could pay for my sin with death.
Stop with that absurdity.
You did not choose your father, did you?
Whether I chose him or not,
the fact that I am his daughter does not change.
Are you implying the child is a murderer if their father is one?
Had I really thought so,
you would not be before me right now.
I would have had you killed a long time ago.
So, do not think like so.
Are you able to walk?
Yes.
Gun. It is I.
Come in.
She has left safely.
Great work.
I told her once again...
not to go home.
Do not worry.
The fortress gates will open when dawn breaks.
She should sleep within the capital tonight.
I wonder if there are any places to sleep.
By the way, where do we sleep...
if we do not go home?
I found a place near the gates to stay the night.
Let us go home.
We cannot do that, my lady.
If I disappear like this,
who do you think will take the blame?
It is crystal clear His Royal Highness...
or Prince Dosung will have a hard time.
I cannot let that happen.
What now?
I will not allow it. You cannot go home.
- Move. - No, I will not.
I am ordering you to move.
My lady.
You know better than anyone else why I am stopping you.
And you know better than anyone else why I wish to go home.
I do. However,
please follow my words this time.
My lady.
Keep stopping me,
and either you or I...
will get hurt.
You know me, no?
Do not test my volition any longer.
I cannot handle this.
What is wrong with her?
Let us go.
Pardon? Are we going home?
But will we not die if we go home?
Should you not make her pass out and carry her?
We should not go home, should we?
Moo Baek!
His lord has returned home.
My lady?
Do not bother.
Sit down.
Did you not hear me?
Sit.
What happened at the Queen Dowager's quarters...
I do not want to hear about it.
We must settle the misunderstanding, no?
What...
could be a misunderstanding...
when I clearly saw it with my own two eyes?
What you saw is not everything.
If not,
is there more I must know about you two?
We...
Did you...
just say "we?"
I could not believe what I saw.
Nor did I want to believe it.
Do not assume...
that what you saw is the end of it all.
Loving someone...
You...
You loved someone you should not love.
A queen dowager of a nation...
gave way to her temptations...
and deceived others and brought them misery.
Myung Yoon,
you can resent and condemn me all you want,
but not her...
How can you be this brazen?
How could a person be this cruel?
Do you not fear the skies?
That...
is what I would have said if I were not your daughter.
Do you not think that there is a story...
behind what led us to be this way?
Of course.
I am sure there is one.
But your relationship is not what I cannot tolerate.
To conceal this relationship,
you killed those innocent...
and framed His Royal Highness as a traitor...
which resulted in his deposition.
Not only that,
you poisoned...
His Majesty.
What I cannot bear is the fact that my father...
is a terrifying, cruel, and despicable sinner.
Whatever story you may have...
could never be an excuse for what you did.
Even your own child cannot tolerate it,
so how could anyone forgive you?
They will not.
Not even the skies...
will forgive you.
Until the petals that fall...
make a mountain of their own,
I will remember you forever.
You did not choose your father, did you?
Whether I chose him or not,
the fact that I am his daughter does not change.
Are you implying the child is a murderer if their father is one?
Had I really thought so,
you would not be before me right now.
Myung Yoon...
This is the royal order from the Queen Dowager...
regarding the status of the deposed Crown Prince Lee Gun.
You ought to read it.
I will excuse myself.
Read it for us.
Sure.
"Government officials continue to discuss and argue..."
"about the reinstatement of the deposed Crown Prince."
Due to lacking virtue and fortune,
I suffered a series of misfortune...
which led me to be in constant worry...
ever since I took over as regent.
So how could I possibly be at ease even if it is for a brief moment?
The Crown Prince is the root of this nation,
and with him lies the future of this nation and the royal family.
The people's and the sky's trust also lies with him.
For that reason...
"The deposed Crown Prince..."
"who murdered a material witness that could prove treason..."
"His reinstatement..."
"is prohibited."
However,
I have come to realize...
that his so-called crime of treason is also beyond reason.
Thus, he will be exonerated.
(Shinwon: Exonerate)
He will be given the royal name Susung...
and be addressed as Prince Susung.
(Jinchek: The act of bestowing a regnal name)
How can you be chuckling at a moment like this?
Are you suggesting I weep instead?
That is not what I meant.
How can you be downgraded...
to an ordinary prince?
That is not the matter at hand.
Who cares whether I am a crown prince or not?
I am glad to have been exonerated from the crime of treason.
The Queen Dowager wants us to be at each other's throats.
You are absolutely right.
The officials are already taking sides...
between you and Prince Dosung.
The Queen Dowager...
let her affection sway her decision.
We all know why he murdered the royal taster.
That is preposterous.
He should have been reinstated, not just exonerated.
Think of why...
His Majesty had him take the royal seal.
The situation is completely different now.
Obviously, Prince Dosung should be Crown Prince and...
That is enough.
I wish to deliver a few words.
I am aware of the heated discussions...
that take place here regarding my situation.
However,
discussing my situation...
should not keep you from doing your work.
While you have been arguing about my reinstatement,
appeals have been piling up.
If I must be punished for a crime, I will gladly accept my sentence.
Still,
the concerns of the people should not be pushed aside.
Let us stay up all night...
and handle all of these appeals.
I ask that you aid us...
with your vast knowledge and experience.
I hear a disease is spreading in the Honam region.
We could use your advice, Inspector General Choi.
Your Majesty, your grandson has a request.
Speak.
I heard the position of Left State Councillor...
still remains vacant.
If the court shuts down for a day,
the people will suffer for a year.
It is why I ask for Yoon Yi Kyum...
to be reinstated.
Please share your thoughts on the matter.
Prince Susung's request is thoughtful and appropriate.
Please consider his request.
(Ganab: Approving one's request)
- Please consider his request. - Please consider his request.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
- Congratulations, Lord Yoon. - Congratulations.
He is not a pushover, that is for sure.
It did not take him long to captivate the officials.
His innate qualities of a monarch are finally blossoming.
If only we could change Prince Susung's mind.
Could there be a way?
Should I brew a tonic for her?
As if she would drink that...
when she is refusing to eat.
What do we do, then?
I do not remember...
her being this disheartened at anything before.
Hold on.
Well...
The Queen Dowager sent me.
What does the Queen Dowager want?
Lady Myung Yoon...
is to obey the Queen Dowager and make way...
to the palace.
Tell her I cannot travel due to being ill.
My lady.
We are prepared to leave,
so give me the word,
and I will escort you.
If I could, I would love to leave this house.
However, he is still my father.
How could I abandon him...
and run to save my own life?
Now that you know what is going on,
I will fill in the blanks.
You see, the day the royal taster died,
Lord Choi was planning to escape the palace...
with the Queen Dowager.
He ordered me...
to escort the Queen Dowager to the rendezvous point,
but he gave me no instructions...
regarding your safety.
That is the day I finally learned the truth.
To him,
the Queen Dowager's life takes priority over yours.
Watch your words.
Lord Choi...
is more terrifying than you could imagine.
You must know that he would abandon his child...
- if that was an option. - Enough.
No matter what you say,
I will never choose to abandon my father.
My lady.
- Lord Choi... - I know.
He took innocent lives.
And among his innocent victims are...
The Crown Prince...
and also His Majesty.
Your mother is also one of them.
He is the one...
who took the life of your birth mother.
Are you saying...
that my father killed...
How dare you accuse him of such an outrageous crime?
I swear on my mother's name that I am telling the truth.
Your mother was lying in the pool of her own blood,
and I remember that as if it happened yesterday.
That cannot be.
You must be mistaken. Why would my father...
For the Queen Dowager.
For her,
he killed his own wife.
You were just over the age of one and with your mother.
As if you knew what was happening,
you were crying your eyes out.
And I remember it like it was yesterday.
Myung Yoon...
My lady.
Moo Baek.
Yes, my lady.
Myung Yoon...
My lady...
My lady, no!
My lady!
This...
is the baby quilt you were wrapped in.
I could not bring myself to throw it away...
after how she was robbed of her life...
which is why I kept it.
But never did I want to display it...
in front of you.
Mother...
Mother.
Why did you want to see me?
This is what the Office of the Inspector General found...
while looking into your grandmother.
What do you mean by this?
We should let bygones be bygones.
For you and I...
have the same objective.
What if I decline the offer?
Do you want me to reveal...
who actually killed the royal taster?
You must be aware that she did not die...
at the hands of the deposed Crown Prince.
(Until the petals that fall make a mountain of their own, )
(I will remember you forever.)
It is Mother's silver dagger.
She dropped it at the prison cell...
which I retrieved.
Good.
I will get rid of it on my end,
so forget that such an event ever took place.
Is it true?
What are you asking?
Was it you...
who killed my mother?
Please answer me.
Was it you...
who killed...
Mother?
Tell me if it is not true.
Why are you not saying anything?
Father!
Yes,
that is true.
I killed your mother.
(Missing Crown Prince)
Find out where they are keeping Kim Dal Saeng.
I am certain it was his doing.
I put my life on the line and entered the palace...
to put a stop on my father's evil deeds.
We are only in this mess...
because the two brothers share a tight bond.
We should sever that bond between them.
It was the Crown Prince's bodyguard...
who attacked Left State Councillor Yoon.
Did it seem like Prince Dosung was wavering?
And then some.
I cannot let Lady Myung Yoon be sacrificed as well.
There are things in this world we must do...
even though it goes against our wishes.