A party with wild wine
It's as fluffy as a skull, refreshing and breathing.
It's like drinking wild wine
It's as fluffy as a skull. My scalp will breathe.
will watch Love Brothers first.
will watch Love Sisters first.
Go on Weibo to participate in #Love and Sibling Variety Show #1
Weibo. (Join #Love & Sibling Variety Show #Talk) Share your point of love.
Go on Weibo. (Join #Culture and Entertainment Jik Talk Love Siblings#Security) You'll get another chance.
Go on Weibo. Participant #Culture and Entertainment Jik Talk Love Siblings# Security You'll get a chance to fail.
I hope so.
A map.
My first impression
He is "Happy Puppy".
He is very good at organizing games.
and interactions with everyone.
It won't make the atmosphere awkward.
If we can go on a date together,
we can be very happy.
and relaxed.
Actually, when I received
when I received
I was very happy.
So I'm looking forward to
Who are you going on a date with?
Hello.
Hello
The first second I saw the map,
I felt
put down the stone in my heart.
He walked in like a rabbit.
He looks energetic.
Did you guess it was me?
Guess if I knew it was you.
I think you are so smart.
you should be able to guess.
A little bit.
Okay.
The first time I saw her,
I was very happy and surprised.
Because she basically has curly hair in front of her.
She has a smooth straight hair today.
There's a contrast.
If it were you,
if you choose,
who do you want to be with?
When I first came in,
I...
you were the last one to come in.
You suddenly said
your ears were so big.
You suddenly called me.
Your ears were too obvious.
When I look at you now,
I can't take my eyes away.
because of my ears.
I was shocked.
I said,
Esther can
such a reaction.
At that time,
impression and favourite.
So when I compliment your ears,
when I compliment your ears.
No.
It's just that
Many people
Yes.
Thank you.
This is huge.
You start first.
I also want to eat this dish first.
Because I know you like it.
It's really spicy.
This is a dough twist.
I love spicy food.
Sure.
I like Sichuan cuisine. Hunan cuisine.
Me too.
Sichuan cuisine. Hunan cuisine.
Guizhou cuisine is also delicious.
Guizhou cuisine
It's delicious.
Especially that potato.
Well
Chicken stewed with potatoes
Potatoes are bad
Yes.
Don't you want this ice cream?
Let me try it for you.
Is it good?
But greasy.
But it's not ice cream.
We work hard.
If you...
if
have such a crush,
would you talk to her?
I'm actually
a person who depends on the feeling.
But I think
more importantly, when we get along
or chatting,
I think
you and I
we are quite compatible.
Or our daily routine and hobbies
are very compatible.
and daily routine.
So you sleep early and get up early?
No.
Sleep and wake up late.
Something like that.
What if...
If...
if you have
you have a crush on,
But your siblings
doesn't suit you.
or let you see it again.
Will you listen to her
or move forward bravely?
I think we'll listen to it.
Listen
I do.
But I don't think you can change my mind.
Like this.
It's up to you.
But you will listen to her
and then think about it yourself.
Yes.
I'm not that kind of person.
A brother.
Yes.
You can replace him.
Got it.
You want to be with the person you like.
You're very determined.
Or is there a girl who likes you?
You'll be moved too.
You really asked me.
Because there were few cases
in the past.
Case?
Yes.
That means you have no relationship experience.
You can think about
what I like.
Right?
I really can't think of it.
I might have to experience it again.
After that,
you may think
what kind of person
when you're with someone.
I feel like my sister is here with you.
I don't want to be a teacher.
Actually, these things are...
I can understand these things.
And why did I
at the beginning?
Because I think you are very similar to my sister.
I'm like a brother to Tu.
Because I feel like
from his brother's perspective.
what kind of girl you like.
It's okay.
I feel that
I don't know why
It's very similar.
and open-minded.
Have you ever liked a girl older than you?
Yes.
Actually, I think
I don't have a specific type.
I think you are the right person.
or I feel comfortable with you.
I think that's me.
I can contact.
It's like this.
It depends on the feeling.
Yes.
If you're cute,
you can...
Yes.
Indeed.
Kill you.
Got it.
And I think
you are a very detailed person.
You will remember many details.
Like you said,
your sister will cook for you.
Yes.
I don't remember at all.
I remember everything.
If I had to remember one thing,
I will definitely
For example, what clothes are you wearing today
What are you wearing?
necklace or something.
I can remember it.
The exam is tomorrow.
Okay.
In a few days,
Next week.
Yellow powder dust.
Okay.
So,
you don't care about the girl you like.
You're a person who cares a lot.
Yes, I am.
I'm not saying
I want to show everyone my charm.
And
I want to be the central air conditioner.
What do I want?
"Three-timing"?
I really didn't.
I just...
You must be scared.
We were just joking.
Because you have a good personality.
and you're good at expressing emotions.
Yes.
I know you're joking.
I had a good chat with Tu today.
I feel that
at first,
the first time we met
comes from his liveliness.
After getting to know him,
I feel this kind of relationship is like a good friend.
Like sister and brother.
Through today's date,
makes my heart flutter.
Because I think
she is a very generous person.
She can joke with you.
she can also keep it.
She also expresses
in this way
her feelings.
So,
I will give her some feedback.
In the future,
I will pay more attention
the habits of our life
or hobbies.
We're about the same.
Okay, let's go.
Cupid's invitation card.
I filled in Harry.
The reason I gave Xinxin
I thought Harry was her brother.
Before we set off today,
I did my hair.
I chose a suit for myself.
Hello.
The result is the same as I expected.
The first person I wanted to date
is Hua.
Order something.
Okay.
What do you want to eat?
Take a look.
Let's order a mousse.
and Swiss rolls.
Which one do you want, mousse? Sea salt.
Butter.
Sea salt.
I want to ask you a question.
You asked me a question as soon as you came.
Soul torture.
The moment you gave me my brother,
you knew it was me?
Did you guess one thing?
I saw her in front of the restaurant.
Then I laughed.
When I saw her, she was smiling too.
And I think
I don't think it'll be rude.
So I asked this question at the beginning.
When we first entered,
Harry took over
the whole housework.
When we are cooking,
Then we need to write
"Pitt's Heart Card".
I thought
Xinxin
It's Harry's sister.
So you thought it was Harry at first.
Yes.
On the first day, I thought
But yesterday
my mind might have changed.
So I guessed again.
She said she thought
she wrote Harry first.
I was a little disappointed.
At that moment,
I thought my "Cupid" cut
is not because of the first sight,
but because you might get it wrongly.
I think, OK.
On the first day,
I didn't know anything about my siblings.
Harry and that...
Yes, Susu or me?
I'm thinking about it too.
Can you confirm it now?
I can confirm it now.
Can you confirm it?
100 percent?
I looked at the map behind you.
It looks quite similar.
I thought it was too late.
that I look like the map.
When I first came in,
when I just came in?
Because on the first day,
he and Susu had a tacit understanding.
The map and Susu have a tacit understanding.
Didn't we play games?
Because we have a tacit understanding.
Can you tell?
Not at all.
I didn't even think you two look alike.
I thought you and Susu
Because both of you
are taller.
Harry and Xinxin
are short.
I thought if the genetic probability
it should be you and Susu.
Yes.
I was completely sure on the first day.
I'm really confident that
you and Susu are siblings.
So you gave the wrong one.
It's not wrong.
Now sitting here, you...
Because on the first day,
I didn't have much contact with Fatty.
Later,
we didn't go shopping at the supermarket.
and communicate more with Fatty.
I want to know more about Fatty.
So after yesterday's contact,
I'll do it today.
After meeting yesterday,
I think this afternoon tea is right.
Not at all.
I went to the supermarket yesterday
I said I wanted to eat this.
You said you wanted to buy it.
You were at the supermarket too.
What do you want to buy?
Just tell me.
He walked through the curls first.
He said,
Curls should be good at making breakfast.
No one cares about him.
I thought he would take it himself.
But the second time,
we went to that circle together.
He said,
I think we can
eat this breakfast.
I know he wants it.
but no one responded.
I said take it.
But I am
When I'm hesitating,
when I hesitated.
Because I'm not very independent.
I want to be recognized.
When I doubted it,
I asked if I wanted this.
Then you say you want it right away.
So...
In the past,
basically we can get the map.
No one will say
Hua, you can take whatever you want.
Did you buy too much chili sauce?
No everyone likes it
One more.
Take it.
When he said I could take it,
I think it's a kind of recognition for me.
I feel very warm.
I saw Susu there.
take whatever she wants.
Yes.
I think you're a girl too.
You can take it too.
It's nothing. Just take it.
According to the day we went to the supermarket,
she said she didn't make the wrong appointment.
I was happy at that moment.
That means
I bought her
was the right choice.
Cheers.
Cheers
Why not?
A cup will do.
When the three of us
sitting there together yesterday,
we asked you about the black mask.
Your black mask scared me.
Can I have one?
No.
You just said you can only be biased.
You didn't apply it for the three of us.
Xiao Ling wasn't there.
not for Xiaoling.
The three of us asked if you could.
You said you could only be biased.
And you refused to give us three.
Only Xiaoling is not here.
You think I can't?
I want to give it to Xiaoling.
She doesn't need that face.
So we need her, right?
You're really...
No.
I mean she's not here.
I won't leave it to her.
So what I said
I want to give someone
But you didn't answer the next one.
Because the three of us knew it.
So I dropped my words.
When you came to my room,
I asked you
Susu said one thing.
Then I asked you
if you want to
Fatty.
Look at your black mask.
What? Do you want to try?
You didn't understand my point.
Do you want some?
Have some.
We'll go back later.
We should have dinner together.
We can eat more tonight.
Why can we eat more tonight
Because the chef is good at cooking, right?
Yes, it's their turn to cook tonight
Yes.
Who did the dishes today?
It might be you or the drawing today.
Can you come over and check?
Yes.
Can you help me?
No need.
We can enjoy ourselves today.
Sit there and watch.
It's them today.
So are you someone who worries?
I won't worry if someone is here.
In love,
in love?
I don't know.
You know it yourself.
Let me tell you.
I'll tell you everything.
Can we have a chat?
Because I think Harry is going today.
I don't have to worry at all.
So you wanted to observe
Harry and...
Me?
This is your first impression.
Yes.
Because
The soup is my first impression.
Very handsome and tall.
But the soup
He doesn't talk.
So you like to talk more with you.
Be cheerful.
What do you mean?
I think
Really.
I'll go back for dinner later.
Okay.
Save some stomach.
Harry will say we don't give him face.
He's eating so much outside.
Let's go.
Did you drive?
I drove.
Take my car.
Okay.
If you grade this date today,
you can get 95 points.
Because usually,
I'm the one who speaks.
Yes.
But today I feel Fatty is leading me.
I'm grateful to him too.
The snow is so romantic.
Aren't you coming down?
You're going down.
Let's go down.
Let's go down and have a look.
You...
Good evening.
Do you want a photo?
Let me take a photo for you.
I'll take two for you.
My phone is really nice.
It's like...
Why don't you wear more?
It's okay.
Really?
I'm really fine.
Cold legs.
Watch out!
Let me take a photo for you.
I'll take two for you.
Let me see.
I'll go down.
Go over there.
I'll find it for you.
Okay.
A little bit to the side. Don't move.
Just move slowly.
My phone is a bit old.
Why don't we just take a few photos?
I'll take it for you.
Put your chin in.
A little bit.
That's it.
I'll find the light.
Don't laugh.
You look like a stiff robot.
Don't move.
Stand here.
Okay.
In front of the light,
Are you cold, Susu?
Let me get you a coat.
Where is it?
It's in the jacket.
Is it white
White down jacket
It's snowing heavily.
You need to put on your clothes.
One more?
It's okay. I don't wear it when I take photos.
I'll take it for you.
I'll hold it for you.
Thank you.
Then you can finish it.
Wait.
It's huge.
What?
No, I think it's fun.
I feel happy.
It's snowing heavily.
It's really on my face.
Look up.
It's snowing heavily.
Turn around.
But my left face is pretty.
I couldn't hold it.
Sorry.
It's okay.
When I took a picture of her,
in the snow,
in the snow.
Is it stiff?
Maybe she's pretty.
It might not look good.
What?
Take a photo for me.
It's too stiff.
What should I do?
Stand here.
I'll go around you.
That's it.
MV.
You like MV, right?
No.
Give it back.
The way we get along
more relaxed.
He keeps asking me if I'm cold.
Should I wear something?
He even took my phone.
and took my clothes.
That's it.
is a bonus to me.
It's like a drama.
watching the snow together,
I think they stand there
They look great together.
I envy you.
It's too cold.
I can't stand it.
I'm going up.
Are you still wearing it?
Shall we go in first?
Let's go.
I'll put this phone on.
Okay.
I wanted to learn
the sound of snowfall.
I was going to say,
but I failed.
Is it hard to learn?
No.
It doesn't look like this.
Don't be nervous. It's okay.
I don't feel right.
Let me take a photo for you.
Take a photo.
Great.
Who can play the piano so well?
Who is so talented?
Amazing.
The emotional value is too great.
Why did you button it?
Are you done playing today?
Little spotted dog.
Little Love Dog.
Good.
Too many talents.
Please keep it.
Thank you.
Doesn't it look good?
Yes.
Will you play it?
I don't know how.
Didn't you learn
When I was young,
I forgot.
You can take a photo if you can't.
No.
Too pretentious.
When you were playing,
Do you know I was up there?
Yes.
I wanted to keep it down.
But
The louder you step on it,
Then I gave up.
Anything.
Show your charm.
Show.
and charming.
I can't play.
Yes.
Someone said he couldn't play the piano.
Then less than half an hour later,
the performance begins.
A package is at the door.
You can look inside.
You can't ask.
What is this?
It's like...
Why does it look like space sand?
Truth or Dare.
Okay.
What can you play?
A game other than rock, paper, scissors?
Say one.
The one I play is...
The winner
will win.
I don't understand.
I'm playing
advanced version, a group of smart people.
You're bullying me.
Because you don't know how to play.
Let's play rock paper scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Scissors.
Okay.
You don't care about money.
What do you want to do the most?
is actually quite a lot.
Dessert chef.
You want to be a dessert chef?
Although I don't know how to make dessert,
but it's an open kitchen
Then the chef cooks
You squeeze cream next to him
You squeeze each part.
It feels very relaxing.
It's very healing.
Yours.
What?
Let me see.
If your friend
No.
Then do you think the relationship will become strange?
The first time we met,
I would introduce my friends
and people
I can tell clearly.
If we have become friends,
it means in my heart,
in my heart.
It will never change.
If you can't be with someone,
can we be friends?
What a profound question.
But if I like him,
I might not be able to be friends.
That's why
I don't like him anymore,
I think we can be friends.
Okay.
It makes sense.
When you like someone,
how can you be friends with him?
It's hard to control this level.
So I think
friends are friends.
That's impossible.
we've been friends for a long time.
Then one day, we were together.
In my world,
in my world.
Or we knew each other before.
But we weren't close.
After we got to know each other,
it's quite suitable.
Or I like it.
I can date or something.
But if I
as a friend,
I can't.
Never.
Impossible.
The bottom line is very high.
I actually felt it at first sight.
I did feel it at first sight.
But I don't take the initiative.
I may not be able to
to give her emotional value.
I will consider many aspects.
But I think love is emotional.
It's not rational.
Maybe sometimes you don't have to think too much.
I should make some changes.
Let's go.
Will you get off from me?
Yes.
Okay, let's go.
He's not a gentleman.
So cold.
Why is there no snow here?
I just wanted to say
Can you stop stealing my lines?
Right?
Yes.
Why isn't it snowing at all?
He even left the door.
Who is so sweet?
So sweet.
Yes.
We're back.
No one is talking to you.
Shut up!
When will Tu come back?
He has something to do today.
I'm leaving, Hua.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
I'm leaving.
Really?
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
Come back early.
See you tomorrow.
It's ten o'clock.
Why did I send it to him today?
We had a date today.
After our date,
and get to know more about each other.
Turn around.
But my left face is pretty.
I think some of his parts
he's very careful.
So I will send this message
to him.
I have to guess.
I want to listen to more piano songs in the future.
It's kind of like a forced song.
Maybe I want to listen to "My Tears Smashed".
Maybe
I want to try it with you.
Maybe.
But I think you've sent me your messages.
Isn't this what it means?
It's still different.
I think it may change in this moment.
It's hard.
It's obvious who sent it.
It must be Fatty.
I think it's Hua's message.
I'm happy to see this message.
Because I think
is the same as mine.
I think it's probably from Harry.
Because when we were eating,
when we were eating.
I'm not embarrassed to eat with you.
That's the topic.
We also talked about
I texted Xiaoling.
I figured it out.
Although it's a good impression,
but there are many kinds of feelings.
I think I can be
with Xiaoling.
So after the text I wrote,
my friend
I guess it might be a map.
from Tu Tu.
During our date today,
we might have shared some things about me.
The map is sensitive.
So in his summary,
I may be a very careful girl.
When the message was sent,
I didn't check my phone.
I was thinking about something.
What if it's about the guy from yesterday
and the date today,
Text me at the same time.
What should I do?
So I didn't dare to look.
What's wrong, Potter?
You're thinking.
But I don't know how to deal with it.
I sent my message to Harry today.
We had a good chat today.
and relaxed today.
And I want to express
the feeling of today's experience.
for a long time.
I was a very tangled person.
Later I thought
Follow my heart.
It's a text message that I understand.
The person
the guy who likes girls and boys.
I think both of us
are very sensitive.
If his little head is smart,
he should know it's me.
When I saw it,
I think it's the person from yesterday.
sent it to me.
I was happier subconsciously.
She sent me this message.
I feel a little disappointed.
I'll try my best to make it up to you tomorrow.
If it doesn't work,
make ten sandwiches for her.
I wondered why he was so charming.
I don't understand.
What are you doing?
I'm not happy.
I thought
if my brother hadn't received the text,
I would laugh at him.
But when he texted me,
and told me
We're brothers today.
When I didn't receive the text,
I felt quite uncomfortable.
Maybe his shining point
hasn't been discovered yet.
At that time, I looked up at flowers.
I felt that
feel lonely.
I can feel it right away.
Maybe it's because the map didn't receive the message.
I'm a very complicated person.
We haven't talked in private these days.
We
have a lot to say to each other.
Many times,
subconsciously, I said, look.
I want to be like this.
But I can't.
I felt like I was putting up with it and he was putting up with it.
So today I opened
the house of siblings.
I have to talk to him.
Fatty.
Xin.
What were you doing just now?
Washing the dishes?
Yes, do the dishes.
I'm fine today.
There aren't many bowls today.
Did you get the text?
I got a text.
How many?
Do you trust me so much?
One.
Is he on a date with you?
Yes.
Because the text we sent
quite...
ambiguous.
No.
I can tell at a glance
Who sent it to me?
I just talked to her.
She said you were the one
when you were dating.
So she felt very secure.
She said you brought her along.
I led her
she was a little nervous when we were dating.
I don't think she'll be nervous.
She will.
We're on a date.
She's folding the paper crane opposite me.
She kept folding it.
It's too much.
I asked her if she was nervous.
She said no.
Do you think she's cute?
Yes.
You will start the next date
with her.
Yes.
Because I think I haven't finished
Because girls
I've talked a lot today.
I've already started.
My brothers are so happy today.
He's already setting off firecrackers in his heart.
Fireworks?
He's smiling.
The corners of his mouth keep rising today.
I'm in a dilemma today.
I'm very torn today.
Why?
Because today,
After receiving that message,
it will say how many messages
have received.
Then I looked at Hua.
Then I could feel the flowers.
What does that mean?
Why?
Because I think
I didn't send it to the map.
I think it's normal.
So you think I won't send it to Map?
I don't think so.
It's mainly about your date.
I had a great date today.
The picture is very eloquent.
He's also very talkative.
He's like a happy puppy.
He makes me feel like a younger brother.
I'm not familiar with
with Hua these days.
I have a similar personality with Hua.
So I put myself
I put myself
like a sister.
Later,
when I asked him,
like this.
Will you like her?
Will you accept that?
I don't think
between me and him.
So do you think
what you did today hurt the map?
I think there might be.
I'll keep thinking about it.
Because if you go on a date today,
you didn't receive
I received so many texts,
I might visit you
and see your date.
And I think a lot.
if you think
if I'm not good enough.
But you won't.
Yes.
If I don't receive a text
after my date today,
I'll...
go back to my room.
and cried all night.
Yes.
Then I thought
if the map would say the same.
He's actually very carefully prepared.
But mainly,
I think this is mutual.
If I can feel
the drawing's feelings for me,
I can do it too.
Can you feel it?
No.
If not,
you don't have to worry about it.
You didn't feel it.
I think
love can't be forced.
Just get to know more about it.
Even if I'm a little disappointed today,
I think it's normal.
This is not a problem.
Because we came here
to explore better people.
He just advised me
It's okay. Just follow your heart.
You can tell him
You can text him.
But later, you need to know how you feel.
It's not a problem to know first.
Who did you send it to?
Who do you think I sent it to?
I think Harry is the only option.
Did he send it to you?
He sent it to me yesterday.
What did he send?
Something like having a crush on him.
So,
he probably got two today.
You can't guess this.
How many messages did he receive?
You sent them to him.
He sent you a good impression yesterday.
He went on a date today.
So his date today
is another one.
And he wants to know another one today.
Let's get to know each other.
I think it's okay.
I think because we just moved in,
to get to know everyone.
And then...
He went on a date today.
He didn't talk after the date.
We get to know each other slowly.
I think it's a matter of order.
right?
But I need to be firm
to like.
It's still early.
Yes, I know.
I'm a person
I'm not worried
I'm not worried.
I think we should at least
until the end.
I think...
Let's stop talking.
Okay.
Let's go.
I suddenly feel
he was relaxed to see all this.
He solved most of
in my heart.
After talking to him,
after talking to him.
You took over the house of siblings.
You took it, right?
You're going too?
I wanted to.
I brought you some medicine upstairs.
What medicine?
It's at your bedside.
You'll see it when you get there.
Do you want some melatonin?
Yes.
I'll wait for you to come back.
Okay, wait for me, okay?
Okay.
Come on.
Two.
Thank you so much.
Did you have a good date today?
Come in and talk.
Okay.
Wait, I need to talk.
How was your date today?
It's my first date today.
But I'm happy.
If this weekend
let you choose a girl,
would you still choose her?
or someone else?
I have to know everything.
Can't you?
Wait. No.
You won't.
Are you sure that
to the end?
If you know one,
you won't understand the next one?
I don't know her by dating.
I can understand her
I can understand her.
No.
Dating is very attractive.
Because today,
I saw a different person.
Really?
Yes.
But Xiaoling and I
a very good friend today.
There's nothing
Love
It's true.
I'll write my diary.
When this party is organized,
there's no purpose.
We talk about every day.
When I knew that
after his date today,
after the date today.
I was happy.
When did you...
When did you bring me cold medicine?
After that,
I went to get it.
Come in.
Present the medicine.
Ten.
Three packets for Xinxin.
Didn't she catch a cold?
Do you want some?
I'll give you one.
Thank you.
Bye.
I'll give you medicine.
One pack of cold medicine for each.
Drink it today
Drink it when you catch a cold.
Thank you. You're so sweet.
You're welcome.
No.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Seven, eight, nine, ten.
Ten, twelve.
12 packets.
Come in.
I found that there are twelve packs. I'll give you two more.
It's hilarious.
I'll give you two more.
Okay.
You're a good person.
But you gave me five packets.
One for each.
Here's the thing.
I left a pack for myself.
I left a bag for soup.
So you got two today, right?
Are you happy?
Didn't you see that I was afraid to look at my phone?
Guolifang.
Why?
Guoli.
I thought about it.
I thought about it before.
Because I'm very consuming.
I'm afraid that if there's a misunderstanding,
or two, I'm afraid it's about your choice.
But I think
you texted me fast.
I don't have to think today.
Well,
Maybe I thought too much.
I'm going on a date with Xiaoling today
It's just...
friends.
You don't have to tell me.
It's fun anyway.
Guoli.
But I think
I want to know more about everyone's personality.
Guoli.
But I still think
I think I know more
I know more.
When it's alone,
Unless you like someone
or someone you like,
to know more.
But I don't know much
I don't know much.
Guolifang.
I really want to know a question.
If you have someone
in the room,
It's a fruit cube.
You chose it
because you're here.
Or
whether in reality,
in reality,
You will choose too.
Of course. We can't be so hasty.
It must be
if I don't go on this show,
if I meet my friends in real life,
70 to 80,
I also think this girl is good.
And I chose her.
Yes.
But here,
we might spend time together
and more interactions
more quickly.
Yes, the advantages and disadvantages will be amplified.
Yes, but
Because there are
We don't spend much time together.
We didn't get along today.
Including you, Hua,
including Susu.
You're good at talking.
I think the core meaning of his sentence
is
Come on, keep sending it to me.
Send it to me tomorrow.
Send it to me the day after tomorrow.
I'm still here.
Let's talk later.
Wait.
Come on.
What are you talking about?
I have a lot to tell you.
But we don't have that.
To be honest,
I don't really want to write a diary.
I want to ask if there's anyone you want to know more.
I want everyone to know the truth.
Who else do you want to know?
I know about girls.
I want to know more about boys.
I think
Harry received the most today.
So, Harry, have you made any progress?
You're so gossipy.
He's done.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Do you think you took a step forward?
Anyway, I did.
We were talking about today.
We took a step of friendship today.
I see.
I got it.
I haven't been in contact with him before,
So I asked him directly.
The feedback I got
maybe he and Xinxin will be more connected.
He said he took a step yesterday.
I might not be able to
Harry, I want to try again.
Sometimes, when you say you like someone,
is not necessarily about love.
Maybe it's about friendship.
Yes.
So the definition of this text message
is not necessarily right.
So what I received was friendship?
Because text doesn't count.
To be honest, I'm more proactive than you.
I'm a person who I'll try my best
I will try my best.
But don't you think three days are too fast?
I think three days are a bit fast.
Then I can't...
Dude.
I can't understand her a little bit today.
Then tomorrow I'll get to know
another little bit.
I'll come back the day after tomorrow to understand her a little bit.
Why not?
You advised me to
to get to know everyone first.
Then...
Yeah, I think you should...
I'm just alone.
I think I will be like this.
So you think
I'm too...
because I want to lock you up too much?
I don't want to lock it.
I just don't think
It's just a little flashy.
I think three days are more secondary.
I haven't shown it yet.
I want to know what others mean.
Is that what it means?
In your feeling.
Yes.
Not really.
I think you might get an A on your first day.
The next day and the third day, maybe B.
So I think you can do CD
Not necessarily DC
How do you know my first day is A?
The next day is B.
How come you don't know I'm B every three days?
I'll try my best to understand.
But my personal opinion is
I won't say I know one today
and get to know the other one tomorrow.
I might
spend two or three days to get to know one first.
Actually, I wanted to remind him.
But I can't tell him directly.
Do you want to know more about me
and be nice to me?
Because
I think we just got along.
for such a short time.
in such a short time.
to me.
I might be a little scared.
I want to accept
your kindness to me.
But I think your kindness
You can treat anyone.
Because it's only three days.
That's why I want to go further.
and observe him slowly.
or wait for him to get along with others.
I want to see
if he's like me.
What I fear the most is
his outfit is the same for everyone.
The idea Hua gave me is
if you want to know more about others,
as soon as possible.
If you want to know me,
please continue to understand me.
and understand me.
Please be more determined and continue.
Don't say you know me for a few days,
or after a few days.
She doesn't accept it.
I can feel that
Are you still chatting?
chatting?
Let me join.
Will you be moved?
You'll be moved by love after a long time.
Yes.
I will.
I don't fall in love at first sight.
My love grows gradually.
Love can grow as time goes by.
But I think the touching love
is that I love him
Yes.
Then I won't.
Right? I won't be touched either.
Yes.
Not at all. Of course not.
But if he likes you more,
and treats you well,
and you were moved.
I think this possibility
Yes, I think so too.
Why should I let him succeed?
You're the only good person.
He's starting to get confused again.
I can understand.
I'm absorbing experience.
Are you observing girls' thoughts?
Actually, these thoughts are very normal.
But I remember yesterday,
Harry said he would be moved.
Yes, he will.
Even if you don't
for this girl,
No.
I think it's OK.
If you think she's okay,
I'll try to get along with you.
No.
I don't have a place to look at this.
As long as I'm sure that girls like me,
I'll take the initiative.
What if someone else in your WeChat
suddenly pops out
Delete.
Will you take the initiative to delete it?
You can delete it.
Awesome.
You delete it when you're in a relationship.
If you need it, delete it.
When she comes to you,
you said I have a girlfriend.
Delete it.
I deleted everything before.
What was I thinking?
I thought
as long as I want to invite my boyfriend
to do something,
I have to do this first
to invite my boyfriend to do this.
You also ask your boyfriend to delete it.
A big part. Yes.
Most?
Are you a control freak?
I used to be a little...
You've grown up.
It's quite controlling.
Yes.
Are you a control freak?
I'm fine.
What about you?
I'm the kind of person
If he asks me to do something,
I'll ask him to do the same thing.
That's what I thought.
Harry is the first person
for a long time.
But I think he's more like a friend.
Xin and Harry.
They did the dishes together yesterday.
And they gave each other medicine today.
So I think it's interesting.
I think we all need
people in the same frequency.
with the same frequency.
will be more synchronized.
and get along better.
Let's go.
What do you need
Cucumber bread
Tomato sauce
Brush a pan.
There should be a pan.
to cook for the first time
to make up for the sandwich incident.
It's a good show.
Turn on the smoke engine first.
Right.
And the third one.
So scary?
Is this oil This is oil
It's oil
Touch it first.
Pour it directly. It's quite hot.
How much?
Enough.
How many people do you make?
Two.
You eat.
Then you make one.
There are four of us in total.
Pull my roommate up.
I said you were watching
and guide me every step.
I'll do it myself.
I want to make one for Xiaoling.
There's an egg shell.
It's okay.
Stir-fry the eggs first.
Let me learn.
Just take the shovel.
You do it yourself.
Why is it so hard to cook?
How much strength do you usually use?
Medium strength.
Why is my egg shell falling again?
It's okay.
How to break it
Just keep stirring it.
Okay.
Why is it uglier than yours?
Dude.
Did you fire?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I thought you opened it for me.
No.
The more I think about it, the more I want to laugh.
I haven't fired for half a day.
Why are you laughing? You just learned how to fry eggs yesterday.
You're a talent even if you didn't cook it for half a day.
I stir-fry it.
What should I put
Oh-Ee needs to
Do I need to wash them all
You need to wash your hands.
Let me do it.
Rub it. Rub it in the middle.
Come on, cut one first.
Let me see how big each piece is.
That's it.
Okay.
Almost this big.
Okay, I'll try.
What's next?
Tomato.
No tomatoes.
I have no choice. Put more ketchup.
Is it enough?
Not enough.
Again.
Don't ask me why.
Others may put less.
She must put more.
How do you know?
I guessed.
It's almost done.
What should we put after the ketchup?
Eggs.
Be careful.
This cheese is quite delicious.
Susu, do you want cheese?
Yes.
Well, I can put some
and one without.
She can eat whatever she wants.
A piece and a half.
Like this.
Let's cut it from the middle
and wrap it with plastic wrap.
Okay.
Check it.
How do you use plastic wrap for sandwiches?
Okay, got it.
No, bro.
How many layers do you want to wrap?
Are you going to keep it for tomorrow?
I think it's full in teaching.
Okay, I'll do it too.
Or it'll be leaked.
I'll do whatever it says.
You're right.
I'll do whatever you do.
After all, nothing will go wrong following Tsinghua.
Don't put a hat on me.
No.
How did you cut it with a plastic wrap?
Like this.
Okay.
Yours is so honest. Your sandwich.
My first success.
Very good.
Enrolled.
That's all. I'll clean up later.
I'm tired.
Take a break for two minutes.
Should I eat it?
Are you crazy?
I'm so hungry.
Then why do we get up early?
Get up early and work on our own.
We're the benchmark.
We have to get up early.
We got up early for an hour and a half.
and ate it ourselves.
Yes.
I'll go upstairs to the bathroom.
Okay.
Hello.
Eat that.
It's all your fault.
No, that was made for someone.
I'll make another one.
Because Xiaoling is going out.
I want to make one too.
I'll make you a dumpling.
I'll get one for her.
Where is Xiaoling going?
She went to class this morning.
It's already broken.
It's not finished.
Not enough. Dig another one for me.
Okay.
Dig one.
I'll make another one.
Because Xiaoling has a class.
I thought she could eat it at school.
Harry made me some avocado there.
Crush it
And he cooked eggs for me.
Actually he made it.
Do you need to wash this plate?
Yes.
I look so ugly.
Is it too ugly?
As long as it's delicious.
Cut it like this.
Yes.
Do it yourself.
What's wrong?
It's not my fault.
You can cut it well.
It means you're skillful.
Because I didn't cut it well just now.
I think it's dry.
It won't taste good.
It's okay.
Even if it doesn't taste good,
she'll say it's delicious.
Just wait to be praised.
Did Xiaoling leave?
Has Xiaoling left?
How would I know?
Go take a look.
This is the breakfast I made for her.
I need to make sure she's still here.
I'll ask her.
Xin made breakfast for you.
Don't forget to eat.
Is it too late?
You finished it in five minutes.
You know what?
You're lucky.
Lucky?
Yes.
Who's lucky and I'm lucky?
Yes, the one who gives is happy.
Right?
Who are you trying to trick?
When you put in effort,
you're full of yourself.
I heard someone made me breakfast.
Yes.
But
it may not be delicious.
It looks good
Eat now
Thank you.
I want to hear the truth.
Sometimes,
he said it's not good.
You're so annoying.
Is it good?
It smells good.
Don't lie to me.
I'll be sad.
Try it yourself.
Leave it to Hua.
She finished it. Look.
This is delicious.
It's not bad.
Are you two competing?
No, I think you're too kind.
Are you coming back for dinner tonight?
I should be back at 6 p.m.
You can eat it when you come back.
Okay.
Who told you that?
You ran away and asked you to eat directly.
Make a radish squat and eat one
One radish squat and one squat.
I want to sew his mouth.
He's really annoying, you know?
Who's annoying?
Bye.
Do you want to drink this coconut?
I'll drink it if you don't.
You drink.
No.
I want to know if it's in.
It's not open.
But I can't get in.
What should I do?
Can you drink it?
Give it to me.
Can't you just cut it?
Can I drink it?
Am I swollen? My eyes are fine.
I'm very swollen this morning.
Do you want pumpkin juice?
To reduce swelling?
Yes.
The secret to my small face every day
You have to drink it secretly.
Don't let others find out.
I won't tell others.
Because I don't have that much.
Let's make a deal.
You're so ugly. I'm speechless.
Bro, do you know that?
This is the ugliest coconut I've ever had.
Do you know how difficult it is?
Susu is wearing a mask.
Why is there a butterfly mask?
No one can look at me.
Morning.
Is this edible
No.
Is this mine?
It's not mine.
Your smile is mine and not mine.
Why are you jumping?
I'll do it myself.
Dude, do it yourself.
Are you down there?
Yes.
Who's there?
Me, Fatty.
Harry is doing his hair.
I'm here.
Hua.
or Xinxin.
Or...
Can't you tell who it is by the sound?
You can.
Of course.
Tell me now.
Susu.
I guessed wrong.
It's okay.
I was too gentle.
I know it's me.
Talk nicely.
I'll speak very slowly today.
What? Blood pressure?
I'll start talking slowly today.
Why?
She bit her tongue last night.
Because I'm very gentle.
I'm hungry. I want to eat something.
Whose is this?
I left it for Hua.
This should be made by Harry for Susu.
Harry for Susu.
No.
He didn't make it?
I made it for Susu.
Did you really make this
You cut the cucumber yourself
Yes
The other half.
I don't know who changed it to corn.
I don't know.
Maybe later
two corns later.
When I first came down,
half of it was gone.
Hurry up, Susu.
Your breakfast has turned into two corns.
I can tell from the footsteps.
Someone is learning from me.
This...
Someone is learning from someone.
Love is everything.
He woke up early to make sandwiches for me today.
because he mentioned
he said
he'll go with Harry Potter tomorrow.
to learn how to make sandwiches.
It's good
I can do what I say.
I think
the sandwich he made
is a little better
than Harry Potter.
Xinxin is hungry.
Who did you give this sandwich to?
Why not?
She wanted to do it with me.
For Xiao Ling.
Is the sandwich good?
Did you eat it yourself?
No.
You dare not eat?
I left it for Hua. I dare to eat anything.
Xiao Ling said it's delicious.
It's okay. I'll feed it now.
You eat it.
You eat.
I wish I could see you eat.
I've never seen him eating.
I just ate some rice this morning.
When did he eat anything?
This morning.
Have you seen it?
I don't remember much.
Yes, it's just vague.
No.
Who knows how to gain 6 kilos in eight days?
You've gained 6 kilos.
Why?
What did you eat so delicious?
Who knows?
I eat and drink every day.
Take a bite and it'll turn dark.
You eat it.
He ate the flowers.
Is it good?
A little salty.
Is it bad?
No, a little salty.
Why is it salty?
My taste is light.
I can't. Let me have a bite.
I don't believe it.
Could it be...
I'll eat this side.
Add a sausage
It's not salty
It doesn't taste at all.
What's wrong with you?
You just want to eat what I've eaten.
It's a bit salty.
Hello.
Hua.
Ask Harry to make breakfast for you.
It's okay.
Harry, go.
You ate someone else's food.
Whom did you eat?
Eat her.
Go help.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I'll just drink yogurt.
Hua, do you want some eggs?
What?
Eggs. Okay, put it there.
I'll eat it.
Whose breakfast is this?
They all made it for Susu.
Whose is this?
Susu's.
It's Susu's again.
Come and eat your breakfast.
You're so happy.
This is soup for you.
Harry made this for you.
Eat.
Do you want it?
No.
It's not for me. I don't want it.
I can't eat it.
I ate half of it.
Don't waste it.
I think girls like favourite.
So I think
a little bit disappointed.
You got up so late.
I got up early.
I ate half of it.
I thought someone took it.
I ate it. I ate it upstairs.
That's good.
Eat up.
All sandwiches.
Someone's coming.
Hurry!
Someone is coming.
Who's here?
My name is Tae-seo.
I'm a model.
Hello
Hello.
Who is it?
New guest.
We have a new guest.
Hello.
Let's go in.
As soon as he came in,
at a distance.
Because I like tall guys.
If it's his first look,
I couldn't control myself.
I was too excited.
Have a seat.
Let me introduce myself.
Hello, I'm Terri.
Hello, I'm Susu.
Hello, Susu.
Xinxin.
Hua.
Fatty.
My name is Soup.
Soup?
I didn't expect a rookie to come.
I had a high first impression of him.
He should be a model.
Because the other boys
other boys may still be in school.
So after he came in,
his aura is different.
He looks mature.
and similar.
who acts as a bossy president.
I think Terri
should be Xiao Ling's type.
Handsome.
Of course he's handsome.
But I'm happy too.
Because this boy may give my sister
a better way
or she has more choices.
What's MBTI?
ENFP.
But I'm a little introverted.
Okay.
I understand.
There's an ENFP.
He's not back yet.
Aren't you also an ENFP? No.
Three.
Yes.
Okay.
So sudden.
Harry, you're so happy.
What's your smile?
Can you tell me?
Harry, your smile is that you're happy with a boy.
No.
We have a similar name, but...
He's already looking forward to new girls.
So a new friend will come today.
One?
Two Guoli.
Two, but she can't.
Together?
I can't do it.
I've already started calculating.
So one of us
one of us will come.
Yes, we can have brothers.
Three.
Do you all know
each other's occupation?
Okay.
Can we tell him everything?
Isn't it fun not to tell him?
Okay.
I have a guess.
Colleague.
I'll...
I think I can say it out loud.
Me too.
Two words.
I think I know.
Two words, right?
MT?
You said that.
MIT, right?
Yes.
Im MiT.
Yes, I'm from MIT.
Do you all have pets?
Do you have one?
I have two cats.
And mine has two dogs.
Yours has two.
Your brother has two dogs.
Yes.
When are your brothers coming?
Or are they already here?
I can't tell you.
Hurry up.
Why are you so excited?
You go. You are the most excited.
He said something wrong. I really...
No.
Guess if it's a man or a woman.
A girl.
Three, two, one.
It's a mission.
Okay, it's the mission.
You need a plan.
The picture is not here.
Okay.
I'll read it this time.
You read it.
To the boy in the house.
Welcome new members to the cottage.
We prepared a
for boys.
Let's go to the designated location.
Let's go.
When I got the text that a guy went out for dinner,
I was thinking,
Oh no.
The three boys
would ask me a lot of questions.
and attack me.
I'm actually a little nervous.
You said you wanted to eat pizza.
Yes.
Let's eat.
Anyone wants some?
This tastes like white grapes.
I'll drink white grapes.
My 30 degrees
30 percent.
That's juice content.
It's my favorite peach flavor again.
I'll have a low alcohol.
Cheers.
What did you talk about yesterday?
Let's start with the soup, okay?
What did I talk about on a date?
Because you're the first one among the three of us.
What did you talk about?
Did you choose your date by yourself?
or random?
Not yesterday.
The girl chose the date yesterday.
It's girls who choose boys.
It's not girls who choose boys directly.
but after the girl chooses the boy,
you have to vote for his brothers.
So the date yesterday
was a coincidence.
Yes.
If a girl chooses a boy,
For example, she wants to go on a date with you.
But she must guess
who your brother is
to succeed.
If you guess my brother,
go on a date with me.
Not with you.
I gave you the wrong one.
Really?
What?
Isn't that strange?
When you arrived,
you're not the person you want to see.
Really?
It's her, not me.
Yes, the girl.
Yes.
I think boys
will have this part.
Tonight?
But you already know.
We don't know.
But
we have a guess.
But we don't know.
We know more than I do.
Tell me.
You came in today and saw this.
The two you think are the most alike
Harry and him.
The girl on the right.
Harry and the girl on his right.
That's Harry and Xinxin, right?
Okay.
It's okay.
You guessed right.
Amazing, right?
Right?
That's amazing.
Very confident.
Because
you two have more interactions.
Yes.
Yes, she should be the elder sister.
It feels like talking to you
Yes.
Very overwhelming.
Yes, it feels like a sister
to her younger brother.
Yes.
The two most alike
are not inside.
He and his brothers...
Right?
No, she's here today.
I don't believe it.
His brothers are here today.
Really.
I don't believe you. He's definitely not here.
Is your brother here today?
Guess.
She must be here.
Do you think she'll come today?
Is it possible that she's already here?
Impossible.
Why?
No reason.
I can only say that I'm good at acting.
It's possible, really. I majored in acting.
Yes.
I learned acting.
This boys' chatting house
shouldn't talk about
but about the opposite sex.
Yes.
Is there anyone you like?
Who do you like?
I haven't touched
Just say the first sight.
We're not all here.
It's hard to say.
Let's talk about the three here first.
Kind of.
Because I
I think
I don't think we've got enough contact.
Because I think all three girls are good.
Yeah.
Let's ask what type do you like?
I like people who get along well.
We may have more common topics.
But appearance doesn't matter.
Not very important.
Personality is more important.
All important.
I'm sure they all look good in our house.
Yes.
You can also ask us a question.
Let me think.
After all, you've lived
for three or four days.
Did you have a date?
Yes.
Just get in touch.
Are you interested in it?
Yes.
All of them?
Some people still haven't arrived.
Both.
You too.
Someone's here.
What are you doing?
Someone is there.
He's the most obvious.
Really?
Really? I didn't feel it.
You didn't feel it?
If you feel it, something will happen.
Your siblings.
Soup is interested in your brothers.
If you guess it like that, he's my brother.
For example, Soup likes your brothers.
How do you feel?
You will...
If Soup likes my brother,
I'll pay more attention to the soup.
Normally.
What do you think of him?
Yes.
Where's the soup?
It depends on
if he can play ping-pong.
Can I play with you?
Can I beat you?
Maybe it depends on his sincerity
or his character.
The rest may be behind.
It depends on his character first.
I think we're all the same.
I'm not.
Aren't you?
Then answer me.
I'll see if he's pretending or not.
If he is,
no matter how good he is,
he may not be able to tell.
He's just pretending.
What if your brother loves him very much?
No.
Then you will...
Tell your brothers
if you want to be with him,
I won't help you.
Yes, will you stop it?
I won't.
I think
if I had found out,
it wouldn't have happened.
made my brothers like him very much.
You will get involved.
I will.
You would tell her a lot about this man.
that he's not good.
If he's really bad, he'll...
What about you?
I should be like you two.
I know how to observe.
Yes, I won't say it.
I'll deny someone
by some trivial things.
I may have a long period of time.
If you go out
with a girl,
what would you do with her?
Good question.
I don't think I'll take her.
I'm good at it.
I want to take her
something I want to try.
For example, skiing.
But I've never skied.
Neither have I.
You don't either?
Do you want to try?
I want to try.
Can you take me there?
The three of us.
Like this.
OK?
Okay.
What about you, Fatty?
What do you think
with a girl?
what would you think?
I might feel relaxed
and choose a nice cafe
and have a chat.
Will you take her to race?
No.
Because I think the first date
is mainly
to get to know each other.
Maybe we should communicate.
I agree.
I will take her to a hotel.
I guess...
Yes, let's eat and have afternoon tea.
and watch a movie.
Let's have afternoon tea.
I think afternoon tea is a good choice.
Show us.
I think different situations
different situations.
For example, in the small house,
our personal information is relatively confidential,
We don't know
each other's growth experience.
At this time,
I might choose to take her
where I grew up.
or what I've done the most,
I want her to know more about me.
If it was in the small house,
I would be like this.
But if it's outside,
I'm usually socialising.
At this time,
maybe we should go somewhere for dinner
or go to the park.
My name is Tata.
I'm a full-time model.
Hello.
Hello
What's your name?
My name is Fatty.
Fatty. OK.
You can call me Tata.
Tata.
A lighthouse.
Okay.
I saw a pretty girl at first sight.
smiling at me.
So my mind went blank.
I didn't know what to do.
I don't know why he chose me.
I was caught off guard today.
I was really nervous.
So you
at the same time?
No.
You're my first guest.
It's an honor.
Yes.
Did you see the photo or
Your childhood photo
I picked RICHMJRYD when I was young
I picked it when I was young
Yes.
Okay.
I decided to see this first.
Your childhood photo.
This photo
smiling brightly.
I think you're a cheerful person.
Really?
It's an honor. Yes.
Take a look again.
But I can see that you're a little fat.
So cute.
I didn't expect
I would meet the first male guest
to meet the first female guest.
It means when I was a baby,
I was far ahead.
The back is crooked.
I'm honored
as the first person I met.
How about a toast?
So you've been here for four days.
Yes.
How is it? In the small house.
I think everyone gets along well.
Are you familiar with each other?
Yes, we are.
And we have brothers.
So we got into that state quickly.
And everyone is relaxed.
So tonight,
for the first time.
I might feel awkward.
I'm an introvert.
You are an introvert.
I need you to guide me.
OK.
Our current situation
Boys and girls E and I
and I.
I think girls have good personalities.
That's good.
What do you do?
I start my own business.
RIC HM
I'm a full-time model.
You're a full-time model.
We have a full-time model today.
Really?
What a coincidence.
Maybe earlier than you.
A little earlier.
Today?
Tata is a model
Terri looks very elegant too.
They have the same occupation.
I think they are siblings.
Can I ask you a question?
Because I think you are slimmer.
So do you have any requirements
your ideal type?
No.
It depends on the eye.
My eyes are round.
Fatty gives me the feeling.
Just as I expected.
He's a cheerful guy.
He can liven up the atmosphere.
I'll have some more cake.
Our food is good today.
Did anyone cook during the day?
Yes.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Are you cooking?
What do you think, Rich?
I think you can cook.
Feels like RICHM
Feeling
Really
No JOHN
I didn't feed myself
with my own hands.
Whose hands
Delivery.
But I ordered too much food.
I don't know what to eat.
I have a lot of delicious food there.
Is it spicy?
No.
Make it light.
I'm going to eat a bit hard.
You'll eat a lot.
It's a bit spicy.
Then you and your brother have different taste.
How do you know who my brother is?
I can infer
based on this news.
Because I like to guess.
I won't tell you.
Okay.
I'll slowly discover
Do you have any romantic lines
Is there someone you like?
Or someone you like?
Yes.
At present,
we are still getting to know each other.
It's okay. You came just in time.
What do you mean?
Everyone is getting to know the stage.
But no one came so early.
You can take a look at the rest.
some boys.
Does this photo look like me when I was young?
Yes.
Really?
I need to reply.
I think it looks like me too.
Pretty cute.
You're the only
with a big smile.
Okay, I'll get going.
See you later.
Okay.
Bye.
I didn't choose to extend my weight.
That's because
he was the first guy I met.
Just keep it.
I want to leave the chance to the boys behind.
and see what's going on.
Tata gives me
a Japanese girl.
A very elegant girl.
After all, the house has been here for four days.
Three or four days, right?
Do you have any good suggestions?
Good advice?
For girls,
It depends on who you like.
If you like someone,
I can't give you advice.
What if
in your situation,
she might want to go on a date with you,
but she chose me.
Should I
know how to get along with her?
If you like someone,
or someone you like.
Look at me.
I can see that
that my roommate and I like.
I'll ignore them.
But when I see someone,
I'll give you an idea.
Or see your siblings?
It doesn't matter to see my brothers.
I can give you some advice.
Okay.
That's enough.
What did you do
what did you do in the house?
What's the most important thing?
Every night at 10 p.m.,
send a message to those who like you.
Yes.
Then your brothers
will know how many texts you received.
Thank you. This message is very important.
Where's Fatty?
Bathroom.
It's a little far.
A little long.
I'm home.
Did I miss something?
A lot of things.
Look at his face.
You'll know how hot the conversation is.
You know what?
Why am I the only one left?
Did you guys speed up?
Did I miss that much?
A lot.
So
guess who my brother is?
I don't think your brother is here.
Your brothers are not here.
Maybe she's here.
I don't believe she's here.
Shall we make a bet?
A bet?
A bottle of fruit cubes.
Ten bottles. One bottle is too little.
That's right.
What do you mean?
A bottle and a half.
No, we have so many days
right?
This thing...
I'll apply for it.
Can I go to the bathroom?
Sure.
I just went there.
You guys talk first.
Don't feel awkward.
Don't miss me too much, okay?
The bathroom is over there.
Outside, right?
Put on some clothes.
The bathroom is over there.
Okay.
Don't miss me too much, okay?
Hello.
Isn't it here?
It's here
It's here Hello
There's a new face
There's food.
I'll take off my clothes.
You're not full?
No.
I'm not full.
I ate the most.
I ate five or six pizzas.
Okay, you can continue.
I can't.
Look at my stomach.
I haven't eaten yet.
If you told me earlier,
I would have brought you the pizza.
I didn't know you were eating.
I'll eat it later.
It's all gone.
No.
I ate it all.
Let's eat.
It's okay.
I'm not hungry.
What's your name?
I'm Harry.
Harry.
Yes.
Okay, you can call me Tata.
Okay.
Do you mind if I stretch my stomach out?
I'm really a little full.
No problem.
When Harry came in,
he gave me
he was actually relaxed.
When he came in and sat down,
and started to take off his clothes.
He kept saying he was stuffed.
I think he's a little funny.
I don't mind if you eat more.
It's okay.
It's okay. Give me some noodles.
Yes.
Can you cook?
I can cook.
You can cook?
Yes.
What will you cook?
What do you want to eat?
What do you like to eat?
Spicy food.
Spicy.
Oh no, you don't know how to cook.
You can learn.
Okay.
Actually, I'm not good at it.
I learned it step by step.
I can cook everything my brothers like.
But
I learned it for her.
Not really.
It's mainly to make a living abroad.
to make a living abroad.
It's really a foreign student who cooks
Foreign students fool students.
I'm in London.
I can't order any Chinese food at home.
I can only learn to cook by myself.
The Chinese food there may not be authentic
It's definitely not authentic here anyway.
Your accent is...
Guess where I am from.
No, I have the answer in my heart.
You have the answer?
Okay, let me know when you have a chance.
Do your brothers have accent?
No.
I can only tell you that my brothers
are not very similar to me.
It's not easy for me to guess.
Not easy.
It's not easy according to normal logic.
It's not easy for others.
You already guessed what you think.
I've basically guessed it.
Tell me something.
I haven't seen them now.
or anyone.
I'll be the first one.
It's an honor.
Seriously.
I have a photo of you when you were young.
Why?
You have my childhood photo?
Yes.
Aren't you curious?
Wait.
Sort it out.
Wait, I'm a little nervous now.
I was chosen
chosen me
and chose this meeting.
Okay, got it.
I chose this meeting.
Just looking at me
I see. It's okay.
You're so clumsy.
Do you know which one it is?
No.
Here.
Wait.
What? You don't dare to look?
I'm afraid it's too ugly.
Just break it for me.
It's not ugly. It's cute.
Okay, let me see.
This one.
Wait.
Did you choose me because of this photo?
So cute.
I thought it was just
I was assigned.
You can also say that.
Yes.
You're now roll, roll, roll, roll, roll, roll.
Me, right?
No.
Okay, here's the regular question room.
Okay.
Hobbies.
Hobbies, taking pictures, watching movies,
Playing badminton.
Really? I play badminton.
But I'm not good at it.
but I love playing.
Speaking of which,
I just bought a badminton net today.
Really?
I bought a ping pong table
and a badminton net.
Good.
Do you have any other hobbies?
No, about the movie.
Movie, suspense.
Wait.
I like suspense movie too.
What's your favorite movie?
The Unseen Guest.
Wait, I haven't seen it yet.
"fatal ID".
I've watched "fatal ID".
This is OK too.
I seldom watch those.
It's like listening to songs.
I never remember the name.
I can't remember either.
I only remember its melody and its
Just listen and listen.
Yes.
And you can hum.
Work news.
Where were you?
Excuse me.
We talked about the movie
after the movie.
Can you sing?
I think I can do it.
Not bad.
But my family said I can't sing well.
I get along well.
Because when I was chatting with him,
the atmosphere is more harmonious.
Because he'll take the initiative to talk.
It makes me more relaxed.
So at this moment,
to extend the chat time.
Yes.
We actually have a segment.
Every time we enter the house,
I ask what MBTI is.
I'm ISFJ.
Then I'm "little old man".
"Little old man".
INFJ.
Yes.
You're not introverted at all.
Because when I feel awkward,
I want to talk.
When you feel awkward,
It's awkward to talk to me.
No, it's just self-embarrassment.
On the first day,
when I entered that room,
I talked a lot.
When I went in, they said,
I said, "Hello, I'm Harry."
I'm INFJ.
After 10 minutes,
Are you really an introvert?
You've been questioning me
Am I an introvert?
But on the second and third day,
I didn't talk much today.
Because it's already cooked.
You were so talkative just now.
This is the first time we met.
It's okay. We'll get to know each other again.
No, it won't be like this tomorrow.
Okay.
Fortunately, I'm an introvert.
I was wondering how we could talk.
I (introverted) and I (introverted)...
with me.
Let me tell you.
If you want to go on a date,
or hang out with someone else?
do you think it's someone who talks a lot
or someone who talks less?
He must be talkative.
ISFJ, right?
J.
I have a plan.
But...
I understand.
You belong to
If someone else is better at making plans,
I'm willing to let him do it.
Yes.
But if that person
P,
you can make this plan.
Yes.
We need a plan.
I think so.
Yes.
I agree.
We actually finished our date yesterday.
So you had a date yesterday?
Yes.
I was on a date yesterday.
I felt like a good friend.
We just met, but...
No, I think my first sight was very accurate.
You thought we were friends at first sight.
you can't develop anymore.
And I'm someone
If we were good friends,
I wouldn't be a (lover).
Yes.
Hold on.
I'm a bit full.
Didn't you hear that it's ripe?
I don't want to hear it.
Actually, I really want to guess the love line.
I guessed it on the first day.
Can you guess mine?
Can you guess it?
Only you have intentions.
Or your brother?
I meant it.
I can guess it.
You can never guess.
I can guess it all.
Not folding.
I look forward to it.
to predict him.
Can I guess?
Yes.
We only talk about the first sight.
Are you sure you want to say it now?
Because two girls haven't arrived.
Take a guess.
I think
you don't remember his name at all.
I know the order.
One to the right side of Harry
In the middle, two.
Then three.
Okay, let's guess each other.
Okay.
Really?
Tell us.
I think three.
Say something.
I think neither of you can guess it.
Maybe.
Tell me.
I didn't know
you are actually
If you're interested in someone,
you will deliberately avoid it.
Yes, intentionally. Yes.
I'm like this.
The three girls
a little bit in front of one.
But I'll avoid it.
It's my turn to ask you.
You can ask me.
I'll ask Fatty first.
What type of girl do you like?
I like Fang.
I get along with my personality.
and cheerful.
It seems that
hobbies are very important.
You need to
have a good chat.
I must have common hobbies.
We are very similar.
Yes.
Because I'm an E
an outgoing person.
Maybe I'm more
In this way,
we can do many things together.
Will you take the initiative to the female guest you like?
I am.
You are?
I'm completely opposite of you in this aspect.
Do you take the initiative?
He's just like me.
He means...
If the girl you like
there are two people in love at this time,
will you choose
wait or give in?
Or do you want me to go too?
Will you fight for it?
I will wait.
You will wait.
But
if the girls will respond to me,
I'll take the initiative.
If you don't take the initiative,
if you don't take the initiative?
I mean
maybe one of the two boys
she might take my side.
and give me some information.
You'll try to communicate with her
and see if she'll give me this response.
If I did, I would...
you would take the initiative.
But you won't be too active.
Yes.
Okay.
Well...
I just said
We're friends now, right?
Give me five.
Fair competition.
OK. No problem.
I agree.
Right, I just said
we might be
the same girl.
That's what I mean.
I didn't mean
I thought you were passive like me.
Yes, you were passive too.
Right?
Yes.
I think it's good.
We all know it.
This is fair to everyone.
Su Su's eyes are always on Terri.
I think
I'm more handsome than him.
But he has a better temperament than me.
He makes me feel threatened.
and pressure.
But fair competition
Compared to soup,
I can cook.
I think this is my advantage.
I may be more mature
and more interesting.
What are you doing?
It's nothing.
Fatty said luckily there was no conflict with me.
No.
See you tonight.
Okay.
See you later.
Bye.
Good morning.
How are you?
Not bad.
We just went up the altitude.
It's going up.
What height?
I really can't tell you this.
This is a secret.
Exciting.
How exciting.
Which one do you think
my first impression of?
My brother.
How did you guess Xinxin?
No.
No?
No, it's a little funny.
It's so funny, cube.
This is so fun.
It seems right after a long round.
But it doesn't seem right.
Why not?
Really? Inner?
Don't you think so?
Probably.
I'm just like him.
It's okay.
So why don't the three of us live together?
Sure.
I need to use the bathroom.
Okay, go ahead.
Thank you for your permission.
Hello.
Hello
The third person I saw was soup.
Soup?
His appearance is unique.
and distinctive.
Hello.
How should I address you?
Just call me Soup.
Soup?
Yes.
You can call me Tata.
Tata.
Okay.
Nice to meet you.
A little cold.
You're an introvert E.
I am. Take a guess.
Little I (introverted).
E.
Not really.
No.
You are E.
I'm an outgoing person.
E is not.
You are not E.
Are you here alone?
Yes.
Okay.
How many people did you meet?
Guess.
Two.
No.
I'm the first one.
So you just arrived?
Yes.
I took a photo of you when you were young.
A childhood photo?
Let me see.
I thought he was a foreigner.
He looks like a half-blood.
I'm a mixed.
Which part?
China, America.
Okay.
I think you had a bite of this blueberry.
I didn't have dinner.
Eat more.
I actually ate a lot.
It's okay. I'll drink some water.
How did you get along in the house the other day?
I felt quite reserved at first.
Do you have
in the house?
Something like that?
Yes.
Did you have a date?
What do you usually do?
Maybe in sports,
For example,
Do you want to guess
I'm actually a semi-professional.
I'm working out.
Sports?
Basketball.
You look tall.
How tall are you?
I don't know about 1.85 meters to 1.9m.
It's too much.
1.85 meters to 1.9m.
Actually, the reason of my exercise
I have a little chest, a little hunchback.
Tennis.
Tennis on the table.
table tennis.
Ping-pong. Will it be like this?
Because you are
The stage is so high.
You have to play on your knees.
I thought tall guys play basketball.
What about you? Can I ask about your occupation?
Sure.
I guess models.
Is it so easy to guess?
How?
Because the new guy
I knew he was a model too.
Is he a model too?
You didn't know?
I've never seen anyone.
That's interesting.
My brothers
are almost the same.
I'm a little confused now.
You're almost right.
Is it easy to guess your brothers?
It's hard to guess.
You can only
and details
can be guessed.
For example, when something happens,
when something happens.
Who is the first person he looked at?
Normally, he would guess it through this information.
So you'll ask your brothers for help.
quietly.
No.
I should know this.
I'll take the initiative to avoid this.
My brother and I are a little obvious.
A little.
You've already guessed it.
We already guessed it.
But I'm not sure if you're right.
Maybe.
I'll go back tonight.
Okay.
We're siblings.
I think the soup
It gives me
a dull feeling.
Among the three boys,
He just doesn't know where to go.
Let me reply.
Okay.
I have to go.
Okay. See you later.
Bye.
Nice to meet you.
You'll be a good friend.
The first time you saw her,
This is it.
Because she's not so arrogant.
and she kept laughing.
We were smiling.
for so long.
What?
What took you so long?
No, only three minutes.
Okay.
What?
Why are you laughing?
Nothing.
I want to laugh at you, OK?
Yes.
What do you want to know about us?
Because...
I think
I have some questions.
About you
About your date,
not siblings.
Partner?
Yes.
The one you like
In a relationship,
in love
or emotional?
I want to be rational.
But I'm always emotional.
We're the same.
We'll just have a slap and a punch.
One more.
We are the same.
I'm just like him.
I may not be alone
I'm not alone at all.
I was very rational before I fell in love.
in many things.
But after I fell in love,
a "loser" lover.
Me?
the same?
I'm rational.
Reason?
Actually, it's good to be rational.
More rational.
Reason will make you happy.
I'm more rational.
I need to go to the toilet.
Okay?
Go ahead.
I'm going to organize my makeup.
What do you think?
How is it? Let's talk.
I'm not telling you.
How could you say that?
They asked me about my first impression.
Because I saw three girls
I saw three girls.
Three?
Yes.
There's a boy and a girl.
They are working today.
Yes.
I only met three girls.
Then they asked me
question you.
Yes.
You must choose one among the three girls.
Who will you be more interested in?
The three of them were wrong.
So
there are people
in the house.
You can't say that.
Someone you're interested in.
Yes.
The first impression may be more interested
one of the three girls.
So you've already moved in?
Yes.
How is it?
When we just entered, we were all together.
and have a chat.
It's still a little awkward.
But everyone is nice.
They'll say it's more touching.
some topics.
What activities do you have tonight?
Let me join you quickly.
Before entering the house,
they were playing games.
They're already playing.
Yes, we're playing games.
We sat together
and played.
They have a box
a box like Truth or Dare.
You draw.
If you have questions,
You can ask others.
or others.
Are there any activities tonight?
I think so.
You or them?
They organize.
I came later.
Yes, we'll follow the arrangement.
Okay.
That sounds fun.
Did you talk about
did you
a little...
I won't tell you.
Okay.
How do you feel?
Guess.
I guess you are
Soup.
Right?
I'm not telling you.
Do you know how I chose them?
You chose them.
Then why am I the last one?
I didn't choose you.
Okay.
He gets angry right away.
No.
I chose it.
You have to plan for me.
So you should...
So I asked them some questions
ask them some questions.
What kind of girls do they like?
And...
I didn't ask them that.
So what did you ask?
Almost.
We need to resonate
and have common hobbies.
and get along well.
Yes.
It's almost the same.
I actually want to eat blueberries.
Let's eat.
I think Harry wants to eat it.
Harry really eats a lot.
We just had dinner.
he should eat the most.
He kept touching his stomach.
So we...
In their eyes,
we are siblings.
Yeah.
I'm telling you.
It's not easy for me to play your brother.
You know what?
Hello.
I feel like I've seen you before.
I think I've seen you before.
Okay.
You can call me Tata.
How should I address you?
You can call me Terri.
It's an English name.
Yes.
Open it first.
Okay.
See if there's any problem.
Introduce you and your brother to them.
But besides age,
except age.
Go ahead.
I have a brother.
He's three years older than me.
Same as me.
as me.
He may talk more than you,
but he's gentle
and calm.
And I
I have a sister.
But she's seven years older than me.
When I was young,
he would take care of me
I might play the role of my mom.
My parents may be busy with work.
I even think you know my brothers.
Maybe I do.
Really?
We met in Shanghai before.
Because once on the road,
we met
You were with your brother.
Okay, I remember now.
Do you remember?
I remember everything.
It's closed.
It's closed now.
I didn't expect it was you.
I was surprised.
At first, I thought
I would live in a small house.
I wasn't familiar with the place.
I don't know anyone.
I suddenly feel a familiar
I feel relaxed.
Surprise.
It seems to be fate.
It's like destiny.
Go ahead.
I'll get it.
Take a look.
Let's watch it together.
We will join
as a special identity.
Please do what's below.
Don't reveal our real identity.
We need to disguise ourselves as siblings.
(to fake the truth.)
Don't tell anyone about our first meeting.
It's okay. We're real siblings.
Let me tell you.
Okay.
Two privileges.
Before we announce our relationship,
he entered the siblings' house every night
and share stories with their own brothers.
Everyone has a chance to go on a date with Cupid.
Easy.
Very easy.
What do you think?
Do you think you can do it well?
Yes.
It's a bag.
To be honest,
your brother and I are quite close.
I know what kind of person he is.
Okay.
We may meet less often.
I played with them a lot.
So when I came in,
I said you looked familiar.
Yes.
Let's continue.
I'll do it.
Okay.
What support do you want me
in the house?
Do you need my help?
I need you to identify men for me.
A bag.
Check it from your man's perspective.
If you have feelings for someone,
I can help you.
I can ask around for you.
Okay.
It's mutual.
I suddenly feel like I really have a brother.
We're not siblings.
It seems that we are
we are not siblings.
It seems that we might be...
Yes.
Let's decide the order of you entering the house.
I'll go first.
You go first.
You can ask around first.
Get along with them first.
and get close to them.
Then take me in.
Sure.
Let's pack up and move in.
Okay.
I'll wait for your good news.
Remember to pick me up.
I'll come as your brother.
I'll go first.
Okay.
Ask around.
Are you still nervous?
I'm fine.
Really?
But it's a little...
Just like me.
It's the same when I went into the house.
But everyone
It's good that you're integrated.
Everyone is
quite relaxed.
There's a text message.
Okay.
I'm going back.
Okay, bye.
See you later.
Bye.
Now I can choose a man
to accompany you into the house.
Every Thursday at 18:00 p.m. Members will enjoy the reproduction of "Sibling Defense Diaries".
12:00 on Friday. Members enjoy the pure version of "Love and Sisters".
TV. Enjoy high-quality audiences.
International to unlock multiple language subtitles
Creation Center and win the bonus.
Send live comments to witness the bond between family and love.
Go on the news and search "Super Drama Show". and watch more interesting content.
(Search "Love Siblings") It's all about Baidu Encyclopedia.
Ask Xiao Yan. Wen Xiao Yan. A new search intelligence assistant.