It's called Tata. It's called Tata. It's called Tata. It's called Tata. Ta-da. Ta-da. Ta-da.
I like taking photos.
I like pets.
I like walking dogs.
I like watching movies.
When I was a sophomore,
my brothers took me into the industry.
and started to be a model.
My hands and feet are like
a cheerful boy.
I was three years older than her.
I saw a photo by chance.
I think it was when I was five.
with my family when I was five.
She was wearing sunglasses.
and made a cute pose.
That was the first time I realized
I had a sister.
We planned to get the second child.
I told her when we got married.
I told her to have two children
Both daughters
Both sons and two children
Because when she gives birth to a daughter,
many people told her not to give birth.
I said no.
I want to give birth now.
The two of them are younger
They're smaller.
and have two children.
Both have friends
That's how you consider giving birth to two kids
It didn't go so well when giving birth to a daughter
The delivery room
About five hours
Maybe four or five hours
I was very sad.
Then there was a power outage.
It's been over an hour. It's been a while. It's been a while.
It's more urgent
My family is outside
I don't know what happened.
But the nurse
told us that
It's okay.
The electricity came after the birth.
Our comrades just said
call her a power outage.
Children can be
One girl and one child.
It's good to have both children, right?
It's still full of happiness.
I've liked you since I was a kid
When I first saw her,
Touch her feet
Kiss her face
It's very warm.
Seeing this scene,
my daughter is a very beautiful
and adorable girl.
She's really a good girl.
In the eyes of others,
They are all very polite
From elementary school to college
from elementary school to college.
We work hard.
My family said
they are the top dishes of the Luo family.
The best dish.
The most beautiful dish.
That's what it means.
We fought a lot when we were kids.
Yeah.
Come on. Come on.
I don't have much
to play a brother.
When I was young, I was at home with him.
I had a
Mickey's watch.
He pretended to take a look.
But he removed the Mickey on my watch
on my watch.
She cried at home
Then he told his mom to come here
It was memorable
Until now,
my Mickey watch.
I think you did it on purpose.
Because I feel that every watch
was ruined by him.
My hand is really bad. My hand is really bad.
She bought an ice cream
She bought ice cream
I asked her if I could have a bite.
She said yes.
She said you could only bite a little.
Then I took a big bite on purpose.
Half of it.
Half of what?
She ate the whole ball.
Then she threw the ice cream
and left crying.
I liked playing Go back then.
I played Go with him at home.
And he
in the game,
he was a little naughty.
Then I just
I flipped the chess.
and opened it.
Then I left crying.
I was angry.
He lost. He lost.
Because he lost.
Then he retracted the game.
Maybe he's a bit "cheating".
to tease her.
After she graduated,
we're in the same industry now.
That's why
like a brother.
I don't have many friends in Shanghai.
I don't know
I don't know anyone.
Then he took me to make friends
his friends.
This is to expand my circle.
It makes my personality
more outgoing.
Only when you grow up
You know how important he is.
He can be best friends
and family love.
I can't tell my parents
to his parents.
with him.
and grow up together.
and company.
We can help each other
and help each other
friends or friends.
can also share
I can't tell my parents.
A confidant who shared her secret.
Isn't that what I just said?
Right?
Daddy has decided
I've decided
a father may
and education
and education.
Maybe
Mommy. Mommy.
Mommy will be more
Dad will be a part of it too.
Yeah. Yeah.
Like this. Like this. Like this.
Okay. Okay.
Right. Right.
If it's dad's red face
Mom will sing the white face
Mom sings red face and dad sings white face
I also learned calligraphy.
My family is all on my own.
I can learn whatever I want.
They won't force us.
But I gave up halfway.
After learning,
I don't want to learn it anymore.
Like this.
When I was a kid,
because they helped me
for me.
Street dance, taekwondo
But I took too much of my weekend time.
I was going to pay that time.
But I cried.
Then I didn't pay the bill.
Yes.
We were not at home once.
they drew
on the bedroom wall
a flower.
Right? When we came back,
I was angry.
But it was funny when I saw them
Because they felt
as if they did something wrong.
Scared of us.
But we can't
We don't usually
to their children, right?
That's how we laugh.
Tell him not to do this again.
Every week,
every week.
The owners there
They all know us
They also know us.
When we were young,
If I had a fight with him,
I'll throw things at home.
This is taboo
It's very serious. It's very serious.
Yes.
Once we fell something,
he asked us
to reflect on our mistakes.
and stop us from going to school.
Let us reflect on ourselves.
One is not to talk back to mom.
You can't touch these two
I usually nag a lot of kids.
She's not afraid of me.
Don't talk back to your mom
You can't touch it.
When his dad says something,
they were afraid.
I just corrected the big direction.
But when his dad talks too much,
when he talks too much.
I feel bad for my child.
I've been dancing
in class.
I may be worried
my parents worry about me
more than her.
They don't worry about my study.
I know how to watch mobile phones
watch TV and play mobile phones.
And sometimes
I'd peel the door quietly.
I used to be the role.
I saw him there secretly.
or there.
or playing with something.
or playing with my phone.
I'll snitch.
My sister often complained to us.
The elder brother bullied her.
That's it.
But we spoil our sister
more.
in his mind.
I think it's...
It's me. It's me.
(Dad!)
Dad! Dad!
He...
The younger sister
in front of her.
Everyone cares about her.
She is a kind
who loves pets.
It's cold in winter.
I'll make them a cat nest.
But my daughter can't take care of herself.
I fed her until seven years old.
Like grapes,
I peeled them one by one
in front of her.
For example,
we have a separate room.
She reserved the room first
Then her son will choose the rest.
A room that's not good enough
But we'll give her
and give her something better.
My daughter is her university entrance exam.
I couldn't help but
I hugged her and cried.
I was worried that she couldn't eat well or eat well.
I'm afraid she'll catch a cold when she sleeps.
I was worried.
When I get home,
I've been in a bad state for days.
I was thinking about
with my daughter.
I cried for days.
I can't stop
can't calm down for a long time.
The way we express love
is to think about each other
about each other.
It's mainly when we walk on the street,
on the street.
We hold hands.
When he goes shopping,
when he sees something nice,
he would take a photo and tell me
"This is pretty."
Do you like it?
I'll buy it for you.
The four of us
in our family.
It's called "House of triumphant."
The kids are outside.
outside?
and life
talk inside.
Join us
share with us.
What did you do today?
To exercise.
or take a walk.
When are you going home?
Tell her
at home.
For example, grandpa and grandma.
How are you feeling?
We often chat like this in the group chat.
We should talk every day.
I'll be more straightforward with them.
I said I love you
They should be shy.
They're all in the form of photos
to answer like this.
Every New Year,
or when I have time to go home,
I always give them a big hug.
Son or daughter, I miss you.
That's it.
My daughter.
What Mother's Day?
she wrote to me
or give me a little card.
and draw
of the four of us.
At the beginning,
didn't think highly of their parents.
I just think maybe my dad is too aggressive
and a little masculine.
We often joke.
At first, we were the least optimistic couple.
But I didn't let you down.
His company opened a hotel.
I was a receptionist there.
One day,
he and his staff
with his staff.
The first time I opened the door for him,
I didn't know why
when I saw him.
Then he came to eat many times.
I...
I wanted to avoid him several times.
That feeling.
My heart beats.
I blushed too.
Maybe it's love at first sight.
Then he might know
through his friends,
we'll be together like this.
We grew up
a happy family.
And I watched
how my parents come all the way here
tolerate each other
and take care of each other.
Dad will change himself because of his mom.
I think this is very important.
Before they got married,
at the beginning,
he was very stubborn
and tough.
But later
I got along with my mom.
All these years,
I have
has been made up by my mom.
Can I say that?
He is
a very gentle state.
I think
change yourself for each other.
This is actually a rare point.
I think good love is
tolerate each other
and help each other.
and accompany each other.
will affect
on our love view.
She would also share
about her love life.
For example, let me be the judge
or analyze this.
I'll give her some advice
and some feedback.
I don't know if he'll listen or not.
He's very objective.
Who can listen to this?
Because she probably
she would tell me after the deal was done.
I didn't participate in the process.
Because she is
a slow person.
is among a group of people.
if she is willing to talk to someone,
or share,
Maybe she is interesting.
Yes.
I hope she can become more independent and stronger.
and make the family less worried about her.
Yes.
Daughter, go to this show.
Dad and mom
are your strong support.
Come on.
I'll go first.
Grab your track.
Xiao Ling is so fierce.
I'm so happy. I'm back.
What's wrong with me?
I gave myself away.
will you give it to me?
Do you think
I'm here to help you?
What do you mean?
I will focus on observing
Susu and Xinxin.
Comedians don't have love
If he had been in contact
for a whole day.
I didn't think he would give me that day.
What does this mean?
What does it mean?
They started this date.
I want to know
Is it the same person you want?
Did you talk so much
when you went on a date last time?
Who did you date the other day?
Can I call it a cold war?
What kind of girl do you like?
Now there's a quiet girl
and a proactive girl.
who do you want to know more?
I brought a book of answers.
Go ahead.
Yes.
I think
she doesn't really like me.
I never
to meet many people.
Today we also want to welcome
the new member
Huang Hongfan.
Hello, everyone.
I'm singer Huang Hongfan.
Welcome.
Welcome Huang Hongfan.
Do you feel blunt in love?
Huang Zihong, you're a blunt person.
I still believe in details.
No wonder he rejected
was turned down by him.
You're a little blunt.
I can't be alone at all.
I just fell asleep.
In my dream,
I have friends with me.
I had many dreams.
You're too E.
So many dreams.
I'm the opposite of him.
I'm the opposite of them.
Try it. It feels good.
No.
Impossible.
It's amazing.
This scene is so confusing.
Wonderful.
Is the date that serious?
It's okay.
College students are at a good age to be sad.
He's just like me.
just like me.
So, please.
This episode
we are
too dramatic.
It's not like that.