Come on. Come on.
Feels like we have wild wine right away.
Feels like there's a wild wine.
will watch Love Sisters first.
Who?
Li Ronghao: Li Ronghao. Li Ronghao: You're like this.
Can you?
When Xiaoling was playing the piano,
when Xiao Ling was playing the piano.
I don't want Xiaoling to see it.
I don't want her to notice.
I think it's best for her
is the best.
Thank you.
I almost cried.
You must have learned it for a long time.
Yes.
But I didn't take the exam.
I just learned to play.
I've always been interested.
Almost.
I learned to play drums when I was a kid.
I can't do it at all now.
Drums
It sounds cool.
He was so handsome.
Of course it was a bit dark
Like a little coal
Do you have a photo
You'll see.
Looking forward to it.
Yes, what's your hobby?
Playing the piano?
I actually like outdoor.
I like skiing.
I only know how to play two strokes.
Me too.
I just want to learn how to play doubles.
Let's go on a date.
Let's go skiing that day.
We went skiing together.
What did you drink?
Chinese medicine.
There's a silver cat outside.
I want to show you.
What?
Stop!
You'll scare him away.
Go one by one.
Where?
Mommy.
Mimi.
It's so family.
Do you want to play the piano?
What do you want to hear?
Jay Chou, order.
I'll play whatever I want.
Susu said
she likes Jay Chou very much.
Then I played it.
but she wasn't there.
I should hide the cat.
Who is charming?
I don't know why he started playing the piano.
I like Jay Chou the most.
My favorite.
Jay Chou seems to write good songs.
I'm going to feed it.
It's coming.
Not every one of them takes a bite.
I saw her with Tu.
I don't want to disturb them.
I think if
the map is interested in Susu,
I'll give them some space to get along with.
I'm not a person
to disturb others.
Dinner?
Shall we get ready first?
Then
Don't have so many people in the kitchen
It's too troublesome.
Yeah, I think we should just divide it.
Four in a group.
OK.
Black and white.
Then call them back.
Why don't we leave them alone?
Leave them alone.
Why didn't you tell me earlier? I'll lock the door.
I'll lock something for you.
Let me tell you.
Let me ask you.
We're going to choose the squad.
We choose the squad.
What squad?
Do you want to fight?
We've decided
to cook.
I don't care about the other four.
OK.
Two boys and two girls.
The back of my hand
Chef and I
Can you cook
To be honest, I'm not good at it.
According to my heart,
I don't think you need to make it based on your cooking skills.
Yes.
Who do you choose?
I choose Hua.
Okay.
How hard is it?
Hua is good at cooking.
Yeah.
OK. You are not qualified to choose flowers.
I chose Hua.
I choose Xiao Ling and Xinxin.
Thank you for today.
Let's cook.
It's okay. We won't do the dishes later.
Come on.
We're having hot pot today.
I thought he chose Xinxin and Susu.
My head seems a bit messy today.
I can't remember his name.
What should I do?
Oh no.
Do you want your polar scallops today?
Yes, or it'll break.
Eat it all.
Come on.
So many people.
You can do it.
Now I find that I can't remember anyone.
What's my name?
Your name is Hua.
You're also called Hua?
He did it on purpose.
I can see it.
Go ahead.
Okay.
Then you two take the hot pot base out.
Put it in.
Where is the hot pot base?
Here.
But we can only eat one flavor.
Right?
So spicy.
I bought the tomato pot.
I can't see I'm a little short.
Let me find it for you.
Tomato flavor?
I bought it.
Let's eat tomato pot, right?
Let's eat spicy food.
He can't eat spicy food.
Why don't you eat?
Less spicy.
less spicy.
How about two pots?
Two pots or two electromagnetic ovens?
No.
No two (pot).
I'll take it.
Eat spicy food. It's okay.
I'll put this back.
What if you can't eat it?
Cook more sesame oil.
It won't be spicy, right?
Are you sure you can drive?
I just finished.
How much do you want?
1.6 liters.
Which one is cold water?
Okay, it's fine.
It's cold water over there.
Put cold water.
Ask him.
You ask first.
Cold water, right?
Hurry up if it's boiling water.
It's okay.
It's too hard for me to do it.
Just put it casually.
Is it appropriate?
So what?
Okay.
I'll set it up.
Okay, I cracked.
Why?
It's too ugly.
It's okay.
I just made salmon casually.
Okay.
Now,
we can wash some vegetables
and iron it?
Of course.
Okay.
I'm coming
Should I peel the garlic?
It's okay. You wash it.
I don't know how.
You can't wash, right?
I can.
I'm good at washing vegetables.
How hard it is to wash vegetables
What if the chef is cooking vegetables tomorrow
Whatever
Whatever.
It's a little cold.
Is it hot water?
No.
What if it's cooked?
It's okay
I'll cook it before eating later
Let me wash it
Okay, wait a moment.
It dropped garlic
It dropped garlic.
Let's flush water.
Come on.
Okay.
Be careful.
Let me do it.
Can you let me pull that?
You can't pull that much.
You can do that.
You can do it.
No way.
Okay.
Failed.
You're so cute.
You have great emotional value.
How stupid you are!
Okay, slow down.
I'm afraid you'll "fly".
I'll cut some pork belly.
But we have enough meat
Let's cook for them tomorrow.
I want to eat, OK?
I'll be straight with you.
Cut.
Finish it.
You must eat it.
I'll be mad if anyone doesn't eat it.
Is this potato slices?
Does it look like potatoes
No.
Don't cut your hand.
You can't cut it.
Okay.
You protected yourself well.
Yes.
Okay.
As long as we can be close.
I haven't said anything yet.
When I saw you say "En",
I know what you want to say.
Really?
The size is different.
I think it's amazing.
Okay.
The emotional value is high.
Eat more later.
Can you cut it?
You can try.
I can't.
I can wash it for you.
No.
Can you cut your nails?
I can't.
He said he could try.
Okay, come on.
Come on.
Don't get spicy.
Cut it with this.
Should I cut it like this?
No.
Looking at him
when I look at him.
Try it.
Come on.
A boy.
What?
Here we go.
OK.
Fatty, look at the camera.
Three, two, one.
I haven't cooked hot pot at home for a long time.
Fatty, you can't dip it.
You have to stand up and eat if you can't.
I have a map.
Oh no.
Wait.
Who made this?
Me.
thought of something sad.
You can eat the meat now.
You can eat the bottom.
What's this
This is pork belly
It's my first time eating hot pot pork belly
I made it
I've only had barbecue
Eat soft food.
Susu.
Su Su. Su Su.
No wonder you can dance.
I should know what kind of dance you can dance.
From elementary school?
No.
Not really.
I learned it when I was a kid.
And it broke.
But now
I do it when I like it.
What kind of dance?
All kinds of dance, right?
The floor.
When we mop the floor,
when we mop the floor?
Sure.
Wipe it.
Just like that cleaning machine.
Xiaoling.
I've never seen you smile so happily.
No, I found Fatty
grow on the smile
of soup and Xiaoling.
They think it's funny.
We think it's okay.
The soup was also at noon today.
Really?
It's funny when you smile suddenly.
We think it's a little funny.
He thought it was funny.
The soup understands my joke.
I'm a little nauseous.
Why? Are you sleepy?
You're up too early.
Sleep more tomorrow.
It's Harry and me today.
Okay.
Do you need my help?
You need to wear this.
Pull.
Pour it directly later.
It can't be removed, right?
Yes. Just throw it into a trash bag later.
It's more convenient.
I can do it myself.
Let me wash it for you.
I'll wash it after I'm done.
Gloves.
These gloves are so funny.
What's so funny?
This is to prevent dripping on your sleeves.
It's just the two of us.
They all went to rest.
Could it be...
You...
Can you wear it properly?
No.
Can you wear it properly from the beginning?
You either don't wear it
and go back to do the laundry.
Have you decided what to do tomorrow?
I'm going to make beef rice.
Beef rice.
Oh no.
I didn't buy tomatoes just now.
What should we do?
Beef with needle mushroom.
Sweet.
You can't eat it.
I've never heard of this.
Just put the needle mushroom in the beef.
Okay.
Of course.
Should we fry it or steam it?
Just use oil.
Fried.
We need to cook eight dishes.
Sorry.
I'll learn one today.
You make seven.
Curry potato chicken legs.
I think it's okay.
You want it?
I can do it.
Are you sure?
It's not hard, right?
It's just cutting potatoes.
It's easy to peel your hands.
Then you do it.
I think cooking is quite interesting.
Cooking is very interesting.
Really.
Every time I cook, the process is complicated.
I may use several bowls.
But when I was waiting for that dish,
I already washed the dishes.
Right
When you cook,
If everything is messy,
to the end,
I'll slack off the moment I finish eating.
I'll give up.
I don't want to face it.
or there was only one pot left.
I said no.
Wash it tomorrow.
Yes.
Enough.
Do you really have OCD?
You can be dirty secretly,
but not in front of me.
in front of me.
You know?
You just need to look at him
he looks good.
I think personality is more important.
To be honest,
How much do you think looks
to make you like it?
Five points is fine.
Not less than five points.
Six points.
Hey.
That's good.
It means you care about your heart.
You think I talk less today?
I didn't argue with you.
Guoli.
You know oil can't fall into the sewer.
You said fish can't be eaten.
Who told you not to eat fish?
You said you can't eat the intestines.
You can't eat your organs.
What should I do?
In your words,
I lost it.
Lost?
We won't wash it tomorrow anyway.
We're so bad.
Don't let others speak ill of you because of this.
Seriously.
During our cooperation,
there should be
Eight points.
He did most of the work.
Actually, I've been talking beside him.
and quietly...
Actually, time passed.
Two points.
I hope he can keep up the good work.
I'll buy a glass.
Do you want it?
You mean a big glass?
Yes.
Sure.
Let's buy it.
Different colors, right?
Okay.
I heard "Ding Dong".
There's a doorbell.
Take a look.
Are you sure you don't want to choose a color?
Both are fine.
You or me?
Me.
What about me?
Don't you pick one for me?
Green one.
It looks nice.
Life.
Let's go down.
Let's go.
Is he here?
Yes.
Come down.
Another mission?
Fall in.
Is this the center?
You take the center.
To the members of the small house.
Today is the second day
the second day.
(In order to make everyone understand each other better,)
I'll reveal your life album later.
Please go to the living room and wait for the announcement.
(A photo album of life.)
Text.
The soup is on the bookshelf.
on the bookshelf
and share it with everyone.
Soup.
Why did you...
Why are you peeking?
Please.
These eyes.
So cute.
Kind of cute.
Very cute.
You look fat.
"Crown Prince".
This should be me who grew up for years.
and became a little prince.
At this time, I may not know
I would fall in love with something
that you will love with your whole life.
I'm
(who participated in)
(in the United States.)
Table Tennis?
You play ping pong.
I won the second place in the youth group.
And this one.
This is the first time I represent the American team
on behalf of the American team.
Although I didn't win,
I'm still very happy.
This photo
is the National Championships I participated in.
My teammates and I
won the second place of the team.
In this competition,
in this competition,
I won.
The top American man.
Awesome.
This is the photo
I entered Tsinghua University.
Lucky.
Tsinghua University approved
My talent in sports
gave me the qualification.
So happy.
Great.
This photo is
is organised by Tsinghua University.
Global High School Z Generation
of the Global High School.
I'm happy to be recognized by the school.
This is my favorite teacher
my favorite teacher.
Mr. Liu Guozheng.
I think I'm very lucky
to receive his guidance.
This is Gook-jung's dad.
brought me
Beijing High School Competition for the first time.
I feel very happy.
This photo represents Tsinghua University
on behalf of Tsinghua University.
I've been the champion of men's singles
for two years.
And then
This is the champion I won in three years.
Mr. Gukjung.
He gave me an award.
I think it’s a meaningful moment.
So you’re 1.9 meters.
Yes.
He is indeed 1.9 meters.
Real evidence.
When the soup starts, it will be the king.
He's handsome
And he has high education.
and experienced.
Every photo is classic.
Every photo is highlight.
Everyone has been
really excellent.
I was shocked.
There are no photos at the back.
A letter.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm really nervous.
Me too.
To the soup.
He's handsome and smart.
and good at sports.
These are all the comments you gave him.
He has been working hard
to show others his good and good quality.
He is strong.
I hope everyone recognizes him.
Wait.
It's okay.
A little sad.
He's strong.
I hope everyone recognizes him.
It's not a bad thing.
Anyway, it's his personality.
He has excellent grades
in learning and sports.
But these labels
doesn't form a complete him.
I don't want this letter
can make him cry.
But between me and him
between me and him,
Lettering is a good choice.
Let's be honest.
Indeed, he is excellent.
But these results made him contribute a lot.
When he was in primary school, he started learning piano.
He started practicing sports not long after.
After school, other kids went home.
But he came back at night.
This kind of life
until high school graduation.
for more than ten years.
his willpower
is the strongest I know.
He's tired from training.
He played countless games
for several hours every day.
Maybe the piano was his vent.
Every time I see him playing the piano quietly for a long time,
I would think that.
Then he got into a very good university.
He was also good at studying.
and continued physical training.
and made great achievements for the school.
If anyone
I don't think
Sports Piano Learning
These three are excellent.
He cares about what others think.
he might be sensitive inside.
It's stressful.
I've seen his small breakdown.
Why is it small?
Because he always digests it himself.
He doesn't want to be negative.
So many times,
I didn't even notice his emotions.
But we met every day.
in our life,
Talk to me more.
You don't have to be so strong in front of me.
In my heart,
I hope other than those handsome
and excellent labels,
can be more carefree
and be yourself.
I thought
he might be moved.
or touched.
Because we don't usually
say these things.
But I didn't expect
he would cry at the beginning.
I remember it was all about
Although you have your own shining point,
but please relax.
Don't worry too much.
fear others' comments.
Maybe mom and dad
give you some pressure.
They may think pressure is motivation.
I do care too much about what others say.
I think the letter Xiaoling gave me
in the letter Xiaoling gave me.
I used to think she took care of me
just because she wanted to be good to me.
But now I think
she wants me to be less stressed.
Susu.
This is me.
So cute.
Why are you so thin now?
I'm on a diet.
I just learned to sit.
I won't leave yet.
You can tell it's me at a glance, right?
A round head.
So cute.
Cute. Okay.
This should be when I was three or four years old.
I learned some dance.
and my favorite fluffy toy.
Since childhood
since childhood.
And this is me.
Three or four years old.
My mom took me downstairs
to take a walk.
I was good at posing when I was young.
I knew it would make your face look smaller.
I was skiing.
So pretty.
That's why
I never skied again.
It's because
fractured.
Because... Yes.
I fell into the net.
But no one saw me.
for half an hour.
So I haven't
skiing again.
This is my wig and scarf
at home.
I've always loved my beauty since I was a kid.
This is the first sports meeting
after I went abroad.
About 14 years old.
14, 14, 5.
This is my 18-year-old birthday.
my dad held a adult ceremony for me.
When I was in school,
a famous landmark over there.
It's full of cherry blossoms.
So beautiful.
This is my graduation ceremony.
It was pretty that day.
You're still pretty now.
Okay. That's all.
Okay.
I'm going to read my brother's introduction letter.
Let's listen.
I can't imagine
My brothers have
in my heart.
After all, blood is thicker than water.
But if I have to describe my feelings for her,
I can only say she's a little "big-minded".
She always forgets things.
I don't have a good memory.
Don't cry.
It'll swell tomorrow
It looks silly.
But in a good way,
her optimism and cheerful
and broad-minded.
always brings joy
the people around you.
I'm sorry.
I made a bad start.
Really
Really.
Although someone said she's magnanimous,
in my eyes,
She just
and her family.
It's okay.
So awkward.
She lives
every day.
Be happy.
and happy.
She seems carefree.
This is what she's suitable for.
So when I shoulder
the burden of my family,
I will do my best
to keep her happy and happy.
I can't help crying.
I want to cry again.
Because my brothers and I
never express our feelings.
or say something cheesy to each other.
My sister and I
so frankly.
This time, I'll express my emotions
in a letter.
and write her true feelings.
Let her understand.
As for Susu,
I think from her album to the end,
I think she is
a very cute little princess.
She is also very considerate.
I think she is
who is irrigued by love.
should be the love given by her parents.
are full of
Susu.
May I ask
what do you do now?
I'm a business major now.
I'm in charge of
the copyright of the media company.
Okay.
Got it. Got it.
Come on, Fatty.
Come on.
Smile.
Why does he smile?
Take a look.
Why am I called Fatty because
So cute.
So cute
Meat pout
Yes
Because I was fat when I was born.
So Fatty is my nickname.
My eyes are getting red.
Maybe when I was young,
I might be a bit like soup.
I know cars.
sports player.
This is the first car
when I was young.
Yes, because I was naughty when I was a kid.
I liked
amusement park.
And this was when I was in sixth grade.
What are you doing?
Playing with cars.
You really like cars.
Yes, I really like cars.
When I was in college,
In school,
my classmate celebrated my birthday.
I like sports.
or playing basketball.
Another photo of exercise.
Ride
Ride.
Yeah, maybe I didn't lose weight.
But I still love sports.
By the way,
my occupation.
I'm a car manager.
No wonder.
So handsome.
Yes.
I run three garage.
I started my own business.
And my hobby became my job.
I admire Fatty.
Because many of my classmates and friends
want to start their own business.
But 99.9 percent
is a failure.
If he succeeds,
and run three companies,
or a workshop,
I think
a great thing.
Really.
It's okay.
Not much. I think I can hold it.
I can't hold it anymore.
I can't do it anymore.
When I wrote this letter,
I can only think of three words.
Stop eating.
I remember you've been cheerful and playful since you were a kid.
You're the child king of the kids around you.
You always play pranks and bully me.
I have to cry every time.
It's so hard.
It's really hard for me to read.
I wanted to be the only little princess in my family.
But dad told me
we're brothers.
Wait for me to grow up.
Why are you writing such sentimental words?
Let's hold hands in the future.
and walk together.
Then you became mature and reliable.
We still bicker
Just look at me
you'll know what he's thinking.
People always joke about
you are the male version of me.
I'm the female version of you.
You have
in work.
You always look happy
and happy in life.
You can always see
my lack of confidence and anxiety.
gives me a sense of security.
I know something.
You have many weaknesses and grievances.
But you've been hiding them in your heart
I never say
I'm afraid I'll think too much because of this.
because of that.
You've always been
who loves me the most.
So your big hand
has been holding my hand.
Let me tell you secretly
You're the most handsome guy among the comedians.
Let's do this together.
and enjoy this rare journey.
I didn't expect to cry so much.
The reason I cried
because my brothers and I
don't say these things.
I won't say it either.
Fatty.
I think he's a tender man.
He said he wouldn't cry.
But when he sat there,
I felt like he was about to cry.
I think so too.
he doesn't usually say something sentimental.
He’s actually a very fragile
very fragile.
When I opened the letter,
when I opened the letter.
I saw something in my mind.
What she meant
not only me,
More importantly,
I thought a lot.
I think it's our next life.
Let's hold hands.
When I think about these things,
I really want to cry.
Xiao Ling.
Go.
Here.
This is mine.
So pretty.
A hundred-day photo.
A doll.
Is that all you have when you were born?
Yes.
So beautiful.
This is the first time
went to the park to catch goldfish.
It's really like a doll.
And
This is my graduation photo from kindergarten.
So pretty.
And this is...
I like animals.
That's why I'm riding a horse.
This should be in grade 3 or 4.
I was that tall.
I grew taller.
This is my first time fishing in the lake.
I caught a bask.
This is a photo of me and a lizard.
So I like animals very much.
When I was performing,
when I was performing.
Xiaoling's mom.
I read it out.
Because my classmates
they all think I'm a maternal halo.
I may take more care of others.
Like this.
And this is
when I graduated.
So beautiful.
This is the video
in class.
a makeup photo.
So pretty.
The last one is my graduation photo.
I'm still in Beijing Film Academy.
I have my master's degree.
I'm still studying for postgraduate studies.
How can everyone be so excellent?
Yes, they are all excellent.
Here's the letter.
Let me see if it's enough.
A little.
I won't cry.
Nice to meet you.
Today, let me introduce
the best siblings in the world.
Since I remember,
Xiaoling and I often
because of delicious food and remote control.
No one goes easy on each other.
We've been following the principle of fair competition.
(We grew up fighting.)
After entering puberty,
I gradually have my own pursuit.
I paid more attention
on my own.
She's carefree.
Xiao Ling became more quiet.
She always takes care of everyone's emotions.
Because I'm too tired,
because I'm too tired
in secret.
Xiao Ling never shows herself.
Although she's pretty,
and kind.
She's good at drawing.
She is gentle and delicate.
She's gentle and delicate.
is full of selfishness.
You're out of line.
I like a saying.
We love ourselves more than love others.
but we care about others' opinions
than what they think.
Everyone is good at showing
to everyone.
But Xiao Ling is an exception.
She's self-conceited.
I don't think it's necessary to show
Accept the good or bad you are now.
and improve it little by little.
my own life.
I envy her.
She laughs again.
I can't watch the last part.
I won't let go
I won't let her go easily.
If you want to pursue her,
you must pass me first.
Who wrote it?
It's nice.
I didn't expect my siblings to be so delicate.
Who is it I'm curious
I'm curious.
You're curious too, right?
In the whole letter,
many things
I think it's all about my heart.
But the most touching thing is
he said my existence
in this world
in this world of self-esteem,
in the world of self-esteem.
That makes me feel
he really saw through me.
My sister doesn't like being criticized.
Everyone is showing a better self.
and their true self.
But what I want to tell her
that you may be better than me.
I hope you can
show yourself confidently.
Map.
The first one.
This is my 100-year-old photo.
A hundred-year-old photo.
So cute.
It's totally different now.
My ears were pressed.
In fact, my ears could tell
It's big, right?
It's like this.
Look back later.
You can see this.
This is a picture of me when I was ten months old
So fat.
Yeah I was chubby when I was a kid
Like a fairy
My ears were this big
When I was young
I learned drums in elementary school.
So cute.
The next one was
was a certificate I got
in a model competition.
In 2014,
in 2014
is to help Lin Zhi Ying dance.
Who?
Lin Zhi Ying.
Yes.
I was very happy and excited.
After everyone left,
I left a video there.
And this photo is my transformation.
This is the photo
in high school.
In my opinion,
is the most handsome cut.
Now the hairline is getting higher
So you can't keep a inch
And this.
I couldn't find
a photo with the school.
At home,
at home.
It's Zhejiang Media.
The last one is in the school.
Host?
Yes at school
at school.
I was very happy.
I picked up
on the ground.
When you sprinkle it like this,
this beautiful photo.
This is my current situation.
I'm a student.
It's so long.
(Dear Drawing, Exhibition)
About this letter of introduction,
I thought about it for a long time.
I received your letters many times.
And this is the first time I wrote to you.
I have a lot to say,
but I couldn't say it.
Somewhere
Let's talk about you first.
I remember
When you grow up,
they would chase me and make a wish.
As if as long as I'm by your side,
I can grant all your wishes.
At home,
you are the babies of the elders.
But when you're with me,
you'll become very carefree.
and listen to me in everything.
Give way to me.
In front of you,
I can be the real me.
I can be lazy,
You can be angry,
or do something wrong.
You can say whatever you want.
Many people say that they give me the sense of security.
But you must have given me the sense of security.
What impressed me was one Spring Festival.
I was scolded by my elders.
I was in my third year.
You pulled me behind.
and yelled at her elders.
Don't scold her.
I know you always
want me to feel loved.
You don't want me to envy others.
You're still
to be loved.
but you gave me all your love.
You always show
that don't fit your age.
When you're here,
I'm a capable and independent person.
always like to be a shopkeeper.
Because I know
you would arrange everything well.
You can always take everything down.
and reassure me.
When I ride a motorcycle,
I might fall.
and use your hands to hold me.
is the corner
in a certain degree.
I don't care what happens.
Because you'll always be there and love me.
All this time,
you seem to be a born Letian.
You seldom have worries.
I've never seen you cry.
I feel happy and proud
for your personality.
I hope you can be
happy and happy forever.
But the path of growing up
is not always smooth.
If you want to stop when you're sad,
take a break.
You don't have to be so sensible.
Because when you need me,
when you need me.
I'm grateful to you
in my life.
I've always wanted to say thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you for always being here.
This is not bad.
This is the first letter she wrote to me.
When I read the letter she wrote to me,
I never thought about crying.
I cried while reading.
I don't think I ever cried in front of her.
I can't cry for a while.
Let me tell you.
It rained just now.
That's different.
It's raining.
Have some.
No hurry.
The more I drink, the more I want to cry.
He's nervous.
His hand is like this.
Stop talking, okay?
Sit here. Hurry.
Come on.
If my roommate hadn't said
I wouldn't sit here.
I'll give you energy.
Here.
This one.
They are all funny anyway.
I didn't pick the most handsome one.
I don't remember when
It must be in the shower
Soup is also in the shower
How about we roommates?
What about your roommates?
To be honest,
Actually next to this
is my brother.
I just dropped it.
She looked like this.
I think I dislike her.
You know?
It's kind of pretentious.
I used to pretend when I was young.
What's wrong?
What?
What is this?
Too ugly.
A bit charming.
Very charming.
Halloween
He was raising his little butt.
I thought I was handsome.
I put on makeup.
They are also my brothers.
I can see that.
Yes, I can.
I don't like taking photos.
but my brothers love taking photos.
So most of my photos
with her.
Harry's photo
It means he doesn't like taking photos.
We took photos for him.
They must be very close.
Very close.
It's also a drum.
I learned it.
It was a little dark.
Why is it dark?
Let me explain.
I trained track and field every day.
I won a prize in elementary school and junior high.
It was my school.
in my school.
He can win the first place of nine.
So it's very dark.
Awesome.
I hope in my next life
in my next life.
I don't need to be so dark.
Interior sports.
and got the trophy.
A medal?
This is a medal.
And this shield.
Amazing.
Awesome.
Wait.
Middle school.
It's ugly.
I'm still trying to hide my innocence.
This photo
when I first learned how to pretend.
Is this a headache?
Yes, a headache.
My head hurts.
When we meet Harry next time,
we'll do one, two, three.
Then I shave my hair.
This looks good.
Kitten.
This is my kitten in England.
Bring Eleven.
Eleven.
And then,
my brother was next to me.
to celebrate my birthday with me.
And this is
to shoot.
Angel lamp.
I went to England for eight years.
It's my first time taking a picture with an angel lamp.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Wait.
Don't rain.
I'll take an umbrella.
I can't cry.
Wait. I want to laugh.
Draw yourself.
I won't cry.
My brother
is a big boy with a strong personality.
He has a personality
and has his own opinion.
He looks cool.
He looks like a player.
But in fact,
who hides
in his heart.
He has been smarter than me since he was a kid.
Very right.
I think my brother
very clearly.
He keeps provoking me.
Trying to provoke me?
No matter what I say,
or what I do,
he seems to be going against me.
In my memory,
he's always good at being naughty.
Every day after school,
he always comes home with scars.
My mom will be called to school
she would be called to school to meet her teacher.
At that time, I thought
what to do when he grew up.
Unexpectedly,
as he grew up,
many advantages appeared.
He loved sports when he was young.
He also participated in various sports competitions.
Many sports competitions in school
in many sports competitions.
Although I don't know how to praise,
but I'm still very proud.
And the expression of a wave.
Wave.
It's very detailed.
After high school,
I gradually got busy with my studies.
We've also lived
to go to cram school every day.
I didn't expect that
he actually loves
a science that I've never learned.
Philosophy?
Maybe it's because
his science was better.
So when I quarreled with him,
I couldn't beat him.
Although we were just playing around,
but most of the time,
he always did something that touched me.
When I was sick,
when I was sick.
Although I don't remember this,
but I think I did.
When no one wants to eat with me,
without any complaints.
At last, I hope
he can shine
in the field he loves.
Her letter of introduction is not as emotional as others.
The compliment is more than the emotional part.
I'm touched.
My brother and I
in normal times.
I've never praised him face to face.
This is the first time I wrote to him.
and the first time I praised him.
In the letter,
I wrote many good points of my brother.
I want my friends in the house to know
my brother is really good.
Am I the first one
who set a goal and didn't fall?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It rained just now.
It's sunny now.
It's over.
Xinxin.
Coming.
I'm getting nervous.
I think I'll be choking later.
Prepare the soup.
Yes.
We'll start anytime.
Tu Tu, don't cry.
Tu, don't cry.
This
is a photo of me when I was half a year old.
Half-year-old?
This is about one and a half years old.
Your head is so fashionable.
I've had a lot of hair since I was a kid.
I'm so jealous.
This is the first time I came to Beijing.
You looked like a boy when you were young.
I think you were two years old.
About three years old.
My photo
in my photos.
After that, my family
family reasons.
Then my parents separated.
Then...
my grandma passed away.
for a long time,
I went abroad alone.
When I was 14,
I was alone
with no siblings.
I went to America alone.
Not many photos
I didn't save them.
and moved often.
I didn't even
graduation photos.
I've been changing schools.
I came back from America and went to Singapore.
After three years,
This is the first time
when I was 19 or 20.
So pretty.
She's already 20 years old.
When I was 20,
I went to Japan for a trip.
About a year.
It's in Barcelona.
I love traveling.
My hobby is to travel.
And last year,
I went to Xinjiang.
It's so beautiful.
This is the Global Film.
My brother took this for me.
Nice shot.
You're good at shooting.
This is the investment meeting
last year.
I'm here as the manager of the marketing department.
This is a photo of me and my dad.
Okay, over.
My siblings have been good at studying since childhood.
My little head is more flexible than mine.
She's the daughter of the family.
Especially after being naughty
I got scolded by my parents.
Xinxin always comforts me.
Esther has big eyes.
Smile is warm and shiny.
It always brings joy to our family.
It's the brightest star in the house.
But Xin is also a crybaby.
When I was a kid, my mom scolded me and cried.
I cried when I got bad grades.
She cries even if I steal her snacks.
Speak louder to her now.
I cry too.
It's heartbreaking.
I want to tell my brothers
about the future.
I hope you don't worry.
Don't worry.
Do what you want.
I'll talk about you a lot,
no matter what you do,
I will support you.
Life is full of thorns and challenges.
But we're not alone.
No matter where we are
our bond has never broken.
I hope you can
with a happy life.
Meet the right person and love.
and try it boldly.
and enjoy life.
I'll always be by your side to protect you.
I hope you can be happy every day.
Everything is the best arrangement.
This is my personality signature too.
Your brother wrote it well.
Yes, it's good.
I was touched.
I was crying when he cried.
I cried my nose out.
I think...
But I have no choice.
I couldn't stop crying.
Then I cried.
Because he can sense my emotions.
And when I'm sensitive
and fragile,
he always encouraged me
and told me not to be anxious.
Show your brothers.
Aren't you too relaxed
when you were relaxed?
I started playing by myself.
I think my appearance
in all aspects,
in front of the screen.
Not to mention a romance show.
I think she's pretty.
I think she can do it.
But I never thought
to come to this show.
because of my sister.
I'm He Wenxin, He Wenjie's dad.
Fatty is mostly happy.
and simple.
and sensible.
and responsible.
Esther
It's the same.
filial
and thoughtful.
She studied early too.
She went to school with her brother when she was five.
She had good grades.
So I doted on her.
I've spoiled her since I was a child.
When I was young,
I spent 10 yuan a week.
My sister is 100.
The difference is ten times.
It's not that exaggerated.
Yes.
I found out later.
I was quite shocked.
I thought everyone was $10.
I went into my sister's room
I saw it.
full of snacks.
That means I saved them.
Really?
Yes.
No.
I saw her room
full of snacks.
All kinds of snacks
Something like that.
A pen. A pen. A notebook.
When you were young,
you didn't spend much money.
You don't like studying.
You have a happy family.
He smiles and is gentle.
and brings warmth
to family.
In daily life,
in daily life.
Fatty.
or Fatty, what are you doing?
I seldom call him brother.
Because he had a round face since he was a kid.
He was cute when he was born.
Actually, he was cuter than me when he was little.
A lot cuter.
Although he likes to bully me,
he can also make everyone
to everyone.
They always go out
It's just the two of us.
There are always two people everywhere.
It's good that they have a boyfriend.
They have a girlfriend.
Only the two of them know.
None of us knew.
When I was young,
I liked snatching snacks from my brother.
and milk.
Then my brothers get angry.
I'll cry first
and tell on you.
Then get angry
and then make up.
There's a process.
I could only complain when I was young.
All kinds of complaints
Complain to mom and dad
Tell aunt and grandma
the whole family.
Then I was beaten.
Right.
No.
Keep up the good work.
and figure out a new way to trick me.
I think the way I get along with my brother
is love and hate.
I can tell my sister everything.
and share everything.
Even the two of us
have no secrets.
He taught me something.
I taught him something.
I'm more strict with He Wenxin.
Because she's a girl.
When she was in third grade,
I asked my teacher for tutoring.
and accompany him myself.
Because I used to be a teacher.
and accompanied her every day.
for a year.
Every day, basically in the afternoon,
every day.
I'll see her off at 7 a.m.
I do this every day.
for a year.
I don't care about boys.
I'll let him play basketball.
Go out.
Fatty can play outside.
He's a bit wild.
He likes to play with cars since childhood.
When I see these cars,
since I was young.
So, in the end,
he did what he liked.
He did a good job.
Basically,
I don't need any support from my family.
So I let him develop on his own.
A sense of loss means
I broke up with his dad.
Although love was there,
I think
relatively,
Parents' separation
I owe a little to my child.
I didn't feel it at that time.
When I grew up,
I feel it's a bit weird.
I can feel it
I can feel it.
In junior high.
I felt it in junior high.
Because the two of them are getting farther and farther.
When I was twelve or three, I could already feel it.
I had my own emotions
and locked myself in the room.
Before I went abroad,
my father had a serious talk with me.
Tell He Wenxin first.
We were taking a walk downstairs.
I said your mom wanted a divorce.
What do you think?
At that time, I felt
I could only accept it.
I learned it from my brothers.
12th grade.
I was a grown-up then.
I could accept it at that time.
Because they separated peacefully.
When parents separated,
she was rebellious.
has a great impact on her.
Her personality changed suddenly.
I used to love studying.
It feels like a gentle sheep
a gentle
a wild horse.
The impact of my parents being apart
the most
affect my view of love.
I think
girls should be
in this society.
Wake up.
She's going abroad.
She said there was an exchange student.
She's really thoughtful.
and bold.
I've contacted everything.
She did it herself.
We couldn't contact her.
I was confused at that time.
When I think back, I was scared.
She's only 15 years old.
She was happy.
not afraid at all.
One person carried two boxes
He went to America from Hong Kong Airport, China.
When I was abroad,
It's like holidays.
during holidays.
Maybe I've always been alone.
Sometimes, I don't have friends.
So, the festival is over.
Ever since I lived abroad,
I think
enjoy being alone.
After all,
you have to do everything on your own.
Because if no one helps you,
you can't finish this.
I can't finish my study.
You can't complete your life.
You can only muster up the courage
to do everything well.
So this year in America,
I think after experiencing these things,
it's also a growth for her.
It's a training.
She's very independent.
I used to
I used to sleep with my phone off.
Ever since she went to America,
I haven't
I've never turned off my phone and slept.
I remember
their class ended at noon.
I'm at 2:30 p.m.
She was the first year in America.
She called me every night.
She called me after class.
I waited for her call at 2:30.
I think I've grown up
when I grow up.
Maybe I was naughty when I was a kid.
When I grow up,
when parents
and communicate with each other,
my parents came to me first.
At that moment,
I felt a burden on my shoulder.
For example,
some problems in love,
and conflicts,
he would tell me
Don't be afraid.
It's okay.
I'll help you.
You can do whatever you want.
When I feel a little wronged,
or unhappy,
I want to call him right away.
I hope he can enlighten me by my side.
I'll tell him
emotional words.
he will accept it all.
It feels like we're more than siblings.
Like family and friends
Like brothers and besties.
Multiple identity.
One time Fatty was bullied by a student.
I hit him.
He Wenxin even talked about that boy.
to teach that boy a lesson.
When he grows up,
he told He Wenxin everything.
He was afraid of something.
He Wenxin also dealt with them.
Now I feel
he has grown up.
My family
to train him.
Be responsible.
Right take care of your sister
Now everything
He Wenxin follows you now.
It's upside down.
Fatty told me.
He said he actually
had a boyfriend.
What do you think?
He said I'll watch.
I won't let my sister suffer.
He's like this.
So I feel relieved
I feel relieved.
They are together every day.
So how can I be at ease
How can I be at ease?
Because Fatty saw it.
I'm very interested in his love life.
gossip.
I have to know it as soon as possible.
and know immediately.
she is
who likes to eat my love affairs.
Yes, I do.
They said I can grow up if I eat melons.
I don't need to eat anything.
I don't eat much every day.
She eats a lot.
If she is bullied in love,
I will stand out immediately.
As for their relationship,
I won't interfere in other things.
But I just
I can't see my brother being bullied.
He will...
He gets involved in everything.
He's very involved.
"The three are talking."
Do you think you have the invitation card?
Not necessarily.
Don't be modest.
You're the most cheerful.
But I may not have a card.
Do you think you have it?
I think I do.
You just said no.
If I say yes, you do.
Aren't you disappointed if I say no?
But I know who likes you.
Who likes me?
I said there are two houses.
They have feelings for you.
That's impossible.
Don't do this.
I really didn't feel it.
I think there might be.
Go ahead.
Tell me who it is.
I don't think he...
he didn't say anything.
All the topics
Today.
That's all for today.
I think
Harry...
No, he doesn't.
If not, it's a map.
I think
is like this.
No.
He will answer my words.
Tu is my roommate.
Just ask?
Yes, I was talking about this with Tu.
Then Tu Tu guessed me.
Do you know
Guess who my crush is.
Who is it?
Tu Tu thought you were my guest.
Tu thinks you like me.
Yes, it's funny.
Because when we play games,
when we play games.
You love to pick up my words.
I love to pick you up.
No.
And sometimes,
you call me by my full name.
You scared me.
Show your brothers.
Show your brothers
Go out and freeze me.
He Wenxin.
No.
subconsciously.
That's my problem.
But I think you did well today.
You're quite natural.
I think you're more natural
than the interview.
Loosen it.
You and
Yuanyuan is in charge.
Who am I controlling the scene with?
Not Yuanyuan.
A map.
When playing games,
when we play games,
Can you tell?
Someone likes drawing.
It's too obvious.
I don't like it.
Not like.
I just liked him at first sight.
No.
It's just a game that will hit a car.
I think girls
are not sure about her feelings.
Oh no.
But boys...
I think you and Tu
a little bit.
Do you know who I am?
I think it's obvious.
Who is it?
Hua.
The drawing is also a guess.
Aren't you Hua?
I'm not good on my first day.
You have to stick to your choice.
We haven't started yet.
I think we need to get along.
Congratulations.
You got a card.
Really?
Yes.
Let me help you.
No.
Are you peeping?
Let's watch it together.
No.
No, this.
You're so curious.
Good.
Congratulations.
I didn't expect that I would have one.
To be honest,
Because I think they are all handsome.
You're handsome too.
No.
I can go on a date tomorrow.
Yes.
You can go on a date tomorrow.
Show your brother.
It's my turn.
I look forward to it.
You must be cute when you were young.
Look forward to me.
Look at my childhood.
You really love sleeping.
Yes.
This is when I'm sleeping.
Such big eyes
It's still big now
His eyes are really big.
Dark eyes.
Yes
This was taken by my mom
in Zhuhai.
This is an art photo of my childhood.
So cute.
So pretty.
What a familiar hairstyle.
Dora.
Dora!
It's trendy.
Frowning bangs.
Yes.
I don't have bangs anymore.
This is the same as you.
wearing a wig.
Me? Yes.
Mom wig
Yes, my mom came back.
She was wearing a wig
and took her wig.
When I was young,
I learned a little dance.
This is also the graduation photo
This is a graduation photo
It's pretty.
Skiing
This is skiing.
So
I said we were here.
we could ski here,
it would be good.
And this is...
When I was in Taiwan, China,
in Taiwan, China.
Try the makeup.
Start your own business.
It's comfortable to open a small shop.
Very professional.
Yes.
The most beautiful person in the world
Hello.
I really want to tell you
you are the most important person in my life.
Beautiful.
generous,
and considerate.
All the good words in the world
can describe you.
We grew up together
and grew up together.
You're not like your family.
like your family.
You always make fun of me.
and do childish things with me.
From catching ants
raise turtles,
and play house with flowers and grass.
My favorite is after school this weekend.
after school.
You like taro flavor.
I like strawberry flavor.
We can't finish it.
So you always compromise
and drink strawberry flavor with me.
When I was young,
you grew up with me.
has been deeply engraved in my memory.
If you ask me
the most unforgettable thing for you
I think it was that time.
I had a minor surgery
for personal reasons.
One day, the adults were not home.
You took a leave to take care of me.
Our family asked us
to have dinner at the aunt next door.
But she went out for something.
It's not nutritious to order takeout.
You can't cook.
made me nutritious food.
I didn't know how to cook at that time
Now I know
I know it now.
I learned to cook online
Looking at your busy back in the kitchen
I'll remove the fishy smell
Cut the vegetables carefully later
When you put the meat in the pot,
I forgot to cut the side dishes
and took out the green onion, ginger and chili in a hurry.
I was so scared watching you from behind
but I couldn’t help.
When the last dish is served,
you feel relieved.
You wiped the sweat on your forehead and said
I've never cooked for anyone in my life.
You're the first one.
My parents haven't eaten it yet.
I was very happy.
Is this part "Chef Little Fugui"?
It seems all my worries are gone.
But I regretted the first bite.
Too much soy sauce
The meat turned black.
Potato shredded slices mixed
The cabbage is stir-fried.
I'll argue with you
You can't get married if you do this.
You said it's fine.
If you can't get married, stay at home forever.
I'll cook you bad meals every day.
Although the dishes are unforgettable,
your words comforted me.
This comfort makes me
in puberty.
and conflicts.
You always guide me patiently
face problems one after another.
In my memory, you didn't teach me much.
but more importantly divertizing.
and affect my personality.
Let me smile like you
sunny and considerate.
and always full of energy.
Behind these shining energy,
I know there are many heartaches
when you grow up.
We both know
our family is a bit special.
Don't cry.
They don't seem to care about
your strengths.
are affected by
tenacious concepts of men over women.
I can feel it every family gathering.
You're facing the sex trials of adults.
Wait.
I didn't expect
my brother would say
in the album.
Hua read her brother.
When I wrote to her,
she mentioned that there might be
in our family.
She is still so optimistic
and outgoing.
I think she must be
must be very strong.
When you respond to each other cheerfully,
they feel extremely uncomfortable.
Everyone wants to be loved by their family equally.
But because of me,
because of me.
I can clearly feel
that this is how
is formed slowly.
I also saw clearly
your fragile side
your fragile side.
You always consume more.
No matter what happens,
you have to find the reason.
Not only in love,
but also in life.
Once you fell down,
you went to the hospital to treat your wound
and solve the dispute.
If this happens again,
I hope
stop thinking about solving it yourself.
Just tell me
I can carry you to the hospital
and help you solve everything.
Lastly, I want to say it out loud.
You're the best person in the world.
You're like a gift.
Be more confident.
and less internal consumption.
You don't have to feel sorry
for others' kindness.
Sorry.
I feel burdened.
You deserve to be loved.
Straighten your back.
and embrace everything that belongs to you.
and pursue what you like bravely.
You brought me along when I was young.
Now, I'll protect you.
I'll always be behind you
as your protector.
Thank you.
The last signature is
to get married behind your back.
Because there is
There's a custom when we get married.
Well,
to get married secretly.
The closest man.
She rarely cries.
She rarely cries
in front of so many people.
Because she is
who can hold herself back.
I think crying
is a kind of emotional vent.
so that I can
find the right way
to let
the burden of your daily life.
Show your brothers.
I'm really tired today.
Finally (you)
I'm telling you, I'm suffocating.
You first?
You go first.
Okay.
I think she looks very beautiful
and amazing.
She is a very kind person.
Sometimes,
a little fragile.
But she will be strong
through her appearance
to hide
little thoughts.
is too considerate.
and sometimes
the person I feel.
You punk.
You're so eloquent.
My brother.
He looks like a sheep.
but a big wolf in his heart.
On the outside,
harmless.
But in fact, Xiaojiu and his thoughts
including the dark side.
in fact.
I've smeared more people.
I can still control him.
I can control him.
The first impression she gave me
she must smile a lot.
and be optimistic
is optimistic.
I'm not sure
the first side.
In my mind,
in my memory.
So cute.
White and fat.
I want to pinch it.
Because I knew at that time
I wanted a boy at home.
So when the result comes,
I've already prepared myself.
there won't be
Besides,
I really like kids.
When I knew he was my younger brother,
he was really cute.
I love recording his
in my album software.
I may not have the most photos.
He can take most of his childhood photos.
I think
we are very close.
We never fought.
Although I'm so much older than her,
our work
or in different directions.
But my communication with her
is really zero.
He kissed me cute when I was young.
Bye.
I'll miss you.
I'm leaving. Kiss me.
Stand here and kiss me.
Sit there and kiss me.
Since I was a kid.
Now that you've grown up,
Let go.
She asked me to kiss her when she was young.
When she was young,
when she asked me to leave,
You don't want to?
Every time you say I'm leaving,
you didn't kiss me?
You wanted to kiss me.
So at that time,
it might have become a habit.
You don't want it?
Did I force you?
But when you grow up,
there was no such thing.
After all,
I remember a few years ago,
I forced him to kiss me.
He was so embarrassed.
He...
After all, he's so big.
Right
But now I know how to hug
Just hug
Yes.
She always
help me
sensitive topics.
My family may often say that
I may not be manly
or something like that.
Maybe they think
too many women around me.
She didn't mean to
to hurt you.
but to let you know
They think that's what they meant.
But in my opinion,
it hurts some self-esteem in my childhood.
or something.
Actually my sister could
at that time.
I would tell them
and tell me in private.
Be yourself.
Don't force yourself.
Just grow up happily.
I think the manliness is
the pillar of our family.
can lift up the sky
or protect
and protect.
I think that's the real manliness.
Yes.
We are half-siblings.
a family.
Hello.
I'm Hua's mother.
I'm Yu's mom.
Dad is a handsome man.
My dad is actually an all-rounder.
What are you talking about?
And the mechanical workshop can do anything.
He will take me to the competition.
and put me behind him.
and then the front wheel.
Back wheels.
Drifting
(He shook me around.)
Because her dad
He's very ambitious.
He doesn't want me to get involved in his business.
And I
I have some ideas
and his work.
As a woman,
as a woman,
I just want to
for the rest of my life.
But I don't want to quarrel every day.
and cry.
Then...
we chose to divorce.
I divorced her dad.
But I never
in front of a kid.
Her dad is so handsome.
Kind.
I was young back then.
I was young and immature.
He insisted on getting a divorce.
That's why
to grow up.
When I was young, I thought my dad had an impact on me.
my dad had nothing to do
it doesn't affect me at all.
After I grew up,
I think my insecurity
and sensitive.
may also come from
the lack of father's love since childhood.
I've never...
including now,
I'm actually allergic to romance.
I think it was formed when I was young.
Because I don't think anyone will surprise me.
No expectations, no disappointment.
I've always felt that way.
Because elementary school and junior high school
basically boarding.
So I've been quite independent since I was a kid.
My family life
in my family.
After college, it's because of work.
I moved.
I feel like I'm always moving.
Well,
I want to have my own home.
After the divorce,
I went to Guangzhou.
When I left Ze for the first time,
she came to see me off.
She cried heartbroken.
She grabbed my box and said,
"Mom."
I want my mom.
This scene has always been in my heart.
I'll call my mom.
And...
my mom's phone number
It hasn't changed,
but I couldn't get through.
Every time I called,
I remember a smooth part.
It's...
Hello.
The subscriber you dialed is powered off.
(If you need someone to call back,)
China Telecom from Hunan Province.
(Mobile users of China, please dial 1259.)
Add each other's phone number.
This part
in my mind.
Because
every time I called,
Because he called me in Guangzhou.
and called my phone,
Then you have to add a zero
to get through.
Because my mom
very frugal.
are all like this.
She didn't tell her the zero.
So I've been regretful.
Sometimes,
she wants to call me the most,
When she heard my voice,
I wasn't by her side.
I felt guilty.
I feel sorry for her.
Yes.
The happiest time
is that she comes back every year.
Because she seldom comes back.
She comes back every year to celebrate the Spring Festival.
I'm so excited every time I see her.
I want my mom to remember me.
when I was the prettiest.
I wear pretty clothes every year
But that's a spring dress
Wearing a denim jacket in winter
It's wearing
that was blue when I was young.
It's not cotton shoes below.
She's wearing single shoes.
When I saw her,
when I saw her.
Mom.
I saw it from afar.
and ran over.
She was heartbroken when she saw it.
But I want to show her
to her.
The most exciting thing is reunion.
I'm most afraid of parting with her.
She would ask my mom
where my mom would sleep tonight.
Is she on the train tonight?
I asked my mom
What does she eat?
I don't have to take ten yuan from my mom.
I asked my mom to buy more delicious food.
Later, my mom told me this.
I was so touched.
To be honest,
So sensible
I sleep with my mom every time I go back.
And my mom is still willing to kiss me.
She kisses me when she sees me.
Hugging my face and kissing.
Because we didn't spend much time together
in childhood.
So when I grow up,
I cherish every meeting.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Yu's mom.
and Xiaomei's mother.
We're from Changsha, Hunan.
She gets along with me
like friends.
Maybe it's because she's too young
So she's quite
with me.
Every weekend,
every weekend.
Watching a movie?
and play with my friends and friends.
She didn't teach me much.
She will influence me quietly
She always supports me
she always supported my idea
and gave me
and do everything she can
to provide me.
Actually,
sometimes I call her by her full name.
I think he'll never grow up.
But in his heart,
very sensible.
My first impression of my dad
he was different from other men.
He was attracted
by this mature charm.
Actually, Yu's dad was my first love.
I was with him in my twenties.
For a girl,
when I established my view of love,
my dad entered my life.
and Yu.
But
a harmonious atmosphere.
This kind of warm scene
last long.
When Yu was one year old,
my dad got sick.
When he was four,
he passed away.
Yes.
After dad left,
the atmosphere in my hometown
will be touching.
Then I brought my child
to Changsha alone.
Since Yu was a freshman,
when we were seven,
we lived in Changsha.
and study.
My child is very young.
I can't
let other kids
know he doesn't have a father.
I'm afraid...
He's just a kid.
He'll make fun of him.
or him.
Then we reached a consensus.
We won't tell others in a tacit way.
How is dad?
It's not easy for me.
I don't know how to fill in
I don't know how to fill in my father's column.
But I still write my dad's name.
My number is on my dad's column.
Because the first person he contacted
is dad.
Then I left
another number.
I'll use two numbers.
Yes.
When I realized
this love is gone,
I may think if he is here,
I would imagine
if it will be a better result.
I have many families around me.
are happy and happy.
I think
when I visit them,
I would think
if he was my dad,
if my dad was like that,
will he make me happier
and happier?
Will my mom be
be happier?
I just need someone to rely on.
instead of the shoulder.
I think like this.
Although
our family is not a normal family
is very complete.
A corner is missing.
But I think our family
is a loving family.
I think
get along so well now.
most of the credit comes from my siblings.
She was very nice to me.
and took good care of me.
as my own.
The most memorable thing is
I was at my grandmother's house.
It was already midnight.
I found that I had a fever.
Grandma can't go.
My weight...
Then I called my brother and mom.
Ten minutes.
she appeared in front of my house and knocked.
and carried me on her back.
and knock on the door of the small clinic.
Because our medical conditions
wasn't very advanced.
Basically, our county
is a small clinic.
It was already midnight.
So I had to knock one by one.
Then find the IV and give me an injection.
and accompany me.
This is the most memorable thing.
And my grandma
my grandma told me.
I used to be Mrs. Xiang.
Then I became Mummy Xiang.
I remember the first time
when I called her mom,
she was cooking for us.
She kept shouting
I was behind and patted her.
Nanny Xiang.
Can I call you mum in the future?
Of course.
I think the image of a child
a mom may wear an apron
and cook delicious food for her.
Actually, when I heard
my responsibility to her
I think this child
I must love her
and love her.
My mom told me
we need to
we need to love each other.
Mom often taught him to love sister
Be good to sister.
Yes.
Anyway, he always reminds us.
to engrave our genes.
Sister Wang Yin-cheol sleeps with me.
I'll sleep with you if you dance.
I think after my dad passed away,
after dad passed away.
There's more than one person.
My grandma
my mother,
and my brother's mom.
Although there's a corner missing,
I think this part
has made up
in other ways.
and even beyond it.
Just be yourself.
Don't feel too burdened.
Laugh if you want.
No matter how much corners of your mouth are,
just smile.
As long as you're happy.
Let your true self attract those who love you.
Wish her success
in this room
who can match you.
If you can't find him,
It's okay.
I'm here.
Because our family
So my younger brother
in life
as a man.
I am
very insecure.
But he gives me a great sense of security.
Like he asked me before,
What if
no one likes you in the house?
I said it was okay.
In the corner,
in the corner.
I hope she can find
who can hold her in her hand.
as a treasure.
Of course, if none of you
who you really want to be with,
Then go home.
We'll wait for you at home.
I'm telling you, I'm suffocating.
Let me take a rest.
Close the door.
We are like
like agents.
What is this?
A letter.
We received that message today.
Like me.
give my brother to the man I like.
Someone likes you.
So you gave me this letter.
Is there a day you like?
Today?
Yes.
Who do you think
For now,
which one do you think is better?
Who is easier to get along with?
I think...
Soup.
But he is E.
He doesn't talk.
Yes.
My roommate just guessed
he said Susu seemed to have feelings for me.
What about himself?
He...
I'm not telling you.
I still can't tell you.
Why not?
I can't say that.
Just discussing.
I'm your sister.
Why can't I tell you?
Hurry up.
Xiao Ling.
Yes.
Because he thinks Xiaoling is pretty.
And...
Very high.
But I asked him
I said you like I (introverted).
or E?
He said he likes E.
But Xiaoling is an introvert.
Yeah, Xiaoling is pure.
I think after getting along,
after getting along.
Actually, I want to know
who they like
I like a little.
Find out
who the first impression is.
I went to ask about girls.
Let's go for a walk.
Yes, ask around.
Fatty has found out anyway.
Yes, Fatty found out.
Ask about the soup and Harry.
I'll ask Su Xinxin for you.
Who's going?
Me.
Let's go together.
Let's go.
It's a long page.
I saw it.
Please read it.
Give me a freestyle.
Read it.
From today onwards,
in an anonymous way.
And send the message.
You need to complete it in one space.
Text messages are personal secrets.
No discussion.
Be serious and sincere.
I didn't know who to vote for.
The three of them
Tu Tu, Fatty, Harry,
I really want to know.
But if I have to choose,
I want to choose
to talk about.
Because I feel more relaxed.
and happier.
I was a little anxious at first.
Nervous? Maybe I'm fat.
The three of them are really handsome.
The picture looks sunny.
Harry
I saw it today.
I think
especially when he cooks.
No need to say the soup.
He's handsome at first sight.
He's handsome.
And he has great experience.
and has high education.
I think he must get the most votes.
I guess it's from Susu.
She's quite happy.
I remember
familiar language.
She usually says
if you are
See if you have the ability
to study in Tsinghua.
So you’re 1.9 meters.
Yes.
The soup impressed me.
First, he’s from Tsinghua.
Second, he’s 1.9 meters.
I can feel that
he's usually a quiet person.
But he's talking about what he loves.
and his school,
he was talking about
about his experience.
I want to know more about
I wanted to know more about him.
So I sent this message to Soup.
I guess it was soup.
Because when we were in the car,
we were listening to music together.
And
we looked through
the growth album,
he mentioned that he practiced sports.
So I think
the soup must be sent to me.
I sent it to Susu.
After all, my first impression is more interested in her.
She's kind of
a little special to me today.
When I was in the car,
she gave me her earphone.
and listen to it together.
I think it's either Xin
or Xiaoling.
Because when I talk to them today,
more.
I haven't figured it out.
I guess it can't be Hua.
The message I sent today
to Harry.
I have a new feeling about him today.
Maybe what I said to him today
to him today.
And yesterday I thought
he's hard to communicate with.
I think it's easy to communicate today.
When we were talking a lot,
I received a message about your feelings today.
But I didn't understand it.
I only understand the last sentence.
I do have feelings for him.
Maybe Harry.
Today's message
I chose Xinxin.
After a day with me,
I did get to know more.
So I can try to know more.
What are you laughing at?
Did you see my phone?
No.
It's quiet.
I want to laugh.
You're good at
It's good.
I can't see it at all.
The screen is the best.
It's clear.
Just kidding.
The message I received today
I really can't guess
who sent this message to me.
Because I think
Susu may have some hints.
I'm quite confused.
I sent you a message
to Tu.
Because our majors
is similar.
I also think
a relaxed person.
So I think drawing may be
I want to know more about
and get to know
such a candidate.
I guess it's a map.
Because he said
I wanted to go skiing with you.
Because when we talked
in the piano,
we talked about hobbies.
Then I said,
I actually like outdoor.
I like skiing.
I only know how to use double boards.
I don't know how to play alone.
I can't do it alone.
So I think
these two are related.
So I guess it's a map.
I'm quite happy.
I sent Xiao Ling
to Xiao Ling.
I think Xiaoling
is very compatible
are very compatible.
Flower.
My reaction was Hua.
Because she told me this before.
So at that moment,
when I saw that text,
I thought it was Flower.
She must be happy.
You can't keep your mouth shut
the corners of your mouth can't be suppressed.
There are three handsome guys there.
I got one.
I think
I'm more competitive.
I voted for Fatty because
I think his emotional value today
is really full.
It makes me happy and comfortable.
I think it should be Fatty today.
sent me a love message.
He bought me a cup.
He asked me to choose the color.
I sent this message to Hua.
I feel more comfortable
with Hua.
We can go shopping
including when we're cooking.
We have great chemistry.
So I think my feelings for her
more.
I think Hua can guess
when she receives that text.
My brother
received a message.
I was so happy.
I wanted to see him.
I think he must be happy.
This is bad.
I think it might be Hua.
When we were together today,
I can feel
Hua and my brother interact more.
At the moment,
I wonder who it is.
I'm a little confused.
I don't know if it's a map
or Harry.
I'm having a headache.
I don't know who it is.
I guess Harry.
Harry
chatting with me.
I don't know.
he just made friends with me.
Making friends?
Or...
It's hard to say.
A little surprise
I thought he would receive more soup.
I think the person who texted him
is Susu.
Because Sue
The person who gave me
to me yesterday.
When I found out
when I got the message,
I was already thinking about a storm.
I was wondering who it was.
To be honest,
I really don't know
how attractive my brothers are.
I really don't understand.
Because when I saw them talking,
I think Xiaoling's eyes
is shining.
Very happy.
And my eyes
are shining.
We get along well.
I think the soup will choose her.
Because yesterday,
Truth or Dare,
Soup said
his first impression of my sister was the best.
Because I want to gossip about my brothers.
Who sent him a message
or he expressed his feelings for someone.
Okay.
Good morning.
Let's start today's topic.
I applied.
for a chat.
Actually, I wanted to ask you directly.
but I felt there were too many people.
Who did you send it to?
The one beside me.
Xin.
Pay attention to the question today.
Who sent it to you?
No.
Isn't it anonymous?
Who sent it to you?
I guess the soup
is written.
Tell me first.
But both of us are ambiguous.
He sent
if you are also interested
or sports,
I think we can try
to get to know each other.
Who else?
Yes.
Because I think
He only talked to me.
Because he doesn't talk much.
He talks a lot.
Not much to the opposite sex.
Yes, we are close.
You two seem to know each other.
for ten years.
very familiar.
I think he's your brother.
He doesn't talk much to men.
And I think...
I personally think
he sent it to me because
he only had contact with me.
Because we listened to songs in the car.
We played a game yesterday
I mean...
Who do you like?
Let's play Truth or Dare.
He said he likes you.
It's only the first day.
It's not a good impression.
I want to get in touch.
Then I asked why.
Tell me.
When you play games,
when you play games.
That's great.
You asked me why.
Of course.
I think the reason is in the car.
I was going to listen to the song.
Then I asked him
if he wanted to listen.
But you have to know
At that time,
the four of us were in another car.
But he said
he wanted to take that car.
It's not because there's no seat.
Actually there are.
There are two seats behind.
But I don't know what he's thinking.
Don't flatter yourself.
Write your diary.
Yes.
I need a notebook.
Let's go.
Let's write it down here.
You scared me.
Want something to eat?
Freshly made sandwich
Eat.
Just a little.
Because I'm too late.
Take a bite.
It's finally our first date.
I'm looking forward to it.
I think my card is right.
To be honest, I'm looking forward to it.
But a little worried
A little nervous.
Because I'm afraid we might be cold.
We might not have anything to talk about.
Get out.
Bye, baby.
Bye.
The person I love
Hello.
I waited so long for you.
A long time?
Not really.
Sorry.
It's okay.
When I saw Susu,
I was right.
Good.
You don't know
It's me.
I knew it was you.
No.
It's my card.
I know.
How did you know it was from me?
Maybe I hope it's from you.
I was the first one to give it to you.
You guessed it was me.
I knew I invited you.
Is that what you thought?
Of course.
I'm the hero charge.
I'm the first
Well
After everyone came to my room,
I think everyone is sitting here.
It's quite awkward.
After I finished,
I'll give it to you immediately.
You gave it to me casually.
I didn't give it to you casually.
I must have guessed it.
Is it hard to guess?
What do you mean?
Because I'm very passive.
I need to feel
the signal released by others,
I can contact others.
If I can't feel
any signal from me,
I won't have any contact with him.
Actually, the sentence you wrote...
If I wrote it,
I thought about writing that.
Like me.
Do you believe that?
Do you want to experience the winter in Beijing together?
What do you want to do
I wanted to go to Yi He Garden.
I wanted to go to the Shicha Sea
I think so.
Because there's ice
There's also one in Yi He Garden
And that car is fun
If there's a chance later,
I've never been there.
I haven't.
You haven't?
It's really fun.
And you bought candied haws there.
it won't melt.
It will freeze hard
It's really fun.
Are you an introvert?
You don't remember?
I remember you're an introvert.
I'm I (introverted) What?
No, you're ENFP. I'm a candidate.
You...
I'm not an ENFP.
You got the wrong person.
ISFP.
Yes.
He's totally different from me.
Because I remember you are
ENTJ.
I got the wrong person.
It's a flower.
No.
I only remember you.
you two came in after me.
Anyway these two
I'll remember both of us.
Let's eat.
Have you eaten?
Breakfast.
You must have eaten.
You got up early.
I ate your sandwich.
Really?
You didn't have breakfast.
No.
No one's eating, right?
I don't know.
Let me see.
I'll find something to eat.
Have you eaten?
I didn't.
Do you want it?
This should be
Harry for Susu.
Really?
Maybe Susu said no.
I'll have some.
You eat.
It's scary.
Fruity juice wine
I said I went down to look for it.
Where's my sandwich?
I told you to leave it for me.
I'm sorry.
I said I was hungry.
I'm really hungry
Let's eat now.
My sandwich
That's too much.
Is it good?
So
What filling?
Think about it.
Eggs ham
Cucumber tomatoes
These are all your favorite
I'll try it when I get back.
Okay.
Don't draw pastries
I need to learn from my roommate
how to cook
You can't cook anything.
You can't do anything.
You don't know how to cook instant noodles
I can still cook
Dumplings
Sure.
It can float.
You and I are at the same level.
You won't starve to death.
Because I've been training.
Let's go to class.
You don't have time to go out, do you?
When I was young,
I could feel that pain every day.
But when I grow up,
Actually,
I think
table tennis and piano
It's fun.
Just go out for fun
Something like that.
I don't know why.
when I was young,
when I was a kid.
I've learned a lot since I was a kid.
or ping pong.
I learned a little.
I learned a little about piano
I also learned flute
But I felt tired when I was a kid.
I wanted to play.
Maybe it's because of my parents.
because they want me
to grow up happily.
They didn't force me to say
you have to hang in there.
So I tried many things
I didn't make it to the end.
You said yesterday
you mentioned yesterday,
I said
Because I envy others
I envy others.
So you're not working
or leave?
I just graduated.
So
I didn't say clearly
which industry I want to work in.
I want to try everything.
Because I'm an undergraduate.
Design?
Yes, almost.
But it's not a simple design.
It's fashion media.
You don't know us artists, do you?
You can.
Okay.
Take this away.
You want it?
Try it.
Actually, I...
Take a spoon.
Let me help you.
Really?
Thank you.
Help those who don't cooperate well.
Really.
I'll show you how to swallow it.
Then you get choked.
You can't talk for five minutes.
Oh no.
I don't talk much.
You've become a mute.
No, I'll be embarrassed.
I remember when we were upstairs yesterday,
I saw Xiaoling playing the piano.
I asked if you could play the piano.
You said you couldn't.
But when I turned around,
you played the piano.
What does this mean?
Humblebrag.
I thought you were
to see if we are siblings.
You think too much.
No.
So you played it yesterday.
It's Jay Chou's.
A song?
Can you sing?
Not out of tune, right?
You're being modest again.
Can you play the piano?
No.
Then I started playing the piano.
Next time I won't go off-key.
I'll sing well next time.
I'm already...
I can't believe it.
Really.
You really didn't sing well.
But you said you weren't out of tune.
I'm out of tune.
As long as you sing happily.
Be happy.
I don't usually sing.
But I really like to listen to songs.
I love that song.
Maybe many people don't know
what it's called.
My Tears Smashed.
You know?
This is it.
Yes.
I love it.
This is my favorite song.
So sad.
The flowers are pretty too.
What is this?
Stars?
Are you singing?
No.
What are you singing?
You're singing Jay Chou.
You're singing "My Tears Smashed".
I'm a little hungry.
Why are you hungry?
I don't know who ate it.
Why am I hungry?
I don't know why I'm hungry.
I'm quite curious.
This joke
can be said
Oh no.
The sky has collapsed.
Every day
Every day.
Why am I hungry today?
I don't really care about it.
I just think it's funny.
It's fun.
I wanted to get closer to him.
So I kept teasing him.
What's your zodiac sign?
I'm Taurus.
Really?
I'm Virgo.
From September.
I have filters for the Earth Signs.
Good or bad?
Good filter.
Really.
It's kind of scary when you're not talking.
Do you know
is Taurus and which constellation matches the best?
Virgo.
Perfect match.
Go and search.
What a coincidence.
You do look like an elephant.
You talk too little.
Because I'm afraid of saying something wrong.
I'm afraid I might say something wrong.
But my mouth is fast.
So my mom always says
my mouth is flying in front.
Your brain is behind you.
I can't catch up.
I haven't decided yet.
I'll say it out.
That's good.
Be happy.
Next time I'll change my phone wallpaper
Think twice before you act.
Say less and do more.
You scared me.
What?
A bug.
Kitten.
What is this?
Samhwa?
Yes.
Flower.
That cat was pretty yesterday.
You didn't feed it.
I think someone has fed it.
I won't go.
I'm afraid it'll suffocate.
Then it said, "Go home."
The owner said
Why did you gain two kilograms?
Tu and I fed it two sausages.
It jumped up.
It's rubbing you.
I want to take a photo for you.
See if you can run.
Three.
You don't have to look at me.
I'm happy
in Cupid's date.
Because I think
we know each other's growth experience better.
I think we can get along.
Maybe we are interested in the same thing.
I think we can
we can continue with the soup.
more about soup.
Let's go.
Bye, Xiao Hua.
Give me your bag.
I'll hold it for you.
Don't hurt yourself.
You'll hurt yourself.
It's too high.
If you want to touch the map,
He's optimistic and cheerful.
He has something in common with me.
Cupid's invitation card.
I filled in Harry.
I hope so.
A map.
Have a seat.
I want to laugh.
At first, I thought it might be a map.
but I found it was Harry.
Okay.
I already ordered.
Wait a moment.
What did you order?
You don't eat fish, right?
I eat fish.
You eat fish?
Who doesn't eat fish?
Susu doesn't eat fish.
I don't eat sheep.
I don't eat fish.
I don't eat blood.
I don't eat pig brain.
Pig brain.
I said I should avoid the fish.
I didn't order fish.
It's okay.
You're wearing it.
contact lenses?
I wear contact lenses every day.
I can wear contact lenses,
but it's too soft.
So sometimes I can't wear it.
I can teach you.
I'll wear contact lenses.
Three.
Wearing contact lenses doesn't make my eyes look bigger.
I don't have big eyes.
You're thoughtful.
Of course.
What? Men also have the right to love beauty.
How about we talk about that?
Well...
Let's talk about INFJ, right?
InFJ, you old man.
Why did you say that?
Because the MBTI image
Well
One has beard.
Like he took a magic stick.
Like Mason.
Yes.
Aren't you an introvert too?
I am.
What's your MBTI image?
I'm a little butterfly.
Little Butterfly.
I'm an INFP.
You're a butterfly. What does that mean?
sensitive and fragile.
This is...
a general concept
a little bit.
I heard about you from your roommate.
Aren't you very consuming?
I'm not in that state anymore.
Are you still a little butterfly?
Yes.
Why?
You're not a little butterfly
you won't be a little butterfly.
I'm a powerful little butterfly.
But I'm still a little butterfly.
In fact,
has also changed.
After taking off a layer of shell,
I'm a moth now.
Didn't I turn into a butterfly?
Why did you go back?
My best friend is
INFJ.
We just get along.
To put it bluntly,
Yeah.
They all say I (introverted).
I know L.
Do you think
Do you know me well?
I don't think
the minefield of me too much.
or lightning point.
At least not when it's just the two of us.
It's different when there are many people.
When there are many people,
you have to “CHUANG fly” everybody equally.
Yes.
You look like ENTP.
You don't look like I (introverted).
No. I just like joking.
Act according to the situation.
Stop if you don't look right.
No more words.
You'll be in trouble if you keep talking.
Hello.
Your special "Miss You".
Enjoy.
Thank you.
I prepared this especially for this date.
I thought we could
have a chat while drinking.
Choose one.
This one.
It's my favorite.
Peach-flavored fruit cube.
It smells like fruit.
How did you make it?
This is mixed with white grape-flavored fruit.
This is my favorite
peach flavor.
Cheers.
It tastes good.
Let's try your new wine list next time.
Eat.
Thank you.
What is this
This is vegetable soup
Try it.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Make yourself at home.
You're too polite.
Are you going back to your room?
Not really.
We need to find something to do.
Isn't there a badminton?
I want to buy a net.
I don't know where to buy it.
Sure, I want to play badminton too.
But I didn't see the net.
Right?
You usually
when you don't have class.
When I don't have class at school,
when I don't have class.
There's nothing in your university
Yes, you major in acting.
I haven't said it yet.
You already guessed it.
It's in the album.
Yes, the one I performed
there's "Xiaoling's mom".
Didn't someone raise the sign for you?
Or what?
No.
I didn't come with you
to say hello to you.
Why?
Your photo...
Hua and I were imitating you yesterday.
This photo
when I first learned how to pretend.
I remember.
That's...
My friend took it for me.
How old were you?
Ten.
16.
Not too young.
About 15 or 16 years old.
Do you think
If I let you choose,
Are you optimistic
or pessimist?
I'm definitely a pessimist.
We're quite alike in this aspect.
Seriously.
But I'm not a little butterfly.
You're an old man.
I don't think it's awkward to talk to you.
Why?
It's awkward to talk to E.
It's a little awkward sometimes.
To be honest,
I feel awkward
except eating with you.
It's awkward for you to eat with another I.
There's another I (introverted).
It won't be awkward to eat with Susu.
But
E
it would be awkward.
I'm just a little flustered.
Except the three of us are E.
It's awkward.
It's just awkward between us.
It's not awkward to talk with others.
What do you mean by that?
But it's okay.
I'll give it a try.
Okay.
Which one is better?
I think both are delicious.
I'm quite good at ordering.
I ordered all these signatures. They are all delicious.
No.
It's called the recommended dishes.
Yes.
I thought about it.
It's a date
eating cakes and desserts.
I'm here to show off meat.
That's more practical than them.
That makes sense.
You want to eat meat and cake?
Of course.
That's great.
What about you?
What do you think?
Look what I'm holding.
I'm making sandwiches today.
When did you make sandwiches?
Why didn't I know?
I woke up in the morning.
You asked me if I wanted to eat it.
Then I said I wouldn't eat it.
Yes.
Who is the most familiar person in the house?
Soup.
Yes.
If the person he likes
the person he likes is there,
What would you do?
How will you help him?
I'm straightforward and rude.
I'll give them
to spend time alone.
If it were me,
how can I help him or my brother?
I think I'm trying to create opportunities.
I'll go
I'll go.
Me too.
Do you think
you should find someone
with a good personality.
For you,
to you.
Maybe
to argue with you.
The most important thing is that we can get along.
This is what I value the most.
What about you?
If we just met,
I'll choose to look good.
Because we're not close.
We're not very close.
But in the middle stage,
I think
Because personality
will take 60 percent.
I think
I think people in the same frequency
Yes.
That's more important.
The longer it takes, the more frequency it will be.
Yes, that's right.
I remember the game we played last night.
Didn't you say you had a boyfriend?
You haven't dated since college.
Or...
Yes.
I haven't met anyone I like.
We had contact.
We did, but we didn't talk.
What? You don't like it enough? To put it bluntly,
or you don't like it enough.
or
(Things don't work.) Wook out
It's not what I want
No, you're slow to warm up.
Yes, because I didn't fall in love at first sight.
I'm 100% the type of love that grows over time.
I said the same thing yesterday.
Yes.
So when I heard you say,
I said he resembles me.
Gosh.
You're done too?
Let's go.
Let's retreat.
What do you mean?
Retreat.
To be honest, I was quite happy.
At first, I thought
I met someone
someone I've only known for a couple of days.
Then we eat alone
It might be awkward.
But I think
the atmosphere is relaxing
I think the atmosphere is relaxing.
And we have a lot to talk about.
So I think it's not bad.
Through this date with Xiaoling,
we have many common hobbies.
But different things
Maybe she told me
that her little butterfly turned into a butterfly
is indeed different from what I thought.
Then I found that we can be friends more.
Every Thursday at 18:00 p.m. Members enjoy the reproduction of "Sibling Defense Diaries".
12:00 on Friday, Members enjoy the pure version of "Love and Sisters".
Creation Center and win the bonus.
Send live comments to witness the bond between family and love.
It's on the newspaper. The clients are searching "Super Drama Show". and watch more interesting content.