Her life is like an idol drama.
Yes.
Tell him before you get in.
I like you.
Then I got on the car and left.
Luckily there was no traffic jam.
Otherwise, it would be awkward.
I like you.
Your own hair.
Yes, I will.
Once you say that,
you have to wake up an hour early every day.
I'll punish you to get up one hour early.
Next.
I'll be quick. 20 minutes.
You scared me.
Praise me. Did I look good?
Say it.
It's pretty. Okay.
When I received
the "Cupid Invitation Card",
Xiaoling got rid of it quickly.
Because we didn't communicate.
But on the first day,
we didn't communicate at all.
Do you think it's the next date
or next time?
Okay.
Love and Sisters.
Let love double.
(Welcome to "Love Siblings")
"Love Sisters".
We're a loving family member group.
We're going to
the update of this episode.
We're almost done.
Okay, let's go.
You look good on camera.
Of course.
What did you learn after all?
Your head is so small. You do it.
Let me do it. Tell us.
How do you feel about our date today?
I'm very happy.
It's over.
Very happy.
We really...
We can definitely play together.
Because in the crowd,
in the crowd
who can talk to me.
Absolutely feel
I'm looking forward to the snow.
I thought you were looking forward to the next date.
You pissed me off.
Are you looking forward to the next date
or next time?
Okay.
Don't be good. What do you expect?
I think you're looking forward to the next date.
You'll be happy for your next date.
No.
Hello
Hello.
I didn't do it at first.
When I received
when I received
I pushed it too.
But I did the exclusion method.
I did.
What did he say?
That letter.
I excluded it.
I think it's probably you.
Why?
Let's get rid of Xiaoling's first.
Because we didn't communicate,
and there was nothing
But on the first day,
on the first day.
And you sit opposite me.
Yes, opposite you.
But you didn't say anything on the first day.
I think we had the most contact
I went to the supermarket yesterday.
I said I wanted to eat this.
You said you wanted to buy it.
Didn't you buy it at the supermarket?
You said you would buy whatever you wanted.
Yes.
Yes, one more question.
Do I have too many questions?
No, go ahead.
Well...
the first day
when you brought sausage here,
I guessed the location.
Do you know where I guess?
I want to guess.
Sausage.
Sichuan.
Really?
Yes, because
There's one more thing.
The drawing doesn't have an accent, you know?
Me neither.
I'm very authentic.
I'll pack it authentic.
It's your first day.
I'm fine now.
Very plastic.
Plastic when I read letters?
When I read letters,
you read it in Hunan dialect.
I'm not from Hunan.
Who told you I'm from Hunan?
You are?
I didn't tell you I'm from Hunan.
right?
You got the wrong person.
Did I tell you I'm from Hunan?
No?
I think your Mandarin is plastic.
It's Hunan.
Where are you from?
I'm close to you.
Hubei, Yongzhou.
Sichuan.
Yongzhou? Why Hubei?
Yes, Yongzhou, Hunan.
Guangdong, right?
Yes.
But I think you speak like Fujian.
I've been in Changsha for four years.
Really?
Yes.
When did you go there?
2019.
In Changsha, 2019.
2016 2017.
I was there too.
I was in 2014.
When I saw the fried pork with chili,
I thought
you were from Hunan.
you've gained a lot of popularity.
You gave me extra points in Hunan.
Yes.
Because I really like Changsha.
Do you still go to Changsha often now?
Maybe you didn't make me happy.
I think a place
makes you like me.
I think it's easy for you to have feelings for me.
When we go back,
Let's have dinner together.
We can eat more tonight.
Why can we eat more tonight
Because the chef is good at cooking, right?
It's their turn to cook tonight
Yes.
Who did the dishes today?
I washed it with soup first.
Yesterday it was Xinxin and Harry.
Maybe it's you or the drawing today.
Your folding paper is...
No.
I just wiped my hands.
You're a little nervous, right?
No.
She has many moves.
She's quite stubborn.
But she's not nervous.
She folded one after another.
She's still cute.
Let's go back for dinner.
Okay.
Save some stomach.
Harry will say we don't give him face.
He's eating so much outside.
Let's go.
Did you drive?
I drove. You can take my car.
Okay.
It's snowing.
The first snow.
So romantic.
Really.
At this time,
to see the first snow
and meet love.
It's snowing.
Really?
Let's go! Let's go!
It's snowing outside
It's really snowing
It's huge.
My camera!
Camera
Where is it? I'll take it for you.
You have it.
I gave it to you.
Really?
Yes.
You don't have it in your jacket?
When did you give it to me?
After the tea.
Do you want to take a photo?
Yes.
Let me see my camera.
I saw snow in Beijing.
I've been thinking about the first snow this year.
The snow is so romantic.
I found the camera
Okay.
I'm not looking forward to snow.
but the winter with you.
We're really...
Stand here and I'll take a photo for you.
Try it.
So pretty.
You take photos here.
Go away.
Three, two, one.
Should I light it?
No, I won't see the snow if I light it.
But the snow is very small now.
Come on. Let me help you.
Take one vertically.
Nice.
Yes.
This atmosphere is amazing.
Your phone is so good at buying.
"God of atmosphere."
When you're in a relationship,
when you're in a relationship?
or record each other?
Yes, because I
I also like to record myself.
I record everyone.
But I'm more willing to
to record many beautiful moments.
every moment.
For example,
on a notebook today.
There's a little pendant here.
It's about you too.
Like that.
It's been so many years.
It must have recorded a lot.
Of course some important moments
I'm sure they're willing to share with us.
Record.
Do you often
like filming?
I rarely take photos of myself.
But I think
I think it's more ceremonial.
Like snowing
or eat
delicious dessert,
will take photos of each other.
I think Susu did a good job.
Sometimes his partner looks ugly when taking photos.
You hope he doesn't record it.
Let me tell you.
My husband takes ugly photos of me.
One meter, right?
Yes, it's really ugly.
When we were filming
on the show,
In the end,
he made a photo album.
but it's all my ugly pictures.
But I'm so touched.
It's like you'll find that
not your beauty,
or your makeup.
but the most real moment.
When you're down,
you were so focused.
When you do something,
you'll find that the way your lover looks at you
is like this.
I couldn't help crying that day.
Then I felt
when your lover is willing to take pictures of you
your real state,
It's a different expression of love.
Yes, you've seen by your lover.
Actually, no one else has seen you.
the ugliest version of you.
Yes, but he's willing
to record you.
How do you understand love
I also had
For example,
I'm also a guy
I got along with him first.
I knew I liked him at first.
But I wasn't sure if he liked me.
Then we had a date
at a cafe.
Then I felt that I started to be certain.
I think...
I think this guy
is interested in me.
That day, we said
we were going to go home.
We'll go home separately.
Before I got in the car,
I immediately told him I like you.
Then I'll go upstairs and leave.
I didn't even answer.
I just left.
And then?
Then he texted me on WeChat.
He said, "Why are you leaving?"
I said I didn't want to hear your answer.
He said, "But I like you too."
Her life is like an idol drama.
Yes.
Luckily there's no traffic jam.
Otherwise, it would be awkward.
I like you.
The red light is ahead
Life is full of jokes
Yes.
I'm going to write my diary.
Go down and write your diary.
I'm leaving, Hua.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
I'm leaving.
Bye. Come back early.
When I saw him,
I think it's the person from yesterday.
sent it to me.
I was subconsciously happy.
After we got to know each other yesterday,
After yesterday,
I think this afternoon tea is right.
Not at all.
Hello.
Turn around.
But my left face is pretty.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Great.
Who can play the piano so well?
Who is so talented?
Actually, I think this is mutual.
If I can feel
I can also accept
I can accept it.
Do you feel it?
No.
Love can't be forced.
Because we came here
to explore something better.
I'm 100% the kind of love that grows over time.
I said the same thing yesterday.
Yes.
So when I heard you say,
I said he looks like me.
Gosh.
Do you want pumpkin juice?
Yes.
It's not good.
How much more do you want for reducing swelling?
I wasted a day to reduce swelling.
How many packets do you bring?
20 packets.
I'll buy it now.
Where's my phone?
You'll definitely...
Susu will definitely want it.
It's okay. I'll just buy two people's quantity.
I won't give it to others.
I'll mail it here. Buy 40 bags.
Enough.
Is 40 bags enough?
Yes.
20 bags.
I drink two bags every day.
I want three bags.
You drink three bags.
You have double eyelids.
Really?
No, don't be shy.
Who told you I have single eyelids?
You have single eyelids.
I have double eyelids.
Yes, I am.
It's really awkward.
I thought you had single eyelids.
I have single eyelids.
If I don't open my eyes, I have single eyelids.
I open my eyes with double eyelids.
Do you want to play badminton later?
Yes.
Go outside.
No.
No, the wind...
Out.
No, the wind is blowing this way.
I have to hit over there.
This is...
How can I play badminton?
I can't. I really can't.
You can throw that.
Let's throw the ball.
I'll play this.
Come on.
Is it far?
Can you throw it here?
Nice.
This is okay.
Do you want to play?
Take one.
Come on.
Let me show you.
You can do it.
Take it easy.
Come on, you do it.
We did a good job.
Right?
It's mainly because the pitch is good.
I threw it higher.
Okay.
Not far.
Flying disk, right?
You've gone too far.
Hurry, shoot two shots.
Let's have a shooting game.
We don't play that.
Let's start.
I'm starting to use my strength.
It's a bit far.
There's wind.
The wind is blowing over there.
A little to the left.
The bullet is right.
So accurate.
The last one to vote in the sand pit.
I'll show you
360 degrees shot.
No, three points here.
I have to run.
Let me take a photo for you.
Take a photo.
You have to raise the ball like this.
Raise it. Yes.
So stupid.
Three, two, one. Look at the camera.
You two ruined the scene.
What do you mean?
Sorry.
Three, two, one. Cheese.
Cheese.
The soup is so cool.
It's cold. Let's go.
Let's go.
You wear three dresses every day.
Bring it here
I won't get stuck and awkward anymore.
You're awkward.
Don't get stuck and awkward anymore
Do I have to smoke it myself?
This is for you. This is for you.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Praise me. Did I look good?
Say it's nice.
It's good. It's good. It's good.
Let me ask you this.
Which movie star do you want to
to have dinner with?
Why?
I want to know too.
She's here.
Jin Yeon-hee.
It's sweet.
I just like her face.
I watched
the drama "The Condor Hero".
The little dragon girl
Too many.
Choose one.
I want to see Hu recently.
Who is Hu?
Hu Xianxian.
He's funny. I think he's so cute.
He's humorous.
He has a good sense of humor.
He's relaxed.
describe the perfect day you think.
You go first.
Have some fruit.
Eat this melon. So sweet.
Eat and drink.
Nothing is rushing you.
You can
at home.
What about you?
I think a perfect day
Practice in the morning.
In the afternoon.
in the afternoon.
Do you train every day?
Five times a week.
What do you think is a perfect day?
I want to take a small bite, right?
Did I raise your voice?
I'm waiting for your answer.
I'll join later. It doesn't count.
It's your turn.
Who should I ask?
Everyone
doesn't care about money.
What do you want to do the most?
eating broadcasting.
Why did you steal my job?
What about you?
I...
I like music.
But I don’t think I’m gifted.
I'm off.
Harry.
Be the captain of the police team.
Do you have a strong will?
No.
But I like watching those cases.
detectives,
including forensic doctors.
Back then, when I was little,
I always wanted to be a forensic doctor.
Why did you quit?
Because he went to philosophy.
Yes.
Psychologist?
Susu, come here.
You don't care about money.
What do you want to do the most?
a stylist.
You draw.
Another one.
The one who broke the rules has appeared.
It's so natural.
I forgot to bring money on my date.
What will you do?
Then I'll tell my date
I didn't bring money.
Let her pay for me this time.
You can say it out loud.
I'll take care of it myself.
If you haven't finished
before the last meal,
I can only say
I won't hide it.
Then the girl blocked you.
I have no choice.
I hope she can understand me.
I'll tell her too.
I think
since she's willing to accept your date,
she must
to understand you.
I think you can
show some
You should show us.
If she stays away from you right away,
I think
she doesn't like you enough.
It won't last long.
What was your best subject in school?
Geography.
I must ask a geography.
a great question.
No, no.
What is the north city in China?
Mohe.
We played together yesterday.
What are you afraid of the most?
Why?
I'm afraid of balloons.
and firecrackers.
These things will ring.
I'm afraid of ghosts.
I'm afraid of jumping machines. I'm afraid of heights.
I thought you were going to say you were afraid that you were too handsome.
I didn't say it.
I know you didn't.
Fear of heights.
Afraid of heights?
I'm afraid the air suddenly becomes quiet.
It's kind of funny.
What's the most precious memory of your childhood?
Childish.
The most precious memory of childhood should be
the time I spent with my parents.
when I was little.
And I had grandma with me.
Childish.
Did grandma bring her up Confucius
Grandma brought her up.
The same answer as you
Really.
I'm not.
No one asked you
My parents love massages.
They went out for a massage.
They were riding a bike.
But my parents
don't know how to ride a bike.
Then he asked me to choose the back seat
to sit up there.
Then we
fall into the bushes together.
Doesn't it hurt?
It hurts. It hurts.
All that's left is anger.
It's your turn, Harry.
The most precious memory
The most impressive guess is
I wore my grandma's clothes when I was a kid.
jumping from the sofa
Step on the sleeve when jumping to the bottom
The first bone fracture
He broke my left arm.
How old were you?
I was very young. Two or three years old.
Who's back?
Someone is coming.
Hurry!
The fifth boy.
My name is Tae-seo.
I'm a model.
What game were you playing?
The awkward question.
Pick one. You can ask everyone.
Really?
It has two sides. Which side?
You can choose one of them.
I want this side.
This side.
Yes.
What do you want to do
what do you want to do the most?
I want to start a business.
I don't know. Answer me first.
You first.
What's wrong with ping-pong centre?
Table Tennis Club doesn't make money anymore.
Are you good at ping pong?
Just so so. Just a little.
Me too.
I only know a little.
Do you want to see his life album?
and you'll know.
You can show him this.
You are...
badminton player.
I can see it.
The American professional basket.
What about Hwa?
I want to open a crystal shop.
I'm most interested now.
I bought yellow crystal a while ago.
Me too.
I've recently bought it on some platform.
Harry.
I...
A pet shop.
I want to take in a stray pet.
That's the pet rescue station.
A pet rescue station?
Yes.
I'll keep taking him in.
I'm like Harry.
Really?
I have something about pets too.
I want to...
I want everything.
adopt stray cats and dogs.
and find them an adoptive family.
and visit them regularly.
I'm making clothes for them.
You can try it.
Put on your clothes
for our seven cats. Thank you.
You have seven cats.
Will you take them to take photos every year?
Yes, I haven't.
Let's go together.
I want to go.
Why are you so excited?
I guess it's a mission.
Mission?
The boy from the cottage.
Welcome new members to the cottage.
We prepared a
for boys.
Please go to the designated location.
Let's go.
Did it snow yesterday?
It rained for ten minutes.
I've never seen snow in the south.
You exposed yourself so quickly, right?
There are many in the south.
Take a guess.
Zhejiang.
Guess it yourself.
It's from Zhejiang.
Because I guessed it right,
So he said, "Come on, guess it yourself."
It must be because he guessed right.
Guess.
Zhejiang is also big.
Do you want something sweet
Yes.
But I can't eat spicy food.
I don't eat spicy food.
It doesn't make sense that you're not from Guangdong.
It doesn't make sense.
I guessed you were from Hangzhou.
I answered this question before.
Yes, he said he lives in Hangzhou.
No.
I said I don't live in Hangzhou.
You don't live in Hangzhou?
I don't live in Hangzhou.
I think you're in Shanghai.
Take a guess.
That's right.
Zhejiang people are in Shanghai.
I think his work
may be in Hangzhou.
in Hangzhou.
in the world.
Did you make your hair?
Yes, I will.
Once you say that,
you have to wake up an hour early every day.
I'll punish you to get up one hour early.
Next.
One hour. One hour is too much.
I'll be quick. 20 minutes.
A few days ago,
Yes, from the next day.
I texted yesterday and the day before yesterday.
Did you go on a date yesterday?
Yes.
Everyone went on a date yesterday.
I think
I think they have a girls' chatting party.
After we leave,
after we leave.
Do you understand?
You look familiar.
Really?
I also think he looks familiar.
He looks like Yu Shi.
May I ask if your brother
or you?
I'm curious about that.
We're all interested in it.
Which one is more interested?
Almost.
50 50
Half and half.
Which country are you from?
America.
I used to work in New York.
Work?
for a long time.
For many years?
Yes.
Three years
It's like
Almost.
In 2018,
I stayed for a year longer.
Just for ten months.
How did you train your eyes so well?
You can do special training.
We can only say that we might watch
supermodel movies
Imitate their expressions.
And their expressions.
And eyes.
Why are you so skinny?
Eat less.
I don't eat much.
Really?
Ask them. I don't eat much.
I can't see the effect these days.
Eat less for two years.
I also think we should eat less for two years.
What's the effect of two days?
I'm 126 kilograms now.
Have you noticed
I don't feel hungry every day?
We had a lot of free time the other day.
and everyone kept eating.
I can eat the best.
I always
get fat.
You'll see me eating over there.
My mouth never stops.
Do you have muscle?
Is there any effective way?
Muscle-boosting powder.
Does it work?
Muscle acid is useful.
But you have to keep working out.
I held on for three months.
to 150 kilograms.
I don't think you can increase muscle in soup.
Your sports direction can't increase muscle.
But I'm too thin.
Power is not good.
Can't you do the traditional exercise?
You should practice that.
I'll train for power transformation.
There will be special training.
But he has to do it.
What he wants to do is different
from our gym.
Yes, we are
Just...
just to look good.
Yes.
You said you wanted to eat pizza. We have all.
Let's eat.
I need to use the bathroom.
Are you the proactive type?
Fatty said he was the initiative.
If he likes girls, he'll take the initiative.
Do you think
I do look like E.
But in love,
in love.
For example,
if we like someone together,
If the girl...
I'll take the initiative.
Yes, just like you.
As long as that girl gives me a little signal,
I'll take the initiative.
You will take the initiative.
Okay.
I don't need to be 100% sure.
As long as I have a chance,
I like him too, so I take the initiative.
He is proactive.
If I were a girl, I wouldn't take the initiative.
If I were a boy,
I would be like this.
I think
it would be better for girls.
That's why I chose this.
I agree.
Although I'm usually passive,
But if the girl gives the signal,
I will take the initiative.
If you don't have any thoughts,
I'll still be passive.
Yes.
You can try to hint.
If you really like someone,
or like someone,
look at her and talk to her.
You can try it.
In this environment,
in this environment.
Yes.
Is breakfast a hint?
Breakfast must be a hint.
Tata and Terri's joining
also makes our "catfish Effect"
is happening.
As for the details,
See you next week.
Love Siblings.
Let love double
Gather!
Coming.
Here are five invitations for partners.
Finished forming.
First come first served.
It's like a love letter.
Seriously.
Did you give it to me?
Of course.
Harry gave it to Xinxin.
Why are you giving it to me?
I'm inviting you.
Tata gave Harry
Here's your invitation card.
Thank you.
Can you come over?
I gave it to her.
Every Thursday at 18:00 p.m. Members will enjoy the reproduction of "Sibling Guardian Diaries".
12:00 on Friday. Members enjoy the pure version of "Love and Sisters".
TV and enjoy high-quality audiences.
Creation Center and win the bonus.
Send live comments to witness the bond between family and love.
Go on the news and search "Super Drama Show". and watch more interesting content.
(Search "Love Siblings") It's all about Baidu Encyclopedia.
Ask Xiao Yan. Wen Xiao Yan. A new search intelligence assistant.