♪In a different universe, time flies♪
♪Strands of fragrance linger in dreams♪
♪Interrupting the course of this story♪
♪It's our initial encounter♪
♪Love is a tear-inducing spell♪
♪Yet I'm willing to linger in the story♪
♪Seeing your eyes again
amid the struggle♪
♪Becoming a lonely vigil♪
♪White clouds drifting slowly♪
♪Who's gradually becoming gaunt♪
♪Changing all of the future♪
♪Only to keep the same smile♪
=Choose One of Four=
=Episode 17=
(The Dangerous Pinxiang Meeting)
No wonder
the streets are empty.
Zhao Wumian.
Let's settle our grudges today.
Spare an arm. What do you say?
We're not in a marketplace.
You don't get to bargain with me.
It is
your life that I want.
I think
you've misunderstood me.
Wuxin Swordsplay.
(When did he become
as powerful as in the comic?)
If martial artists are poisoned
by Beisu Qingfeng Powder,
they must find true love
to remove the poison.
I meant I'd fight you
with one arm
because you were no match for me.
Wumian.
Spare him.
Tingyu.
I can't spare him.
Our masters taught us
not to go to extremes.
I bet Mr. Xu has things to say.
Please let me interrogate him.
Fine.
He's yours now.
I'll head to the Ruyi Pavilion.
Take care of this.
Wumian.
You've regained power?
Your Majesty.
Don't drink that.
You can't drink that.
How dare you barge in?
It's you again, weird young lady.
Tell me.
Why can't I drink it?
Your Majesty.
This is not a delicacy,
but a type of poison.
If you do not take the antidote
within an hour,
you might become their puppet.
Shut up.
Are you trying to slander me?
It's a tribute from the Kingdom of Bili
that prolongs life.
Your Majesty.
The Big Dipper Sect
infiltrated the Ruyi Pavilion
and grew raw materials for the poison.
The mandrake flower
is the raw material.
I have heard of it.
After refining,
the mandrake flowers can be made
into a hallucinogenic drug.
Is that true?
Your Majesty.
It's just a rumor among the folk people
without any written records.
Tang Bocheng.
As the physician of Ruyi Pavilion,
how dare you lie to His Majesty
about the mandrake flowers?
Your Majesty.
The mandrake flower
is the raw material to make Feini.
And the fresh mandrake flowers
can detoxify you.
Please have it.
Fresh mandrake flowers
have long disappeared from Beichao.
Who knows
what decoction
you're holding?
Miss Lin, please bring it here
for me to have a look.
Something's wrong with her.
Encircle them.
Your Majesty.
Let me go.
The mandrake flowers must be simmered
for two days and two nights
to remove the Tiangu Vessel.
Otherwise,
the marks on the hands
will only disappear for half a day.
Impede them
when they return
to make them believe
that they must return.
Once the medicinal conductor gets close,
we will be able to control the emperor.
Let go of me.
Let me help you.
In your dreams.
Tang Bocheng...
What are you doing?
Let go of me.
(What's going on?)
(Haven't the marks disappeared?)
Thank you.
Without you,
we couldn't have done this.
So all of this
was part of your plan?
The situation is settled.
Commander Han.
His Majesty is poisoned.
Give him the antidote
before it's too late.
Yeah.
Do it now.
Kill Lin Lusheng and Zhao Wumian.
Wait.
Bring it to me.
Bring it over.
Commander Han.
Are you alright?
Perish, you nasty emperor!
If...
If you make a move,
I will arrest you
in the name of Daoming Court.
♪Who is admiring
their own solitary elegance♪
There's no turning back if you kill him.
Do you know?
My brother.
Ten years ago,
only I survived
out of the 20 palace maids
who served the emperor.
Zhao Wumian.
Capture this rebel!
♪Scattering in the city
filled with flying ash♪
Go.
Mr. Zhao.
I knew it.
You are the Master of Poisons.
♪Gardenia petals give off a fragrance♪
The mandrake flower
is supposed to be pure white.
But once it is stained with colors,
it can't return to its original state.
♪Sunset all over the West Mountain♪
♪Who is admiring
their own solitary elegance♪
♪Strolling leisurely in the courtyard♪
♪Dust adheres to the brick walls♪
♪So stubborn, can't bear to collide♪
♪Who weaves garments
of feathers and rainbow silks♪
♪Contented with oneself
amidst the chaotic world♪
♪Who lets the lonely petals fall♪
♪Scattering in the city
filled with flying ash♪
♪The bloom of the gardenia,
oh so fleeting♪
♪Thinking of the songs
and the sighs of the parted♪