How are you doing, sunshine?
Today everything seems to
Shit, this is insane!
Have you thought of who you are erasing tonight?
Meen, his close friend.
So cruel
if I can't go back then I'm going to erase,
erase everything in this darn world.
Rain, the owner of Rainmaker. Is he here?
No, because there's no such person
There's me - Krod, the owner of Acid rain
The place looks kinda cool with this new design huh?
What would you like?
Iced americano please.
Are you new here? I don't recognise you.
Don't forget, It's not the same world anymore.
I've been working here for a while,
Our promotion today is
couples who order two of our signature drink
will get a coupon for a free drink, it's available only on valentines day
But I already ordered
And we're not a couple.
And where's rain?
Rain? Who is Rain?
Preaw, You seen Rain?
Who's Rain, and how do you know my name?
Are you playing tricks on me?
Focus
Rain, the owner of Rainmaker. Is he here?
No, because there's no such person
There's me - Krod, the owner of Acid rain
Here, have some. To cool your temper…
You're not thirsty?
Come on - I changed it to the signature drink,
to get the free coupon for valentines
You've gone too far!
Don't break that, you don't have money To buy a new one.
Let me borrow your phone, I want to know where Rain is.
I don't have a phone.
Where are you going? you have an audition later.
Haven't you learned anything?
You can't resolve anything by using your temper.
This is another world caused by your choosing
and It didn't turn out like you expected.
You still have three More nights, remember?
Let me tell you something, Q
I'm beginning to have serious doubts about you
everytime when you say you're this cupid reaper guy.
What I believe is that you're inhuman,
what the hell are you? Why did you choose me? What do you want?
why did they send you for?
If you are cupid,
where's your wings? Where's your bow?
You're just tricking me to erase people.
You tricked me into killing people.
You're a devil , everything about you is just evil.
Let go! I hate you!
Nat
You're…
Do we know each other?
Yes we do,
Well we used to know each other
I went to find Rain at the Rainmaker but now It's called Acid Rain.
The Rainmaker closed down five years ago.
So, do you know where Rain is?
When I first saw you. I felt like we've met
But I have no idea where.
Doesn't matter, we've probably met somewhere
Maybe at the Rainmaker.
Rainmaker.
I love that place.
But it went through many owners
It's now Acid rain, owned by that guy.
Doesn't quite feel the same though, does it?
And what about Rain
Rain…
he...
quit.
And do you know where he is?
What are you to Rain?
I'm his -
Friends, they're friends
Rain...
is no longer here
What do you mean?
Rain opened the place for just a year
And then he…
died.
WHAT?
You're not from around here, so you might not have heard.
He didn't like the world he was living in,
so...
chose not to live in it anymore.
WHY?
It was sad for all of us.
But it was his decision.
Why??
Your friend must really care for Rain.
Same for me.
Harder,
put your back into it.
Hey, Sunshine, I have something to -
What's the matter?
Hey Q.
What's going with men nowadays,
chasing each other around like a Bollywood movie.
Scrubb! Keep at it.
I know...
I suck,
I have nothing to offer,
but did you have to do me like this?
Why did you do this to someone I love,
I messed up.
But did I deserve this?
Rain didn't do anything
Have some soup,
It's past noon. You're not hungry?
Try it.
Corn soup, nice and warm, I added a touch of milk.
Do you remember
when I told you about loss
and how painful it is.
I promise you,
I don't want you to go through what I did.
There's no reason I would want  to hurt you.
You can believe me or not,
I didn't think that the last wish
would turn out like this.
Once a physician believed that
if we knew the location and speed of all the molecules in the universe
and apply the right calculation.
We can see into our past and future.
But now I realize that's not true.
Certainty is knowing that everything is uncertain.
Damrong may just know more than Einstein.
Who's Damrong?
I'm glad you're speaking to me.
Yeah, Damrong. The musician we met yesterday.
It's a shame that the world yesterday is not suited for him
People will never know.
we thought we knew better.
Question with everything in the sky
Assign meaning to fate
That person is so big.
To see what's around it
oaring into the sky, challenging the sun
No matter how high you go up, you will fall down.
But you saw that he didn't give up.
Humans tries to give answers reasons and logic to a universe that has no reason,
We want to able to see into the future,
But we only see ourselves,
our ego blinds us
and we are never here
in the present
Because we only see ourselves
When we realize, it's already too late
Or maybe...
we will never know
But you still have a chance
Chances that we wish we have when we've used it all
Chances that we squander
because we take it for granted.
Yes Elsa,
my battery died,
No..I'm okay.
Yes,
I haven't forgot.
Are you just going to let time go by without making use of it?
Now that he's no longer here,
life means nothing
I know,
I keep telling you to live in the now.
This is the now.
The present becomes the past and the present keeps manifesting,
You only see yourself, you think that things go on forever,
nothing is forever,
you were sad just now then the phone rang and interrupted that moment,
which might be a new opportunity
but you chose to wallow here
because you think that your grief is forever.
Can you at least tell me,
how things turned out like this?
I think you can put two and two together.
Rain killed himself before he met me.
Can you guess why?
Because Meen does not exist.
You never considered that.
I hate myself.
Don't blame yourself,
we're both just as guilty.
Why didn't I see this coming?
Happy birthday to you.
That's it.
What is this thing?
What this?
you should try it first.
I never saw it coming at all…
Thank you so much my dear, thanks for everything
It's the best birthday,
I thank that you are here on this earth as my friend.
Thank you
for giving me the chance to celebrate all your birthdays with you and so on.
You sure you don't want me to take you?
The car is here, you hang out with Sunshine.
Call me when you get home.
see you.
Bye Sunshine.
See you, Meen.
Take good care of Rain please.
You got it.
Meen loves you a lot.
Yes,
she loves me the most,
we really love each other.
I can feel that, sometimes it feels like I'm not needed.
Hey, Don't say that.
Wait, are you jealous of her?
Oh no, why would I be?
But don't you have any friends?
No
I'm fortunate to have Meen,
if I didn't Maybe I wouldn't be standing here.
Rain
What I said to Meen earlier…
What did you say?
Well...
she said take good care of you
And…
I told her I would and I really meant what I said, Okay?
Thanks.
Rain…
What now??
I get that Meen loves you a whole lot.
But apart from Meen
Can I also love you as well?
No you can't.
Why not?
We're just friends, friends can't love each other like that.
Unless we change our status.
I get it,
If Meen doesn't exist,
Rain has no one to console him to give him support after breaking up with Mek
you already got a new friend.
Hey Meen, this is…
Sunshine.
Nice to meet you, sunshine.
And Mek leaving Rain wasn't because he found someone else
but he had to make sacrifices.
We won't accept it.
I...
have someone else.
And what hurt Rain the most,
wasn't just breaking up with Mek
but what happened to Mek after…
Nice to meet you, sunshine.
I have someone else.
Behold my hand,
it's color matches yours
The color of sin,
my hand is tainted
Water, where's the water
Just a splash may make this hand anew
Be gone! be gone! Be gone!
It does not come off
The sin remains
Erase it! Erase it! Be gone with it
Don't fall weak
Hide the hand from prying eyes
But even so, it matters not
A warrior's hand like yours is familiar to  blood
It is time
Rise!
Onwards we go
Hands withheld, head high smile , be brave And onwards we go
Okay, thank you, We'll consider and someone will call you.
Thank you.
Looking forward to your guidance. I really want to work with you.
Okay, the team will be in touch.
Not bad.
Her name is Maxima, right?
For the part of Lady Macbeth, I think she could do it.
Give her a call back.
Okay, I'll take care of it for you.
And for the male role...
is this all we have, are there more? We still haven't found our Macbeth.
I want you to see another actor
- Where?
- I've told him to come
Where is he?
But I have no idea where he is.
Well it's theatre you know,
tiring work, young people these days aren't interested,
no fame in doing it, not like those Y series.
Y series...
He should come soon.
Is that him?
Yes.
You don't have to look at just his -
Speak of the devil.
Come on in Sunshine.
Are you ready?
Say hello he's a big name director,
You told me you studied theatre
So I called you in.
Director, this is Sun.
he also did theatre so perhapsthis could be a senior, junior type thing.
Well, I think our age is way far apart for that.
Hope you're well,
coming to an audition why do you look so lifeless
Maybe he forgot his soul at home.
Oh,
so...
do you know what we're looking for?
Here, try this.
You want me to read?
Well, do you need to rehearse first?
Just do a cold reading,
Go ahead.
You can do it.
Good luck.
Give him a chance.
It has been done,
It has been done
Death is more quiet than I thought
Not even…
I'm sorry
Can I start again?
yes.
It has been done
Death is more quiet than I thought
Not a sound to be heard
Not even…
Okay let's try this,
Elsa.
Yes.
The woman who came just now, Maxim Maxima?
Maxima.
Has she gone back yet? Go follow her.
call her back
Okay.
Weakling.
Weakling. I'd never thought a warrior like you can be so weak hearted
If it was me,
even if a newborn child was sleeping blissfully in the bosoms of it's mother
I would snatch it and end it's breath
If that child was to come between my destiny
Power, status, do you no longer desire such things?
Give me the dagger
It has been done,
It has been done
Death is more quiet than I thought
Not a sound to be heard
Not even a plea for mercy
Behold!
Behold, my hand
my tainted hand of sin
that cannot be ridden.
Behold my hand,
the color matches yours the shade of sin,
our hands tainted in sin.
It cannot be erased,
this sin cannot be erased.
Water, where's the water
Just a splash may make this hand anew
Be gone! be gone! Be gone!
It does not come off
The stain won't come off
Erase it, erase it Be rid of it all
Don't be weak
It won't come off
No water can rid this
All the water from the ocean will not rid it because it has been done
What I did can never be undone
No, there is hope,
tonight
if not tonight then the next, And the next
For me to undo my wrongs, I can still make it right.
And rid this mark of sin,
be gone! Be gone!
I've wronged, I've wronged the more I try
The worse it gets
I don't know what to do
Helpless, I am completely helpless.
He's very good.
Very good, even though it's a bit off script.
You okay?
Where are you going?
I don't know.
Let's go home,
I'll take you home.
Snap out of it,
I'm worried about you.
Cupid Reaper,
Can you let go?
I want to be alone.
I don't want you to be by yourself.
You're worried I'll do something?
I know what you're going through.
I'm worried about you
Really worried about you.
Remember that tonight you still have another chance…
really worried about you.
I don't want to mess up again.
Have you decided who you're going to erase tonight?
I don't want to do it anymore.
You have to go through with it.
I'm scared.
It's the only way to bring Rain back.
If tomorrow…
Shut up and just make your wish!
I wish...
that who ever is the reason for Rain not returning to me
would vanish from this universe