Let's break up
Why?
because of what?
Is it someone else?
this dull face is the guy?
Stop it!
It's who you are!
you can't love anyone
because you only love yourself!
Did you do the right thing?
You're a good guy.
Whoever doesn't see it, it's their loss.
I won't accept it!
Hey!
I am the grim reaper
I'll give you the opportunity to 'erase' any obstacle 7 times.
I want that guy 'Air' to disappear from this world!
=Episode 2: Revenge=
What are you looking at, Dad?
These tangerine branches are overgrown.
Tomorrow I'm going to climb up and trim them.
No. Dad
you can't.
What if you slipped and fell?
Oh, come on, it's just nothing
Let me exercise a little.
Or else I'm going to die of boredom.
I have only one Dad
Once I finish my exams tomorrow, I'll come back and do it myself.
You can be my assistant.
Is it your last exam, right, son?
Yes, Dad.
Criminal law.
Oh, Dad
my advisor asked me today
if I wanted to become a professor at the faculty.
Really?
That's great for you
So, what did you say?
I told him...
I'll think about it.
Why?
it's a great opportunity.
What do you need to think about?
The advisor said
if I wanted to be a professor
he would find scholarships for me to study abroad.
But I don't want to leave you, Dad.
Air
you've done a lot for me already.
Do something for your future, son.
If I go
who will stay with you?
Your health is not so good.
Even if I'm sickly
I'm still a tough old man.
I won't keel over that easily.
I want to see your success.
Let's talk about this later.
It's late, come inside.
Today, Rain told me that you dissapeared.
He was really worried.
He promised to walk me home
but I didn't want to bother him.
Our house is just right around the corner.
I walked to his café alone
so why can't make it back?
Well let him know next time, Dad.
He was quite busy.
He has a lot of customers now.
What a kind-hearted man.
What about you
not going to bed yet?
not yet.
I'm gonna read for a while.
I'll prepare breakfast for you
in case you're not awake yet.
Go read then
so you can go to bed soon.
Goodnight, Dad.
Love you.
Goodnight, son.
Remember
Air, you are the 'air'
that I breathe.
10.00 AM. 8 February 2023
Good morning, Sunshine.
I brought Nancy as you asked.
Nancy?
Thanks.
I'm was gonna bring her in the morning
but Tae-Tae told me that...
you won't be awake till late.
Tae-Tae?
The shop owner.
Tae-Tae was right
you really wake up this late every day?
Well, look how drunk I was last night.
Where did you go to get drunk??
What?
At your shop of course.
My shop?
Last night, you ordered flowers and didn't come back.
What?
Was I that drunk, or are you delirious?
I know I'm not quite like regular folks
but I'm never drunk
and my clarity is intact
Have a good day, sir.
Take care.
Hey, wait.
wait.
Good morning, Sunshine.
Would you like a cup of coffee?
Hey erm - are...
you... a real person?
I'm not real
but I do exist.
Go on, touch me.
That's my towel!
Do you want me to stand here naked until I'm dry?
I... I..
I'm not drunk...
I'm not dreaming...
It doesn't get any more real than this.
Well then...
Air
That dull face is really gone.
Really gone.
I've erased him
as you ordered, sir.
Unbelievable!
Mr. Q, I'll do anything for you.
I'll repay you for everything.
That bland guy is gone from this world
and Rain is still my boyfriend.
I'm going to see Rain.
Wait
I suggest maybe take a shower first?
You fell asleep like this last night.
I had to carry you from the balcony to this bed.
You're so heavy
and also very smelly.
Well...
then I'll shower first.
You can think about what you want to eat.
you've eaten human food before right?
I saw you drinking coffee earlier
Hey
Why are you standing there? I'm taking my pants off.
Why?
Then take them off.
If you're shy, take them off in the bathroom.
This is my room.
Why should I have to take them off in the bathroom?
Well, suit yourself.
They say...
to take off your clothes when you see a ghost
to scare them away.
Aren't you scared?
I'm not a ghost
or a demon.
I am the Cupid Reaper.
I'm not scared.
You're really not scared.
It's you who should be afraid of me
mortal.
Can you wipe it off?
Huh?
No, I can't.
Why are you following me?
Go somewhere else.
Don't you want to see how the humans live in this city?
You can't follow me around.
If someone sees you, I'll tell them who you are.
I want to go see my handy work.
No one can see me
believe me.
Good morning, Big sis, Nom.
Redecorating the lobby again?
Sunshine.
It's for Valentine's Day.
But I don't know who left their footprint on the wall.
Must be those peeps last night.
So rude!
Look!
Iit's not coming off.
Just paint over it.
Sis.
Then the room will completely lose its classic look.
Hey, Sunshine
I wanted to talk to you about something.
What is it?
Your next door neighbor and the other tenants
have been complaining all morning that you got drunk last night
and made so much noise they couldn't sleep.
Is that true?
Uh, well...
Well..
Did you hear it?
I sleep with earplugs.
Even if all hell breaks loose, I wouldn't know.
But watch it, okay?
I don't want problems with the neighbors.
Sure, sis. I'm sorry.
And who's that?
You said no one could see you.
His aura is glowing like that
how can I not see?
Uh...
he's my friend.
His name is...
Q.
Hello.
I'm Norma.
Nice to meet you. Norma.
I'll make sure to remind Sunshine not to get drunk and make a ruckus.
Thank you.
If you fancy a drink sometime
feel free to come to my room
both of you.
Thank you.
So...
I'll excuse myself now, sis Nom
I mean...
Norma.
I'm in a rush.
Have a good day.
Are you finished yet?
I can't -
Keep do it.
You said no one could see you.
I don't know.
I thought no one could see me except you.
This is news for me too.
Aren't you hot
all dressed-up like that?
Of course I am.
Where are they going?
Crossing the river to the other side.
Can we get on?
I want to try the ferry.
No. I can't swim.
Let's take a car.
You said I could ask you for anything.
Well, yeah, maybe another day.
Hey!
Have you heard the story about the tragic river?
it's a greek mythology
they compare death to crossing the river.
Some can't pay the price to cross so they spend hundreds of years waiting.
Only heroes can travel back
and forth from hell to the human realm.
You want to return to this world, don't you?
But I'm no hero.
Hey
but you're here now.
Let's go
Rain wants to know if the 'Yok lor' is ready?
Oh
that uncle is here again?
Didn't see him come in.
How are you, Uncle?
I'm fine.
I'll let Preaw make 'Yok lor' for you.
he will come out and serve you.
Okay. Thank you.
Rain is so kind.
He never makes him pay
and this Thai-style iced coffee isn't even on our menu.
Wow...
Nat, new pastries?
They look delicious. Can I try one?
No!
I set yours aside in the kitchen.
Thank you.
Please feel free.
You guys must be tired.
So many customers today!
No, It's better to have a lot of customers
you make more money
and I get paid
Here.
“Yok lor”
a special drink for a special customer.
Preaw, serve it to him.
Hey, Rain.
Hmm?
Sunshine...
You wait outside.
What do you want to drink? I'll go order.
Iced Americano.
Thank you so much.
What's this for?
Just a gift.
Oh.
Give me one hot Americano.
I thought you didn't like the coffee
It's for a friend.
Is that your new date?
He's handsome.
Come on, he's a friend
you kidding?
Sorry, I thought you had a new date for real.
Wait, how can I have a new date?
When the two of us...
Let's go talk over there.
Sun... I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I didn't have much time for you either
I've thought about it.
It's also my fault too
that I let our relationship turn out like this.
I said it's alright.
I admit that when I first met you
I was pretty broken.
So when I met you
I thought we had something in common...so I -
Hey, come on
But time proved that...
we have nothing in common.
How can we be the same in every way?
You used to say that you like the diversity in this world, right?
Yes...
but for a relationship -
Let's start over again.
Like brothers.
I promised
I'll be a good brother to you. Forever.
What brothers?
How can we be something else when we are lovers?
We are trying to understand each other and start a new, right?
Sun...
can't you let it go?
Let it go? Let go of what?
I thought you were okay about it and just came to see me.
I thought you got over it.
Oh
how? when -
Sun. Listen.
I told you last night that I still love you
but it's not the same kind of love anymore.
One day, I woke up
and I was worried about you
like an older brother worried about his younger brother
like a friend who wished the best for his friend.
It's because I really care about you
but it's not that same feeling of love I had before.
The old feeling of missing you
yearning to see your face
to be close to you
to talk about things
to live together...
I guess I've gotten used to it...
to how
you were never here for me.
Rain
who's this?
“Finally I've found you, My Valentine”
It's Earth
my new boyfriend whom I told you about last night...
Liar!
Why did you lie to me?
Wait, wait, what lie?
You said you erased Air, right?
I didn't lie.
I erased him as you said.
Then why is that guy, Earth, there instead?
You're losing your mind again.
You said...
you're the “Cupid Reaper”
who had the power to bring Rain back to me.
You fraud!
I never said I have the “power” to bring anyone back to you.
What I can do is to “erase” anyone as you command.
Whoever you think is an obstacle
whoever you think if you eliminate them
will make Rain come back to you.
There...
you just said it.
I told you to “think”
about who to choose to “erase”
so that it will make Rain come back to you.
You might have made the wrong choice
or -
Erase the wrong person?
How can that be?
That's why I told you to use logic and reason.
Do you see now? That even if you erased Air, he still has Earth.
Then just tell me who do I have to erase?!
Sun
Rain asked me to return this.
Darn it!
What the hell?
Why don't you look where you're going?
I almost hit you! Do you want to die, man?
accept my apologies young man.
Sorry my ass!
If I hit you, who's gonna be responsible?
Are you alright, Uncle?
It's fine. I wasn't careful
You don't just walk onto the road like that
Stay home where you belong old man
Have some respect!
He's an elderly! He's older than your father!
If someone talks to your father like this, how'd you feel?
Nat, Preaw, call the police!
No, please don't.
It was my fault.
I walked in front of his motorbike.
I'm really sorry.
See?
Just get the hell outta of here!
And don't let me see you again!
Are you sure you're okay?
No
it's nothing really.
Where do you live, Uncle?
He visits here every day.
I'll have someone take you home, Uncle.
It's fine.
my home just right here.
I can walk home myself.
No, please. I'm worried.
I can't lose an important customer like you, Uncle.
Oh...I caused such a mess.
I was lost in thought for a moment.
Next time...
I'll be more alert.
Thank you for your concern.
I'm so sorry.
Preaw
walk him home.
I said it's okay. Go back to work, kid.
Come on, Uncle. Don't be stubborn
I was watching him drinking his coffee
it happened all so fast.
He lives around here?
Yes
a regular customer.
I felt sorry for him.
He's all alone, no children.
Do you know
why that old man doesn't have any children to take care of him?
Because I erased his son from this world.
Do you think Rain can hear you?
Why did you follow me?
To see how long you're going to stay angry
I'm more than angry.
I'm going crazy.
So...
if you realize
then why let emotions get the better of you?
Because I'm only human.
A man with flesh and blood
unlike you, an inhuman with no heart.
Okay.
So, even without Air
Rain still won't come back.
You still have a chance to erase 6 more people
6 times
6 nights.
I'll erase -
Wait...
not now.
It's not the time.
Wait til tonight.
And also
you have time to think carefully.
Use your head...
Alright
fine
I'm tired of listening to you.
Use my head
be reasonable.
I'll see you tonight.
Hey
where're you going? let me tag along
No. We part ways.
Part ways?
We're weren't even a thing yet.
Don't mess around.
Show me around... please.
I'm not in the mood.
I didn't want you to be in that “mood” with me either.
Just go away!
Thank you so much.
It's good that we get to close early
so we can all rest.
It's been a long week.
Not really tiring.
The more customers we have, the more motivated I am.
During the pandemic, our shop was in a bad way.
Thank you so much for not leaving me.
You can believe in me.
I'm not going anywhere.
you know that?
You're more than just a coworker to me
You are like my...
Family.
Alright then
let's finish closing the shop.
I need to get going
I have an appointment
Go ahead. I got it here
Rain, you have a date, right?
Stop it.
So fresh and dapper.
See you.
take a picture, why don't you?
Clear the tables so we can go home.
It's done.
Hey
your pastries were so delicious.
Please save me some more tomorrow.
Greedy boy.
I'm giving you a compliment.
Nat
I think you could open your own café with your skills.
Or you can easily work at a famous one that pays really well
Money isn't important as a peace of mind
and that is doing what we love
and following our dreams.
True.
I have something to ask you.
What is it?
I want to pursue my own dreams too.
What?
What do you mean?
I want to be a dancer.
But you can't dance.
But I am passionate.
I can't dance well now
but if i practice
I'll get better one day, right?
So what?
You'll quit and go practice dancing?
Do you think it's a good idea?
I study and work
and it takes up all my time.
How do I find time to practice?
How about you dance while you're serving?
I've seen it in western movies.
The lead actor serves and dances at the same time
Pretty cool.
Then you also have to make coffee while dancing.
Oh
You're daring me?
I might do it
Let's go.
How about this?
Your turn.
Okay.
Enough of this.
Think about it
if you quit then who will replace you?
The shop is doing better.
Stay and help Rain.
He's always been good to us.
I think...
the reason you're not going anywhere
is because your heart...
is here with Rain, am I right?
Stop it.
Are you looking for someone?
No. I just happened to... I...
We met at the coffee shop earlier, didn't we?
Yes, that's right.
Ah, I thought
you looked familiar.
Thank you for your help.
And what brings you around here?
Who will you give the flowers to?
Nothing.
I... um... I came to visit a friend nearby
and happened to see you, Uncle.
Why don't you come in for a sip of water?
It's okay, Uncle.
I think I'll be heading back.
Heading back?
Where do you live?
I came...
from out of town.
I'm here temporarily.
And how about Bangkok?
Do you like it?
Why don't you
come in for a bit
if you don't mind my house.
Oh, of course not, Uncle.
Sometimes, it gets kind of lonely with no one to talk to.
I've taken a liking to you.
These flowers smell so good.
They're Japanese Honeysuckle.
I planted them since my wife was still here.
Now they're overgrown.
I want to trim it, but it's beyond me.
Do you need my help, maybe?
Oh, it's okay.
They're fine as they are.
The good thing about them is that they give off a fragrant scent
from dusk till dawn.
Sometimes
I sit here and reminisce
dozing off
until it's dawn
and it's time to prepare the alms for the monks.
The mosquitoes must have had their fill
Let them bite
fellow beings, sharing this world.
I don't have much to give anyone
only blood to donate to mosquitoes.
Do you go to that coffee shop every day?
The owner is so kind.
Well
I'll tell you a funny story.
When he opened the shop
I walk past the store every day.
It looked quite modern
and expensive
but there weren't many customers.
So, I decided to give it a try.
When I go inside
Oh, my, I didn't know which coffee to order
there's just so many fancy ones.
I told him I wanted a simple old Yok lor
you orderd Yok lor?
Yes.
The staff burst into laughter
but that guy, Rain, the owner
he's really nice to me.
He ordered the staff to make me that special menu.
So now
it's their “Yok lor” was a
“special menu” that only I can order.
It's so cute.
Yes.
And you...
being here... do you miss home?
I know who I will ask you to erase tonight.
If you had the power to erase anyone from this world
who would you erase?
Nonsense!
people change all the time.
Use your brain and think
When did things change
and why?
I know who I will ask you to erase tonight.
Earth?
Wrong!
That's surprising.
Will what I wish last night be the same as before?
Then who do you want me to erase tonight?
Mek.
Mek?
Who is Mek?
Rain's ex-boyfriend
before he met me.