Being your teacher
was just my temporary form.
I am going back to my own world.
And where is that?
Far beyond the moon.
Nebula M78.
Near Iscandar.
I'm sorry, but…
I will erase all your memories of me.
Goodbye.
Here he comes!
I have won the Chairman’s Award!
CHAIRMAN'S AWARD - TAZAWA TRADING
SALES DEPARTMENT
Settle down.
The International Expo
was a great success.
It was a festival of hopes and dreams.
This award is proof of it.
It's thanks to all of you in Sales!
Thank you!
I say you'll be transferred
to HQ, next term.
You're on the same track
as your older brother.
We’ll see.
No, it's basically decided.
We'll be sad once you're gone, Boss.
Don't you mean to say, "Good riddance"?
Hello.
Don't come without an appointment!
Metropolitan Police! Freeze!
We have a search warrant.
Is something wrong?
You are Yuta Yoshii, correct?
Yes.
An arrest warrant has been issued
for you, for bribery.
It's 2:08 p.m.
I'm placing you under arrest.
We're doing detox cooking today,
to be beautiful in both mind and body.
A healthy spirit comes from healthy meals.
Today, based on Zen cuisine,
we'll cook using seasonal ingredients…
I'm home!
Welcome home.
Good day.
What a refined young lady.
You must have raised her well.
No, she isn't like this normally…
IS THAT YOUR DAD ON THE NEWS?
Now, a few tips for today's Ganmodoki.
Okay.
First…
- A search warrant has been executed…
- Hey, don't turn on the TV during class.
…for bribing the Organizing Committee.
The arrest was made at Tazawa Trading,
under Tazawa Group Holdings.
A Mr. Yuta Yoshii, 51,
Manager of the First Sales Department.
To secure the adoption of company products
for the expo held last November,
Mr. Yoshii allegedly made donations
to the Organizing Committee.
Were you in cahoots?
In cahoots?
Teacher, you make it sound so bad.
We're a team.
I'm not one of you yet.
- This is a setup!
- This can also be seen as justice!
I didn't make you believe it.
It was your own greed!
Cut!
FILMING SCHEDULE - SEPTEMBER 16
What time is it?
It's 11:00 p.m.
Well, okay. I'll give it the all clear.
Okay.
Okay, that's all for today!
Thank you, everyone!
- Thank you.
- See you.
This guy can only do expressions
he thinks will look cool, right?
Director.
Yes?
A moment.
Sure.
No, that’s impossible! We can't return
to the original work's plot now…
I know, but the fan backlash
is more than expected.
We decided on it together!
That we would have an original plot.
The author gave permission.
In fact, they were happy about it, right?
In this day and age,
the fans are scarier than the author.
We must do what we can for now.
The quality will drop.
I cannot do it.
I understand.
It pains me to ask
this of you, Mr. Fujimaki.
So, you should take a break
and Assistant Director Takeuchi
will take over.
What?
Wait, am I being taken off the project?
This project was my idea! Are you joking?
To be honest, I’m not confident either.
But I have to do it.
I'll properly inherit your spirit,
Mr. Fujimaki!
I don't remember giving you my spirit!
What?
Wait, isn't this a breach of contract?
You shouted at the staff, right?
No, it's a young cast…
things needed to be kept tight.
You shouted "Hey!" loudly at Kanazawa.
That's nothing to complain about--
You called Ide an "idiot,"
Kamata and Ito "stupid" many times,
and each a "moron" and "oaf" once.
That's harassment, isn't it?
No, but…
Please wait in the back lobby.
Thank you very much.
AOBA PHARMACY
The daily login is in two hours!
Wait, this is bad.
Only 30 minutes left.
You should've said that earlier.
Let's dash home!
Begin the battle to login!
- Yes!
Let's gather once home.
Get on comms!
Run!
Put your back into it!
Be careful.
It's just a deer.
Ms. Nishino!
Hello, sir.
Not being allowed a visit
for ten days. That's inhumane.
It’s no big deal. How is the company?
I'm keeping things running in your stead.
Acting Manager…
Your wife and daughter
are also keeping calm.
Right, thank you.
I haven't said a word.
I know. I trust you.
They were all legal donations.
Manager, you were framed.
Someone sold you out behind the scenes.
Traitors are everywhere.
Our lawyer also says
the police jumped the gun.
You will not be indicted.
When can I get out?
Our entire group is pressuring the cops.
You should be released in two days.
I need to meet Mr. Kagami,
to explain things.
The police haven't made a move
against the company yet.
It's better if you don't make contact.
I’ll handle the apologies.
Don't leave the house
even after you're released. Got it?
Don't look at social media either.
Delete your accounts.
Okay.
CHILDREN UNDER 12 NOW 2400 YEN
DISCOUNT FOR GRADE SCHOOLERS
Kisuke!
Kisuke. Help me.
- That person is bullying me.
- I had her take her medicine.
Did she bite you?
Oh, it's no big deal.
Mother.
I won't be fooled.
That person is trying to kill me.
You murderer!
What happened to Saito?
You said you hated him,
so we switched him for a veteran!
Ms. Shoko, shall we go for a walk?
How about it?
No way!
Ms. Shoko!
MITAKA GUEST HOUSE
"Ruiner of original works…"
"Never make anything again."
"No respect for the source material."
You critics should mind
your damn business!
You’re destroying the industry
with your lack of knowledge.
KINPO
"To Chen.
Did you see this news?
A familiar place
made me suddenly think of you all.
I would like to see you,
after all this time."
Kinpo?
Huh?
I'm just asking this to be sure,
your arrest won't affect
my university entrance exam, right?
I already explained.
I didn't do anything wrong.
The police made a mistake.
Focus on your studies.
But if you're indicted,
over 99% of Japanese trials…
I told you I won't be indicted!
I'm off.
Have a good day.
I’ll help.
Don't worry.
Between the police and the Tazawa Group,
which do you think is more powerful?
If we keep protesting,
the police can't do anything.
I have a class today,
so can you stay outside?
I was told not to go out.
YUTA YOSHII
"He finally got found out."
"I saw him on TV,
he has a villain's face."
KINPO
"Did you see this news?
"A familiar place
made me suddenly think of you all.
I would like to see you,
after all this time."
Kinpo?
FROM KINPO
HUMAN BONES FOUND ON CONSTRUCTION SITE
TANBE CITY
Tanbe City?
Oh, welcome. This way, please.
- Let me take your jacket.
- Sure.
TANBE CITY SEPTEMBER 1988
WELCOME! TANBE CENTRAL SHOPPING DISTRICT
SHOE SHOP SENDAIYA
LADIES' SHOES SPECIAL SALE!
HALF PRICE
- Bye!
- Goodbye!
TANBE MIDDLE SCHOOL
Yuta Yoshii. I hear they
kicked you out of the baseball club?
Hey, why not join the Movie Club?
We’re starting a new Movie Research Club.
Because they crushed
our Manga Research Club.
We need four members and an advisor,
and it would be great
to have you star in our movies.
I bet girls will join too.
I’m not an otaku like you guys.
- What?
O-ta-ku. Don't you know?
They call people like you "otaku."
You're in middle school, yet you obsess
over manga, anime and movies.
Those geeky--
- Don't call us otaku! Don't stereotype us!
- You'll tear my shirt! Let go!
No way! You started it!
I told you, let go!
- Never!
- Stop this.
- Who cares!
- It hurts!
- Are you okay?
- So nice to be full of energy.
- Who is she?
- No clue.
Michiru Miyashita, filling in for Mrs.
Koda while she's on maternity leave.
Nice to meet you.
- She's just like Matilda.
- True.
Kick it back to us!
What?
Movie Research Club? Who was in it?
I had completely forgotten it myself,
but I really was in it for a while,
back in eighth grade.
Doesn't sound like you.
I thought you were all about baseball.
There was a small commotion
at a local construction site recently,
and one of my friends got nostalgic,
so he asked to meet.
I bet that was just an excuse.
They want to meet to cheer you up.
They can't just start off by saying
they saw you got arrested.
Right?
- That's nice of them.
- You should go.
It has been 36… 37 years.
What will we talk about?
I only vaguely remember their faces.
Oh, I'll get it.
He should go.
Right? It sounds fun.
Court-ordered mail!
Please sign here.
TOKYO DISTRICT COURT
INDICTMENT
I know I said and did things
that went overboard.
Maybe I was too fired up and lost my cool.
But I had an idea.
We can still fix things
from episode seven, right?
If we adjust the dialogue, we can
smoothly return to the original plot.
Oh, wait a second. In the script…
In episode seven, where was it…
Did he go home?
Yeah, thank goodness.
He probably won't accept it,
but after you took over,
the atmosphere on set improved.
It was so tense before.
He’s not a bad person,
but his thinking is old-fashioned.
So he just can't help it.
What will happen to Mr. Fujimaki?
I think it will be tough for him.
He had a period where he made good films.
Those Who Eat Soba was a masterpiece.
Oh, really?
- What if he comes back?
- Give me a break.
"I’ve taken over the family business
and now run a small barber shop.
If you like, why not come by
for a haircut sometime?"
Kinpo.
He has arrived.
Hey.
Oh, sit down.
Yes.
Well…
Sorry to make you travel
while you are recovering.
Oh, it's fine.
I also need to walk a little.
Right.
I'm not allowed to drink alcohol,
so I'll have some orange juice.
Understood.
I am very sorry for the trouble
my younger brother has caused.
It’s hard to believe,
but he’s been indicted.
Our Totsuka and Sakurai
were also taken in for questioning.
Well, I’m probably the final target.
No, such a situation must be prevented.
The briber must confess first,
so as long as my brother doesn't crack,
no trouble will reach you, sir.
I will stop it myself--
Sorry for the wait.
Thank you.
Can we win?
This indictment is unjust.
I will definitely win.
Okay.
Must be hard for you too.
Just when things were looking up…
It might affect your wife's work too.
Oh, and I hear your daughter
is about to enter university?
You must be so anxious.
I, Rokuro Kagami, will do all I can.
You are too kind.
Want to go play pachinko?
I'm feeling lucky!
I'll definitely win.
Watch it, old man.
You lowlifes.
- Hey, hold it there.
- What did you say?
What did you just call us, old man?
Ouch…
WHY NOT COME BY FOR A HAIRCUT SOMETIME?
KIKUHARA SALON
Oh, it has been a while.
I’m Yuta Yoshii, the one you contacted.
Long time, no see.
Hello.
Welcome.
You are… Kisuke Kikuhara.
Kinpo!
I figured you would have
a bit of a belly by now.
Hajime Fujimaki. Chen.
You’re still as cool as ever, Yun.
Wow, it has been a long time.
You two haven't changed.
Who was that man earlier?
Just a customer.
He clearly looked like he was in his 60s.
No wonder he didn't look familiar.
Hey, what happened to you?
I’ve been getting injured
constantly since middle school.
You!
CLUB REGISTRATION FORM
MOVIE RESEARCH CLUB
ADVISOR: MICHIRU MIYASHITA
That’s a nice pen.
This is my original character, "Ton-chan."
Here.
Thank you.
I can't do it for long, okay?
HAJIME FUJIMAKI, CLASS 2E
KISUKE KIKUHARA,CLASS 2G
Aren't you joining?
- I…
- We don't need him.
Don't tell anyone the reason
I came to the nurses' office.
Matilda is our advisor!
Amazing.
Who is Matilda?
I prefer Fraw Bow.
You must like Sayla, right?
That's why you're still just a little boy.
Matilda is a real mature woman.
Ms. Matilda!
Ms. Matilda.
The best woman has got to be…
Crowley Hamon.
This is an announcement
from the Tanbe City Office.
- A smog alert has been issued.
- She likes Gundam too.
She said Hamon, right?
She knows all about it!
What should we do?
Don't you want to talk about Gundam?
- I do!
- So crazy!
I haven't been to Tanbe
since graduating middle school.
Me too, no reason to go.
It's the same for me.
It’s like a different town.
That park
is where the chemical factory was.
So that means… That street
used to be the shopping district!
Around that building
was Chen’s construction shop.
- Further down was my barber shop.
- Right.
Then where was my housing complex?
That apartment building?
Wait, what about our middle school?
Seems it got merged and moved a while ago.
Now, it’s a shopping mall.
They really expanded the station plaza.
With the train lines, this is now
a commuter town. The air is cleaner.
You could call it
the "New Happiness Town, Tanbe."
Hooray for redevelopment.
Oh!
Now that it has changed so much,
it doesn't feel nostalgic anymore.
Shall we go to the police station?
Police?
I want to hear what happened
to those bones they found.
Why?
I'm just curious.
Fine by me. It might serve
as material for my work.
Let's go.
In short, we aren't sure
if it's even a case,
so we have no plans for an investigation.
But they're human bones.
We don't know how old they are,
they could be from World War II or older.
They could have washed up
from a nearby cemetery.
Isn't it the police's job
to investigate that?
It is, if there was a relevant
missing person's report,
but there wasn't one.
Where were the bones found, specifically?
Sorry, we aren't allowed
to disclose that either.
In other words,
though he can't say it clearly,
if they investigate
any construction stops,
the contractors are in trouble,
and the police have more work.
No one wins.
Cases like this are often buried,
without even a report.
Right?
I can't say anything.
Thank you very much.
Let's go.
TANBE POLICE STATION
Since we're here, let's go there too.
It's outside the redevelopment area,
it might still be there.
Where is "there"?
Video Jupiter, of course.
Our clubroom.
All right.
What? No way, you mean
you haven't even seen Project A?
- It’s a Hong Kong action cinema wonder.
- The action in Kung-Fu Master is better.
Jackie versus Benny Urquidez was peak.
Watch Police Story and Armour of God too.
I can't watch stuff like that.
TV is only one hour a day at my house.
Then you aren't qualified
to join the club.
Oh, damn, someone else rented it again.
No one is at my home today.
Let's watch it there.
- Nice.
- Let's go.
Hurry up!
It's a coffee chain now.
Rental videos were all the rage back then,
now it's an endangered species.
Nothing lasts forever.
Oh, but look, that the building
is even still standing
is a miracle, right?
Sorry for the wait.
All right.
- Who ordered an Americano?
- Me.
Okay.
I ordered a cafe latte.
- Sweet bean coffee.
- Yes.
Oh?
Take your time.
Is that your real name?
"Hakuba."
Is that your first name? "White Horse"?
Yes.
Truly a Heisei kid.
All my daughters' friends
have names I can't read.
You're a local?
I commute from Tokyo to the Engineering
Department at the university here.
Look, asking personal information
for no reason…
That's a bad habit old men have. Sorry.
- I'm actually in "communication training."
- Communication training?
I have no people skills,
so I'm training by doing customer service.
Communication training?
So she wants us to talk to her!
We used to live in this town
when we were kids.
Oh, okay!
There was a huge chemical factory
in the middle of town. It's a park now.
Back then, there were photochemical
smog warnings all the time!
We used to call it
the "poison gas factory."
Then, they redeveloped the town
to move that factory away.
It was right in the middle
of the bubble era,
there was massive construction,
and our houses were evicted then too.
It has been, what, 36 years?
Everything has changed.
"Oh, I see!"
"I didn't know that."
That's how you deal
with stories you don't care about.
It makes us old guys happy
and order more coffee.
So you're childhood friends,
and you still meet like this…
That's wonderful.
We're just old men, nothing wonderful.
This shop used to be a rental video store.
The shelves were lined up like this…
not DVDs, but VHS.
- They had Betamax too.
- Right.
I see.
In middle school,
we were in the Movie Research Club.
There was a break room in the back.
Oh, is it still there?
The manager was kind enough
to let us use it as a clubroom.
That's unthinkable nowadays.
Do you want to see it?
It's a storage room now.
Yes.
No, I'm fine.
We hung out there every day,
filming all over town making a movie.
When you were in middle school,
was it on film?
Right, they were called "moving pictures."
Still silent back then.
She'll believe you!
Home video cameras
had just been released back then,
so anyone could film easily.
He was the star.
Oh, what kind of movie was it?
Actually, I don't remember.
Since we're here, why not try doing it?
Doing what?
Try acting out what kind of movie it was.
You're joking. It's too embarrassing,
doing it in public like this.
You seem pretty motivated. I'm out.
I don't remember anyway.
Come on, just do it.
Ouch, it hurts! I heard a snap.
- I'm shaking.
- Did you hear it?
Sorry, I didn't.
- It hurts.
- The movie was like that.
Oh, I see.
Was it some sort of contemporary dance?
Well, I guess so.
We made artistic works
depicting the inner world.
Maybe influenced by David Lynch.
That’s amazing. Oh, was it well received?
Was it?
Oh, wait.
I remember.
We rented the community center
for a screening.
We got quite a few viewers.
So strange. There were
a lot of people in this town.
Yes.
MOVIE SCREENING THIS WAY
All right, looks good.
You went too far.
Okay. Right there.
It's done.
Yuta.
There are a lot of people.
Even people we don't know.
They're here for the Koshien star.
- Cut it out.
- There aren't enough chairs.
I'll get some from the town hall.
- I'll help too.
- Thanks, Dad, big brother.
- Kento, let's go.
- Yes.
Can't wait.
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
Mom, Dad, don't drink here!
Is beer not allowed?
Oh, I'll give you this.
Fried chicken to share with everyone.
- Here, eat up.
- Thank you.
Mom!
Your seat is here.
Sorry, I had a guest.
Fujimaki, Yoshii,
thank you for looking after him.
I brought inari sushi!
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
Yun, your girlfriend is here.
- She isn't my girlfriend.
- Hurry up!
You came.
Well, I was also in the movie.
Hey!
Why don't I have a seat?
Do you want me to stand and watch?
Why is that idiot Hachiro here?
What?
What did you say, bastard?
- What?
- Just stand and watch, it's fine.
Shut up, old man.
It hurts! Hey, it hurts, damn it, old man!
- Don't hurt me each time I say "old man"!
- Rambo.
That man is no ordinary person.
He has definitely killed someone.
Sorry, don't stand around here!
If you're coming in, please come in.
Why are so many coming?
Come in!
Yun. Chen. They're here…
The Be-Bops.
What do they want?
Maybe see the movie?
Oh, Mr. Trendy!
Business is booming, I see.
I was going to take my girl
to Maharaja in Roppongi,
but I guess we have to see this first.
Oh, hello.
You're in the way! Move!
Oh, no, the witch is here.
Old lady Kuroe.
How annoying,
right in the middle of the road!
This is a public road, isn't it!
Oh, Ms. Kuroe.
You can watch, if you like.
As if I would watch such trash!
Everyone's brains
have rotted because of you!
This country is heading toward ruin!
Hey! What are you guys doing?
This is the worst. It's Eto.
Did you get permission from the school?
- I haven't heard anything.
- We have permission from city hall.
You have to apply with the school too!
If you cause trouble for others,
it becomes the school's responsibility!
I gave them permission.
I have informed the principal as well.
All right, let's watch. I'm excited.
Let's go.
Sounds like you had fun.
Probably thanks to our advising teacher.
She was lovely.
We called her Matilda.
Matilda?
I liked Frau Bow.
I was in the Frau Bow camp.
Man, Sayla is the only one for me.
She's for kids.
I was into Hamon even back then.
- Hamon was it for me.
- She's too mature!
Stop, we're harassing her
with Gundam talk.
I tried hard not to become
a weird Gundam old man.
Well, anyway,
I got that she was a wonderful teacher.
I wonder how she's doing?
She quit suddenly and disappeared.
Right, she was a sub,
so she was only there for a short while.
- Is something wrong?
- Yeah.
A strange memory just came back to me.
A strange memory?
I saw a UFO.
- What?
- I saw it too.
What?
Didn't the three of us see it together?
Yeah.
Ms. Matilda was pulled into the spaceship.
And flown to another world.
Wait, is this from a movie or something?
Close Encounters, E.T.
Yasuko Sawaguchi
in Princess from the Moon.
Ms. Matilda did look like
Yasuko Sawaguchi.
We even saw Michael Jackson
at the Tokyo Dome with Matilda!
- We did, someone gave us tickets.
- On the way back, we were moonwalking.
They shot an episode
of Oretachi Hyokinzoku here.
During the opening they would film locals
from where they were shooting.
- It's a bird! It's a plane!
- It's Takecha--
Never mind.
Now, we're harassing her with 80s talk.
It's interesting. Like I'm hearing stories
about another world.
Another world, is that right? 1988.
Looking back, it really is another world.
In the middle of the bubble, everyone
was hyped up and bared their desires.
Can you fight for 24 hours?
- Right?
- You got it.
Sounds like it was a good era.
I don't know if it was good,
but it really was chaotic.
The world wasn't just black and white.
It was gray. That’s exactly why
the economy developed.
Now that everything is cleaned up,
the energy is gone.
We have to be mindful of those above us,
below us, and all around us.
You have to make things
that won't offend anyone.
Kurosawa, Coppola, and Kubrick
can't be born anymore.
Same for your industry?
Few domestic companies
can manage international events.
Only we can do it.
But if you do everything by the rules,
you can't move forward.
The reason we work so desperately
isn't to line our own pockets.
It's for Japan's sake!
Ordinary people don't understand that.
People brandish simple justice,
cater to the moods of the petty,
and it's ruining this country!
Right, Kinpo?
I am just a pretty ordinary person.
- I wasn't talking about you.
- I am ordinary, compared to you two.
I’ve not achieved my dreams
or been in the public spotlight.
Never worked on national projects
for big companies.
I run a barber shop,
and I still live
with my mother, unmarried.
That’s respectable.
I'm sure you both came to see me
just to laugh at me.
That’s not it at all.
You came to feel a sense of superiority,
to comfort yourself
that at least you're not me.
- That's not it!
- It's fine.
Even so, I’m happy you came to see me.
Stop it, Kinpo.
I would never look down on you.
At least,
I, myself,
am a miserable person,
far from successful.
But…
I don't know about him.
He’s a certified winner.
Well, it's hard to say for sure, though.
What did you say?
You're looking down on us, aren't you?
Even when we first met,
you looked down on us.
You've always been like that!
I bet you're hated by more people than me.
You are correct. I'm good-for-nothing.
We're making it awkward for Ms. Hakuba.
It's wonderful, isn't it?
A reunion with childhood friends
always ends up like this.
Sorry to make you listen
to such ugly talk.
Thanks for the drink.
The sweet bean coffee was good. See you.
Thank you very much. Please come again.
That’s 1,390 yen.
Let’s go home.
Why don't we look into them a bit more?
Those bones…
Bones? I think it's enough already.
I'm curious.
If we check each construction site,
we might find something.
What will you do then?
It was fun to see you two today.
I feel refreshed after speaking my mind.
Let's leave it there.
Did Matilda look like Yasuko Sawaguchi?
Did our movie ever get finished?
We had a screening
at the community center.
I remember it clearly too.
That’s how I remember it too.
Matilda watched it with us.
It was exciting.
But…
- But what?
- Ms. Hakuba.
Let us see the break room.
Hey, Kinpo! Hey.
Certainly.
Go ahead.
There was a sign hanging here, right?
Matilda made it for us.
Yes, there was.
TANBE MIDDLE SCHOOL
MOVIE RESEARCH CLUB
- All right, ready.
- Camera test, here we go.
Ready, start!
Good work, boys. Drinks?
- We're filming!
- And, cut!
I really don't like this. It's lame!
- What do you mean?
- Calm down.
Yoshii looks cool, right? Once more.
I'm sure it will look cool
once we've tried it.
All right, one more time.
Ready, start!
A little while ago,
while cleaning the house,
I found this.
She doesn't really look like
Yasuko Sawaguchi, does she?
There was also this piece of paper.
What was this again?
HAVE YOU SEEN THIS PERSON?
MISSING
December 31, 1988.
What happened?
Even I was confused.
When I saw the news about
the human bones found in Tanbe,
for some reason I couldn't sit still,
and I felt like I had to let you know.
I feel we have
to investigate it ourselves.
Like it's our duty.
Well…
I liked my previous part-time job.
It didn't require social skills.
But it became hard to go on, so I quit.
Someone told me not to report it,
but I reported it anyway.
I’m the one who found the bones.
- What?
What are we doing?
It’s just ahead.
Yun, don't you recognize this area?
What? No.
What?
Hey, what are you doing?
- Hey!
- If we find more bones, then the police…
Don't say such crazy things.
Kinpo!
Come here, Yun.
I am on probation.
There's a swamp ahead.
I mean, a swamp used to be there.
Swamp?
Yun, did we see a UFO?
What happened to Matilda?
Memories can easily be misremembered.
Especially for delusional
eighth-grader otakus.
SCREENING CANCELLED
- Come on over, Yun!
- Yun!
What? Wait.
It's over there.
- Miss! Which do you think is better…
- Don't touch it!
Miss?
Your back.
What did we rewrite?
HATSUMODE
What have we forgotten?
Have you seen this person?
Have you seen this woman? Please!
She has been missing since New Year's Eve.
Please tell us all you know.
Remember it!
It's no use searching.
The rumor is she was killed.
They say she was sunk in the swamp.
Remember.
Remember!
You should take a good look at this town.
Everyone is being evicted, right?
Miss, what will happen to you?
You'll be here next term, right?
You'll teach us next year?
I was just a temporary hire.
I'll be gone before you know it.
Where will you go after you quit school?
Who knows?
I’m not really cut out
to be a teacher anyway,
so I'm going back to my own world.
Where is that?
Far beyond the moon.
Nebula M78.
Near Iscandar, maybe?
Don't worry. It won't be sad.
You’ll forget about me soon enough anyway.
See you. Keep our promise.
There's no doubt about it.
The bones were Matilda's.
Matilda was killed.
It's our fault.
This is how I met the three old men.
Subtitle translation by: Quang N. N.