National Radio and Television Administration.
I want you to transfer
at least half of the money to this account first thing tomorrow.
You're being too impatient.
Didn't we have an agreement?
Qin Gang's company is investing in a new project now.
Even if all the money is spent,
they won't notice anything for a while.
I don't care. I want my money.
Fine. I'll transfer it to your account tomorrow.
I hope you keep your word.
Otherwise,
you know the consequences.
Kaiyang.
Tell me what you've done.
Say something.
Speak up. Don't scare me.
Stop drinking.
Just tell me.
Let me ask you something.
Do you think I, Jiang Kaiyang,
am a good husband?
Of course you are.
In my heart,
you're the best man in the world.
Bullshit.
What a joke.
I'm not.
Not at all.
Let me tell you.
What kind of man am I?
I used to be a respectable
deputy director, right?
But now...
Just look at now.
What are all those people I know doing?
What kind of houses do they live in?
What cars do they drive?
Compared to them,
am I even a man anymore?
Kaiyang, don't you understand?
I don't need a big house or fancy car.
I just want you to be well.
Living a simple life together is better than anything.
The daily necessities are what make a real life.
You're right.
You're absolutely right.
Completely right, but...
But it's too late.
There's no turning back.
I can't escape prison now.
Listen to me, Chunli.
Before I go in, I want to do something for our family.
One last thing.
Chunli, tomorrow...
Once I get this money back tomorrow,
I'll feel at peace.
We don't need this money!
I can do hard labor. I can sell my blood.
If you get this money back,
I won't spend a penny of it.
You're being ridiculous.
The sun must be rising from the west today.
It's rare for me to make breakfast.
It's been a long time since I made you
a decent breakfast.
Lately, either you're busy or I'm busy.
I'm afraid if I don't make you breakfast now,
I'll definitely regret it later.
Listen to yourself.
As if we'll never see each other again.
There will be plenty of opportunities in the future.
Yes.
But time waits for no one.
I need to quickly catch time by its tail
to accomplish what I want to do.
Yesterday you were saying I was in a hurry.
But I think you're more anxious than anyone.
Eat quickly. It's getting cold.
Delicious.
My mom just doesn't know you well enough yet.
If she knew,
you'd be the perfect wife in her eyes.
Why aren't you eating?
What's wrong?
I feel really upset.
What's wrong? Are you feeling sick?
No.
I should have been this good to you earlier.
You've always been good to me.
It's different.
Maybe I should never have left you before.
If I had shown earlier
that I could be a good wife and mother,
perhaps your mother wouldn't have made us separate.
Maybe everything would be different now.
Why are you bringing this up now?
Nothing. I'm just
rambling.
There's some good news today.
Huaming Online has been completely shut down.
They can't operate until the investigation is complete.
I want to see
how long he can keep up his good guy act.
What's fake will always be fake.
Sooner or later, the truth will come out.
Now I've caught him by the tail,
let's see where he can run.
Here.
I feel so happy right now.
You feel happy just because I'm eating your food?
Alright, I'll give you this chance.
I'll keep eating your cooking forever.
This is a foreign medical website.
That authorization plan,
please help me communicate about it.
Hello.
Are you Dr. Huaming?
I'm a reporter from the City News.
May I ask you a few questions?
Sure, please sit here.
Okay.
Please sit down.
Thank you.
I heard you've been running
a medical website called Huaming Online.
And it has achieved some success.
But last night,
the website's server was suddenly shut down
and its IP address was suspended.
Could you tell us why?
Could you first tell me
what your version of the story is?
We heard that Huaming Online
obtained medical funds through fraudulent means.
And during your time in America,
these funds weren't fully used for patients.
Is this true?
You heard...
And fraudulent means to obtain medical funds?
If these medical funds
could help more patients,
I wish I had such ability.
Would you really do that?
Can you tell me
what your source of information is?
Well,
I can't disclose that. It's just hearsay.
By the way, I forgot to ask your name.
My surname is Chen.
Hello, Reporter Chen.
You're recording this, right?
Yes.
It's like this.
I need to be responsible for what I say.
Since you're recording, I can tell you
I take responsibility for every word I say.
The same applies to you.
As a news organization,
as the voice of the people,
what you say must also be backed by evidence, right?
Alright, regarding the medical funds,
if it has become a social issue
that prompted you to interview me,
I can disclose to the public.
I can tell you
all the uses of the medical funds,
every single transaction.
We have clear records of everything,
both the hospital and I personally.
I can match them completely
and make them public.
If during this process,
you find that I've broken any laws,
any illegal actions whatsoever,
the law will punish me accordingly.
So I think today,
since you keep saying 'I heard,'
I think this interview
should end here.
Dr. Hua, may I ask you one last question?
Go ahead.
I heard that you once caused a medical accident
that killed a professor who was a Good Samaritan.
And later, to atone for your sins,
you started dating the deceased's daughter
and even tried to marry her. Is that true?
Reporter Chen, you seem quite young.
You probably haven't been working long.
Let me tell you again,
don't rely on hearsay.
You need factual evidence, okay?
The questions you're asking now
concern my personal privacy.
I won't press the matter with you.
By the way,
if you disturb that girl
and violate her privacy,
I reserve the right to take legal action against you.
Goodbye.
Dr. Hua,
you're really keeping your cool.
There are many reporters and people outside.
How will you explain this?
I can understand the public not knowing the truth,
but reporters are just making things worse.
It must be Qin Gang.
Isn't he just suspicious about the surgical procedure
that led to his mother's death from complications?
Why don't you show them the surgical records?
Wouldn't that solve it?
Senior,
it's really difficult being a doctor nowadays.
If we had to publish and explain
every surgical plan to patients,
imagine the workload.
How could we get any work done?
Zhongxin Jikang
I remember when I was in college,
you told me something.
You said,
in the end, being a doctor
isn't about how skilled you are,
it's about having a conscience.
Zhongxin Sale
For this surgery,
I, Hua Ming, can face my conscience.
I have nothing to be ashamed of.
Since things have come to this,
if all else fails, I'll just leave.
Zhongxin Jikang
Then why did you come back?
For someone.
Wan Xinxin.
Zhongxin Jikang
True love is truly great!
So now you're willing
to explain things to Qin Gang?
Explanations must be given.
By the way,
I need your help with something.
All the accounts for Hua Ming Online,
please have the hospital finance department make them public.
Xinxin is right.
If I have to leave, I won't take the blame
or leave with a cloud over my head.
Wan Xinxin is trying so hard to keep you here.
Has she forgiven you?
I'll figure it out.
Sorry for the trouble.
I'll head out now.
Zhongxin Guikang
Excuse me, are you Miss Wan?
Yes, I am.
We're reporters from the City News.
I have a friend at an auction house in France
who saw your paintings
and admired them very much.
He asked us to interview you.
May I sit down and chat with you?
Please, have a seat.
Thank you.
I've heard about your sharp painting style, Miss Wan,
and seeing it today, your reputation is well-deserved.
I've noticed that your painting style
has undergone a transformation recently.
We know that
your father died in the hospital emergency room.
I heard the doctor's name was Hua Ming
and he and you...
I'm sorry,
but I don't want to answer this question.
Miss Wan, please don't worry.
Can we change the subject?
Recently, someone has been attacking Huaming Online,
accusing them of profiting from treating patients.
They're also questioning Huaming's
professional integrity as a medical expert,
calling him a fraud.
What's your opinion on this?
I have no authority to speak on medical matters.
But he has won numerous medical awards,
which I believe are all legitimate.
In my eyes,
Huaming is an honest, kind, and passionate person.
You think so highly of him,
so why did you give up on him?
Was it because of what happened back then?
I'm sorry, no comment.
Would you please leave?
Please leave.
Miss Wan.
Get out!
One last question - will you two ever get back together?
No. Never.
Are you satisfied now?
Why don't you try again?
Liu Wei definitely took the money and ran.
I'll go find her right now.
I'll tell the police
that she forced you to do this.
Come back.
It's useless.
I, Jiang Kaiyang, schemed so carefully,
but in the end it was all for nothing.
This is just my fate.
Kaiyang, I don't believe in fate.
Let's turn ourselves in.
The mortgage and Xiaoxiao's tuition,
I can handle it. I'll find a job.
Chunli, you should still sign the divorce papers.
No, I won't sign.
Kaiyang.
I just think you're the one for me.
I don't care about anyone else.
I don't care how many years you're sentenced to,
three years, five years, ten years, eight years,
I'll wait for you.
When you come out,
when you return to this home,
the home will still be the same,
and I'll still be your wife.
Lili.
I'm sorry. All these years,
it's all my fault.
Don't say that.
I don't want to hear any of this.
Promise me
you'll behave well in there.
Don't think about anything else.
Just think about
the day you come out,
we'll have a good life together again.
We'll still be together.
Nobody's working anymore?
Hello?
I'm from the city police department.
Your company has serious financial losses.
We've already submitted a bankruptcy application to the court.
And also,
after I'm gone,
no matter how tight money gets at home,
don't work yourself to death.
Your health is the most important thing,
especially at our age. Understand?
And in the future, no matter what,
if you encounter any difficulties,
go to Xinxin.
Discuss things with her.
That child can handle responsibilities.
Oh, right.
You must help me
explain clearly to Qin Gang
that his mother's death had nothing to do with Huaming.
He shouldn't take the blame for this.
And also,
That's enough.
No need for more instructions.
I'll take care of everything.
Don't worry.
Trust me.
I need to contribute to this family too.
By the time you get out,
I'll make this home better than it is now.
I swear to heaven. I promise.
I'm turning myself in.
I want to turn myself in.
Vivi.
Liu Wei.
Mr. Qin Gang?
Hello.
I'm from the bank. These two are from the prosecutor's office.
The situation is this:
your mortgage has expired,
and according to the mortgage agreement,
we must legally repossess your house.
I never mortgaged this house!
Here are your mortgage documents.
They were processed by your agent Liu Wei.
She did this. It has nothing to do with me.
I'm sorry, Mr. Qin,
but we must follow the regulations.
What she did has nothing to do with me.
I didn't mortgage this house.
This house is mine. This is my home.
I'm afraid from today,
this house is no longer yours.
Xinxin.
Sis.
What's wrong?
Your brother-in-law
has turned himself in to the police.
What happened?
Liu Wei.
Where is Liu Wei?
She has already resigned.
What?
She's not here anymore.
Liu Wei.
So now Liu Wei and my brother-in-law
have emptied the Qin family's assets.
Yes.
And on the day when Mr. Qin collapsed,
I really did see Liu Wei
running out of her house.
Your brother-in-law prevented me from telling anyone before,
I had no choice.
But if I don't speak up now,
my conscience will haunt me for the rest of my life.
I can't let Huaming take the blame.
Huaming, can you come over?
Liu Wei, you bastard!
How have I wronged you?
Treating me like this.
Hey, Qin Gang.
Where are you?
Xinxin.
I'm such a fool.
I'm worse than a pig.
Where are you?
I should never have listened to Liu Wei.
And I shouldn't have betrayed you because of her.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for everything I've done to you.
Only now do I understand.
Who truly loves me.
Thank you.
If there's another life.
I'll treat you well, I promise.
I'm leaving.
I'm going away now.
Hello?
Where is he?
He didn't say where he was.
But from the phone call,
he seemed emotionally unstable.
Sis, maybe I should go look for him.
What's wrong?
Something might have happened to Qin Gang.
Is Bao inside?
Wait a moment.
What are you doing?
No.
Hurry up, Xinxin.
How could this happen?
Quick, make a call
to me.
Still powered off.
Why is he acting like a child?
Xinxin.
Do you think he went there?
Let's go.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
All the money you worked so hard
to earn for me,
I've wasted it all.
I'm such a disappointment.
I'm just a good-for-nothing.
I've let you down, Mom.
I'm coming to find you now.
Qin Gang's car is here.
Qin Gang!
Don't come any closer!
Qin Gang.
Don't do anything stupid.
Come down first.
Qin Gang.
Whatever it is, let's talk about it when we get back, okay?
There's no going back.
No way back.
It's all gone.
Everything is gone.
How bad can it be, Qin Gang?
You can start over with anything.
Nothing is more important than life.
I have nothing now.
I've lost everything.
You're a man, Qin Gang.
Listen.
Your son will start talking soon.
You've lost everything, yet you have everything.
Look at your son.
Turn around and look at him.
With him, you have everything.
You're only 30 years old.
They say a man should be established by 30.
Who says you have to stand tall at 30?
If you can't stand, then crouch or lie down first.
As long as you're alive, everything else will come.
Come down first.
Qin Gang.
You can't be so irresponsible.
Your son is watching you.
When he grows up and asks me,
where his father went,
what am I supposed to say?
Qin Gang.
You're the only family I have left now.
When your son grows up,
how would I explain to him if something happened to you?
You're the only family I have now.
Look, Qin Gang.
Look at your son.
Look at your baby boy. What are you doing, Qin Gang?
You scared me to death.
How could you even think like that?
If something happened to you, how could you face your son?
Please don't scare me like that.
Huaming, you go back first.
Lie down properly.
Qin Gang,
come, drink some water.
Thank you.
I must find her.
I won't let her get away with this.
Don't scare me, Qin Gang.
You really scared us to death today.
You know, you're Xiaobao's father.
I won't allow you to have such thoughts again.
Did you hear me?
I must find her.
I won't let her get away with this.
Nothing is more important than life.
Money can always be earned again.
You can't give up on yourself.
Okay?
Where are you going, Qin Gang?
I'm going to find Liu Wei.
Where will you find Liu Wei this late?
You're staying here tonight.
Just make do for one night.
You can sleep on the couch.
Haven't you always wanted to play with your son?
Don't you miss him after not seeing him for so long?
Look at daddy.
Come, play with daddy for a while.
Look at your son, he's growing bigger and bigger.
He looks more and more like you.
His eyes and nose...
They look like they were carved from the same mold as yours.
You know?
He's already started eating solid food now.
You want to talk to daddy too, right?
Daddy, I know you're feeling terrible right now.
I know you're facing a big challenge.
But when we face difficulties, we overcome them.
There's no hurdle we can't get over, right?
You said when you grow up, you'll play with me, right?
Play soccer with me.
Right?
Isn't that right?
Dr. Hua.
Dr. Hua, we finally meet you.
You got here quickly. Here again.
You're even faster.
You not only disclosed the surgical records,
but also all of Huaming Online's
financial accounts in the US.
Because what's fake can't become real, and what's real can't be faked.
It was very simple for me to do all this.
But if it was so simple,
why weren't you willing to do it before?
Doctors have their own principles.
Was it also based on principle when you treated
the criminal before
Wan Xinxin's father?
You're Reporter Chen, right?
Yes.
Reporter Chen, I want to ask you,
as a journalist,
do you find it particularly satisfying
to constantly pick at other people's wounds?
Actually, besides the truth,
we're more interested in the development
of your relationship with Wan Xinxin.
Could you talk to us about that?
Let me be frank with you.
Why would I discuss this with you?
I've told you,
this is a matter of my personal privacy.
Would you like to see the footage
of Wan Xinxin's interview this morning?
Please leave.
Never. Never ever.
Dr. Hua! Dr. Hua!
Everything has been explained clearly.
When are you planning to leave?
I wasn't planning to leave.
You came to say goodbye to me, didn't you?
If that wasn't the case,
I'd already be on the plane.
Then I'm sorry for delaying your trip.
I thought you would ask me to stay.
Because you've already forgiven me, right?
I asked you to stay before
completely for my own sake.
I didn't want others to say I had poor judgment,
that's all.
Now that everything has been explained,
you can leave anytime.
Xinxin.
I know you. When you say this,
you're just looking for a way to save face.
That's completely unnecessary.
You're overthinking it.
Why would I need to save face?
Everything I'm saying is true.
What about what you told the reporters?
That was all true too.
I've booked the tickets.
Xinxin.
Let's leave together.
Go to a new place.
We'll only bring good memories with us.
Leave all the unpleasantness behind.
We'll definitely overcome these shadows together.
I can't move past this.
You can get through this. Trust me.
Because between us,
you, me, and baby.
We were good together, weren't we?
Give me a chance.
Give us a chance.
I'm sorry, Huaming. I can't do it.
I just can't.
Give me a chance.
Give us a chance.
I won't love again.
Spring flowers don't bloom for me.
Yet I happened to meet you
in this crowded sea of people.
I thought after all these changes,
my heart would never race again.
Yet I happened to meet you,
but I'm already gone.
Just go.
Believe in love.
Don't come looking for me anymore.
It's not that I don't want to love,
even though I've been hurt before.
Who can predict what fate has in store?
It's not that I don't want to love,
but love has become as vast as the ocean.
Perhaps I'm destined to wait a lifetime.
When he wakes up,
change his diaper.
The formula is here.
I'll be right back.
Xinxin just left.
I came to check on the baby.
Have a seat.
So you're living here now?
We're making do for now.
Qin Gang, can I ask you something?
Go ahead.
What is it?
If Liu Wei
came back now to apologize
and returned your money,
could you forgive her?
I would never forgive her.
Well,
it's just hypothetical.
What if she took your money
to make an investment,
and now that investment is profitable,
she returns triple the amount,
would you forgive her then?
Impossible.
After everything I've been through,
I finally understand
what my mother told me
all those years ago.
Money isn't important.
More or less, you can't take it with you when you die,
it's all just material possessions.
What matters is family, relatives, loved ones -
these are what truly matter.
Now, it doesn't matter if Liu Wei comes back,
or anyone else for that matter,
I will never leave Xinxin and the baby.
That's all I needed to hear.
Good.
I'm leaving next week.
I don't know when I'll be back,
or if I'll ever return.
So anyway,
my house will be empty.
It might as well be used.
You, the baby, and Xinxin
would be comfortable there.
I'd like that,
but I'm afraid Xinxin won't agree.
Li
Wang Yaping
Li Wengang
Jiang Qiaohua