National Radio and Television Administration.
I'm
planning to leave.
I don't know when I'll be back.
Or if I'll ever come back.
So it works out that
my house will be empty.
It might as well be used.
You, Bao, and Xinxin
can stay there comfortably.
I'd like to,
but I'm afraid Xinxin won't agree.
Tell Xinxin
that you bought it.
If she thinks you bought it for them, she'll agree.
I'm broke now. Where would I get the money?
Qin Gang,
we all teach our children
that lying is wrong,
but I'm a few years older than you.
I've always thought
that to make our families' lives better,
telling a few lies sometimes is no big deal.
Don't you agree?
Take it. They'll be more comfortable this way.
Sis.
No, sis.
What are you doing?
Qin Gang, I've let you down.
Do you still consider me your sister?
Of course.
Kaiyang has indeed wronged you.
Look at how much money you've lost because of him.
He's now received his due punishment.
I have no other requests.
I only ask that you forgive him.
For Xinxin's sake, please don't hold a grudge against him.
I've got a job now.
I can run a small business
and make 20,000 to 30,000 a month.
I'll bring you the money on time every month.
As long as I'm still breathing,
I will pay back
all of this money.
Sis, I can't take this money.
We're family.
There's no such thing as debt between us.
Well...
Besides,
my brother-in-law was deceived by Liu Wei.
Once Liu Wei is caught and the money recovered,
we can sort everything out.
Whoever made the mistake should bear the responsibility.
So Kaiyang was at fault?
I should be responsible for Kaiyang's mistakes?
You must take this money.
Otherwise, I won't be able to live with myself.
Sis, I can't accept this money.
Sis.
Don't give us money. I still have some.
You've just started your business.
It's not easy to make money.
That's a separate matter.
If he doesn't take this money,
I'll feel guilty for the rest of my life.
Take it.
Alright, sis.
I'll take the money
and let Xinxin manage it.
When the police catch Liu Wei
and recover the company's money, we'll talk again.
Money isn't important to me right now.
What's important is Xinxin, Xiaobao,
and all of you.
You are what matters most to me now.
Ultraman.
So cool, really.
So cool, bro.
It doesn't matter if the car looks cool or not.
As long as it drives well. Let me tell you.
I bought it secondhand from someone.
It's a used car.
But it's never given me any trouble.
Just take good care of it when it's yours.
Don't worry, I'll definitely treat it
like my first girlfriend.
Wait, are you really giving me this car?
I might not be coming back.
Look, this car of mine
is just a piece of scrap metal sitting in the garage anyway.
Just use it for now.
When I leave,
I'll clean it up a bit and give you the keys.
Wait.
No, I think...
You're giving me such a cool car.
I feel like you have something else going on.
Yes, not just the car but also that apartment.
The... the apartment too?
Oh my god, bro!
You're giving me your apartment!
You're like my second parents!
I...
Thank you so much, I really...
Buddy.
I'm sorry, I shouldn't laugh.
Buddy, let me finish what I'm saying.
I'm not giving you the car right now.
As for the apartment, I want you to
convince Wan Xinxin, Qin Gang, and Bao to
move into my apartment.
The studio is too damp now.
It's not good for their health.
I feel dirty.
I'm sorry.
Wait, you're giving the apartment to them?
What if Wan Xinxin doesn't agree?
That's why I'm asking you, since you're Wan Xinxin's best friend,
right?
Please help me convince her.
Besides,
to be quite honest,
whether I'm with Wan Xinxin or not,
I really want her to have a good life.
I'm counting on you with the apartment. Thank you so much.
And when the time comes, I'll clean up the car
and give you the keys before I leave.
I have something to do. Get yourself a taxi.
Come on, give me a ride.
Bro.
Let me experience it.
It's so cool.
I didn't bring any money.
Qin Gang
What are you doing here?
It's too stuffy in the gallery.
I brought Xiaobao out for a walk.
When I got back to the gallery and saw you weren't there,
my heart started racing.
Please don't scare me like that.
Don't worry.
I'm really enjoying life now.
I won't do anything stupid.
That's a relief.
By the way,
I was just about to tell you.
We really can't live in this gallery anymore.
Look,
those are the clothes you washed a couple days ago, right?
I checked and they're already getting moldy.
It's too damp.
I haven't been in the mood to paint lately,
and I haven't made any money.
I'll start painting right away.
Once I earn some money,
we'll rent an apartment.
Then you can live there with the baby.
Look at you, you're barely holding up.
I just have a slight cold.
It's nothing.
Let me suggest something.
How about
we move to Huaming's place for now?
He's gone anyway,
and the house is just sitting empty.
I won't go back to live there.
You have a fever.
I might just have a slight cold.
I'll take some medicine when I get back. It's really nothing.
Let's go.
No.
Let's go to the hospital right away.
Come on, let's go to the hospital.
Slow down.
Watch your hands.
Yes, this way.
Behind the fridge.
Get out of the way.
Why are you so strong?
I've been helping you all this time and I'm exhausted.
Aren't you young?
I can do this kind of work by myself.
Go do something else.
Come on, how can you say that?
I didn't bring any money during the day.
You made me come back by myself.
You're killing me with exhaustion, you know?
What are you trying to achieve here?
Going to all this trouble.
I've been talking to you all this time for nothing.
Fine. You ask me, I'll ask you too.
You're also Wan Xinxin's friend.
So what are you after if you're not taking any money?
I...
Do you have to be after something?
I understand now.
Your highest level of love is
letting go.
Another highest level is defeating your opponent.
Phone.
Here.
Where's the phone?
TV.
Television.
It's so heavy.
Weimin.
Huaming, Wan Xinxin just came in for a checkup.
Nothing serious, just a cold.
Okay, wait for me. I'll go right away.
Can you help me with this?
I'll handle it.
This...
You're not taking care of it anymore?
Your highest level of love is just hugging?
No, where did I put it?
Qin Gang.
How is Xinxin doing?
She's much better, but still has a slight fever.
What about the moving plans?
Yes, I was just about to tell you that I'm thinking
of moving in tomorrow.
That's fine. Do you need my help?
No, don't show up.
If you appear, Xinxin will be even more upset.
Look, why do you care whether Xinxin likes it or not?
Qin Gang,
just pack everything up,
move in first,
and she'll have to accept it
whether she likes it or not.
Alright,
I'll carry her over here if I have to.
Yes, this is very important.
When you go back, since Xinxin
might have a viral cold,
you need to keep her and Bao
separated from each other.
Yes, got it.
My phone is on 24 hours a day.
Call me directly if anything happens.
Okay,
let's head back now.
Sure thing.
Is there anything else?
That's all.
Don't just sit there. Let's clean up first.
Let me rest for a moment.
We need to hurry up a bit.
I don't want Xinxin to see me when she arrives.
What's the rush?
It's fine. Sit down and let me explain some things to you.
This is the utility card.
Water, electricity, and gas are all paid with this card.
I've already paid for this month.
I've linked it to my bank card.
You don't need to worry about it.
This is a spare key.
And also...
There's a notebook in here.
I've written down Xinxin's...
All of her habits are in there.
Also...
Oh right, the kitchen...
There are two cabinets in the kitchen
with three thermal cookers on the bottom shelf.
The first pot
is for your regular cooking.
And these two are for making soup.
Actually, Xinxin isn't too picky about food.
She likes drinking soup.
She prefers stronger flavors, but don't listen to her.
Don't indulge her.
Make the soup a bit lighter.
Also.
Right, the baby is still very young.
So try not to use the air conditioner.
The ventilation here is very good.
When you open the windows and doors, there's a nice cross breeze.
Alright.
I know all this already.
After all, I've lived with her before.
Yes.
And also.
These are some
basic medications I've prepared.
I've marked all the expiration dates here for you.
And
remember to check those dates carefully.
Make sure to throw away any expired medicine.
I've prepared a phone number
so I can reach you wherever I am.
Just call me if anything happens.
I don't really need this key anymore.
Keep it as a spare.
Also...
What else?
I'm leaving.
Huaming.
I miss you.
Can you come back soon?
I really can't take it anymore.
Please come back quickly.
I'm begging you.
Come.
Come in.
Qin Gang, I should go back to stay at the gallery.
No, Xinxin.
You're still sick.
Stay here and rest properly.
Let me make you something to eat.
Here.
Don't just stand there.
Sit down.
Take a rest here.
Stop fussing around.
I'll put the child to sleep.
You should rest well here.
I'll go put Xiaobao to sleep.
I'll make you something to eat.
Stop hiding.
I'm not hiding from you.
You're not?
No.
This is a snow scene painting.
It's all white. The contrast in this area...
I can't cook either.
I boiled some eggs for you to eat first.
Let me try.
What's going on?
Didn't your fever break this afternoon?
Why is it back now?
It's okay, Qin Gang.
I'll drink some water and take a nap. I'll be fine.
Wait here. I'll get you some medicine.
Huaming, Huaming.
Come over quickly. I have an emergency.
Qin Gang
You're finally here.
Xinxin has a high fever of 40 degrees.
Should we take her to the hospital for an IV?
No need for an IV if there are no complications.
What did you give her for dinner?
Eggs.
Eggs can worsen fever symptoms.
How would I know? That's what I always ate.
What should we do then?
I made some porridge.
And some stir-fried vegetables on the side.
Remember, the food should be light,
but still nutritious.
What should we do next?
Give her medicine.
If that doesn't bring down the fever, try physical cooling methods.
How do you do physical cooling?
Come on, take your medicine now.
Drink more.
I can't drink anymore.
It helps reduce fever by sweating.
I'll drink it later.
It's physical cooling.
Huaming, Xinxin's fever has gone down.
Xinxin went to the supermarket.
There are some things I don't know how to do.
Could you come up and show me?
Is this right?
You can't mix it evenly that way.
Get the air bubbles out.
Give me the eggs.
Spread it along the edge of the pan.
So it cooks evenly.
When wiping the baby, first get him ready.
Then wipe with the tissue like this.
Support him like this. You can hold him this way.
Just add one more spoon of sugar.
Put some baby powder on him.
Like this.
These clothes...
Don't wash them with adults' clothes in the machine.
Keep them sealed in plastic bags.
Thank you.
Sorry for the trouble.
She's back.
Come on, wash your hands and let's eat.
Did you make all this?
Have a seat.
Try this soup first.
Taste it.
Did you cook all these dishes?
I'm learning how to cook.
I learn from TV shows and cookbooks.
Taking it step by step.
Try it.
The taste is off.
It's too salty.
Did you make this soup?
I'm learning to cook.
I don't really know much about cooking.
Just learning little by little.
I just want to make sure you eat and drink well.
And stay happy.
So the baby will be healthy too.
This is broccoli.
This dish may look simple, stir-fried broccoli.
It seems easy,
but it's actually quite tricky to make.
If you cook it for too short a time,
it stays raw.
And if you cook it too long,
it gets mushy.
So the timing has to be
just right.
Let me try it first.
I forgot to add salt.
I'll go add some.
Here, try it again.
Now it's good.
Eat up.
Why are you still wearing an apron while eating?
It's fine. I'll be washing dishes after we eat.
No need. I'll do it later.
It's awkward eating with an apron on.
I just wanted you to rest a bit.
Let's eat.
Okay.
Why are you staring at me?
I'm not.
I just appreciate your recent changes.
I just want to take good care of you all now.
I think if I work this hard,
I should do better than Huaming.
Why compare yourself with him?
You are you, and he is he.
I'm just making a comparison.
You must have seen all the things I've done.
I hope that someday,
you can give me another chance.
I don't know when it started,
but my life seems completely disrupted.
I can't sort it out at all now.
Qin Gang.
Give me a little more time, okay?
I can wait patiently.
Just like you said,
we still have Xiaobao.
We're a family.
Go ahead and eat.
I'll go clean up the kitchen.
Have a heart-shaped apple.
What's this?
The property management now requires
all tenants living in the apartment
to register.
What should I say?
What can you say?
Just say thank you and I'll say you're welcome.
Fine. Let's say I'm renting this place.
Then give me your bank account number.
When I have money,
I'll pay back all the rent to you.
No need.
You did what you thought you should do.
Now I need to do what I think I should do.
Okay.
Qin Gang.
For me,
I've lived in that house for almost three years.
Sometimes when there are just two people in this home,
I feel like
it's just a temporary place.
But when it's just the three of us,
you feel like it's a real home.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Is it a mermaid?
The face should be toward me
and the tail toward the sea.
Don't touch my child.
I won't. I won't touch.
How did you know I was here?
The question I asked you last night,
have you thought about it?
Qin Gang, you know what?
Just now when I was standing here,
I remembered so many things from our past.
When I was at my lowest point,
I met him.
He built a small home for me,
taught me how to love.
But heaven played
a cruel joke on me.
I feel like I've aged so much lately.
Recently,
I suddenly feel like time is passing so slowly.
That day when you tried to kill yourself on the bridge,
I was really scared.
I suddenly became so afraid of losing you.
You know what?
We'll be family for life.
We'll raise our baby together.
But I don't have the capacity to love again right now.
Being together isn't about love.
It's about responsibility.
Huaming left his house to our baby.
Before he left, he was worried about how you'd be doing.
I now do laundry, cook,
clean the house, take care of our child -
all things Huaming taught me.
Sometimes when you weren't around,
those meals were actually cooked by Huaming.
When you had a fever,
he was downstairs
teaching me how to bring your temperature down.
He only left after your fever broke.
If I were to ask you now
to remarry me,
I would be truly selfish.
Huaming wasn't thinking about having you for himself.
He wanted you to be happy.
It's impossible between us now.
Nothing is impossible.
Xinxin,
I'm urging you to keep Huaming in your life.
Really,
it's over. That chapter is closed.
Come with me. Let's go find him.
You should at least say goodbye.
That's right.
Maybe it's difficult,
but for this possibility,
maybe there's another ending
that's worth fighting for.
You old fox.
I know you're doing all this
just to make me stay.
Where is the guest
who checked out already?
When did he leave?
I'm not sure about that.
Where would Hua Ming go?
Forget it, Qin Gang. Stop looking.
Xinxin.
If this time
you don't see Hua Ming,
you might regret it for the rest of your life.
Think carefully. Where might he go?
He should be under the big banyan tree.
Xinxin.
When it comes to love,
I'm not a coward.
No one can stop us from being together.
I can risk everything for you
but I can't ignore our son's future.
Being separated from my daughter for so many years,
I know very well
that a broken family
causes irreparable damage to a child.
For our son to have a complete family in the future,
I have no choice but to leave.
Xinxin.
In this bustling
please forgive me
sea of people.
I thought after all these changes in life.
I would never feel passionate again.
What kind of person are you?
Yet I happened to meet you.
But I no longer believe in love.
It's not that I don't want to love, even though I've been hurt.
Who can see through fate's arrangements?
It's not that I don't want to love,
but love has become vast as the ocean.
Forget about me.
Give me some time.
Hua Ming, forget about me.
It takes a lifetime to wait.
I thought after all the changes in life.
Stop talking. Please stop.
I still happened to meet you.
But I no longer believe in love.
It's not that I don't want to love, even after being hurt.
Who can see through the arrangements of fate?
It's not that I don't want to love.
Love has become as vast as the ocean.
Perhaps it's destiny.
Are you with me because you pity me?
Do you pity me?
Every moment I think of you.
I can't forget you because I love you.
It's not that I don't want to love.
Even after being hurt.
Perhaps it's destiny.
I once made a promise to you.
I said,
if everything could start over,
I wouldn't let her go again.
Hello, Officer Ye. What can I do for you?
The suspect Liu Wei
has been arrested.
She has now been transferred to the prosecutor's office.
Like a gentle breeze
blowing through my heart.
The little monkey and the little elephant.
How about drawing a baby and a mom?
Draw this big circle.
Scattered my gaze, taking away my longing.
Alright, go ahead.
I'll take care of this.
If fate is meeting a stranger
that familiar feeling comes in an instant.
The heart flutters and stays in this moment
as we fall in love.
I want to stay like this
cuddling close to you
forgetting about time.
If everything could start over
I would never let you go again.
Yours, mine
the line of happiness
is right beside me.
I want to stay like this
accompanying you in your world forever
forgetting about place.
If love has no boundaries
no matter each day
you're here, I'm here
in our hearts
love never changes.
Wang Yaping