National Radio and Television Administration.
As long as Xiaobao is fine,
I'm okay with anything.
Yes, that's definitely right.
Look, the situation is like this now.
In the future, this child will
be taken care of by his sister, right?
Well, it's like this.
No matter when you
or your mother want to see the child in the future,
just let us know in advance.
After you tell us in advance, we can
create time and opportunity for you.
That works.
As long as my mother can fulfill her wish,
I'll do whatever you ask. That's fine.
Sounds good now.
Come on, let's go inside.
Time to sleep.
Well then,
I'll be straightforward.
Is there anything
you two need my help with?
I actually
don't know how to tell you right now.
It's nothing.
You've already helped me so much.
If I don't do something in return,
I'd feel uncomfortable about it.
Alright, I'll just say it directly.
Go ahead.
Actually, there is something
I'd like to discuss with you.
Look, it's like this.
Recently our work unit went through restructuring.
But as a senior Party member and veteran cadre,
I needed to take the lead, right?
So I
voluntarily stepped down.
After retiring, I wanted to
travel around with my wife.
But that's impossible now,
because she has already decided
to help you take care of this child.
You see, it's become a situation where
she helps you with the child,
and I'm left at home with nothing to do.
I'm not the type who can stay idle, you know.
I've been working for most of my life, right?
But once I'm idle...
I understand.
Director Jiang, you mean you want
to work at my company, right?
Yes, that's right.
I'm afraid our company might be too small
to accommodate someone of your caliber.
Your company isn't small at all.
I've done my research.
Your automotive industry
is one of our country's
economic hotspots, right?
I really want to
learn and improve myself.
Besides,
I have work management experience, right?
I can contribute my remaining energy at your company.
Alright, I'll think about it.
I'll make arrangements at the company tomorrow.
That's great, Director Qin!
Just one request - please don't give me any special treatment.
I won't.
I can't go on.
We've made it through a day and night. Just walk a bit more.
I need more.
There's only this little left.
You drink it.
Aren't you drinking?
You have it.
Then I'll drink it.
It's gone.
What do we do now?
Give me the bottle.
No, how much further?
Look at you, wanting to take a taxi.
Neither of us has a wallet.
You don't want the taxi driver to think we're crazy.
I can't go on. I really can't walk anymore.
If you want to go, go ahead.
Wan Xinxin.
Let me be honest with you.
I actually admire you. Really.
You have incredibly strong willpower.
Look back.
Turn around. Look back.
Look over there.
Look back at the path you've walked.
The path you've traveled for a day and night.
Do you still think that's a big deal?
When we were on that log bridge,
I rushed across quickly.
I left you there.
You were scared, weren't you?
But you still made it across, crying and screaming.
What's the big deal?
After crossing it, did you still think it was difficult?
I left you alone
in that dark cave.
So dark you couldn't see your hand in front of your face.
You must have been terrified, right?
Screaming like a stuck pig, weren't you?
But you still ran out with your eyes closed.
Xinxin, honestly,
when you've gone through all
these difficulties,
look back at what you've overcome.
None of it is a big deal. You can get through it all.
Let's go.
I really can't compare to you.
You're all muscle.
I really can't match your stamina.
I'm hungry and exhausted now.
I really can't walk anymore.
Let me ask you another question.
Do you miss your baby?
I do.
Liu Chang's car is waiting ahead.
This pickup system for my training
has all the locations pre-arranged.
It's up to you whether to come or not. I'm going ahead.
Really?
Are you serious?
Hey, wait for me!
What are you trying to do?
I want to buy a couple of apples.
I'll steam them for the child when he wakes up.
I don't have time.
What are you busy with?
I need to go to work.
So you're really going to work for Qin Gang?
Don't you feel guilty taking his money?
What's wrong with that?
Xu Chunli, you have long hair but short vision.
I'm just protecting my nephew's inheritance.
Think about it.
You're leaving now?
Well...
Um... uh...
No, they're playing tricks on me again.
All night long,
where have Wan Xinxin and that guy gone?
Have we reached the top of the mountain?
How is it?
Not as scary as yesterday, right?
It's really beautiful here.
So you see,
as long as you're willing to move forward and climb up,
what awaits you ahead
might be challenges or beautiful scenery.
Yes, maybe it's difficult.
Yes, maybe it's difficult,
but for this possibility,
for a different outcome,
it's worth our effort,
worth trying, don't you think?
Old bacon,
I know you're doing all this
just to make me stay.
I'm not doing all this
to make you stay.
I just want you to know
that as long as we strive to move forward and climb upward,
what awaits us ahead
might be beautiful scenery or something wonderful.
But I'm still afraid
they'll take my precious brother away from me.
Wan Xinxin, listen carefully.
If you hold your loved one in your arms,
hold them gently and keep them in your heart,
no one can take them away.
Have you noticed this tree?
What kind of tree is this?
This is a wishing tree.
It's very powerful around here.
Many people have left their beautiful wishes on it.
This yellow ribbon
represents a beautiful wish.
I have hope again.
Back to business.
Your position has been arranged.
You can take up the role at our company
as Deputy Director of Sales.
Deputy Director.
The main thing is to let you get familiar with the business first,
and we'll make other arrangements after you're comfortable.
As for the compensation,
it will be the same as the General Manager's.
That's good.
So...
Mr. Jiang.
About my mother looking after the child...
Mr. Qin, don't worry about that.
You see...
Wan Xinxin is too busy with work,
so my wife is the one mainly taking care of the child.
Look, if your mother wants to see the child,
she can do so anytime.
Yes, but my mother doesn't know
about our divorce yet.
Don't worry. It's confidential.
But you can't keep a secret forever.
You see, my mother has high blood pressure.
I'm afraid if she gets upset,
it could trigger a serious episode.
She doesn't know
that the divorce was because of me.
No, no.
Mr. Qin, how can you say that?
This isn't your fault.
It's quite obvious.
I know Wan Xinxin quite well.
Her temperament is terrible.
Anyone who marries her would suffer.
I never expected, truly, Mr. Qin,
that your marriage with her could last this long.
What does that prove?
It proves you're generous and tolerant.
You...
Right?
Mr. Jiang, you're too good with words.
No, it's just the truth.
Well, Mr. Qin, rest assured,
leave this matter to me.
I'll definitely handle it.
I believe your mother
will trust what I say.
Good.
With your help, this will be much easier.
So, Mr. Qin, when should I start?
Anytime.
These are already printed.
I'll go prepare right away.
As soon as possible. Thanks.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Should I really stay here?
If you have doubts...
Fine. I'll take you back to the campsite.
If you can find your way out of the forest by yourself,
I'll let you leave whenever you want.
What do you mean by 'you'll let me'?
Whether I stay or go
isn't up to you to decide.
But you're right about one thing.
When facing difficulties, never look down,
because I have a double chin.
Now that's the girl I know,
the indestructible, unstoppable, unbreakable
demon queen Wan Xinxin.
What?
Sis.
Xinxin.
Sis, where's Bao?
Keep it down. He just fell asleep.
You're finally back.
You had me worried sick.
I'm sorry.
Sis.
What?
He didn't do anything to you, did he?
You've been watching too many TV dramas.
I was just worried about you.
You didn't answer your phone all night.
I couldn't sleep at all.
Okay. Thanks for your concern.
I'll go check on the baby.
Go ahead. He's in the room.
Sis, how about this?
If you're tired, you can go home first.
I can watch the child.
I've always been taking care of the child.
I have experience. Nothing will go wrong.
That's fine.
I need to go home and cook for my husband.
Then tell Xinxin about it.
Okay. Take care.
Sis, be careful on your way.
Babe.
You're having quite a good time here.
No. Why did you come back?
Why can't I come back?
Wan Xinxin is back, why can't I be?
Didn't I tell you
that your most important task right now
is to help Wan Xinxin take care of the child?
And wait until Qin Gang's mother returns.
Why are you running back here for no reason?
It's a waste of time.
I think you've lost your mind.
The child has his mother and now a nanny too.
Why shouldn't I come back?
They hired a nanny?
A male nanny, actually.
In his forties.
He's Xinxin's neighbor.
He's helped her a lot before. He's a nice person.
Xinxin went out with him yesterday.
This is going to cause trouble.
You're being such a clueless sister.
Go there quickly.
What's wrong? What happened?
What do you mean what's wrong?
A man and a single young widow
fooling around. How could that not lead to trouble?
They're both getting on in years. What could possibly happen?
Hurry up. In a few days,
Qin Gang's son will be calling him dad. You believe it or not?
Go quickly.
No, it's you.
What are you doing? Sneaking around in broad daylight.
I thought we were being robbed.
Hey, why are you coming in with a pot and yelling?
You're so jumpy.
I'm just helping you pack your things.
Wait, why are you moving my stuff here?
Didn't Xu Ke sell his house?
They need to clear out.
Yes.
My baby and I
will have to live as homeless wanderers from now on.
Someone as beautiful as me,
with public safety being so poor these days,
what if I run into someone who wants to rob and assault me?
Can you stop playing the victim?
I've raised Ruirui by myself, so I know
raising a child isn't easy.
It's not easy for you to raise your baby alone either.
So, you can stay in this home for now.
That doesn't seem appropriate.
A single man and woman living under the same roof...
What if you can't control yourself late at night?
Could you stop being so full of yourself?
I'm not staying here. I'll stay at Xu Ke's place.
You're not staying here?
Let me set some ground rules with you.
First, don't touch any of my things.
Second.
Don't touch my books.
Third.
Stay away from my books.
Mister.
I've noticed when you're being serious,
you're really charming.
Just like my dad.
Get lost.
If you were about ten years younger,
I might have fallen for you.
Can you stop fooling around and pack up?
Hello, the number you have dialed is powered off.
Is this St. Church?
I'd like to speak with Ms. Chen.
Yes, I'm her son.
What?
She's already left the hospital.
Okay, thank you.
What's wrong? Why are you so flustered?
Come with me to my place. My mom has been discharged.
She's probably on the plane right now.
If that's the case,
she'll probably arrive tomorrow.
That's so sudden.
Go to my place now
and pack up your things.
When do you plan to tell your mom?
Not yet.
Hey.
Hey there.
You know what?
Despite how you usually are
so slow and indecisive,
you're actually pretty good at packing when you put your mind to it.
Of course.
I cleaned up nicely, didn't I?
So, are you hungry?
Since we're moving into a new place,
let's get some late-night snacks to celebrate.
Yay!
Bye-bye.
They've left.
Okay, let's take a nap.
How about we try out your new bed?
Okay, let go.
So about this matter,
you must listen to me, okay?
Yes, I'll definitely listen to you.
You are...
There's absolutely no problem with that.
Sometimes you are...
you are right,
sis.
Why are you back again?
I... well...
Yes, I'm back, I...
Comrade Huaming.
Yes, I'm Huaming. This is...
This is my husband.
Hello.
You're here to see Xinxin, right?
Xinxin is upstairs, in my home.
In your home?
Why is she at your place?
She can't stay at Xu Ke's place anymore.
So Xinxin moved to my place.
Of course, I'm not living with her.
I'm just helping her look after the child.
You're taking care of the child?
This...
Yes.
Her child is too young to be left alone.
So I'm helping to watch over the child.
That doesn't seem appropriate.
This isn't right.
Comrade Huaming.
Look, we are Wan Xinxin's sister and brother-in-law.
Right.
Correct?
We're very grateful for your previous
care for Xinxin.
And for taking care of the child.
However, from today, we've decided
to take care of the child ourselves.
Yes.
Xinxin actually told me already.
She said your family conditions are quite good.
But you seem to lack time.
You don't have time to take care of the child.
No, that's...
What do you mean we don't have time?
No, the child is...
Does it make sense? Listen to me.
Even if we're busy,
we're still family after all.
Right.
How could we possibly let
strangers take care of our own family's child?
Exactly.
Right?
Yes, what I'm saying is...
The child is too young to be left alone.
So I...
Comrade Xiao Hua.
I heard that last night you went out
all night. What were you doing?
Yes, what were you doing?
We just went for an outing. Nothing special.
Well, Comrade Xiao Hua,
let me be straightforward.
Please go ahead.
Look, it's like this.
Xinxin...
She just got divorced and has a child.
She is a woman.
Yes.
She's still young.
She needs someone to rely on in the future.
Right.
Don't you agree? She needs to move forward with her life.
Looking at your age...
I...
No, no. I didn't mean anything by it.
Look at you two all the time,
coming and going like this.
If there's no outcome,
it will hold back her future.
Do you understand what I'm saying? Can you comprehend?
Right. We don't mean anything else.
We're just thinking about Xinxin's best interests.
I understand, sister, brother.
I completely understand what you're saying.
As you mentioned, I'm 40.
I'm 10 years older than Xinxin.
I'm an adult.
I know my boundaries.
I'm just helping Xinxin take care of her child,
nothing more.
Well then, you should go upstairs and check on Xinxin.
That's good.
So what you just said,
that was truly from your heart?
From my heart, absolutely.
That's good then. So we'll...
We'll head upstairs now.
We... Good.
Sixth floor.
Coming!
Sweetie!
Sis, brother-in-law, what brings you here?
Xinxin,
so you're living here now?
Yes.
Huaming let me stay here. He's really nice.
I'll introduce him when he gets back.
Your brother-in-law and I came to tell you something.
In the past, we
have done many things that wronged you.
Your brother-in-law has been feeling very guilty.
We've discussed it.
From now on, I'll take care of little Bao
so we won't have to trouble others.
No, it's fine.
Isn't it?
I understand why you're here.
Little one.
Sweetie.
Why don't you stay for dinner then?
No need to trouble you.
Hey, Xinxin.
Hey there.
My sister and brother-in-law came over for dinner
to your place.
Could you buy some extra food on your way back?
I have something urgent. I can't make it back.
There's food in the fridge. Help yourselves.
Hello?
You suddenly have something to do?
What could be so important?
Look, Xinxin
is recently divorced with a child.
She's a woman.
You two are always going back and forth like this.
If there's no outcome,
it will waste her future.
Right.
Do you understand what I'm saying? Do you get it?
[Page 2/2 Air Travel & Harmonious Journey - Strengthening Air Transport Order Management 10:56]
Finally back home.
Xinxin!
Xinxin! Mom's home!
Xinxin! Mommy's back!
And my grandson! Come down!
Mom, she's not here.
Where did she go?
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
Mom.
You must be tired from your trip.
Why don't you rest for a while?
Wait.
Xiaogang.
You've been hesitant the whole drive here.
I have a feeling...
You're hiding something.
Tell me. What is it?
Mom, I'll go prepare your bath water.
Wait.
Since you were little, whenever something happens,
you always hesitate to speak up.
I know you too well.
Don't keep me in suspense. Just tell me
what's going on.
It's nothing.
Did you have a fight with Xinxin?
No.
It's a bit more serious than that.
How serious could it be?
At worst,
you'd get divorced.
We did divorce.
You got divorced?
Yes.
Mom, your medicine is in the bag, right?
It's fine.
I'll get it myself.
Here, drink some water.
Xiaogang.
Tell me quickly what happened.
What did you do to Xinxin?
I didn't do anything. It's not my fault.
Then whose fault is it?
Wan Xinxin cheated on me.
Baby.
You're awake.
Mommy will get you something to eat.
Strange uncle.
You scared me to death.
Oh my goodness! Why is it you?
Why can't it be me?
Well, um...
The older guy didn't come.
I didn't have time before.
So I asked someone else for help.
Now I've made time.
They've already lent you the house.
How can you still have the nerve to trouble them again?
But he promised me he would come today.
Mom!
Mom, please stop.
Come with me.
Mom, we don't need to make a scene about this.
Let's go home and talk about it.
Listen carefully.
If Wan Xinxin is cheating on you,
I'll handle it for you.
But if you're lying to me,
you'll be in big trouble.
Call Wan Xinxin right now and tell her to come back to work.
You still want her back?
I will not.
Wan Xinxin.
Hello. Who would you like to speak to?
I'm looking for Wan Xinxin.
Where is she?
May I ask who's calling?
Why aren't you eating? What are you doing?
You look so distracted. Is my cooking poisonous or something?
No, it's just... that weird guy.
Why did he suddenly stop talking to me?
Hello, Mr. Shi.
You want me to come back to the company?
Okay.
Alright, I'll come back as soon as possible.
What are you doing? What's going on?
The she-devil called me.
She wants me to return to the office immediately.
She says there's something I must handle personally.
See? The company can't function without your sister.
Right.
The Earth would stop spinning without you.
Look at you being so important. Hurry up and eat.
Heaven always leaves a way out.
The universe wants me to rise from the ashes.
You're not eating anymore?
Sweetie, Daddy has to go work far away.
Daddy, please don't go.
I'll be good. Please don't leave.
I'll miss you.
Good morning.
Morning.
Xinxin.
Hello.
Why are you back?
Mr. Shi asked me to come back.
Where is Mr. Shi?
What's wrong?
What happened?
Mr. Shi, I'm back.
Wan Xinxin, you don't need to come to work today.
Mom?
No.
Mom, why are you here?
You shouldn't be calling me mom anymore, should you?
So you know everything.
Did you think you could hide something this big from me?
I wasn't trying to hide it from you.
I knew something was wrong.
Alright. Mr. Shi gave you time off.
Let's find a place to talk.
Please.
Thank you, Mr. Shi.
Goodbye.
I'm leaving.
You had an affair.
Ah.
If you hadn't cheated,
how could you have gotten divorced so quickly?
Did Qin Gang tell you that?
Since I'm sitting here today,
I know exactly what's going on.
I know my son well.
He didn't like studying in school,
and he doesn't like working as an adult.
These are his flaws.
But he also has two important virtues.
Filial piety and loyalty.
When he loves someone, he puts them on a pedestal.
He chose to marry you,
so he would never betray you.
I just want to hear one thing from you.
Auntie.
You've come all this way across the ocean to find me,
not just to criticize me, right?
As for why we got divorced,
you can ask your son.
You probably wouldn't believe me anyway,
and I'd just seem petty.
Qin Gang and I are already divorced.
It's all in the past.
Since you've come to see me today,
just say what you want to say.
Where is my grandson?
He's at home.
He's so young,
yet you leave him at home while you work.
How can you bear it?
I...
No need to explain.
Life is hard.
Of course you need to earn money for formula.
You don't need to say anything else.
The situation is clear.
You don't have the ability or the means
to give my grandson a happy life.
Therefore, you have to give him to me.
Name your terms.
Will you agree to any condition I set?
Whatever you want.
Then please don't come looking for me again.
From the moment my baby was born,
I told myself
that he belongs only to me,
and I won't let anyone take him away.
Auntie, you just got off the plane.
Please get some rest.
I have things to do. I'm leaving now.
Goodbye, Mrs. Qin.
Wait a moment.
You're quite impressive.
Fine, let's not talk about this matter today.
But I should have the right to see my grandson.
This way.
So you live in a place like this.
To be honest, yes.
And this apartment isn't even mine. It's rented.
Where did you find a postpartum nanny?
I didn't hire one.
My family is taking care of him.
What are you doing here?
Hello.
This is my home.
Your sister had to go out.
She asked me to look after the baby.
He just fell asleep.
This is...
Seems I was right about you.
So this is what you meant by 'your family.'
No, ma'am.
Where is my grandson?
Who is this? She's so intimidating.
Qin Gang's mother. Mrs. Qin.
We're doomed.
No, why did you
choose this moment to show up?
The baby is right here.
I just came to bring some things for your baby.
Your sister said she had something to do and asked me to watch the child.
So here I am.
I really can't explain this situation now.
You.
The food is ready. Are you going to serve it or not?
This is my grandson.
Sweetheart.
I finally get to see you.
Grandma is here to take you.
We'll go live in a big house.
Ma'am.
What are you talking about?
Who is this?
He...
He's my uncle.
Ma'am, don't listen to her nonsense.
I'm not her uncle.
My name is Hua Ming.
You can call me Xiao Huazi.
Or you can call me Xiao Dengzi.
I'm just here to serve her and her mother.
Xiao Dengzi.
Do you think living here is good enough?
Yes, it's quite nice here.
So it's just the two of you taking care of the baby?
No, he...
No, my sister usually takes care of him.
Today she couldn't.
I don't know what happened.
He just came here temporarily.
I've been through it all. Nothing escapes me.
Temporarily?
How could he possibly be here temporarily?
If he were just visiting,
he wouldn't be so familiar with this home, would he?
Yes, I'm living in his apartment.
So you're living together with him after all.
No, please let me explain.
We are just...
Xinxin...
You don't need to explain anything to me.
I don't care about your personal affairs.
But there's one thing I must make clear.
My grandson absolutely cannot
live in this kind of environment.
The conditions here are inadequate in every way.
You are his mother.
You keep saying you love him.
If you love him, you should give him everything.
If you give him to me, he can have everything.
I... give him to you?
Wait, is he lacking food or clothes?
Can you feed him?
Won't I still be the one feeding him?
What he needs most right now
is me, his mother.
If you give him to me,
you'll still be his mother.
Yaping.
Jiang Qiaohua.