[This drama is a work of fiction. Any resemblance
to real people or events is purely coincidental]
[All child actor and animal scenes were filmed
in full compliance with broadcasting guidelines]
[Episode 8]
It was my first time.
Dancing at the center of the stage
felt like my stage, prepared just for me.
Is this what it feels like
to be the main character?
I'm exhausted.
Ah, Genie.
Oh my.
[Episode 8 The Color of Success]
No.
This isn't working.
Let's match the outfit.
Ah, it's dark.
I have nothing to wear, seriously.
Life keeps surprising me.
Even came with a chauffeur.
Seeing this car come to pick me up like this...
We can hear you, Ms. Yoo.
Just speak normally.
I'm doing this because I'm happy, okay?
I'm so happy that I could cry.
Who's our client this time?
He's definitely rich!
- He's rich.
Hey, you!
Jinx!
Ah, Ms. Yoo!
That joke's outdated.
You can't hide your excitement, Ms. Yoo.
Why hide happiness?
It's hard enough hiding sadness in life.
Oh?
Why is everyone giving me that look?
Like it's a big deal?
Why did he dress up like that?
Yeo Reum.
Yeo Reum, you look really pretty today!
Stop it.
Here's another person who can't hide his emotions.
You're drooling.
When was she ever not pretty?
Yeo Reum, get in.
Have a good trip.
Ms. Yoo!
Take care.
Nervous?
The bag's luxury.
You're a luxury too.
Perfect match.
Really?
Take this tomorrow.
Ms. Yoo.
All my bags are Grade S fakes,
but this one's real.
I bought it last year after much hesitation.
You don't have to lend me this...
They say good shoes take you to good places.
What'll you do when you get there?
When women reach good places,
expensive bags become their pride.
Walk in confidently.
Thank you.
I'll take good care of it.
Mr. O, you look cool today.
I'm kind of like that sometimes.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Shall we go?
Yeo Reum looks excited, huh?
Of course she's excited. It's a masterpiece.
What?
Yeon Seok.
Do you like Yeo Reum?
What?
I mean
you're cutting out everyone else's shots
but only putting Yeo Reum's scenes like this.
I can see your bias in the editing.
Well, Yeo Reum
represents our agency.
And also,
she dances well.
I can dance too, you know.
Maybe it's the difference between
an amateur and a professional.
But, being honest isn't a bad thing.
Why hold back when you like someone?
Mr. Know-It-All, any idea why?
Right.
I...
like Yeo Reum.
I like you too.
Ms. Yoo.
I love you.
"I love you."
Wow.
Reminds me of old times.
Huh?
Like being called to the teacher's office
to get scolded.
Relax.
Why did they call us though?
Must have some reason.
Don't stress.
Yes, I...
I, um...
I am O Sang Sik,
CEO of Ohkoo Entertainment.
You think I called you not knowing that?
I've been wanting to tell you this
if I ever got the chance, ma'am.
It may have seemed like
a small, insignificant show,
but I am truly grateful for your support
of the 'Day Trip' program for five years,
a program that I loved so much.
[Travel Contract]
Oh, no need for formalities.
It's not that I'm refusing,
You're quite impatient.
I know from the report that my daughter managed to
get rid of that show.
I was born into wealth,
lived as a wealthy person,
and became even wealthier.
The more successful and wealthier you become,
the more advantages you have.
I can get whatever I want.
If I don't like seeing someone sitting
in a more comfortable chair than me,
I can make them sit in that chair,
whoever they are.
What is it that
you want most in this room?
Pardon?
Do you want to be successful like me?
Yes, I do.
Success is...
No,
being rich,
it starts when you have more things you want to do
than things you want to have.
Once you've either got or can get most things,
what you want to do
starts to surpass what you want to have.
There's something I want to do in here,
but I can't anymore.
I want you, Kang Yeo Reum,
to do it for me.
To help you get what you want,
I'll pay you generously for it.
If you take what I tell you to do
and the fact that you met me to your grave.
I'm not wealthy,
but I have more things I want to do
than things I want to have, Ms. Chairwoman.
Could you compensate me
with something other than that?
Wow.
I've been on edge all day, and now
I'm so drained that I feel hungry.
We should've eaten something
at that hotel earlier, right?
By the way, how did you
think of all that in that moment?
If I complete these trips you mentioned,
please revive
the Day Trip program.
I want our show back.
Wow, Kang Yeo Reum
has really grown up.
Now, you know how to make deals
and your confidence is through the roof...
I need to
succeed, too.
Ah, of course, you absolutely should.
Alright, let's go up, have dinner, and head home.
Oh, once I get there,
everyone will be curious about who the client is,
so they'll probably bombard us with questions.
You know the deal with confidentiality, right?
Right.
I know.
Just tell them I'm taking about ten days off.
I'll pack and leave immediately.
Yes, alright.
Yeah, go ahead and rest. Call me often.
Yes, Mr. O.
- Fighting.
Take care.
She's...
She's been so distant since her trip to Japan...
Has her confidence grown?
Or has her greed grown?
Number One Radiance Cover.
- Mask Fit Red Cushion.
- Hello.
This is my chance.
The final chance.
[Mom]
Of course.
Oh, the show?
I'm preparing it.
Oh, Mom, today some chairwoman...
Never mind.
My 'Day Trip' show might return.
Yeah, I'm telling you.
You'll soon be able to see
your daughter on TV again.
Well,
can you make sure to tell Dad too?
Yes.
It'll work out.
It's a fresh start, Kang Yeo Reum.
You rejected it?
That's how it went.
If they're even sending a driver and a car,
the deal must be huge, way bigger than usual.
What kind of conditions don't match
that you'd throw away such an opportunity?
It's not just about missing the chance.
The numbers didn't add up...
And also...
It was too risky.
It was too dangerous.
Why are you laughing?
No.
Eat well, Mr. O.
Isn't this situation funny?
Oh, what was that?
Scratching the back of your head.
Mr. O, you always scratch your head
when you lie. It's a habit.
What? No.
Is that so?
He kept scratching his head
when promising my raise last year.
When did I ever do that?
You're doing it right now.
Oh, really?
No, this is...
It's just chronic dermatitis.
My skin gets dry in autumn.
Very parched.
Look at the sweat on your nose.
Your 'truth spring' activates when lying, right?
Here.
Above your nostrils.
Ms. Yoo,
what's wrong with you?
Why misinterpret the sincerity of someone
who just wants to live without shame?
So, the request today
turned out to be a bust, that's all.
Wow, kimchi jjigae with pork.
Yeah, wow.
You've got something going on, huh?
What's with this vibe you're giving me?
You don't trust me right now, is that it?
Oh, it's delicious.
Why's this food so good?
That's not it.
It's not that I don't trust you,
it's just... It's driving me crazy.
Explain it then.
Listen to me again.
Look, I went to the hotel.
- Skip details, get to the point.
- Got it.
At the hotel...
Look at the sweat on your nose.
I went to the hotel.
But, it felt like a mansion.
There were so many books.
When I thought 'Why so many books?'
and pulled the chair...
- Did you wait long?
- Not at all.
Let's order food.
How should I put it?
Your screenplay... It touches on
primal human instincts but...
Fails to show raw desires strongly enough.
That script has that ink smell, you know?
That really bothers me.
It shouldn't be that way.
People want honesty, but...
Do you think people would be moved
by a piece of writing that reeks of someone
trying too hard to show off what they've learned?
You...
lack depth.
That's your fundamental flaw.
Listen, movies should...
So?
So, it's boring? That's your verdict?
Don't oversimplify what I said.
If I must be blunt,
my script sucks.
It got rejected.
That's what you meant, right?
- Hey.
I asked you to review my script.
Not my entire life trajectory.
My life is my own.
I'll draw my own conclusions.
Alright, alright.
Understood.
There's a good place nearby.
Let's talk over drinks.
We might need crew for future projects.
Ah.
So you're here to say that my script is crap
and I should just be the one
cleaning up after your movie?
Is that what you wanted to say?
You...
Ah, you're talking weird.
This place has food, too.
And ice.
I'll go.
Hey, Yeon Seok.
Lee Yeon Seok.
Ah.
Autumn nights are nice.
Well.
I want to travel.
I need to get away!
A ticket to Jinju.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
[Train Ticket, Seoul to Jinju]
Yeo Reum.
Huh?
Yeon Seok.
It might not look like it.
But it's 100% coincidence.
[Final Station: Jinju]
- Thank you.
Have a cup of coffee while you're at it...
- Oh, thank you.
- Thank you.
This is why I love traveling.
Unbelievable.
How did we end up meeting like this?
Dividing the world into things
that make sense and things that don't
is overly binary thinking.
Most things in human society
only seem like they don't make sense.
I once ran into my aunt at the Gold Coast lookout
in Australia,
and she was on a group tour with her ladies' club.
Sounds unbelievable, right?
No way.
That's so amazing.
Nice.
Looks like the train is about to depart.
Is there something worth looking at over there?
Do you think I'm looking at this?
I'm looking at you.
Your dad jokes that reek of cheesy humor
are your trademark, as always.
Have I really hidden
any secrets from you, honestly?
They just said
they'd pay a lot,
so they asked me to treat it
with confidentiality, that's all.
They said they'll pay a lot? How much?
Well...
Enough...
They're saying... a big one,
like a big bill, just one.
Oh my, really?
So, Yeo Reum went for that job?
Exactly. She couldn't talk about it either.
So, she just jumped at the opportunity.
That girl. Always overthinking everything.
You gave her the cold shoulder...
She's too considerate.
Does it matter if I don't know her work details?
As long as she earns well,
I'm not asking questions.
Right.
If it's like that, you could just say it.
Why hide it and make me feel hurt?
But I
have nothing to hide from you, Mr. O.
We've been through so much together,
so how could you compare me to Ba Ram?
Exactly. Ugh.
I guess I was thinking too shortsightedly.
Where's Mr. Lee today?
He's on vacation.
I heard he's going to
his grandmother's house
in Jinju to clear his head.
What? Jinju?
I have a rough idea, but I won't confirm it.
Because confidentiality is a promise.
Alright.
The car with the chauffeur
and the hotel they stayed
when making the request...
Anyway, the destination being that village
means it's from a well-established family
that everyone in Jinju knows.
But, the trip they requested is really simple.
My grandmother used to say that if you
climb the Seongjeon Am Temple ten times,
you'll achieve enlightenment.
Maybe it was thanks to that,
but she lived her life as a rich lady,
enjoying wealth, and even when she passed,
she left without hardship and peacefully.
It's the greed of a rich old person
wanting to enjoy luxury
both in life and after death.
Since I became like this,
I couldn't even complete the ten climbs.
It's been three years since I last went.
You just need to go there.
Simple request, but odd part is...
Why choose our agency? That's the question.
They could've hired anyone with money.
Well,
there are two possibilities in that case.
Either the person who can get
anything with money is not trustworthy,
or there's a reason why
it has to be you, Yeo Reum.
A reason why it has to be me?
This train feels magical.
Everything tastes better on trains. Even rocks!
Why is that?
Should I make a movie with something like this?
A train journey with kids who are picky eaters.
How is it? Good, right?
Thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
- Wow...
- Alright, let's dig in.
It's cold noodles with beef pancake?
Yeah, I've heard somewhere that this place
is famous for its gibang culture,
and the cold noodles that were originally eaten
in the north for hangover have been passed down
and adapted to the local flavors
of the southern region...
My grandmother used to make
soy sauce-based milmyeon.
Give it a try.
Jinju cold noodles are different
from other regional cold noodles
because they use a seafood broth.
What's this?
Where'd you get all this knowledge?
My previous job was travel reporting.
Oh, that's right.
Actually, Yeon Seok...
After this trip, the show...
No, it's nothing.
Here.
- Got the shot?
- Yes.
I'll enjoy it.
[Si Wan]
- Eat up.
- Okay.
The noodles will get soggy.
Here.
Let's part ways here.
Alright.
Feeling sad?
Of course I am.
'What meets must part, what parts must meet.'
Meet then part, part then meet again.
Isn't that life and travel?
Is this why he said my script was no good?
Huh?
No, forget it.
Anyway, we're in the same county.
Call me anytime you need.
I will.
- I'll go.
- Okay.
Time to go.
Yes.
You take the bus here,
and I'll go to the bus stop over there...
I'm off.
But being honest isn't a bad thing.
Why hold back when you like someone?
Mr. Know-It-All,
any idea why?
Yeo Reum!
Yes?
I'm...
I'm thinking of writing a romance.
A romance?
Or maybe
a rom-com screenplay.
That'd be great.
You could write anything well.
Why?
Because if it's you,
you wouldn't write
without knowing what you're doing.
Yeah, I should write with knowledge.
From now on, I'll try to learn more.
How about,
after I finish the script,
you play the lead role?
Really? I'd love that.
I'll do my best.
Yeah.
Enjoy your meal.
Two boxes to go, please.
Understood.
She's subtly oblivious.
Really? I'd love that.
I'll do my best.
Did I complicate simple things?
Does she prefer direct approaches?
[Mr. O Sang Sik]
Huh?
Yes.
Ah, Director...
Are you with our Yeo Reum now?
Well, I'm not with 'our Yeo Reum' now, Father.
Got it. Bye.
'Father', really?
What?
No wonder the daughter's clueless.
Wow.
Is this it?
They said it's over there.
One, two...
Found it.
The traditional house,
where my grandmother lived, is still there.
Once a year,
I go there to relax for days.
Since there's someone managing it,
it's not bad to stay anytime.
It doesn't matter which room you use.
It looks exactly like a period drama set.
The old houses remain perfectly preserved.
No residents?
Yes, I'm here alone.
Not scared?
I'm fine.
It's right in the village center,
and the caretaker lives next door.
If you're scared, just call someone.
This isn't a haunted house. Nothing to fear.
You seem excited.
Yes, I'm thrilled right now.
I might return to broadcasting,
maybe even star in movies.
Movies?
Never mind.
But, Mr. O.
I don't understand something.
What?
I don't know how harsh the trip to the temple
the chairwoman mentioned really is.
But still,
I don't get why she asked me to take on the job.
Going up to the temple
isn't exactly a difficult task.
Well...
Maybe it's the kind of reason
that's only possible because it's you.
Perhaps you're just the only one
who doesn't know it.
Huh?
For now, just see the trip through to the end.
Once you do, you'll understand the reason.
I know a few rich people,
and the truly wealthy
don't waste money.
If I were born into a family like this,
people would probably call me
'young lady'
or 'lady of the house,'
right?
Must be nice.
Huh?
Oh, hello.
I saw lights on, and figured you arrived.
I got word from Seoul that someone's coming.
Ah, yes.
Thank you in advance.
Will you be staying in the annex?
Yes.
A small room will be just fine.
Chairwoman always uses this room when visiting.
Really?
Just eat and put the tray aside.
Yes, I'll enjoy the meal.
This trip's rather peaceful.
Wow, looks delicious.
So, this is what people mean
by being born with a silver spoon.
I'll enjoy it.
Huh?
[Yeon Seok]
Wow.
Beautiful.
Not going home?
Whether I'm here or at home,
being alone is the same.
Then, shall we grab a drink?
Oh.
Look at this, just look.
- First, this...
- What?
Wow, how many views already?
No way, seriously?
I should call Jeong Woo
to thank him for the interview.
130,000 views in just five days...
Thanks to Genie's popularity, it's going viral.
Our Genie.
Unbelievable.
This many views already?
Amazing, right?
Yes.
Check these comments.
- Comments?
- Yeah.
[Genie's like a music video director
What's with these guys, hilarious nonsense vibe]
[Middle-aged guys in the back row
look cute like puppies and cats]
[She used to be in a girl group,
no wonder her moves are sharp]
Oh, my.
[Right-side guy's cute!
He's a film director, actually. Quite charming]
♫ If we could make it happen, how wonderful ♫
You might become a YouTube star at this rate.
Being the guy next to the star would be perfect.
You should take center stage.
- Center stage?
- Yeah.
♫ What do you feel when thinking of me ♫
♫ Rare moments when you approach ♫
[Chokseongnu Pavilion]
♫ Make my heart race with hope ♫
♫ Tell the moon I like you ♫
♫ Want to confess to you ♫
♫ This ambiguous 'friendship' label ♫
♫ Keeps hiding my true feelings ♫
♫ Whisper to the moon ♫
♫ I miss you ♫
♫ Tell me how you feel ♫
♫ If I could reach your heart ♫
♫ I'd run straight there to confess ♫
♫ I like you ♫
Yeah, here.
Oh.
The views went up again already.
Oh, what's going on?
And if I restart broadcasting again...
What am I going to do?
Wow, this is amazing.
Thank you.
Wow, what should I do?
[Eun Chae]
I'll be off now.
Wish me luck.
I need to walk hard today.
This house doesn't have a single locked door...
It's strange.
[Seongjeon Am Temple]
Let's go.
I'm my way up to Seongjeon Am Temple, ma'am.
Looks like the seasons are changing.
You've been here before,
so the scenery must be familiar,
but they say the fall colors are more beautiful
this year because there's been little rain.
Oh, my.
No wonder people say one can
reach enlightenment here.
How did she manage to climb all this way?
Resting will make it harder.
Ah...
Alright, let's keep going.
Are you resting?
Oh, thank you.
I haven't seen you before.
Must be from out of town.
Yes.
Are you also heading to Seongjeon Am Temple?
There's an event at the temple.
I went down to the main temple
to get offering rice.
Carrying all that up to the temple
seems too heavy.
Shall I help carry some and go up together?
You?
If you think something is heavy,
even a bottle of water feels heavy.
If you think it light,
even a sack of rice feels light.
Life is all about carrying
as much as your heart allows.
You're heading up already?
Take your time.
Please go ahead, sir.
I'll head up a little later.
There you go.
Life's all about perspective.
[Message]
Chairwoman Sung Yi Hwa has passed away.
Come back to Seoul quickly, Yeo Reum.
No,
no...
This can't be real.
After a long battle with cancer,
Chairwoman Sung Yi Hwa,
one of the leading women in the beauty industry,
died suddenly of cardiac arrest.
Mourners from the business world
and beyond continue to pay their respects.
I got excited for a moment.
I thought this time it might work out.
I wondered if this was what opportunity
looked like, arriving so suddenly.
But just as quickly as that hope appeared,
that my show might come back to life
once the trip was over, it vanished overnight.
If you think something is heavy,
even a bottle of water feels heavy.
If you think it light,
even a sack of rice feels light.
Life is all about carrying
as much as your heart allows.
Right.
It's all about perspective.
Well, that's...
It's hard to say yes
and hard to say no...
You're saying the client of the Jinju trip
isn't Chairwoman Sung Yi Hwa?
Probably...
No?
Probably not?
Snow's falling.
Nonsense, it's too early for snow
with leaves still green.
Because you keep scratching your head, ugh.
What kind of lies are just spilling out like that?
You punk.
The Jinju Sung Family Estate
was Yeo Reum's destination.
Upon hearing of Chairwoman Sung's death,
she returned to Seoul immediately.
My mom read me
Sherlock Holmes during pregnancy.
No, it's not.
Shouldn't you hire part-timers?
Anyway, you do dinner service here,
and it's not just for a day or two.
I can't easily replace someone
who said they'd be taking a few days off.
Could you check the seasoning for me, Ms. Yoo?
Hmm, a bit salty?
Oh, really?
Just leave it.
Mr. O likes strong flavors anyway.
Anyway, he always says
the unhealthy stuff tastes the best.
He needs to eat well to live long.
Yet, he stays so slim.
Oops, it burst.
He likes semi-soft yolks.
Exactly.
O Sang Sik likes salty food and runny eggs.
I know.
He says al dente ramyeon's the best in the world.
He likes slightly burnt rice too.
And he prefers unfermented kimchi,
and he eats spicy jjamppong on rainy days.
He prefers beer over soju
and prefer someak over beer.
You know all this, right?
Still,
he can enjoy a meal even if all there is
is over-fermented kimchi,
burnt instant noodles, and soju,
as long as there's a good person to eat with.
Wait, I meant...
Mr. O and you,
you two should
eat together now.
That's not what I meant.
Ms. Yang, seriously...
If you know him so well,
why not go for him?
Come on, let's drink.
Down it.
Yum.
Wow, eggs!
Something wrong?
Hey,
Ms. Yoo Ha Na.
What?
Why?
Uh...
Eat some side dishes, too.
What does it matter
whether I eat the side dishes or not?
Do you want me to cook some ramyeon
if you're not feeling like eating?
Want to eat ramyeon?
You like egg ramyeon, right?
With bloated noodles.
Why's he suddenly being so sweet?
You like soggy ramyeon, too?
Yeah.
Even al dente noodles
get soggy in your stomach.
It's good.
Yeo Reum...
I think I finally understand.
I was always anxious.
But never when I was with you.
I want you back.
♫ Like a rain-soaked petal ♫
♫ That faded away powerlessly ♫
♫ The beautiful smile
that once bloomed beautifully ♫
♫ Is no longer here anymore ♫
Si Wan, thank you
for being there for me and being so kind.
What is this feeling?
Is it feeling pathetic?
Or is it anxiety?
I think it's fine for us to try it ourselves now.
A travel story from Kang Yeo Reum,
who's truly passionate about traveling.
Are you two seeing each other again?
Would it be wrong if we are?
No!
Yeon Seok,
are you confessing to me now?
Yeo Reum's leaving!
Why did you meet the Chairwoman?
I can't tell you.
Need bribe money to talk?
If...
If I had held onto Si Wan,
would I be happy now?
That night
was my most painful night.