[Love in the Big City]
[Episode 7]
Go Young?
This is you, right?
Go Young.
Ah... yes...
I guess so.
Would you sign my copy here?
Not so formal, just write my name.
Sure…
So, what's the book about?
Oh... just the usual love story.
It's been a year since Gyu Ho left.
I finally quit my job
and became a full-time writer.
In the meantime, I published a book
that wrote an obvious love story.
I haven't really been in love for a year.
Hooray! Congratulations,
Go Young, on leaving your job!
It's a series of calm and gloomy days.
I want to cry but I have no tears.
Hey! Go Young!!
Oh! Open the door! Go Young! Seriously!
Hey!
Go Young!!
What if he's really dead?
What do you mean, he's going to die?
Shall we call 119?
Hang on, is it 119 or 112?
What do you mean 112! Oh my gosh.
Oh, Go Young!
Open the door! Go Young!!!
Hey! Go Young!
Oh! Hey! Go Young! What!!
See? I told you he wasn't dead.
Hey watch it… my wiener!
What's the matter with you guys?
We couldn't get in touch
with you for six days!
We were scared it was like last time,
when you took those sleeping pills…
Six days? Has it been that long...?
Yes!
We thought we'd find your dead body when
we opened that door. We were so scared.
I mean, it does smell like
decomposing bodies here.
T...true...
Look at the state of you…
Come on, let's get you washed up.
- Yeah! Get up!
- Uh, uh...!! Hey!!
Use body wash!
Look at the state of the house.
Oh! Wow! It's cool!
Wow! It's cool!!!
The food is going to get cold.
I'm going to eat it all. Then?
Eat up.
Why does yours look more delicious than mine?
It's good!
Chill out, will you? You're overreacting.
I quit my job after three years of non-stop work.
Can't I go silent for a single week?
I guess, yeah...
It's just... it's that time of year...
What time of year?
- Gyu... It's when he left for China… - Hey…
Come on, it's not my first heartbreak.
Besides, that was so long ago now.
It's been over a year.
You're right.
We've all had our fair share of heartbreaks.
But Young.
Have you not... heard from him since?
I haven't heard anything.
He deleted his messenger account, too.
Why would you ask him that?
Anyway, you have to know
that you break the mood.
I just... I'm worried...
And curious…
It's no big deal!
I'm sure he's doing just fine in China.
Come take a picture of me!
- Wait, me too!
- Me three!
Suddenly?
I'll snatch your heart.
You look like a sissy.
Can't you stand more... vanilla?
What, me?
Who else?
Eun Soo, how about me?
Do I look good?
You look hot, Young.
Then I'm going to take a picture?
One, two!
Good!
Hey, give it to me!
Give it to me! Give it to me!
I'm the only one who needs to
look good in the picture.
The three of us are taking it together,
but this isn't right.
Let go Let go.
Hello?
Don't do that. You really.
You look like Donkey.
Yes...
Pardon?
- Uh? Young.
- Young.
What? What's wrong?
Are you feeling dizzy?
I guess it's been a long time
since you got sunlight.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
What's going on again?
You must have had some troubles in your life!
- Hey, what is it?
- Are you alright?
Let me start by congratulating you
for being the first-ever Korean recipient
of the Dublin Literary Award!
Many readers were moved
by the vivid descriptions
and characters in your book,
some say that the writer
actually experienced it.
some even claiming the story
might be autobiographical.
What are your thoughts on this?
All novels are ultimately works of fiction.
I guess I wrote a story
that was so realistic that-
I'll take it as... a compliment.
Yes, next.
Yes. Reporter Jung?
I'm reporter Jung Joon Young
of the Daesan Ilbo.
The Dublin Literary Award is
also known for its substantial monetary prize,
second only to the Nobel Prize in Literature.
Have you thought about
how you'll be using it?
Not yet.
Yes. Next.
Yes. This is Kim In Ae from VIXX News.
Please tell us about your plans
for your next novel..
My son.
Why are you here?
What do you mean why? Son,
I'm here to congratulate you.
I should have brought you
some flowers or something.
I'm sorry I'm empty-handed.
Hey! Go over there!
Go over there!
Stand like this!
Okay, one, two, three.
Wow, it came out well.
These days, bookstores aren't
from the old ones, right?
Thanks to the novelist's son,
I have a good view.
Ah, so...
Me, your father?
A bed for the Swedish royal family.
I have obtained an import distributor.
With just one finger flick!
It's a situation where money comes rolling in.
So?
Did you lease the apartment?
I paid off all the loans with
the rent of Jamsil apartment,
But the economy is in bad shape,
so the shop is also negative.
I'm on the verge of being overwhelmed
because I couldn't pay inheritance tax.
I live in a studio apartment
in front of the school.
What do you think of this father as?
You feel like you're doing something, don't you?
This can all disappear in an instant.
Why didn't you come to mom's funeral?
Hey, give me your address.
What's up with the address!
I can't do anything else
because I'm bad as a father,
and I'm going to send you
a mattress used by royalty.
So go ahead and give me an address!
After my mother's death,
my father only asked about the apartment.
In the face of a tough life and a long time,
love is powerless.
A relationship in which love
has disappeared is so shabby.
[Author Go Young, Achieving the Dublin Literary Award]
[Where did you do your make up?]
[Author, let's open a bottle of champagne at Itaewon.]
[Is he meeting a guy? He's not reading the messages.
-He just read. - Hey there?]
Express delivery!
Go Jin Chul was always like this.
He gave me some unwanted pocket money
and pretended to be a responsible father.
Whenever that happened,
I wanted to spend the allowance
on the worst possible place.
[Right now?]
Do you need to wash?
Already have.
Not there!
Sorry?
Not there... but over there…
That's... cool. It's like it's alive.
Supplied to Swedish Royalty…
That's... sudden…
Phytoncide...!
I told you not to wear them like that!
Your feet are so small.
Then wear your own!
Why are you always wearing my shoes?
- Your feet smell really bad..
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Well... Why..
Why? Uh... Ah... Ugh...!
Hahaha!
Oh, my… It's cold! Ha..
Hey!
Oh, I'm hungry.
Let's hurry up and eat.
Let's eat.
Feels like we're millionaires.
Right?
Your company's nice, they're very
generous with the holiday bonuses.
Nice? Not so nice.
They pay me peanuts.
Still. I only got toothpaste from my work.
True. Why do they insist on giving you
four tubes of toothpaste every holiday?
How many teeth do they think you have?
They'd be better off giving you Spam.
Augh..
Ah..!
Ah!!!
I knew that would happen.
We'll never get the smell out…
Ah… what the..
Oh, I'm going crazy. Come on.
Oh, I'm sorry…
- Oh, I washed this yesterday!
- I didn't do it on purpose..
Oh, my…!
Aaugh..
Oh, my. What a waste...
I... I'll... I'll wash it..
The machine does the washing, not you.
Young, are you busy?
- Have you checked the group chat?
- Not yet, why?
Eun Soo's boyfriend Jun Bae,
he really fucked up this time.
Eun Soo's flying off the handle!
- Hurry up! Hurry up! Hurry up!!!
- Let go! Hey!
That fucker.
Now we're definitely over.
I'd rather date a woman
than a selfish prick like him.
I'm sure he didn't mean to piss you off.
Would anyone in their right mind,
drag someone around all day
after working an overnight flight?
He always does whatever the fuck he likes!
I always let him...
Everything is going to shit.
Let's go up quickly.
Give me the luggage.
I fucking love peanuts.
Why did I give up peanuts
to be with an asshole like him?
I don't care if he dies from an allergic reaction!
No, it's all over now.
He thinks he's so agreeable.
Actually, it's me who's always obliging.
What he always wants to do,
what he wants, what he wants.
You know what you need? A hotel staycation.
I have tons of discount coupons so it's all on me.
The Three-second-man!
Do you know how small his dick is?
You need a microscope to find it!
You couldn't even imagine the
pigmentation, freckles, and wrinkles
that he hides under
that thick layer of foundation.
It's embarrassing to be seen in public with him.
- You know that, right?
- I know, I know.
I was with him out of loyalty!
Emotions? No way.
Not even as much as a peanut.
I was biding my time
to break up with him anyway!
Rat shit tiny dick!
Goodbye--
Eun Soo! Let's get married!
I'll make you happy.
Let's spend our lives together!
B...babe...?
Silver bead, it's already been 1,871…17
days since you rolled into my arms.
I was in heaven for the time
I spent with you.
What is this?
They fought so Jun Bae called us in for backup.
You seemed busy so we didn't
have any time to explain.
With silver bead, I'm in a cozy cloud.
You may refuse.
I respect your choice.
But I'm gonna slowly wither
and disappear from this world.
My silver bead, Eun Soo.
I'll die without you.
So will you marry me?
Say yes!
- Say yes! Say yes! Say yes!
Eun Soo and Jun Bae were
in a relationship for five years.
This is a happy ending
for a long-term relationship.
Now that you've been promised
the love you've wanted forever.
Why doesn't Eun Soo laugh.
- Say yes! Say yes!
- Say yes! Say yes! Say yes!
Ti--Ti--ffa--ny!
How much is that.
Hey... Take a picture!
Nice!! Yeah!
Yes!!!
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss..
Peanut...!
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
Wow! Wow! Congratulations!!!
Are you... okay?
- I... think I need to go to the ER.
- I think you're allergic, too
I'll come with you.
No... I think we should stay apart today.
Eun Soo! Enjoy tonight for the both of us!
Let's meet tomorrow--
I love you!
Did I just become a bride-to-be?
All this cardio is making me sober.
Refill, please.
No, go do it yourself.
Drinks are on the bride-to-be!
Bride-to-be!
Young. Haven't seen you in a while!
Right, hi. Could I get four Gin and Tonics?
How have you been?
Alright, I suppose.
I read about you getting that award!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Oh, my…Oh...! You crazy!
And this is from Gyu Ho.
Sorry?
He asked me to before he left to Shanghai.
Every time you show up,
I'm to give you a glass of this.
On his tab.
You're in touch with Gyu Ho?
Well, sometimes?
He says he's coming back to Korea soon.
Gyu Ho's coming back? To Seoul?
Yeah, he says he has
some work to sort out.
Anyways, thanks for this.
Okay. Have fun.
I can't believe I'm getting hitched!
I bloody love you guys!
Me too!
Who wants my bouquet?
Uh? Me!! Me!!!
Hey! My hat!
Oh! My ring!
Determined to break up, Eun Soo was proposed to instead.
I thought I would be with Gyu Ho forever,
but now I can't even ask
how each other is doing.
Many lovers will love and say goodbye
tonight in the big city of Seoul.
Me?
Okay! It's my last night.
Young, checkout is in an hour.
Let's clean up.
Where is everyone?
They made a run for it, cheeky bastards.
Those bitches...
What about Jun Bae?
He's got work okay.
It's a shame you had to spend
your proposal night apart…
It's alright.
We were together for five years,
and probably will be forever now.
That's true.
And you'll see each other tonight.
Yes.
Eun Soo?
Yeah?
How did it feel?
You were there, how did I look?
I'm so happy!
You?
Fucking ecstatic.
A mattress sold under the
enchanting slogan 'Sleep in the Forest',
has shocked the nation following
a revelation of its use of carcinogenic materials.
An investigation by the Korean Research
Institute of Standards and Science uncovered
that company's mattresses exceeded the legal
limit for carcinogens by an alarming 200 times.
The company's CEO, Mr. Go, has mysteriously vanished,
prompting authorities to launch
a thorough investigation...
About 30 complaints were filed from
the end of last month to this morning.
The amount of damage totaled 560 million won.
Currently, the company run by Mr. Go is closed,
and about 200 victims are have opened
a social network service chat room
and are discussing additional countermeasures.
Phytoncide my ass..
After investigating the complainant,
the police plan to find out where Go is
and the details of the incident..
Elder Park from church once said
that my mom had a lot of love.
My father had a little too much love.
It seems that I have also inherited
my parents' tendencies to love.
Why is it that despite having so much love,
none of us ever knew quite where to direct it?
Kylie Wilde…
I know it's a ridiculous delusion
to think of Gyu Ho.
But sometimes I want to blindly
believe in something ridiculous.
Gyu Ho had smaller feet compared to me.
The owner of the shoe is not Gyu Ho.
Thank you for the warm welcome.
Oops, I'm sorry.
Extraordinary, huh?
That's because I'm the best bartender in Korea.
Koo-e-tan-hay-ra.
What?
Condemn! Condemn!
Condemn instead of silence!
Do you mean 'Condemn?'
Yes, I think so.
People have been shouting
that outside the hotel.
Does it mean something funny?
Uh…
It's means 'you're fucking evil'.
Name?
You don't have to tell me
if you don't want to.
William.
William, Habibi.
What does it mean?
It means love in Arabic.
And what's your name?
Go Young.
What does it mean?
Shine high and bright.
Like a star?
No.
Like a bomb. A nuclear weapon.
You can do it diagonally like this,
We're not going to do a separate ceremony.
Just a party at Ho Min's cafe.
That's a good idea.
Unpretentious, I like it.
Eun Soo.
If you tie them too tight,
the stems will snap.
Ah, got it!
We'll choose everything ourselves,
make it cozy and sweet.
And we'll have people perform.
- Want me to sing for you?
- That's quite alright.
We want to throw away everything
that's wilted and misshapen.
All that should be left is
the fresh and beautiful.
And when you're bringing them together,
these flowers that have all withstood
their own time and histories,
I want you to imagine how two people are
coming together to form a harmonious union.
You're really good.
Imagine your futures, exquisite and fresh,
just like these fragrant flowers.
Eun Soo!
It's okay, we have plenty of flowers!
The thing is,
I can't imagine an exquisite future...
I can only smell the fragrance of shit.
Eun Soo…
Young…
I've got the fucking marriage blues.
Eun Soo and I and everyone
in this big city were
being swept away by something unknown.
past, future, things I want to believe it's love.
If I were to be swept away,
I wanted to end up somewhere that was exotic and stimulating,
rather than familiar and boring.
[Q: Right now?]
Q!!!
Habibi!
It's a present.
It's been over a decade
since I ran anywhere other than a treadmill.
Extraordinary, isn't it?
That's because...
I'm Korea's best florist.
What does it say?
Fuck me deep.
Nuclear weapon.
Would you like to come with me to Bangkok?