♪ Through thick and thin you can get to know ♪
♪ You and I coexist in the city of good and evil ♪
♪ That light leads me to get out of my sorrow ♪
♪ It was meant to be you when we met ♪
♪ Desire ridicules tenderness but never prevails ♪
♪ Yet I’m determined to feed love everlastingly ♪
♪ Standing at the center of billow ♪
♪ Wind is my mind and rain is my hunting ground ♪
♪ Look back to the time long gone ♪
♪ The torch in front is flaming ♪
♪ It gets dark and the way ahead is still long ♪
♪ I know I can’t waver ♪
♪ Shedding blood to be the king is the only way ♪
= Princess Agents =
= Episode 24 =
You can see Jiuyou Platform from here.
Chun.
Whatever you’re doing now
can’t change anything.
Mother.
How could you be so heartless?
Yan Xun is a suspect of rebellion.
If you speak up for him openly,
you will be against your father.
By that time,
all your maids,
your brother and I
will be implicated.
Mother.
Why did you take us
to the execution ground?
I want you here
to show you
that whoever you are,
whatever title you hold,
you could be
on the chopping block.
Deputy Supervisor of Execution presiding!
Yuwen Yue!
Chief Supervisor of Execution
shall read the imperial edict!
Kneel!
The edict is as follows:
Marquis Dingbei, Yan Shicheng,
acted against heaven and earth,
bent the law,
misled the public,
sided with the crooked
and rebelled against the state.
He discarded justice,
built imperial pantheons,
assembled private troops secretly.
His heart of disloyalty
is evident to all.
Also, he dispatched troops to Chang’an
to take over the capital city.
His grave sins
are too numerous to be listed.
Thanks to heaven,
the revolt has been squashed,
and rebels have been exterminated.
Given that Yan Xun
grew up in the capital
and didn’t get involved in the rebellion,
he’s ordered to identify the culprits
and watch their punishments
to redeem himself.
Respect this.
= Jiuyou Platform =
Is what he said true?
Yes.
My family…
Send in the traitors!
Your Excellency Yan Xun,
they all have been executed
except you and your mother.
No one else is left.
Your Excellency Yan Xun, please receive the edict.
Kneel!
Yan Xun!
- Yan Xun!
- On your knees!
Kneel!
Yan Xun!
Identify the corpses as requested.
On your knees!
Then you will be spared.
Look, look!
He is revolting!
Kill him now!
Don’t!
Challenging the imperial edict
equals a capital offence.
Seize him!
Aye!
Wait!
Yan Xun.
Pick up the edict
and thank His Majesty!
Yan Xun, receive the edict.
It’s noon!
Time for the roll call.
Yan Xun!
Get up!
If you can’t do it,
I will.
Your Excellency Yan Xun.
It’s been a while
since you met your father, hasn’t it?
Come here.
Say hello to him.
Yuwen Huai!
Come here.
Don’t move.
Kill him if he refuses to comply.
Yan Xun!
See?
This is the cost of disobedience.
This is too much.
Why?
Why are they doing this
to Yan Xun?
Father!
Step down.
Yan Xun!
Get up!
Move!
Yan Xun!
Disobeying the edict deserves the death penalty.
Go check if he is dead.
He seems so!
Yuwen Yue.
Go check
if your buddy is still breathing.
Jiuyou Platform is sacred.
He didn’t kneel or obey the edict.
That’s an act of revolt.
Bowmen!
Yan Xun.
Don’t come up again.
Chun!
Yan Xun, please!
Don’t stand up again.
- Yan Xun!
- Chun!
Yan Xun.
Don’t!
Mother.
Please do something!
He’s dying!
We’re losing him!
Please help him, Mother.
Mother!
Brother.
Please help him.
Do something.
Please save him.
Yan Xun!
Let go of me!
Let go!
Chun!
How dare you!
Obey the imperial edict now.
No identification is needed.
Execute them now.
Don’t you dare!
I’m given the order to execute rebels.
Are you following it or against it?
I hope I can
buy him more time.
The edict clearly stipulates
only after Yan Xun identifies the corpses
can the execution proceed.
Receive the edict, followed by identification.
Execute them now.
I will take
full responsibility for it.
If you disobey,
I can kill you right now.
If Yan Xun still refuses to obey,
I will end him right here.
Let me remind you again.
Xing’er is right over there.
Apparently, I’ll have to do it myself.
I’ll do it!
Wait!
Mr. Yuwen,
I’ll identify the corpses.
Those up there
are my husband,
sons and daughter.
They’re my family.
I believe
no one else
is more eligible than me
to identify their corpses.
Ma’am,
who allowed you to come here?
His Majesty, the Emperor.
His Majesty has issued an edict
to task me with the identification.
My son, Yan Xun, is young and ignorant.
I am sorry he offended you, Master Huai.
The edict is on the way.
You won’t disobey
His Majesty, will you?
Xun.
Mother.
Xun!
Mother!
It’s them.
They destroyed Yanbei.
Why?
Xun.
Do you believe your father?
I do.
Then don’t ask why.
Not everything
in this world
has its reason.
Like tigers eat wolves,
wolves eat rabbits,
rabbits eat grass.
All that happens without a reason.
Our family…
Father, eldest brother
sister…
This is my husband,
Marquis Dingbei of Yanbei,
Grand Marshal of Northwestern Wei,
Yan Shicheng.
This scar
was left by a sword
outside the Palace
when quashing Prince Qi’s revolt.
Those rebels burned the Palace
and trapped everyone inside.
Shicheng took his men
and risked his life to save them.
He found His Majesty first
who was then a prince.
He carried the unconscious prince
and fought his way out
amid three thousand enemy troops.
His body and hands
were wounded over 30 times.
He could barely get out of bed
until half a year later.
All that happened
when he just reached 17.
You are here to identify the dead,
not to spew nonsense.
Please continue, Ma’am.
This scar
is due to his wound
during the Baima Pass Battle.
They were mourning the ancestors that day.
The entire imperial family
was present.
But Rouran launched a sudden strike.
They crossed the Pass
and surrounded the Ancestral Temple.
After Shicheng learned the news,
he and his men set out from Yanbei.
After riding for
seven days and nights
without rest,
they rescued everyone from danger.
Your emperor
vowed right there
that Wei and Yanbei
would never betray each other.
Most of you
witnessed that, too.
My husband’s head
was cut off by you, Mr. Yuwen Huai
right outside Chang’an.
You are in your prime with sharp eyes.
You can certainly recognize
the cuts made by your sword.
Did you make this cut?
Isn’t this man Marquis Dingbei,
Yan Shicheng?
Don’t you know that?
I confirm,
this man is my husband,
Marquis Dingbei of Yanbei,
Yan Shicheng.
Where is the edict, Ma’am?
I can order them
to kill Yan Xun now!
Yan Xun!
♪ The wind blows the moonlight ♪
♪ I’m born with a heart of fire ♪
♪ Who laughs at my humble beginnings ♪
♪ Fate has my wings broken ♪
♪ Fall into the abyss with the memories sealed ♪
♪ What an arrogant blizzard ♪
♪ Not looking up even if trampled again ♪
♪ I’ll get stronger and stronger ♪
♪ The breath is heat The heartbeat is light ♪
♪ Go forward bit by bit in a lifelong struggle ♪
♪ Tears hot in eyes light up the hope ♪
♪ No matter how much it hurts ♪
♪ I’m willing to burn my heart out ♪
♪ To melt the frost in the whole world ♪
♪ The moon knows my mind ♪
♪ So what if the road ahead is in endless dark ♪
♪ I want my heart burn like fire once again ♪
♪ Burning to be the light in the sky ♪
♪ Reborn from fire The world thrives ♪
♪ I’m blooming on the other side ♪
♪ Burning to be the light in the sky ♪