♪ Through thick and thin you can get to know ♪
♪ You and I coexist in the city of good and evil ♪
♪ That light leads me to get out of my sorrow ♪
♪ It was meant to be you when we met ♪
♪ Desire ridicules tenderness but never prevails ♪
♪ Yet I’m determined to feed love everlastingly ♪
♪ Standing at the center of billow ♪
♪ Wind is my mind and rain is my hunting ground ♪
♪ Look back to the time long gone ♪
♪ The torch in front is flaming ♪
♪ It gets dark and the way ahead is still long ♪
♪ I know I can’t waver ♪
♪ Shedding blood to be the king is the only way ♪
= Princess Agents =
= Episode 29 =
Wei Shuyou!
You bastard!
How dare you call my name!
Surrender now
to die intact.
I killed those men and hurt him.
Do your job.
If we don’t take action now,
it’ll be too late to save His Excellency.
Anything we do
will prove Yan Xun guilty.
We can’t leap in the dark anymore.
But Emperor is fickle
and gullible.
At court, His Excellency will...
I have an idea.
It’s feasible.
But you’ll be in grave danger.
I’ll do it.
Alright, I can’t go see her.
Only you can.
Time is running out.
Any delay,
we’ll be stuck in here.
Fine, you take care.
Princess.
What’s wrong?
His Excellency Yan Xun’s maid
bought over an entrance guard,
and is waiting outside.
She says that His Excellency Yan Xun is in trouble
and needs your help.
Move!
Mr. Zhu,
Young Master Wei Shuyou failed.
Yan Xun is being sent to the Palace
to see His Majesty.
Young Master asked us
to move the killers’ bodies away
on the sly.
Go check.
Aye.
You guys take the chance
to bury those bodies.
Be quick.
- Aye.
Take those bodies away.
Get lost!
Princess has orders
to secure the killers’ bodies.
Go!
Move!
Mr. Zhu,
someone ambushed Wei’s guards.
Those bodies were taken away
by Princess’s men.
That useless Wei Shuyou!
Mr. Zhu, what’s next?
You need to ask? Get them back!
- Aye.
- Let’s go!
Take them outside the city.
They’ll be unconscious there
for at least for 4 hours.
They won’t make any trouble.
Your Majesty, your liquor pot is empty.
Here’s more.
Who are you?
I’m your maid
and your woman.
My woman?
Everyone and everything in this world
belong to you.
Aren’t you sweet?
What’s your name?
My name is Lan’er.
Lan’er.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty. Are you asleep?
It’s urgent!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Come in.
Your Majesty.
What happened?
Something urgent
requires your immediate attention.
She is good. Promote her to Concubine
with the title Lan.
She can move into the Palace of Orchid.
Aye.
Yan Xun, I’ve just pardoned you.
You haven’t atoned for your sins
before wounding others.
I’m guilty.
I can’t thank you enough
for your kindness.
But that was self-defense.
Wei Shuyou attempted
to assassinate me earlier.
If I didn’t fight back,
I wouldn’t have a chance to survive.
Your Majesty,
I went there
for Yan Xun’s safety
to patrol as usual.
But I caught him
trying to escape,
so he wanted me dead.
Your Majesty.
Just like his father,
Yan Xun is too wild to be trusted.
Are you blind?
Can’t you see
those dead bodies
all over the Oriole Courtyard?
Wei Shuyou assembled the assassins
and Yan Xun
just tried to protect himself.
Prince Yu.
Don’t you believe
your own cousin?
Did you see any assassins, Your Highness?
Or did you see any dead bodies?
I didn’t.
- But...
- Song.
Stand down.
Your Majesty, I have got the testimonies
from the guards overnight.
They only saw Wei Shuyou and Yan Xun
without any sign of assassins.
Your Majesty,
guards of the Oriole Courtyard
all came from the Yuwen family.
Their testimonies are unreliable.
Your Majesty, I understand
it’s hard for me to defend myself.
But I grew up in the capital city.
Your Majesty are
a good judge of character.
What kind of person am I?
Would I stoop so low
as to act as the crooked?
I believe
Your Majesty will have
your own conclusions.
Your Majesty,
if you punish Yan Xun for this,
that may be categorized as persecution.
Like father like son.
Here you are playing the martyr.
You not only framed Young Master Wei,
but also fooled Noble Consort.
You are much better
than that treacherous father
of yours.
What’s this called?
The son outdoes the father.
Young Master Huai.
If I were really as good as you said,
I wouldn’t have
ended up like this.
But thanks for showing me a backstabber,
fabricator and liar.
I’ve learned
my lesson.
Your Excellency,
don’t throw dirt on me.
His Majesty can tell the truth.
Well,
you wounded others
in custody.
We all saw that.
Who saw your so-called assassins?
Do you have eyewitnesses?
You are lying to His Majesty.
He who has a mind to beat his dog
will easily find his stick.
I’m only a concubine’s son
with no power at all.
Telling lies aside,
I wouldn’t dare to wound anyone.
You overestimated me.
Yuwen Huai.
You alone aren’t that capable, of course.
My respects to you, Father, Mother.
What are you doing here?
Don’t mess around.
Go back, now.
Father,
I’ve got something important
to report.
Go ahead.
The dead body outside
was the assassin
sent by the Wei family
to kill Yan Xun tonight,
and he was
Wei Shuyou’s henchman.
Wei Shuyou always went out
with him.
Many people in the Palace recognize him.
And some of you here
must be familiar with him
as well.
Young Master Yuwen, am I right?
Song, Yuwen Huai,
check the body outside.
- Aye.
Your Majesty.
The dead man was indeed
Wei Shuyou’s henchman.
What Chun just said is true.
Young Master Yuwen, don’t you
recognize him?
He looked familiar, but I don’t know him.
Yuwen Huai.
What do you mean by “he looked familiar”?
You hang about
with Wei Shuyou every day.
How could you not know
his henchman?
Shuyou, go and check the body,
and see if he was
your servant.
Look carefully.
Don’t you think
you can muddle through this
by telling lies.
You know,
I have got so many ways
to verify your story.
Aye.
Your Majesty. Your Highnesses.
It’s true that man
was my servant.
Did you hear that, Yuwen Huai?
He has admitted it himself.
What more do you have to say?
Your Highness,
although he was their servant,
he could be a spy
planted next to Young Master Wei.
You...
By the way,
when Marquis Dingbei planned to
rebel,
he could certainly plant spies
in noble families.
You...
That’s right.
How could Princess know
what happened in the Oriole Courtyard
in the middle of the night,
and then encountered the assassin
and brought him to His Majesty?
Your Majesty.
This man was my servant,
but never a henchman.
He seemed to be smart,
so I kept him.
I didn’t expect
he was skilled in martial arts.
I bet someone powerful
planted him next to me.
I have been living in the capital
since childhood.
I have always been cautious
to stay away from mistakes
and trouble.
I don’t have
any fighters around me,
not to mention highly skilled ones.
Liar!
There are two
skilled martial artists around you.
A man and a woman.
Your Majesty,
if you have no idea about that,
we can bring them here for questioning.
Your Majesty, the truth is
Wei Shuyou planned
to assassinate me first.
And now, he’s framing me.
He’s evil beyond forgiveness.
I’m a sinner.
Thanks to your mercy,
I can live to this day.
I would never have any martial artists
around me.
Nonsense!
Without them,
how could you survive
the assassination tonight?
You would have been chopped into pieces
by us.
So that’s what happened.
Did you hear that, Father?
He said it himself.
However you spin this,
it’ll be of no use.
Didn’t you just say there was nobody else
other than Yan Xun and Wei Shuyou
in the Oriole Courtyard?
Your Majesty.
He’s on drugs,
so he doesn’t know what he says.
Do I look like a fool?
Your Majesty, I’m to blame.
I’m negligent.
His Majesty’s given the explicit order
to forbid noble families
from approaching Yan Xun.
Shuyou,
you’ve really
disappointed His Majesty.
You’ve crossed the line
and tried to deceive His Majesty.
You should be damned.
But Your Majesty,
I watched him over the cradle.
Although he’s rash,
he has a good nature.
It’d never be his intention
to do such things.
He must’ve been abetted
in the deception by the ill-intentioned.
You are right.
Father, the truth
has come out.
They should be punished.
Yan Xun is a victim here.
Please let him stand up.
Yan Xun, you may rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Wei Shuyou,
since Noble Consort has
put in a good word for you,
you shall be flogged 20 times.
Reflect on yourself in home confinement.
Without my permission,
you are not allowed to leave your place.
Father,
he was going to assassinate Yan Xun
and he lied to you.
He has committed more than one felony.
How can you just
flog him 20 times?
Where are your manners?
- Father…
- Chun.
You may all leave.
My night is totally
ruined by you.
Your Excellency,
you are quite smart
and made Wei Shuyou confess.
But smart men in history
weren’t necessarily the winners.
Power matters the most.
Yuwen Huai.
You are sharp-tongued
and good with words.
Your Highness.
I meant well.
Meant well?
Give it a rest.
From now on, stay away from
Yan Xun.
Next time,
I’ll make you pay.
Your Highness, I know in your eyes
Yan Xun
is the best.
Whatever I do is wrong.
Here’s a friendly reminder
to Your Highness as well.
Don’t trust the wrong one
and get yourself hurt.
Yan Xun,
I got this ointment
from the Imperial Physician.
Apply it to your wound.
It’s just a scratch.
This is unnecessary.
Thank you for your help today,
Your Highness.
I appreciate it.
Yan Xun…
Your ointment.
Your Excellency, hold on.
Yan Xun, I am sorry
for what you went through.
I apologize
that I didn’t visit you.
What’s your point?
If you don’t like Her Highness,
don’t give her false hopes.
Will His Excellency make it back tonight?
He will.
You’re injured.
It is nothing serious.
You’d better go inside and have some rest.
I’ll wait here.
I am fine.
Yan Xun.
Your Excellency.
How are you?
We are fine.
What did Emperor say?
He flogged Wei Shuyou 20 times
and gave him home confinement.
That’s all?
Yes.
His Majesty never intended to
punish Wei Shuyou.
That was to send a message.
If he was punished too harshly,
everyone would act cautiously from now on.
No one
would ever
try to kill Yan Xun again.
Clearly,
that’s not His Majesty’s intention.
He only wants to control Yan Xun
in order to control Yanbei.
Yan Xun in danger
is easier for him to deal with
than him being safe.
Look likes we need to be
more careful from now on.
As long as we are still in Chang’an,
we need to be extremely careful.
He wants me dead.
And I want the same
for him.
= Pine Hall =
Achu.
There you are.
I think
we are safe for tonight.
I’ll sleep here.
You are wounded.
It’s nothing serious.
Let me see.
I am fine.
Let me check.
I have had it treated.
It’s stopped bleeding now.
Yan Xun.
Where are you going?
To get some medicine.
From where?
From Princess.
There are killers everywhere.
We are wounded.
Even if we are not killed by them,
you are committing a felony.
Please don’t
cause more trouble.
Yan Xun. Yan Xun.
Yan Xun. Be patient.
Hang in there.
I am fine.
Don’t lose your head
because of me.
We almost died.
We need to be
very careful.
Think about your family.
Think about your parents.
They are looking at you from heaven.
Don’t act rashly.
Be patient. Be patient.
Be patient, please.
Everything will be fine.
I am fine.
= Qingshan House =
Young Master.
Do you need anything else?
Gather Yue Guards.
Aye.
= Pleasure Pavilion =
Young Master Yue.
Please don’t make things difficult for us.
Young Master Huai is not here.
Young Master is here
to visit Master Xi’s wife,
not Young Master Huai.
Her Ladyship has been paralyzed for years.
Her condition is too bad
to meet with anyone.
When Young Master Huai is back,
you can come again.
= Pleasure Pavilion =
Yuwen Yue greets my lady.
How are you?
I am just
a dead woman walking.
How do you think I am?
You are Yue.
I have heard that
you’ve devoted yourself to Buddhism
since I was little.
I’m surprised to see
you imprisoned
in this secret chamber.
It has been sixteen years.
I am like a mouse
living in the dark.
I hope you won’t mind.
I am here
to ask you to check an old item.
This was what my mother
was changed into
in the Pleasure Pavilion.
Everyone said
only the lowest concubine in the Pavilion
would wear this Herbaceous peony dress.
Two months ago,
I found this dress
in the Pavilion.
I realized that
this is a peony dress
exclusive to the wife.
Herbaceous peony and peony
are similar
and this dress was damaged on purpose.
You are right.
This is mine.
My mother was framed.
They accused her of adultery
because she was found drunk
with Yuwen Xi that night
and changed into
a dress she didn’t even
recognize.
Yuwen Xi lied
to everyone.
Your mother was with me
that night.
With you?
I am the daughter of the Xie family
dating back to the Southern Dynasties.
I am your mother’s aunt.
That night, your mother came to visit me.
We had some liquor.
I asked your mother to stay for the night.
I’m sure you know
Yuwen Xi’s character.
I was afraid that your mother’s reputation
might be ruined,
so I activated the mechanism
and went down here.
I asked your mother
to change into this peony dress.
Then what happened?
Then?
It was a disaster.
That night,
Yuwen Xi went out his way
to trap me here
for 16 years.
Only two deaf maids are here
to watch and serve me.
How could he be so cruel?
Then why didn’t he kill you?
You think he didn’t want to?
He kept me alive
only for his greedy desires.
He hooked up with the spies from Liang.
I have talked too much today.
It takes time
to tell you everything.
Yuwen Yue.
Who let you in?
I came in myself.
Can’t you see it?
You started it.
Don’t blame me for it.
By the way,
I took your grandmother away.
You’d better
be smart
and give her back.
Or there will be a bloodbath
in Qingshan House.
Are you threatening me?
What do you think?
You may be fine
with being laughed at
for the internal strife.
But aren’t you afraid
your grandmother’s reappearance
will destroy
the entire Third Branch?
Once the secret is revealed,
I may not get away with it.
But you are also a Yuwen.
You can’t
stay out of it, either.
Fine. We’ll see.
If I told His Majesty
about your branch
colluding with the spies from Liang,
would he
let me off the hook
for telling the truth?
Yuwen Yue.
What the hell do you want?
I’m about to go to the border.
Wild wind, bad weather.
Not comfortable to live there.
While I am there suffering,
you can still
enjoy yourself in your mansion.
I don’t have a big heart. It upsets me.
How about this?
I have another place for you to stay.
Go guard the Imperial Mausoleum.
Because you are really good at
dealing with dead people.
I give you three days
to volunteer for the job.
I don’t want to see you in the city
before I leave.
Or,
I’ll send you to hell
to accompany your grandfather.
Yuwen Yue,
how dare you!
Young Master.
Come in.
Young Master, good news.
Yuwen Yue is leaving Chang’an
for the border
tomorrow morning.
Young… Young Master…
Why are you hitting me?
No reason.
You deserve it.
Your Highness.
I received a secret report.
Yuwen Xi’s wife
has been moved to Qingshan House
from the Pleasure Pavilion.
No wonder Yuwen Huai
volunteered
to guard the Imperial Mausoleum.
Yuwen Yue must’ve had
dirt on him.
You are really wise.
Your Excellency, as per His Majesty’s order,
we’ll be guarding this courtyard.
And Prince Yu asked me
to bring you this sword
to return it to its original owner.
Please extend my gratitude to him.
Aye.
Starting from tomorrow,
the lockdown will be lifted.
Except for His Excellency,
everyone has free access to the courtyard.
Your Excellency, it’s true
that Yuwen Huai and Yuwen Yue
will leave the city.
The Yuwen family won’t target us for now.
Although our biggest enemy Yuwen Huai
is gone,
we still need to be cautious.
I understand.
Taste the dishes
from my hometown.
Haven’t had these for a while.
Have they been tested?
Your Excellency.
Your Excellency, Ajing is here.
Ajing, do you remember me?
Your Excellency, I thought
I’d never see you again.
Get up.
Where is General Meng He?
Your Excellency.
My father died on the battlefield.
His last words were
to find you.
Luckily,
I survived the war.
Then I came to Chang’an.
I looked for you for three months
before finally meeting Zhong Yu.
Your Excellency, my father died a tragic death.
Rest assured.
We will take revenge for the deceased.
Your Excellency, I want to follow you around.
I can cook
and wrestle.
I will do whatever
I can for you.
Good.
You can be my guard.
Thank you, Your Excellency.
♪ The wind blows the moonlight ♪
♪ I’m born with a heart of fire ♪
♪ Who laughs at my humble beginnings ♪
♪ Fate has my wings broken ♪
♪ Fall into the abyss with the memories sealed ♪
♪ What an arrogant blizzard ♪
♪ Not looking up even if trampled again ♪
♪ I’ll get stronger and stronger ♪
♪ The breath is heat The heartbeat is light ♪
♪ Go forward bit by bit in a lifelong struggle ♪
♪ Tears hot in eyes light up the hope ♪
♪ No matter how much it hurts ♪
♪ I’m willing to burn my heart out ♪
♪ To melt the frost in the whole world ♪
♪ The moon knows my mind ♪
♪ So what if the road ahead is in endless dark ♪
♪ I want my heart burn like fire once again ♪
♪ Burning to be the light in the sky ♪
♪ Reborn from fire The world thrives ♪
♪ I’m blooming on the other side ♪
♪ Burning to be the light in the sky ♪