♪ Through thick and thin
you can get to know ♪
♪ You and I coexist
in the city of good and evil ♪
♪ That light leads me
to get out of my sorrow ♪
♪ It was meant to be you when we met ♪
♪ Desire ridicules tenderness
but never prevails ♪
♪ Yet I’m determined
to feed love everlastingly ♪
♪ Standing at the center of billow ♪
♪ Wind is my mind
and rain is my hunting ground ♪
♪ Look back to the time long gone ♪
♪ The torch in front is flaming ♪
♪ It gets dark
and the way ahead is still long ♪
♪ I know I can’t waver ♪
♪ Shedding blood to be the king
is the only way ♪
= Princess Agents =
= Episode 56 =
Your people provoked us at the Pass
and led me here.
This place is steep.
It seems that someone led us
here on purpose
to take your life.
Was it Cheng Yuan?
Did Yan Xun turn a blind eye to it?
Hatred in Yan Xun’s heart
is harder to melt
than the ice on this lake.
Yuwen Yue.
At first,
I simply wanted to get out
and live my own life.
Later, I met Yan Xun
and heard from him about Yanbei.
I felt my heart
starting to beat again.
I realized
I was born for a reason.
Maybe
that was my fate.
Unfortunately,
my dream was shattered
because I overestimated myself.
I thought I was capable enough
to make a difference
and protect others.
Eventually,
I realized
there wasn’t much I could do
on my own.
My friends and relatives
left me one by one.
I failed to protect them,
and many others…
Died because of me.
I’m not a good leader.
Xiuli Army didn’t have any belief
but they believed in me.
But I was the one
who put them into wars and danger
over and over,
causing them to shed blood and die.
The peaceful life
I promised them
never comes true.
I saved their lives once.
I should not be so selfish
to let them fight for me.
If...
I mean if...
If I had obeyed Yan Xun’s order
and expelled Xiuli Army from Yanbei,
then many of them
would not have died.
They would have still been alive.
Do you regret it?
I’ve been through a lot.
There’s never an easy path.
I have done so much
and come this far.
I’ve made mistakes, too.
But
I have never had regrets
because I always follow my heart.
I just...
I just feel tired.
If you are tired,
then stop
and take a break.
That way, you’ll be able
to move forward.
Roma wasn’t built
in a day.
Even without Cheng Yuan,
there’d be someone else.
What do you picture
Yanbei is like?
That everyone is loyal and brave?
That everyone is looking forward
to your return?
Where there are people,
there are disputes.
The one who can achieve big
has to go through plots and conspiracies,
life and death.
Since you have chosen this path,
you must finish it
at all costs.
Why are you telling me this?
Didn’t you try to stop me
from going back to Yanbei?
Instead of keeping you with me,
I hope
you can live
as your own will
and live happily.
Yuwen Yue.
I have never owed anyone
other than you.
I’m in so much debt to you
that I can never pay you back.
If you want to cry,
just let it out.
Pull yourself together after that.
♪ Because of you ♪
♪ I abandoned a city ♪
♪ I guess ♪
♪ I’m trying to find the balance of love ♪
♪ Because of you ♪
♪ I’m in pursuit of a lifetime ♪
♪ I am who I am ♪
♪ As if I had never left ♪
Yan Xun.
Have you forgotten about our promise?
♪ That person ♪
♪ Unlocked the gate ♪
♪ Melted the ice ♪
Have you forgotten about our promise?
♪ Explored the world with me ♪
♪ Because of you ♪
♪ I abandoned a city ♪
♪ I guess ♪
♪ I’m trying to remember
the look in your eyes ♪
♪ Because of this city ♪
♪ I lost you ♪
♪ In this battle of love ♪
♪ No one wins in the end ♪
= Yanbei Mansion =
Achu, it’s me.
Come in.
Achu.
I’m here to say goodbye.
Are you still mad at me
for not stepping out
to help you protect Xiuli Army?
You should know
His Highness had already
made his mind to kill them.
I wouldn’t be able to change his mind
but would only get people
I want to protect
into trouble.
So I had to stay out of it.
Now, I’m leaving for Lancheng.
Then I will escort Mr. Wu to leave Yanbei.
Mr. Wu?
Is that Mr. Wu
Wu Daoya?
Yes.
Cheng Yuan’s men went to Lancheng
to collect grains.
That city was hit by the flood.
Mr. Wu and
the locals
stood up to him
and he got imprisoned by His Highness.
Mr. Wu is the soul of Yanbei.
If he died,
all the others who were always loyal
would be bitterly disappointed
in His Highness.
So, I couldn’t help you.
Achu.
I am sorry.
You had your own reasons.
I understand that.
His Highness was an
innocent man.
But what happened on the Jiuyou Platform
has changed him
tremendously.
Things would never go
as we wished.
My concern is
if this continues,
we’ll be even further
from our original aspiration.
People change.
Achu, you know what?
I realize
the soldiers I see
patrolling in the streets
are not those
I know anymore.
It occurred to me
that those I knew
had either died in battles,
or left Yanbei.
Maybe
it’s time for me
to leave as well.
I understand how you feel.
I was in the same position as you were.
I witnessed
his hatred and pain.
his suffering.
We, as bystanders, could never
understand those feelings.
Everyone has the right
to choose how to live their lives.
It’s his choice.
I disagree with it,
but
I respect it.
Our decisions are not
always right,
but they aren’t always wrong either.
But there are principles
that we need to follow.
We can’t be partners,
but
we won’t be enemies either.
In this
chaotic time,
except for freedom
and love,
I’ll only risk my life
to keep
my faith.
And that
has already become
part of the plateau of Yanbei.
Zhong Yu.
Maybe we should go together.
I know you won’t.
Achu. His Highness can
rule the world
and conquer
every piece of land.
As long as he wants,
he can do whatever it takes
to destroy everything
that stands in his way.
But you’re different.
He can’t do anything about you.
Achu.
Don’t give up on him.
Only you can save him now.
Think about those days.
Think about how he struggled
to come this far.
Think about his suffering.
Don’t let hatred
blind him.
Don’t let bastards
like Cheng Yuan
succeed.
Before you leave,
could you do me a favor?
I’d like to meet with Mr. Wu.
Mr. Wu.
Chu Qiao. We’ve finally met.
It is quite difficult
to find you.
As the most trusted counselor
to Marquis Dingbei,
when he was killed,
you weren’t around.
When Yanbei was slaughtered,
you weren’t around, either.
When Ms. Bai Sheng killed herself
on the Jiuyou Platform,
when Yan Xun was nearly killed
during those three years in Chang’an,
and when he set Chang’an on fire,
when the war was on,
when Hongchuan was in danger,
you were never around.
I almost doubted
if you were still loyal to Yanbei
and whether I should
still meet with you.
This meeting
has nothing to do with Yanbei.
I think you knew that already.
I heard you lost your memory.
How are you now?
My memory hasn’t fully recovered.
I can vaguely remember some of it.
I happen to remember them quite well.
Since we have time today,
why don’t we catch up?
I only remember
bits and pieces
about my childhood.
Speed is the key to victory.
If you are fast enough,
you don’t need complicated skills.
One strike is enough to defeat your enemy.
- I can only remember
- Mother.
my mother wasn’t always around.
She was often away for months.
I could only practice martial art myself.
I didn’t know what she left to do.
She never told me, either.
One day, before she left,
she told me she wasn’t sure
when she’d be back.
Then she took me
to a secret place
and taught me the Ice Trick.
Then she told me to go to a family
of Jing.
I went there
and was renamed Jing Xiaoliu.
The Jings treated me as their own child.
I got along well with my siblings.
My skills also improved
with time.
But I couldn’t
forget about my mother.
She didn’t come back.
Only the bad news came.
I had to rescue her
because she was the only family I had
in this world.
I broke into the prison.
Mother.
I ran to my mother.
When I held her,
I saw a strange face
smirking at me.
That stranger and I
looked alike.
Mother is gone.
I rushed out
and attacked
by a huge crowd.
At that critical moment,
the woman who pretended to be my mother
came out of nowhere.
She pretended to be me and fought with
those in black
to buy me time to escape.
On my way out,
I heard someone in black
branded me as the one
who killed my mother.
If I say
you killed your mother, Luo He…
I never know why
that woman saved me.
It has haunted me
all these years.
The woman pretending to be you
is the killer from the Death Camp,
Xia Chong.
My memory is incomplete.
Who am I?
Your mother, Luo He,
was the owner of the Storm Token
and the leader of Underworld Spies.
You are her daughter, Chu Qiao.
Who killed my mother?
Yuwen Hao from Wei.
Yinxin from the Secret Service of Liang.
The real killer
is a traitor who was close to Luo He.
Why did they
kill my mother?
To protect the good
and get rid of the evil.
Your mother tried to free
slaves and end wars.
In the eyes of those rich lords,
she was evil.
She had been their enemy
for years.
The owner of the Storm Token
could command Underworld Spies.
She posed a threat to them.
What is the Storm Token?
Your mother had already
given it to you
without telling you.
Once you mastered the Ice Trick,
an equinox flower would appear on your shoulder.
That is the Storm Token.
Your mother wrote to me in secret
that she had transferred
most of her energy
to you.
Therefore,
you are the new owner of the Storm Token.
I don’t have any flower
on my shoulder.
Nor do I practice the Ice Trick, either.
I am not some almighty
Storm Token holder.
Maybe your loss of memory
has blocked your energy.
Maybe only the extremely cold weather
could stimulate you
to perform that skill.
Zuo Baocang helped me recover
some of my memory by hypnosis.
Unfortunately, it was interrupted.
What else do you know
about my background,
Mr. Wu?
I know what happened
after you got out of the prison.
I sent Zhongyi,
the Snake Maid and the Untraceable
to rescue Luo He.
But they arrived too late.
The Snake Maid fought her way out
and saved you.
At that time, you were badly wounded.
They escorted you to escape.
However,
Yuwen Hao and his men were after you.
Yuwen Hao was a valiant general.
His family, the Yuwen Household,
had full control over the Eye of Intel,
Underworld Spies’ mortal enemy
for generations.
He was cruel
and wanted to catch you alive.
The Snake Maid was extremely loyal
because your mother, Luo He,
saved her life.
She sacrificed her life
in order to save you.
She fought with Yuwen Hao
with her last breath
and almost died.
Go!
In the end, the Untraceable
stalled Yuwen Hao with his life.
The Snake Maid and you managed to escape.
Unfortunately, the spy from Liang,
Yinxin, ambushed you.
The Snake Maid fainted.
You knocked Yinxin out in rage
and fought with Yuwen Hao.
In the end, you killed him
with the Ice Trick
but fell into the Yellow River.
The Snake Maid managed
to find me.
When we learnt
that you fell into the river,
we sent people searching for you
along the bank for ten days
but to no avail.
Turns out
you were taken by traffickers.
Since then, your fate has changed.
Who would know
you would end up being a slave
in the Yuwen Household
serving Yuwen Yue,
your archenemy?
Who would know
after all these years,
you killed three generations
of the third branch of the Yuwen Household
to take your revenge?
Then you followed Yan Xun
back to Yanbei
where your mother
guarded with her life.
Maybe it was
all predestined.
Now, the truth is out.
I know
you, Yuwen Yue and Yan Xun
have a complicated relationship.
You need to choose
between them.
I want you to help Yanbei
to restore peace.
Will you?
I no longer
belong here.
You should come with me.
As Luo He’s daughter,
you should continue
her unfinished mission.
I am sorry, but I don’t remember
much about what happened in the past.
Thank you for your honesty.
I can’t leave with you.
I cannot
allow Yan Xun
to drown in hatred.
I will do my best
to help him ashore.
Princess.
I have been looking for you for two months
and finally found you.
Princess.
How did you find me?
My instinct told me
that Your Highness would take
this direction,
so I searched for you along the way.
Meilin Pass is five kilometers away.
That’s where Yuwen Yue is.
Even you have noticed that.
I have been with you for years.
I can read
Your Highness’s mind a little bit.
In the past few months,
I allowed myself to drift
and wander
because
I found out Yue is actually Yuwen Yue.
I kept writing letters
to my archenemy
who I had treated as a close friend.
Heaven played
such a cruel joke on me.
I know I can’t let him live.
But I don’t have the heart
to kill him.
What should I do?
I really don’t know.
Princess.
I understand your feeling, Princess.
I’ve kept this to myself for long.
Do you want to hear it?
Say it.
In my eyes,
noble as you are as a princess,
you’re never
a delicate little girl.
You’re ambitious,
thorough
and decisive.
You’re as good
as any man if not better.
Princess,
how could you
stop by
that Yuwen Yue?
I know what you mean.
It’s easier said
than done.
Princess.
Chaos is rising.
Chang’an was besieged.
Hongchuan was almost lost.
Rebels are taking this chance
to stir up trouble everywhere.
All that
concerns the future of Liang.
Princess, you are
the future ruler of Liang.
You cannot
give up your state for anything.
Whether it’s Liang or Wei,
at this stage,
I simply
want to stay away from the mess.
Why can’t I?
I know
how painful you are.
You’re caught
between the love of your life
and the state that raised you.
Does Yuwen Yue know any of this?
Think about it.
If you two switched places,
and put him
in this dilemma,
what choice would he make?
Would he betray his state
for you?
To Your Highness.
How is everything?
Thank you for saving Yuan Chun’s life.
Prince Yu really appreciates it
after knowing it.
The border is in peace now.
Yan Xun is still holding a grudge
and coveting our land,
but our troops at Meilin are well-trained.
They are solid in defense,
enough to battle Yanbei’s cavalrymen
before making peace with them.
So you can be at ease, Your Highness.
Sincerely, Yuwen Yue.
Guards.
Yes, Young Master.
Send this letter
directly to Prince Xiang.
Aye.
Waiter, where’s our food?
Coming right up!
Fill the cup.
Let’s drink.
Please enjoy.
Here comes your dish.
Let’s eat.
Enjoy your dish.
Put it here.
All is here.
Please enjoy.
Coming.
Come in.
Princess.
The messenger has been silenced.
= To Your Highness =
Peace negotiation is only an excuse.
Hate can’t be erased easily.
It won’t be
that easy to make peace.
This matter is of great significance.
Yuan Che may not believe it
with just a letter.
The more pressing the situation is,
the less the time for him to think.
And I’ve had eyes
on the Death Camp for so long.
It’s easy to tap into
their communication channel.
Not to mention I am familiar with
every word, every move
and every plan
of Yuwen Yue’s.
They won’t be able to tell
the difference between us.
The rest is up to you.
Aye.
In the turbulent days,
shelter is hard to be found.
I want to be a rock
however the river flows.
I’ll always stand still,
wherever leaves fall.
Who are you?
In such chaos,
I no longer remember who I am.
You, Young Master Yue,
are the only one to wake me up.
So I invited you over.
You read my letter.
Are you…?
Yes.
Yue, it’s me Xiaoyu.
I never expected
that the one writing to me
was you,
my archenemy.
Spies of Liang and the Eye of Intel
are born enemies
as if they were meant to
fight against each other.
I never asked to take charge of the spies.
You and I are the chosen ones.
Nothing outweighs national interests.
I’m glad
to have been given
the wooden bird.
Many things
I couldn’t tell others
could be shared with you.
I found another me,
the real me.
Likewise.
I could share my feelings
and suffering
with Xiaoyu.
Because I am
your most loyal friend
who can keep your secrets.
You are.
What a pity…
I will ruin the wooden bird
and bury Xiaoyu in my memory.
♪ The wind blows the moonlight ♪
♪ I’m born with a heart of fire ♪
♪ Who laughs at my humble beginnings ♪
♪ Fate has my wings broken ♪
♪ Fall into the abyss
with the memories sealed ♪
♪ What an arrogant blizzard ♪
♪ Not looking up even if trampled again ♪
♪ I’ll get stronger and stronger ♪
♪ The breath is heat
The heartbeat is light ♪
♪ Go forward bit by bit
in a lifelong struggle ♪
♪ Tears hot in eyes light up the hope ♪
♪ No matter how much it hurts ♪
♪ I’m willing to burn my heart out ♪
♪ To melt the frost in the whole world ♪
♪ The moon knows my mind ♪
♪ So what if the road ahead
is in endless dark ♪
♪ I want my heart burn
like fire once again ♪
♪ Burning to be the light in the sky ♪
♪ Reborn from fire The world thrives ♪
♪ I’m blooming on the other side ♪
♪ Burning to be the light in the sky ♪