♪ Through thick and thin
you can get to know ♪
♪ You and I coexist
in the city of good and evil ♪
♪ That light leads me
to get out of my sorrow ♪
♪ It was meant to be you when we met ♪
♪ Desire ridicules tenderness
but never prevails ♪
♪ Yet I’m determined
to feed love everlastingly ♪
♪ Standing at the center of billow ♪
♪ Wind is my mind
and rain is my hunting ground ♪
♪ Look back to the time long gone ♪
♪ The torch in front is flaming ♪
♪ It gets dark
and the way ahead is still long ♪
♪ I know I can’t waver ♪
♪ Shedding blood to be the king
is the only way ♪
= Princess Agents =
= Episode 58 =
This time, I came here
for personal business.
Don’t worry.
I’m done eating.
See you.
Yuwen Yue,
we’ll soon meet again on the battlefield.
That’s our fate.
When that happens,
don’t be soft on me.
I...
Xing’er,
be honest,
if we’re against each other
on the battlefield,
will you chop my head off?
I won’t kill you,
but I’ll do my best
to beat you.
Really?
I can’t do the same.
The world we live in
is like a jungle.
Don’t be affected
by emotions.
No feelings, no pain.
Otherwise,
hearts will be broken.
Excruciating pain can’t be avoided.
No feelings, no pain?
I’m afraid that’s too late for me.
Has Yuwen Yue come back?
Not yet.
The risk is too high.
We must send reinforcements
to back them up.
Also,
is your information true
that Yuan Che is coming with troops?
It is.
He’s been discussing peace talks
with Yuwen Yue.
That makes his arrival suspicious.
Yuwen Yue went to Xiuli Mountain
and met with Achu?
Correct.
Messages just arrived
from our scouts there.
It’s true.
He was there.
Report!
Your Highness,
Prince Yuan Che of Wei
is heading towards
Meilin Pass with his army.
What are they up to?
Your Highness, I’m not sure
if I should say this.
Get to the point!
Miss Chu is
prejudiced against me
and she’s holding
a grudge against you too.
You’d better take precautions.
She wouldn’t harm me.
What about Yuwen Yue?
Would he also do nothing?
What are you implying?
Your Highness,
why don’t we take this chance
to get rid of Yuwen Yue for good?
Now that he’s here,
don’t let him leave.
Lately, we’ve lost
tons of men at Meilin Pass because of him.
And now, he’s poking around
in our hinterland.
Clearly, he has an agenda.
Under his leadership,
his fort is full of troops and supplies.
His force
is well-equipped.
Now, Wei’s prince
is coming to assist him.
We must do something
or Yanbei will be in danger.
Your Highness, I understand
you two go way back,
but there’s no friendship
in war.
Every misstep,
every bit of hesitation
will cost
tens of thousands
of our men’s lives.
I hope
you can put our mission first.
Pass my order.
Gather the crack troops
to kill Yuwen Yue.
Aye.
Stop.
Brother,
why are you here with the army?
I received Yuwen Yue’s letter
saying Yan Xun refused to make peace
and he was going to
launch attacks again.
Is that so?
He wrote that to me.
It can’t be wrong.
Brother, we don’t know
if what he said is true.
If you strike now,
civilians will suffer
and peace will never be restored.
We can’t keep procrastinating.
I’m going in.
Don’t, brother!
Step aside!
Move!
No!
Your Highness!
Let’s go!
Stop, all of you!
I’m Duke Yanbei conferred by His Majesty
and Prince Yuan Song of Wei.
Who gave you the right
to attack my fief?
My target is
that rebel Yan Xun.
He controls Yanbei
and refuses to make peace with us.
He must be eliminated
to rebuild our prestige.
Brother,
Yan Xun revolts against us for a reason.
I suggest we be humble
and clear his family’s name
before holding the talk.
If that doesn’t get him around the table,
you can still
resort to force then.
Yuan Song,
why are you taking
that traitor’s side?
Has the wind in Yanbei
damaged your brain?
Do you still remember
you’re a Yuan?
That bastard almost
took Chang’an.
He killed thousands
of our people.
Our brother Yuan Qi
was killed in Hongchuan.
Have you forgotten all that?
Of course not!
What about
the deceased
on the Jiuyou Platform?
What about
those innocent people of Yanbei
killed in the battle?
You’re grieving
for the death of your family.
So are the bereaved
and Yan Xun!
Ridiculous!
Don’t equate that rat
with a noble prince!
Whoever we are, we only have one life.
Brother,
I didn’t understand
until I lost my arm
how painful
and how desperate
the disabled were.
Do you know
how many arms and legs
and even lives a war costs?
Brother,
I’m begging you.
Please withdraw your force.
Don’t stand in my way,
or they’ll
ride over you.
Go ahead.
If that can stop you
from raiding Yanbei
and protect those in Hongchuan
from the war,
I’m at your disposal.
Hadn’t Father
suspected Marquis Dingbei
and slaughtered his entire clan,
things wouldn’t have gotten to this stage.
It’s Father’s fault.
Why are you
turning a blind eye to it?
I will not allow you
to make more mistakes
and inflict more suffering
on the innocent.
If you insist on moving forward,
get over
my dead body first!
Young Master, watch out for ambush.
Yuwen Yue is the target.
Follow me.
They’re gone.
Yes.
We let them out on purpose.
Yuwen Yue is at home
with this place.
Their people are few
and they move fast.
We lost them in the woods.
His Highness is going after them.
Go back
and head to Xiuli Mountain with our troops
to arrest Chu Qiao
and take her back to Hongchuan
in the name of conniving with enemies.
General,
once His Highness finds out about this,
he won’t be easy on you.
I’m not afraid of death.
But once the Wei Army arrives,
Yuwen Yue will kill His Highness.
Forget about peace talks.
They’re nothing but lies.
To achieve big,
one can’t be sentimental.
As long as Chu Qiao is around,
His Highness won’t strike Wei.
We have to let him know
she’s in love with someone else.
And tell Zhou An
it’s time
to proceed with his mission.
He can rest in peace.
Yanbei won’t forget him.
Let’s see
after knowing that,
whether Yuwen Yue will leave Yanbei
or not.
Young Master,
we caught him snooping around.
He demands to see you
for emergency.
General Yuwen,
I’m Miss Chu’s man,
Zhou An, commander of the Xiuli Army.
Miss Chu asked me
to report something important to you.
Isn’t He Xiao
the commander?
He was killed in the battle,
so I took over his place.
Miss Chu said
your whereabouts are no longer secret.
Whatever you’re here for,
you must leave immediately.
Xiuli Mountain has been surrounded
by the Back Eagle Army.
You can’t get out.
She’s arranged for an exit
at Yao Mountain.
You can leave through it
if you trust her.
His Highness’s force
is coming.
Leave now
before it’s too late.
What happened to her?
And
how did Commander He die?
I’m only here
to deliver that message.
I can’t tell you anything else.
You said all that
without anything concrete.
How are we supposed to trust you?
Be honest. Don’t you dare lie!
His Highness knew you had come here
and met with
Miss Chu.
He ordered her to kill you
but she refused to
and she had others stop Cheng Yuan’s men
from assassinating you.
They even engaged in a fight.
General, leave now,
or members of the Xiuli Army
would die in vain
and so would
Commander He.
Where is she now?
She was battling the Black Eagle Army
when I left.
I’m not sure where she is now.
I’ve said what I should
and shouldn’t say.
I disobeyed Miss Chu’s order
and shouldn’t serve her anymore.
General, go!
If you’re blessed
to get out safe and sound,
please
stay away from her
or take her away.
Don’t put her
into such a dilemma again.
Young Master,
don’t trust him.
What did the intelligence say
yesterday?
The Black Eagle Army branched out
into three columns
to the hinterland
in the direction of Xiuli Mountain.
All prefectures and counties
along the way
set up roadblocks.
The militia was constantly
on the move.
But all that doesn’t mean anything.
It’s likely
to be a trap
Yan Xun set for us.
If it was Yan Xun,
since he could’ve tracked us down,
Yan Xun could’ve come at us
with his force.
Why go through so much trouble?
Perhaps
someone is trying to
get rid of you
in Yan Xun’s name.
That makes sense.
Zhao Kuang’s men
at Meilin Pass
always hold a grudge
against you.
Maybe they followed us
all the way to Yanbei
and tipped Yan Xun off.
It could also be Yan Xun’s general
Cheng Yuan,
or someone
from Chang’an.
Yes, Young Master.
This whole thing is fishy.
I agree.
But what if it’s true?
It’s most certainly not.
I bet
someone is waiting for us
to rise to the bait.
And if you’re wrong?
I started this.
I must see her to be sure.
Young Master.
Miss Chu, a message came from Hongchuan.
We’re accused of conniving with enemies
and disclosing military secrets.
They’re going to arrest you
and take you back to Hongchuan
for questioning.
Is that Yan Xun’s order?
Only a verbal command.
Who’s the messenger?
He claimed to be a Black Eagle
but I know him.
He’s Cheng Yuan’s man.
Tie him up.
Take 20 men
to go to Hongchuan with me.
Aye.
Prince Yu.
Your Highness, don’t worry too much.
You’ve done your best.
Anything about Yuwen Yue?
And my brother?
Our source of information is limited
but what we do know is
Prince Xiang’s force
has camped 25 kilometers
away from
Meilin Pass.
My guess is
if Young Master Yue isn’t back,
Prince Xiang will level Yanbei.
I’m so useless.
The war must stop.
Barbarians are invading us from the north.
Liang is also coveting our land.
Wei is falling apart.
The world has returned
to the chaotic state.
Everyone is suffering.
It’s all my fault.
Your Highness.
Trust me,
Young Master Yue will be back.
He knows what to do.
He’s our only hope.
What’s up, Miss Chu?
It doesn’t feel right.
What’s wrong?
Yan Xun is crazy.
I’m not his target.
Yuwen Yue is.
What to do now?
We split up.
You and the Xiuli Army
head to Meilin Pass.
I’ll meet you there.
Sure.
Everyone, follow me!
Yan Xun,
do you know what you are doing?
You tell me.
Where’s Yuwen Yue?
I’ve shot him to death.
Why did you kill him?
A Wei general
sneaked into
our hinterland.
Why couldn’t I
kill him?
Achu, do you honestly
care more about him
than me and Yanbei combined?
You could kill him.
You could kill him fair and square
on the battlefield.
But how could you use me
and his feelings for me?
We had a deal.
That we’d show no mercy
on each other in war.
Achu,
as the ruler of Yanbei,
there are things I have to do.
Don’t you understand
all that I’ve done is for you?
You slaughtered my soldiers and army.
You deprived me of our ambition.
You exiled me,
suspected me, used me,
doubted me and spied on me.
All that is for my sake?
I’m trying to protect you.
That’s your so-called protection?
Achu,
I only have one question.
Have you
ever loved me?
I’m not sure what I have for you
is love or not.
All I know is
I care so much about you.
I can’t allow others to hurt you.
Your dream is my dream.
Your hometown
is my hometown.
Your status, safety
gains and losses
mean the most to me
over the years.
My biggest dream
is to go back to Yanbei
with you
and watch you return home intact
as you’ve ever wanted.
I’ve lost my family
and memory.
All these years,
you mean the world to me.
You’re the hope of my life.
But now, I start to question
if all that I’ve done
is worth it.
Do I know the real you?
Yan Xun,
since you arrived in Yanbei,
your suspicion has started to grow.
You suspect Zhong Yu.
You suspect Mr. Wu.
You suspect me.
You suspect everyone who might pose
a threat to your rule.
You’ve become a slave
to power.
Your hatred and grudge
are only tools to serve
your selfish desires.
Yan Xun,
I don’t blame you for killing Yuwen Yue
but the way you killed him
is despicable.
You shouldn’t have abused
my loyalty.
You shouldn’t have taken advantage of
our relationship.
Now, as you wish,
I’m going to find Yuwen Yue.
Here’s my last warning.
If he’s killed in Yanbei,
I’ll never forgive you.
Move!
No!
Fine!
Too bad, you’re late!
Save Young Master.
He’s at the Icy Lake...
Go, Miss Chu.
I’ll cover you.
Take care.
Run!
Yuwen Yue!
- Yuwen Yue.
- Xing’er.
I’m here.
Leave.
Go.
No.
I’m not going anywhere.
I won’t leave.
Xing’er, be good.
I’m sorry.
I won’t leave you ever again.
Hang in there.
Stay with me.
Hang in there!
Get up.
Get up, Yuwen Yue!
Get up!
Go... Go now.
Leave!
No!
No! No!
Wake up, Yuwen Yue.
Achu, you said I had changed.
Truth is, I’m always the same.
It’s just you never know
what I truly want.
Now,
I’ve shown you
my belief and ambition
in this way.
Your Highness, the ice is too fragile
to hold more weight.
Wait for me.
No!
Yuwen Yue!
Live on.
Don’t give up.
Stay with me.
Don’t leave me alone.
Don’t give up.
Yuwen Yue!
♪ The wind blows the moonlight ♪
♪ I’m born with a heart of fire ♪
♪ Who laughs at my humble beginnings ♪
♪ Fate has my wings broken ♪
♪ Fall into the abyss
with the memories sealed ♪
♪ What an arrogant blizzard ♪
♪ Not looking up even if trampled again ♪
♪ I’ll get stronger and stronger ♪
♪ The breath is heat
The heartbeat is light ♪
♪ Go forward bit by bit
in a lifelong struggle ♪
♪ Tears hot in eyes light up the hope ♪
♪ No matter how much it hurts ♪
♪ I’m willing to burn my heart out ♪
♪ To melt the frost in the whole world ♪
♪ The moon knows my mind ♪
♪ So what if the road ahead
is in endless dark ♪
♪ I want my heart burn
like fire once again ♪
♪ Burning to be the light in the sky ♪
♪ Reborn from fire The world thrives ♪
♪ I’m blooming on the other side ♪
♪ Burning to be the light in the sky ♪