♪ Through thick and thin
you can get to know ♪
♪ You and I coexist
in the city of good and evil ♪
♪ That light leads me
to get out of my sorrow ♪
♪ It was meant to be you when we met ♪
♪ Desire ridicules tenderness
but never prevails ♪
♪ Yet I’m determined
to feed love everlastingly ♪
♪ Standing at the center of billow ♪
♪ Wind is my mind
and rain is my hunting ground ♪
♪ Look back to the time long gone ♪
♪ The torch in front is flaming ♪
♪ It gets dark
and the way ahead is still long ♪
♪ I know I can’t waver ♪
♪ Shedding blood to be the king
is the only way ♪
= Princess Agents =
= Episode 43 =
Chun.
Brother.
What happened to you?
It’s all because of Chu Qiao.
Without her,
nothing would have happened.
It’s all because of her.
Chu Qiao?
If you catch her,
you will catch the traitor,
Yan Xun.
Just go and catch her.
Yuan Song.
Where did Chu Qiao go?
That way.
Let’s go.
Yes.
Please calm down, Your Majesty.
Fortunately,
the Thirteenth Prince and Princess Chun
have come back safe and sound.
They’re not!
My most beloved son
has become disabled.
Pass my decree.
Capture that traitor Yan Xun.
Bring back him or his body.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, what about the maidservant
who escaped with Yan Xun?
Kill her as well. No exception.
Aye.
Darling,
you look unwell.
I know that you are worried about Hao.
But you still need to
take care of yourself.
I have already sent out
Court of Judicial Review,
palace guards
and the government of Chang’an.
There will be news about Hao soon.
Your Majesty.
Your Grace,
Zhu Siliu from the Hongshan House
of the Yuwen Household is here.
He must know what happened to Hao.
He must know it.
Send him in.
Aye.
You found Hao, didn’t you?
You found my son, didn’t you?
Your Grace, I know
that you are worried about Prince.
I have searched everywhere
for him.
But... I...
Where is he?
Your Grace, it’s all
Yuwen Huai’s fault.
I searched every corner.
By the time I found him,
it was already too late.
Prince.
Open it.
I said open it!
Don’t, Your Grace.
You can’t see it.
Move!
Your Grace.
I knew
someone like me
didn’t deserve a good life.
Your Grace, please don’t say that.
But
I’m the sinner.
If you want to punish anyone,
please punish me.
Why did you
take my son away?
He was so young.
It’s you, isn’t it?
You couldn’t keep
your own kid,
so you just sent your daughter
to take mine away,
didn’t you?
Your daughter
has stolen everything from me.
She killed my son.
I’ll let her pay.
Killing you
would be too easy.
Castrate him.
- Aye.
Your Grace!
Move!
Your Grace, please just kill me.
Your Grace!
Give me a quick death!
Kill me now!
Your Grace!
Listen,
from now on,
you’re my servant
because you owe me.
Yes, Your Grace.
Your Excellency,
our people are back.
There is no sign of Miss Achu.
It’s been days
but you still haven’t found anything
about her.
Your Excellency, we tried our best.
Keep looking.
Send in more men.
You must bring Achu back.
Understand?
Your Excellency,
right after that prince
and princess returned,
Miss Achu was
on the wanted list.
Right now,
the order for arrest
with Miss Achu’s portrait
has been spread
all over the state.
The entire state is searching for
Miss Chu.
They bite the hand that feeds.
Ajing.
Send out my order.
Whoever lays a finger
on Achu,
I will
slaughter his entire family.
Aye.
Your Highness. Young Master Wei is here.
Your Highness?
Your Highness, it’s me.
Your Highness.
Chun.
Come in.
I am so glad that
you’ve returned safely.
I was so worried about you
that I couldn’t eat or sleep.
Thank heaven,
you’re safe.
Otherwise…
Wei Shuye,
you fancy me, right?
I…
I’ll be with you
only on one condition.
Chun…
Are you leaving now?
Yes.
Where to?
Before Yan Xun escaped from Chang’an,
we arrested a spy
from the Liang State
and managed to get a detailed confession.
That information
helped us to get rid of
Liang spies planted in Chang’an.
Then we followed this lead
and acquired the entire network
of their spies throughout the state.
They were involved in
Marquis Dingbei’s case
and the riot in Chang’an.
This time,
I’ll wipe them all out.
After I leave,
you need to be careful.
Take care.
I heard that maid
who escorted Princess
and Prince Yu back to Chang’an
is separated from the Xiuli Army
and has become a wanted criminal.
Yes.
If you come across her,
what will you do?
Grandfather,
what do you think I should do?
I am not telling you to kill her,
but I hope you won’t
get involved with her again.
You are disobeying my order?
You were just like me.
You’d rather break your legs
to protect
that woman.
Why are you
forcing me to give her up now?
Because I regret what I did.
Does that surprise you?
I was too young.
Her sweet talk fooled me
and clouded my judgment.
I risked my future
and ruined my life.
I let the entire family down,
and broke their hearts
for a woman who betrayed me
and my love
and didn’t belong to me
from the very beginning.
What’s wrong?
Shouldn’t I regret it?
If you could turn back time,
would you do nothing
and just let that woman die?
Maybe you’d regret
what you did
many years later.
But if I don’t do it now,
I will definitely regret it.
Please excuse me.
Those who are competent
should serve the court.
When the state is in peace,
the legislators should revise the law.
According to the poem,
even a great power will be afraid of you.
Don’t be nosy when you are out there.
Better safe than sorry.
Mencius says…
Mencius says,
“a gentleman should always
keep benevolence
and manners in mind”.
Always be caring and respectful.
But…
If someone is bullying the weak
and I walk away without doing anything,
won’t that be the opposite of benevolence?
Daibao,
we’re living in a peaceful world.
There won’t be any bad people, right?
I think
if I come across two farmers arguing,
I can stop them
and let them make peace with each other.
That will be all,
right?
You agree with me, right?
Daibao, am I right?
What…
Daibao,
are you taking the wrong path?
My name is Liang Shaoqing.
I accidentally
took the wrong path and ended up here.
I am leaving now.
Right now.
I am going.
Daibao,
let’s go. Why aren’t you moving?
let’s go.
Well…
Look,
you people
are ganging up on a girl.
That’s unfair.
There is an old saying that
fairness is upheld by the world,
while unfairness won’t survive.
What you’re doing is unfair.
I can report your case to the government.
Let’s go to court.
Your dispute
can be easily resolved there.
Other than that,
you can tell me
what happened.
I can help you make peace.
Shut up.
Well…
You are
a delicate girl.
How could you
battle those men?
Look, they are all
holding swords.
What if they hurt you?
You’d better
come with me.
If something is
bothering you,
I can be of help.
No more violence.
It is uncivil.
Look…
Why are you on my horse?
We shouldn’t be so close.
My books! My money!
My poems!
My pass!
Why are you doing this?
Stop right there!
You…
How could you
be so rude?
I saved you,
but you threw
all my money and stuff away.
How dare you!
I guess I am just in bad luck.
What a day!
Let’s go, Daibao.
Let’s go.
He was running too fast,
and needs some rest.
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
To get back
all my stuff.
Do you want to die?
I’d be dead if I lost them.
Without the pass,
how can I get into the city?
How can I stay in an inn?
Besides,
I have nothing to do with them.
What could those officials
possibly do to me?
You recognized
who they are.
Do you know who I am?
You saved me.
They probably think
you are my accomplice.
You are Daibao, right?
Thank you for saving me.
Miss,
I am the one who saved you,
not him.
Why did you thank a horse
instead of me?
Daibao,
I am sorry.
I am not speaking ill of you.
You saved me?
When did that happen?
Why didn’t I know?
I saved you,
but you didn’t even thank me.
How could you treat me like this?
And you even humiliated me.
Did you kill those officials?
Did you
carry me to escape?
You did nothing.
Why should I thank you for saving me?
Am I right, Daibao?
You…
I…
I went to
reason with them.
I solved the mess
and then…
Then what?
Did they put down their swords
and let us leave?
It is good
that you have a sense of justice.
But don’t forget to use your brain.
Don’t bite off more than you can chew.
Without your horse,
we would be dead by now.
I…
You won’t be able to
get your things back.
Take this
as my compensation.
I…
I am sorry
that you lost your pass.
You can report the loss to the government.
It’s not safe here.
I’ll escort you to the next town.
How about this?
I don’t want your money.
I am a mature
and honest man.
I won’t be safe
if I am with you.
Why were those officials
after a young girl
like you?
You are either a felon
or a thief.
Let’s go. Come on.
Let’s go.
Come.
Daibao, let’s go.
Nerd.
You really don’t need this money?
Xianyang is right ahead.
Without money, how could you get in?
I would rather die than take your money.
Your Excellency,
we are about to arrive in Hongchuan.
When I left Yanbei,
this is where my father
bid me farewell.
Back then,
all dukes guarding the border
were asked to
send one of their children
to Chang’an as a hostage.
No one responded.
Then Emperor wrote to
my father.
He read the letter,
turned around
and asked me and my two brothers,
“does any of you
volunteer to go to Chang’an?
You’ll only be there for a year”.
My eldest brother asked my father,
“aren’t the Emperor
and you are sworn brothers?
Why is he doubting you?”
My father responded,
“we’re closer than others.
If I don’t support him,
no one will”.
That day, I decided
I would go to Chang’an.
Because he was my father.
If I didn’t support him,
who would?
♪ I hope my palm ♪
♪ Can heal the wound ♪
♪ And bury the pain ♪
♪ I hope my chest ♪
♪ Can shield the blade ♪
Open the gate.
♪ Protect this land ♪
It’s me, Yan Xun. I am back.
♪ I hope my wish ♪
Open the gate.
♪ Will resonate forever ♪
♪ It’s everyone’s belief ♪
♪ I hope my sacrifice ♪
= Hongchuan =
I’m the Prince of Yanbei.
♪ Will make good on the promise ♪
Open the gate.
♪ I’ll come to you in the next life ♪
I’m the Prince of Yanbei, Yan Xun.
= Hongchuan =
Open the gate!
Yanbei,
I’m back!
I’ve changed.
Have you?
Your Excellency.
General Cheng, where are the leaders
of all tribes?
Your Excellency, we went 10 kilometers
outside the city to check,
but saw no one coming.
Did you send the invitation letters
to them?
Of course.
And the date is said
to be today?
Yes.
Then why no one is here?
Your Excellency,
maybe something happened
on the way.
I’ll go and check again.
No need.
Your Excellency,
since the letters were sent out
three days ago,
no one has shown up.
The only possibility is that
they’ve never meant to come.
Why?
You burned Chang’an
fighting your way back to Yanbei.
Right now,
who doesn’t know your name?
The Emperor of Wei lost his dignity.
He won’t let it go.
I’m sure he will gather his troops
to attack Yanbei.
By then, the eight tribes
will have to battle the army of Wei.
They’re intimidated.
They were allies of
my father’s.
I thought they could
be of help.
It seems I was thinking too much.
I heard Huotu Tribe
is holding a beef feast today.
The leaders of all tribes
will attend.
Huotu Tribe?
Headed by Agutu
former leader Enge’s younger brother.
Enge is your father’s sworn brother.
When Beishuo was attacked,
Enge led his troops to help
but was killed
by Agutu on the way.
Agutu killed Enge, took his wife
and slaughtered
all his sons.
He is known as a wolf
on the grassland.
If you set off now,
you may be able to attend the feast
in time.
Let’s go.
I’ll lead the way.
Your Excellency,
Mr. Wu is on his way here.
Let him deal with
things here.
Since I am back,
no need to trouble him.
Wait for him here.
We’ll be back soon.
Your Excellency!
Your Excellency.
This is the new plaque.
Zhong Yu said
we can hang it up
after declaring war on Wei.
Hang it up now.
Are you deaf?
What are you waiting for?
His Excellency says to hang it up now.
= Yanbei Mansion =
This saber is called Phoenix.
It’s said to be owned by Bai Qi,
a famous general
in the Warring States period.
Because of the demon spirit sealed in it,
it needs to be fed with blood.
Do not waste it.
Thank you, Your Excellency.
= Yanbei Mansion =
Come on.
Here, fill your cup.
Let’s toast leader.
Fill it.
Leader.
Drink up.
Listen,
that beast Yan Xun
intends to drag us all down
with him.
In his dreams!
Look at his father,
the Lion King of Yanbei,
who was invincible for 20 years
in or outside the border.
Still, he was beheaded
so quickly.
Yes.
That’s right.
Come on. Let’s drink.
Come on.
Drink up.
But
I heard on his wedding day,
he refused the marriage
right in front of the Emperor
and painted Chang’an with blood
with his men.
That’s really something.
That’s bluffing.
Yes.
Painted the city with blood?
Did you see that yourself?
Drink!
Drink up! Drink up!
I... I’ll drink.
Fill the cup.
Yes.
- Don’t bluff about him.
- Yes.
That kid simply
took a chance to
sneak out of Chang’an.
Then he ran all the way back to Yanbei
like a defeated dog.
He was sent to Chang’an
when he was a child.
He enjoyed a comfortable life there
for so long
that he no longer
has the backbone
to wield his saber.
Yes, right.
Once the war begins,
he cannot beat this girl.
That’s right.
Yes.
Right.
Let’s drink.
Here.
Let me fill your cup.
Come on.
Who are you?
What are you here for?
I am asking you.
Are you all deaf...
Sit down.
Let me introduce myself.
I’m Yan Xun,
your new king.
Young Master,
Xianyang is right ahead of us.
Over there.
This way, please.
Is everything done
as requested?
Yes, Young Master.
Upon receiving the secret message,
I found three hidden strongholds of
Liang spies in Xianyang
following
your order.
The biggest one is here
and is likely the most important one.
But we came too late.
When we broke in,
all the secret letters here
had been burnt into ashes.
The spies here
had killed themselves with poison.
Who are they?
She is
the chef here
to cook meals.
That is her son,
said to be a local.
He doesn’t know anything.
Please!
Do not kill my baby!
We do not know anything.
Please let us go!
Come here, kid.
No, don’t.
My baby!
No!
What are you doing? Let me go!
Let me go!
My baby!
Is she your mom?
Where is your mom?
Take her away.
Interrogate her.
Aye.
Kid,
do you have any other relatives?
From now on,
he’s yours.
I…
But… Young Master,
I am not even married.
How can I have a son
all of a sudden?
Young Master cares about you.
If you remain single forever,
at least, your son
can look after you when you’re old.
But, I...
Take him with you.
Go.
Call me Father.
Father.
Young Master,
that woman has confessed.
She said
the people from Liang
were close to a chamber of commerce
recently.
Most importantly,
the chamber isn’t clean.
Here’s the thing.
Businessmen here
formed several chambers of commerce.
They did businesses together
and supported each other.
Gradually,
four Grand Chambers appeared.
These four chambers
almost controlled every business
in the city.
But three years ago,
a Xianyang Chamber
appeared out of nowhere.
It developed quickly.
Whoever acted against it
ended tragically.
Now, in the southeast, rice
flour, grains, oil,
tea and silk,
everything, except for water transport
and salt,
is in their control.
I heard that
they even trade
war-horses and iron.
The one Liang contacts
is this Xianyang Chamber?
Yes, it is.
Who’s their leader?
Their leader
seems to be
a wealthy merchant
named Liu Xi, Lord Liu,
also known as the Kind-hearted Liu.
He used to
hold an official post,
but somehow
gave that up and returned home
to do business.
But rumor has it
that the one
in charge of the chamber isn’t him
but a gangster.
Who is that?
What does he look like?
I’ve never seen him.
They call him Mr. Feng.
You mean
this chamber is related to Liang?
Yes.
I think
they are all from Liang.
Look, in this chamber,
except Liu Xi,
everyone else just came out
all of a sudden.
Their identities and backgrounds
are mysterious.
About that Liu Xi you mentioned,
where did he serve?
That I don’t know.
But I can ask around.
Alright. Check him out.
Aye.
Wait.
Where are we
on the task I gave you?
Rest assured.
I have sent out
the portrait of that girl.
Now,
our people in the city are working on it.
Once the girl
enters the city,
we will locate her instantly.
Do not be too confident.
They are just like you.
They can change their looks and voices.
It won’t be easy to find her.
Look, guys.
Have a look.
New arrivals.
Best slaves
in Xianyang.
Take a look.
Anyone you prefer?
The price is negotiable.
Have a look.
Best slaves
in Xianyang.
All new.
You don’t recognize me?
You...
Be quiet.
Or I won’t
get you out
and I’ll leave on my own.
Tell me
if there’s anyone you like.
Sir,
do you want to buy a servant?
I’m checking to see
if there’s someone suitable.
Alright.
How much is this one?
Him?
He was just caught by the guards
at the city gate.
He was rude
and he cursed the judge.
You sound like a handful.
I like someone with a temper.
I’ll take him.
Lucky you!
Fine.
Hurry up!
Untie me.
Is this how you speak to
your master?
What master?
I am a scholar.
How can you buy me
with money?
You are insulting my dignity.
I end up like this
all because of you.
That is not true.
First, I did not ask you to save me.
You stepped into something
beyond your ability,
you know.
Now that I saved you,
we are even.
Second, I offered you money,
but you were too arrogant to accept it.
I...
Third,
you ending up like this
is all your fault.
You deserve it.
I have nothing to do with it.
How dare you...
Zip it.
Listen,
I have something
important to do.
No one will save you
if you get caught again.
Goodbye.
Fine.
A man has his own principles
to do or not to do certain things.
I’ll take my leave.
Your Highness,
I assume you aren’t here
simply to drink
or chat with me.
You are a boring man.
I wouldn’t come here
for drinks.
= Chu Qiao =
Chu Qiao?
She works for Yan Xun.
All eyes are on her lately.
A bounty of one thousand taels of silver
is put on her head by Emperor of Wei.
So,
do you also know her?
I met her
in Chang’an
earlier.
Your Highness
are indeed a player.
She must have seriously offended you
that you’re having no mercy
on her.
No.
On the contrary,
I want you to save her.
Your Highness,
I, Zhan Ziyu, live to kill people.
Saving lives
is new to me.
You’ll be rewarded handsomely.
I have information
which is important to you.
It’s about a person
you’ve been looking for,
Xia Chong.
You know where he is?
In the prison of Liang.
Let me out!
- Let me out now!
- Be quiet!
Let me out!
Miss.
Miss, are you here for me again?
How did you get caught again?
I... Well...
How would I know?
Miss, you are the only one
who can get me out of here.
I am a scholar.
How can I become a slave?
Also, they are always
picky about me.
This is...
Get me out now.
How?
Buy me again.
♪ The wind blows the moonlight ♪
♪ I’m born with a heart of fire ♪
♪ Who laughs at my humble beginnings ♪
♪ Fate has my wings broken ♪
♪ Fall into the abyss
with the memories sealed ♪
♪ What an arrogant blizzard ♪
♪ Not looking up even if trampled again ♪
♪ I’ll get stronger and stronger ♪
♪ The breath is heat
The heartbeat is light ♪
♪ Go forward bit by bit
in a lifelong struggle ♪
♪ Tears hot in eyes light up the hope ♪
♪ No matter how much it hurts ♪
♪ I’m willing to burn my heart out ♪
♪ To melt the frost in the whole world ♪
♪ The moon knows my mind ♪
♪ So what if the road ahead
is in endless dark ♪
♪ I want my heart burn
like fire once again ♪
♪ Burning to be the light in the sky ♪
♪ Reborn from fire The world thrives ♪
♪ I’m blooming on the other side ♪
♪ Burning to be the light in the sky ♪