♪ Through thick and thin
you can get to know ♪
♪ You and I coexist
in the city of good and evil ♪
♪ That light leads me
to get out of my sorrow ♪
♪ It was meant to be you when we met ♪
♪ Desire ridicules tenderness
but never prevails ♪
♪ Yet I’m determined
to feed love everlastingly ♪
♪ Standing at the center of billow ♪
♪ Wind is my mind
and rain is my hunting ground ♪
♪ Look back to the time long gone ♪
♪ The torch in front is flaming ♪
♪ It gets dark
and the way ahead is still long ♪
♪ I know I can’t waver ♪
♪ Shedding blood to be the king
is the only way ♪
= Princess Agents =
= Episode 38 =
You’re awake?
Why are you here?
Where is the Crown Prince of Liang?
Did he escape or die?
Or did you kill him?
How long have you been here?
Since you fell asleep
as soundly as
a pig.
Have some water.
Don’t interfere with my business.
It has nothing to do with you.
What are you doing?
You dislike owing people the most,
right?
I shall let you owe me one
which you can’t repay
even for the rest of your life.
Let go of me!
Why are you out of the city?
Shall we not go back?
No way. You are wounded.
I am late, Your Highness.
I am so sorry.
What took you so long?
You have no idea
how rude the killers were!
I was freaked out!
If I didn’t have martial arts
and fight desperately,
I...
Do you have any idea
who they were?
No.
I found this
during the fight.
Looks like an address.
Go and check it.
You may find something.
= Jinyuan Inn =
Young Master.
What happened today looks weird.
I agree.
I’m afraid we were used.
What should we do?
Xiao Ce wants to use us
to get rid of his domestic enemies.
I happen to have the interest
to meet the spies of Liang
who came to Chang’an.
Maybe we knew them already.
= Jinyuan Inn =
Young Master.
Here we meet again.
Where am I?
Let go of me!
Yuwen Yue! Come out!
Kill me if you dare!
Let me out!
I shall count to three.
Then you will fall.
As if you were floating over Zixia Lake
outside of Jiankang.
Your feelings will disappear.
You will give your body and soul
to me.
To me.
Taoye, what’s wrong?
My Lady.
Seems like I am distracted.
Taoye.
You are the best spy
at the Secret Service.
I trust you
as much as I trust myself.
Thank you, My Lady.
Tell me every spy
we placed
in Chang’an
and burn the list of names.
At Anshangmen Avenue,
Li Yu, the owner of Shuanglin Inn.
Wu Fangkun.
Wang Wen.
Stop!
Go.
= Lingyue Chamber =
Action.
Miss, you have a good taste.
It is made
with natural ingredients
according to a unique recipe
in history books.
I can assure you
you will be even more beautiful
after using this.
Thank you. Bye.
Bye.
Contact every spy in Chang’an
you can reach.
Tell them to stop whatever they are doing
and escape from Chang’an
through their own routes.
The sooner, the better.
But we made a promise
with Yan Xun.
Without us,
he could hardly break out of Chang’an.
Someone else
will do it for us.
= Qingshan House =
Has she all confessed?
The hypnotism was too powerful.
She is kind of delirious.
I let her have some rest for now.
I shall resume the interrogation later.
Shall I arrest
all the remaining spies?
It’s been overnight.
They have escaped already.
It will be pointless
even if we catch some now.
What should we do now?
= List =
The businesses they have run from years
including shops and channels
are what matters most.
Through them,
let’s find out
all spies of Liang
who have stayed
in our nation.
Xiao Ce dare
to use me.
I shall teach him a lesson
and let him pay the price.
Aye.
Taoye also said something
about His Excellency Yan...
Confirm it first.
Remember not to tell him now.
When you have precise news,
let me know.
Aye.
= Pine Hall =
Your Excellency, are you in?
Xiao Ce of Liang has come for a visit.
Tell me what you want.
Sounds so rude.
Considering what you did today,
and how I feel now,
I’m already showing mercy
when I don’t kill you.
This is the deployment diagram
outside of Chang’an.
Don’t stare at me like that,
Your Excellency.
The Secret Service
and I
both work for Liang.
Our goals are the same, too.
The Emperor of Wei is so cruel
that he killed loyal ministers.
Such an honest man like me
can no longer stand that.
I need to do justice
by helping you
get back to Yanbei safely.
You want me
to rebel
and have a war with His Majesty
so that you can benefit from it?
Don’t be so straightforward.
Where are spies with the Secret Service?
They’ve gone back for some reason.
I am in control now.
However,
they didn’t tell me the plan
you made with them.
They left in a hurry.
Those who fell behind
have been arrested by Yuwen Yue.
But don’t worry.
This deployment diagram
can be authentic and reliable.
It includes the geography and
population of each place
from Chang’an to Yanbei,
the armies stationed there, their generals
and their war experience.
It is very detailed.
I spent half a year travelling here.
I wasn’t just enjoying the scenery.
All right. I am finished.
It’s late now.
Well, Your Excellency, wish you...
If it happens again,
I shall let you pay the price!
What are you talking about?
You know what I am talking about.
Achu.
Please get better soon.
I’m afraid
everything here will be ruined
in a couple of days.
If Yan Xun has the guts,
I would rather
he set the whole city on fire!
Your Highness.
Was Yan Xun rude to you
because of Taoye?
No.
Only because I put Qiaoqiao in danger
and she ended up wounded.
That’s fine, then.
I had planned to let Xiao Yu
hurt Qiaoqiao
so that Yan Xun
would hate her.
Then I could
take over her business.
Unexpectedly, Yuwen Yue interfered.
He wiped out all spies in Chang’an
who worked for Xiao Yu.
What a pleasant surprise!
But Yuwen Yue caught Taoye.
She knows a little bit
about Yan Xun’s plan.
Yan Xun isn’t aware of this.
If Yuwen Yue arrests Yan Xun,
will it disturb our plan?
Maybe.
Can Yan Xun get out of Chang’an safely?
I am not his father.
Why should I help him?
Anyway,
he’s going to rebel.
He should have a perfect plan
including a retreat.
If he cannot even
get out of Chang’an,
he won’t defeat anyone else
back in Yanbei!
If so,
he would rather die in Chang’an.
It’s just a pity for Qiaoqiao.
Achu.
You’re awake?
Does your wound hurt?
Not anymore.
You are so badly wounded.
You must feel the pain.
How reckless you were!
I knew
you wanted the deployment diagram
outside of Chang’an.
So, I wanted to take the chance
to check it out.
Unexpectedly...
When you were asleep,
Xiao Ce came.
What for?
He gave us the deployment diagram
from Chang’an to Yanbei.
I know he can’t be
a common man.
I’m right.
But,
he’s born wicked.
I’m not sure
we can trust the diagram he gave us.
We’d better be alert.
He may not stay too long in Chang’an.
Since he has achieved his goal,
he will leave, I guess.
Does your wound ache again?
No, no.
I’m just wondering.
Since you took the risk
to get out of the city,
why didn’t you just escape?
You were badly wounded.
I needed to take you back
to see the doctor.
Sorry, sorry to be your burden.
Yuwen Yue has kept a close eye
on us.
Yan Xun.
I have something
to discuss with you.
What is it?
How will you
deal with Xiuli Army?
They opened
the Gate of Hongchuan and Beishuo
for Zhao Dongting.
Let me think about it.
Achu.
You must be hungry.
We can talk some other day.
Let me get you something to eat.
= List =
Young Master, we have checked it out.
What Taoye said is
mostly true.
We cannot find proof
for some people.
But I believe they are spies.
Most of them are officials
under the sixth level.
They seem common in normal times,
but work in every field of the government.
They can cause huge mess.
Put them under control.
Shall we inform Chang’an Office?
Not yet.
What we should do is
to use our own men to make sure
they cannot leave home
on the wedding day of the Princess.
Aye.
First, put Guard Deng Jia of the East Gate
under control.
On your birthday that year,
Princess Yuan Chun
brought us a jar of Jade Wine
from the palace.
She said it was the one and only.
We all found it precious
at that time.
But recently,
I’ve got another jar.
Seems like it’s how the world goes.
What you believed
may turn out to be wrong.
Right or wrong
depends on
who thinks of it.
You don’t decide
the right and wrong alone.
Are you really going to marry Yuan Chun?
Of course.
I am very curious
what you’ve prepared
as the betrothal present.
You are?
Check it out, then.
I am checking on that.
Meanwhile,
I’ve found an interesting list.
Cui Jia, Councilor
in the Ministry of Works,
Pei Mingshu, Left Officer
in the Construction Department.
Wang Mianzhi, Chief Director
of Fire Department.
Qu Yi, Warrior of Wulin Guards,
Deng Jia, Guard of the East Gate.
You want more?
I also checked the recent working record
in the Ministry of Works
and Construction Department.
I found Longsheng Canal,
Wei Canal and An Canal
had been all cleared recently.
Cui Jia led the work,
while Pei Mingshu assisted.
It is the rainy season now.
The water line rises.
You’ve made all these efforts
and spent all this money
to make them work for you.
Yan Xun.
Are you going to flood the city
on your wedding day?
How can you not know
what I want to do?
Eighty thousand families live in Chang’an.
Including stationed soldiers,
there’re over five hundred thousand.
You really want to
kill all of them
just for your own desire?
Then through the East Gate
where Deng Jia guarded,
you could break out of Chang’an.
Zhao Dongting attacked Yanbei by surprise
with fifty thousand imperial guards.
Beishuo and Hongchuan
were burned into ashes.
The fire lasted for three days and nights.
200 thousand soldiers and civilians died
in the fire.
They’re all innocent!
You also survived from the tragedy
and escaped from death.
You should know it
more than anyone else
how it feels
to lose families.
But what you plan to do is
exactly what Zhao Dongting did.
It is not.
He slaughtered innocent citizens
and killed loyal ministers.
But I only take revenge,
making eye for eye.
Pretty fair!
If you do this,
will you feel at ease?
Something may not
make me happy.
But if I don’t do it,
I won’t be happy for sure.
Happiness is not the only thing
we seek for,
living in this world.
I don’t think
you can understand.
Anyway,
I won’t let you succeed.
If you’ve made up your mind,
come to me at any time.
I will help you.
Don’t dream about
anything else.
Try me. We’ll see.
If you want to stop me,
come as you wish.
Does Xing’er know
what you plan to do?
I know people from Liang
can’t be trusted.
Turns out
they did something wrong
and exposed our plan.
Luckily, we have a backup plan.
Then can we still use
the deployment diagram
from the Crown Prince of Liang?
We have
a preliminary deployment diagram,
mainly the same as his.
I think we can use it.
Your Excellency, those guys don’t matter.
They are agents from Liang
and spies in the government.
It is Taoye’s plan
to flood Chang’an.
We never expected them
to succeed.
The problem is...
Deng Jia and Qu Yi
work for us.
After being exposed,
they are now controlled by Yuwen Yue.
Without them,
we would get no help from the military.
It will be too hard for us
to break out of Chang’an alone
and get rid of pursuing troops
on our way back.
I have an idea.
I wonder if I should say.
No.
I know what you want to say.
But Your Excellency,
- I...
- Our priority is
to stop Yuwen Yue.
When he’s around,
he will reveal
all our plans
on Zhuque Avenue.
Where are you going, Your Excellency?
Go get changed
and get to the palace.
You two.
Put the lamp in my bedroom.
- Aye.
Put this on the table.
Be careful!
All of you! Be careful!
Caiwei, how is everything going?
Everything’s ready.
If we need anything,
make it up.
Don’t overlook anything.
I see.
His Excellency Yan Xun has arrived!
Yan Xun.
What brings you here?
I come to have a look.
Are you coming to see
how ready I am?
Time is so tight
that many things can’t be prepared.
But it doesn’t matter.
When I can be with you,
nothing else matters.
Do you want to see
my wedding dress?
Let me show you. Go.
His Majesty has arrived!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Greetings, Father.
You may rise.
- Thank you, Father.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
Father.
Yan Xun comes here
to see me.
You’re free to come here.
Seems like you’re mostly ready.
Ceremony Department is
taking care of this.
I think it’s almost ready.
Time is tight.
But I don’t want my daughter
to feel bad.
She is born
to be a naughty girl.
And she is
my favorite daughter.
I still remember
when she was of this height,
- I was thinking
- Father!
who would be
her husband.
How time flies!
Now she’s getting married.
Chun, if you need anything
or want anything,
just tell me.
Let the servants
do everything.
Don’t get exhausted.
Father, I am not tired at all.
When you marry me to Yan Xun,
this is the best award for me.
I feel happy from the bottom of my heart
and I don’t feel tired at all.
I’ll leave you alone.
I gotta go.
I’m getting in.
After the wedding,
you will go back to Yanbei together.
It’ll be a long trip.
I wonder
when we can
meet again.
Don’t worry, Your Majesty.
When you want to see the Princess,
I can take her back to see you
at any time.
Haven’t you lived enough
in this city?
Chang’an is wealthier than anywhere else.
I love it without doubt.
If I didn’t miss my hometown too much,
I would be living here forever.
By the way,
I haven’t picked the general
who would take you back to Yanbei.
Do you have any friend
in the army?
Choose one
who can send you back
in case you get bored on the way.
Pick whoever you want, Your Majesty.
No?
Isn’t Yuwen Yue
your friend?
I can transfer him from Cavalry Battalion
so that he can take you back to Yanbei.
His Majesty, to tell you the truth,
we were friends only when we were little.
Having not met each other for three years,
we are now strangers.
You were childhood friends.
Even if you’re not close now,
you will get to know each other soon.
Never mind.
Your Majesty.
I’m no longer a friend with Yuwen Yue.
Please choose someone else.
After he came back this time,
didn’t you meet him?
No.
No?
Achu.
You can walk?
I’m nearly recovered.
So is my wound.
Then I come out for a walk.
Your healing ability
is incredible.
Where is Yan Xun?
He visited the Empress Dowager last night
and didn’t come back.
Maybe he was asked to stay overnight.
Achu.
Are you going back to Cavalry Battalion?
No.
Yan Xun asked for a leave for me.
That’s good, then.
What happened?
Nothing. It doesn’t concern you.
Never mind.
Miss Yu,
I can see from your face
that something did happen.
Tell me what it is.
Someone from Xiuli Army came,
asking to see you.
I stopped him.
Someone from Xiuli Army?
His name is Ge Qi.
He asked
if you remembered a warrant
granted by Yuwen Yue
with which you could get new bows
for Xiuli Army from the arsenal.
I remember.
I gave it to He Xiao.
What? Did he not get them?
He said
He Xiao lost that warrant.
But people in the arsenal said
they received the warrant
and they gave the bows and arrows
to Xiuli Army.
However, no such weapons
can be found in Xiuli Army.
Now, He Xiao is arrested
and accused of embezzling weapons.
He is to be executed.
Executed? When?
At noon today.
At noon today?
I’ll go and check it.
He Xiao, time is running out.
Are you going to confess or not?
I have nothing to confess.
I lost the warrant.
I should take the blame for that.
However, Commander!
You accuse me of embezzling soldiers’ pay
and reselling military weapons.
I will never
plead guilty.
You sound stubborn!
Fine. Since you don’t confess to me,
confess to the demons
in the hell.
He Xiao embezzled soldiers’ pay
and resold military weapons.
According to military laws,
he should be executed!
Commander!
Neither Chief Commander
nor Deputy Commander is here.
How can you decide alone
such an important issue?
Mr. He has been in the army for years.
He is conscientious and loving!
He came to Chang’an
with no family around!
What does he need money for?
Yeah.
He is a good man!
Don’t kill the innocent man!
- Don’t kill the innocent man!
- Shut up!
The evidence for his sin is conclusive.
As the commander of Xiuli Army,
I have the authority to punish him.
But you plead for him.
Are you his confederates?
Commander Xue.
Don’t sling mud at us!
- Don’t sling mud at us!
- Shut up!
Don’t sling mud at us!
There is human testimony
and material evidence.
I won’t take the blame
for slinging mud at you!
But look at you!
You slandered your superior.
What punishment do you think you deserve?
Our Vice Commander
isn’t a corrupt man.
Let him go!
- Let him go!
- Shut up!
Let him go!
Are you going to rebel?
Dudes!
Let him go!
Dudes.
I appreciate
your help.
However,
I took you to Chang’an,
leaving our hometown behind
and struggled for life,
not because I wanted you
to get killed like this.
We can’t go home
or acknowledge our families.
Everyone hates us.
We’re even abandoned by the whole world,
only because
we’re known as traitors!
But I know
you are not.
Nor am I!
Who can tell me
the highest honor
for a soldier?
Die in the battlefield!
Dudes, I don’t think
I’ve got a chance
to die in the battlefield.
Therefore,
you must survive.
When you have a chance
to protect your country,
and fight in the battlefield,
kill more enemies for me!
Use your blood
to wash off the shame
we’ve carried!
When I saw that in heaven,
I would be grateful!
Cut the crap.
Time is out. Kill him.
You can’t kill him!
What are you doing?
Time is out!
You can’t kill him!
Stop!
Ms. Chu?
What are you coming for?
What are you doing, Commander?
Punishing a sinner
according to military laws.
What is He Xiao’s sin?
He embezzled soldiers’ pay
and resold military weapons.
Which pay?
Bows and arrows
General Yuwen granted us.
He Xiao said he lost the warrant
and couldn’t take them back.
But according to the arsenal,
they received the warrant
and delivered the weapons.
If he hadn’t stolen them,
who else could have done that?
Maybe someone got the weapons
in his name?
I don’t know that.
Even so,
he is to blame for dropping the warrant
and making the weapons gone!
He should be killed as well!
Fine, do it then.
Ms. Chu.
What do you mean?
General Yuwen gave the warrant to me.
I lost it.
It didn’t concern He Xiao.
He was just taking the blame for me.
Ms. Chu.
Say no more.
I am on a mission given by His Majesty.
Also, I am a military officer.
The warrant was given to me.
I should take the blame
for its loss.
Ms. Chu, you asked
to get involved.
Do you think
I don’t dare to kill you?
You certainly dare.
As the Commander,
you dare to kill anyone.
However,
let me remind you.
When the Crown Prince Xiao Ce
was assassinated,
I stayed with him
and protected him.
The Crown Prince Xiao Ce
pleaded to His Majesty on my behalf.
His Majesty allowed me
to get recovered first
before he rewarded me later.
If you want to kill me,
you’d better report to your superior,
in case you get into trouble
due to your own decision.
Commander Xue.
I’m saying it for your own good.
Fine, I’m going to report it.
I’d like to see
how much support you can have!
You two, stay on your knees!
See you, Commander Xue.
Awesome! Awesome! Awesome!
♪ The wind blows the moonlight ♪
♪ I’m born with a heart of fire ♪
♪ Who laughs at my humble beginnings ♪
♪ Fate has my wings broken ♪
♪ Fall into the abyss
with the memories sealed ♪
♪ What an arrogant blizzard ♪
♪ Not looking up even if trampled again ♪
♪ I’ll get stronger and stronger ♪
♪ The breath is heat
The heartbeat is light ♪
♪ Go forward bit by bit
in a lifelong struggle ♪
♪ Tears hot in eyes light up the hope ♪
♪ No matter how much it hurts ♪
♪ I’m willing to burn my heart out ♪
♪ To melt the frost in the whole world ♪
♪ The moon knows my mind ♪
♪ So what if the road ahead
is in endless dark ♪
♪ I want my heart burn
like fire once again ♪
♪ Burning to be the light in the sky ♪
♪ Reborn from fire The world thrives ♪
♪ I’m blooming on the other side ♪
♪ Burning to be the light in the sky ♪