[Magic Factory]
[Park Hae Jin]
[Jin Ki Joo]
[Jung Joon Ho]
[Park Seo Yeon | Jeong Seok Yong | Ko Kyu Phil]
[From Now On, Showtime!]
[All characters, locations, groups, and incidents are fictional.]
[Episode 13]
Greetings!
I am Go Seulhae, the newest member of the detective squad.
I hope we get along.
- Welcome!
- Nice.
It's good to see you here.
Welcome.
- What on earth?
- What?
Tenacity is your game, isn't it?
You finally made it here. "Relentless" is what I'll say.
From here on out,
I will keep showing you just how relentless I can be!
Welcome.
Stop!
Darn it.
Come at me. Come on.
Darn you.
You piece of...
Come here.
You little...
Seulhae, are you all right?
I'm fine.
What just happened?
Thank goodness. I thought you were hurt.
Register her death?
Ma'am, please let me explain.
Five years after you report someone missing,
you can legally register them as deceased.
- Your daughter's situation is...
- I have no way of knowing...
whether or not my daughter is dead!
If you think she's dead, at least go find her corpse.
Ma'am, please sit here.
What's the matter?
My daughter, Mi Young... It's already been five years,
but she's still not back.
The police said they'd find her,
but they're now saying I should register her as deceased.
No, it's not that... Ma'am, you've been coming here every day.
He feels bad and is just trying to help.
I understand how devastated you must be.
I'll look into it again.
I promise I'll find your daughter.
[Missing Person, Kim Miyoung, female, age 39]
Age 39...
Hey, Go Seulhae.
- Must you keep acting up like that?
- Pardon me?
Don't go around saying you'll find her missing daughter no matter what!
Will you only look for her daughter and not work on other cases?
Do you think we have that much time on our hands?
- Still, we should...
- You're talking back to me again!
Hey, go get me a cup of coffee. With lots of ice cubes.
Yes, Sir.
That brat.
Detective Byun.
That was out of line.
Well, you know that the chief told us to close the case.
I'm just worried that clueless brat
will run around and cause trouble again.
I'm in charge here.
I'm not saying anything, so why...
Why must you overstep your bounds?
Right. I'm sorry.
Also, do not send Cheon Hwa on an errand like that again.
Okay. Wait, Cheon... Who?
Go Seulhae, who else?
Right, yes.
Oh, how pretty.
Sorry, that must've sounded awkward.
I'm not good at hiding stuff like this.
Come see me after work.
Promise?
What do you think? Was it good? Let me see.
It was perfect.
Why do you need this all of a sudden?
Seulhae must be having a hard time getting used to her new team.
Hopefully, this will cheer her up.
You think it'll cheer her up? Won't it make her angry?
If I were her, I'd arrest you on the spot.
Arrest me? Why?
If you send a video that arouses fear or apprehension,
you can face a prison sentence of a year or a fine of up to 10,000 dollars.
Hey, just leave him be.
When you're so in love, especially for the first time ever,
no one can stop you.
Oh, right. Wasn't Detective Seo her first love?
Now, they'll always be glued together in the detective squad.
Then she'll fall in love with him first.
That's why I invited her over today.
- So I can beat him to it.
- I see.
[Go Seulhae]
Oh, how pretty.
- Sorry, that must've sounded awkward.
- Why? What is it?
What's wrong, all of a sudden?
- Your exceptional beauty...
- What? What is this?
had me drawing a blank.
- I knew it.
- By any chance, is there anything you want to eat?
- Cha Chawoong likes you, right?
- Tell me...
- and I will make it for you.
- I don't know.
- What? Hey, look. You don't know?
- ♪ Would you like a cup of coffee? ♪
♪ Would you like a cup of coffee? ♪
- ♪ I mustered up all the courage I had ♪
- To say this, he's crazy about you.
- I see you love it, my sweet girl.
- Gosh.
No one in their right mind would do this.
The thing is, the person he likes...
could be me.
But it's not actually me.
However, it is me in a way.
It's hard to explain.
What are you saying?
Anyway, go see him this evening and you'll find out.
Looks like he wants to tell you how he feels.
Gosh, girl.
Hey, what's going on? Men can't get enough of you these days.
Introduce me to him later.
What are you reading?
This article says Cha Chawoong has donated half of his wealth.
My gosh, that's cool.
That's amazing.
Yes, it is.
Thank goodness I made the switch.
Why would he donate his money?
Yeji, try this.
Yongryul, your parents...
aren't really interested in donating to charity, are they?
I think I've seen them make a few small donations to the Salvation Army and to help flood victims.
I see.
That's nice. It's perfect.
Try it.
It's so good!
See that girl? She's the new shaman in the neighborhood.
- She's a shaman?
- Yes.
I knew it. She looks so intense.
Why would she do that kind of work when she's still so young?
- She should get a decent job.
- My point exactly.
Don't mind them.
I'm used to this.
Even if we argue with them, they won't change.
It's better to just ignore them.
Excuse me.
Watch what you say, please.
You ladies should learn basic manners before you criticize someone else's job.
It's very rude to talk loudly on purpose, so she'd hear.
We're sorry. We didn't know she'd hear us.
We're sorry!
- Sorry, we apologize.
- Sorry.
Wait, Yongryul!
This.
What about it? Can we not hold hands?
It's not that.
I'm just not ready yet.
Really?
Then get yourself ready. I'll give you ten seconds.
One, three, five, seven, nine, ten.
We're good now, right?
I have a son, and I'm so worried about him.
He's so timid that he has no idea how to ask a girl out.
He can't even strike up a conversation with a girl.
He's timid?
He's still such a mama's boy.
He's the sweetest son any mother could ask for.
- He has someone.
- I know... What?
I see a pretty, foxy girl right next to him.
I see them together.
Of course. Girls wouldn't leave my son alone.
Hold on. She's foxy?
I was hoping he'd meet a quiet girl who's nice.
If you say stuff like that, your son will never get married.
Just be grateful that your son has found someone... who cares for him.
Keep your mouth shut.
But is she really not nice?
No, she's not. And she's got a temper.
What's with this feast? Are you throwing a party or something?
Officer Go... I mean, Detective Go.
Since you're a detective now, I thought we should celebrate.
I reached out to a royal cuisine expert for help.
- Take a seat.
- You didn't have to do this.
I told you that I'd treat you like a princess from now on.
- A princess?
- Dig in. Eat up.
This looks delicious.
My stomach has been a little upset all day.
Then you should stay away from greasy foods.
- I'll eat this.
- Then try this. The soup will help.
Here, have this.
What's wrong? Why aren't you eating?
Oh, are you not a fan of traditional Korean dishes?
Should I have prepared Western dishes?
Goodness. How can she eat if you keep staring at her like that?
Even eating shows don't have such close-up shots these days.
Yes. Just let her eat, will you?
I can't even look at her?
Oh, how come Adviser Choi isn't joining us?
Did he go somewhere?
Even so, how could you kick him out?
He left of his own accord.
I just didn't stop him. That's all.
You should've stopped him.
He must've been so anxious.
He should have some shame after all, shouldn't he?
He was the person you and I trusted the most in our past life.
But he betrayed us and brought death upon us.
Had it not been for him, the two of us...
could have been happy together.
Then, what about this? Are we happy now?
You told me that learning about your past life
helped you understand why you were reincarnated,
and how you should live your life from now on.
Is this why you...
I mean, is this why you and I were reincarnated?
Fighting about our past lives, feeling angry and disappointed?
You said Adviser Choi hadn't been able to ascend
for 2,000 years because he had to pay for what he did. Then...
Then I'd say he deserves to be forgiven now.
To him, it's something that happened 2,000 years ago.
But to me, it's still so vivid as if it happened yesterday.
I don't want to face him when I still feel this way.
Then, how do you think I feel when I'm facing you like this?
At the hospital,
I kept praying that you'd wake up. I bet you have no idea.
You have no idea how happy and grateful I was when you woke up.
But these days, I wonder from time to time
if you really are the person who I so desperately waited for.
I don't even feel like you're looking at me.
I think I need some time to gather my thoughts.
Okay.
I don't want to see you like this,
so let's not meet until you have pulled yourself together.
There's been another accident on a road near Kangguk Tunnel.
What? Don't tell me it's another black Adagio.
Yes, I checked the footage that the Traffic Division had.
I swear, there was nothing around.
But the driver suddenly turned the steering wheel
as if they wanted to avoid something, and crashed into a ditch.
Do accidents happen often in that area?
Sure, you could say that.
But every time, it's a black Adagio.
How's that possible? The same car model every single time?
Here's something spookier. The drivers all say
they saw a woman dressed in white.
Has the ghost on the Jayu Motorway moved to Kangguk or something?
Ghost?
- What else could it be? The footage shows nothing.
- Go Seulhae.
- Let's go on a stakeout.
- What?
What?
You still have this? You've had this for over ten years.
What is it?
Well.
To tell you the truth, the stakeout was just an excuse.
I brought you out so we could be alone.
And I have something to tell you.
Oh, sure.
Welcome to my team.
- What's wrong?
- This...
It looks very expensive. I'm uncomfortable accepting it.
You're uncomfortable? But this is nothing.
I'm going to give you a lot more from now on.
"A lot more"?
Money, fame, power.
Whatever you want.
Because you're mine now.
I had a lot going on, so I haven't been able to give you my answer.
I thought a lot about what you said the other day,
but I wish for us to stay... as colleagues and good friends.
What's your reason?
That's...
Is it because of Cha Chawoong?
If we're not here because of a case, I'll get back to the office.
I will not lose you again.
Excuse me, Ma'am!
Move out of the road!
It's dangerous! Ma'am!
Yes, over here.
What's wrong with you? Stop!
I'm certain that ghost is related to that car accident-prone spot.
But I'm too scared to go back.
Nobody can.
She's pretty much an evil spirit.
Ghosts like them scare me, too.
Right?
But it's not like I can just let her keep causing accidents.
- How about talking to Mr. Cha and...
- No way!
Why not?
To be frank, I insisted
we shouldn't see each other for a while yesterday.
So asking him today is going to make me lose face.
Then, what will you do?
So I was thinking...
We've known each other for a while now
and have worked together before.
So how about... we leave Mr. Cha out and go alone?
Leave me out and do what?
I didn't say a word. No, I didn't.
What are you planning with my workers?
I just have things to talk about with them.
It has nothing to do with you, so mind your own business.
I'm paying them... for whatever they do,
so how can it have nothing to do with me?
And right now,
it's business hours.
They can't go anywhere without my permission.
Well,
unless you take me with you.
It's that ghost over there, right?
Yes.
She looks extremely unstable.
Will it be all right? She looks dangerous.
You call this dangerous?
Remember who I am?
The chief priest who sealed an evil spirit.
Just you wait.
It's showtime!
Go!
- Are you joining us?
- Yes.
Hey, you there! Let's have a chit-chat.
What do you think you're doing here?
Run!
Mr. Cha!
Darn it. Hey!
- Run!
- How can you be scared of ghosts?
Wasn't it showtime?
Seriously, you traitors!
- It can't be helped.
- Run!
- Oh, my gosh!
- Officer Go!
Mr. Cha! Darn it.
Miyoung?
Dongcheol?
- Hi.
- Welcome!
You're all set.
Oh, my! I'm sorry. Are you okay?
It's on the house today.
It was just a slight trim.
Just take it.
By the way, why do you come so often?
You even come twice a week at times.
No reason. Can't I?
No, you can.
- Okay, bye.
- Wait a second.
Here. It's for your wound.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry for saying that I have feelings for you.
I was foolish to dream a man like me could become happy.
- I should get going.
- I...
don't like you getting hurt.
It's not too late.
You can start again with a clean slate.
It'll bring happiness
to both, you...
and me.
Darn.
Miyoung.
Hey, Mingu!
- Hi, Mr. Ma!
- Hey.
When is your wife giving birth again?
Gosh, it's already next week.
- Really?
- Yes.
- What was that? Postnatal care?
- Yes?
I heard it's important.
Buy her... Darn it.
Buy her lots of delicious food.
My gosh, that's too much. It's all right.
Just listen to me, punk.
- Welcome back.
- Right.
Hi.
Boss, I have something to tell you.
Okay, go ahead.
Hey, give us some room.
Grab a meal.
My boys. Grow out your hair.
Get going.
Boss.
I would like to quit.
Hey.
We only just got a client by getting a large company,
an assemblyman, and the police involved.
What will I tell the higher-ups?
"I don't know what our number two, who knows all our connections,
will rattle on about after quitting,
but I'm leaving him be?"
You're planning to go to the Brown Bear Group, aren't you?
You're going to make off with my client, right?
No way, Boss.
You know I'm not smart enough.
I fell in love.
I want to become an honorable man in front of her.
- Love?
- Yes.
Fine.
If you really want to quit, do something for me.
The Brown Bear Group's right to run clubs.
Bring me that and I'll believe you.
Okay, I'll get it for you.
Miyoung, I'll drop by the salon tonight.
I've got something to tell you.
Tell me?
I'll wait until you come.
You must come, okay, Dongcheol?
Brown Bear is inside, right?
Do you have a death wish?
Mr. Ma! Are you okay?
Why would you come alone?
- Give this to the boss.
- What?
[Right of Operation Waiver]
Mr. Ma!
Hey, wash your hands of this, too.
Think about your baby.
[Bom Hair Salon]
Miyoung!
Gosh.
I was taken to the hospital,
but died after being in a coma for a month.
When I visited the hair salon as a ghost, it was already closed.
Well, it was only natural after what you went through.
So I thought you'd be living happily somewhere.
But what happened? Why did you become a ghost?
That day,
I died as well.
He dragged me to his car...
and killed me.
That jerk even took your life?
Darn it.
I knew the Brown Bear Group was wicked, but how could they?
So that's why you were on that road.
Yes, I was waiting.
Waiting for that punk who killed us to take revenge.
Even so, innocent people got in accidents because of you.
Burning with vengeance makes you visible to humans.
And you're even on the verge of turning into an evil spirit.
I'm sorry.
Why are you scolding her?
Imagine how unjust this kindhearted person felt!
If only we had caught that jerk earlier,
Miyoung wouldn't have ended up like that.
You saw his face, right?
Is there anything you can recall?
You little... Darn it!
A knife scar.
There was a long knife scar under his eye.
A knife scar?
Can we catch him, Officer?
My mom...
is still looking for me.
I feel so sorry for her.
This is all because of him.
That scumbag.
Calm down.
Miyoung?
At this rate, you'll die first.
Where to?
Open the door! Open it!
Open it!
She won't be able to step outside for a while.
I need to go kill that jerk!
I'm going to kill him!
Based on her current state, there's not much time left.
She'll soon turn into an evil spirit.
She can't revert back when that happens. What do we do?
Isn't it obvious? Catch the culprit and satisfy her grudge.
We know his car model and signalment.
I'll look into it.
But she hasn't told us about the car model.
Every car that was in an accident back there was a black Adagio.
What? A black Adagio?
The culprit is the Badger.
The boss of the gang I was in.
What? But you did everything he asked. So why?
He never intended to let him go.
You were thrown out after being used.
And Miyoung got caught up in it by ill luck.
It was because of me.
- Gosh.
- If only I didn't like her.
If only I wasn't head over heels for her.
- I'm going to kill that Badger jerk this instant.
- Hey, stop.
Do you also want to become an evil spirit?
It's at times like these you have to be rational.
He's right. Think of how Miyoung would feel.
We can't handle you if you turn.
You...
I'm sorry about yesterday.
It took you by surprise, right?
Honestly, I was shocked at myself too.
I guess I liked you more than I thought.
- Senior.
- No.
I'm not being clingy, so don't worry.
Yesterday after that, I thought long and hard about how I'll treat you from now on.
And I realized I should follow in your footsteps.
What?
Keep liking you, but don't be forceful.
Stay by your side, but don't put pressure.
Set aside public and private matters and do my best at work.
And if you end up liking someone else,
don't bother with it.
What do you think?
Don't you think we'll be able to get along well even from now on?
Yes. I appreciate it and I'm sorry.
I feel much better now.
By the way, didn't you have something to tell me?
Well...
I looked into Kim Miyoung's missing case.
Kim Miyoung's boyfriend was in the Badger Group?
And the day she went missing is when her boyfriend was stabbed.
Given the circumstances, I think both of them
got caught up and ended up as victims of the Badger Group.
But that group wasn't mentioned in any of the investigation records.
So? Did you dig deeper?
Not yet. I'm going to interview Badger as a witness first.
Good thinking. Proceed with it.
Okay.
Captain Seo, I got a call today.
An investigation?
Why are you digging up a case that was covered up five years ago?
Covered up?
Officer Go Seulhae. She's the newbie on your team, no?
You should've stopped her.
How are you educating your underlings?
Aren't you the one who needs a lesson first?
What?
If you want me to take action, you should do so first.
And stop yapping.
That's how you make a deal.
Or how about you quietly rot behind bars?
Fine.
What do you want?
I need someone gone.
An accident would be preferable.
Have you heard of Cha Chawoong?
Cha Chawoong?
The magician on TV?
Why him?
Miyoung, have some water.
I apologize for my unstable state.
Ms. Kim, do you have physical evidence that directly links Badger to your killer?
Physical evidence?
There isn't much time.
We must gather the evidence before your condition worsens.
I know it's a painful memory, but I need you to recall the night of your murder.
Why you...
Darn it.
Before I died, I pulled out his hair.
Compared to other human tissues, hair is slow to decompose.
It has only been five years, so there's a good chance it hasn't been damaged.
Finding it could lead to a DNA match.
Where were you buried?
Ms. Kim, are you sure this is the place?
Yes.
Yes, I was buried not far from here.
You have no idea...
how long I wandered around these woods in tears.
I will never forgive him.
Die!
- Miyoung, no!
- Ms. Kim.
Please calm down.
- It's okay. It'll be over soon.
- Ms. Kim.
Please don't give up.
Ms. Kim, this isn't the time to give up.
- Are you all right?
- Are you?
Gosh.
What on earth? It's Badger.
Move!
Why won't you budge?
Take the dive, darn it.
Mr. Choi?
You've held on long enough.
What on earth?
Why won't the car move?
Badger, you piece of scum!
Ma Dongcheol?
What the... Were my eyes playing tricks on me?
Darn it.
You know me, don't you?
And who might you be?
Don't you remember?
You killed me.
You killed me!
Die.
Miyoung, stop!
No, let go.
Let go of me!
Let go.
Miyoung, get a grip on yourself.
Miyoung!
This isn't who you are.
You're the one who encouraged me to start over
and told me that I could be happy.
If you kill him, it will be over for you.
But it's unfair.
It's not fair at all.
He should die, too.
He shouldn't live!
All you need is for him to die, right?
Will that finally put you at ease?
I'll do it instead.
Your hands will remain clean.
Miyoung, head over to Mr. Cha.
Killing him will turn me into an evil spirit
and I might attack you afterward.
Mr. Cha will protect you from me.
Forget about someone like me
and enter Nirvana in peace.
- Stop.
- Let go!
- Stop!
- Dongcheol.
No, don't do this.
That's enough.
Let go of me!
Don't do this. Please snap out of it.
As if you would know how I'm feeling.
Miyoung died because of me.
Who am I to sit back and do nothing?
- Dongcheol!
- I...
I know how you feel.
Avenging the one you love? Of course, it's what we want.
But it never ends there. It doesn't.
Choosing a dark path
will come back to haunt you.
Not just you
but all those who you care about.
And when that day comes,
you will regret your choice.
Forever.
I'm sorry, Dongcheol.
I'll stop this. So don't do this for my sake.
I'm sorry I hurt you.
No, Miyoung.
I'm the reason you...
If only I had been able to put you at ease.
I am...
at ease.
Just seeing you again,
knowing that I have someone on my side...
has put me at ease.
Here. Let me carry that for you.
Forget it.
Right.
How did you know to come here? You were here when we needed you.
Oh, that.
As a bodyguard, staying undetected has become a talent of mine.
Hold on. Are you saying that you've been following me?
- Well...
- So much for privacy.
How is that different from stalking?
You give me the creeps.
I'm sorry.
Since that's the case, I'll head back down first.
Where do you think you're going?
We must find the body before day breaks.
There's no way Mr. Ma and I can get it done ourselves.
We need an extra set of hands.
Stay on my tail.
Yes, of course.
Shall we?
Badger, you know her, don't you?
Take a good look at her. Do you know her or not?
No, it can't be.
I... Back then... No. No way.
As if. There's proof that you killed her.
Don't come near me!
I'm sorry, okay?
Just... Please don't kill me.
What has gotten into you?
My daughter.
My Miyoung.
She is finally back in my arms.
In that dark, cold place.
She must've been so lonely.
Thank you, Detective.
Mom.
I'm sorry I came back to you in this state.
I committed the unthinkable, didn't I?
How will you live without me?
My Miyoung...
was always so lonely.
How am I supposed to let her go all by herself?
Don't worry about me, Mom.
I have Dongcheol now.
I'm not alone anymore, and I will be all right.
Yes, Mother.
I'll take good care of Miyoung.
For Miyoung's sake and yours,
please eat your meals...
and get plenty of sleep.
I should.
Getting my act together...
is how...
my daughter can move on as well.
Mom...
[Trustworthy Police, Safe Country]
Thank you, all.
I was finally able to leave that part of the road.
We're the ones who are grateful. I'm happy for you.
Now that nothing's holding you back, will you be entering Nirvana?
No, we agreed to stay a little longer.
We'll be having a ghost marriage.
Besides, we should make up for all the dates we didn't get to go on.
We'll enter Nirvana together after the wedding.
Goodness.
Can you put off entering Nirvana of free will?
Well, I talked to Hyeonjoon about it, and he allowed it.
He'll be handing in a petition for us.
Gosh, this is great news. Congratulations.
No wonder all your blind dates never worked out.
We all have someone we're meant to be with.
- Blind dates?
- Of course not.
It's just that the lady ghosts all wanted a chance to date him.
How could any of them live up to someone as kind and beautiful as you, though?
He wouldn't let any woman win him over.
Exactly. I didn't even bat an eye.
Are you lying to her just to get married?
Congratulations.
- Watch what you say.
- Sorry, my bad.
Congratulations, Miyoung.
Please sit back down.
It would've been nice for Mr. Choi to join us.
We wouldn't be here if it weren't for him.
Since you're all here, I have an announcement to make.
Now that Mr. Choi has left us
and Mr. Ma will soon be entering Nirvana,
I have decided to hire additional staff.
- I see.
- Right.
Get in here already.
- Hurry on over!
- What on earth?
- What?
- Adviser Choi!
Hi, it's me.
Good thinking, Mr. Cha.
- Adviser Choi, how...
- Hold on. Stop.
He is no longer an adviser.
Due to how he deceived me, an advisory position wasn't an option.
Instead, he is back as an entry-level employee.
- What?
- Please greet your colleagues.
Greetings, I am Choi Geom, the new recruit.
I hope we get along.
What on earth?
Hold on. Does this mean I'm his senior?
Is he a junior staff member?
Don't tell me his experience grants him a higher paycheck.
What does this mean in terms of hierarchy?
Don't you worry. Simply put...
As of today, you have been promoted to assistant manager.
Congratulations, Assistant Manager Kang.
Yes!
Let's have fun, new recruit!
Right, of course.
I mean, yes, Ma'am.
Ms. Kang.
I hope you think fondly of me!
- Right.
- It's a pleasure, 2,000 Years.
Mr. Nam,
have Geom do that and take a break.
Geom? Who's Geom?
Gosh. You can't shout out Adviser Choi's name like that.
He's a new recruit, not an adviser.
Right. Please address me as you see fit, Mr. Nam.
But still...
New Recruit.
Sorry?
Mop up the floor and let me have that instead.
Yes, sir.
Mop from here to way over there.
Gosh, my back is killing me.
My back aches.
- I've got this.
- Goodness.
I guess I have no choice.
I'm Choi Geom and I can do this.
- It's dirty over here as well.
- Right.
I'll suck it up.
There's something I've been wanting to ask.
The sword you have on your person.
Where did you get it? It seems like a rare item.
Ms. Kang, you seem to have a keen eye for things.
I went to... the capital's most famous blacksmith 2,000 years ago...
and waited three months to purchase it.
Gosh. No wonder.
Can I wield it sometime?
I bet it's well-balanced.
I'm afraid not anyone can brandish that kind of weapon.
Anyone?
New Recruit, you upset me.
I'm your superior, Assistant Manager Kang.
How am I just "anyone"?
- Is a hostile work environment what you want?
- No, of course not.
Please let me know when you're free, and I'll set it up for you.
How generous of our junior.
Set it up for me once you finish cleaning up.
Yes, Ms. Kang.
- Keep mopping.
- Sure thing.
Yes, of course.
I deserve this.
Mr. Cha, are you kidding me?
Aren't you too old to play with a toy like this?
They must make fancy marbles these days.
All right. Let's see if I still have it.
What are you doing with a cosmetic product?
Wait. Is this a cosmetic product?
Gosh.
No way.
Ta-da. It will straighten out those wrinkles.
Right, my wrinkles. Nice.
Can you apply some right here?
Have you been hoarding this all to yourself?
No wonder you have good skin.
Why did you need flawless skin when you're a ghost?
I only put some on you since you're going out on a date.
Just a second.
This is nice.
- Let me see you.
- Right.
Here.
This one looks better.
Dongcheol.
These flowers are long overdue, aren't they?
Thank you, Dongcheol. They're beautiful.
Don't mention it. Besides, they're not even as pretty as you.
I actually have one more gift for you.
As you know, I work for a magician.
- What?
- A surprise gift.
Goodness.
Watch closely.
I bet it's in that hand.
Miyoung, please accept my love.
- Sure.
- Oh, no!
- No!
- Goodness.
Are you kidding me?
- Dongcheol!
- I'm going in.
- Where are you going. You can't.
- No!
I can't believe he botched that magic trick.
I spent the whole day teaching him that.
How can one learn that in one day? It looks complicated.
That's one of the easiest tricks in the book.
I can perform tricks that are more complicated.
Show me.
Do you know that rings have different meanings depending on the finger they're on?
Beats me.
One on the index finger stands for friendship.
The thumb stands for beliefs.
The middle finger stands for success.
The pinkie stands for luck.
How on earth did you do that?
A ring?
This.
Isn't it the one from your room?
And one on the ring finger stands for love.
I have had feelings for you for a long time.
Even before I knew about our past lives.
The one I like...
is Go Seulhae, the woman right in front of me.
The cool, confident, honest, and quirky Go Seulhae...
who never turns a blind eye to injustice.
I'm done mimicking my past life.
I'll now do things my own way.
As in how?
Poong Baek held back and waited.
But Cha Chawoong will be different.
Different how?
♫ I look into your transparent heart ♫
♫ The small flower seed that was blown away by the tickling wind ♫
♫ That kind of love ♫
♫ With a sigh, I knew it was love ♫
♫ Let's go together wherever the spring wind leads us ♫
♫ We walk holding hands and when we go to rest ♫
♫ We sit in the middle of spring and look into each other's hearts ♫
[From Now On, Showtime!]
Oh, how pretty.
Sorry, that must've sounded awkward.
I'm not good at keeping my feelings hidden.
Your exceptional beauty had me drawing a blank.
Seriously?
- Is there anything you want to eat?
- He's adorable.
Tell me and I will make it for you.
Would you like a cup of coffee?
♪ Would you like a cup of coffee? ♪
♪ I mustered up all the courage I had to say this ♪
I see you love it, my sweet girl.
[From Now On, Showtime!]