[Magic Factory]
[Park Hae Jin]
[Jin Ki Joo]
[Jung Joon Ho]
[Park Seo Yeon | Jeong Seok Yong | Ko Kyu Phil]
[From Now On, Showtime!]
[All characters, locations, groups, and incidents are fictional.]
[Staff ensured the animals' safety in the filming of this drama.]
[Episode 6}
Take her.
Are you kidding me?
You're only making us show our nastier side.
Come quietly while we ask you nicely.
What the...
Let go of her.
Mr. Cha?
Who's this punk?
Don't be an annoying brat and get lost.
What if I can't?
I asked you who you are.
Me?
Her partner.
Come on. Hurry!
I knew you'd end up like this again.
- What?
- The keys!
What? You had the keys until just now!
I have no idea what happened!
Darn you! You're always so useless.
What are you doing?
I'm just so frustrated.
I can't harm humans, so I'll just do this.
I told you that I got this.
Relax your shoulders!
I'm not doing this because I like you.
You see, your body is mine too.
You little...
So what do you say? If they hit you with that, you'll drop dead.
- Fine, just this once.
- Okay!
Let's do a little warm-up. It's been too long.
It's showtime!
Stay put!
Dalgu, bite him!
What was that?
Bring it on!
Stop! What are you doing?
It looks cool.
Go on! Keep going.
What? You fought with my energy. Why are you exhausted?
It's not because of you.
I sent too much of my energy to my employees.
Are you all right?
Hey! Get them!
No!
- You're surrounded.
- Drop your weapons!
Get them!
- Let go!
- Shut it!
- Come on!
- Let's go!
- Hey!
- Move it!
- Hey.
- Get in.
- Go!
Mr. Cha Chawoong.
We need your statement. You'll have to come with us.
Senior, he should see a doctor first.
Could you wait until he recovers?
- All right, then.
- Thank you.
Let's go.
Mr. Cha, are you all right?
How did you know? You came to my rescue.
- No, that's not what happened.
- I'm so touched.
You always said this was strictly business and that you didn't want to get involved,
so I didn't know you had such a warm heart.
Does it hurt a lot?
Let me take you to the hospital first.
It's not the injury.
My spiritual energy is depleted, so I just need to get some rest.
Take me home, please.
Oh, your employees must've helped out, too.
I knew it.
Thank you! You guys were so cool.
Can we get going?
Okay.
All right. Let's go.
Here.
Oh, no. I guess you're hurt.
I'll get you some pain relief patches. I know where they are.
I wanted to help Dalgu reach Nirvana,
so I went there to catch the jerk who killed Dalgu.
I wasn't there to rescue you, so don't be overly nice to me.
Whether you came for me or for Dalgu, you came anyway.
So you deserve to be treated nicely.
One moment.
"Me? Her partner."
Darn it. Why did I say that?
Her... Partner!
I don't see any pain relief patches.
Are they in that box?
What's all this?
[Kangguk Police Department]
Cha Sageum.
I found some pain relief patches, so you can get going.
Oh, okay.
I'll be off, then.
Get some rest.
- Have some.
- Thanks.
Is everything coming along smoothly for the drug case?
Yes, Sir.
They're still keeping their lips sealed,
but skimming through the evidence we've already seized, I know we have more than enough.
- Is that so?
- I mean, with Aris alone.
It's huge, you know?
This case will make you famous, Sir.
You can put your worries to rest.
All right.
Well, there's something I need you to take care of.
A press briefing? I already took care of all the preparations.
Of course, the spotlight will be on you, sir.
No, it's not about that.
- About Assemblyman Jang's son...
- Oh, that bald jerk.
- I'm sure that scumbag...
- I need you...
to delete his name before anyone else sees it.
What do you mean, Sir?
Don't ask questions. Just do as you're told!
Assemblyman Jang is planning to run for president, you know?
I'll give you all the support you need to move up the ladder.
Hey, Taesik. Keep up the great work.
I've got your back.
This is my dad.
The shaman intervened while they were trying to arrest the perp.
That's why they lost the perp, and my dad...
Right. I do recall reading an article about that.
But wasn't that shaman...
eventually, released due to lack of evidence?
There's been an accident at Kangguk Intersection.
Calling patrol units in the area to the scene.
Officer Go.
Officer Go!
There's been an accident at Kangguk Intersection.
Calling patrol units in the area to the scene.
Patrol...
Patrol 12, we're on our way.
What was that? Did you not check your battery?
You've been doing this for three years. Must I teach you such basics?
I'm sorry.
Seriously, what's with you today? You've spaced out all day!
I apologize. This won't happen again.
The soups that I eat at the memorial ceremonies don't even compare.
Doesn't it just perk you up?
There's nothing like ramyeon when your spiritual energy is depleted.
It was a good day though.
Officer Go said I looked so cool. You heard that, right?
Hey, she wasn't talking about you.
I did such an amazing job today.
I kicked them and poked them in the eye like this!
Hey, didn't you see Mr. Cha practically flying around?
I taught him those skills, you know.
That's right.
Mr. Cha can't do anything alone. He can't even punch.
He's a lousy fighter.
I don't care what you say. Dalgu was our hero today.
He recognized Hwang and led us there.
That's true.
By the way, I wonder why he hasn't entered Nirvana yet.
Officer Go said she'd find and bury him,
so I'm sure he'll ascend soon.
Areum, you seem to know a lot about dogs.
Did you have a dog in your antemortem life?
My dog was my only friend.
I contracted polio at a young age, so I never went out.
All I did was study and spend time with my dog.
I see. No wonder you're so smart.
Of course, that shrewd man wouldn't have hired you for no reason.
Shouldn't we save some ramyeon for Mr. Cha?
He's probably sick as a dog now.
Just let him get some sleep.
[Okhwa House]
What? He arrested a drug trafficking ring?
Why do I keep seeing a magician in the local news section?
Why doesn't he just become a cop, then?
This is all that lady cop's fault.
Excuse me. Are you open now?
No, not yet.
- Oh, you're that guy from the other day.
- You remember me?
- Are you unemployed?
- Sorry?
Today and the last time, too.
Most people are at work now, but you're here.
Right. It's my day off today.
Well, I want to get a reading for my love life.
Come back later. My grandma is busy right now.
You can do it.
I can't. I'm still training.
Then I'll help you clean.
- No, it's okay.
- Let me help.
- Why?
- Just let me help you.
[Okhwa House]
You like someone, don't you?
- Sorry?
- You'd better watch out.
You asked for a reading, so I told you what I saw.
My goodness. You're already head over heels.
Isn't that a good thing?
I want to fall hard for her.
She's like a swamp. She's too dangerous.
Your life could be turned upside down like this.
So what? I'll just let it happen.
What?
I'm telling you. She's like a little witch.
She thinks she's pretty and makes other people do all the work.
And she's very greedy with money.
In any case,
you should be careful.
What an unusual way to introduce yourself.
Take this to Chawoong.
Woong?
My goodness. Why does he keep getting involved in stuff like that?
Check in on him and see if he's okay.
Don't say useless things that could upset him.
Okay, I heard you. When did I ever say useless stuff?
- The house?
- It's on the market?
You what? Put the house on the market?
Yes.
We'll move to the outskirts of Gyeonggi... as soon as this house is sold.
What? Who are you to decide that?
This is my house.
Of course, I can make this decision. Whose permission do I need?
Then, what about my plan to enter Nirvana? And the civil police unit?
Go Seulhae isn't the only one with a strong seven-star channel. We'll find an alternative.
Okay, but that will take forever.
I'm not moving. I refuse.
I liked this neighborhood because my wife and daughter were here.
If we move, I won't be able to see them often.
You can take the bus and visit them on weekends.
There's a young female ghost whom I have fallen for.
That young lady in a white dress... who's always sitting at the intersection?
- She's been there since last month.
- You saw her, too?
- I knew she was your type.
- You can't even strike up a conversation anyway.
Just forget her.
I don't care where we live as long as there's wifi.
But I quite like Officer Go.
I was worried about your health, so I put my skills to use.
You didn't have to do that.
Look at you being difficult again. It's cute.
Be honest.
I know you missed me.
You were waiting for me, weren't you?
My goodness.
I took some time out of my busy schedule to come here,
so let's go. It's a date!
Go alone.
I'm expecting a guest.
Who?
That... lady cop with a puppy face?
- No, my realtor.
- Realtor? Why?
- Because I'm selling the house.
- What?
Woong! I moved here because of you.
You can't move!
What am I going to do? No, don't move.
Let go of me.
Go tell your grandma...
that I'll accept it this time, but not again.
This is such a nuisance.
It's this house.
You don't even need to see the inside. It's perfect.
My gosh. Why would you want to buy a haunted house?
Excuse me. What did you say just now?
Oh, no. You heard that? I was just talking to myself.
Please don't mind me.
But there must be a reason the owner wants to sell it fast.
No, don't listen to her. It's not true, ma'am.
Let's go inside and take a look first.
- Hello.
Oh, my. Everything looks flawless.
You took such good care of the house.
Have a look around.
Okay, thank you. This way.
This is the master bedroom.
As you can see, it gets a lot of sun.
You can keep this space separate...
or combine it with the living room if you want to keep it more open.
As you can see, the layout maximizes space in every room.
It was designed by a world-renowned interior designer.
The top-of-the-line Italian brand... Oh, what was it called? Bol...
- Bultani.
- Yes! Bultani.
You know Bultani, right? It's from that brand.
Look at this.
I'll show you.
Let's see. It's different from the machines in my neighborhood.
What do I do?
[Start]
This is very nice.
My gosh, what's wrong with this?
Goodness. Oh, no!
- Oh, no.
- My gosh. Mr. Cha!
- Careful.
- Mr. Cha! Hey!
Mr. Cha, your house is so luxurious and modern, just like you.
Are you ready to sign the contract?
Here. You brought your seal, right?
Here and... My gosh, what's happening?
What is happening?
My gosh!
Look, that thing... What's wrong with it?
Goodness.
- My gosh.
- What is going on?
- Gosh!
- My goodness! What is happening?
- Oh, no.
- What is going on?
Well, it's just a magic trick.
Surprise!
You scared me for a second.
Stop!
[Kang Areum | Nam Sanggeon | Ma Dongcheol]
You're so mischievous.
He's a magician, you know.
- Have a seat.
- Yes.
Stamp your seal right here.
Here, yes.
- My gosh!
- Goodness.
What is happening?
- What is this?
- Gosh! This can't be a magic trick.
- Let's go.
- Hurry!
These are just plush toys!
Quit your antics.
What kind of joke is this? Are you out of your mind?
This is highly inappropriate.
I just followed Adviser Choi's orders.
Is he your boss?
Who do you think is the owner of this company?
Did I ever ask you to do this?
I told you we're not moving.
You shouldn't have gone against the Worshipping Spirit.
Here.
Seriously?
[Kangguk Police Department]
Seulhae.
Senior!
What brings you here?
I stopped by on my way from lunch to see you.
You don't look too good.
I couldn't get much sleep last night.
Why? Is something troubling you?
No, nothing like that.
Aren't you here to tell me something?
I thought long and hard if I should or not.
But it's best if you know.
While looking into the Full Moon Murderer,
I came across shaman Cha Sageum's family status.
He only had one family member.
And who is that?
Someone you know.
Cha Chawoong. He's Cha Sageum's grandson.
I thought it was a coincidence and Cha Chawoong had no idea about it.
Officer Go.
Her father died because of your grandfather.
I thought you should know that.
Stop taking advantage of Seulhae... and stay out of her life.
Whether I take advantage of her or vanish from her life...
is up to me to decide.
Did Mr. Cha really say that?
Something felt off about him from the beginning.
Cha Chawoong doesn't care about... other people's pain.
Knowing that, I thought you shouldn't keep crossing paths with him.
Were you really close to him?
Other than working together in the civil police unit,
was there anything else?
No.
If you feel uncomfortable, how about quitting being in charge?
I'll even try to get you transferred to a different station if you want.
Do you understand why we must move now?
So Officer Go...
is Detective Go Youngshik's daughter?
Who would've known?
That's why we can't live here any longer.
Crossing paths and getting on each other's nerves...
will bring us enough pain as is.
I understand.
With that said, please start packing.
I never knew he had such a painful past.
Me neither.
I always thought he was a haughty, self-centered jerk.
Aren't moves usually full-service these days?
Of course. There's no way we can move all of these.
Fate...
is truly frightening.
You're right.
Just when things are getting peaceful,
the above throws hot water at me.
Because I'm a sinner, they're playing the fool with me.
You became a spirit to expiate karma, right?
Did something happen in your past life?
Every life has a story.
And I did, too.
Then, General,
make a clean slate once and for all.
As you know, karma continues from this world...
to the afterlife and the afterlife... to the next life.
Yes, you're on point.
I've suffered enough for the past 2,000 years.
It'd be a waste if I failed now.
How must I get on about it?
[Full Moon Murderer's 5th victim rescued, but detective passes away]
Who is it?
Who is...
Really? Playing pranks?
Right.
Could you be from Magic Factory?
Why are you here?
Come in.
Would you like something to drink?
Coffee or green tea?
You just want me to sit?
Yes.
Did Mr. Cha send you here?
If so, I have nothing to say.
He really let me down.
That is the very reason I came.
I'm going to tell you... what really happened that day ten years ago.
Okay?
Hello?
Are they gone?
No.
If only I could hear something.
I forgot.
She can't hear me, can she?
Darn it.
Yes! The laptop!
Let's start with a greeting.
[H]
He... Gosh, where is it?
[He]
- Hel...
- He...
[Hel]
Hel with a lot of L.
Yes. Then O.
[Hello]
- Hello with four O?
- No, that's not it.
What's this code?
Goodness. Typing isn't easy at all.
- Is that it?
- No, wait a second.
- Again.
- Why delete everything?
Next. Hold on.
[Ne]
[Next]
T for time.
Does that mean they'll come again next time?
Yes, that's it.
- My gosh.
- It is?
Yes, it is.
- It is? Nodding, all right.
- Yes.
Right, then I'll see you off.
Please come again.
Gosh.
That day,
a black rainstorm came rushing from the other side.
Scratch that.
It was just wind, not a rainstorm.
[That day, a black wind...]
The branches swayed in all directions.
Crows cried at that moment.
Caw.
And...
his robe fluttering in the air, a mysterious man appears.
The name is Choi Geom!
Seriously, Adviser! Are you writing an autobiography?
We've been at it for three hours!
Isn't this a letter? Make it crisp to the point.
But I should explain every detail of that day.
And it's going down on paper, so I can't be sloppy.
I should liven it up to make it feel more realistic.
That's what people who don't read books do.
Why don't you just talk to her?
I'd love to. But I can't converse with a human being, can I?
Maybe.
What?
I can?
In a paper on the poltergeist phenomenon,
it said a spirit's voice reacts at 19 Hertz.
- Can you do it?
- I'm not sure.
But it should be better than writing your autobiography.
I'll try it.
Oh, my. If it isn't Chawoong's girlfriend.
Oh, my. If it isn't Cha Chawoong's fiancee.
Yes, that's me. Cheon Yeji.
So you remember.
By the way, I'm not his girlfriend.
My gosh, Seulhae! Really? Did you two break up?
What great news!
Did you dump him or did he dump you?
Forget it. That's not important now.
Anyway, thank you so much.
So that's why he's moving.
Moving?
You must have fought big for him to do that.
Will a bottle be enough?
These are on me.
That quack shaman brought it on himself.
He tried to extort money from me.
That fraud. Take this!
We should just burn this cult fanatic's house down.
He's an embarrassment to the whole town.
No, Chawoong!
You must protect the shrine.
I won't live like you, Grandfather.
No matter how much you help others, nobody helps when you need it...
or believes in you. So why should I?
Are you a fool?
Are you crazy?
[Crook]
[Magic Factory]
[Information Theory]
[Anomaly detected]
Aris intentionally approached celebrities and wealthy people,
addicted them to drugs, continued to supply them,
and secured a solid client base.
Didn't you know that?
How could I? She's a total stranger.
How about any words or moves that seemed suspicious?
Like a special offer.
I've already told you about the coffee stick.
Nothing other than that.
And she put it in my bag without my permission.
I had zero knowledge that it was drugs.
Then... how did you know Officer Go was held in that building?
I live in that neighborhood.
I was passing by and just happened to see her.
Does that bother you, too?
Should I have turned a blind eye?
I wonder how you were passing by such a remote area...
so early in the morning and happened to see her.
"Aren't you also a druggie?"
Just ask me straight.
And stop wasting my energy.
Look through my call records and text messages.
Let's do a drug test, too.
That should be easier.
Fine.
Then I'll take that you agree to a urine and hair sample.
We'll run the drug test with it.
Seulhae?
I'm here to fix the date on a document.
- I see. Go once you've done that.
- Okay.
Mr. Cha!
A word, please.
I heard you're moving.
Why?
Are you running away?
Running away?
Why would I?
Cha Sageum, your grandfather.
Why didn't you tell me? The least you could do was apologize.
I did nothing wrong.
My dad died.
But you don't feel one bit guilty?
It wasn't my grandfather's fault.
On the contrary, Detective Go...
ruined both my life and my grandfather's.
You mean my dad?
Yes.
The one who asked for help in catching the culprit...
was Detective Go Youngshik.
Nonsense.
- The chief told me a quack shaman messed everything up...
- The chief?
You already believe that's the truth,
so what use is this conversation?
You're not going to listen anyway.
The chief was at the scene that day.
If anything, his testimony is more truthful than...
Here's the truth I know.
If it weren't for Detective Go Youngshik,
my grandfather wouldn't have been considered a fraud...
and I would have been able to live with my family.
Don't shoot your mouth off! Why my dad?
Why?
You asked for the same thing from me.
Help.
As much as you despised my grandfather,
I resented your father.
Quack shaman?
I'd watch my words if I were you.
Is this the real estate office? It's Cha Chawoong.
Cut my house price in half and sell it as soon as possible.
Goodness, that punk. He didn't have to throw these away.
You scared me!
What happened to you?
You look like the dead.
What's this?
Ghost intelligence. In other words, a GI speaker.
What?
I've heard of AI speakers before.
Don't compare this to that.
I pushed the ghost's boundaries with this.
Really?
What does it do?
Do you want to try it?
This here is an ordinary voice recorder.
Say something.
What? Like what?
- Okay. Then how about I sing a...
- That should do.
Already?
As you can see, it works at a different frequency,
so it can't record our voices.
But this GI speaker I invented can.
For real?
So we can do something with this?
What? Like what?
- Okay. Then how about I sing a...
- It...
- That should do.
- It really works.
What do you think? Satisfied?
You're amazing.
My gosh.
The poor world lost such a talented person so early.
Actually, no.
You're nothing short of a blessing to me.
Yes, a blessing.
How did she do this?
[Discounts, Free gifts]
We can't tell if this student stole the phone from just this alone.
The camera couldn't catch him because this is a blind stop.
He took advantage of it.
I didn't steal it. I swear.
But how was this in your pocket?
Well...
I'm not too sure either.
Just apologize to him.
There's evidence right here.
Officer, it's not me. I didn't steal it.
Please believe me.
And your parents' number?
Even if it's a minor theft,
you can end up in jail for up to six years...
or be charged with up to 10,000 dollars...
depending on the seriousness.
Then you can't dodge the criminal punishment.
So I need your parents' numbers to settle.
Then you could be released with just a warning.
He doesn't have parents.
How about any other guardians?
He lives with his grandmother.
But she's in no condition to move, so she can't come here.
Then your teacher's number will do.
Officer, I didn't do it. Trust me.
I really have no clue why that phone was in my pocket.
Tell them. You must have seen the whole thing next to me.
Did I steal it?
Hey, just tell her the truth.
- What?
- Think about it.
The police are busy as it is.
- You'll get busted soon, so...
- What was that, jerk?
Did you see me steal it? Did you?
- And what are you so happy about?
- Stop it.
- Let go.
- Stop.
[Police]
I'm telling you.
Yes. He's being questioned at the police station right now.
That blockhead.
He didn't even realize I put the phone in his pocket.
That jerk.
Darn it.
It's a relief the misunderstanding was cleared.
You wouldn't have believed me if it weren't for his phone call.
- I'm sorry. But the evidence and testimony...
- You're the police.
Shouldn't the police listen to both sides?
But you only listened to the owner and weren't willing to listen to me.
You almost ruined my life.
Do you know that?
The chief? You already believe that's the truth,
so what use is this conversation?
You're not going to listen anyway.
It being at half price was definitely appealing.
He offered to purchase it without even taking a look.
You can sign right here.
It's true I don't know him, but I know his words are sincere.
And I can't turn a blind eye to it
so that I can make it out alone.
You can call it what you want, but how many perps have we caught together so far?
The one with spiritual power teams up with a pretty cop... to catch bad guys.
We're like Superman and Lois Lane.
Mr. Cha. What's wrong?
Are you suddenly having second thoughts?
No, it's not that.
Of course not. I'll stamp my seal.
[Cha Chawoong]
Maybe we should ask Mr. Cha to reserve a spot next to our ancestral tablets.
Dalgu slept on the floor all night.
Poor thing.
As if he'd ever do that.
He badly wants the dog gone.
Why won't this dog enter Nirvana though?
I thought he was found and buried.
What unresolved business does he have?
Dalgu, do you have more affairs to sort out?
What is it that you wish to do?
Is it because you died as a bachelor, too?
Why don't we find him a nice dog to mate with?
You and your ideas.
That's because I know how lonely it can get.
Mr. Nam, I bet his heart is as black as coal.
Dalgu, where are you going?
- Dalgu!
- What on earth...
Dalgu, what's wrong?
Is something here?
[My little brother Dalgu]
Dalgu, is this it?
That darn pig.
The collar has Dalgu's name and the owner's phone number,
so he threw it away to keep Dalgu from being found.
No wonder Dalgu wasn't able to leave the living.
This must be of importance to him.
We should give this to Mr. Cha and have it buried too.
Then Dalgu will enter Nirvana.
Dalgu, is this what you've been looking for?
Will you finally be able to move on?
This is your little brother, Dalgu.
[My little brother Dalgu]
Here.
Drink.
You want details? Regarding what exactly?
On the day my dad died, you said the shaman named Cha Sageum...
interfered with the arrest.
I was hoping to hear what actually happened.
Goodness. But it happened over ten years ago.
Didn't the news article cover everything?
Why has it suddenly intrigued you?
I was wondering if my dad and the shaman... knew each other before that day.
Who speaks such nonsense?
Let me be clear.
That day, right before your dad and I...
were about to move in on the perpetrator, that shaman cut in.
Not only did he invade our scene, but he recited some chants causing quite a scene.
The shaman's life was at risk, which is why we had to intervene.
What happened to your father
was the result of him saving the shaman.
How did the shaman know that the Full Moon Murderer was there?
That's exactly why we suspected that the two were in cahoots.
A partnership gone wrong is what we thought.
I guess that's a reasonable deduction,
but he was released based on a lack of evidence...
Seulhae, that's enough.
Youngshik wouldn't want his daughter to be hung up on him
when she has a bright future ahead of her.
Isn't it about time you quit the force
and find a nice man to marry?
You can count on me to walk you down the aisle instead.
Better yet, why don't I set you up with someone?
Go ahead. Have your tea.
Naeun, is that you?
But I didn't buy anything online.
Officer Go!
She must be able to hear us.
Did this startle you?
Areum, you can't surprise her like that.
Are you Mr. Cha's employees?
Yes, Officer Go. It's us.
Gosh, hello.
I see you're here together this time.
That's right.
We're in front of you right now.
Mr. Cha has had it rough these days,
but it must've been the same for you, too.
It's why we... I mean, that's why Areum made this device.
The one who was there ten years ago...
wanted to clear up all misunderstandings.
Who may that be?
It's me.
As Cha Sageum's Worshipping Spirit,
I was present at the scene along with Detective Go.
Is it true that my dad went to see the shaman?
I mean, Mr. Cha's grandfather?
Before I tell you anything,
I request that you believe my words just like you believe in our existence.
I'm a spirit of 2,000 years who will soon enter Nirvana.
What would I gain from lying?
For the past 2,000 years, I have stayed in the Cha family
making sure that evil spirits were sealed.
But one day, an evil spirit escaped and possessed a random human.
A human possessed by the evil spirit.
It was none other
than the Full Moon Murderer.
An evil spirit?
Detective Go was after the serial killer
while Cha Sageum was after the evil spirit
both hoping to prevent more of its evil deeds.
The two joined forces.
Ten years ago, on that day,
they almost found success.
He must be around here.
I can sense his energy.
We should hurry.
The full moon will soon be shining.
I will set up a force field so that it can't escape.
That's your window of opportunity.
Yes, Mr. Cha.
Gosh.
You want the promotion all to yourself, is that it?
As if I'd ever let that happen.
Pass it on to me.
Your energy.
Changho?
Worthless humans.
Don't move.
You... It's you that death will find today.
Release me.
I order you as your master.
Hurry.
Please place it on the urn.
Only that way will the evil spirit remain sealed.
Hurry.
No.
Youngshik.
Youngshik...
I...
That...
is what happened.
Dad...
I didn't know.
I had no idea.
I only believed Chief Seo's story.
Of course.
In the eyes of a mortal who has no knowledge of our world,
it would've seemed as though Sageum was pulling tricks.
Detective Go and Sageum's teaming up
was hidden from his coworkers.
I'm sure you understand...
why it had to be a secret.
[To my good partner, from Youngshik]
Not aware of the situation, I told Mr. Cha...
I'm sorry.
This all happened...
because I let the spirit escape and failed to capture it on time.
It's my fault.
What?
The evil spirit broke free from our family?
Yes.
And you're just telling me now, after a whole ten years?
You were never home.
I couldn't speak to someone who wasn't present.
Unbelievable.
I said too many things that I shouldn't have to Go Seulhae.
Oh, that. I managed to solve that issue, too.
Areum helped me tell her the truth,
so mend the bridge when you can.
You told her everything?
How?
Areum made this device that looks like a radio.
She called it a G... What was it again?
Well, ask her when you can.
Anyway, aren't you grateful that I saved the day?
You really are a piece of work.
(Why you little...)
So...
How is Ms. Go doing?
Who knows? Check on her if you're that curious.
That little brat.
[Go Seulhae]
Darn it. If only he had told me sooner.
What do I do?
Mr. Cha, I have a favor to ask.
Could you have this delivered?
I'm in no state to do people favors!
Then I'll revisit this.
Hold on!
Give me that.
[Dalgu's]
[Dalgu, my dear brother, goodbye.]
Mr. Magician!
As asked,
I brought Officer Go with me.
Kid, when did I tell you to bring her?
I told you to say that... she should come if she had the time.
I can't believe you had a kid run errands for you.
You could've come to me if you had something to say.
This from a guy who always ignores my calls.
What did you want to say?
Well...
It's nothing much.
I found this, you see.
Wait.
[My little brother Dalgu]
It's Dalgu's collar.
[Dalgu, my dear brother, goodbye.]
[My little brother Dalgu]
I'm sure Dalgu went to a good place.
Let's wish him that.
Hey, kid.
Being a gifted magician... lets me talk to Dalgu's spirit.
Really?
Dalgu says...
he was happiest... when he was with you.
[Dalgu, my dear brother, goodbye.]
He enjoyed playing Frisbee...
and walking around the neighborhood with you.
He's grateful for all the times you nursed him back to health.
He woke up excited...
thinking about what games to play.
Mr. Magician, please tell Dalgu...
that even though we can't see each other...
I'll always be his brother.
That I'll wish for him never to get lonely...
and... that I miss him so much.
Of course, but I'm sure he has already heard it all.
Did Dalgu really say all those things?
You didn't make that up, did you?
I added some details, but Dalgu confirmed the rest.
Even if you don't believe me, there's nothing I can do about it.
Well, I believe you.
Adviser Choi told me about what happened ten years ago.
I'm sorry.
Why? I'm the one who should apologize.
I resented you based on false facts.
Still, I didn't have to be that confrontational.
I guess.
I was deeply wounded that day, you know.
Your words have a way of making people bleed.
In a way, I guess that's a gift, too.
Well, that...
Come to think of it though, you were right to be offended.
People condemned your grandfather, calling him a liar.
You must've felt wronged.
For ten years, it must've only made you angrier.
You must've hated people... as much as I missed my dad.
But I know that ghosts exist, so don't be intimidated by me.
Me? Intimidated by you?
That's right.
Don't be confrontational as a defense mechanism.
Even though everyone else calls you a liar,
I'll believe what you say.
Just like my dad believed your grandfather's words.
That's how partnerships work.
Okay?
You're not here with me
Where are you?
Maybe I missed you
"Okay" it is, then.
Are our memories
Darn it.
The five fishermen who went missing in Gangneung...
are still lost at sea.
Since they were reported missing, the maritime police...
have been searching the waters via cutters and aircraft,
but to no avail.
Around the time the fishing boat was found,
no surging waves or high winds were reported.
But still, all five fishermen were nowhere to be seen
when the boat was found
which only makes us question how they went missing.
The authorities are looking into...
Mr. Cha, does this mean you're back in the civil police unit?
Of course. There's no better way to improve my public image.
Then, are you free tomorrow?
At what time?
Just a second.
- Hello?
- This is your real estate agent.
Double the cancellation fee was successfully wired.
The sales contract on your house has been breached,
but may I ask why you changed your mind?
Of course. I got the message. Thank you.
What was that about?
That? Well...
The potential buyer changed his mind about purchasing the house.
Really?
Does this mean you're staying? You are, right?
Yes. That's how it is, I guess.
I'm glad.
It's a freak show
Hidden trap with my magic stick
You got me struck, there's no answer
Giving my chills, Oh I love this thrill, I'll tell you the truth
On my freak show
Come a little closer, I'm gonna show you
[From Now On, Showtime!]
Is it because of Officer Go?
You must see her in a romantic way.
I'm not that desperate, you know.
Why are you flirting instead of working?
We're not!
Does it seem like we're dating or something?
Even though you like someone, you don't want to acknowledge it.
I love it.
You don't remember anything?
I'm saying that we should play matchmaker for them.
Mr. Cha may not be the best at giving love,
but he seems to have a kind and gentle soul.
Love?
I'm capable of it, too.
[From Now On, Showtime!]