Few people ate today.
No one ate.
I'll eat.
You have no manners at all.
Master, is it on the table?
No rules.
No need to wait.
Master, I don't want to eat.
Xiaorou went down the mountain with Yulang.
I won't eat either.
I need to prepare some ointment
for wounds to his master.
What happened to his master?
Is injured.
Saying my butt hurts
because I'm lying on the kang.
My butt hurts.
And lying prone.
He's...
Lying prone like this.
Or...
Lying prone like this?
Dezhu, are you out of your mind?
Aren't you lying down?
This is lying down.
So here comes the question.
Why isn't Master sitting down?
Didn't I tell you just now?
My butt hurts.
Is it hurt?
I can't sit up.
What medicine should you prepare for Master?
Wound medicine?
What are those for?
Your brain is shrinking as you live.
What is the sore wound medicine for?
Scratch.
And scald,
It's to stop the bleeding.
Nothing.
You two can eat.
My butt hurts.
Stop bleeding.
Eldest Brother,
the rapist
and got stabbed by me.
Master's buttocks ached today.
Is this something
something odd?
Could it be
rapist?
It's Master.
That's him.
Can you?
See that?
The strength of this stick skill
see that?
This is Mei Family Stickstick.
It turns out that I was teaching
Is the Gao family's method.
We're from the Tianchi Gang.
The method of palm?
Now she changes the stick method.
It
It's not aiming at attack
the main reason is
to channel the meridians.
And open seven apertures.
To improve your health.
At your age,
mother Pornpan,
It's good that you're here to practice.
Are you using the stick
or the stick?
You were behaving like a monkey.
How can you say that?
Can you show some respect?
This is Mei Fa Fight.
What do you mean by playing monkey?
What are you talking about?
Don't be so loud.
Let's watch.
Then go home.
Mind your words.
The recruitment of students
any enrollment?
Anyone who's registered?
Don't be like him.
He is quite young.
Still young?
Because he is strict
of disciplining his disciples strictly.
That's the only way to be an excellent disciple.
You're really bold.
Recruit students?
Aren't you afraid the government will arrest you?
I'm not.
Because now she's
sect Leader Mei.
Nothing to do with Tian Chi Gang.
I've passed Heavenly Chi Gang to him.
The more reason we can't go.
Just go.
Get out of here.
Liar. Come on.
He's a liar!
Say something.
You are a liar!
Don't say those harsh words.
What you mean by liar
you, the liar!
Tell me you don't want to learn.
You really have a bad temper.
You really need to improve your temper.
What? My temper.
I told you it wouldn't work.
Now you are the dung beetle
notorious
we all know that Heavenly Lake is defeated,
we can't recruit any new students.
Another one.
What the hell did you introduce
we are not selling medicine.
You have a good command of all five senses.
How did I trick you
what can I tell you?
You won't be able to do this.
Stop thinking. Forget it.
Shame on you.
Embarrassing? What's the trick?
We should
this incident again.
What if it wasn't Master?
You can't judge a person's mind by his or her appearance.
Back then, Huashan Sect's leader Yue Buqun
In front of his disciples,
but I still have five men and six women.
Who would've thought
he hid himself that well.
Don't mention Yue Buqun.
Let's talk about Xi Men Qing.
On the surface,
a man of striking appearance
and secretly,
he's doing
theft and prostitution.
For causing Mr. Wu's death.
Our master
Is not as handsome
as Xi Qing,
he dare not go out in the daytime.
But at night
to hide his face
can't you see what he looks like?
Ximen Qing.
Ximen Changhai.
Could it be that the Ximen family
picked flowers as well?
This root
younger Sister,
what are you talking about?
Everything you said.
My father was so good to you all.
And you're even suspecting him behind his back.
Are you still human?
Xiaorou.
Lower your voice.
Listen to me.
When it comes to major issues of principle,
make your position clear.
That matter
almost done.
But please don't tell Master.
It'll alert the enemy.
We must
we're trying to
to turn Master
forsake heresy and return to the truth
rou.
Rou.
What to do?
You're listening to me?
I thought to myself,
to prevent more women from
be harmed,
we should uphold righteousness above family loyalty.
How do you want to kill them?
Just watch.
Pervert!
She is resting there.
Two Senior Brothers,
I thought it over.
We are convinced
master is the rapist?
That's too hasty.
After all, we don't have enough evidence.
I was afraid that we would frame Master.
Your Highness,
we didn't want that.
After all, we got involved.
Face it.
You know what?
Why does he always
In recent months?
If you can't find him, then...
Such an evil stratagem.
I have faith in you.
But I also believe in Master.
If the rapist wasn't Master,
I...
I'm your grandson!
Your Master is a rapist?
He's my grandson.
It's none of my business.
We're the grandchild.
What about
senior Brother.
If you two
Insist on thinking that I'm
who steals flowers.
I have my reservations.
I won't get involved.
This brat.
I'm going back to sleep.
That's crap.
Look at that dead man.
We should have a sense of justice.
Come on.
Master.
I call you Master.
Maybe he'll
to call you Master
I'm the last to call you Master.
Are you leaving?
It's not certain who will leave first.
What do you mean?
Although I, Zhao Dezhu,
although we were born in the wild,
they still have
a sense of righteousness.
Today,
on behalf of the
on behalf of those innocent people
and bring you to justice.
Get rid of an evil for the people
and give them justice.
Although I was a teacher for a day,
and always a father,
how about the last one?
But when it comes to major issues of principle,
I still can stand
and stand on your side.
This ill-advised plan
I have no choice.
Master,
I hope you can understand.
Grab a rope
for what?
Should we hang ourselves?
Don't argue, OK?
Goodness.
In front of both of us.
We will be gentle.
You have to explain to the government,
this will not be the same.
You two are talking nonsense.
Does it hurt?
Both of you.
Really something.
To become the Chief?
Do you want to strangle
to strangle him?
Rapist?
Just tell the truth.
Come on.
Pick what?
Rapist?
Who is it?
You
I've been in Que Sword Sect for so long
I don't have a wife
I'm waiting here.
But I don't need to pick flowers.
What do you mean?
Stop it.
What happened to your buttocks?
You don't know?
It's a witness.
Material evidence?
And your wound.
What wounds?
How did you get the wound on your buttocks?
Are you not talking nonsense?
My ass...
I was careless
when cooking the tea.
When the kettle is tilted,
I put it on.
It just burns!
What happened?
What a good excuse.
Looks like you're an old hand.
You two.
Show us your wound?
What do you mean?
You can cure him?
Look at this.
It's done.
It hurts.
It's stuck! Come on!
It's all glued on.
Dezhu.
Where did you go?
I stabbed
should be of two parts.
The horizontal opening,
vertical Mouth.
I don't have any mouth.
You're really cunning...
He is
got stabbed by a knife.
In order to
deceive
she scalded
on purpose.
What do you two want?
Are you trying to rebel?
Just tell me if you want to leave.
Alright?
What are you talking about?
Looks like you're stubborn.
I've taken them off.
Look at this wound.
How else can I be hurt?
Is your skin peeling off?
Dezhu.
It's just a scalded blister.
There's no hole inside.
That's right.
Did you heal so fast, master?
What was the misunderstanding?
What are you talking about?
Are they scald or hemorrhoids?
Which are they?
They are scalds.
Whose hemorrhoids are external?
You two are studying my butts.
My ass?
Put it on!
Quickly come and help.
Xiaorou has been taken
captured by a butterfly.
Honey,
hurry up.
Come on, Mrs. Dezhu. Give me a hand.
Hurry up!
Honey, get up.
Honey,
what's going on?
My head hurts.
What's going on?
Hurry up.
Finished.
Xiaorou is caught
got caught by that butterfly.
It seems that the rapist
Is someone else.
What did I say?
Xiaorou,
honey,
lock the doors and windows.
I am going to save Xiaorou.
Where are you going?
What's up, sister-in-law?
Eldest Brother.
Mr. Jade.
Hurry and save Xiaorou.
Xiaorou was caught by the rapist
by the rapist.
Hurry up!
You've wronged me.
Why are you still blaming us
why are you still blaming us?
Also,
didn't Second Brother say that
the rapist was stabbed.
If he gets stabbed by the thief.
Can you stop acting like this?
Go and save them.
Alright.
Sister.
The others
and they even decided to
what do they want to do to my father?
They want to uphold justice at the expense of relatives.
Report to the authority.
Report to the authority?
That won't do.
What will my father do?
For light punishment, he'll be locked up for two years.
What about the heavier one?
Be executed by slicing them.
I can't.
My father can't die.
Xiaoqin.
My father was not that kind of person.
I also thought about it carefully.
Master,
to be that kind of person.
Right.
But they have the evidence.
Sister-in-law.
Don't believe them.
Please help my dad, okay?
I can't even
a weak woman?
Sister-in-law.
I have an idea.
Got it?
But if Master is really a butterfly,
that would be enough.
Sister-in-law.
How could my father be a butterfly?
My father is the chief of the martial art world.
Is he capable of that?
Alright.
I'll take a chance.
Master isn't that kind of person.
Thank you, sister-in-law.
I'm leaving then.
They're starting now?
Come and help.
The butterfly is captured by Xiaorou.
Hey.
Xiaorou has been taken away by a butterfly.
Quickly, come and help.
Senior Sister.
Senior sister.
Rou.
Senior Sister.
Have you found Senior Sister?
No, she is not.
See? I told you.
Master is not the rapist at all.
Enough.
I'm the grandson, okay?
Why are you still doing this?
What are you doing?
Come find Senior Sister.
Just go.
Grandson.
Senior Sister.
Miss, don't be nervous.
I am not the rapist.
I'm the rapist.
Why do you call me that?
I have rules to do things.
Listen carefully.
I will take off
when I remove the thing from your mouth,
then shout at the top of your voice.
Call for help.
The louder you shout,
the more successful I feel.
And then?
I'll do whatever I want.
I laughed like crazy
♫ I turned my back ♫
And here you're crying your eyes out...
Got it?
It starts.
Speak louder.
Help
help
like this.
Help
help!
The procedure is enough.
Xiaorou.
Father.
Xiaorou. Xiaolou.
When will you come back to me?
Xiaorou.
Because I missed you so much.
You're heartbroken
hold it back,
don't cry.
That's bullshit!
She's not your wife now?
Stop it.
Dezhu, what do you mean?
You mean that
that I should get caught.
If you were caught by others,
you will be sent back instantly.
Besides that,
give us 400 kg of rice!
Zhao Dezhu,
did you go too far?
Shut up.
Xiaorou.
You're back.
Rou. Rou.
I'm back
hurry up!
Hurry up!
All right.
Stop crying.
What's going on?
Stand up.
Who sent it back?
Sister-in-law!
I was caught by the rapist.
Yes
your senior brothers all know about it.
Who saved you?
My father.
Who saved my father for me.
Xiaorou, are you muddled?
Master slept for several hours
for several hours.
That's right.
That's impossible.
Go and have a look.
It's my father who saved me.
Look at that.
Come on.
You frightened her.
Your father is sleeping.
Senior.
Hey!
Why are you here?
I'm here to see you.
Do you also think that I have a blurred vision?
Others think that.
I believe that you can
but I really saw my father.
My father really saved me.
But Master,
he's been sleeping in the room.
How do you explain this?
Are you sure that
after I was abducted by the flower-picking robbers,
my father never left home.
I am sure that
that's strange.
I checked his eyes.
Is indeed the triangular eyes
unique triangular eyes.
And we're from the same family.
I have that feeling.
We have deep enough feelings.
Between hearts
that's true.
Hey!
You're trying to get in the mood behind my back.
Right?
Second Brother.
Why are you here? Second Brother!
Can I watch you two if I don't come?
Today I will
I'll jump off the cliff.
To fulfill your wish.
Alright?
Second Brother.
Just hear me out.
Don't stop me.
Second Brother.
Second Brother!
Hold onto me.
Don't let go of it.
Don't loosen your hand.
You come up first.
You first.
What's going on with you two?
What do you mean?
It was about the father-daughter relationship.
How is that relevant to me?
Right.
Come up here!
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Pull me up.
Second Brother,
why didn't you tell me earlier?
You didn't listen to me either.
It's my master who saved you,
then who's the one in your family?
Second Brother.
I wonder if you have heard of
there is a kind of occult in the world of martial arts
called disguise technique.
Disguise technique?
Did someone change
to disguise as Master?
No wonder Master was acting strangely
It was strange.
Mysterious.
I suspect that he is not possessed by the devil.
I have something to tell you.
Then he'll disguise himself as my father
will my father be in danger?
Senior Sister,
don't worry.
This is just our speculation.
If this person
really use this disguise technique,
then his face
he'll surely have flaws
then how should we
make him expose himself?
I have to think about that.
No more pondering.
I won't believe it
I won't believe it.
They look so ugly.
I'm an old man.
What the heck is that?
This is even older.
What's this?
It's too shabby.
My goodness.
Your face is good.
That's good.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
That matchmaker
make this pair of mandarin ducks for me.
You mean that...
Is older than the other.
You know...
Let me ask you this.
Who exactly are you?
Who am I?
I am your master.
You are my Master.
You're not my master.
You're a fake one.
Didn't I tell you that?
Don't you
If you don't believe me?
If my guess is right,
Is this your disguise skill?
What skill?
The disguise technique.
You wore a disguise.
Who is behind your face?
No one is there.
You are good at pretending.
Your face is
It's a fake face.
Who is the man behind the fake face?
Behind the fake face?
Are you looking for Erpifacial?
Instead of going to Que Sword Gate?
You want to turn against me?
Who sent you here?
What's your intention?
What is your intention?
I gave you face, right?
Take it off.
Let me see it.
Isn't this still you?
And playing with us?
Come on,
It's sick.
Can we pull them up without pulling on them?
Senior Sister.
Second Brother.
Is reckless,
and simple-minded.
Isn't it inappropriate
to entrust it to him?
Right.
She has been in for a long time.
What should we do?
How about
I'll call him out.
Let's stop checking.
Give me that.
What are you doing?