I'm done here.
Hurry up.
Hurry up!
How is it?
Are you listening to anything?
Don't talk.
Two of them.
Both of them are martial arts masters.
Here they come.
Stand up.
Your Eldest Brother and I
xiaoqin.
What are you doing all day?
Prepare to attack.
Hold on.
Try fair means before resorting to force
there's no need to lecture them.
What do you know?
There is only one trick to avoid.
Let them be captured first,
and then...
You people in the house,
you're surrounded!
Drop your weapons!
And surrender.
Otherwise,
we won't be easy on you.
Brothers!
Prepare to attack.
Hold on.
The gate is open.
There must be a trick inside.
Eunuch Cao,
I have a plan.
We can use poisonous smoke.
What smoke?
Seven Star Begonia Cigarette?
This is the formula that I captured from foreign lands
that I captured from foreign states.
The smoke is extremely poisonous.
Smell it,
you may vomit,
or you'll lose your fighting ability.
Release Smoke!
Smoke!
Look at that!
What is this thing?
It's not good.
It's the poisonous smoke of Seven Star Begonia!
Hurry.
Get in the room.
Run!
Xiaorou, hurry up!
Come on! Hurry up!
Come on!
Hurry.
Xiaorou,
find the fabric strips
you usually make clothes.
Find it for me.
Honey,
what kind of poison did you say?
Seven Star Begonia?
My master once said that
those poisoned
most likely, they'll lose their martial arts skills
and the worst is
his life may be threatened.
Hurry.
Use this piece of cloth
with this rag.
Xiaorou.
Come on. Hurry up.
Come on! Hurry up!
Honey, hurry up!
There's no water.
Let's do it this way.
Come on. Hurry up.
Give it to me.
Sister-in-law.
What's the problem?
Me?
I'm still a yellow guy.
Xiaorou and I haven't got married yet.
What should I do?
Second Brother.
When can you stop talking?
There's no chance down there, is there?
Cover your mouth.
Where did you get the water?
Go on. Don't ask.
Thank you, brother.
What is the smell?
Use it quickly.
Don't waste it.
Dezhu.
I remember now.
The nemesis of Seven Star Begonia is Xuejian Plant.
In my room.
Go get it.
Sister-in-law.
Since the antidote is in your room,
why don't we just go to your room?
Why are we here then?
That's right, honey.
Why do you come to this room?
What's the use of talking about it now?
I'll go fetch it.
Hold on.
How can I let you go
such a dangerous thing.
Let's go to Dezhu.
You are both humans!
I'm not a human. Why?
We can't be too selfish.
Jade Man, go with me.
Alright.
The wind rustling, the water is cold.
The warrior is gone and never returns.
Why are you making poems at this time?
I told you to get the antidote.
You made it look like a smile in the underworld?
Go on.
Mr. Jade.
You don't know Xuejian Grass?
Let me go instead.
Honey,
If you want to go, let's go together.
If we die, we'll die together.
-Go. -Let's go.
Sister-in-law.
They two
they're like a pair of desperate lovebirds.
That's not good.
It's back.
What's going on?
Let's count how many we still have.
Father.
Half of the staff are reduced.
(The Jade Queen) Jade.
Dezhu.
Open the door.
Sister.
Help Eldest Brother.
I found
the smoke outside is gone.
Yes
now the wind is blowing in their direction.
What happened to my Eldest Brother?
Your Eldest Brother left in a hurry.
He hit the doorframe.
She was knocked out.
Didn't he have Iron Head Power?
What's the use of Iron Head Skills?
He didn't use his martial arts back then.
Come on.
Chew the antidote.
Rou,
see the grass in snow,
prince Yu,
dezhu.
This is nux-vomica.
This is Sichuan Wu.
You two light it
and throw it into the front yard.
With the poisonous smoke of Seven Star Begonia,
will form two more poisonous gases.
Let them try
the smell of the poisonous smoke.
What happened?
Eunuch Qiu,
this must be the smoke from the Que Blade Gate.
Quick!
Let's count how many we still have.
Father.
We still have five men left.
What?
I suspected that you were an undercover agent
are you an undercover?
Eunuch Cao, calm down.
Alright!
I'll meet you in person.
Eunuch!
Help
there's a booby trap.
What happened to you two?
Eunuch,
we don't know what the poison is either.
I suddenly feel that
I'm so scared.
Eunuch, please calm down.
We are not imitating you.
Trash!
Traitor Cao!
We have taken down your subordinates.
Give yourselves up!
All of you
you overreached yourself.
Stupid eunuch!
Meeting the four of us today
Is your birthday,
the anniversary of your death.
Death anniversary?
As a few ignorant young people,
you think you can stop
don't try to hold back the cart
don't do anything like that.
Traitor Cao,
give me your life!
Second Brother,
the Cao thief is highly skilled in martial arts.
Don't act rashly.
What are you afraid of?
We can fight him together.
We'll fight with him.
Eldest Brother.
Junior Brother.
You great traitor!
I'll fight you!
Stop!
Father.
Father, don't come out.
What does she wear?
I'm really grateful
the new Chief of Que Blade Sect.
Master Ximen is here.
The scapegoat.
This is the cook.
This dress really suits you.
You know what?
Your good days are over.
My brother Ximen Changhai
has gone to the capital with your father-in-law
to report you.
Alright.
That is thoughtful of you.
Can we discuss about it?
We're familiar with the past.
You know I am a good cook.
I don't know how to fight.
Right?
Well, we had drinks in a group together.
Can you discuss about it?
Should we use military tactics?
Or military?
How to fight an article?
How to fight?
And physical fighting.
Don't use force.
I'll use three moves first.
We can talk when it's done.
Alright.
What if it is martial arts?
That would be different.
I'll use five moves
and then you're done
here are ten tricks.
I won't move.
Come here.
He is a real martial artist.
Don't move.
What kind of weapon is this?
Hero Ximen.
You're finally out.
I thought you were scared
you were so frightened that you have committed suicide in the room.
Today,
I'll deal with you first
and then I'll kill your brother.
Good always prevails over evil.
Good guys live longer than bad guys.
Alright.
Why not try it?
Why don't you work hard?
I only used 10% of my martial arts ability,
you won't be able to handle it.
I can see that.
You're not the Ximen Changhai at all.
You are the chef, Ximen Changzai.
And want to kill with the knife?
This knife
has never killed anyone,
only animals.
Come.
I'll give you a chance.
Who...
Who exactly are you?
Brother.
You played me in the past.
Today, I'll play you.
Take Eunuch Wang to the capital through the path.
I'll send someone to protect you.
Go after them!
You can't escape!
Stop!
-Stop right there! -Stop!
Stop right there!
Stop.
Stop!
Hurry.
What's wrong?
It hit me.
How come you're weaker than me?
Stand up.
Can you stand up?
Cauliflower?
Heroine Gongsun.
Why are you here?
I heard Eunuch Cao led the troops to attack the Quedao Sect.
I knew you would be in danger.
And hurried here.
Are you alright, Changhai?
I'm alright.
A letter from a pigeon of Jade Man.
He told me to meet you.
Great.
The hero never showed up.
Who are you?
I was sent by your brother
to be with you and protect you.
That...
Why are you covering your face?
Take it off.
Let me see who you really are.
Mother!
You're the matchmaker?
Then you...
You are a part-time matchmaker?
Was arranged by your brother.
Who has been lying to me.
Is there no such thing?
Listen to your brother.
You're really Changhai's brother.
How many times have I told you
even if I told you?
Where is Changhai?
I need to find him.
Don't look for him now.
Find him a place first.
To the capital as soon as possible.
This is a big deal.
Right.
I'm scared.
Don't be scared.
I'm right here.
You're talking and you're calling me
I'm really scared.
You should have
hurry up.
See him off.
Come on.
Don't be scared.
Our group at the West Gate Changhai
reported to His Majesty when they reached the capital,
his Majesty was so furious.
Eunuch Cao was put in prison.
His hawks and dogs
when the trees fall, his hangers-on disperse.
And in order to uphold justice,
for their heroic deeds against Eunuch Cao
made them famous all over the world.
Everyone praised them
a red heart of complete dedication
outstanding figures
but this
It's not that simple.
For the rest,
new troubles may come to them.
Bottle gourd?
Bottle gourd.
Take the blame.
Don't be scared.
To avenge you.
Little brother,
you've never taken care of the family
you've never taken care of our family.
I've always
with you.
But today I understand.
You are right.
Without everyone,
without everyone.
As for me,
no martial arts.
He won't be
I won't be a warrior like you.
But I'm proud to have you as a brother.
Are you a hero?
It has nothing to do with martial arts.
As long as you care about the country,
for the state and the people
you are already a hero.
I remember you once said that
If a room is full of darkness,
we need a flame to illuminate it.
In the future,
I...
This is the flame.