Master.
Where have you been these days?
You gave us quite a lot of worries.
Don't mention it.
It's exhausting.
There's something
a lot has happened recently.
You've become a child again.
We're worried you might be caught by bad guys.
I'm back now.
What are you afraid of?
Have you heard
there's a fugitive in the underworld.
His name is Oriental Mold.
Caught by him.
Stealing children.
Providence will not forgive
you should arrest her.
That's right.
There's something more unusual.
Tell me now.
What exactly is going on?
He is a child when he sleeps.
But you become an old man after midnight.
And you let him sleep next to me.
What are you thinking about?
I'm the tiger?
As the leader of Heavenly Pond Gang,
carrying the kid out at midnight,
and bring Ximen Changhai back.
Let Ximen Changhai hold you while you sleep.
Why would I want to do that?
I'll be embarrassed if this gets out.
Who opened the door for him?
Was that you?
I was out for the bathroom.
Or else
I don't know someone's lying here.
How did he come in?
Enough.
Don't you have to tell me anything?
I'm going back to my parents' place
and I won't come back again!
My goodness!
He is really something.
Who is so shameless?
I heard that old man is not far away from us.
There aren't many people
nearby
master.
There are many
there are only a few people
as old as you.
You know that old man?
My...
So what?
Do you know me? I thought you guys
how can you learn like this?
Don't gossip.
Behind others.
Everyone has grown old.
Right?
What's more,
tall guy and his wife don't match.
It's a long way from that.
You'll score anyway.
I only ask you one thing.
The day we part,
you brought his wife here?
You'll fulfill your master.
Master, what's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
You picked up everything.
That's not leakage.
Do you want to pick it up?
Hey,
how can you be crazy?
What do you mean?
I won't involve you in this.
Please?
The day you married her back,
I would embarrass you guys.
I'll go out with her.
We'll open a restaurant.
If I leave the clan of martial arts,
are you alright?
Not right.
Something happened here.
Master.
If my guess is right,
this old man
Is younger than you.
If you are right,
that old man is me.
Ximen Changhai.
What's up
I have no idea either.
Why are you yelling?
Where's my son?
How would I know?
It's embarrassing.
Brother-in-law!
Get up and take the medicine.
I feel so depressed.
What's the use of holding that down?
Cheer up!
Let's seek revenge against Ximen Changhai.
I can't defeat him.
I know.
But we are rich.
Bro
we can hire someone to do it.
Who?
There is the most powerful combination in the world now.
Called the 12 Devils of Mohe.
They are called Cultivators of Martial Arts.
Of martial arts.
Fish farm?
What fish?
People doing this.
Killing fish.
Kill people.
He's really strange.
Twelve of us,
and most of them are martial arts masters.
Let's go to them.
Go find them then.
Alright.
But that's expensive.
How much is it?
The price of the underworld.
20 taels of silver per person.
Twelve people.
12 people here?
You can't
It takes two to make a quarrel.
Your sister thinks you're old too.
I don't want Changhai's life.
He just destroyed his martial arts.
To make it cheaper.
Then I'll have to find someone
to bargain with them.
If that's not enough,
we have to at least ten taels of silver per person.
I have 130 taels of silver.
Brother-in-law, 12 people
this is for you.
Or you'll get kickbacks too.
Bro
am I that kind of person?
Take them back.
Hurry up and get it done.
When this matter is done,
I will be refreshed.
Okay. Don't worry.
Alright.
Take the medicine.
Go on.
You can get the Twelve Devils of Mohe
you can invite the 12 Devils of Mohe.
What about that?
I have no choice.
That's all you gave me.
Just treat it as a favor, okay?
Not this much.
That's a big gap.
How about this?
When it's done,
I invite you to play in Yihong Yard.
That new head board
Is called Floret Butterfly.
She's beautiful then.
Don't...
Don't talk about this with me.
I see that you are so sincere.
And let me help you.
I'll brush my face.
Thank you so much.
Thank you again.
It's just Ximen Changhai.
I'll get some servants to take care of your things.
That's it?
Thanks.
What's her name from Yihong Yard?
Little butterfly?
60 taels of silver.
I can't do this.
Take this back.
I can't do it.
Hey,
they only give these
to Master Gao?
With them.
As I ran the errand for nothing.
You're a high-ranking agent.
And know so many martial arts masters.
Brush your face.
Try to think of other ways.
Please?
The Eighth Jie of Plum River accepted the face,
the money.
Hey.
Then you must have something good.
Please help me.
When you're done,
I invite you to Yihong Yard.
Is there a new one?
Its name is Little Butterfly.
No matter how old you are,
don't give me the nonsense.
How about this?
I'll just brush your face for you.
Because of me?
I'll find you someone
and the Eight Jie of Plum River.
Is martial arts.
And level.
It's the same.
Who's that?
Six young people in the village.
That's not good.
Three whistles, six whistles and five horse spears?
Are always unreliable.
It was called a big trick.
What is that?
That's six young people in a mountain village.
Not six little whistles
they're the six young warriors hidden in the mountains.
Let's clean up your Kalami.
They are so frivolous.
Master Gao can't do
for you to do well
I'll let you know.
Alright.
That's it.
Take this.
I will arrange for you
I will definitely arrange it for you.
Alright?
Please.
Don't make any flaws.
30 taels of silver?
A little less, right?
We are descendants of a famous clan after all.
The underworld will laugh at us.
I know the three of you
are the descendants of the hero Ke Zhenyao.
But you only have so much in the budget.
I also heard that
are well-known thugs in the world.
I am only thick-skinned.
To invite the three of you?
You have good taste.
You are right to come to us.
But I'm willing to pay
hero.
The market is down now.
The price
Is pretty good.
Alright?
Come find us when you can.
That's fine.
I'm sure they'll be your regular customers.
Brother-in-law!
You are back
have a seat.
How is it?
That's all.
That's right.
How is it?
Does it hurt?
Is he crying?
Pick his hamstring?
Report him? I did that.
It's not that serious yet.
We just found someone.
What are you waiting for?
I won't spend the money?
No discounts?
No discount.
The original price.
The price is...
You
are Master Gao's most trusted disciples.
Master Gao used to be
In Guandong.
It's your honor
to be his disciple.
As the saying goes,
a teacher for a day
Is a father forever.
You should practice martial arts
and then morality.
And remember the rules.
To repay your kindness.
Please.
Master Gao is giving a lecture.
Big Brother.
We'd better find a guide.
It has been 8 hours.
Second Brother.
The three brothers of our Ke family
are highly skilled in martial arts.
So I get a guide.
Wouldn't it be a joke?
You're right, Lixing.
According to my judgment,
que Blade Gate should be near.
The rest of you
are all my trusted fellows.
My enemy is Ximen Changhai.
Then your enemy
also Simon Changhai.
You will regard me as the Ximen Changhai later.
Show me the rage.
And unleash the hatred.
Simon Changhai.
Simon Chang Hai.
Ximen Chang Hai. Simon Changhai.
Ximen Changhai.
Big brother, here you are.
- West Man. - Changhai.
Come on.
Simon Changhai.
Simon Changhai?
This is it.
Simon Changhai.
Simon Chang Hai.
Simon Chang Hai. Ximen Changhai.
Go to
and get a few copper coins
with a few coins?
Keep a good mood.
And don't forget who I am.
I am Ximen Changhai.
Ximen Changhai.
Catch it.
It's hard for me to find you.
I've been looking for you so hard.
Simon Changhai,
Brother.
Waste his martial arts as soon as possible.
So that we can report to him.
Slow down.
Hero.
Can I ask
who sent you?
Stop knocking.
She's upset.
I need to discuss something with you.
Master is possessed by the devil.
Is not good for old.
Can you make another dose of medicine?
How can I do that?
My stocks
my stocks of aweto and summer grass.
But it's not good.
What about aweto?
Is used to nourish the body.
Are you getting little strength?
Is it strong?
Show Master
and strong.
I have
the recovery of your power is effective.
But I can't
the dosage well.
I wouldn't dare to use it on my master.
Master is old.
I won't be responsible
I won't be able to take the responsibility.
I'm young.
You can use me to test.
Don't think too much.
A teacher for a day
and a father forever.
I'm after all the Eldest Brother.
And I have to take the responsibility.
You've thought it through?
I still don't believe you?
The medicine you made must be okay, wife.
This one.
Is too sore.
Sister-in-law!
Come out and take a look.
The worm cage is open.
Why is it opening again?
Come on.
Let's see how I'm feeling now.
If I spend more money,
see if you can find me a writer
to write down my story.
You know what I mean.
I will use the money
to hire people,
hire thugs.
To hit myself.
I have to settle
my story
can't it
what's done is done.
What's the use of blaming yourself?
I am blaming myself.
I am scolding you.
What were you thinking?
You tricked me.
The Twelve Evil Devils.
Just three of them.
Your eyes are not good too.
What about the Nine Evils?
You know
my brother-in-law's position in the society
In the society these years.
This guy has three evil spirits.
One shot on the left,
and fired on the right.
He often stares at his words.
What's the use of that?
Isn't that what I'm asking for?
You should...
I'll beat you to death!
How did that happen?
To hire the Twelve Devils
the Twelve Evil Devils?
Yes, the Twelve Devils.
I can figure it out.
Three evil spirits, please!
Twelve evil spirits.
These three evil spirits?
One is against four evil spirits.
If you can figure it out,
I don't know what went wrong either.
What went wrong?
It's my turn.
Brother-in-law.
Luckily the nine people didn't come,
come, we'll both be dead.
My goodness!
So it means
you have become my savior.
I have to thank you.
Come on.
Brother.
Please accept my bow.
Stand up.
What are you doing?
Brother-in-law kowtow to you.
Thank you for saving my life.
Bro, don't be too angry.
I'll find another person.
This time we come to Meihe Bajie.
This time.
But also cost-effective.
How about this?
Don't confirm the number yet.
Not all of them
can you see people clearly?
Alright.
Can you pay the bill or not?
I'll pay.
Go there.
Sent them here?
Hurry!
Luckily, I ran so fast.
And caught them all.
What's wrong with you?
What's the matter?
Where are my medicines?
Take them all.
You can take two drops at most.
The poison.
Spit it out.
Hao Meng!
Hao Meng...
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Dezhu.
Let's go now!
Your eldest brother is crazy! Run!
He's crazy.
You quarreled with Eldest Brother?
About what?
He doesn't recognize you anymore?
He'll beat anyone he sees.
Very aggressive.
Sister-in-law.
We can hide outside.
Hurry up!
What are you afraid of?
When Second Brother and I
each one held his hand
and you just subdue him.
I can't.
There are only 20 of you.
He won't be able to be suppressed.
Then you don't believe in the ability of me and our second brother.
There are 20.
Two thousand?
He can't see anything now.
He can only hear some sound.
Attack wherever there's sound.
It is fine now.
It's all right now.
They didn't catch up.
Sister-in-law!
What's wrong with my Eldest Brother?
What's wrong with him?
She took too many tonics.
How could a tonic be this way?
It's a tonic.
I didn't expect him to eat that much.
Nothing.
It will be fine when the medicine wears off.
We have already escaped.
What should my father do when he goes back later?
Right.
Where's Master?
Go right now!
Go! Go back!
Return?
This is exhausting.
Guys,
this mission is simple.
But you should still be cautious.
Mei He used to make 108 masters.
And now there are only 8.
What's the reason?
Most people die from carelessness.
Listen to me.
Master Gao has given
given us enough.
As long as we get this done,
we can move out of Mei River
and settle in Central Plains.
Everyone,
do you have confidence?
Yes, we have.
Remember that.
You take people's money
and eliminate disasters with others.
If he can fight with his life.
He can.
Cheers.
Cheers!
Brother, where is nobody?
Could it be the empty city strategy?
Big brother, is there an ambush?
Ximen Changhai.
Aren't you going to come out and welcome them?
I see you.
It's broken.
Something is wrong.
What happened?
It hurts!
Dezhu.
Oh, Hao Meng.
Hao Meng!
Oh, Hao Meng!
Hao Meng,
how are you?
Get up now.
Jade, give me a hand.
I'm so tired.
What's wrong?
You drank too much medicine
you can't recognize people?
So many people are lying?
Who are you?
I'm here for Ximen Changhai.
Master is back.
Hurry up!
What happened?
Father!
They came for you!
They were beaten up by Eldest Brother.
Why do you always make trouble?
Master, I don't even know what happened.
I have no energy.
I...
That good.
Like this?
This is it?
I don't know what happened.
Master...
He drank too much medicine.
Why do you always prescribe medicine to him?
No, Master.
It's for you.
He'll try it on for you?
Stop it.
And see if it's blackmail against us.
No. Let's withdraw.
Hold on.
Don't move.
You
where did you come from?
You can't change your name,
or your family name.
The Eight Remarkable of Meihe.
What's it?
I want to speak to Ximen Changhai.
Simon Changhai?
He's not here?
She's not here? Say something!
Why are you beating me?
I'm leaving.
Hold on.
Since you are a martial artist,
hang around in the underworld.
Can you end this before leaving?
If not, we can
be the official?
We can't.
We'll be exposed.
I think
you are a martial artist.
This is our life in the underworld.
It's too long to report it.
How about private?
Then negotiate a price.
I'll offer this one.
Can I get this?
Can be lowered?
Come down?
That...
This
Is easy to talk to.
What about this?
Come down.
Calm down.
Give me the money.
Hurry up!
Master,
where am I going to get 100 taels of silver?
One tael.
As long as I'm alive.
We can afford one tael of it.
Give me the money.
It's here.
Once and for all.
Take the knife.
Don't look for anyone else.
What's this?
Money!
What's going on?
No, Master.
What did you talk to him just now?
Sorry,
don't move the money.
If my guess is right,
something is going on here.
They should have given us money
to appease us.
Then they'll report to the government.
Prince Yu,
what do you think?
I don't understand.
Yes, I do.
What's going on?
Don't spend the money.
What if he files a report to the government?
We have to pay him back.
If he doesn't report it,
to return these silver to us,
they are of low skins as well.
There is a trick here.
Mei He's Eight Remarkable.
Plum He stole it?
He did it alone
they did that to the other eight.
I'm impressed.
Don't lose heart.
We should spend more money
we must punish the worst culprits.
No need.
You are crueler than anyone else.
From now on, I'll rely on myself.