♪Knowing that duckweed and moss♪
♪Vanish in the sweep of millennia♪
♪I beg a year's bloom and fade♪
♪One life of love and hate, untouched♪
♪By soil's embrace♪
♪In the torrent's rush, wreckage remains♪
♪Knowing we sink in dust♪
♪Still I stand by your side, unafraid♪
♪Storms drench the city.
Blood stains our shade♪
♪I'm not afraid the world
turns into our foe♪
♪As I turn my gaze♪
♪You arrive, holding an umbrella, as always♪
=Born To Die=
=Episode 23=
Your Highness,
there's a body in the main hall.
It's Li Qi, the hostage prince of Nanlu.
Another death of a Nanlu Kingdom native.
And it's related to Song Dianxin again.
This time, it's even the ninth prince.
The moment he died,
you arrived.
Could it be that you can foresee the future?
I don't possess such divine powers.
I was simply concerned about you
and came to check on you.
I didn't expect
to stumble upon this.
This makeup box...
Isn't it yours, Sister Dianxin?
It's mine.
This is correspondence with the enemy.
Former General of Haiyin Kingdom,
Manager of Qianwei Teahouse, Song Dianxin,
has been found guilty of excessive association
and colluding with Nanlu Kingdom.
You're now arrested for treason.
Kneel!
Let go!
Dianxin.
Take the grand master away.
Move!
Let go!
Leave us alone
to catch up.
You approached me,
calling me "Sister Dianxin" with every breath,
yet set a trap to harm me.
Why have you always targeted me?
To be honest,
in this court,
the only woman I truly admire is you.
Song Dianxin,
I originally intended to
promote you to serve me,
but you insisted on opposing me.
Why must you seek war
between the two nations?
Because they deserve to die.
Over a hundred lives
from my mother's family
were slaughtered
by the Nanlu royal family.
I must avenge my family.
But Song Dianxin,
you obstructed the war
against Nanlu Kingdom,
preventing me from avenging my family.
I have no choice
but to change my plans again and again.
I planned to use
Su Xuefu's jealousy of you
to eliminate you.
Unfortunately,
she lacked the wit to succeed.
Keeping her around only hindered my plans.
Li Qi is cautious and meticulous,
just as you like.
See?
How well he cooperated!
He successfully lured you in.
But you didn't fulfill
what you promised him.
That's right.
I did promise him freedom
once the task was completed.
But death
is the ultimate liberation.
He was abandoned by Nanlu Kingdom,
and Haiyin Kingdom
has no place for him either.
Where could he possibly find freedom?
This is the best ending for him.
To be honest,
matching wits with you
was quite entertaining.
In the past,
I would have played with you a bit longer.
But you somehow got your hands on
a list of all my people.
That takes the fun out of it.
That day, I tried to
kill you at the Imperial Court,
but so many people came to your defense.
How dull.
They worked for you,
yet you killed them all.
Your actions today
will surely come with a price.
This is the look I want in your eyes.
Hate me.
Hate me even more.
Because the more you hate,
the more you'll understand me.
Hatred is poison,
but also medicine.
It keeps me awake at all times,
reminding me of my purpose and meaning.
My mother told me this,
and even in her dying breath,
she reminded me
that I live for revenge.
You're utterly mad.
You've underestimated me.
Even greater madness lies ahead.
Grand Master Shen Musi
is negligent in his duties.
Commoner Song Dianxin
is guilty of treason.
Put them in the heavenly prison.
Tomorrow,
they will be publicly executed.
Song Dianxin,
once a first-rank general of Haiyin Kingdom,
has committed the grave crime of treason.
Thanks to my timely discovery,
a great disaster was averted.
For so many years,
you relied on your military achievements
to act recklessly in Haiyin Kingdom.
All of this
ends today.
You framed the loyal,
and took the lives of innocent people.
Your every crime
appears in my mind's eye.
Justice will prevail.
The truth
will always come to light.
Is that so?
After your death,
you will vanish with your notorious name
into the long river of history.
No one will remember you.
Shen Musi,
it falls to you
to read out Song Dianxin's list of crimes.
(Indictment)
After all,
she is your betrothed.
(Indictment)
In the 55th year of Haiyin Kingdom,
Song Dianxin captured
Tianhe Valley with the light cavalry,
defeating over ten thousand enemy troops
and seizing their provisions.
That year,
Song Dianxin was seventeen.
I want you to read her charges.
What are you reading?
In the 56th year of Haiyin,
Nanlu Kingdom seized our stronghold.
How dare you!
Guards, Shen Musi has neglected his duties.
I hereby strip his title as grand master.
Song Dianxin,
guilty of treason,
is to be executed on the spot.
Whoever dares harm the general
must first kill us!
We will defend her to the death!
Are you all deaf to my words?
In the 56th year of Haiyin,
Nanlu Kingdom invaded our borders,
endangering our people.
General Song Guolin
was severely wounded.
With few soldiers and scarce supplies,
Song Dianxin led an elite force to help,
repelling the enemy
and safeguarding our people.
That year,
Song Dianxin was eighteen.
In the 57th year,
she led her troops
deep into the northern deserts,
annihilating 30,000 enemies.
From then on,
Haiyin unified the northern deserts.
♪A final farewell♪
♪Like dew, like lightning,
led all astray♪
♪Gazing at the moon across the sea♪
♪Through mountain mist♪
♪I'm willing to close my eyes♪
♪Countless lives in this world♪
♪Betrayed by a single snowfall♪
That year,
Song Dianxin was nineteen.
Our kingdom's territory is vast,
with a million soldiers,
yet the duty of protecting our homeland
fell on the shoulders of a young woman.
♪Of human hearts♪
Everything Song Dianxin did
was for the sake of a peaceful land
and a prosperous era.
If we could start over,
what would you do?
I...
I would do as my father hoped
to continue being a general,
protecting the country
and my family.
♪I never knew your heart♪
♪Let alone love♪
♪Time gently brushed them away♪
How could such a person
be a traitor to the nation?
♪One glance leaves all silent♪
♪Outside the gates
of my heart, who lingers♪
This is a loyal hero!
Indeed.
There's no way she could rebel.
In the highland battle,
the general risked her own life
to rescue us from the enemy camp.
She is devoted to protecting the nation.
She would never betray it.
In the northern deserts,
the general was severely wounded,
yet she gave the last of the healing herbs
to the injured soldiers.
Our lives were saved by the general.
I, Yuan Xiao, grew up without parents.
If not for the general,
I would have been long dead.
We will defend her
to the death!
To the death!
Silence!
This is rebellion!
Have you all gone mad?
Seize these people at once!
Who allowed you to put down your swords?
Pick them up!
This is rebellion!
Who said they've rebelled?
♪Shattered rainbow cannot hold drizzling rain♪
♪Sighs echo through destiny's cycle in vain♪
♪Broken zither plays no joyful lines♪
♪I resort to Bodhi as winds rise again♪
♪The moon tells of parting's pain♪
♪Across lifetimes, yearning whispers our fate♪
♪One teardrop, one dream♪
♪Fallen petals turn to mud
with the rain at night♪
♪Half a cup of worldly wine, I drain♪
♪To trade dawns and dusks in mortal chain♪
♪Half-written chronicles, it resumes♪
♪To recall memories of another life♪
♪That arrow pierced the heart, severed the vow♪
♪That day's snow witnessed death in vain♪
♪At that moment when we pass by♪
♪It is enough to mark my life♪
♪This farewell leaves no reunion in sight♪
♪In this life, I wish us♪
♪Be like cranes living a carefree life♪
♪Leaving worldly affairs behind♪
♪My longing for you is within reach♪
♪I only wish in this life♪
♪We share our destiny♪
♪Not like our previous lives♪
♪Wielding swords as enemies♪
♪Even constellations burned bright♪
♪Before being shattered into pieces♪
♪Let us blaze as celestial light♪