=When a Snail Falls in Love 2023=
=Episode 15=
(An adaptation of the novel
"When a Snail Falls in Love" by Ding Mo)
(Police Investigators Team)
Have you brought Thana over, Ning?
He's inside.
Captain.
Thank you
for what happened yesterday.
Tell me.
What do you mean
by the real culprit?
Three years ago,
I was set up by the real killer.
He planted my hair at the crime scene
and threatened me.
He forced me to turn myself in.
Have you seen the real culprit?
No.
He gave me a call
and asked me to turn myself in.
Why didn't you turn yourself in
if you didn't commit the crime?
I thought of turning myself in then.
However, he asked me out.
I'm here.
Where are you?
Have you brought the items I ordered?
Yes.
You must keep your promise
and clear my suspicion.
Okay.
Put down the items.
Save me.
It sounded like
there are two culprits.
Do you think
that the woman is beautiful?
She was beautiful.
However, to me,
the most beautiful woman is Ming.
He might be lying.
No.
He acts like a normal person.
He was imprisoned for three years,
forced to be a scapegoat.
That's unbelievable.
It's possible.
There's a lot
of strange things in this world.
For instance, me.
As a police officer,
who would know
that one day, my lover
would be a murder suspect?
However, the culprit threatened me
that if I refuse to be his scapegoat,
he'd kill Ming.
I had no choice.
Captain.
I'll leave this to you, Vita.
We found the third victim.
(Royal Thai Police)
The female corpse
that was found this morning
is the third victim
of the serial murder case, right?
The police is doing our best
to investigate the case now.
In fact,
this should be the sixth victim.
In addition to
the three victims three years ago.
There's still no evidence that the crime
is committed by the same culprit.
Please confirmed this then.
It's rumoured that the police
managed to arrest the suspect, Thana.
However, during Thana's
detainment, another victim was killed.
Does this mean that the police
has arrested a scapegoat?
We're still investigating the case.
When can you arrest the real culprit?
Does the police have any leads now?
Our Police Investigators Team
are investigating the case.
We'll surely bring
the real culprit to justice.
That's all for today.
Thank you.
(Royal Thai Police)
(Thai police arrests the wrong culprit,
a third victim appears, serial killer at large)
Everyone is panicking
and blaming the police.
Are you aware of this?
Yes.
I'm informed
that you were in a fight
with Luger's men yesterday.
I told you.
Solve this case first.
How did you know?
Do you think
that you can keep this from me?
It's all my fault.
Release Thana.
We need to reduce
the public opinion pressure.
In two days,
find me the real culprit.
Noted.
Does he look similar to the culprit?
Yes.
According to his figure and behaviour,
he must be the real culprit.
Did the culprit say anything
about your imprisonment?
He wanted me to be his scapegoat.
One day, if he has reached a dead end,
he'd kill me
to make it seem like I committed
suicide to escape punishment.
How do you prove
that you're not lying?
When you barged into the room,
you saw me being tied up.
That woman said
that the one who captured her isn't me.
You might be feigning this up.
Perhaps you changed your voice.
Then, you took your own photo
and sent it to Ming.
How do you explain it then?
It's the works of the real culprit.
He knew that Ming is my ex-girlfriend.
He wanted
to lure her there and kill her.
But when we were there,
we didn't see anyone else.
Maybe he saw you
and escaped in advance.
I can't take this anymore.
I need to rest.
In the past three years,
he's been feeding me tranquilisers.
Please stop asking me
the same questions again and again.
Okay.
I can let you rest.
However, there'll be doctor
and nurses to look after you.
Also, remember
that we still need
to talk about this regardless.
Do you want to meet him?
Never mind.
It's over now.
(Sen's message)
(Let's meet here, Vita.)
(I'll share the location with you.)
(I don't have time
for your nonsense today.)
(If you don't come,
I'll go to the police station.)
Vita.
I'm here, my darling.
Shush.
Sen.
Hey!
Butler.
Miss Vita.
This is my inner thoughts.
(I need to be honest with you.)
(You're the most special woman.)
(You changed my world and myself.)
You reshaped me.
(Lastly, I want to say)
(I want to say)
Pla...
Pla loves Vita.
(Pla loves Vita)
Pla?
Thank you so much.
(Pla loves Vita)
For amending the spelling error.
(Please edit it to the name I sent you.)
Okay, Mr. Pla.
(Delete Sen loves Vita.
Change it to Pla loves Vita.)
I've revised it, Mr. Pla.
(Thank you.)
Three times.
I have three dates with Vita
and you appeared three times.
Am I dating Vita or you, Pla?
Do you want to marry me then?
Calm down.
Are you pursuing me?
Isn't that obvious enough, Vita?
There's no need to.
I like you too.
Vita.
Love is so lovely, isn't it?
Even if I can't stay by your side,
I'm happy as long as you're happy.
Captain.
I can only borrow
the boat to you for one day.
You need to return it to me.
Thanks.
Don't worry about Sen.
One day,
he'll meet his Miss Right.
As for us,
I won't disappoint you.
I'll make you happy every day.
Okay?
People are watching us.
There are boats passing by too.
There are people watching us.
♪I was heartbroken♪
♪As I lost someone♪
♪Someone who was dear to me♪
♪Memories of the past haunted my mind♪
♪Afraid of entering a new relationship♪
♪Afraid of repeating
the same mistake and history♪
♪But you entered my life just like that♪
♪My wretched heart is
being played by fate♪
♪My heart is awakened♪
♪You made me realise♪
Vita.
♪That I love you with all my heart♪
♪I'm no longer afraid♪
Can I hold your hands?
♪Regardless of tomorrow♪
Is that okay?
♪How much time do we have left♪
♪I won't ask for much♪
♪As every second loving you♪
♪Is worthwhile♪
We've arrived at your level.
Okay.
You can go in first.
Everyone's here, right?
Please start with the reporting.
Okay.
Mr. Han and I
have sent Thana to the hospital.
Did you find any substance in his body?
The dosage of tranquiliser that's enough
to knock him out is detected.
Captain.
Do we really have to release Thana?
That's right.
We have to release him today.
The Chief has stressed
that detaining Thana will only confirm
that the police got the wrong man.
Ning.
Yes.
Report the third victim's conditions.
Okay, Captain.
Here you go.
The victim's name is Jiang.
She's 24 years old.
Same as the previous victims,
she died of cyanide poisoning.
The only difference is her occupation.
She works as
the cleaner of a nursing home.
Nursing home.
I have something to say.
Look over here.
According to my previous speculations,
the first and second victims
were killed by different culprits.
Now, I have the evidence.
Jiang and Lina
have similar situation,
including the locations
where we found their bodies
and the knotting method.
As for the second victim,
which is Pink,
she brought the culprit back home.
Her body was found in a remote location.
The first and third victim
were found in the wilds.
There's no evidence showing
that they brought the culprit home.
This tells us...
The culprit wants to be seen.
You're right.
Back to the knotting method,
theoretically, by definition,
have an important trait.
Most serial killers
are compulsive in some way.
The position and the way
the tie knots are the same,
Their ways of killing
their victims are similar too.
As such,
it's highly likely that we have
two suspects working alternately.
Is that possible?
During the second murder,
the culprit might not have enough time,
so he didn't do the special knot.
I don't think so.
Captain.
I want to go to the nursing home.
Please share the location with me.
Okay.
I'll send it to you later.
Vita.
I'll go with you.
Sorry to disturb.
Someone is looking for
Ming from the Police Investigators Team.
Who is it?
What is the person's name?
He said that he's Chayan.
Chayan.
Who's Chayan?
He's my friend.
But
I've asked him to wait outside.
You can go home first.
Please meet non-work related
people outside the police station.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Captain.
Officer.
Yes.
This is the latest poisoning case files
from the local police station.
I was just going to call to ask for it.
Thank you.
Okay.
Here you go, Captain.
Let's talk in my office.
Sure.
This way please.
I'm sorry.
Did I come at the wrong time?
It's okay.
I'm the one who called you over.
I was worried about you,
after what happened yesterday.
I need to apologise.
I invited you over, but now
I need to investigate on the case.
No worries.
I totally understand.
Where are you going?
Well, we're actually
going to the nursing home
that you're sponsoring.
Is there anything?
Is there a worker named Jiang,
who's 24 years old?
Yes.
Her body was found
in the wilds yesterday.
Let's get going now.
You didn't find
any fingerprints and evidence, right?
Yes.
Similar to the previous victims,
the culprit was careful,
as he must have been wearing gloves.
Besides, it's in the wilds,
hence it's hard to analyse the DNA.
It's the location
where the body was dumped,
but it's not the crime scene.
The culprit parked his car
outside the restricted area
due to road maintenance.
The culprit dragged
and dumped the victim there.
The distance is
about 100 metres, Captain.
28cm.
Thana's shoe size is size 42.
Is Vita right about this,
that there are
two culprits in this case?
I'm sorry, Chayan.
The police cars are all out for duty.
Thus, I have to trouble you.
It's all right.
It's my pleasure to help.
I'm actually planning to go there too.
Yet I didn't expect this incident.
Do you know the victim?
I saw her,
but I never talked to her.
Are you going for volunteer work today?
I thought you always go on Fridays.
Recently,
a lot of senior citizens
are moving into the home.
They need help to move their things.
So, I'm going to help them.
Vita.
Do you know?
The senior residents of the nursing home
are dumped by their families.
Chayan
gathers them there
and looks after them.
He cares about them.
He even encourages them.
It's really heartwarming.
This reminds me of my grandmother.
Thank you.
Hold on.
What's wrong?
I like how Mr. Chayan
ties your shoelace.
Can you teach me how to tie it later?
My grandmother
taught me that when I was little.
It's just a normal knot.
It's my first
seeing such a beautiful knot.
Do you want to tie it
on your other shoe?
Sure.
To have the same knot on both shoes.
Come on, let's have a seat there.
Hello.
Vita.
The culprit is a size 44.
Size 44.
What's the matter?
I'm at the nursing home now.
If there's anything, contact me.
Okay.
Now it looks the same.
Are the home having
new residents regularly?
Yes.
Our nursing home has
the best facilities in the city.
When the senior citizens are left alone,
they want to move in to our home.
Whenever there's a spot,
the senior citizens in the queue
would move in right away.
Well.
Can you share with me the entry log
and death list of the residents?
Death list?
That's right.
Okay.
I'll pass the list to you later.
Thanks.
(Dalan Nursing Home Resident Name List)
Hello, Wasu.
(Come to Mu Dessert House later.
She has made desserts for you.)
(That's all.)
Captain.
Let's meet at Mu Dessert House later.
Okay.
(Mu Dessert House)
Mu.
What's the matter?
In your last birthday,
I haven't given you a birthday gift.
So,
this is a belated birthday gift.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Are you telling me
to use the gent's perfume?
That's not what I mean.
This is a couple perfume.
Oh.
Let me do it.
I can use it with this bottle, right?
That's right.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Wasu.
Serve the mango sticky rice
to Vita and Captain later.
Okay.
Well.
I'll keep it for you.
Let's go inside.
Okay.
I've checked on it.
After Chayan started
to manage the nursing home,
the death rate
has doubled these three years.
I compared the death rate of
the nursing home with the others.
I found out
that after Chayan started working there,
the death rate of
the nursing home increased by 80%.
Okay, have a seat.
Are you saying
that someone is drugging them?
That is possible.
All the bodies were cremated,
so we couldn't prove it.
Bodies?
Death rate?
Hey.
Did you send Vita on
a dangerous mission again?
Wasu.
Stop the nonsense.
We're discussing about a case.
He's right.
Don't worry.
I won't put my girlfriend in danger.
You better don't.
Wait a minute.
Girlfriend?
You brat.
Wasu.
That's right.
We're in a relationship.
We're a couple now, so we can
stay this close to each other.
Yes.
Do you want to sit on my lap?
Vita.
When do you start dating him?
Why didn't I know?
Two days ago.
Wasu.
Help me serve the desserts.
Okay.
I'll do it.
I knew it the moment
they stepped into the shop.
Are you keeping this from me too?
I didn't expect you to be this slow.
Back then, when Captain Pla
and Vita came to our shop,
they sat far away from each other.
However, today,
Vita, Captain Pla...
- What?
They're sitting close to each other.
All right, fine.
It's okay.
You can date each other.
However,
please keep your distance.
One step at a time.
The first requirement
is to know each other's parents.
Do you understand?
I've never seen Captain's family.
But I know that he's the third child
and his mother is not around,
as she's overseas.
If that so,
we need to meet his parents.
What about my parents?
That is me!
Wasu.
Please help me out in the kitchen.
Okay, I'm coming.
Vita.
Did you see it?
This is called inseparable like shadows.
Well.
Let's talk about the case.
Okay.
I heard from Ming
that Chayan started volunteering at
the nursing home three years ago.
The death rate has increased since then.
He's a size 44 too.
Most importantly,
I saw how he tied Ming's shoelaces.
It's the same knotting method as
we found on the first and third victims.
This knotting method
needs to be learned.
Based on the evidence,
Chayan must be the culprit who killed
Lina and the nursing home worker.
If that so,
your hypothesis is right.
I thought that there are
more than one culprit too.
There are two culprits.
Although Thana is in the police
station when the cleaner was killed,
when Pink was murdered,
he didn't have an alibi.
This means
that Chayan and Thana
committed the crime alternately.
I think
that we need
to return to the nursing home.
(Do as I say, otherwise
you know what I'd do.)
Thank you.
You betrayed my trust
because of a woman.
I didn't betray you.
Why didn't you kidnap her then?
The police is suspecting us now.
I'm waiting for the right timing.
If I tell Ming
that your encounter is staged
and the nursing home you brought her to
is the place where we kill for joy.
That you get close
to her so as to kill her,
do you think
that she'd want to see you again?
Are you going
to kill me to keep your secret?
Come on then.
I dare you.
You just need 15 seconds.
I won't be able
to tell the truth anymore then.
Ming wouldn't know
that we killed those women together.
Come on.
I dare you.
Screw it.
Hey.
What did I tell you?
Don't ever hesitate.
If you hesitate,
you'll die.
Since you didn't act according to plan,
I'll do it on your behalf.
Since the both of us
are partners for life.
Do you know the man in the photo?
He's Mr. Chayan's friend.
He sent the bodies for cremation.
Thank you.
That answered my question.
Why did Thana hold back his
killing desire for these three years?
They used these senior citizens
to fulfill their desire to kill.
Ming.
Is Ming in danger then?
Hello, Ning.
I have an emergency.
Find out Chayan's address
and contact Ming.
Inform me at once if you have any news.
I'm acting
like a stalker.
I can just tell her
that I'm worried about her.
Vita.
Chayan.
Who are you?
Thana.
Why do you have Chayan's phone?
What did you do to him?
You're so cruel, Ming.
It's hard for me to escape.
Yet you didn't visit me at all.
Let bygones be bygones.
I know that you're not the culprit.
You're still alive.
I'm happy for you.
But we both need
to start anew, don't we?
Is this the start you're talking about?
Chayan.
What have you done to him?
(Captain Pla)
Chayan.
Wake up, Chayan.
You're the culprit, right?
What do you think then?
Leave.
Let go of Chayan.
This has nothing to do
with him. It's between us.
Between us?
It should be between the three of us.
When the third victim was killed,
I was detained in the police station.
Think about it.
Who would be the killer?
When I was little,
I always knew that I was different.
Well.
I enjoyed seeing the animals
being poisoned to death.
My parents also said
that I liked to do abnormal things.
Until I met Chayan.
He's the son of my dad's friend.
Do you want to have a try?
You discovered my little secret.
You either be my partner
or end up like the hamster.
Think about it.
Is
this true, Chayan?
Thanks to the man you love,
he brought me to the nursing home.
It's so boring to kill these old people.
But it's better than none.
Am I right?
You both are hopeless psychos.
That's right, Ming.
We're psychos.
We can't live like a normal person.
We can't control our desire to kill.
Why do you approach me, Chayan?
You should tell her yourself, Chayan.
Run, Ming.
He has lost his mind.
The women we killed
did not fulfill our desire to kill.
Until we met you, Ming.
We're both obsessed with you.
We long to kill you with our own hands.
So, Chayan...
Come here.
He approached you.
He does anything for you.
That's part of our plan.
He killed the third victim for me.
Hey.
Are you vomiting?
Let's take a closer look.
That's enough.
Take a deep breath.
Come on, let's wrap this up.
The next victim
is you, Ming.
Run, Ming.
Don't worry about me.
Shut up.
How dare Chayan betrayed me!
He betrayed my trust,
because he has fallen in love with you.
He loves you too dearly.
He wanted to leave with you.
What about me?
Do I not love you then, Ming?
Ming.
Shoot him.
My life has been a living hell
when I committed the crime with him.
If I can die in your hands,
I have no other regrets.
Don't hesitate.
Fire the gun.
Fire the gun, Ming.
Aim it right.
If you miss the target,
he'd die.
Fire the gun, Ming.
Remember, you're a police officer.
Also, remember
that I love you.
Let me go.
Don't be scared, Ming.
I won't shoot you to death.
I'm going to poison you.
Just do it.
Do whatever you want.
Follow me, Vita.
Run.
Come on.
Someone is here.
Seems like I need to use the gun then.
Follow me.
Da.
Wake up, Da.
Don't fire the gun.
Goodbye, Ming.
Chayan.
Wake up, Chayan.
Ming.
In this world,
there are people
who love you more than I do.
No, Chayan.
Don't cry for me.
Chayan.
Wake up, Chayan.
Da.
Wake up, Da.
Do you remember
the day when Eig was killed?
We were hunting down a criminal
who pretended to be a doctor.
We got the security footage.
Before he killed the victim,
he made a call.
I passed the call log to
the relevant department.
What do you mean?
If the owner of
the number turns out to be one of us,
there's a traitor
in our force.
If there's a traitor,
he'd surely give himself away.
Let's not act rashly and alert him.