Kajorn, what are you doing?
You're finally mine.
I'm here to talk to you about Kajorn.
This is the very first time we've met.
Why should I share stories
about my lover with you?
So you found me here
because you can't handle
my crazy family in Phuket, huh?
You're from Phuket, Uncle?
I am from Phuket as well.
If I could turn back time…
What would you want to change, Uncle Ree?
I wouldn't want to change a thing.
Are you talking about the fortune?
To be right by my fortune.
I was chased down by that Wild Bull,
yet you're still laughing?
What is your heart made of?
Well, what did you expect me to do?
Neither of you would tell me
what the fight was even about.
He only said
you took his money.
I couldn't just blindly intervene.
Let's find something to eat,
so we can return to Phuket.
Alright.
Tri.
Sasi.
Your life is always so eventful, Tri.
Even in Phuket, you still manage
to stay extraordinary.
Extraordinary?
Is that a polite way of saying unlucky?
And what about you, Sasi?
How have you been?
I…
I'm engaged now.
Congratulations.
Also,
please pass along my best wishes
to that lucky man as well.
Thank you.
Your friend's niece is quite lovely.
You should've invited her to join us.
Better not. I have far too many secrets.
Besides, Rajit is far too good
to be associated with a man like me.
In what way are you not a good man?
I misspoke.
I should've said
I'm just a man who's completely broke now.
That would be more accurate.
What took you so long?
And where did your friend go?
If you're that curious,
you should've just joined the table.
Well, I saw how eager you were
to talk to your friend.
I didn't want to be a third wheel.
Sasi already left, and so must we.
We still have a long way to Phuket.
Your friend is quite stunning.
She has such a soothing presence.
Is she just another friend,
like Ms. Srichan?
No, she isn't.
She's not a friend.
She's my ex-fiancée.
Let's go.
Huh?
What did you say?
You went to see Tri?
Yes.
We bumped into each other by accident.
Good heavens.
Why on earth did you meet him?
You already have a fiancé, Sasi.
Don't you forget that.
I haven't forgotten, Mother.
I haven't forgotten
that I had to break off my engagement
because he went bankrupt.
I haven't forgotten
that I had to rush into a new engagement
because our family
is running out of money, too.
Any pride or dignity I ever had
died long ago.
How could I forget that?
Are you talking back
to your own mother like this?
Please excuse me, Mother.
Initially,
I intended to wait another year or two
before discussing the wedding.
However, my health is failing by the day.
I fear
I may pass away
before seeing Sasitorn settled down.
Do not hold it against me, son,
but I want the wedding
to happen as early as next month.
One day, you'll understand
that I did all of this for you.
PHUKET
Your friend is quite stunning.
She has such a soothing presence.
She's not a friend.
She's my ex-fiancée.
Miss, you can't go up there.
You really can't.
Ms. Paetai strictly ordered
that you are not allowed upstairs.
As if I care. I've slapped her
with my own hands,
so why should I listen to you?
Miss, you can't go up there.
-You really can't.
-Noi.
Please go back to your chores.
I'll handle her myself.
-Let go of me.
-Yes, miss.
Uncle Ree isn't home.
He went to meet with the District Officer.
He vanishes for days, and the moment
I come over, he's missing.
Ms. Srichan.
Do you have a moment?
I'd like to talk about Ms. Sasitorn.
What? They actually ran into each other?
Uh, well, it was purely a coincidence.
Ms. Srichan.
Do you know why Ms. Sasitorn
and Uncle Ree broke up?
Looking for intel on your rival?
You must be jealous.
How can you say such a thing?
Why would I be jealous of my own uncle?
Right…
But I don't know much, honestly.
Tri never told me why they broke up.
If I had to guess, it was probably
because of money.
Well,
didn't Ms. Sasitorn
love Uncle Ree at all then?
How should I know?
But one thing's for sure, Tri loved her,
or he wouldn't have gotten engaged.
He probably loved her for a long time
since they grew up
next door to each other.
They only officially became a couple
after Tri returned from…
Uh…
From working in the province.
But now that Uncle Ree
inherited Grandpa's fortune,
he's a wealthy man.
Do you think
they might get back together?
And what about you?
Do you want them
to get back together or not?
Of course I'd want them
to get back together.
You hesitated.
I'd better get going.
Now that Sasitorn
seems to be making a comeback,
I need a new game plan
before their old flame reignites.
No more wasting time on you.
Oh.
Poor Uncle Ree.
PHUKET TOWN DISTRICT OFFICE
According to Colonel Nakamura,
this shipment includes rations,
fuel, weapons,
and military supplies.
The Colonel fears
their escort is insufficient,
so he requested backup from me.
And what do you need me to do?
I have urgent business
to attend to in Bangkok
and must leave today.
Please assist Colonel Nakamura
on my behalf.
With pleasure.
Though,
handing over your work
for a long trip like this,
you're secretly visiting that fiancée
you mentioned, aren't you?
District Officer, Mr. Poj
is here to see you.
Mr. Poj.
What can I do for you?
How could I ever dare
to order a District Officer around?
I heard you'll be away for several days.
I might head back before you return.
So, I decided to drop by
with some souvenirs.
You shouldn't have, but thank you.
-Thank you.
Thatri,
where are you going?
Thatri…
You bastard.
Even from Chiang Mai,
you still crept up here
to sleep with my wife?
You're sleeping with her, right?
Answer me! Spit it out!
How can I answer when you're choking me?
Stop it, Mr. Poj.
This is a government office.
If you attack me, I will report this.
Playing smart with me, are you?
Look, let's talk this out calmly.
I've never wrecked your home.
I'll even swear on my own life.
I don't buy it.
Think about it. If I actually did it,
Sri would be living with me by now,
or I'd be using her to drain your wealth.
But have you actually lost a single thing?
Think about it.
Fine. Then why are you
still chasing after her?
I've never chased her.
Are you suggesting
Srichan is the one chasing you?
What a self-centered jerk.
Can't you see
she's doing it just to spite you?
You two have been bickering
ever since you got married.
She loves to party,
while you do nothing but work.
Eventually, it led to a fight.
She knows how jealous you get,
so she's just using me
as a tool to hurt you.
To prove my sincerity,
how about I help you reconcile with Sri?
What's your plan then?
To Srichan.
I'm in a state of distress,
and you are the only one
who can ease my mind.
For old times' sake,
come to Room 411
at Phuket Hotel tonight at 7:00 p.m.
Yours truly, Thatri.
Desperate, aren't you? That's why
you're crawling right back to me.
Just you wait. I'll make you pay back
with interest and make it a night
you'll never forget.
PHUKET HOTEL
Tri, I'm here.
Poj?
How did you get here?
I came here for you, of course.
Did you actually forge
Ree's letter to lure me out?
But it worked, didn't it?
I know every single lie you've fed me.
How dare you
betray your own husband like this?
You bitch!
-Did you just call me that?
-Damn right!
And I'm going to do worse.
It's time you learned
how a proper wife should behave
after acting like a loose woman
for so long.
Poj.
What are you doing? Stop it!
Stay back!
Look at that bright smile.
I bet it's from meeting a special someone.
There's no one special.
I'm in a great mood
because I did a good deed.
Since when do you ever do anything good?
It wasn't just any good deed.
I played Cupid today.
-Cupid?
-Yes.
Are you going to treat
your wife like this again?
How could you do such a thing?
They are husband and wife.
It's no big deal.
A little back and forth,
and they'll make up.
You really have no understanding
of women, do you?
Look at you. You dirty old man!
No woman would ever love
or soften up to a man who abuses her.
Have you read too many trashy novels?
Is it really that serious?
Come here you.
-Do you yield yet?
-Yes, I do. I give up.
-But they're husband and wife.
-It doesn't matter.
You'd better prepare to visit Mr. Poj
at his sickbed tomorrow.
No way, you're exaggerating.
DISTRICT CHIEF'S RESIDENCE
I am terribly sorry, Mr. Poj.
You dirty old man.
You're saggy all over, yet you still
had the nerve to try to assault me?
Even though he was in the wrong,
he only did it because he wanted
to win you back.
He merely received
some misguided advice, that's all.
Please forgive him, Ms. Srichan.
I beg of you too, Sri.
Everything is my fault.
Even if you can't forgive me,
please consider the love
that Mr. Poj truly has for you.
But I don't love him.
I've said it many times,
I married him for his money.
I can't wait to divorce him,
so I can take the cash and find a new man.
Calm down, Sri.
I know you're just trying to provoke him.
Acting out of spite only serves your ego.
It never does any good for anyone.
Well, I don't care.
If it were up to me,
I'd divorce him and split
the assets right this second.
We can't do it right now.
But once we're back in Bangkok,
I'll give you a divorce.
Just be patient.
Once I'm back in Bangkok,
I'll get the divorce sorted out.
If you think she'll run to me
with your money like she claims,
you're mistaken.
She's only saying that to provoke you.
She'd never choose
a life of hardship with me.
I know…
But even without you,
Sri would leave anyway.
She despises me.
No matter what I do
or how much I give her,
it's never enough for her.
It was a mistake from the start.
I should've never loved her.
Love is never a mistake, Mr. Poj.
If Sri truly hated you,
she wouldn't have stayed for this long.
You know her better than anyone.
Yet she's leaving me now!
Calm down and gather yourself.
I wouldn't dare to lecture you,
but let me speak
as someone who has known
both you and Sri for years.
The issue between you two
stems from a lack of time
and excessive pride
more than anything else.
If you can find peace of mind,
I truly believe this can be resolved.
He thinks a divorce scares me?
All he ever does is work and make money,
constantly leaving me all by myself.
I am so utterly sick and tired of it.
But if you actually divorce Mr. Poj,
you'll suffer a massive loss.
I'm not stupid. I'll make sure
I walk away with a handsome settlement.
I didn't mean it in terms of money.
What else could an old man like him
possibly have left to give me?
It's love.
He might be older
and perhaps a bit boring in your eyes,
but no one will ever love you
as deeply as Mr. Poj does.
I believe you already know that.
Is this really for me?
Well, didn't you want it?
I haven't even said a single word.
I knew the moment I saw you looking at it.
We're husband and wife, after all.
In that case, could you put it on for me?
It's going to look
absolutely stunning on your neck.
Thank you so much.
Sure.
That lady accused you
of selling your body to me?
She didn't dare say it to my face,
but she said it to my mother.
That makes no difference.
Just because she's some elite's wife,
she can do anything?
She doesn't know who she's dealing with.
What are you going to do?
Picking a fight with them
will inevitably harm your business.
I don't care if my business goes bankrupt.
Let it be known that no one
talks trash about my wife.
I think it's best if you go back
and talk things through.
Don't throw your marriage away over this.
You're way younger than me.
Don't you dare lecture me.
Uncle Ree.
Hmm?
Do you think
Mr. Poj and Ms. Srichan
will ever reconcile?
Hmm.
What if they actually
end up getting a divorce?
What are we going to do?
Uncle Ree.
Are you looking for trouble?
Fine, then. I'm ready for it.
Have you ever heard this?
"No mistake is too great
for love to forgive."
Of course I have…
It's by Kahlil Gibran.
Did you gain this insight while serving
rich families in the past too?
But what if the love is really gone?
What's the solution to that?
Go get some sleep.
We need to head out early tomorrow.
Where are you going?
Since we're getting a divorce,
I should be sleeping in the other room.
Who said I'm going to divorce?
Hey.
Promise me.
About what?
First.
Stop being a workaholic and abandoning me.
You have enough wealth for ten lifetimes.
What are you hoarding all that money for?
If you love money so much,
why bother getting a wife?
How about I only work five days a week,
keep my weekends free,
and never bring my work home?
Deal?
Deal.
Easy.
Second.
You must take me out on dates
and dinner every few days.
-Sure.
-When the war ends,
we're traveling abroad
and visiting the countryside.
I've been stuck at home so much
that I'm turning into a house ghost.
-Hey.
-Ouch.
Stop.
Do you want a new diamond set
every month too?
You can go pick them out yourself.
Huh?
And if you ever break your promise,
I'll bring a side piece into our home.
Not a chance. I will never break it.
I haven't kissed you in such a long time.
Ah, so refreshing.
You're so adorable. Give me a hug.
So, you two have reconciled?
Of course we did.
That's why I dropped by to thank you
before heading back to Bangkok.
No need to thank me.
I'm just relieved
you aren't blaming me
for that terrible advice I gave you.
Now that things are good between us,
let's forget the rest.
Anyway, Sri told me everything.
Rest assured,
I won't tell a soul who you really are.
Thank you so much.
But seriously, isn't it suffocating
living like this?
What do you mean?
Well,
about Miss Rajit.
Staying here as her older relative
completely ties your hands.
Why not just reveal the truth
and pursue her properly?
Right?
She's my friend's niece, Mr. Poj.
I would never dare to think that.
If you say so… Uncle Ree.
Please don't tease me.
You know well enough
that I'm completely broke.
Even my own fiancée
broke off our engagement.
How could I possibly dare
to dream of such things now?
Are you secretly seeing Tri?
Ms. Srichan. You're joking around
like this again.
We're uncle and niece.
Who would think that way?
What if he weren't your uncle? Would you?
Can't answer that?
Look, I won't tell a soul.
Besides, I'm returning to Bangkok.
I won't be standing in your way.
You're getting ahead of yourself.
Uncle Ree is my uncle.
How could he be anyone else?
You asked such a bizarre question.
So it took me a moment to respond.
A guy like you
isn't good enough for anyone,
Thatri.
-No, please. Spare us!
-We surrender!
Shut up!
Loot the place clean!
-Just take everything!
-Take it all!
I said, shut your mouth!
Take it all. Just don't hurt us.
Just take everything.
Is this all you got?
This isn't even worth the pearls I spent.
That's just how it is during wartime.
Nobody is reckless enough
to buy luxuries anymore.
Then next time,
learn to target wealthier houses,
so there's actually a decent haul for us.
I get it.
If there's nothing else,
I'm taking my leave.
Wait.
What is it?
Do you know who's been undercutting
our prices in the black market?
Not yet.
You can't get a single damn thing right!
But I did know that the Japanese
are moving a massive cargo
into Phuket soon.
Word is that Zhang Gong Cheng
has raided another local household.
I'm worried about the arrival
of the Japanese military in Phuket.
I share your concern.
If the military supplies
being transported this time are looted,
the Japanese
will suffer a massive setback
for a very long time.
Can't you increase the security escort?
As of now, I doubt we can hold them off.
If I could do that,
I wouldn't have requested assistance
from the Thai authorities
in the first place.
Right now,
the war situation
is extremely critical.
I must keep my troops stationed
only at absolute vital positions.
So, what's our move now?
Who the hell are you?
And why are you following me?
Speak up right now.
Mr. Thatri, it's me.
Wai? Is that you?
-Yes, sir.
-Why were you sneaking around like that?
I could have broken your neck.
What are you looking at?
I'm afraid of being spotted.
I had to sneak around just to meet you.
To meet me? Why all the secrecy?
I don't get it.
I came to warn you.
About what?
After leaving the Som Song Saeng house,
I've taken various jobs.
And now, I'm working for…
Get in here.
Am I really starting right away?
What about your boss? Won't he be angry?
He won't mind.
He ordered an urgent replacement
for the previous one.
Grab that and follow me.
All this gold… Where did they get it from?
Hurry up and load the goods.
We need to raid the next target.
Yes, Boss.
Raid?
What the hell are you doing?
Spying on the boss?
-The boss?
-Damn right.
That's Zhang Gong Cheng, our boss.
They used to call him Black Beard,
but he got rid of the beard now.
Zhang Gong Cheng…
Stop standing there and help me lift this.
-We're almost done loading the goods.
-Good.
We can finally plan
to eliminate Thatri for good.
That damn Thatri.
I wish I could kill him right now.
Hey, hurry up
and load the rest of the goods.
Yes, Boss. Hey, move your asses.
Thank you so much for warning me.
So, Zhang Gong Cheng's boss
is actually a woman?
Yes, sir.
But her voice sounded familiar to me.
Do you have any idea
why Zhang Gong Cheng leaves pearls
at the crime scenes after his raids?
I want to know his motive behind it.
I don't know either.
Let me spy on them further.
Better not. I'm worried about your safety.
But I'm the only one
who can get this close to them, sir.
But it's too dangerous.
Let me make amends for the awful things
I did to you and Miss Rajit, sir.
Just be careful then.
Zhang Gong Cheng and his men are ruthless.
If things go sideways, let me know.
I'll send backup right away.
Yes, sir.
I'll take my leave now.
Uncle Ree.
Is there a blackout?
Yes. There's an issue with the generator.
Why aren't you using a flashlight?
Well, the batteries are completely dead.
Supplies haven't made it to Phuket yet.
Is the old man having a growth spurt?
If I grow more than this,
you might as well host my funeral.
All the food has been put away.
Let me whip up
something quick for you to eat.
Go ahead. I actually miss
the taste of your food.
Here it is.
Are you eating this too?
Since I made it, I should enjoy it too.
The elderly might not want to grow,
but we youngsters still do.
So, this is the famous Phuket Mee Hoon
that I've heard so much about?
That's right.
But it's such a pity
we don't have
pork bone broth to go with it.
If paired together, it would taste better.
If it took any longer,
it would be breakfast time by then.
Having this dish is more than enough.
Give it a taste then, Uncle Ree,
and tell me if it's good.
This is delicious.
Just so you know,
this is Aunt Paetai's secret recipe.
Really?
Someone like her
could actually cook this well?
That's right.
But ever since she got promoted
to assist Grandpa Som,
she hung up her apron
and became a loud, fussy madam
as you see today.
Back then, I used to enjoy
so many dishes made by her.
And you managed to learn her recipe.
Speaking of which,
I really miss how Aunt Paetai
used to be back then.
You must've been a child back then,
considering how old your aunt is now.
-Is it good?
-It's perfect.
I'm so happy for you.
At least you'll have someone to look after
and won't be left alone in your old age.
But I…
I feel absolutely terrible, Mother.
Today of all days
is supposed to be
the happiest day of my life.
Are you still yearning for that…
that Thatri again?
I don't miss Tri
in the way you think, Mother.
If you ask me
whether I ever truly loved him,
I honestly wouldn't even know
how to answer.
To me,
marriage is merely a means of survival.
Because in reality,
I love absolutely no one,
neither Tri
nor this groom of mine.
Stop overthinking this, Sasi.
Go pack your things.
It's time for you
to move in with your husband.
Am I a horrible person, Mother?
Let the blame be mine.
May all the bad karma
strike me down instead.
I am the one who forced you
into this marriage.
But I need you to know.
Everything I've done
is entirely for our own good.
What the hell?
Your friend here is an ungrateful dog.
He dared to steal from me.
I didn't steal it, Boss.
Please, have mercy on me.
Caught red-handed with proof,
and you still dare to lie to me?
I saw it lying on the ground.
I was about to put it back,
but you spotted me first, Boss.
I'm no thief.
Wai. Help me.
Don't you move.
Don't even think about it.
Anyone who dares to steal my things,
their penalty is death.
Wai,
if you are truly loyal to me,
you must execute him.
Wai. No. Don't touch that gun.
Wai.
-You want me to shoot my own friend?
-Damn right.
If you are my man,
you obey whatever orders I give you.
Wai, please don't do this.
Wai. Please don't.
Please, I beg you. Don't kill me.
Wai, please. Don't pick up the gun!
Wai!
Please forgive me, man.
You really can be trusted, after all.
Welcome to the crew, Wai.
Hey, let's celebrate!
Were you going to blow my brains out?
-Damn, you've got real balls.
-Come on, boys.
-Come on.
-Here.
Come on.
Let's cheer.
-Cheers!
Wai, keep watch and be our lookout.
Yes, Boss.
Help! We're being robbed!
-Is everything cleared out?
-Yes, Boss.
How did it go out there, Wai?
Too easy, man.
Just broke a little sweat with the boss.
Total walk in the park.
Stop blowing your own horn, will you?
Hey, actually, there's one thing
I'm curious about.
What is it, Wai?
How come the Boss always drops a pearl
right next to the dead bodies?
The pearls?
I heard the pirate crew mentioning
that the Boss Lady
ordered him to leave them there.
It's an offering for the souls.
So their spirits won't seek vengeance.
They're top-grade pearls, too.
Cost a fortune, really.
Though if you ask me,
those dead bastards
probably have no use for them anyway.
-You want one then?
-Hell no.
Are you out of your mind?
That means I'm dead.
Does Zhang Gong Cheng's boss
actually hold such a belief?
I'm not quite sure, sir,
but that's what they told me.
If they can afford pearls,
they must be wealthy.
Exactly, sir.
The reason he can walk around
so high and mighty
is probably because
there's an influential figure backing him.
That aligns with what
the District Officer once said.
Wai, here's the plan.
Where did you sneak off to?
Did you think I wouldn't find out?
You went to see Thatri.
That's right, Boss.
I was planning
to lure him straight into a trap.
Why would you do that?
Because I despise him.
You probably didn't know this,
but I used to work at their house.
Is that so?
Yes, Boss.
I was kicked out because of him.
So when I found out
that you were planning to kill him,
I wanted to lend a hand.
So what?
If you hate his guts,
why didn't you just do it
and be done with it?
Do you honestly think
I wouldn't have killed him
if I had the chance?
But the fool accidentally leaked intel
regarding a Japanese supply shipment.
I knew you've been itching to raid them,
so I kept him alive
just to get his information.
What information?
Here is our transport data,
including the cargo details,
the departure times,
and the exact supply routes.
I've already leaked all of it to Wai.
Do you truly place
this much trust in that man?
Yes, I do.
If you trust him, Thatri-san,
then so do I.
As for my men,
the forces are fully deployed.
We await your direct command,
Colonel Nakamura.
He trusts me completely.
He'd never suspect that I'd turn on him.
Now, all you have to do
is double-cross him,
slit his throat,
and seize all the supply shipments.
You aren't trying
to play me for a fool, are you?
Boss, if it weren't for Thatri,
I wouldn't be living like this.
How so?
My mother was Som's mistress,
yet we didn't inherit a single thing.
Meanwhile, Thatri,
who hadn't even seen the old man's face,
walked away with half the fortune.
How am I supposed to not hate him?
Not to mention how he kicked me out,
discarding me like a worthless dog.
ADISUAN PEARLS
Do you think we can trust
someone like Wai?
I'm not so sure how trustworthy he is,
but every single thing
Wai told you is the absolute truth.
Both the part where Thatri kicked him out
for trying to kill Rajit
and the fact that his mother
was Uncle Som's mistress.
But just to be safe,
make sure you prepare a backup plan
before launching the raid.
It has to be a plan
that Thatri would never see coming.
And Wai must be kept
completely in the dark.
Brilliant.
What's all this?
Just some things
we might need during the raid.
What is it even for?
Stop asking so many damn questions.
Just be our lookout here.
If the police or the Japanese
show up around here,
fire this signal flare to warn us.
You're leaving me behind.
Do you not trust me?
Why are you being so paranoid?
You've always been
our lookout from day one.
Yes, Boss.
Move out.
-Hey.
There really aren't
any Japanese soldiers around.
Wai really is trustworthy after all.
Go grab that truck
and seize their supplies.
-Their reinforcements will be here soon.
-Yes, Boss.
Move.
Zhang Gong Cheng's crew
really did show up to raid us.
Everyone, get ready.
Please be careful, Mr. Thatri.
If you get hurt, the Chief will kill me.
Don't worry.
Attack!
-Go!
Freeze! Don't move!
You're slower than I expected.
What's the meaning of this?
It means I've prepared
a little welcoming gift for you.
I don't care about your petty tricks.
If you fear the police's bullets,
you'd better surrender right now.
-Hey!
Did you forget we're in the jungle?
We have guns too, you fool!
What did you go to Bangkok for,
District Chief?
I went there to get married.
-Married?
Here she is.
-Tri?
-Sasi?
You must take them down today.
I've noted every single detail,
including the escape routes.
Freeze! Don't move!
Drop your weapons!
Die, you bastard.
So, they used to be engaged.
Old flames won't reignite,
will they, Rajit?
A one-winged bird can't fly alone,
so I guess it's grounded forever.
Subtitle translation by:
Khathathong Thongtumlueng