Uncle Ree, what are you doing?
Hey!
Rajit!
Don't ever do this again.
I was worried about you, okay?
I'm not surprised
to see you here every day.
What exactly do you want?
All I ask for is your forgiveness, Rajit.
According to my detective,
Kajorn already has a wife,
but they aren't legally married.
Is anyone home?
You…
Hey, you.
You're Suda, right?
And you are?
I'm Thatri, Rajit's uncle.
I went to your house
and found you unconscious,
so I rushed you here to see the doctor.
Are you feeling any better now?
I'm feeling a bit better now.
There's no need to rush.
Just lie down for a bit.
Thank you so much for taking
the trouble to bring me here.
It's no trouble at all.
I actually came to see you
because I need your help.
What is it?
It's about Kajorn.
Thank you so much for bringing me home.
Don't mention it.
Looking at the state of this house,
you probably wouldn't believe
that a girl from a wealthy family,
who could afford to study in Penang
like me, would end up living here.
The lowest point of my life
all started with that man named Kajorn.
If you don't want to end up dead,
get out of my house right now.
Father, stop. Please don't hurt him.
This pimp is just using you for money.
Can't you see that? Huh?
That's not true.
Kajorn loves me. I'm certain of it.
I truly love Suda, sir.
Suda, please.
Open your eyes, my child.
Listen to your father.
He's only trying to protect you.
I don't believe you.
If you really loved me,
you'd let me marry him.
The only reason you're refusing
is because you don't love me.
You're just protecting
your precious fortune.
Please, sir.
I really do love her.
Liar! I don't believe you!
Let us get married, please.
Please, Father. I'm begging you.
Please.
If you're going to shoot Kajorn,
then you'll have to shoot me too.
Fine. You love him that much?
Then both of you, get the hell
out of my house right now!
And mark my words,
once you walk out that door,
you're no longer welcome here.
Now go!
Get out of my house! Leave!
Leave!
You're back, Kajorn?
Huh?
Can't you see past your own filth?
I'm standing right here, aren't I?
Of course, I'm back.
You must be exhausted. Are you hungry?
I can fix you something to eat.
I'm not eating.
Just looking at your face
makes me want to puke.
Understand?
- Ouch.
- Hey.
Now tell me.
When the hell are your parents
going to accept me, huh?
Huh?
But even if they don't,
we still have our love.
To hell with love, you idiot.
I threw away my fortune
just to live in this miserable dump?
We actually had some savings at first.
But we lost everything
because of your gambling, didn't we?
Huh?
You've got quite a mouth on you today.
You're asking for it, aren't you?
Fine.
Damn it.
Always talking back.
These stairs are so steep.
- Where are you going?
- Stay away from me.
I'm going back to Rajit.
You found out she inherited
that fortune, didn't you?
That's why you're leaving me.
Damn right.
Why would I stay in this dump with you?
You're broke, you're sick,
and you look like a corpse each day.
No, Kajorn!
Please don't leave me.
I truly have no one else left.
Like I give a damn!
Kajorn, please.
I'm begging you. Please, stay with me.
Let go.
No. Please don't leave me.
Let go!
I said let go!
Damn it!
I keep playing back my friends' warnings
in my head every single day
that I would eventually regret my choices.
And now, I truly have no one left.
How are you getting by these days?
After Kajorn left,
I lost my baby.
My body is failing,
and now I have tuberculosis.
If my employers find out
how sick I really am,
I don't know
how much longer they'll keep me.
You're a total stranger.
Why are you pleading
on behalf of my ungrateful daughter?
I may be a stranger,
but I truly could not bear
to see her in such a pitiful state.
Is her condition really that bad?
Dear.
Sir,
you might call her ungrateful,
but you still call her your daughter.
That word alone shows that deep down,
your love for her hasn't changed a bit.
Don't let your ego
come between you and your daughter.
Suda is gravely ill,
and we don't know
how much time she has left.
If you wait until it's too late,
all the love in the world
won't mean a thing.
PHUKET
Where on earth
did your owner disappear to, Don Jose?
Where have you been?
Were you waiting for me?
Who's waiting?
Hey, Don Jose,
were you waiting for your owner?
I take such good care of you,
even if he stayed away for years,
you wouldn't miss him at all, right?
Good to know.
So…
Where exactly did you go?
If you were waiting, just admit it.
It's not that hard.
I already told you, I wasn't waiting.
I just wanted to know
where have you been, that's all.
Everyone. I've told Nid
and Jiam to wait out front.
They'll lead you all
to the government shelter.
Aren't you two coming with us?
This sounds far worse than the last one.
Don't worry. We'll be right there.
What about Aunt Fuang and Aunt Paetai?
I have no idea. I haven't seen them.
In that case, everyone go ahead.
I'm going to find them.
Aunt Fuang. Aunt Paetai.
Wait, Rajit.
Go now. I'll go after Rajit.
Let's go.
Aunt Fuang.
Aunt Fuang. Are you there?
Aunt Paetai.
Any sign of them?
I couldn't find anyone.
The bombing is getting too intense.
We'll never make it in time.
Wait. Before Grandpa passed away,
he told me he'd built
a private family shelter
in the backyard.
He said to go there
in case of an emergency.
- Let's go.
- Okay, hurry.
Watch your step.
This way.
We should be safe now.
There's nothing left to fear.
Hey. Whoa.
Grandpa stored
so much food in here, Uncle Ree.
We're all set for food.
Are you even worried?
You're always thinking with your stomach.
Well, I'm out of energy.
An army marches on its stomach.
You know the saying, right?
Is that a stomach or a bottomless pit?
It's impossible to fill it up.
Hey.
This really takes me back.
Why? Are raisins your favorite?
Not really. It's just…
When I was a kid, we were so poor.
I could never even touch treats like this.
When the neighbors had parties,
I'd just stand by the fence
and watch them eat.
I finally got to try them
when I came to live with Grandpa Som.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Do you feel sorry for me?
I'm fine, Uncle Ree.
That was a long time ago.
I keep it as a memory,
but now I live for the present
and dream of the future.
Dreaming of the future, huh?
Mind telling me what those dreams are?
That's a secret.
Here, I'll share some with you.
Thanks.
Just kidding. Here you go.
Is it good?
Delicious. Eat up. You need it to grow.
Rajit!
Hey!
That's herbal liquor.
You nearly drank the whole thing.
Hey, Don Jose.
Your owner is so cruel.
He abandoned me.
Right, boy? He just left me.
I knew it. You're drunk.
You're the guilty one,
and yet you're blaming me?
Watch it, or I'll have Don Jose bite you.
Oh, look at that. A feisty drunk, I see.
Of course, it's because
I'm not good enough.
That's why you left me, Uncle Ree.
I didn't leave you.
I had some business to take care of.
And I'm back now, aren't I?
I don't believe you.
Where did you go?
Tell me the truth, Uncle Ree.
I went to Bangkok.
Why didn't you say anything?
You have no idea what I had to go through
while you were gone.
Alright, tell me then.
What happened while I was gone?
While you were gone,
It was so suffocating.
I had to deal with Kajorn and Vijarn.
And then, when I went out
with Primprao and Nareewan,
I was taken away
by someone I didn't even know.
On top of that, I had to work
with Aunt Paetai,
who nagged and bit at me every single day.
You don't get it, but when you left,
you took all my peace of mind with you.
I only went to Bangkok
because of you, you know.
If it's for me,
then don't go at all.
Because
I don't want to be
in this house without you.
I promise I'll never
leave you behind again.
What did you say, Uncle Ree?
I promise
I'll never leave you behind again.
Can you keep that promise?
Of course.
For you, I can do that.
Promise me.
Come on, promise.
I promise.
You promised, okay?
Rajit?
Rajit!
Don Jose, are you waking Mommy up?
What's that smell? It's disgusting.
You're finally awake?
Uncle Ree, why do you smell so bad?
Don Jose, stay back. Come here, boy.
Your owner smells like
he's been rolling around in vomit.
Would a head-flick be ungentlemanly?
I'm going to puke. So smelly.
What's this, Auntie Jiam?
It's ginseng chicken soup.
Since you mentioned having a headache
from that herbal liquor,
I prepared this to help clear your head.
Just eat it already.
Ginseng is hard enough to find as it is.
Even in the middle of a war,
I can't believe you'd still
go to such lengths for her.
This was kept by the master
specifically for his granddaughter.
That's why it wasn't offered
to anyone else.
Can I skip this?
I really can't stand the smell.
Not used to high-quality stuff, are you?
Typical of someone from your background.
Try to force it down, dear.
It works wonders for a hangover.
Just eat it. Maybe you'll stop
puking all over people.
You eat it then,
if you like the smell so much.
And why wouldn't I? It's just soup.
This is incredible.
It's simmered to perfection.
The broth is so sweet.
Thank you. I'll go get
a fresh one for you.
No need for that, Auntie Jiam.
If Uncle Ree can eat it, so can I.
Good heavens. How scandalous.
Oh my…
It's an old Chinese tradition, dear.
But don't worry. People don't really
stick to it much these days.
What was that all about?
It's just chicken soup.
Why the dramatic reactions?
This specific jar,
it's called a Kam Cheng.
In Hokkien Chinese,
it means a jar with a lid.
Okay. And?
What's so strange about that?
Well,
the word "Kam Cheng"
is a homophone for the word
meaning deep affection.
Well, tradition dictates
that a bride and groom
share soup from the same jar
to symbolize their lifelong bond.
An unmarried man and woman
simply don't share the same jar.
I'll go get that new jar now.
How's the hangover?
Still got that headache?
It's gone.
I had no idea I was such a lightweight.
I only had a little bit.
You chugged half the jar in seconds.
I wouldn't call that a little bit.
Uncle Ree, besides puking on you,
did I do anything else embarrassing?
If it's for me,
then don't go at all.
Because I don't want to be
in this house without you.
I promise I'll never
leave you behind again.
Can you keep that promise?
Of course.
For you, I can do that.
Nope.
You just threw up on me
and passed out. That's it.
Your voice went a bit high there.
Did you want something to happen?
I'm telling the truth.
No, of course not.
Mr. Thatri.
There's big trouble, sir.
Last night's bombing
sank several cargo ships.
Goods are nearly impossible to find now.
We're facing a severe emergency
across Phuket.
- Primprao. Nareewan.
- Rajit.
Are you guys okay?
My house is safe,
but my father said
the rice shipment was hit by a torpedo.
Everything is lost.
The government issued ration cards.
Everything is strictly limited.
My family is so large,
I don't know if this will be enough.
It's going to be okay.
Mr. Thatri. Miss Rajit.
I've secured the ration cards
for everyone.
- Here you go, sir.
- Thank you.
This should keep us going for a bit,
but it won't last more than a month.
Let's hope we get fresh supplies
before mid-month.
Otherwise, there will be riots.
- You thief!
- Stop!
Stop that!
Stop that right now!
- I said stop.
- That's enough.
Break it up.
You're a thief!
- You thief.
- Stop it!
Stop.
I said stop!
That's enough.
Yong, are you okay?
What is going on here?
Why are you all fighting like this?
Yong stole my rice.
We already split the portions,
but this thief still wanted more.
My kid was starving.
Would it kill you to spare for a child?
That's your kid, not mine.
Why should I do that?
- Hey, stop!
- Stop.
I said stop!
This is my ration card. You can have it.
- Don't steal again. It's for the kid.
- But sir…
Now, take it.
Thank you, sir.
Mr. Thatri.
What will you eat?
We have no idea
when the next shipment will arrive.
It's fine.
I am the head of Som Song Saeng house.
If my people are suffering,
I can't just stand by and watch.
I know times are hard.
With food and supplies running low,
this makes everything feel impossible.
But the only way we'll survive this
isn't by being the strongest,
it's through our unity.
If we are selfish,
we will all perish together.
But if we are generous
and kind to one another,
we will survive this as one.
Uncle Ree,
why don't we combine all our supplies
and cook as one?
It'll be more economical,
and we won't have to cook separate meals.
As for the food,
I'll leave all the decisions to you.
Miss Rajit.
Do you intend to share
the same meal as the servants?
In times like these,
we shouldn't be divided.
Whether master or servant,
we're all in the same boat.
- Auntie Jiam.
- Yes, miss?
I'll need your help in the kitchen.
If we have any yams or taro,
we should cook them with the rice.
It'll help stretch our supply further.
Of course, miss.
I'll take care of it right away.
I'll go dig up some yams and taro.
The forest outskirts are full of them.
Thank you, Nid.
Everyone else gets yams mixed with rice.
Meanwhile, the owner has to settle
for plain old yams and taro.
That's what happens
when you like to show off to everyone.
You end up grumbling
all by yourself when no one's looking.
You came to mock me, is that it?
Here. It's salt, pepper,
chili flakes, and some honey.
I'm sure this'll be better
than eating them plain.
Definitely won't be like last time.
It's burning!
Serves you right.
Maybe your tongue
should've stayed blistered for a few days.
Serves you right.
Maybe your tongue
should've stayed blistered for a few days.
It smells so good.
This tastes way better than before.
Do you like it, Uncle Ree?
If you do, I'll bring more.
Since you're going to be stuck eating this
for a couple months.
Everyone will probably
start calling me Yam-Face.
It's not that bad.
So good.
A bit more honey would be good.
Want some?
You still haven't told me
where you went when you were gone.
I already told you when you were drunk.
Well…
I don't remember any of it.
Tell me again? Please?
Please, Uncle Ree?
Pretty please?
Why would you want to know?
You're so nosy and persistent.
Forget it then.
I was in Bangkok.
I had some business to take care of.
It's not done yet, but I have a friend
looking after things for me there.
That wasn't so hard.
Such a child.
You're happy when you get your way.
Hey,
since I've been back,
I haven't seen that ex of yours around.
Looking for work, maybe?
Or maybe he finally left.
Not that I care enough to check.
You've learned your lesson.
I've decided not to be a fool twice.
Looking back,
I'm so relieved I got through it.
But the one suffering the consequences now
is Suda.
I wonder how she's doing.
Spoken like someone who's moved on.
That's good.
Why is that good?
Huh?
Keeping secrets again?
- What is it?
- A spider!
Okay. Okay.
- Shoo it away!
- Keep your--
- Alright.
- It's coming this way!
Go away. Shoo.
Long time no see. I thought you'd finally
headed back to Bangkok.
If you're here every day,
why on earth should I leave?
- Rajit.
- Miss Rajit.
I'm sorry, Kajorn,
but I have work to attend to today.
Vijarn, let's head to the office.
Certainly.
Mr. Kajorn.
Yes?
I'd like a word with you.
It's about Miss Suda.
And why is that?
Why should I stay away
from Rajit because you said so?
What right do you have to give me orders?
I'm asking you nicely, not ordering you.
Suda is your wife.
It's your responsibility
to care for her while she's ill.
And the fact that you're the one
who ruined her life in the first place.
What are you talking about?
I don't care what rumors you've heard,
but Suda and I are finished.
Where she lives
or how ruined her life is,
that has nothing to do with me.
I've tried to reason with you.
If you insist on being difficult,
don't blame me for being ruthless.
Why? Are you going to tell Rajit?
Go ahead. You have no evidence.
It's your word against mine.
Even if Rajit kicks me out, I'm not going.
I'd actually love to see
what you think you can actually do to me.
You're not a man.
If there was no inheritance,
you'd be long gone.
You're just here for her money.
You pathetic pimp.
I don't care about
the situation with Suda,
but if you lay a finger on Rajit,
you're a dead man.
The secret's out.
What the hell do I do now?
Why is this leech so hard to shake off?
He just won't budge.
I have to rely on you now, Sri.
You can't do it? Why?
The information you're asking is too deep.
I don't know where to begin digging.
How deep can it possibly be?
All I want to know is why Kajorn resigned,
if his gambling addiction is real,
which dens did he go to,
and who else is involved.
It's so simple. Why can't you get it done?
These are private matters, madam.
People don't even tell
their closest friends these things.
Besides, Kajorn isn't even here.
Where am I supposed to find the trail?
You're useless. Just leave already.
Absolutely useless.
Hey! Is anyone alive in here?
- Hey!
- I'm coming.
I bought all this stuff,
and no one bothers to help.
- Get to the car, now.
- Yes, sir.
I'm coming, sir.
Hurry up.
The laziness in this house.
It's a good thing I had a profitable day,
or I'd be giving each of you
a piece of my mind.
Yeah, it's in the car.
So lazy.
Yes?
Are you feeling okay?
I'm perfectly fine.
Are you tired, Poj?
Why should I waste my time
investigating this nobody?
I have work to do.
It won't take much of your time.
You have connections everywhere.
How many high-ranking officials
are in your debt?
Just a few questions to them,
and I'll have everything I need on Kajorn.
Too much trouble. I'd rather not.
Wait, are you sure
you don't have a crush on this guy?
Why are you so obsessed with him?
I have a grudge against him. Happy now?
Huh?
Why the attitude? I was just asking.
If you help me with this,
I promise I won't go visit Tri
in Chiang Mai.
Do we have a deal?
Are you serious?
You're my wife.
Not going to see Thatri should be a given.
Besides, a trip to Chiang Mai
is too exhausting for someone like you.
I don't see how this benefits me at all.
Ugh, Poj.
What's your price then?
I'm not telling.
I think you can guess, can't you?
You're a cold-blooded shark.
Always looking for an advantage.
How else do you think I got this rich?
Poj!
Poj.
Let's go.
Put me down.
- Hmm…
- Poj.
Poj.
Now,
it's the worst since the war began.
Food is scarce, jobs are non-existent,
and all of Adisuan's products
are sitting idle.
Our warehouses are overflowing
with unsold stock.
The market still needs what we have.
Agarwood, pearls, and minerals
are always in demand.
It's just the poor economy
and broken logistics.
I believe,
once the war ends, we'll bounce back.
We have enough to last.
What worries me more are the smugglers.
How so, sir?
Colonel Nakamura informed me
that contraband,
mostly food and medicine,
is flooding the market
at ten times the normal rate.
If we let this continue,
it will only crush the people further.
Phuket will be impossible to recover.
Come in.
Sak, what brings you here?
I've come to ask for a huge favor.
I'm not an idiot.
I don't eat grass for breakfast.
Please calm down, Aunt Paetai.
Sak must be in a desperate situation.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have come to us.
But buying up all that tin
at 30 baht per hap is just too much.
It totals over a hundred thousand baht.
That's no small change.
But from what I understand, 30 baht
is the absolute floor price.
He's not asking for anything unreasonable.
Mr. Thatri,
no one wants tin right now.
International trade is frozen.
Even if it were free,
nobody would take it.
And once the war is over?
It still won't exceed 30 baht.
Even before the war,
the price was dropping.
Tin isn't like other commodities.
It's unlikely the price will ever recover.
Please, just this once.
I haven't been able to sell
a single gram of tin.
I owe my workers months of back pay,
and after that bombing the other day,
I'm at my wit's end.
If you buy this stock,
my men can survive.
They'll have enough to start over.
Please, have mercy on me.
This isn't a charity ward.
Now get out. Go back the way you came.
Sak,
you haven't even cleared
your debts with us.
Coming here to ask for more help
is simply out of the question.
But--
There's mo more buts.
This is Adisuan Company money.
Even if you are the heir, you can't just
throw it around as you please.
I'm so sorry.
But we truly cannot accept this.
As Vijarn said,
the price of tin is only going down.
It would be a guaranteed loss for us.
We simply cannot help you.
‪Yes.
Father…
Mother… I'm sorry.
Sorry I couldn't take care
of the inheritance
as I promised.
I don't have much left to give,
but I hope this is enough
for each of you to start over.
If you buy this stock,
my men can survive.
They'll have enough to start over.
I had a feeling
you wouldn't be able to sleep.
Are you worried about Sak?
Aren't you a clever one?
I'm not a dog.
I just guessed that you have a soft heart.
After seeing Sak in that state,
I knew you wouldn't
be able to just stand by.
Acting smart and all.
And what about you? Why are you still up?
I have the same thoughts as you do.
So, you're a softie too.
I was incredibly poor as a child.
If Grandfather hadn't stepped in,
I'd never have made it to Penang.
I might not have even
finished the fourth grade.
Seeing Sak like that,
I can't help but see
my younger self in him.
But everyone else is right.
Helping him means losing money.
As much as I disagree,
I didn't dare speak up
because they were right.
Helping others might hurt us.
Even if it feels wrong,
we have to accept the reality.
So there's really nothing we can do?
Thank you so much.
Are you buying
the entire stock, Mr. Thatri?
Yes, 30 baht per hap,
exactly as you requested.
Thatri, dear. I don't think we should be
throwing money down the drain like this.
Don't worry, Fuang.
This is from the private inheritance
left to Rajit and me in the will.
It's not the company's fund.
I'm within my rights to do this, aren't I?
Yes, sir.
Uncle Ree and I have agreed
to split the cost fifty-fifty for the tin.
Please deliver the tin to the warehouse.
- Yes, miss.
- Then, I'll have Vijarn settle the bill.
Yes. I'll get on it right away.
Thank you both so much.
Idiots.
You didn't work for that money,
so, of course, you're throwing it away.
Go ahead, bankrupt yourselves.
Live like dogs for all I care.
You're still smiling?
We earned that insult.
It's a loss. I don't know why
I went through with it.
But it's done now.
Besides, we saved so many lives today.
We've already profited so much from them.
We can afford a setback for a change.
But it wasn't my money.
I'm sorry, what was that?
I said I'm hungry.
Let's go find something to eat. Come on.
Auntie, I can just have the boiled yams.
Please save this food for the others.
I've already set this aside
for you and Miss Rajit.
It won't take away from others' portion.
I've watched you eat boiled yams
and taro for a week now.
You need a real proper meal.
Thank you.
A fish soup?
This is so refreshing.
Is it?
Mmm. Try some.
The Kam Cheng jar…
ADISUAN LUMBER
Our goods aren't selling,
food is being strictly rationed,
and on top of that,
I'm forced to work with those idiots.
I could just kill them both.
Pae, don't say things like that.
Someone might hear you.
Besides, those two are our relatives.
They're Uncle Som's relatives, not ours.
And even if they were,
I'd disown anyone
who squanders a fortune like that.
That fortune belongs to them.
As long as they don't touch
the company's funds,
we just have to accept it.
Whatever, you little saint.
One day,
they'll squander everything
and come crawling to us for more.
Using money so foolishly.
Saying it
makes me so resentful of Uncle Som.
He didn't leave us a dime,
yet I still have to work
with those people.
Stop complaining, Pae.
If you appreciate what we have,
It'll save you from all this misery.
In that case, I'll head back now.
Fine.
Her saintly act is annoying.
I can't believe that saint
is actually my sister.
Help me.
Caught him stealing.
I had to teach him a little lesson.
Bury him, and make sure he's gone.
Going this long without a raid,
my hands are going to start itching.
Eliminate Thatri.
If we let him live,
he'll end up being the death of me.
You think you're so good, Thatri?
Mr. Thatri and Miss Rajit
have been kidnapped by Zhang Gong Cheng.
Huh?
Oh my God. I'm so worried.
What if something happened to them?
Please let those two vanish forever.
May they never find their way back.
Let's go, Rajit.
Subtitle translation by:
Khathathong Thongtumlueng