Are you Yang Hyeji?
What?
[The Witch Store]
[Episode 3]
[A Rival Spurs a Love Triangle]
I can't stand it any longer.
What am I supposed to do if you suddenly appear at school?
Didn't I tell you that I would be going?
Then, you really came?
- Who took care of the shop during the day?
- We are not busy during the day anyway.
Don't say that like you stayed here during the night.
Right. Guess how bored I am without any customers coming in.
Who would go to school just out of boredom?
Well, I'll continue going for a little while. So let's get along, please.
Oh, speak casually at school.
We are the same age there.
Fine. However, please make sure you follow some rules.
Let me hear what they are first.
First, your identity as a witch should be kept secret.
Okay.
Second, don't use your power at school.
A witch is not supposed to use her power?
Okay, fine.
- Thirdly...
- You don't want me to tease Yuho.
Okay.
I just kidded around with him today. He is not my type.
Anyway, please make sure to follow these three rules.
Fine, that's easy.
There's nothing else, right?
Like what?
My business is in trouble.
I could sell these at school.
Fourth, don't do any business activity at school.
You are too bad. Too bad!
Yuho, are you having fun with Youngji these days?
It's not like that.
You gave her my chocolate milk.
- Your milk?
- Oh, it's over.
Congrats!
Focus.
- You missed it.
- You are not qualified to be a top athlete in class. You are really bad.
Oh, would you mind passing the ball to us?
Who is that?
- Here!
- Thank you.
- Do you want to play?
- No, thank you.
- I haven't seen him before.
- He is in class 2 so you may not know him.
- Focus!
- Block him. Block him.
Oh, Hye...
- Do you need a hand?
- What?
You are in class 1, right? I can carry these there.
- Oh, I am fine.
- No, I can do it for you.
- My class is next to yours.
- Thanks.
- Are you Yang Hyeji?
- What?
I'm right. It is you. It's been a while.
- Do you know me?
- You don't remember me?
I am Yoon Sungwoo. I used to live next door.
Yoon Sungwoo? You transferred when you were in elementary school!
I've come back. You have not changed at all.
Really? Do you attend this school?
- Do you still do judo?
- Yeah.
This school is famous for its judo team.
Oh, yeah. Where do you live now?
- Now...
- Hyeji.
Oh, Yuho.
He is Yoon Sungwoo. He used to live next door. He transferred to class 2.
- This is Han Yuho. He is my classmate.
- Nice to meet you.
- I saw you at the gym earlier, right?
- Yeah.
Right. Nice to meet you.
- This...
- No! I'm fine.
- Hyeji, let's go.
- Okay.
Let's go, Yuho.
Shouldn't I have been between them?
That gym boy and Hyeji are friends?
Class 2... who?
- Sungwoo.
- Sungwoo?
Oh, Yoon Sungwoo?
Do you know him?
He transferred and got a full score at the September mock test as soon as he got here.
Oh, so what?
Yeah, what would you know about that?
What's more interesting is that he is specialized in judo.
Oh, really? He is too competent.
I don't even feel like studying anymore.
- Let's go to the internet cafe.
- Okay, let's go.
Yeah, why don't we...
No thanks. You guys enjoy. I'll study.
- Hey, why?
- Let's go.
- Yuho, let's go.
- No thanks.
Let's go, Yuho.
Let's go!
I should play Jungle Teemo. Let's go just this once.
Oh, hey, block him.
- Hey, Baron! Baron is coming.
- I have Gangta here.
Why would you use Moondo for Gangta? What a waste.
Hey, focus. Stop them from coming in.
Taeil, Yuho is taking the back.
Hey, where are you going, fools?
Okay.
- Wow, the diamond class is excellent.
- Awesome.
Yuho, save me!
- One more?
- Let's go.
Hey, is that...
Oh, such a top student comes here.
Hey, what tier is he at?
- Never mind. Why?
- Silver?
Oh, wait. He is going to charge money.
I am going to patrol.
Why? What?
Silver?
- Challenger.
- What?
Oh, Yuho.
- Hi.
You are Challenger—
No, I mean Yoon Sungwoo. I am Park Hyungseok.
Hey you're Sungwoo, right? I am Choi Taeil.
My tier is gold... bronze which is like gold.
Would you join us if you are alone?
Oh, the computer is on. Come here.
Do you like sausage with rice cake?
What is going on here?
You did so good.
Can I call you Professor?
No, no. I haven't played for so long.
Wow, professor! You are Challenger!
You are humble.
Yuho is a good player too.
Hey, he is way lower than you.
Be quiet, bronze.
Oh, yeah. I heard that you know Hyeji.
Right. I used to live next door.
Okay.
You do judo? How long have you been doing it?
Well, I started it when I was young.
I am not too good at it.
Well, Yuho does judo too.
What are you talking about?
Really? You do judo?
- Well...
- He was a prospective player.
- Hey, what are you talking about?
- Speaking of that...
- You have a photo of doing judo at home.
- That is...
Come visit our judo team.
- What? The judo team?
- Yeah.
Yuho must start practicing today.
Okay, I will go later.
Hey, Taeil, you shouldn't have said that.
Why? It was all true.
- You used to do judo.
- Just two months in elementary school. That's all.
Exactly, it's not like you never did it.
Hey, why did you tell him about the photo?
I saw it. You have it in your house, right?
My mom took it when I was young. That's all.
How would I know such details?
- What should I do?
- Just don't go.
No! You have to go.
- If you don't visit him, you'll admit your loss.
- What are you talking about?
Oh, yeah. You promised to visit him.
Yuho could win.
- I trust you.
- Right. You are a source of our pride.
- Fighting!
- You two really are of no help to me.
- Yuho, fighting!
- Fighting!
We're going.
I'm ruined.
Oh, what is that?
[The Witch Store]
[Contract]
Oh, you don't believe me? Why do I have to sign a contract?
I can't trust you. Hurry up and sign it.
Okay, I will do it later.
Is it a cafe?
What?
Why is he here?
Welcome. I have been waiting for you.
[Shoes That Let You Jump High]
♫  It's moving in your direction  ♫
Sungwoo can we play duo from time to time?
Of course. Call me whenever you want to.
Wow, you are so generous. You want more food?
- What do you want?
- I only want something to drink.
- Okay, I got it.
- Get me chocolate milk.
Hey, you just go with plain water.
♫  I understood what you were  ♫
♫  Can you feel it coming tonight?  ♫
He won't buy you anything.
I know.
I will work hard to be Challenger by next week.