(Sung Dong Il)
(Kim Hee Won, Jang Na Ra)
(House on Wheels: Beyond the Ocean)
(After fishing in the wilderness...)
(with Hye Young, Dong Il's handful daughter)
(They're expecting another guest.)
(Someone is crossing the dead zone without signal.)
There's no signal here, so they won't receive my call.
Hello? Yes, it's me.
I'm almost there.
There's no signal here.
I know. The call didn't go through,
and I'm talking to myself.
The call doesn't get through.
(Laughing)
You got fooled. You thought that I called them.
(Without knowing anything)
- We're going to the supermarket.
- Turn right.
Turn right.
We'll buy marshmallows...
- And soda.
- and soda.
What else do we need?
It’s not strange despite the direction changes.
But going there alone was very strange.
Thank you.
We'll buy marshmallows.
(Dancing)
- Suddenly, my mouth is watering.
- There's a lot of food here.
Suddenly, my mouth is watering.
There's a lot of bread too.
Oh, my gosh.
(At that time...)
(Someone from the wild heads heading to the convenience store.)
How much is it?
(The doorbell rings.)
(The doorbell rings as if someone came in.)
(They have no idea.)
Mint soda?
It would be easier to drink that mint chocolate.
Mint soda sounds okay.
Should I try this one?
Try it.
- Soda.
- Soda?
- With soda...
- This is really...
(Stumbling out of surprise)
Hello. It's nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Gosh.
It's good to see you.
- Mi Ran, pick a drink.
- Hello.
I got all the groceries already.
Really?
(In "Reply 1988," Hye Young played as Dong Il's handful daughter...)
(who even tamed the “cheetah lady” next door.)
(Now they even travel abroad together.)
(Real friends in reality)
- Hee Won.
- Yes?
(She became close to Dong Il and Hee Won like family.)
What's wrong?
(Ra Mi Ran, a guest for life at House on Wheels)
(You're here.)
Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
- Now...
- From here...
It takes two minutes to get here by car.
- Did you two come here together?
- Yes.
(Saying hello politely after a violent hug)
Did they send you here?
- They're cooking.
- Right.
- Really?
- We came out to have fun.
- They're cooking?
- Yes.
I should make something delicious for Mi Ran.
- They're cooking?
- Yes.
- They sent us out to have fun.
- What are you going to buy?
- We're here to buy soda.
- Soda...
and marshmallows. We'll make a fire.
S'more?
(She picks it up right away.)
What don't we buy this instead?
It's delicious with potato chips.
(Surprised)
You know a lot about food.
- You know a lot about food.
- On potato chips...
Potato chips are over here.
Let's get a consomme flavor and this one too.
- Okay.
(Like possessed, they add another bag of potato chips.)
- Do you have eggs?
- We have eggs.
You must have side dishes too.
- Yes, we have a lot of things.
- Okay.
That should be fine.
- Is there anything else you'd like?
- In France...
Something else? No, it's okay.
- Bananas, then?
- Morning apples.
- I want to eat apples.
- Apples.
Here they are. Let's see.
- Should we have tangerines?
- No.
- In the morning.
No.
- Morning pineapples.
- No.
(Sad)
(Trying not to laugh)
(Ms. Cheetah is keeping her handful daughter in check.)
- Okay.
- Okay?
There are Maitake mushrooms.
- Hey.
- These look nice.
(Really wanting them)
- Let's get one of these.
- We can eat mushrooms with meat.
- Mushrooms?
- Maitake mushrooms.
- Okay.
- Oh, different mushrooms.
(Laughing)
Oh, driving.
(Shy)
Na Ra's...
Oh, are you a good driver?
- I'm good at following...
- Best driver.
(Shyly laughing)
I'm a bit...
(Getting too much praise is tough for introverts.)
I find it hard when using GPS.
We've never met before, right?
- Not even once, right?
- Right.
- Right?
(It was quite an intense first encounter.)
(Excited about having a new friend)
(Du-du-du)
(Du-du-du-du)
Sadly, I can't back up well.
Just don't back up into a well.
(Oh, gosh)
(She can praise anything.)
- That was funny.
- Was that nice?
Yes.
(She can praise anything too.)
(Proud)
It took you so long, right?
(Sighing)
You almost passed out on the way here, right?
I took off at 6am this morning from Seoul.
- Dong Il and Hee Won kept saying...
- I've been on the road...
for 12 hours now.
(It's 6pm right now.)
I've been on the move this whole time.
On the way here,
- I saw that supermarket.
- Right.
I found a specialty product of Hokkaido.
- You bought something.
- I bought a specialty product...
- from that supermarket.
- Oh, my.
That's nice.
Mostly snacks Hye Young would like.
I love that.
Na Ra loves snacks too.
- Really? Snacks?
- Yes, I do too.
(Sweet Tooth Sisters)
I'm glad you two met.
She always said to me, "Just try this one."
"This one is really delicious." Then, I said, "Hey, it's so sweet!"
- "It's too sweet." - "Mi Ran, just try a bite."
"No! It looks so sweet."
- Do you not really like sweets?
- No.
- I love sweets.
- I see.
I think she's on a higher level than me.
No, I can't eat too much either.
I just like buying them.
- I like looking at them.
- Right.
I like buying and collecting them.
I also like seeing others eat them.
- Totally.
- Like watching a baby?
Yes, there's a happiness in that.
The joy of feeding someone.
(That's my expertise.)
We're here now.
It's close.
Oh, it's a campsite.
- Yes.
- That's good.
(After chatting a bit, they're already at the front yard.)
Oh, my. This...
I think this is the best thing we've had in Japan yet.
- Really?
- Of course.
(What are they cooking?)
- Go get some aged kimchi.
- Okay.
- Aged kimchi?
- Yes.
(Aged kimchi, pork belly)
(The first dish for tonight's dinner uses pork belly and aged kimchi.)
I want to eat braised pork and aged kimchi.
(She put in the order.)
That's what I'm talking about.
That's how we should've made it before.
(On the nicely seared pork belly, )
(pour some water.)
I brought this aged kimchi from Gangjin.
(The aged kimchi from Gangjin is working hard as usual.)
This has to be good.
(By the red color, you already know it's going to be delicious.)
My gosh. This smells good.
Oh, my gosh.
I can already tell this is going to be delicious.
Seriously, I can already tell.
- That looks pretty good, right?
- Yes.
I think this is the best thing we've had in Japan yet.
(The aged kimchi really stimulates your appetite.)
- Is that the car coming in?
- Where?
- It must be them in the car.
- You're right. It's Mi Ran.
Mi Ran is here.
Best driver.
(Laughing)
(The car with Ra Mi Ran has come to House on Wheels!)
Let's go greet them.
Where's Mi Ran?
Oh, gosh.
Mi Ran.
(Throwing her leg up)
Oh, goodness. I'm glad you're here.
Dong Il, please take her.
- Help me.
- He can't carry me anymore.
(Like when she came to House on Wheels 5 years ago)
He can't carry me anymore.
(They greet each other with a hug like last time.)
- Your back is too weak now.
- Mi Ran. Come here.
- Come here.
- I'm so glad you're here.
- Go here. Stand here.
- Okay.
- Stand here. Hee Won, come here.
- Should we get on our knees?
- Thank you for coming all this way.
Thank you so much, Mi Ran.
We asked you to come, but I feel so bad.
- Right. It's so far.
- Seriously.
- It was very far.
It felt like going to Europe.
- It was so far, right?
- Thank you so much.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- Of course. I came to see you guys.
- Right?
Thank you so much.
Who knows what would've happened to me if I didn't come?
(Laughing)
- No, seriously.
- Thank you so much.
Even after inviting you,
Hee Won and I kept talking about it for days.
Are you sore anywhere?
- Sit down.
- Sit here.
Sit down, Mi Ran. Let's sit down and chat.
- Stretch out your legs.
- Hye Young.
- Yes.
- Take a seat next to Mi Ran.
Hee Won, let them stretch out their legs on your back.
Okay, Dong Il.
Get down and let them stretch out their legs on your back.
There's not enough space. I'm sorry.
I'm serious.
Mi Ran. Why did you become so much lighter?
- What?
- Did you lose weight?
- Hee Won...
- It was so easy to lift you.
I told you I was on a diet when we were filming " Hi-FIVE."
- Exactly. Dong Il.
- I thought she was sick...
because she lost so much weight.
- Not that much.
- I can't lift most women...
- She's so light.
- Exactly.
When I lifted her earlier...
You didn't think you'd be able to, did you?
(While they continue to tell their happy stories...)
- Seriously.
- You know I... Oh, gosh!
- Oh, gosh!
- What is it?
Your fart smell just came to me.
Dong Il. She traveled 12 hours to come here.
I'll smell the fire instead.
(Neutralizing the fart with the smell of the fire)
(Dong Il ran away.)
Hey, her pants are stuck.
Her pants are stuck.
Why did you get your pants stuck?
- They just got stuck...
- Hey, Dong Il just...
(Total chaos)
Dong Il farted because he was startled.
Oh, gosh.
Anyway, I couldn't bring anything...
when I came here, so I...
Hey, Mi Ran. You didn't need to bring us anything.
- We're just happy to have you here.
- I just got...
some things from the supermarket.
Apparently, these are products you can only find in Hokkaido.
- Really?
- Supermarket specialty products.
We've had lots of those,
but if you brought them... Is that makgeolli?
- Makgeolli?
- No.
- Milk?
- It's yogurt liquor.
(This is new, right?)
- Yogurt liquor.
- Yogurt liquor?
- There's yogurt liquor?
- It's a specialty product here.
- I see.
- Nice.
- Milk for tomorrow morning.
- Milk.
Slightly healthy cereal. And not healthy cereal.
(Mi Ran's housewarming gifts)
Snacks for Hye Young.
(The gifts just keep on coming!)
I think this is partially cooked.
- We could grill that.
- This is cheese.
This is toast for tomorrow morning.
I brought just some Camembert...
and orange jam.
(Mi Ran's housewarming gifts made our house more bountiful.)
Let's sit. Wait. Hold on.
Everyone, sit down.
(Seeing all of the gifts made Dong Il want to hurry.)
You're hungry, right, Mi Ran? Today,
I'll make you every food there is in the world.
I'm being serious.
Tuna. Tuna fillet.
(Urchin roe they bought in Yoichi)
This area is famous for Wagyu.
We went and bought some famous Wagyu ourselves.
(He'll serve every delicious food they've had in Hokkaido!)
Oh, my. I think I can smell some delicious jjigae.
I brought kimchi aged for two years from Gangjin,
- from a place I know.
- Gangjin, South Jeolla Province?
Yes. I brought 40kg of it. We're surviving off of that.
- I see.
- Today, Hye Young said...
she wanted to eat braised aged kimchi.
(My gosh!)
What did you put in here? Oh, my gosh.
(Gasping)
Over here.
(Slurping)
We just have to cook it down a bit more.
Oh, my gosh.
It's so delicious.
(Happy)
- This with just rice is enough.
- Yes.
- Hee Won.
- Yes?
- Make sushi.
- Okay.
Mi Ran.
- Hee Won is great at making sushi.
- What?
Hee Won is.
- No, I'm not.
- Does he know how to do things now?
- Yes.
- No.
(Laughing)
There's nothing he knows how to do.
You're right.
(Hokkaido's Sushi King starts cooking.)
- This may be the only thing...
- You can make sushi?
- Gosh.
- Here's the tray.
Gosh, I've not expected...
I'd be able to see you cook in my lifetime.
Mi Ran, can you pass me a big dish?
(An unusual scene she didn't expect to see)
- Did the rice cook well?
- Yes, it did.
Here. Try a bit of it.
- Good, isn't it?
- It cooked perfectly for sushi.
- Mi Ran, look under the sink.
- Yes?
This much should do.
Are there wet wipes, Mi Ran?
- Wet wipes?
- We do have wet wipes.
- Where?
- Here.
- Thank you.
- When you store wet wipes,
store them like this and not like this.
- To keep it moist.
- To keep it moist?
Gosh, you've become a housekeeper.
I happened to see it in shorts.
(5 years of House on Wheels has made Hee Won a housekeeper!)
I never thought a day would come when Hee Won would teach...
how to store wet wipes.
(He finds it hilarious too.)
This...
(Housekeeping King starts making sushi.)
Hey, Hye Young.
- Do you need help?
- Did you take the cooking oil?
Yes, someone took it outside.
Then I can use olive oil.
It's because the rice sticks to the gloves.
To mix the rice.
On the hand?
Just a tad bit. That's enough.
Is olive oil normally this sticky?
It's oligosaccharide.
Oh, dear. I didn't know it was oligosaccharide.
Wash it off.
I thought it was olive oil.
You brought oligosaccharide.
Isn't oligosaccharide sweet?
No wonder it was sticky.
How about perilla oil?
- Yes, that works.
- Perilla oil, right?
(Perilla oil)
- Good. Yes, it should be oily.
- Right?
(Sushi making is back on track thanks to Hye Young's support.)
It's hot.
It's so hot.
So hot.
(Despite it, the Sushi King does his best.)
It's hot.
(Meanwhile, Dong Il is busy before the griddle.)
Hey, Mi Ran.
Mi Ran, look at the beef.
Oh, my gosh. Shall I try it raw?
Go ahead.
(For Mi Ran who came from afar, Dong Il prepared...)
(beef from Biei, the paradise of dairy farming.)
Is this stone? Is it a stone grill?
- It looks like one.
- It's actually ceramic.
- It's a griddle.
- A griddle?
I kept taking care of it...
- while using it.
- The griddle looks thick.
It's really thick.
It's too heavy to lift. I'm serious.
Gosh, didn't you visit Italy multiple times? Really, Mi Ran.
(Miming)
- Mi Ran.
- Yes?
You know how you guys will put CG on it?
(Sure thing.)
Before you came,
- Yes?
- here's what I told Na Ra,
"Mi Ran takes on funny roles,"
"but she's actually very dignified and quiet."
- Really?
- Yes.
(Dignified and quiet Mi Ran)
I should take back what I said.
- She hasn't seen me yet.
- Not yet?
Okay, got it.
(Washing the vegetables, Na Ra missed Mi Ran's true nature.)
- Is that the sink?
- No.
You will get chances to do the dishes tomorrow. Go take a seat.
(Na Ra returns from washing the vegetables)
Here are the washed vegetables.
(The fresh vegetables washed by Na Ra are ready!)
Like oil?
That's not lard.
(It's a broccoli.)
You know how you use radish before making jeon?
Did you turn the stove off?
For what?
- The braised kimchi. Go check.
- I turned it off.
- You did?
- I'll go get it.
(Throwing in some butter)
This is a super luxurious barbecue party.
(The buttery aroma spreads on the griddle.)
This is beyond my imagination.
- It's been a while.
- The smell of butter.
Oh, my gosh.
(Getting excited with the aroma of butter)
You're dropping everything.
(Throwing in the vegetables washed by Na Ra into the butter)
You must really love it, Mi Ran.
Mi Ran loves activities like this one.
(In bliss)
(An unexpected happiness brought by the griddle)
It's just like...
letting the fox guard the henhouse.
Like asking the fox to guard the henhouse.
I keep dropping them.
Is that so?
- In front.
- Yes, right here.
Good. It's best to be careful.
(Fidgeting)
Have some cheese, Dong Il.
- The one in front?
- The one we bought?
(Sharing snacks with the cooks)
Isn't it tasty and spicy?
- It's really good.
- Here's some cheese.
Try the cheese.
- It's my favorite, Na Ra.
- It's delicious.
- Isn't it?
- Yes.
Why didn't you cut this one?
(While eating the cheese from Na Ra)
(The vegetables are getting cooked on the hot griddle.)
How did you come up with the griddle?
Push all of it to the side.
Do we have it raw?
Let's have it as sushi. Don't eat it plain.
(The next teppan dish is tuna from Sapporo!)
- All done?
- Yes, give me a second.
- Tataki.
- Yes, tataki. You grill it.
- Tuna tataki.
- That's right.
(Grilling the outside of the thick tuna meat to eat as steak)
All good, right?
With you here, Mi Ran, I feel reassured.
- Hee Won, go and make sushi.
- Yes?
Okay.
- And remember our grill?
- Yes.
- The one we used for the meat.
Warm it up.
- Okay.
- Good.
Okay.
At least he understands what you say.
Hee Won has really matured.
- Exactly.
- Right?
He has changed.
Yes, Hee Won has changed.
(The Sushi King is open for business.)
(Wasabi)
Can I watch you from here?
- Go ahead.
- Yes.
Don't do a thing, Mi Ran.
(Mi Ran came over to watch.)
Isn't it one per person?
Hee Won, it's 222 pieces of rice, right?
- Even if you're my daughter.
- Oh, my gosh.
It's supposed to be 280.
What a weird shape.
No, the shape doesn't matter to us. It's okay.
- Hee Won, it looks like...
- Well done.
Someone dropped it.
- Right, like snot.
- Yes.
It's because there's not enough rice to make it hold its shape.
(The Sushi King has yet to master the visual part.)
Hurry up.
(It's just funny to Mi Ran.)
(The A-grade beef is on the griddle.)
I'm going to cook it with a torch.
(The torch is on.)
(With the heat from the griddle for the bottom...)
(and the torch for the top, )
(the Griddle King has conquered both the smokiness and the show.)
(Grill mine too.)
(2 beef sushi)
Gosh, the show is...
Why is Hee Won holding that up?
- To put it on there?
- To torch it.
No, to torch it.
The sushi?
- Yes.
- It's raw.
- These.
- I see.
- So you're smoking them.
- Yes.
(Torching the raw sushi)
Oh, no.
Don't worry. The inside is still raw.
- It'll go on top.
- Gently.
(A mouthwatering visual)
I can't... I have to stop eating.
It looks amazing.
Right?
(The beef is about to be done!)
- Bring the grill over.
- What?
The grill.
Place it over there.
(While the dishes are being done, )
All set.
(what are the sweet tooth sisters doing?)
Is there anything more you need?
This is the soy sauce we bought earlier.
I want to smell it.
This is that very soy sauce.
Urchin soy sauce. Uni soy sauce.
- The urchin roe must be in it.
- Yes.
- But it's soy sauce, right?
(Before leaving Biei, they stopped by...)
(100-year-old soy sauce brewery with over 100 varieties.)
(From the rare cherry blossom soy sauce...)
(It's the soy sauce to spread on bread.)
(to the good-value urchin roe soy sauce)
(We don't need to buy urchin roe.)
(After sampling them carefully)
(It's not a perfume.)
Yes, it's this one!
(They chose 4 soy sauces for the guests!)
- The color is...
- It has a rich flavor.
Try it.
If you buy one bottle...
This smells like vegetables.
- That must've been green onions.
- What is it?
This one is the bomb.
Try a bit of it.
- This is just urchin roe.
- That alone would be delicious...
enough in my opinion.
It's very good.
(How is it?)
Isn't it good?
- The umami flavor is incredible.
- Amazing, right?
- But it's soy sauce, right?
- Yes.
It's more than just tasty.
It's like...
Let's take these outside,
- place them next to the dishes, - Okay.
- and eat them together.
- I'm in.
All right, let's sit.
- Hold on.
- "Hold on."
Sprinkle some sesame.
(Mi Ran finds the sight of Hee Won hilarious.)
It looks delicious.
(After sprinkling some sesame on top of the urchin roe...)
(The salmon roe is waiting.)
Salmon roe.
(Topping it with salmon roe as much as the guest wants)
Pour some soy sauce and it's done, right?
There are four types of soy sauce.
We bought some soy sauce that might suit your taste.
Try a bit of the soy sauce.
- These are the soy sauces?
- Yes.
- The soy sauces are...
- Is this soy sauce too?
- That was garlic or...
- It's onion soy sauce.
- It could be onion soy sauce.
- Onion soy sauce.
Urchin roe soy sauce.
That one is really good, Mi Ran.
- Is it?
- Yes.
(Rich flavor, urchin roe soy sauce, highly recommended by Na Ra)
- It smells rich.
- It must be a little salty.
(Exclaiming)
(Making sound effect)
Oh, my gosh.
Urchin roe soy sauce.
My mouth...
- It looks good.
- is watering.
(Making Mi Ran get up)
It looks delicious.
(The table might break.)
(A table of Hokkaido's delicacies)
(Tuna from Sapporo, urchin roe from Yoichi, wagyu from Biei)
These are...
(Teppan wagyu and vegetables, straight from the Biei farm)
(Whole tuna teppan received from Sapporo)
(A table of teppan dishes made with the best quality ingredients)
Look at this. Look at the visual of the food.
Unbelievable.
The dried seaweed...
- is made by Na Ra's mother.
- Yes.
Really?
(Grilled wagyu rice bowl with dried seaweed from Na Ra's mother)
(A spicy appetizer)
This might be the best dish.
(Even Dong Il's number 1 dish, braised aged kimchi with pork too)
It looks delicious.
- It looks delicious - Gosh.
(A table full of Hokkaido ingredients)
Try the sushi first. The beef sushi.
- Okay.
(Wagyu sushi smoked right before the meal with love)
(Warm)
- What's this?
- Thank you for the meal.
- Cheers.
- Try that one first.
(Eating the fist-sized sushi whole)
(Their cheeks are stuffed.)
How's the beef so tender?
(Mumbling)
- It's smoky.
- Sorry?
- The smokiness.
- Right.
I can taste it.
It's for you two.
(It's good, right?)
Delicious.
(Worked up the appetite with the welcome food)
- Not bad, right? Keep it there.
- Okay.
This has tuna and all sorts.
(Trying the rice bowl topped with...)
(urchin roe from Yoichi and salmon roe)
(Admiring the spoonful first)
It looks great.
(Eating a spoonful of urchin roe and salmon roe)
(Emptying the spoon)
(How is it, my handful daughter?)
(Putting the spoon down)
(You're the best, Dad.)
- Shall we dig in?
- Go ahead.
- Did you pour soy sauce on it?
- Yes.
Make sure to pour some in.
(A roe party inside the mouth)
- It's good, right?
- Yes, absolutely.
Amazing, isn't it?
The saltiness of the salmon roe.
(The salty salmon roe that's chewy and popping)
The urchin roe soy sauce is incredible.
(The umami-rich urchin roe soy sauce really plays a role!)
(Mi Ran calmly makes a tower.)
(Egg yolk)
(Dried seaweed flakes)
(Even if it's a bite, she puts in a lot of effort.)
Take a tuna each.
How is it?
Wait.
The shiso.
(As soon as she says it, )
(Dong Il gets up.)
(I love shiso.)
A.M.A.
A man of action.
(A man of action)
Thank you.
(Shiso looks like Korean perilla leaf.)
This is a must.
I'm going to make a ssam.
With some urchin roe.
(A mountain of urchin roe on a shiso ssam)
Unique, right?
- We could boil it too.
- Delicious, right?
It's aromatic.
(Cutting the stalk off)
(Aromatic)
(Is it that good?)
(An endless refill of salmon roe)
(Happy)
How luxurious.
(Dig in, Hye Young.)
Good job.
You're really digging into the kaisendon.
Yes.
(Today, she's the daughter of a rich family.)
(In bliss)
(Dad is feeling proud.)
It's good.
(Tearing a piece of kimchi)
(Leaving with a piece of kimchi)
(She's really excited.)
(Tearing the kimchi apart)
It looks good. Gosh.
(Wriggling her eyebrows)
(Eating the rice and kimchi at the same time)
(Hee Won tries the kimchi first out of everything.)
(This is what I'm talking about.)
(Dong Il starts with the braised kimchi as well.)
I'm sure the pork in the braised kimchi is good.
(The meat is tender and seasoned well.)
I asked the meat to be cut into thick pieces.
- It's a whole kimchi.
- It's too big.
The knife was somewhere here.
- The knife...
- No, I'll cut it with scissors.
(Attentive Dong Il)
(Cutting)
- You're supposed to tear it.
- Here.
- You can have the big pieces.
- But you're supposed to tear it,
- not cut it.
- No, it needs to be cut.
- Tear it with your hands.
- I should?
But I only have one glove on.
- Use the scissors to tear it.
- Got it.
Leave after dinner.
Leave, Mi Ran.
(But Mi Ran came to Japan from Korea.)
I'll tear it for you, Mi Ran.
- It tastes different.
- Got it.
(I'm a guest today.)
- This is what you want, right?
- Yes.
Here. Get some rice.
This is what mothers did in the past.
Eat it.
(Sighing)
She's the pickiest guest we've ever had.
(Coughing)
(Feeling small)
- Dong Il.
- What?
She's a guest from Korea.
I was talking about you.
(Thank you.)
(Regardless, Na Ra is blowing a kimchi pipe.)
(Tearing)
(Wrapping the meat with kimchi cut by Dong Il)
(Eating a mouthful)
(Is it too big?)
Good, right?
- It's delicious.
- Isn't it?
- The best dish with rice.
- Yes.
(The legendary braised kimchi approved by all the members)
(Na Ra and Hye Young have become close.)
- Is the tuna seasoned?
- Slightly.
- Is it?
- Enjoy with grilled vegetables.
- I'll try it with onion soy sauce.
- It's awesome.
The tuna is amazing.
- The tuna?
- Yes, this one.
- Try it, Mi Ran.
- Okay.
(Trying a piece of tuna after dipping it into the onion soy sauce)
How is the thick tuna so good?
(This time, it's raw tuna shiso ssam.)
Mix it together.
(Eating Expert Mi Ran)
(A combination of raw tuna and onion soy sauce)
(Impressed)
You've dug in, right?
- I'm not done yet.
- Eat more.
After dinner, I'll serve potatoes and corn that are famous in Japan.
Do you know about...
raw corn that you don't boil?
- Super sweet corn?
- Yes.
- The sweet ones.
- We've got some.
I'll serve them later.
There's a 20,000-dollar melon.
You know what it is, right?
- Was it Umeda melon?
- Umeda melon?
- It...
- Yubari?
- Yes, that one.
- Yubari melon.
- Yubari.
- Yubari?
- I'll serve you potatoes and corn.
- Okay.
That's a great idea.
(Let's have potatoes and corn.)
You can eat it, right? Hold on, run a bit.
(While Hye Young is off to digest)
(Struggling)
(The warmest spot)
(Hee Won takes the guest's spot.)
How nice.
Hee Won, that's where the guest should sit.
I'm only here to cook, but you...
(Nagging)
(Trudging)
Stay seated, sir.
How big is your thick puffer jacket?
(Your thick puffer jacket looks warm.)
- Do you want to wear it?
- No.
I can keep running.
- It'll make me warm.
- Right?
- Come here, Na Ra.
- Sit over there.
- Sit here, Na Ra.
- Do it.
- Thank you.
- Toast the marshmallows there.
Okay.
Closer. Good, right?
- Yes, it's warm.
- Nice, isn't it?
- Dong Il, the potatoes.
- Right.
There are five kinds of potatoes in Japan.
Look at these.
(Colorful potatoes)
(Hokkaido, a vast potato patch, )
(produces 80 percent of potatoes in Japan.)
(There are around 50 improved kinds of potatoes.)
He's someone we met in Japan.
He sent it to us.
(Even an explanation of the potatoes)
It's so pretty.
- This is the translation.
- Yes, here.
May Queen.
This potato is May Queen.
Here.
- May Queen.
- Good.
Here.
It's warm. Try it.
- Really?
- It's warm.
- May Queen...
- Yes?
Is similar to Korea's Sumi potatoes.
- I love Sumi potatoes.
- Yes.
May Queen.
- It has a chewy texture...
- It looks good.
- and subtle sweetness.
- Sweetness.
(May Queen is commonly used in cooking.)
Dong Il, this potato tastes like injeolmi.
(The potato is very chewy.)
- Next is Red Moon.
- All right.
(Red Moon Potato?)
(It looks like a sweet potato.)
It's red on the outside, and the inside is yellow.
It looks like a sweet potato, but it's a potato.
- This one?
- Yes.
(Sniffing Red Moon out of curiosity)
(What?)
(Does it taste sweet like sweet potatoes?)
Red Moon tastes like an ordinary potato.
I like this one. It has a unique scent.
- The potato scent?
- Red Moon?
- This one.
- Yes.
(He tries a different type of potato.)
Dong Il, it tastes really like a chestnut sweet potato.
Which one is that? "Kita Akari."
Kita Akari.
Due to its strong sweet taste, it's also called chestnut potato.
(Fluffy)
This is just like a sweet potato.
(It tastes like a chestnut sweet potato.)
This is really like a sweet potato. Do you want to try it?
(She takes out another type of potato.)
This one is...
(Is it a roasted sweet potato?)
That one looks delicious.
It looks like a roasted potato. It's called Shadow Queen.
A colored potato with a subtle sweet taste.
(A colored potato with a subtle sweet taste?)
(Colored?)
It looks like radish from Ganghwa.
You mean a turnip?
(She cuts Shadow Queen open.)
(What is it?)
You mean a turnip?
(Moaning)
- Hey.
- It doesn't look good.
(Purple)
What? What's wrong with the color?
The color doesn't look delicious.
I actually think that it'll be good.
(Taking a bite of Shadow Queen carefully)
- Isn't it nice?
- It tastes like a potato.
- Isn't it more bland than others?
- Yes.
(Shadow Queen has more moisture than stickiness of a potato.)
- This one looks the best for me.
- Let's add butter and honey to it.
Honey.
- It's really good.
- Honey.
Don't you have honey here?
- We had potatoes with honey.
- I'm sorry, but we only have sugar.
- Sugar?
- We have oligosaccharide.
That sounds good.
(Oligosaccharide that Hee Won applied on his hands)
(Fumbling)
How will you eat it?
I'll add butter and honey on it.
(Mi Ran's Honey Potato: 1. A lot of butter on the potato)
- It's like butter potato.
- It looks delicious.
(2. Pour honey or oligosaccharide on top.)
(One for Na Ra)
It's butter potato.
- Butter potato?
- Yes.
- Did you add butter to it?
- This is for Na Ra.
(Me?)
- Thank you.
- Is it for Na Ra?
You also put oligosaccharide.
- Butter potato?
- Would you like some?
(Mi Ran's magic makes an ordinary potato taste 2 or 3 times better.)
It's delicious.
(Mi Ran is the best.)
You put it on your hands earlier.
(This time, she delivers it directly to his mouth.)
It tastes good.
(Finger-licking delicious)
Really?
(Delicious food should be shared.)
(Isn't it good?)
Usually, this corn is more yellow than that.
I was very surprised after tasting it.
(This is pure white corn you can eat uncooked.)
Try some.
- Oh, my. It's sweet.
- I was very surprised.
(A bite of corn with the husk removed)
- It's very sweet.
- Isn't this an apple?
- Right?
- It explodes with juiciness...
in the mouth.
Even though it's white, it tastes like super sweet corn.
ASMR.
(Laughing)
(Whatever she does, she's cute.)
ASMR.
(Crunching)
(I don't know what it is, but I'm strangely drawn to it.)
(While she's working hard on creativity)
Dong Il, it doesn't burn.
- No, in the countryside...
- You're making smoke.
We burnt this on purpose to keep mosquitoes away.
Does it keep mosquitoes away?
The smoke keeps everything away including mosquitoes and people.
(I see.)
The smoke keeps the living beings away.
Go away.
(Very upset)
- Dong Il. Hye Young.
- She just got here...
Thank you for coming.
(Are you siding with them, Hee Won?)
Hee Won has a warm heart.
What's wrong? Isn't this what we decided to do?
Go away.
(A married couple's argument never lasts.)
(Na Ra cooks the marshmallows by gently rotating them.)
It got burnt.
Take these.
Grab it with these and pull it out.
(Mi Ran's suggestion, marshmallow and potato chips?)
(S'more, roasted marshmallow in between crackers)
(Salty potato chips instead of crackers?)
Like this.
(Pulling out the marshmallow with potato chips)
- Gosh.
- There you go.
It's too burnt.
(Mi Ran's recommentation, potato chip s'more)
(Sweet, salty, and crunchy)
(An irresistible combination of salty and sweet)
(The next one is for Hye Young.)
(Stretching out her neck)
- Ta-da.
- Yes.
(A taste you can have endlessly)
Suddenly, I feel happy.
(Thanks to Mi Ran, the sweet tooth sisters became happy.)
I made it last time, and it was delicious.
(What is she making again?)
(Pressing)
(A corn skewer)
Are you going to roast it? Nice.
- When it's roasted...
- Won't the wooden chopstick burn?
It might not taste good when it's roasted.
(Placing uncooked corn right into the fire)
(Curious and anticipating)
Butter.
Hokkaido is known for its butter.
- Right, I heard that too.
- Dairy products.
- Did you just roast it?
- I roasted it.
Corn roasted in butter.
(Dishes come out endlessly.)
- With butter...
- This has to taste good.
Something keeps dripping.
(Butter drips from the hot corn.)
It's butter.
- Eat this side.
- Can I try one bite?
The butter melted. I just took it out of the fire.
(She tries a bite.)
(Quiet)
(How is it?)
It's burnt corn, not butter corn.
(Does it taste strange?)
(She takes another bite.)
She's puzzled by the taste, so she keeps eating it.
(It's almost empty.)
It tastes good.
(When the three are together, they eat until the end.)
It just tastes like butter.
Anything that's grilled or fried in butter is good.
I definitely agree.
(Talking about food lightens the mood.)
Hee Won is working very hard because you came from afar.
(Have a talk with a hot drink.)
(It's time to get warm with tea made by Hee Won.)
(Glasses covered with steam)
Hee Won is like the owner of the campsite.
(Wearing a hat in the middle of the night)
- It's nice to drink something hot.
- The hat looks perfect on you.
- You have a gentle-looking face.
- Right?
I have all the necessary facial features.
And your lips are slightly thick.
(Laughing)
- You seem like a cozy person.
- Right.
As someone who has kissed Hee Won...
That's right. Didn't you play a married couple?
- There was a scene where we kissed.
- Wasn't it called...
It was a movie called "Hot Young Bloods."
- We were a young couple.
- We were in a relationship.
Really?
(That star is your star)
(Touching)
(Forward)
(Shy)
I was very expressive with my feelings, but he was timid.
He wanted to be secretive about our relationship.
I said, "When are we..."
"going to do it?" I was upset at him.
When I approached him to kiss him,
I could feel that he was pushing me away.
(He pushed me away.)
(I'm sorry about that, Mi Ran.)
Then I grabbed him tightly like I was twisting a coil.
(Backing away little by little)
(Throwing herself onto him)
(Scared)
(Lifting and slamming)
- He was a very timid man.
- I'm sorry.
(Just imagining it makes her cringe.)
- You don't have to apologize.
- I've never met Hye Young before.
- She's very positive and honest.
- Is it your first time meeting her?
- It's my first time meeting her.
- Right.
- Don't you two get along well?
- Definitely.
Yes.
I've known Mi Ran...
for ten years.
She raised her voice at me once.
- Did she?
- Yes.
- I was very furious.
- In Japan...
- You remember...
- What happened?
We went on a trip to Japan.
What I imagined as our walking distance...
and her idea of a quick walk.
- There was a huge gap.
- Wait.
- You committed a huge sin.
- I was walking happily.
It was past the mealtime.
We were heading to a supermarket.
She kept walking towards the supermarket.
I told her many times. "Hye Young,"
"let's stop somewhere and eat."
- "It'll be break time soon." - Right.
I suggested eating something at a nearby restaurant.
After saying okay, she kept walking.
Come on.
- She remembers it so differently.
- It was way past the mealtime.
Let's give them some space.
- Tell us when you're ready.
- Then Mi Ran stopped...
in the middle of the way.
She shouted, "When are we going to eat?"
(Plopping down)
(Looking back on it, she's slightly embarrassed.)
Right after that, we went to eat delicious ramen.
- Did she feel better after eating?
- Yes.
- She calmed down right away.
- It doesn't take long.
I became very gentle.
- Yes, right away.
- I get it now.
You get along well because you're simpleminded.
It's 10pm. It's late. Let's go to bed.
- Okay, let's go to sleep.
- Okay.
(They might chat all night long.)
(Tonight, Na Ra and the guests sleep inside House on Wheels.)
It's really nice.
- Goodness.
- Shall we have a night snack?
A night snack?
Should I go to the restroom after eating it?
(They aren't thinking about sleeping.)
Good night, Dong Il.
Good night. Sleep well.
Are you already lying down inside?
I'm just lying down.
(He's ready to sleep.)
Is it okay inside?
(She cares for them violently.)
(Zipping down)
(Chuckling)
It's nice and warm.
(An overwhelming greeting to receive while lying down)
- I really like it.
- Are you saying hello like that?
(Crowding up)
It's really nice.
Why are you sleeping?
Where is he?
- I don't see him.
- I'm right here.
- Go ahead and sleep.
- I need to sleep.
- Sleep well.
- Good night.
Good night.
- He's lying down like gimbap.
- I was curious.
- I was so surprised.
- Put the shoes inside.
Okay.
I got a breakout all over my face.
Oh, no. I also got this...
- today.
- My whole face broke out.
Really? Oh, no.
I have an ointment.
Can I use some of it?
Spread the ointment over your face.
Thank you.
I used to have...
These days, makeup doesn't cover it.
I think it happens when I'm having a hard time.
Can you give me back the ointment?
I'm sorry. Didn't I give it back?
- Do I still have it?
- Did you put it in your pocket?
Did I put it in?
- I'm sorry. I have a bad habit.
- I didn't think you'd do that.
I have a bad habit of stealing.
Where did I put it?
- Hee Won.
- Yes?
The girls are having a lot of fun.
I don't think they'll sleep tonight.
(They expect a very long night.)
Gosh, my stomach feels bloated again.
Right? I feel like I'm becoming water hyacinth.
Exactly like water hyacinth. That's the perfect description.
I feel like water hyacinth.
(They're chatting again.)
What time is it?
It's 1:30am.
Gosh, it's still early.
(The girls' night continued until 3am.)
(Stories as countless as stars at night drift by.)
(The front yard by the lake lights up gradaully.)
(The gentle ripples beckon.)
(The animals of Hokkaido wake up and prepare for the morning.)
(Hye Young of House on Wheels also got up at 5:10am.)
(After stretching for a long time)
Gosh, my handful daughter woke up.
(Turning)
- Are you up?
- Yes.
(With a lot of energy early in the morning)
- Goodness, you're dancing.
- Yes.
(Joining her dad who's having his morning walk)
My body feels very light.
- Really?
- Yes.
I get to walk with my daughter at this hour.
(In a good mood)
Hee Won is up.
Hey, brother.
(I'm glad that I caught him.)
Hee Won.
(Father and daughter in sync)
We should spend the morning with her.
- He's right. I'm leaving today.
- Go up to him.
Bring him from the restroom.
I'll be waiting for you in front of the restroom door.
(Don't wait for me.)
We wouldn't leave so easily.
(Father-and-daughter jogging group that abducts)
That's my handful daughter.
Come out.
(Holding tightly)
It looks like she's visiting her uncle in a nursing home.
We've traveled a lot together,
but it's my first time walking with Hee Won this early.
- Really?
- Yes, we're on Season Five.
- I can't believe it.
- In the morning.
Are you walking right now because of me?
Of course. You traveled far to get here.
(Hee Won wanted to walk with Hye Young who traveled far.)
I feel very moved.
This is my first time.
(On the other hand)
(Flinching)
(Mi Ran also gets up.)
(Na Ra went to wash up.)
(Disheveled)
(She gets up and takes a look outside.)
(Rolling up the curtain)
(She takes a comfortable position.)
(Enjoying the view of the front yard in the morning)
(A fresh view of the outside)
(The sound of the waves in the lake near the front yard)
(Morning when you get good vibes)
(She also takes a quick walk around the house.)
(Na Ra)
(How are you doing?)
(Sorrowful)
I'm doing well.
(Smiling)
(The two of them got very close overnight.)
Gosh, where is my wallet?
(Did Na Ra's wallet disappear?)
My wallet.
Wait. Think, Jang Na Ra. My wallet.
I need to think. Where's my wallet?
- My wallet.
- Your wallet.
- What do I do?
- What does it look like?
It's a wallet with a long strap.
- Is it in your bag?
- I took out my bag.
(The wallet that Secretary Na Ra is attached to)
Did you take it outside?
Where could it be?
- Where could it be?
- I can't imagine where it is.
Wait.
(Thinking)
Did you eat something spicy?
Something spicy?
It's not here either.
(It's not inside the car.)
(In an emergency)
Let's see.
When I lift this, something will come out.
Did you look here?
Did you put it in my bag?
You have a bad habit of stealing.
(Getting even with her for last night)
I'm sorry.
(Where did the wallet go?)
(Exclaiming)
I'm sorry, Mi Ran.
I startled you, didn't I?
(My wallet)
(She finally found it.)
I didn't know the wallet was that big.
(Feeling good)
I hear them laughing already.
- Na Ra.
- Good morning.
Good morning. Hello.
- Did you sleep well?
- Yes.
Did you take a walk this morning?
- Did you run?
- I went jogging...
around the campsite.
I ran, sweated, and took a shower.
That's impressive.
(Time for a simple breakfast)
Did someone make her drink this morning?
This is you, Dong Il.
Are you mimicking me?
(Staggering)
In "Reply 1988."
- In "Reply 1988." - In "Reply 1988?"
He kicked the briquette.
(His extraordinary staggering diagonally)
- "He kicked the briquette." - He looks like Drunken Master.
This is how he came home.
- "He kicked the briquette." - She looks exactly like him.
Don't we look the same?
(Lowering his head)
Kicking the briquette while shouting.
(Here's a master of slapstick.)
That's hilarious.
(Daughters, why won't you listen to me?)
Do you remember his bluish green jacket?
(Accurate)
He had a bluish green jacket when coming from the bank.
(Laughing)
Gosh, my daughters.
Did Mi Ran also play your daughter?
She was the eldest daughter who ran away from home.
(The birth of a secret child)
What time is it?
- We should go. It's 9:20am.
- It's 9:20am.
Do we have to go?
Do we go like this?
- Let's hurry.
- Let's go.
(Where are they going today?)
(Beneath the silence...)
(lies a place filled with fervent breath.)
(Lake Kussharo)
(Lake Kussharo is located on the east side of Hokkaido.)
(Akan Mashu National Park)
(A massive volcanic zone where geothermal heat rises)
(Where the living land breathes)
(Created by volcanoes)
(Huge Caldera Lakes)
(Lake Akan, a spot for flying fish)
(Lake Mashu)
(And today's destination, Lake Kussharo)
(What they will encounter there)
(Primordial heat)
(Where you can feel the breath of Hokkaido's wilderness)
(We're heading to Lake Kussharo.)
Where we're going is close from here.
- It's nearby.
- I see.
The weather is very nice and cloudy.
- It's great.
- I agree.
The weather is perfect for traveling around.
It's difficult when the sun is out.
It's perfect.
- I think we're here.
- Yes, we're here.
We're here.
There's a place to eat.
- In front of the parking lot.
- Something sweet...
There's something over there.
(They find snack bars next to the parking lot.)
- We're here.
- Thank you.
We're here.
(They go straight to the shop like they're drawn to it.)
- Hotteok?
- It looks like hotteok.
It must be something like hotteok.
- What is this?
- It's potatoes.
Let's buy this.
(They decide to order two for now.)
(As soon as they order, )
(it's deep-fried in oil.)
I think it's just potatoes.
Is it uncooked potatoes?
She's just deep-frying the potatoes.
(Are they rice cakes or fried food? While they're getting cooked...)
I'll buy this.
Dong Il, this is what I'll buy.
(Hee Won got a new item.)
(All right)
You're not a child.
- But...
- Let it go. Or we'll have to pay.
- This is for Haidong Gumdo.
- Exactly.
(Haidong Gumdo)
Dong Il, you should buy this.
You should get a cane.
(This is for you.)
- It's the bear.
- My gosh.
The bear bell.
(This is...)
(This is a bear bell!)
(The bear bell the expedition leader carried around!)
(Fiddling with it)
(Dong Il wanted a bear bell.)
- The bear bell.
- It's a bear bell.
- Let's buy this.
- A bear bell.
- A bear bell?
(I must buy this!)
A bear bell.
Getting one bear bell would be nice.
I can wear it for the morning walks.
(He purchases a bear bell!)
(Ringing)
My goodness.
We'll need to hear that the whole day now.
- I can't help but shake it.
- We shouldn't have bought it.
(He can't stop shaking it.)
(He might end up dancing while chasing bears away.)
I just can't stay still.
(While Dong Il is dancing with the bear bell, )
(the snacks are ready!)
(Putting the sauce)
What is he applying?
- Is it soy sauce?
- It's dango sauce.
- Sweet soy sauce?
- Yes.
That's dango sauce?
(Gulping)
Thank you.
- It's hot.
- Okay.
It's hot.
Let's eat.
(Freshly fried, together with sweet sauce. How will it taste?)
- Eat when it's warm.
- When it's warm.
- I'll eat as I go.
- Sure.
- I'll share one with Hee Won.
- Okay.
You eat the left side. I'll eat the right side.
(The younger brother takes a bite first.)
How is it?
It's delicious.
- Is it?
- Yes.
You should eat more.
- It's delicious. You have it.
- Let's go.
(Mi Ran takes a bite too.)
- It's not ordinary potato.
- Hee Won.
This isn't normal potato.
They shaped it into this.
Exactly.
- They boiled it and shaped it.
- It's potato.
Here.
- It's like potato jeon.
- Yes.
(It tastes similar to Korean potato jeon!)
Thanks for the food.
There they are.
What is this? Flour?
Potato.
Potato and...
- Potato and...
- Glutinous rice powder?
(Glutinous rice powder?)
Potato and glutinous rice powder?
It doesn't taste like flour, right?
It's chewy.
Yes.
- It's salty and nice.
- Right?
(It's actually boiled potato deep-fried with starch.)
(Hokkaido's traditional snack, potato mochi)
The lake is beautiful.
- The lake is splendid.
- Dong Il.
Look at the lake.
The lake is so cool.
(They're amazed by the lake.)
Don't you think so?
(The large lake sparkles under the sunlight.)
Goodness.
It's like a painting.
I agree. It's like a painting.
The water.
Exactly.
- It's so pretty, Hee Won.
- Yes.
(A wide, panoramic view of the lake)
(But)
(Video by: Hokkaido Country Life)
(There's another lake behind the lake?)
(Actually, they're not two separate lakes.)
(A huge lake surrounds the whole of peninsula!)
According to the map, it's shaped like this,
and the water flows on each side.
This is like an island.
That's right.
(A gigantic lake, Lake Kussharo)
(It's 79km², which is bigger than 11,000 soccer fields!)
(You can feel the magnificence of Mother Nature.)
- It's nice, isn't it?
- It's so nice here.
It's better than I thought.
(Hye Young dips her foot in the lake.)
Are you showing off your water boots?
How's the water?
It isn't as cold as I thought.
This is a volcanic area, after all.
I think it's warm.
Dong Il, that's the outdoor bath.
- That's the outdoor bath?
- Yes.
- There are people in it.
- There are?
(What's happening?)
(Lake Kussharo was created from a volcanic eruption.)
(Underneath, the geothermal activity is still ongoing!)
(Hot spring water)
(When cold winter comes, )
(the temperature difference becomes apparent.)
(Frozen, not frozen)
(A fascinating lake where cold water and hot water coexist)
(There's something you can only experience here.)
(Enjoying the hot spring with the lake view)
(You can enjoy it in various parts of the lake!)
(In cold winter, swans come to rest too.)
(It's warm.)
It's so nice here.
The water is so clear too.
- Right?
- I can see the river bed.
(The water is so clear that it's as transparent as glass.)
(You can see the river bed of the deep water too!)
(It's even clearer on sunny days.)
Hee Won.
Let's take a picture.
Sure, come here. Let's take a picture.
(Let's take a picture in front of the nice scenery!)
Where we're at isn't important.
You're right.
(They capture their memories in the picturesque view.)
- The canoe is over there.
- Yes.
(A canoe?)
You used to paddle really well, didn't you?
I'm pretty good.
(Laughing)
It must be them.
(They'll soon start...)
(the Lake Kussharo canoe tour.)
- Hello.
I'm Ai, your guide,
and he's Kazuaki.
He's my husband.
They're married.
(They'll be joined by the guide couple.)
(They each wear a life vest.)
My chest feels pretty tight.
Is it? Okay.
- Done?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- That's enough.
Okay.
Today, we'll go to the inferno hot spring...
at the end of the peninsula and come back.
What?
(The inferno hot spring?)
"Inferno?"
(There's an inferno...)
(in this calm-looking lake?)
(Inferno)
(A hot and dangerous zone where geothermal energy erupts)
(Somewhere at the end of the peninsula, )
(which is a 3km round trip...)
Hee Won, look at that.
(There's an inferno!)
Look at that.
(A shocking place that surprised everyone)
(And...)
(a very special experience there!)
We came to this scary place fearlessly.
(The Lake Kussharo inferno tour, coming soon!)
(The members get in the canoes to the inferno.)
(Mrs. Cheetah is the first to get into it bravely.)
My goodness.
(He's already moaning even before starting.)
Let's go, canoe.
- Let's go.
- Go.
Go.
(To the inferno 1.5km away)
(The canoes set sail.)
One, two.
It's nice.
(So far, the lake is very peaceful that you can't imagine an inferno.)
It's so calm and nice, isn't it?
(As they paddle clumsily)
- Dong Il, it's so nice here.
- I know.
People canoe because it's peaceful.
It'll be nice if you canoe alone and play some music.
- Right?
- You'll die from the heat...
on sunny days.
- That's true.
- The weather is very nice today.
The weather helped.
(The slightly cloudy weather works in their favor today.)
The quiet sound of the paddle cutting through the water.
- Isn't it really nice?
- Yes.
The sound of it cutting through the water is so nice.
(The sound of the paddle in the water can be heard.)
This is so nice.
I wonder if Na Ra can adjust well...
in that team. I'm worried about her.
We've never had such active people...
on this show so far.
(We've never had such active people on this show so far.)
Let's go
(Let's go)
- Let's go - Let's go
- Let's go boating - Let's go boating
(She adjusted perfectly.)
My goodness.
I'm so embarrassed.
Can you guys keep quiet?
I'm sorry.
Na Ra
(She doesn't intend to stop.)
Please sing
What's that again?
(The melody is familiar to Na Ra too.)
It's DJ DOC's song.
- I like tteokbokki so much - So much
- So I went - So I went
- To a tteokbokki restaurant - To a tteokbokki restaurant
- In Sindang-dong - In Sindang-dong
- One plate of tteokbokki - You even know that part.
(Are you a singer? Your score is 99.)
(Hye Young's song request, "Cocktail Love" by Marronnier)
(Na Ra's song request, "One and a Half" by Two Two)
(Even ALLDAY PROJECT)
TARZZAN is cute.
I wanted to travel silently. They're annoying.
It's embarrassing.
(With the guide, who assimilated with them)
- Good job.
- Sorry?
- Okay. Good job. I got it.
- Are there three of you?
- Yes.
No.
- Really?
- Yes. We have seven more.
- You...
- Just keep paddling.
(We have seven more. Just keep paddling.)
- Shall we go?
- Yes.
- We'll paddle at top speed.
- Top speed? Hey.
- Start! One, two.
- One, two.
Her voice is getting closer.
It's getting closer.
- One, two.
- See that?
(Going berserk)
(Team Mi Ran moves ahead at frightening speed.)
- We can break the record.
- One, two.
One, two.
(They paddle hard too, caught in the heat of the moment.)
- Let's go!
- One, two.
Why did they come here?
- They're here to train.
- Are they here to train?
I should've secretly tied our canoe to theirs.
- Then we...
- That sounds good.
(What a mature thought.)
(Confused)
(Surprised)
(The attack of tree branches)
(They're forced to do abs workout.)
My stomach hurts.
It looks like dinosaurs live here, like "Jurassic Park."
(It looks like they're in a jungle.)
Why is there yellow moss?
It's interesting.
(Unfamiliar yellow moss is found between rocks.)
- Don't you smell sulfur?
- Is that it?
(Observing)
- I think it does smell of sulfur.
- I think so.
(Yellow?)
(Smells of sulfur?)
- Is this hot spring water?
- It is. Bubbles.
He says bubbles rise here.
- You can see bubbles rising.
- Where?
- My gosh.
- Can you see the bubbles?
(Hot bubbles rise from the cold lake bed.)
(They're popping on the surface of the water.)
Mi Ran, right next to you.
(It's hard to believe what they're seeing.)
It's scary here.
- It's no joke.
- It's scary.
- One, two.
- It's smoking.
Look over there. It's smoking.
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
I suddenly see smoke.
(As soon as they turn the corner, they come to face...)
It looks like it's on fire.
(Steam that shoots up from the ground.)
Hee Won, look at that.
(Surrounded by the thick smoke)
- What's that?
- My gosh.
That's impressive.
(They arrive at the inferno hot spring.)
(Hee Won gets out first.)
(Slightly scared)
(Dong Il gets out carefully too.)
Isn't it hot?
My gosh.
Look at the smoke. Here, too.
(They look around.)
(The cliff colored with yellow sulfur)
We came to a scary place so fearlessly.
(This place feels like it's a different world.)
- Look at the hot water rising.
- It's coming up.
My gosh, something is bubbling up.
You're right. They're rising from the holes.
(Hot spring water shoots up from underneath their feet.)
This is amazing.
(While they're focused on the pool, )
(at one side...)
(The guides are looking for something.)
The shovel.
- Where's the shovel?
- The shovel.
Mr. Kim.
(Why did he suddenly take out a shovel?)
What?
(Dig the ground over there using this shovel.)
Over there.
- Let's go, everyone.
- Let's go together.
(They all follow the guide.)
- The water is lukewarm.
- Really?
- My gosh.
- It's warm.
- Yes.
- I want to sit down here for a bit.
(The warm lake water envelopes her ankles.)
I want to sit down here. Can I dip my butt in?
- It's so warm.
- It's warm.
(Across the lake, which is fascinatingly warm)
It's so warm.
- Dig here?
- Yes.
- Here.
- Yes. Here?
(He hands over the shovel to confused Mi Ran.)
(Throwing)
(Unlike the sounds she makes, she's rather slow.)
Look at her.
(The spectators are thrilled.)
Oh, dear. What to do?
It's hot.
There it is.
It's 100°C.
It's 100°C?
That's the hottest water you can get.
- The water is boiling.
- It's 100°C.
(Really?)
- It's hot.
- The water temperatures of here...
and here are different.
(The water of the lake is below 30°C.)
Is it hot there?
Here and here are different.
(They face the mystery of the earth.)
(Power up)
(A boiling pool of hot spring water)
Okay.
- You add this here?
- Like this?
(What are they putting in the hot spring water?)
Put the whole thing in.
(Eggs?)
That's fine.
(A special experience only at the inferno hot spring)
(Hot spring water which springs up from where you dug)
(You boil eggs using it.)
(Known as inferno eggs)
It's eight minutes for soft-boiled eggs...
and 12 minutes for hard-boiled eggs.
- Who wants soft-boiled eggs?
- Me.
- All of us.
- All of you?
(Will they become nice soft-boiled eggs?)
(At that moment)
Look at that.
(Mi Ran spots something.)
Gosh, look at the water boiling.
It's like lava. It's overflowing.
(The inferno's hot spring water)
Let's take a look at it.
(They carefully approach it.)
Nature is a mysterious thing.
Mi Ran, look at it.
(Blazing inferno hot spring water)
That's scary.
(I need to take a photo of it.)
It's like the volcano is erupting.
- Send me the video, will you?
- I will.
- That's water boiling, isn't it?
- It is.
Let's touch it.
(Laughing)
It's upset. This is so fun.
This is so fun.
What is it?
- It's time.
- Is it done?
- It's done. Let's go.
- It's done.
The eggs turned dark.
(Sulfur-rich hot spring water turned the eggshells dark.)
I wonder how they would taste.
- Goodness.
- Gosh.
Mi Ran!
(It's a huge accident.)
- It's okay. 3, 2, 1.
- In 3, 2, 1.
(Light)
- It was slippery.
- Because you're wearing boots.
- It's okay.
- I'll assist you.
I'm okay. It's wet.
Gosh.
(Why do things like this always happen to Mi Ran?)
(She's got the heaven-sent sense of humor.)
(Feeling moist, she keeps walking.)
What's this now?
- Bento?
- So pretty.
It's a handmade snack gift.
(On the simple table laid out by the lake, )
(there are colorful drinks...)
(and cute snacks made of Hokkaido ingredients.)
She made them from scratch.
I know.
- You made these from scratch?
- Yes.
(Shall we enjoy the inferno tea time together?)
- Thank you.
(They start with today's highlight, the inferno egg.)
It's hot.
(They carefully peel the darkened eggshells.)
(Dong Il tries it first.)
It's soft-cooked.
Look. Doesn't it look like jelly? Look at this, Hee Won.
(Inside the egg white, the yellow yolk is like jelly.)
(Na Ra takes a bite too.)
(It's so good that she wants to cry.)
What's the expression Chef Anh Sung Jae uses?
- About the doneness.
- "Evenly cooked."
It's evenly cooked.
It's silky smooth.
- I know.
- For me, the smoked eggs...
are too dry.
It's nice and soft.
Really soft.
It's good.
(Eggs from inferno are the best!)
Try it. It's really good.
(He puts a cookie into Hye Young's mouth.)
It's so good, isn't it?
- Try it.
- It's moist and soft.
Right.
- Moist and soft.
Cookie?
There's this, too. Gluten-free one.
I see. What's the point of eating a cookie then?
(I don't want to go free.)
- Why would I...
- It's really nutty.
(The tea time gives them the joy of choosing cookies.)
It's too hot to sit here.
- It's hot, isn't it?
- It is.
(Hee Won's seat is too hot.)
You should lie on your back.
You have ondol in Korea, right?
- Ondol.
- Yes.
No wonder it was so nice and hot when I lied down.
- It was nice and hot.
- It's very...
(She uses the log as a pillow and lies down.)
Let's see. What should I eat next?
It's so nice...
that this place isn't packed with people.
(I should enjoy it more.)
(It's another way Mi Ran enjoys the inferno.)
She's sleeping.
She's not sleeping. She's drying her pants.
(She's drying her pants using the inferno ondol.)
Okay.
Let's go.
(The fun inferno hot spring tour ends.)
Would I ever come back? Unless I deliberately travel here,
- I probably wouldn't.
- We need to say bye.
Bye.
(They say farewell.)
Take care, guys.
Let's hurry and get going.
Only then we can go to the volcano.
Are we going to the volcano next?
(After the hot spring, they're going to the volcano?)
- The inferno volcano sounds fun.
- Goodness.
(In a 25-minute drive from Lake Kussharo...)
(Lake Kussharo to Volcano)
I don't want to hear it.
Look there. There's smoke.
That's the volcano.
(Behind the lush trees, )
(you can see the white smoke in the distance.)
Steam is billowing out of the mountain.
(There’s a subtle sense of yet another inferno...)
Goodness.
(Amazed)
(This place makes you lift your camera in awe.)
(The earth’s heartbeat that never stops)
(The sulfur volcano)
(As if the earth was breathing, nonstop, massive plumes of steam!)
It could boil 100 trays of eggs at a time.
When you place the eggs, they will boil instantly,
and by the time they reach the foot, they will be done.
(Just imagining it is fun enough.)
It will be like a boiled egg vending machine.
A vending machine.
It's a vending machine that makes boiled eggs for 100 people.
When you say, "One boiled egg, please,"
someone roll down raw eggs from the top.
(Will Hye Young's imagination come to life?)
They will be done by the time they reach the bottom.
What are you being all chatty about?
I imagined something funny.
(The fascinating Mother Nature makes you imaginative.)
Something coming out of the volcano...
- blah, blah.
- So funny.
But in reality, it's a dangerous place.
- You're right.
- Right? It can erupt any time.
Is it a dormant volcano? Or is it an active volcano?
It must be an active one to be producing the steam.
(Is it a dormant volcano or an active volcano?)
They said it wasn't an active volcano.
I don't think it's a dormant volcano.
(It's spurting out the steam endlessly.)
(The spring water is boiling hot.)
(It's an active volcano...)
(that's very much active.)
- Right.
- The steam...
- spurts out.
- And it makes that hissing sound.
They are walking all the way there.
(It turns out...)
(there are many people on the volcano.)
(They are observing from right next to the steam.)
(Sulfur volcano is a volcano that usually discharges steam.)
(So you can follow the permitted sightseeing track...)
(and observe it closely.)
(It's a special experience to walk on the active volcano.)
(Take me a good photo.)
How can nature be like this?
Why is the floor white?
- Perhaps it's sulfur?
- Is that sulfur powder?
Wouldn't it be because of sulfur?
(Why is there white powder piled up on the floor in summer?)
(He smells it first.)
- Does it smell?
- It doesn't smell of anything.
Let's ask AI.
We're at the mountain where a sulfur hot spring runs.
Why is there white powder on the floor?
(She somehow managed to ask the question.)
(Searching)
It's sand with high sulfur content.
When it's exposed to the oxygen in the air,
it turns into sulfur crystals,
and they are deposited on the floor as yellow or white powder.
(Yellow powder contains sulfur, )
(and white powder contains silica and sulfate.)
Right. But it's like that only here. Look at that mountain.
(Unlike this mountain, barren and covered with mineral dust...)
Compare the two mountains. It's like inferno and paradise.
The two mountains look completely different.
(The mountain without the steam is nice and green.)
(It's a fascinating terrain with two types of mountains.)
Compare the two mountains. It's like inferno and paradise.
This mountain, that mountain.
- Flowers bloom.
- Bloom.
- Run!
- I knew she would do that.
(Running)
(Laughing)
(Come, Hye Young.)
(Wait for me, Mi Ran!)
Mi Ran!
(She's like a zebra...)
(racing on a white snow field.)
(She jumps lightly like sulfur smoke.)
Because the ground is white,
- people stand out more.
- I know.
Because of the color of their clothes.
Okay.
Let's go.
(They leave the heat of Mother Nature behind.)
(It's time for Hye Young to leave.)
Goodness, I don't want to leave.
(What did you say?)
(A bang filled with bittersweet vibes)
(Affectionate)
(Sighing)
(Peeking)
I feel sad.
(Posing)
(The three ladies take photos of each other.)
(Giggling)
I love it.
Wait.
(And there's a father.)
(Standing afar)
Mr. Nakamura!
("Yes" is one of a few Japanese words he knows.)
(Very...)
(Laughing)
I am otaku.
(Okane)
(I said otaku, not okane.)
Look here. Please look here.
(I will take a photo of you all.)
I love the composition.
(I love the composition.)
I love how Na Ra is standing away from them.
(Laughing)
Wait. I am going to use the timer.
(She puts the camera upright to take a family photo.)
You can fix it upright.
Hee Won.
(Posing awkwardly)
This is nice.
(Thanks to Hye Young, they take a lovely photo.)
That was nice.
Now... Take care, Hye Young.
Thank you.
- Bye.
- Please come back.
(They show the father-daughter chemistry until the end.)
Before I go,
I will give you...
(She takes things out of it.)
this padded jacket.
(Last night at the camp site...)
It's freezing.
(It's freezing.)
It's freezing here.
Do you want this?
Do you want to try it on?
No, I am too lazy to take off my jacket.
- Really?
- Wear it on top.
You should wear this today.
- Thank you.
- It's too cold.
(Hye Young lent her the extra vest she brought.)
(Happy)
I love it.
(Thanks to Hye Young, Na Ra stayed warm today.)
(I love it.)
I will give you this.
- Give her the vest then.
- I...
I will take the vest.
I will make sure to clean it...
and return it.
- Thank you so much.
- She will return it.
- It will keep you warm.
- Na Ra.
If you go out of reach, it will be yours.
Na Ra shouldn't catch a cold.
I am so grateful.
(They are sweet until the end.)
- I had a lot of fun.
- You traveled so far.
- I...
- Thank you for the jacket too.
- Thank you.
- Take care.
(And...)
Thank you for coming.
Yes.
Stay happy.
Let's get together sometime.
- Bye.
- I will get going then.
Peace.
She's happy to go alone.
Hye Young,
we parked in the same parking lot though.
Okay.
Let's go.
We are going to the same parking lot, so don't go yet.
- Okay.
- She's...
Maybe someone else might come this evening?
- Someone is coming.
- She must be on the way.
Following the route I took yesterday.
(Worried)
That thought suddenly pops up in my head.
How can I be seeing Jang Na Ra?
(How can I be seeing Jang Na Ra?)
She was my idol.
She was my wannabe.
What am I going to do in front of her?
I don't know.
(When Na Ra's biggest fan arrived in Hokkaido, )
Dot, dot, dot.
(Na Ra, the idol...)
(of Na Ra's biggest fan is...)
(What?)
Look at the sky on the left side!
Look at that sky.
It's like a croissant.
It's like a croissant that's put upright.
- It looks like a croissant.
- That looks like a croissant?
It looks like waves to me.
As soon as I saw it, I thought of a croissant.
Are you craving for a croissant right now?
No, it's the layers that reminded me of a croissant.
It's like a croissant put upright.
(She's just a bread lover now.)
(How will Na Ra's biggest fan and the bread lover meet?)
(Sun Bin is here.)
(Sun Bin is the self-claimed No. 1 fan of Jang Na Ra.)
(She spends the day with her favorite artist.)
(You are a good person.)
(Thank you, Good Person.)
(Pressing with love)
(She's got too much love.)
(Gasping)
(Acting cute)
(Na Ra gets infected with Sun Bin's energy.)
(Spirit!)
(Thanks to Sun Bin, Na Ra becomes full of energy.)
(Jang Na Ra is unleashed.)
(What happened to her overnight?)
(You call pork barbecue a light brunch?)
(Mi Ran, the Eating Expert, joins her in the kitchen.)
(Dong Il and Mi Ran work together.)
(Their collaboration produces many dishes.)
(Give a shout!)
Is she eating it all or tasting it?
(Just eat.)
(Eating Expert Mi Ran...)
(versus Chef Sung)
(Their eventful match)
(And...)
(Hokkaido's biggest wild forest)
(Shiretoko)
(They enter the pristine primeval forest.)
(The deer.)
(They witness the pristine primeval forest.)
(And...)
(another face of Mother Nature)
(The wild zone at night...)
(makes even Dong Il terrified.)
(What happened to the family?)
(Sung Dong Il)
(Kim Hee Won, Jang Na Ra)
(House on Wheels: Beyond the Ocean)