It's a case. It's a case. It's a case. It's a case. It's a case. It's a case. It's a case. It's a case. It's a case.
The case is closed.
closed?
Yes.
But I still
I still don't understand.
I don't understand.
Don't think about it.
If you can figure everything out,
Life is so hard.
Sister Sanxi.
Did I think too much?
I dare not say.
But investigating a case
sometimes depends on luck.
Newspaper! Newspaper!
Extra edition!
The case of Guangren Hospital has been solved.
The real murderer is...
a sick man.
Give me a report.
OK. Take it.
Who is it?
I'm not sure.
It's quite urgent.
Mr. Lin.
Gu Zhang is not the murderer.
You mean Gu Zhang was in the ballroom that day?
Nurse Zhang.
Hello. Hello.
I heard that
you were fired.
I didn't expect
we meet again here.
I didn't see you in the hospital.
Your body...
is really nice.
Your wife and kid are waiting for you.
Was he there all night?
He came right after the opening.
After work,
He's been pestering me for a long time.
Why did you
Why did you get away with it?
Even if he's not a kind person,
he shouldn't be wronged.
You are finally here.
Gu Zhang didn't commit suicide.
Zhang Xiaojuan came to the police station and told me
on the night Director Cao was killed,
Gu Zhang was in the ballroom all night.
So he had no time to kill.
he wouldn't have committed suicide to escape punishment.
How did he die?
I got it.
Look.
Through the color rendition test,
has changed colors.
It means Gu Zhang
in his body.
What... What is phypaytal?
Phylbaccio.
An anesthetic.
People fall into a coma if they use too much.
and lose the ability to resist.
You mean
Gu Zhang was poisoned?
Yes.
We've been neglecting something.
Why did Gu Zhang smile?
Because Gu Zhang was poisoned,
because he was poisoned.
Then he was hung on a rope.
That's why he smiled.
If that's the case,
there's only one person
is one person.
Now, Sun Yuyao is the prime suspect.
And she's the only one
only she knows.
We're investigating Gu Zhang.
And the person who can use phypaccio
must be very familiar with medicine.
But what's her motive?
Dr. Sun has left.
After the French board found out about Gu Zhang,
he was very angry.
Dr. Sun
and her nurses
all left.
Can you show us
Dr. Sun's information?
You do it.
All the information about Dr. Sun
are all here.
Take your time.
Thank you.
I found that Sun Yuyao's patient
is nearly doubled to the other doctors.
Look at this.
She was diagnosed with tuberculosis when she was admitted.
He was rescued twice due to cardiac arrest.
But tuberculosis won't cause cardiac arrest.
There must be something wrong.
Sun Yuyao
We neglected her.
We couldn't find her.
and moved away.
Bao,
Send someone to find out
who rented a house recently.
Okay.
This doesn't make sense.
He graduated from a prestigious school.
She has excellent medical skills.
The death rate of her patients
is twice as much as other doctors.
And I recently found that
she's very popular among the patients.
I also called the Health Department to verify it.
Her education background is fine.
It's not a coincidence that the death rate is so high.
It should be her.
She intentionally caused the death of the patient.
That's a big deal.
Why didn't the hospital call the police?
There must be no evidence.
The hospital doesn't dare to tell anyone
Besides,
who would want to get involved
such a matter of life and death?
How can you explain that she is so popular?
Is there such a possibility?
Sun Yuyao.
She deliberately caused a few critical scenes.
and then turn the tide.
to win the praise of the patient and family.
And the mistake in the process
which led to a high death rate.
Yes.
That makes sense.
She did this
to gain recognition.
Sun Yuyao
doesn't take human lives seriously.
Bao.
Any news from Sun Yuyao?
I sent someone
Bao.
Who told you to come here?
Go away.
Get out.
Bao.
Didn't you ask me to find Sun Yuyao?
She's missing.
Of course.
I don't need you to look for him.
No.
Someone from China reported
saying Sun Yuyao is missing.
Sir.
Sun Yuyao is your daughter.
She works at Huayang Hospital.
She hasn't
for a long time.
I went to her.
But...
She moved.
People in the hospital
don't know where she went.
Are you sure?
Huayang Hospital?
How long hasn't she been home?
Over a year.
This is my daughter.
Please...
find her for me.
Dr. Sun.
She's long gone.
Are you talking about Dr. Sun?
Dr. Sun?
She's not Dr. Sun.
This
Dr. Sun.
Who is she?
Her name is Chen Yulan.
She used to be a nurse here.
If Chen Yulan pretended to be Sun Yuyao,
where is the real Sun Yuyao?
The director of Huayang Hospital told us
a few years ago,
Chen Yulan and Sun Yuyao
went through a medical accident together.
After this medical accident,
Chen Yulan was fired.
But Sun Yuyao went missing.
It's very likely that Sun Yuyao has been killed.
Chen Yulan killed Sun Yuyao
and took her place.
I took her place for a year.
but no one found it.
The household registration in the Chinese border and the Concession doesn't match.
So Chen Yulan probably hid in the concession
because of this.
Yes.
Chen Yulan used Sun Yuyao's identity
into Guangren Hospital.
And she's not a doctor.
So her patients
is extremely high.
Chen Yulan knows
a medical accident occurred in general hospitals.
will not reveal the truth
because of his reputation.
That's why
she is so fearless.
No wonder.
When she gave you the injection last time,
I felt something was wrong.
When the doctor injected it,
the angle of the injection is 15 to 30 degrees.
This will make the needle
to slide into the vein.
And nurses
do more skin injection and muscle injection.
So we're used to the higher angles.
Chen Yulan
most afraid
is to let others know
his real identity.
And Director Cao
found out her real identity.
That's why she was killed.
Baby,
Any news from you?
Yes.
But there is no news about Chen Yulan renting a house.
I've expanded the area to the whole concession.
Did she run away?
Everyone,
Let's welcome our new colleague
to welcome our new colleague.
Dr Sun.
Welcome.
Hello, everyone.
Dr. Sun graduated from a famous school
and worked in Guangren Hospital in French Concession.
Please
learn from her.
From now on,
Nice to meet you, Dr. Sun.
Don't mention it.
We should help each other in the future.
Dr. Sun, go ahead.
Alright.
Stop staring at me.
Reboot as soon as the case is closed.
Isn't this slapping?
Uncle.
I have a word for you.
A mistake can be changed.
A good deed is a good deed.
Lin Lan.
It’s OK if you don’t want to lose face.
But those French masters are not good enough.
If we don't issue a warrant,
it'll be too late if Chen Yulan runs away.
Yes.
You're on the wanted list.
If she hides,
you won't be able to find her.
Enough.
The net has been spilled.
Let's see if we can catch the fish.
The public concession.
Yi'an Hospital.
There's a new doctor named Sun.
Thank you, Inspector Li.
I'll treat you to a drink later.
Why me?
Atropin 0.5.
Hurry!
Okay. Okay.
Wait.
Forensic physician Qin Xin from Central Police Station of the French Concession.
I'm in charge of the patient.
But the patient is very dangerous now.
I'll take responsibility if anything happens.
Let's go.
Her heart is beating. Her heart is beating so fast.
What did the patient have before?
She vomited and vomited.
I have a stomachache.
500 hydrogen.
10 hydrocyanide injection.
Okay.
Long time no see.
Chen Yulan.
Tell me.
What did you inject to the patients?
Nothing.
It's cyanide, right?
You can use the cyanide
causing obstruction in the patient's room.
Heart rate is dropping.
Then use Atropine.
accelerate the room transmission.
But do you know
there's a conflict in medicine?
The Atropine could deteriorate
causing ventricular fibrillation.
How is he?
He's awake.
I've handed it over to the doctor over there.
Tell me.
Why did you do that?
Why did you pretend to be Sun Yuyao?
Since you know it,
let me tell you.
That newcomer.
The Chen Yulan two years ago
was just a little nurse that no one cared about.
Instead of calling a nurse,
Hurry up What are you waiting for Use your hands
It's better to call a maid.
Chen, come here.
Coming.
Change the pants and bed sheets.
All the dirty and tiring work
They only left it to me.
It was their fault.
Why should I take the responsibility?
Give me a Quinetine.
I want Kuening,
not Quinetin.
You just told me that it's Quinetin.
I mean Kuening.
Did you hear it wrong?
If you use them wrongly,
you'll be in trouble.
You know that, right?
I didn't make a mistake.
Dr. Son is talking about Quinetin.
You're still quibbling.
This month,
Ten silver dollars deducted.
I don't know why they did this to me.
Just because I'm new here?
What about the medical accidents after that?
What does it have to do with you?
I did nothing wrong.
I'm just their scapegoat.