This Guixiaomeng Powder
made me forget everything.
These kidnappers are really crafty.
Drink it.
What is this?
Just drink it.
It will refresh your mind.
What is this taste?
Good medicine tastes bitter.
It really is bitter.
But it's quite refreshing.
Bao,
go check for me
where this Xiaomeng Powder is sold.
Got it.
Is it possible
that the Ghost Mother Gang
has started committing crimes again?
Those male kidnappers back then
managed to escape unscathed
because they must have been fully prepared.
There is no reason for them
to use the same method now.
I know.
It's to provoke the Police Station.
How did I not realize he was so smart before?
I'll call you Smarty Bean from now on.
How about that?
Smarty Bean?
Yes.
That's a pretty good name.
Right?
You really push your luck.
Provoking the Police Station?
How is that possible?
Are they itching to get caught?
I guess,
someone wants to be a copycat
and use the Ghost Mother Gang
to divert our attention.
That woman is here again.
This is knockout powder.
It's also called Xiaomeng Powder.
Be careful.
This medicine,
where did you find it?
I found this back then
where Shengnan went missing.
My daughter was probably knocked out by it and taken away.
Why didn't you tell us this
when you came here
this morning?
I've been here plenty of times.
In all these years,
no one was willing to listen to me.
At first, I thought you were just brushing me off, too.
But now I trust you.
You really want to help me.
It's not just that.
Look.
These are the materials
I've collected over the years.
These are newspaper reports
regarding our case.
I took all the relevant info
and made a summary.
And their relationship chart.
It's all here.
You found all this by yourself?
And these photos.
These are the other abducted children,
photos from the scene,
and other information
provided by their families.
I took photos of everything.
It's all here.
All these years,
have you been investigating alone?
Where is your husband?
He can't keep searching.
He's stopped looking.
We really understand you.
All these years,
searching for your child alone,
must have been hard.
But...
I'm just saying, what if...
What if Shengnan...
How is that possible?
They told me
that my child is dead.
But I didn't see the body.
So I have to keep looking.
Don't you think?
For so many years,
I've been having the same dream.
In that dream,
I see a train passing in front of me,
blowing a long whistle,
Whoo.
Clickety-clack.
I was right behind that train,
running desperately,
chasing it.
I ran with all my might,
chasing as hard as I could.
I kept thinking,
why hasn't this train reached the end?
When will it ever stop?
I chased until I woke up.
I got dressed and went out.
I'm out on the streets of Shanghai.
I go from street to street,
searching every single one.
I have a special ability now.
How many children are on this street,
boys or girls,
what they're wearing,
how tall they are...
I take one look and never forget.
I've turned myself into a living map.
How many rats are on this street?
I know exactly.
I keep thinking,
I have to keep chasing.
Shengnan is still waiting for me.
When Shengnan was little, at bedtime,
I used to hold her,
comfort her,
and sing her lullabies.
Now there's no one to comfort her.
She must be so scared.
Inspector Lin.
Inspector Qin.
We will definitely find Shengnan.
She is waiting for us.
No matter the outcome,
we will do our very best.
Thank you.
Didn't you suspect it was a copycat crime?
Why are you looking into Ghost Mother again?
None of the children have been found.
How could they close the case?
Besides,
just because the criminals were executed,
does that mean we stop searching?
That makes sense.
Even if it is a copycat crime,
how did they know?
The blood at the scene back then was pigeon blood.
This person is likely linked to the case from back then.
It's very likely these children are still alive.
Of the missing children linked to the Ghost Mother,
not a single one has been found.
They were likely sold out of town.
The men who committed the crime back then all fled.
If we can find the whereabouts of just one child,
we might find more clues.
Someone provided a lead.
You were here all night.
So you were the one who set up Gu Dachuan
and Zeng Xiaoyi?
Yes.
At the time, Gu Dachuan's first wife
had been dead for two years.
He was raising Gu Yitong on his own.
Zeng Xiaoyi
was also a single mother raising a son.
I saw that they were both
honest people.
So I helped bring them together.
So it was a second marriage for both.
Is there anything you want to tell us?
I thought
the couple,
working hard at their wonton shop,
would have a nice life.
I didn't expect
Gu Dachuan's son
to be simple-minded.
Because of his condition,
Gu Dachuan went everywhere seeking a cure.
All the money
was spent on his youngest son.
Zeng Xiaoyi seems to
dislike him.
I also heard that one time...
Come look! Sugar figures!
Buy one for the kid.
I want a piggy sugar figure.
What's wrong,
kid?
Buy a sugar figure.
I want a piggy sugar figure.
Didn't we buy one yesterday?
Not today. Let's go.
I want a piggy sugar figure!
Behave, Tongtong.
Not today. Let's go.
I want a piggy sugar figure! Tongtong!
I want a piggy sugar figure! Get up.
Behave.
You're not my mother!
I want my mother!
Of course I am. Behave.
You're not my mother! I want my mother!
I'll buy you one tomorrow, okay?
Let's go.
I want my mother!
Gu Yitong!
Is this your child?
He is. He's my child.
You're not my mother!
Tongtong, get up.
Make way. You're not my mother!
It's a misunderstanding.
This is my child.
This is my wife.
It's a misunderstanding.
Move along, everyone.
He really is my child.
Move along.
It's a misunderstanding.
Father, I want a piggy sugar figure.
Tongtong, be good.
I'll buy it for you.
Sir,
one piggy sugar figure, please.
Could it be that Zeng Xiaoyi dislikes Gu Yitong?
So she intentionally imitated
the Ghost Mother Group's method to abandon him.
But she was shopping with the child at the time.
She didn't have time to commit the crime.
We can't rule out that she conspired with someone in advance.
Dou Mingcong,
go ask the neighbors again.
We'll go to the wonton shop.
Detectives.
Please, have a seat.
Do you have news about Tongtong?
Yijun,
want to go out and play with me?
Go ahead.
But don't go too far.
Inspector Lin,
please take a seat.
Is there any news about Tongtong?
We haven't found Tongtong yet.
But the blood at the scene,
after we tested it,
turned out to be pigeon blood.
Tongtong should still be alive.
I heard
that you two are a remarried couple.
My wife passed away four years ago.
We were introduced by a matchmaker.
In other remarried families,
the children usually seem to mind,
but you get along very well.
When we got married,
Tongtong was too young to remember.
Yijun
has always been well-behaved.
Mrs. Gu.
I heard a while ago,
Tongtong threw a tantrum at the market,
and you were mistaken for a kidnapper.
No,
Inspector Lin.
That's not the case at all.
Tongtong.
Since Tongtong was little,
he has had a minor brain issue.
His temper is bad.
But he's not stupid.
He just doesn't understand people sometimes.
Have you taken him to a doctor?
We did.
We saw every doctor in Shanghai.
They said it was oxygen deprivation in the womb.
There's no cure.
Does Tongtong cause trouble for you often?
After all,
Tongtong is different from other kids.
Inspector Lin,
what do these questions
have to do with finding Tongtong?
We're just trying to understand the situation.
Mrs. Gu,
on the day Tongtong went missing,
is there anything else
you haven't told us?
You don't suspect
that I abandoned Tongtong, do you?
Although Tongtong isn't my biological son,
I've always treated him like my own.
How could I do something like that?
Mrs. Gu, you've misunderstood.
We're just trying to understand the situation.
Right now,
the more we know,
the better our chances of finding Tongtong.
I'll contact you if I have any news.
Inspector Lin.
I'm counting on you.
How did it go?
What did the kid say?
Nothing much.
Just that Zeng Xiaoyi treats Gu Yitong well.
Usually, whatever Gu Yitong wants,
Zeng Xiaoyi gets it for him.
One time, Gu Yitong threw a fit for cake.
Gu Dachuan beat him,
but Zeng Xiaoyi snuck out and bought it for him.
What did you find out?
I asked several neighbors,
and they all said the family of four
got along very well.
Xiao...
Xiao... Xiaomengsan.
I f-found out.
Ever since the Ghost Mother Sect was destroyed,
no one in the black market dares to sell this drug.
But,
after my brothers kept investigating,
we found a general store that sells it.
But,
without connections,
they won't sell.
What would you two
like to have?
Borrowing some wilderness.
Which door do you open?
Borrowing the wilderness of Kunlun.
He Xiangtian.
That's not the line.
Liu Du Zhu.
Is it drift or not?
Heavy piece.
Need to pass fire to see the bone.
It really is good stuff.
Central Police Station! Don't move!
Easy. Easy now.
How do you know so much jargon?
When seeking treatment for my grandmother,
I visited every pharmacy.
Detectives.
I picked it up after going so often.
I'm running a small business here.
It won't happen again.
You're selling Xiaomengsan.
You call that a small business?
Tell us.
How many people have you harmed?
None, really.
I only started selling it recently.
Only one person bought it.
Tell the truth.
Really, only one person bought it.
About seven days ago,
a mute came by.
What would you like to buy?
What did he write?
He said,
he wanted to do business with me.
He knew I didn't have any children.
He said he could sell me a boy
as long as I could provide
Xiao... Xiaomeng Powder.
What does he look like?
He's short.
But...
he wore a mask, so I couldn't see his face.
But I noticed
a scar near his right little finger.
It was quite long.
How are you making the trade?
He said to meet
at midnight seven days later,
at the ruined temple in the south.
Wh-Which is today.