Who made
such a mess?
It's early morning.
What are you doing here?
Someone's dead!
Over here.
What happened?
It looks like someone is dead.
Rigor mortis has spread throughout the body.
Livor mortis is fixed.
Time of death was over eight hours ago.
Before death,
the victim was likely struck on the head with a blunt object.
I checked.
There are no footprints or other traces.
It's probably because of the rain.
It washed everything away.
It'll be hard to find witnesses.
Who would go out in such heavy rain?
Look at this pit.
The body must have been dug out from here.
It's all spoiled food.
That's strange.
Why did he bury these things?
Director Cao was such a good man.
Why would anyone kill him?
Take the body back first.
The crowd is getting bigger.
The deceased is named Cao Mingli,
the director of Guangren Hospital.
The body...
was found this morning during garbage collection
by a rickshaw puller.
The victim has been dead for over eight hours.
There is a lot of soil on the clothes,
likely left when he was dug out
from the ground.
Except for the head,
no other external injuries were found.
We can conclude
death was caused by a blunt force blow to the head,
resulting in a skull fracture.
Only the head suffered severe trauma.
That implies
the victim was likely attacked
while defenseless.
Has the primary crime scene been found?
Not yet.
I asked around.
He was last seen
at 4:00 PM.
But when he got off work,
no one noticed.
I feel like
the primary crime scene must be near the hospital.
Otherwise, the killer would have no reason
to go through all the trouble
of moving the body to the hospital's back alley.
I feel the same way.
Then who dug him out?
The most important thing now
is to find the primary crime scene.
This is a laboratory.
Up ahead is the nurse station.
There's also a pharmacy here.
This is Director Cao's office.
And the room next to it
is the archives.
All patient records are stored here.
On the second floor,
there are wards
and a dispensing room.
Do you go in and out of these rooms
at night?
Basically everywhere.
Except the director's office.
Bao.
Lin Lan sent us to find the primary crime scene.
What are we doing here?
It rained so hard last night.
If the crime scene was outside,
it would've been washed away.
Where would we look?
Think about it.
The killer buried the body
because he didn't want it found.
Now that it's dug up,
he must be panicking.
He definitely wants to know
how our investigation is going.
He'll likely return to the crime scene.
What if we catch the killer right here?
That's Bao for you.
You haven't lost your touch.
Bao.
Stop running!
Freeze!
Lin Lan.
Don't you think this spot is unusually clean?
It looks like it's been wiped.
There's another spot here.
Only these two places have been wiped.
This must be the primary crime scene.
All the ornaments in this room are symmetrical,
except for this candlestick. One is missing.
The murderer likely used this candlestick
to kill the victim.
Then cleaned up the blood
and buried the body in the backyard.
Don't run!
Stop!
She's not from our hospital.
She often rummages through the trash cans in the back alley.
I've run into her many times.
Yeah, I've run into her many times too.
She doesn't have any wounds.
Where did this blood come from?
Then these clothes probably aren't hers.
She's not even from this hospital.
Where did she come from?
Let go.
What are you doing?
Trying to grab my gun?
Take her back to the police station first.
Based on the evidence collected so far,
it's basically confirmed that
the killer struck in Director Cao's office.
After the murder,
they disguised Director Cao's body as a patient,
transported it out of the hospital,
and buried it in the back alley.
I can't believe after all this investigation,
the one digging up the body
turned out to be a madwoman.
The patient gown she's wearing
must have been stripped off Director Cao.
To commit murder in the hospital
and move the body unnoticed,
the killer must be someone from the hospital.
So the killer is either a doctor or a nurse.
But we've taken statements from the doctors and nurses.
They all have alibis.
Unless someone is lying.
Could it be a patient?
Or a patient's family member?
Whether it's a doctor, a patient, or a nurse,
there has to be a motive for murder.
We need to check first
if Director Cao
held a grudge against anyone.
That crazy woman you brought back,
just let her go if there's no issue.
What's the deal with keeping her in my office?
She keeps looking at me
and laughing "hehehe".
It gives me goosebumps.
Why don't we send her back to the hospital?
Stop her from digging through trash.
Who knows what disease she might catch.
Forget about the hospital.
It's like being in prison.
Besides,
she's used to being free out there.
Who knows what'll happen if she goes to the hospital.
But we can't just ignore her.
Do you have any other ideas?
Look,
she's actually quite cooperative.
Ciyang Hall is a legitimate sanatorium.
It's safer than being outside.
I found it.
I have news.
Last month,
at Guangren Hospital,
a wealthy merchant from Suzhou died during treatment.
The merchant's wife
made a huge scene.
The director
spent a lot of money to hush it up.
You mean
the family is seeking revenge?
That's not what I mean.
I asked around at the hospital.
They said the director was furious
and ended up firing a nurse.
Zhang Xiaojuan, right?
Central Police Station.
Lin Lan.
You were doing well as a nurse.
Why become a taxi dancer?
What's wrong with being a taxi dancer?
Just making a living.
Are taxi dancers inferior?
That's not what I meant.
I just wanted to ask
why you left the hospital.
What mistake did you actually make?
I didn't make any mistake.
I'm just a scapegoat.
I just followed Dr. Sun's prescription
and gave the patient 0.1 of digitalis tincture.
I didn't do anything else.
He is the president of the Suzhou Chamber of Commerce.
If his family
wants to make a big fuss out of this,
I can kiss my job as the dean goodbye.
Anyway, regarding this matter,
someone must step up
to take the blame.
Ten.
You mean
it was Dr. Sun's fault?
I didn't say that.
Dr. Sun has saved many people.
I don't think it was her fault either.
So it was an accident.
Since it was an accident,
and Director Cao
made you a scapegoat,
don't you hate him?
I do.
But what's the use?
He is the director.
I am just a nurse.
Did you ever think about revenge?
What do you mean?
Between 4:00 PM yesterday
and midnight,
where were you?
Officer,
if you have something to say,
just say it.
Director Cao is dead.
Did you know that?
Director Cao is dead?
Wait.
You don't suspect me, do you?
I wouldn't go so far as to
kill for a job like that.
You just need to answer our questions.
Whether it was you,
we will find out.
I got up at 4:00 PM yesterday.
I washed up, had noodles downstairs,
went home to get ready,
and then went to work.
I didn't get off until 1:00 AM.
If you don't believe me, Sir,
feel free to ask around.
But Director Cao didn't offend anyone else.
I still think
the killer must be someone from the hospital.
Otherwise, how could no one have noticed?
The killer murdering Director Cao
doesn't necessarily mean
they had a grudge against him.
Is it possible
he knew a secret he shouldn't have?
Or maybe
he had something on the killer?
Time to eat,
detectives.
Put your work aside for now.
Let's eat first.
Look at this.
Don't rush.
I'll go to the hospital again tomorrow.
I want to see what kind of monsters are there.
Is that enough?
That's enough.
Here.
Okay.
Go to the hospital tomorrow.
Spread the word
that the killer has been caught.
Then proceed as planned.
What plan?
Bao.
These ribs smell amazing.
Where did you buy this?
What kind of question is that?
This is my secret recipe.
You can't buy it anywhere.
Here.
Eat it while it's hot.
Come on.
Officers.
Officers,
you're back.
Yes.
Regarding President Cao's case,
is there any progress?
You guessed it.
We came here today
mainly to inform everyone.
The murderer of Dean Cao
has been captured.
Really?
That's great news.
He's finally caught.
That's wonderful.
Sir.
Who is the killer?
Regarding Dean Cao,
we express our deep regrets.
Dean Cao's killer
was actually a robber.
What?
How could it be a robber?
Dean Cao was such a good man.
How could a robber do this?
Exactly.
What a shame.
What kind of coffee is this?
It tastes awful.
You need to work on your skills.
How is Bao's medicine coming along?
That is what you're drinking.
Why didn't you say so sooner?
I mixed it using Bao's ratio.
Miss Lin,
what exactly did you eat?
Why is it so severe?
She just drank a cup of overnight coffee.
It's nothing serious.
You'll be fine after resting for a couple of days.
If you don't want to stay in the hospital,
you can go home.
Forensic Expert Qin.
Look,
our department is so busy.
Why don't you go back and help?
The doctors here are looking after me anyway.
You don't need to worry.
True.
You seem to be fine.
I'll go back to work then.
Go ahead.
Get some rest.
Dr. Sun,
just let me be hospitalized.
I just finished investigating a case,
and I just want to rest well.
It's not easy for you guys.
Solving a case
has worn you out like this.
But regarding Director Cao,
it's all thanks to you.
I never expected
that Director Cao was killed by robbers.
These days,
it's not safe out there.
When you go out,
you need to be more careful.
How was that kidnapper caught?
Dr. Sun,
are you also interested in solving cases?
Not really.
Ever since Director Cao was killed,
everyone in the hospital has been on edge.
It's fine.
Don't worry too much.
Cases like Director Cao's are isolated.
Besides, the killer has been caught.
Just relax.
Everything here is good.
It just costs money.
I've only been here a few days,
and I've already emptied my pockets.
Life is more important than money.
If you lose your life,
who's going to spend the money?
That's true.
It's a good thing Dr. Sun treated me.
Dr. Sun treated you too?
You too?
Then you're quite lucky.
What do you mean?
She's very skilled.
Yes, she is.
You want to make an appointment with her?
But you need connections.
If it weren't for Dr. Sun,
I would have died twice already.
Let me tell you,
both times I fell ill,
it was in the middle of the night.
Thank goodness,
Dr. Sun was there.
Dr. Sun is here.
Hello, Dr. Sun.
Miss Lin,
why are you here?
I've been alone in the ward lately.
It's too boring,
so I wanted to come out for some fresh air.
In your condition, you need rest.
You shouldn't be wandering around.
If you're really bored,
I'll have the nurse bring you some magazines.
No need.
I'll go back now.
Thank you, Dr. Sun.
Remember to check the temperature of the patient in Bed 3.
Okay.
Mr. Gu,
the Commander sent us to extend his regards.