Please enjoy.
Inspectors.
Mr. Zhou,
we're here today because
we have some questions for you.
That gilded Guan Yu statue
you commissioned,
where was it made?
After it was finished, was it sent to your home first
before being sent to Dehua Bank?
I had this Guan Yu statue
made in the French Concession
at Baogong Workshop.
Their process
is famously rigorous.
From start to finish,
I went to check on it five times.
Yesterday,
I saw with my own eyes
that old craftsman
put the statue into the glass case.
Because the bank
and Baogong Workshop are both in the French Concession,
so I had the workshop arrange for a porter
to carry the statue
directly to the bank today.
We will investigate Baogong Workshop.
But since the deceased's body
replaced your gift,
we are worried the killer
might be targeting you.
We'd like to inspect your home
to see if there's anything unusual.
Is that convenient for you?
Of course.
This room was cleaned quite thoroughly.
It looks like bloodstains.
I'll go see if I can help.
Please wait.
We have some questions
and need your cooperation.
Where is your wife?
No. What does this
have to do with my wife?
Mr. Zhou.
Last night,
between 10:30 and 11:30,
where were you?
Wait, Inspector Lin.
What do you mean?
Are you suspecting me?
Don't misunderstand.
It's just routine procedure.
Please cooperate.
Last night,
I was auditing accounts at Fenghui Bank
until 9:00 p.m.
I was a bit hungry,
so I went to a noodle shop in the Concession.
I had a bowl of noodles
and a drink.
Which noodle shop?
Kangren Noodle Shop.
Around what time did you leave?
And where did you go after that?
I stayed for quite a while.
I stayed until about midnight
before I left.
I went straight home after leaving.
Exactly the same.
It seems Comprador Zhou lied.
Not only did the deceased visit his home,
but it's also very likely
that his home is the primary crime scene.
The most important thing for us now
is to figure out
exactly who
would go to such great lengths to expose the body.
Sorry.
We're not open yet today.
Why don't you wait a moment?
We came here today
to ask you some questions.
We're from the Central Police Station.
Do you want to order Lo mein?
I can deliver it.
Shisan.
Why are you dawdling?
Ladies.
I'm sorry.
We have limited ingredients.
Everything for today is reserved.
Please come back another day.
Boss.
We are not here for noodles today.
We're mainly here to see you
to ask a few questions.
Detectives.
Let's talk inside.
Mr. Zhang,
what time does our shop close every day?
As soon as the noodles are sold out,
we close.
There is no
fixed time.
Uncle,
you're here.
Here I am, Shisan.
They were caught fresh
early this morning.
Comprador Zhou Shiqing.
Do you know him?
Yes, I do.
He is a regular here.
He loves our signature dish,
Crab Roe Noodles.
Did Comprador Zhou come here
the night before last?
Yes, he did.
At that time,
he sat right by the entrance,
at the table on the right.
He ordered a bowl of noodles,
and I think he had some wine.
Do you remember what time
he arrived that day?
It must have been
around 9:30 p.m.
We have a routine here.
Every night at nine,
we prepare the stock for the next day.
At that time,
I had just put the ingredients in the pot
when he arrived.
Do you remember
when he left?
As for when he left,
I really can't recall.
Detectives,
I just remembered something.
I don't know if it helps.
Go ahead.
The night before last,
I was busy in the front yard.
I felt so tired,
so I wanted to go to the inner room to rest for a bit.
At that time, the radio
was playing a song called "Drizzle."
After listening, I didn't dare rest long,
so I went back to work.
I noticed at that time,
Comprador Zhou was no longer there.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Bao Workshop is a time-honored brand.
We've never had any mishaps.
About this matter,
it really has nothing to do with us.
Before,
where was that Guan Gong statue?
Come.
Look at this room.
This room,
is where we usually store our finished products.
It is so strange.
The statue of Lord Guan just disappeared.
When was the last time
you inspected the goods that night?
Seven in the evening.
We closed up after the inspection
and left a worker to watch the room.
At seven the night before last,
were you here the whole time?
Yes, I was.
I didn't move an inch?
Not an inch.
According to the rules of Baogong Workshop,
smoking isn't allowed in this room, is it?
You smell heavily of smoke.
Did you go out for a smoke that night?
I'm asking you!
Let me tell you something. Whatever you say,
if it affects our investigation,
you will be held accountable too. Do you understand?
I am terribly sorry.
I had a craving for a smoke that night,
so I went out for a little while.
What time did you go out?
How long were you gone?
It was around 2:00 a.m.
I was out for 20 minutes.
Is this back door always open?
It's open when moving timber.
Usually, it's bolted shut.
Smarty.
Smarty, come here.
Smarty, come. Come in.
Why is the Guan Gong statue here?
We thought it was lost.
This is the one Comprador Zhou ordered.
Yes, this is it.
Take a good look.
That's right.
You mean,
this person,
while the Baogong Workshop worker was out for a smoke,
sneaked in through the front door,
then opened the back door
and moved the body inside.
That Guan Gong statue is half a man's height.
Swapping the body would take time.
It's possible that when the worker returned,
the person was still there,
so he had to escape through that small window,
and tore his clothes.
I think we can go to various tailor shops
and ask around.
We should be able to find the source of this fabric.
Smarty-pants,
that name suits you more and more.
I found the program list.
Li Minghui's "Drizzle"
aired at 10:00 PM the night before last.
The song is four minutes long.
Zhang Shisan said
he went to the front courtyard after the song ended,
which was around 10:04 PM.
By then, Comprador Zhou
had already left.
He stayed until about 12:00 AM,
and went straight home after leaving.
Then he had plenty of time to commit the crime.
Where is Comprador Zhou?
My master drove out.
Where did he go?
How would I know?
He went out alone.
He was in a hurry.
If he wants to run,
the nearest exit from the city
is the south gate of the French Concession.
Looks like we're a step too late.
Time of death was within the last two hours.
Judging by the wound,
it was caused by a blunt instrument.
Judging by the length, it's a woman's.
And it's permed.
The blood residue found at Comprador Zhou's home
matches the victim.
The thread found
matches the sutures on the victim's abdomen.
We now have reason to suspect
that Comprador Zhou killed the victim.
However, right now...
the murderer you suspect is dead.
Could the person who killed Comprador Zhou
be the one who dug up the female body
to expose him?
It's possible.
But if his goal
was to expose Comprador Zhou's murder
and bring him to justice,
he was about to succeed.
Why kill Comprador Zhou beforehand?
We should first figure out
why Comprador Zhou was in a rush to drive to the wilderness.
We checked Comprador Zhou's car.
The engine was off and it was locked.
The keys were in his pocket.
So it's very likely
he arranged to meet someone there.
And they probably knew each other.
If the killer
just wanted to kill Comprador Zhou,
there was no need to cause such a big commotion.
This case isn't simple.
Everyone be careful.
I have news.
I sent someone to check Sanhe Hotel.
The landlady said
there really was such a female tenant.
Her name is He Xiaolian.
But in the archives,
I couldn't find any information on her.
So I sent my men to check
every girls' school in Shanghai.
But none of the schools had her.
That girl
doesn't talk much.
She keeps to herself.
Also,
she basically spends the whole day
sleeping.
She only goes out at night.
And she always dresses like a student.
So you mean
she's not a student at all?
Definitely not.
Look at her. She doesn't look like a student.
She doesn't even have a pen.
Besides,
who has classes in the middle of the night?
If you ask me,
she's probably a prostitute.
Landlady.
Thanks a lot.
Here's the thing.
We can't have outsiders watching while we investigate.
Why is there a fishy smell in here?
Opium.
I know why
the killer took the victim's stomach.
It changed color.
The victim's intestinal tissue
changed color with Froehde's reagent
due to the alkaloids in opium.
And look at this color.
The concentration is high.
That means
before He Xiaolian died,
she consumed a large amount of opium.
If He Xiaolian had smoked the opium,
the alkaloids would be distributed in the blood,
liver,
lungs,
and other organs.
But they wouldn't appear in the intestines.
Especially in such large quantities.
It must be the intestinal lining
being soaked in opium.
You mean
body packing?
The victim
likely put opium in fish intestines,
swallowed them,
and used a string in her mouth
to pull the drugs out.
So the cause of death
was likely the fish intestines rupturing inside,
causing opium poisoning.
After the drugs leaked,
they passed through the respiratory and digestive tracts
and entered the body.
The victim would suffer respiratory failure
and a drop in body temperature.
Finally, due to paralysis of the respiratory center,
she died of suffocation.
So,
He Xiaolian was likely using this method
to transport drugs.
And we can't rule out the possibility of prostitution.
When He Xiaolian went to Comprador Zhou's house that night,
could she have been conducting such a transaction?
It's very likely.
Her stomach was removed
to hide the fact
that she was using her body to smuggle drugs.
But the body was already buried.
That means
the killer thought the body was well hidden.
So why remove the stomach?
What if the killer removed the stomach
just to retrieve
the remaining drugs inside the fish intestines?
The killer is truly heartless.
The French Concession hasn't explicitly banned the opium trade.
But it is explicitly banned in the Chinese territory.
He Xiaolian definitely has more buyers
than just Comprador Zhou.
And if they were transporting drugs in the French Concession,
there would be no need for such trouble.
The buyers might all be in the Chinese territory.
But we don't have jurisdiction in the Chinese territory.
And even if we found those buyers,
they wouldn't admit it.
Have you seen He Xiaolian?
I have never seen this lady.
You haven't seen Comprador Zhou bring her home?
No.
Between 10:00 and 11:30 the night before last,
did you not see Comprador Zhou?
I was in my own room.
The Master said before he left that day
that he would bring his keys.
Does Comprador Zhou have any
close female associates?
Especially in the last day or two.
Last year,
the Master met a dancer
from the Grand Shanghai Dance Hall.
Her name is Haitang.
A few times,
while the Madam was back in her hometown,
the Master went to see Haitang.
I remember now.
The night before last,
Miss Haitang came to see the Master.