Reinforcements from "Song of the Brocade Moon"
Welcome
Hello everyone, I'm Zhou Ye
Hello everyone, I'm Cheng Lei
I play Xiao Jue in the drama
He suddenly blushed
Sorry
Yes, I did (blush)
But about blushing
I don't remember who it was
It was you
It was me
But I blush easily, yes
Yes, I get red easily
Right
Let's invite the two leads
to help us recreate this classic scene
I've heard the moonlight at Jin Jiao Cui Wang Mountain
is the best in the world
I have to take a good look today
The best in the world
Not necessarily
Looks like the world's best moon is jealous
The world's best moon is yours
Him?
Is there a video to play?
Jump without music
One million isn't quite enough for this
No way
Put your arms around each other's shoulders
How do you clap?
Thank you
Want to see Zhou Ye do it without hands
Feed Cheng Lei a donut
You can do the piggy heart gesture
What's with this microphone
We're pretty in sync.
What heart is left?
There's probably no heart left.
That's awesome.
Not a single heart is whole.
What's this outfit for?
It's for us to wear together, bro.
To wear together.
A two-person outfit.
We have to take off our clothes to put this on, right? Wear it as a jacket.
This is so funny.
Do you want to take yours off?
I'll just leave it on.
This side.
It's inside out.
You put your hand in first.
It's so hot.
Will it be too tight?
The two of us are wearing this.
Yeah, it will.
Everyone wears it like this.
Do you think the two of us can even fit in this?
Is it because you're too fat?
Maybe.
It's good, let's sit.
Okay.
It's suffocating.
You can talk.
But you can't move.
Can we eat now?
Hurry up and eat.
Can we eat?
How do you eat this?
Stop.
You...
Stop peeling it.
How do you eat it without peeling?
I don't know.
It's too big.
Such a big one.
You eat a little.
Here you go.
How are the forces?
Your division of tasks.
Zhou Ye, you can say something too.
You feed him, he feeds you.
He's even peeling this.
He's still peeling.
You really did peel it.
He's just peeling the skin.
So particular.
People before just swallowed it directly.
You can use your mouth.
He can't use his mouth either.
He's been working hard to
hold onto that cake with his mouth.
Alright, I won't make it hard for you anymore.
You can chew for a bit.
Don't peel the skin.
But this is actually pretty tasty.
This one is too fat.
Why don't you eat it instead?
Has my face already...
Has my face already gotten messy?
It's fine.
Just a bit of chocolate on your mouth.
Do you need to put on some lipstick?
It's really delicious.
This one?
Let me break it for you.
Do you want to break it or bite it?
I'll bite it, don't break it.
Half for you, half for me.
I broke it.
Go ahead and break it.
I'll eat the smaller one.
It's fine, I just wiped my hands.
It's gone.
I have to say, you peeled it pretty neatly.
Right?
Let me do it.
Don't rush.
I'll do it.
Is it really that urgent?
I just want to help you.
You're so anxious, here.
It won't wash off.
Is dragon fruit really that hard to wash off?
Yeah.
It's just like dye.
What, haven't you ever
used dragon fruit to paint before?
You can try it when you get home.
Did you guess it?
I think it has something to do with a chicken.
Isn't it a pigeon?
A pigeon?
There's a bee.
Why is there a bee too?
A hummingbird.
Correct answer.
Whether we can guess it or not, let's raise the sign first.
This looks like both a pig and a chicken.
Yeah, it should be related to a pig.
Roast suckling pig.
Nezha with three heads and six arms.
Or just three heads and six arms.
Is it right? Did we get it?
We raised it.
Yezi said.
You say it, I don't know.
Nezha with three heads and six arms.
Just give an answer.
Can you do it or not?
What chicken are you talking about?
The chick pecks at rice.
There's no rice.
That thing on top of it.
You said "rise at the crow of a rooster."
Rise at the crow of a rooster.
Is it really this hot?
It's so hot.
Where's the breeze?
Take it off.
It's see-through.
Can't you take it off?
Is it not okay to take it off?
It's not like I haven't seen it before.
You don't have abs anymore, right?
I do.
Where are your abs?
Here, or here?
I'm actually a bit slimmer than I was back then.
Really.
Who do you think it is?
I think it's the second one, Huang Zihongfan.
Who?
Huang Zihongfan.
Huang Zi.
I think Yang Chaoyue is different.
No.
I think Huang Zi is different.
He's always watching Dige.
So now he's...
...trying to draw attention to someone else.
Yeah.
I'll trust you this time.
Your intuition.
You can't get the answer by asking just one person.
You have to compare.
You ask.
Go ahead and ask.
I'll ask.
Weren't you going to ask Huang Zi?
You suspect Huang Zi.
It's just between those two.
We can only pick one of them.
If Dige is different from them,
Dige alone
could lead everyone to dance like this.
Then let's stick with our first-round choice.
It's not him, right? It is.
I'm talking about Huangzi.
I think Chaoyue is more likely.
I think it's Chaoyue too.
Mainly because Chaoyue is just too confusing.
She was the same last round.
And the same this round.
I really think it's Chaoyue.
Okay.
Alright.
Please play the music.
This one.
It's too obvious.
It's the same song, right?
Yeah.
This.
Spin around twice.
Why aren't you spinning with us?
There is.
There was a spin.
Spinning goes like this.
With a kick.
Okay, the music's over.
Alright.
Cheng Lei is lost in his own musical world.
Why did we dance for so long?
So tired.
No, Lei and I were on the same beat.
We're the same.
The two of us kept doing this.
Yeah.
Alright.
Please play the music.
It can't be you, right?
Cheng Lei
Step over, step over
Every house is decorated with lanterns and streamers
So when I pulled you
Were you already confused?
Were you confused when I pulled you?
When we were dancing to this
Then I felt it
I felt it
Yeah
Your last stage performance
Didn't you do this move too?
Yeah
This one
Did you sing this song last time?
Danced to this song
No
Yes
My world has become wonderful and hard to describe
I can't do it, I'm really "bad" at this
I'm someone who never works out
Still better than Chaoyue, right?
I can't do it
Go for it, General!
Come on
Stand firm
This is too skinny
No, I really can't do it
How about you pull instead?
It's so hard, really hard
Are you still working out these days?
Start
Cheng Lei
My shoe came off
Cheng Lei really respects the game.
They're really fast over here.
One piece.
That's enough.
And how do they eat so cleanly?
Look at your side of the floor.
Three
Two
One
Time's up
Look at how much I'm sweating
But you really have lost weight
You're slimmer than before
And your base makeup today
isn't as pale as when filming "Jinyue Ruge"
The base makeup for "Jinyue Ruge"
was as pale as mine is now
How can period costumes and modern outfits be the same
It was deathly pale
As white as a city wall
It scared me to death
Not like you, going bare-faced
No, I didn't
I put on makeup
I did makeup for three hours
I meant the male makeup
Filming with male makeup is so much easier
I want to do it again
Was there a day
when you didn't wear any makeup at all
When you were wearing a mask
Yeah
No
There was a day you had a bun and didn't wear makeup either
A bun?
When you had a bun, you didn't wear makeup either
One day
Anyway, the makeup was super light
Stop talking
The winning team is
Team Ruge