Disguise is a required course for little "demons".
The next game
Remember to hide yourself well.
Each team will send out three members.
According to their own prompts,
they will have ten seconds to draw.
Among them, there is
an undercover with a different prompt.
The undercover needs to guess their own identity
and stay hidden.
After drawing, everyone votes.
Identify the undercover.
Members who successfully identify the undercover get one point.
If the undercover isn't voted out in the first round,
they also get one point.
The team with the highest total score wins.
Alright, the ten-second drawing time starts now.
They stopped drawing after just two seconds.
Finished before even starting.
Okay.
Time's up.
Please remove the screens.
Protect your own prompt.
Someone even wrote words.
How about we kick out the one who wrote words?
He gave up and just wrote two words.
Give me a reasonable explanation.
Right.
After so many rounds of this,
this guessing game,
I feel like it's basically impossible to guess now.
Can't guess it anymore.
I've started to doubt my own intelligence
all over again.
Then it can't be Kan or me.
You're totally fine, sis.
At first glance, you're definitely fine.
Jiarui, I've got your approval again.
Thank you, Jiarui.
My most reliable supporter.
This time, I'll just say it here.
Xueqin is totally fine.
Alright.
Seriously.
We haven't even done anything and it's already fine.
These three
These three representatives are here again.
Just like a homeroom teacher.
This is the best I can draw.
Got it, very abstract.
It's a special form.
Everyone can see it too.
Di, come here.
I don't dare to draw it too detailed.
But I did draw its eyes.
Does it look like this?
Zhisheng.
Zhisheng is even more than this—
Zhisheng's eyelashes aren't that long.
They're a bit thinner too.
You can feel it, these eyes—
You need to describe this.
Describe it.
Yeah.
That's it.
It can be approached with this attitude.
It can use this attitude.
Right.
Bro, this of yours—
When you’re not doing anything with yours—
It’s the same kind of thing.
Yeah, so if you talk like this—
It’s very easy to get the conversation off track.
I didn’t get it off track.
But I think there’s just one thing—
You haven’t said anything yet, you—
Alright.
Say your part—what’s that thing of yours?
What’s this of yours?
What is that thing of yours?
Tian Jiarui’s is weird too.
Do you get this?
My drawing skills are so good.
This looks very similar.
No problem.
This is a work by Van Gogh.
There's nothing wrong with yours at all.
This is really, really similar.
Isn't it?
Yes.
It really captures the expression.
Right?
Yes, it's lifelike.
This and yours—what did you just say?
This is an attitude.
Attitude.
Alright, then that's not right.
Master predictor Tian Jiarui is online.
That's not right.
Xue'er said
I split it into two parts.
This one might have nine.
And it might also have this.
Yours is a centipede.
Centipede.
Xue'er, does this have something to do with nine?
Yes, it might have nine of these.
Got it.
That makes sense now.
Let's see what Haohao drew.
I need to combine mine with the previous direction.
As in, who is my direction pointing to?
Smart
Right?
He's very smart.
It's you, bro.
It's you.
I feel like we don't even need to discuss this round.
Vote.
We don't even need to discuss this round.
Come on.
This is how our game works.
Whenever Tian Jiarui feels
he has the answer,
that's when we start voting.
I've had it for a while.
Alright, three
two
one
Please vote.
They all voted for me.
No problem.
No.
Duanduan, you can vote for yourself too.
Voting for yourself also gives you points.
Really?
His eyes lit up.
Come on, vote for three.
Okay.
That's true.
Alright, in this round of the game,
we have our first unanimous vote.
The undercover is still in the game.
What?
Bro, your attitude—
has totally confused all of us.
Yeah, I just wanted to cheer everyone up.
Make things a bit happier.
Bro, we are happy, that's true.
But we lost points again.
We analyzed three rounds, and all three were wrong.
But Di-ge's drawing is also a bit vague.
He only drew one eye.
Because I was scared.
Because it has different forms, you know?
But after I saw yours,
I knew I was on the same team as you.
Is that enough?
It's you, Di-ge.
Di-ge.
Di-ge drew a different form.
So enchanting.
The two of us—
We're not the same form as him.
What other forms could there be? Standing or lying down?
It's you.
But bro, what did you draw?
Now I'm starting to suspect it's you.
Who, me?
Yeah.
Let me add a couple of strokes for you.
If you don't add a couple of strokes,
I really can't tell what it is.
The drawing style is just like mine.
This style is way too similar.
Can you tell?
Now it looks even more like it.
Is this—
Can you tell what it is?
Is it an elephant?
It's a ribbonfish.
Ribbonfish.
Your drawing is actually quite vivid.
Is that a Sharingan?
Is that supposed to be a cataract in the eye?
I told you, it's the eye.
Color this part a bit darker.
I think, Di-ge,
Could it be Xue'er?
Why did Jiu Tiao draw it out?
What do you all think?
You make a good point.
Right?
Because it can't be.
Normally, that shouldn't be there.
You're right, bro.
Jiarui, your passion is back!
It's back in you, Jiarui.
I have the answer now.
You can analyze it again, Jiarui.
Why? Why did she draw nine things?
Why?
Normally speaking,
Seeing these characters, drawing it like this is correct.
Right.
But why draw nine things?
Maybe it's nine something-something.
Without nine, it can't become that thing.
No.
Not all of these things
are nine of these.
No, not at all. I was just describing these characters.
Actually, I think her nine is fine.
Come on, Jiarui.
Have you made up your mind?
I'm really conflicted.
I think I'll vote for Dige.
Voting for me won't help.
Vote for Dige.
It would be wrong to vote for me.
I'm really torn.
That's just how Dige is.
He still hasn't drawn anything else.
He just keeps drawing on his face.
That's really vivid.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Seriously, nothing wrong at all.
But compared to us,
he's not in the same form.
Di probably doesn't need to ask anymore.
He already knows exactly what they are.
I think they must be foxes.
Or maybe fox spirits or something like that.
Yeah.
Then, when I took a look,
I saw Li Xueqin standing there and I said,
I said, she's standing.
So I must be lying down.
I'm different from her.
It's very ambiguous.
So I drew an eye.
Thank you, Duanduan.
You're welcome.
Thank you so much.
No problem.
This round was really intense for us.
But in this game with surprisingly low scores,
both sides ended up tied.
Let's bring out the props.
Little "demons,"
it's time to show off your charm.
Every time you write this word for me,
it makes me seem so unserious.
I really have no idea what I'm supposed to do.
Use your expressive faces
to act out an exciting story.
Within three minutes,
team members will go in order of their positions
and take turns in a relay of making faces and guessing.
You can only use facial expressions and sound effects.
Describe the words on the board
The teammate who acted out returns to the answer area
The next teammate immediately takes over to compete
Each correct answer earns one point
Each team has only two chances to skip a word
Within the allotted time
The team that guesses more words correctly wins
Next
Let's welcome the Smile Team
I'll act it out first
I'll say how many characters first
Come on, Dige
We did terribly
We really messed up today
Dige
This is your area of expertise
This is your domain
Dige
You guess over twenty times every month, come on
Three, two, one
Game start
How many characters
Two characters
Fireworks
Impressive
You guys got this one so fast
Four characters
Vomiting and diarrhea
No
What are you then?
I just have a sore throat
She hasn't even started acting yet
She even...
After this, it's a sore throat
Or is it part of the acting?
No
Sore throat
When did the acting start?
Or have we already started?
Boiling water
The boiling water is too hot
Kip-up
Can I pass?
Yes
Is there sound?
Can you imagine a volcanic eruption?
Two characters
Eating noodles
The second character in "eating noodles" is correct
Noodles
So hot
Instant noodles
The instant noodles part was also poorly acted
Five characters
Four characters
Making faces
What's this?
A smile over the shoulder
In the mouth
Mouth ulcer
The first character
Mouth corners lifted
Right
The first character is correct
Fish (as in fishing)
That's right, fish
Mouth
Mouth fish
Caught a "Qiaozui" (upturned mouth fish)
Come quickly, run over
Yours looks like you caught a "Wai zui" (crooked mouth fish)
Three characters
Correct
Eat
Right, that's the first one.
Yes, the second one is
Sizzle, sizzle, sizzle
Eat hotpot
That's right.
Sizzling
Two words
Eat
Bite
Gnaw
Deserves a beating
Creepy
Who guessed "creepy"?
Eat melon
That's right.
Here, you spit out the seeds.
Just now, Di was acting
Creepy
Four words
Panic-stricken
Ding
Elevator
Elevator falling
It really is the elevator falling
Almost right
Elevator descending
Falling
Okay, next person
Three words
Zapped
What got zapped?
Electric mosquito swatter
What?
Huh?
Electric mosquito swatter
Hurry up
It's your turn
Three words
Diarrhea
No
Understand?
Flush the toilet
That's the right idea
Restroom
Sewer
Blow up the toilet
What is this thing?
Unclog
Unclog the toilet
Come back
I'll unclog it
The last word is "unclog the toilet"
You acted out something in the middle
So what is this thing?
This "WC"
He wrote
Toilet
So in our first round
The Laughing Team got seven answers right
Now let's switch to the Bowing Team
Three words
Jasmine tea
Three characters
They probably don't have this where they live
They don't pass by there
There's no such thing where they live
This is rare in Hengdian
Insecticide
Coughing up blood
It must be some kind of flower, right?
A character, Spitting Blood Guy
The one from Stephen Chow
Spitting Blood Guy
Yes, I played Spitting Blood Guy
I really don't know this one
Pass
Jasmine tea
Li tea
Water truck
Okay, next one
Four characters
Suffocated
No one called out
How could there be pain?
I'll just act out the last character
Then
Whoosh
Shooting an arrow
Hit by an arrow
Four characters
Frost Archer
So hard
A volley of arrows
Pierced by ten thousand arrows
Borrowing arrows with straw boats
Impressive, impressive.
So smart.
Quick.
I've never come across this one.
Pass.
Just pass directly.
Try it first.
Pass, pass, pass.
Then there's no chance left.
There's only one chance to pass.
Two words.
Hand.
Can't use hands.
Very scared.
My child.
Keyun.
Even though you didn't use your hands,
I feel like you said the word though.
My child.
To be honest,
I even think our team is kind of cheating.
Even I can't accept it.
This style of our team.
My child.
Could anyone handle that just now?
Who could handle that?
Expression.
Four words.
Eat.
Spit.
Eat grapes.
Spit out grape skins.
You guys are so fast.
This way, we don't use our hands.
Three words.
So hard.
Everything is just a clatter.
Going to the bathroom.
Does it have something to do with water?
Playing mahjong.
You could even guess that?
How did you figure that out?
Xue'er, hurry up and go.
Let her guess quickly.
She's really good.
Xue'er is truly the master of this round.
Come on.
Two words.
Cheer.
Clubbing.
Impressive, impressive.
We're being too sneaky.
I really can't take it anymore.
Okay.
In this round of the winking game,
Team Zheyao has won again.