Once upon a time,
Magistrate Mei and County Princess Wu Zhen went out for a stroll.
Suddenly, they came across a strange building.
Behind its doors was another world.
This modern world and our Chang’an
are truly worlds apart.
We must protect our family heirlooms
and keep them safe.
Alright.
Okay.
Hello, everyone!
Welcome to our Smile Shop.
I’m your lovely little tour guide.
Follow my lead.
Come on!
Who is this? Does anyone recognize him?
He looks familiar.
Yes.
He’s our laughter power machine here.
Yang Di.
You’re Yang Di!
He’s really famous.
We’ll probably see him at every major attraction.
That’s right.
Exactly.
But this is the real deal here.
Let’s take a photo then.
Sure.
One, two, three!
Why did he move?
He moved!
He really is perpetual!
After all, he’s the original.
Right?
Come on, let’s go this way.
No way, that’s too beautiful!
So pretty!
Such good looks!
This is the hardest spot to book here.
Zhu Xudan
This is our "Rui" the Game Genius King.
Tian Jiarui
What is he famous for?
Master of Reverse Reasoning
Anyone who takes a photo with him
can gain a clever mind
and this wise head.
Really?
Yes.
What's going on?
He really needs it.
He needs it a lot.
Wisdom.
That's right.
Who is here?
Full of energy just like me,
Brother Hao.
Then I want to be the first to take a photo with him.
Because I'm just like him.
Strong as an ox.
Alright, this is our final stop.
So handsome.
Impossible.
Still so handsome.
This is Li Dan, our veteran staff member at the Happy Store.
Boss Dan.
So handsome.
Let’s have our exhibits come over too.
Yang Di is really...
Where is he?
Just let him stay right here.
True Fruit "Smile at First Sight".
What’s wrong?
What happened?
No power.
We didn’t pay the electricity bill.
What happened?
Where’s my stuff?
Where’s my magic wand?
My things...
Where’s my millstone?
Your beauty is still here.
Of course, it was stolen.
There’s a thief.
Do you want to find your things?
Yes.
No, because I don’t want it anymore.
It’s pretty heavy.
In your two teams,
there’s one thief in each.
They worked together and took everything.
Who?
The thief.
It’s you, isn’t it, Yang Di?
Who?
At midnight,
the thieves’ identities will be revealed.
Alright, everyone.
Wait until midnight.
Let’s catch these two together.
The ones who were just acting cute among us.
The two thieves pretending to be clueless.
Got them!
Caught you—it’s you!
Let’s catch the thieves together!
Welcome, everyone,
to True Fruit's "Smile at First Sight" Variety Show.
This show is exclusively sponsored by
Mengniu True Fruit.
A warm welcome to the cast of "Midnight Return."
Welcome!
Hello, everyone, I'm Xu Kai.
I play Magistrate Mei Zhuyu in "Midnight Return."
By day, I solve cases with a calm mind.
By night, I hunt down demons.
Demons, I will defeat.
And Wu Zhen, I want her too.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Tian Xiwei.
I play County Princess Wu Zhen, the feline guardian, in "Midnight Return."
She's a headstrong county princess,
and the guardian of peace in the monster market.
Mei Zhuyu and I are a perfect match.
We're sweet from the start.
Hello, everyone.
I'm actress Wang Jiayi.
In "Midnight Return," I play
Liu Taizhen, who manages the monster market with Wu Zhen.
Welcome!
Hello, everyone.
I'm Zhu Zhengting.
In "Midnight Return," I play Wu Zhen's cousin,
Pei Ji Ya.
Even if I can only stand behind her,
I'm willing to give her everything.
Cousin, are you the backup guy?
Are you the backup, cousin?
Pretty much.
It's fine, thanks for your effort, cousin.
A little spoiler.
And we have another friend, Guan Yue.
Who am I?
Who are you?
And you are?
Today, I'm a "Guimi" for Midnight Return.
Welcome, Guimi fans!
Welcome, Guan Yue!
Fans of Midnight Return,
knew you all were coming,
and in our True Fruit Wishing Pool,
many wishes have already been sent in.
The audience makes the wishes,
True Fruit milkshake delivers the luck.
Everyone, enjoy the floral fruitiness.
A bottle of little happiness.
You taste the fruit bits,
and draw the lucky charm.
Get ready for the fans’ truly heartfelt love.
Come on.
Open them all.
Got it.
What is it?
Haohao, read it out.
Okay.
Let’s take a look first.
Move Yang Chaoyue and Xu Zhisheng aside.
Let’s see the hug.
They’re blocking everything.
Seriously.
These two, really.
They’re not even here,
but still manage to steal the spotlight.
Just pull them out by the roots.
Alright, very good.
Okay, let’s go.
Take a look.
Is Magistrate Mei really flirting with respectable women in public?
Yes.
So bold about it?
Are you crazy?
Couldn't get on the cart.
Just swung right over.
Spinning around while hugging.
Come on.
Let's recreate a classic scene.
Okay.
Time for a loving hug.
Wu Zhen.
Magistrate Mei, are you flirting with a respectable lady in public?
Yes.
Not bad.
Evenly matched.
This time it's more cheerful.
Right.
It's not as ambiguous as in the drama.
Let's check out another scene.
Nice grip.
Flirting with Magistrate Mei in public.
Got a hold.
This one's easy, I'll do it.
I'm doing a role reversal, right?
You're playing Wu Zhen?
No, I'm just standing still.
I'll just stand here.
Alright.
One, two, three, go.
Young sir.
Looks like a frail scholar with no strength.
But actually quite strong.
All done.
Your turn, Xiwei.
The suggestion Xiwei just made.
Let's try it.
You two do a role reversal and let's see.
Come on, I want to see.
No way.
I'll "die" if I do this.
I want to see.
Come on.
Pay attention to the "aiya" part.
Magistrate Mei, remember the "aiya."
Hold tight.
Alright, start.
Can't hold it, no.
Louder.
The young lady looks like a frail girl with no strength.
But actually, she's pretty strong.
Looks like Magistrate Mei had a little to drink.
Let's check out the second fan wish.
Dance together.
How do we dance to this?
This is so embarrassing.
Three, two, one, go!
So cute.
Third fan wish.
If you match, there's a penalty.
Everyone takes a question board.
I'll ask the first question.
Midnight Return team dinner.
Who would rush to pay the bill?
This way it's easy to see.
Answer honestly.
We'll talk about whether you've actually paid later.
Just show the act of rushing.
In the end, it's the crew who pays.
Alright, let's reveal the answers.
So, everyone wrote themselves?
Not the same.
Is it you two?
You two get the penalty.
Alright, I'll act cute for you.
You act cute for him.
Okay.
Just keep acting cute all the way, sure.
Go ahead.
Such pure cuteness.
Done.
So that's the kind of character you are.
Wang Jiayi.
It's the first time Little Snake treated me like this.
Let me pass it on then.
No sound?
If we're feeling itchy,
just go find a place to scratch.
Second question.
If there were dolls that could swap bodies,
who would you want to switch with most?
Swap with someone outside our group.
The one who grinds medicine.
Alright, let's reveal our answers.
I picked myself as the Young Master.
Isn't that a repeat?
He picked the same.
Mei did too.
Cousin as well.
You two.
You.
The three of us all chose Young Master.
You're different from us.
That's enough from you.
Seriously, you even stole the chance to act cute.
But...
Enough.
The rule is, you have to be different.
Even if you get it right, you get scolded.
Being different is how you win.
Right.
If it's the same, you lose.
Exactly.
So the three of us lost.
You three.
Come on.
Tell us why Jiayi wants to swap bodies with Cousin.
Because I think his outfit looks great.
I want to try wearing it.
Really.
It's just...
Cousin's look in the show is pretty handsome.
You think he's handsome?
I think my style looks good.
Then why swap with Mei Zhuyu?
Because I didn't get what I wanted.
If I switch into his body,
then I can get it, right?
Sorry.
Like this.
Well said.
I chose myself because
I think Mei Zhuyu looks cool when catching monsters.
And his fight scenes aren't complicated.
Special effects.
Alright, then you three still have to act cute.
Come on.
Go ahead, you and Cousin.
Me and Cousin.
Then I'll go with Li Dan.
Do I have that honor?
Then I’m really...
Should we let the ladies have this honor?
He’s going to act cute to you.
Alright.
Bro, help me out, bro.
Okay, sure.
Help me out.
He’s here to borrow money.
Isn’t this just begging?
This is acting cute, not begging.
What is this?
Life is tough, bro.
Boss Dan
Stop messing with me.
Why are you picking on me?
I'm sweating already.
Someone go scratch his head.
Bro
Alright, let me act cute for the Guimi fans.
Okay.
Bestie
You're my best friend.
And also my sweetie.
The two of us are
besties.
Guan Yue, I'm not mad at all.
We're so in sync.
How did this happen?
Wait a second.
You already said that to me today.
How many people are you going to say that to?
Bestie
Besties, we're all besties together.
The three of us.
Alright, let's go.
This round, we'll split into the Laughter Power Team and the Guimi Team.
Starting from the second round,
there will be a "Close Your Eyes When It's Dark" segment.
The winning team
will get a real clue about the thief.
I mean,
none of you here can figure it out.
Both teams will use the clues they get
to make their choice about the thief.
You're stalling on purpose.
Guan Yue, wake up.
The mystery warehouse will check the results
and give a water spray penalty.
Everyone here is a suspect.
We need to find the thief among us together.
Everyone, pay attention! Jia Rui, go for it!
Why are you pointing at me?
Think carefully.
It has nothing to do with me.
Be sure to listen to Jia Rui's statement.
You Ren
What's wrong?
It's midnight.
The thief is about to appear.
Rumor has it that Chang’an is full of gossip these days.
They say something ominous has been spotted.
So now we are
attending some kind of ceremony for the two of them, right?
For those two people.
Wake up.
We're rolling, Tian Jiarui.
Time to work.
Chen Xinhao, come on.
What time is it?
Once we start,
it doesn't matter what time it is.
It's time.
It's time, okay.
Alright, welcome everyone.
to the dorm of our Smile at First Sight Store.
I really didn't expect
to have the honor in this life
of sharing a dorm with all of you.
Let's ask the cast of Midnight Return.
What do you choose?
I choose
I choose Zhu Zhu.
Because I think her whole vibe
makes it really easy to fall asleep.
Very soothing.
Yeah.
I choose our whole little team together.
Can you cut my part out?
Your answer makes it seem
a bit narrow-minded.
I choose our whole little team together.
It's thundering again.
Why aren't you all asleep yet?
It's midnight now.
I've prepared some delicious food for everyone.
Hurry up and finish all the food
eat it all up.
Then go to sleep quickly.
First, make sure it's actually food.
Getting nervous again.
Seriously.
Everyone in our dorm,
I'm sure you can't wait any longer.
I'm sure you're all drooling by now.
Come, take a look at your food.
Who wants barbecue?
Are we starting with grilling?
Who’s the unlucky one starting with barbecue?
Me.
Why are you eating so well?
I’m cooking it fresh right here, right?
I want to do it here.
I’ll “finish” you all.
This instant noodles are mine.
This is amazing.
Are you eating that dry?
Your hot water is here.
I want to soak it.
I still have to tear it open.
I’m the dragon fruit.
This cake is mine.
Such a big piece.
I’m this one.
This one tastes good.
This one’s soft.
But why is this one so hard?
What is this thing?
What do I have here?
This burger of mine isn't an ordinary burger.
It's so hard, it could knock someone out.
Mine's made of iron.
It's a burger from two years ago.
First round.
This is our warm-up game.
Here are our rules.
Everyone must finish within the time limit.
Eat all the food in front of you.
While you're eating,
listen for my whistle.
When I blow the whistle,
I'll come in right away to check the dorm.
The dorm check rules are:
Minus one point if you're not lying in bed.
Minus one point if you're not under the blanket.
Eat more than half, get two points.
Finish everything, get five points.
I have a question.
How many points do you lose for giving up?
If you give up, just finish eating here.
Why don't you start heating the pan, bro?
What are you waiting for?
Yeah, let me see...
I'll go check the other dorms first.
You guys figure it out yourselves.
Right, give them a bit more time.
It'll take me an hour just to heat the pan.
No problem.
I'll go for a walk first.
You guys get ready.
It's starting.
Hurry, make yours.
Wait, it's started?
The bell rang.
Mine...
Not bad.
This thing is disgusting.
Seriously, you guys...
Me...
Do you think this is okay for you two?
You two...
Who are you two trying to fool?
Never mind being late.
You're slower than everyone else.
Tian Xiwai and Guan Yue, minus points.
You really were too slow.
You almost coughed up blood.
I'll get you a tissue.
Wait a second.
Tian Xiwei.
Tian Xiwei can't even swallow anymore.
Suddenly,
She suddenly looks like she’s come down with a sudden illness.
She can't swallow.
She just lies down over there.
The dorm manager is about to lose it.
Let’s turn off the stove for a bit.
Sorry.
Let me flip it over.
You’re lying down and still want to flip over?
Whatever, do what you want.
I still hope you all do well.
Hope everyone eats well tonight.
No need to rush.
Good night.
Sleep well.
Bye-bye.
I still have to wait.
Never mind, I’ll wait a bit.
What’s this?
I thought I lost a tooth.
Me too.
Here, you take a bite first.
Make some room.
Is it gross?
I’m telling you, it’s super gross.
Why is it you again?
Well, since it’s already like this,
let’s finish eating before heading back.
Let’s finish eating before heading back.
It’s already like this.
Why did you come back again?
I’m back.
I was worried about you.
Dorm leader.
Look at her.
What’s wrong with her? Is she...
She’s “poisoned.”
Wipe your mouth.
I can’t take it anymore.
Chen Xinhao, I’ll hate you forever.
I really will hate you forever.
We agreed to help each other.
That thing is way too bitter.
Guan Yue,
sit up for a moment.
I’m about to fall asleep.
Guan Yue, your gums are bleeding.
Do you want to get it checked?
That’s a lot of blood.
I’m okay.
Come on, Tian Xiwie,
sit up for a moment.
What happened to her mouth?
She’s doing that acrobatic trick.
Showing off her teeth.
Baby fat.
Okay.
Alright.
Let me check things over here.
This one eats walnuts so fast.
I know what’s in your mouth now.
You eat walnuts without spitting out the shells.
Hey, Xu Kai, lift the blanket so I can take a look.
Open your hands.
Alright, take your time eating.
There’s still time.
I’ll go check the other dorms.
Guys,
Good night.
Is this even edible?
Where is this specialty from?
Let me swap it for you, Yang Di.
I don't want yours.
Seriously, try one. It's tasty.
Yours is even scarier to eat.
No, trust me.
Anyone want a bite of cake?
This cake is pretty good.
What is this?
These beef cubes are hard to cook.
These beef cubes...
Maybe grill them a bit longer.
Just grill all of these together.
Alright, come back.
Is there any point?
Swallow it properly.
Minus one point.
Right?
Let me see.
You're a real magician.
When I came over just now,
wasn't this plate empty?
How did all these shells appear?
Did you pull them out of your mouth?
If I'm not mistaken,
Dorm manager.
I really can't eat this "brick."
Seriously.
I have porcelain teeth, I can't do it.
I don't want to risk it for this round.
Or I'll lose tens of thousands.
It's too hard.
No way.
It's impossible to eat this.
This basically means,
It's like, listen to me,
As we mentioned last time,
the storytelling gavel.
Congratulations to Magician Tian Xiwei.
She finished everything.
Add five points.
Zhengting was a bit slow.
Subtract one point.
One last chance for everyone.
Whatever score you get, that's it.
I'm leaving.
I can help you eat some.
We have to finish it.
Because I can't finish it.
Let me help you eat it.
Here, I'll help you.
You take one.
I still have a lot here.
I don't want this one.
I'm not eating this.
Seriously, don't eat this.
Really, don't touch it.
I've eaten quite a few.
If you're a man, eat it.
I'm not eating.
I'm busy.
What's going on with Chen Xinhao?
I won't complain if others are slow,
but why did you run to someone else's dorm?
What are you doing?
Come out here!
Hurry up!
The dorm supervisor is calling you.
You're so sneaky, Haohao.
What were you just doing?
Were you trying to get someone else to eat for you?
No.
Zhengting said he wanted to try it.
So I gave it to him.
I didn't.
He hid the cake on our side.
If it's in your hand, it's yours.
Let me tell you,
my mom told me,
never eat food from strangers.
Zhengting has superpowers too.
It's finished.
Did you really finish your instant noodles?
Yes, we did.
The dragon fruit is gone too.
We finished ours as well.
Zhu Xudan's cake is finished.
Five points.
The Fan Club team wins.
But in this round,
even though the Fan Club team won,
they won't get any rewards.
And there won't be any
clues about the thieves.
Starting from the second round,
we'll reveal clues about the thieves.
No.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
I ate a bowl of instant noodles.
This is just our way of being good hosts.
The first round was just to let you enjoy some good food.
Alright.
Let's get ready for the second round.
Next up is another teamwork challenge.
You can experience it for yourselves.
During this kind of team competition,
you'll see who's sabotaging the team.
The team has to work as one.
Maximum teamwork is required.
Only then can you catch all the thieves.
Now, let's announce
the specific rules for the Sweet Triple Challenge.
There are three rounds in this game.
First,
One teammate lifts another teammate.
After crossing the massage board to the target area,
they must throw their teammate over the high jump bar.
If the thrown teammate clears the bar,
and the bar doesn't fall, it's a success.
Second,
One teammate carries another on their back.
After crossing the massage board to the target area,
the teammate on top
must eat the pineapple hanging above.
If they do, it's a success.
Third,
Four people stand in a line.
They pass the ball using only their chins and shoulders.
Passing five balls means success.
Complete all the rounds,
and the team with the fastest time wins.
I want to know,
between Zhengting and Guan Yue, who will throw whom?
I'll carry her.
What do you mean, sis?
You're really too much.
No, that's not it.
Then between us, who carries whom?
I'll carry you.
Can you even lift me?
Well, he is a guy after all.
Of course I can.
If you carry me, I know it'll be fine.
But to actually
throw me...
I can do it.
Because if we throw you out,
we can definitely do it.
You just touch this side of me.
No, that's not it.
That's fake.
Is it on Maibao's side?
The main thing is,
Feel my strong arm.
The main thing is, he has to throw.
I can throw.
Okay.
I've never been thrown in my life.
Then I'll throw you now.
Let me experience it for the first time.
Yeah.
Give it a toss.
Do we need to take off our shoes?
No need.
No need to take off your shoes.
What's the point of the acupressure board if we keep our shoes on?
Keep your shoes on.
What's the point of not taking off our shoes?
Everyone, get ready.
I'll count down: three, two, one.
Three.
Go for it!
Two.
Come on!
One.
Let's go!
Go!
It's a bit heavy.
One, two, three.
The pole fell.
Throw it again from the same spot.
Throw again from here.
Right away.
I'll go a bit higher first.
I'll go higher first.
Every time it comes down.
Right now.
Wait until I'm ready.
Xin Hao.
You shouldn't miss the throw.
Wait a second.
What are you doing?
Hold on.
My mic...
Slow down, don't rush.
Three, two...
Wait.
You have to let go, Yang Di.
I'll go over there.
That's scary.
Let go.
It's a bit low.
You...
Every time, it presses on the pole.
It hurts so much!
You...
Throw, throw me.
Failed again.
Okay.
No.
You can't throw like that.
How should I throw?
Sorry.
You can't do it this way.
You can flip me backward.
But you can't say that.
Yes, do it like this.
Need to get over.
Over the shoulder.
Alright.
What's this?
A brand new pose.
No, can't get over.
No.
Hold, you have to hold.
Still have to hold.
We look good.
Fix your hair, Guan Yue.
One, two, three, go!
We must look good.
Throw over.
Look good while going over.
No, can't get over.
You can't do it.
You didn't throw your upper body.
I told you, it's the upper body.
Your body...
One, two, three.
Go, this way.
Go.
Are you okay?
Are you alright?
How about this,
let’s do it.
You throw to me.
Let them hold each other and eat pineapple.
Can you eat pineapple while holding each other?
Let’s switch.
You get ready to hold and eat pineapple over there.
He throws to me.
Okay.
They’ve decided.
The first and second players have switched.
They gave up.
They switched the first and second players.
Young Master,
Just throw to me.
Let’s learn from them.
Very successful.
Alright, very successful.
Bro, your sleeve.
This counts.
That's his clothes.
Come on, let's go.
Come on.
Hurry.
Quick.
You're stalling on purpose.
Yang Di.
You're stalling.
There's a thief.
You're still stalling.
You're still wasting time.
Hurry up.
You can start throwing now.
Don't shout.
Okay.
Got it.
I have to carry you.
Let's go.
Second round, go.
My shoe.
Go over.
Eat pineapple.
Go eat pineapple.
Go ahead.
Is that okay?
No, get down.
A bit higher.
A little higher.
Higher.
Keep going!
You got this!
Is it done?
It's done.
We finished.
Four people passing the ball.
No.
Wait a second.
Hold on.
Side by side.
Just like before.
Hurry.
Okay.
That's enough.
Pass the ball.
Zhengting.
Zhengting and Guan Yue.
You could say they have zero teamwork.
It's all about skill.
No teamwork at all.
Pass five times to win.
Pass five times.
Go.
Again.
This scene actually looks pretty harmonious.
Why do some people in this scene
look so close?
Some look like zombies.
Some really look like the undead.
Like they're about to suck someone's blood.
Yang Di's acting weird.
I want to laugh.
Because he's breathing on my neck.
It's so ticklish.
Stop messing around.
Like that.
It's still ticklish.
Hurry.
How many do you have now?
Four.
Just one more.
Five is enough.
We're almost done.
Hurry.
We're done.
What?
Congratulations to the Fan Club for winning!
Good job. Are you okay?
I'm fine.
No way.
It was you.
Yang Di.
Why me?
I worked hard for this.
There's something off.
Seriously, something's wrong.
I'm innocent!
What did I do?
My powder's all on your face, not your body.
You put on so much powder.
This is my own makeup.
Impossible.
My makeup is definitely thicker than yours.
I was just like this.
When did I not try?
You kept...
No.
It's because you kept squeezing.
You were so forceful.
I did it like this.
You made it difficult.
What are you doing now?
You kept breathing on my neck.
It tickled.
No way.
I tried really hard.
I fell a few times at the start.
Every time I hit the pole.
It hurt so much.
Right?
Did Guan Yue feel it?
When practicing below, I did it in one go.
It was easy.
Is that so?
Alright, here we go.
I can't get through.
We should be able to get past this.
I still have to climb up by myself.
You're the ultimate spy.
I'm tired.
I'm sleepy.
I think you're actually quite...
You were just eating something.
That makes sense too.
Yeah.
I think you're pretty nice.
Didn't expect that.
Just now, Guan Yue was climbing up that pole.
The way she went for the pineapple.
It made everyone curious about the pineapple.
I want to drink one of our...
True Fruit pineapple apple flavor.
I'll get it for you. I want one too.
Thanks, Haohao.
This sip is so satisfying.
Premium fresh milk.
A perfect blend with sweet apple juice.
You can even chew on Xuwen pineapple bits.
I guess I've achieved pineapple freedom too.
You guys should try it too.
There are plenty at the store.
Help yourselves anytime.
That was a sweet triple combo just now.
Our Fan Club finished first.
Please step onto the flower board.
We need to work together
to find the thieves among us.
Everyone, take an eye mask.
After you put on the eye mask,
the two thieves will reveal themselves.
They will place the Boom Boom marker
under the flowerpot
where they want to hide the loot.
When morning comes,
everyone on the winning team
can pick a flowerpot.
If you guess correctly,
you’ll receive
a clue about your team’s thief.
Everyone,
it’s midnight.
Night falls, please close your eyes.
Put on your eye mask.
Make sure it’s on.
Okay.
Now, thieves, open your eyes.
Thieves, open your eyes.
You’re stalling on purpose.
Yang Di,
something’s off.
Seriously, something’s wrong.
I’m innocent!
This won’t work.
If you need to hug, just hug.
This feels pretty interesting.
Looks like I'm about to be interrogated.
You can first confirm your role for this round.
You are the thief this round.
Your mission
is to hide your identity as the thief.
Hide the stolen items well.
Don't let anyone else notice.
Our team—
Will they guess my identity?
You mean just the Laughter Power Team?
Honestly,
I'm not saying
it's about any one person.
I mean everyone here.
Maybe none of them will figure it out.
I'll try to mislead everyone.
I'll steer them in the wrong direction.
No way I'll let them find me out.
Okay.
Both thieves, please remove your eye masks.
Identify your partner.
You can now start hiding the items.
Both thieves may stand up.
Thieves,
you can get up from your chairs now.
Alright.
Please hide the items.
Everyone else, please put on your eye masks.
We're not allowed to talk now, right?
Or...
What does that mean?
Is it you?
No one can talk.
Right?
Thieves, please—
Please hide the items.
Are you done hiding?
Okay.
Thieves, please return to your seats.
Alright.
Daybreak—everyone, please open your eyes.
Yang Di
You gave yourself away.
Tian Jiarui is pretty sneaky.
Did you go back there on purpose to talk?
I didn't.
I've been here the whole time.
That's true.
He wasn't that suspicious when he was quiet.
You were quiet, then suddenly started talking.
I thought we weren't allowed to talk?
Yeah, no one was talking.
I have the mark.
So the ones without the mark are it.
Let's stop overanalyzing outside info.
Let's just guess normally.
The winning team is the Fan Club.
Each of you
can pick a flowerpot.
I think
if we go by Yang Di
or Zhu Zhu, it should be
Yang Di would probably put it here.
Why?
Don't try to pin it on me.
It's not me.
Because he'd definitely pick a close one.
He thinks we wouldn't go for one that's far away.
Just have everyone point to one.
Then I'll pick this one.
Okay.
Let's take the close ones first.
The close ones.
I think the middle one is possible.
Then let's pick this one.
I think it's this side.
Yeah, I think so too.
I also think it's this side.
Just said it, so take this one.
Just grab any.
Aren't we each supposed to take one?
Yeah.
Right.
Okay, three, two, one.
Everyone take one.
I'll take this one.
You two are so in sync.
Is there any?
Is there any stolen item?
Speechless.
None of the four were chosen.
No.
Not a single one.
What's going on?
What's happening?
Wouldn't we be at a disadvantage if we pick first?
They should pick first.
No, we can't pick.
We aren't even eligible to pick.
It's over.
That's unfortunate.
You didn't get
any clues about the thief this round.
But everyone can think it over again.
Because the thief definitely
doesn't want you to get it.
Wait a second.
I want to ask something.
Who was the first to pick this just now?
Me.
Him.
I said it right away.
I just said I'd pick this one.
Then he's a bit suspicious.
Him.
Because
Don't interfere with our team's guessing.
The two "wolves" are fighting.
I'm just giving a rational analysis.
No.
The information he gave is crucial.
If he usually thinks it's you,
then it's probably not you.
You're safe.
Right.
I don't think we can trust Jia Rui's words.
Because from the very beginning,
he acted really anxious and eager.
Right after Dan finished reading the rules,
Jia Rui was already
aware of the rules from the start.
But he deliberately responded to Dan's words,
trying to make himself look relaxed.
No.
I just wanted some screen time.
I just...
I'm not...
No.
I just wanted a bit of screen time, that's all.
Was Jia Rui the one talking just now?
And when the thief was acting,
he was the only one making any noise.
Yes, he was talking.
The sound came from his spot.
He was talking while walking.
Because that sound
sounded like it was getting quieter in my ears.
That's probably what he did.
No.
If I were the thief,
I wouldn’t be foolish enough to talk while walking.
I’d definitely sit down and talk.
I do have some brains.
You were sitting down when you said it.
If you say so,
You said it while sitting.
Said it sitting down.
It’s always like this.
Because every time,
I always end up like this.
I’m done talking.
It’s Yang Di.
He’s really happy right now.
Because you all
are blaming me.
I’m not happy at all.
Jiarui and I exchanged a few glances.
He looked very guilty.
I’m not guilty.
Not guilty at all.
Because when I play this kind of game,
I’m always like this.
You might not know,
but I’ve always been like this.
No need to rush this round.
Let’s move on to the next round.
Bring out the props.
Here are the rules for the Mystery Box Heartbeat game.
Each team sends out two players per round.
Their hands are tied together.
Within three minutes,
they search four mystery boxes containing beads.
Grab as many beads as possible.
The team with the most beads wins.
Of course, inside these boxes
there’s more than just beads.
Let’s see what’s in the first mystery box.
What is it?
I have no idea.
Is it one of your family members, Shrimp Boy?
What?
How is this even here?
Stop acting.
That's way too much.
Seriously, you guys are taking it too far.
Can this even be aired? I doubt it.
Is it real or fake?
Wait, let me ask.
Can I ask something first?
What are you usually afraid of?
I'm fine. What?
I'm not afraid of anything.
Yeah.
What about you, bro?
I'm scared of bugs, especially live ones.
Wait, it's alive?
Be brave, Xu Kai.
I feel like you guys are faking it.
Honestly, I'm kind of shocked.
Me too, I'm shocked.
My palms are sweating.
Look, I can still write.
I just saw him write "Help."
It's huge.
Way too big.
I've never seen one this big.
What is this?
This is really not okay, seriously.
This is really not okay.
It's alive.
Are you sure Xu Kai can do this?
Alright, I got it.
We definitely don't want this one.
No, I think this one's fine.
I'll be the main one grabbing.
I'll grab, you don't touch it.
I'll do the grabbing.
Then I'll assist.
Right.
Just hold my hand, that's it.
Keep your hand empty.
Okay.
But I suggest you hurry up.
I'm afraid it might...
It's not poisonous, right?
Will I still be able to walk today?
It's definitely not poisonous.
We have a total of three minutes.
Dan, I have a question.
In three minutes, just take from this one box.
Four items, so listen for the countdown.
Four.
When there's one minute left,
I'll remind you.
You need to take all four.
Remember, take the beads.
Don't take that thing out.
Three, two, one, game start!
So cold.
Wait.
Xu Kai, you just touched Tian Xuwei's hand,
and you're already screaming.
No.
Tian Xuwei, you're amazing.
Bro, step up!
Go ahead and grab it.
Xu Kai, there's nothing on the wall.
Next.
What's this?
Tian Xuwei is awesome.
What is this?
You just grabbed a handful of air.
No.
Tian Xuwei, you're so brave.
How are you not scared at all?
It's dead.
Dead.
In the corner here.
Skip this one.
Not this one.
Slow down.
This...
No way.
Not this one.
No.
Stop, stop, stop.
What is this?
Impressive.
No.
It just came out.
No, it's my shoe.
Don't grab me.
In front.
In the corner, yeah.
It's alive.
It's fine, this one's okay.
Don't move your hand.
This is a hand, right?
It's a hand.
That's it.
There's nothing left in here.
Nothing here.
Time's up.
Tian Xiwei is so fierce.
So fierce.
Xu Kai.
Look at what you all just went through.
Tian Xiwei is really fierce.
This is the boldest I've ever seen someone play this game.
That frog was really scared at the time.
The real fear box is outside.
Alright, next round please.
Yang Di and Zhu, get ready.
Zhu, are you brave?
I'm scared to death.
We just need to send one group, right?
After they're done.
Yeah, I think so.
Not everyone has to play, right?
Everyone has to play.
Kai's eyes look fierce now.
Everyone must play.
Everyone has to do it.
Everyone needs to play.
When we played the fear box before,
it was just for show.
Yeah.
As long as it's fun.
I didn't expect this.
Why does our show always do this stuff?
It's not that bad, really?
Come on, let's check them one by one.
This one seems okay.
This seems alright.
The water is overflowing.
This is alive, right?
The last one was a bit too much.
This one's boiling.
What?
In the pool.
Arowana.
Great ambitions.
No, it's just the smell is really strong.
It's been smelly all the way here.
It all smells like seafood.
Just follow me in and grab them.
Get fifteen balls and we win.
Three, two, one.
She won't let me in.
Wait a second.
Let's go, right now.
Hook your hand first.
Zhu Xudan.
This one's alive.
It's alive.
You caught it.
I didn't feel anything, where's the bead?
Got it.
What?
What's this?
What is this?
Then it's fine.
It's okay, it's fine.
But there's no bead.
Where's the bead?
I got one, let me out.
It's fine once you see what it is.
Don't rush, Yang Di.
Them.
Snails don't count as beads.
How did you manage to grab that out?
He grabbed all of those out.
Why do I get a snail every time?
I got it.
There's a snail every time.
I can't get the bead.
There's one more.
I got it.
Okay, that's the second one.
Come on.
It's fine, my hands are like this now.
It's okay.
This one's pretty gross.
This is really gross.
Go, go, go.
Go.
What is this?
Scared, but still grabbing like crazy.
Wait a second.
Yang Di is already washing his hands.
I found it—it's kelp.
Zhu Zhu realized after hearing it's kelp.
Her hands started moving right away.
Once she knew it was kelp, she relaxed.
Next.
That's it.
Next, grab it.
What is this?
Grab it, just grab it.
Grab this one hard.
Trust me, just reach in and grab.
It's fine, grab it.
Grab it.
What is this thing?
It has legs and antennae.
I think it's moving.
Where is this? What is this?
You touched its antennae.
I couldn't even hear what you said.
Next.
Skip this one, next.
No, I don't want it.
Next.
This one.
Forget it, I don't want it.
No, I don't want it.
That's not right.
Seems like it works.
The more you say no, the more you want to touch it.
What's this?
Don't squeeze it.
It's fake.
Fake stuff.
Just reach in and grab it.
Everything in here is fake too.
This one's fake too.
The ball—I found the ball.
I know what this is.
I know.
I figured out what this is.
Is there a ball in this one?
I found it.
Time's up, it's over.
Come on, let's count.
Brave.
Nine, ten.
Eleven, twelve, thirteen.
Fourteen.
That's fifteen as well.
It's a tie.
Let's bring out the props for round three.
Don't make any facial expressions.
Okay.
No expressions.
Can I just faint instead?
No.
You guys, you're going to scare me.
I probably wouldn't be this scared otherwise.
Let's take a look first.
Wait, really?
Can this actually work?
I don't think this will work.
What?
What is it?
It's alive.
Let's check this out.
What?
That's disgusting.
This is killing me.
What is this?
You guys must have upset someone.
You definitely made someone mad here.
No, it’s you guys.
Seriously, just act it out.
Don’t look.
Seriously, don’t look.
It’s easier if you don’t look.
Yeah, don’t look.
What the heck is this?
Come on, check out the fourth one.
What?
What should we do?
Yang Di, just act it out.
Honestly, I’d rather not get any points for this.
Just don’t stay too long.
Not sure if it’s dangerous.
No way, it’s really scary.
Here, you hold the tray and I’ll reach in.
Okay.
Come on.
Let’s go.
Let’s take it slow.
Take it slow.
Slow down.
Don’t touch my hand.
What is this? It’s all slimy.
What is this?
I’ve never seen anything like this before.
I haven’t reached in yet, wait a second.
How did it come over here?
It’s coming for you.
Don’t do that, guys.
It’ll find you.
It gets excited when it sees your hand.
Okay.
In front, yeah.
Awesome.
That’s it.
Feels like a fish, I think.
They were scared to "death."
Not me, I was just...
Don't grab it.
I know what it is now.
What?
It's fine.
There's no way you know.
No, you can't possibly know.
You can't know for sure.
Because I've raised one before.
He used to have one.
Axolotl.
Relax, it's from your house.
That's it.
What is this?
This one, no way.
Zhengting saw it.
I saw it, I can't do it.
I can't.
I really can't.
Why can those two look?
That expression...
Why did you two switch boxes after looking?
You two, stop looking.
Don't look.
Your hand...
You grabbed it so precisely.
That's a bit too much peeking.
Wait, how did your hand get out?
Don't do that.
My voice cracked.
What is this?
Grabbed a handful.
I almost threw up.
Guan Yue.
Guan Yue was just forced to put her hand in.
She didn't do anything at all.
Zhengting, you're awesome.
That's enough.
Next.
This works.
Yeah, move back.
Grab it all at once.
Right here.
Okay, next.
That's it.
That's it, next.
What is that?
No idea.
Green onion.
Over here, it's here.
It's fine now.
So impressive.
Wait, sis, why are you scared of the onion?
Don't shake.
That's it.
Okay, time's up.
Amazing.
Well done.
What is this thing?
That sandworm.
Watching this is really nerve-wracking.
Fifteen, twenty.
They got twenty-two.
Guan Yue only got one.
Didn't get any.
Mainly, you two saw the sandworm.
Then you just picked them out one by one.
No.
When I first saw it, it was scary.
It just felt gross.
Very good.
Alright, let's switch to the next set of props.
But I think they're just overreacting.
It's really not that scary.
I can't say, I don't know.
It is pretty scary though.
Yeah.
Because when you watch, it seems fine.
But when you touch it, it's different.
Let's just be cool and go for it.
We're really fast.
You and I will be the fastest and most thorough team.
I'll show you what real style looks like.
Go!
They're so calm.
Chicken feet.
Impressive.
I found one.
Found one.
Everyone here is brave.
These two guys.
They made our game look boring.
If we air your segment,
it'll be in the rule explanation.
I found one.
Found one.
The chicken feet are almost cooked.
What's this?
No one's scared?
Careful.
I know what it is.
Grab it.
Those two are too fierce.
They're in invincible mode.
Stop tormenting them.
I think the creatures inside are the unlucky ones.
The creatures are the ones truly facing the fear box.
In the last round, our Laughter Power Team took out
twenty-three beads.
So they got more.
Add them all up.
That means the Laughter Power Team wins.
We won.
Victory for this round.
Okay.
That was really tough.
We can look for the spy now, awesome!
Yang Di, you’re the biggest spy here.
You didn’t give us any hints at all.
Yeah, you didn’t say anything anywhere.
Exposed.
Then you grabbed the bead and put it back.
Alright, night falls, everyone close your eyes.
Thieves, please open your eyes.
Speak up.
Thieves, you can hide the loot.
Let’s go.
Go.
Where’s Yang Di? Yang Di?
You, get going.
Tian Jiarui, say something.
Tian Jiarui, speak.
Where’s Jiarui?
Tian Jiarui, talk.
Say something.
No one’s talking.
Chen Xinhao.
Chen Xinhao, say something.
Chen Xinhao, speak.
I’m here, I’ve been right next to you.
Xiao Tian.
What’s up?
It’s nothing.
Feel around next to you.
Cousin.
What?
Cousin’s here too.
Guan Yue.
Didn’t answer me.
I can’t do this.
What is this?
What’s this?
Daybreak, everyone open your eyes.
That was a chaotic night.
Why are you laughing?
You look guilty.
Yang Di, that crooked smile of yours—
Honestly, it’s iconic.
For this round, our Laughter Power Team—
Each person can pick one flowerpot.
It's our turn, right?
Decide who you think it is.
Which flower is hiding the treasure.
I want to ask Yang Di, what do you think?
They always think it's me.
Come over and give us an answer first.
Point one out for us.
Yeah, just pick one.
This one.
Okay, this one.
Are you taking it or not?
No, I'm not.
If you don't, then just take this one.
Really?
Someone took one.
Because we can take four.
That's true.
I'm not taking it anyway.
Just take this one.
Why are you all focusing on me?
You two are really aggressive today.
I already know who it is.
Who?
It's me again.
Just now, I was halfway there.
Then I called out to Tian Jiarui.
He took ages to respond.
I didn't.
And he rushed back to his spot.
He was on his way back, right?
Yeah, on the way back.
He only replied after he arrived.
I agree with Zhu Zhu.
That happened.
It's fine, just take it first.
Take it first. If it's right, we'll get a clue.
Just take it, that's it.
I'll take this one.
You take this one.
You've named three, there's one left.
See, he's been directing Yang Di the whole time.
He's trying to distance himself.
I think among these four,
If I pick up these four and there's nothing,
Later, if you blame me, I get it.
If Yang Di is the thief,
I'm just guessing, I'll go with this one.
I choose this one.
Is it there?
Darn it.
Is it stuck inside?
Didn't get it.
Yang Di is such a good actor.
Totally convinced.
Jiarui is such a good actor. Jiarui!
No clue.
Alright, impressive.
Awesome, Yang Di.
Impressive.
Your teammate.
I'm trying to figure out who your teammate is.
Tian Jiarui.
Feeling good now?
Jiarui.
Look, is Tian Jiarui happy?
See if Tian Jiarui is happy.
You're not lying to me, are you?
Of course I'm lying to you.
I'm telling you, bro.
Trust me.
Look me in the eyes and say it.
Just do it.
Look into my eyes and say it.
I'm not.
You're not.
Because he never lies to anyone.
He only tricks the gullible "fool."
Impossible.
"Fool."
No way.
You're trying to stir things up.
Do you want the spotlight or to be the "fool"?
It's just that you're way too suspicious.
I really don't get why.
If you're not the one,
why play so badly?
I'm already forty years old.
You weren't like this before.
How was I before?
Trust us, little bro.
We won't lead you astray.
Bro, if you don't trust me,
we'll miss out on this highlight moment.
It must be you.
"Stupid."
Both teams have their players ready.
One of them
is holding the blank board.
Out of six people, one has the blank board.
The other five have the same phrase.
Once the game starts,
everyone acts based on their phrase.
They all choose to agree or disagree at the same time.
After making their choices,
each person explains their decision in turn.
Then, they try to identify who has the blank board.
If the blank board holder fails to hide,
they get sprayed with water as punishment.
Anyone who correctly identifies the blank board gets a point.
If the blank board holder stays hidden, they get a point.
Everyone else gets sprayed with water.
The game ends.
The team with the highest total score wins.
Friends in the first round,
you can check your boards now.
Okay.
Pick up your Agree or Disagree board.
Please answer.
Everyone chose Agree.
Alright.
Let's start with Yang Di.
He's closest to me.
I firmly chose Agree.
Because...
Got it.
Yang Di.
No.
I can't go into too much detail.
From a promo perspective, we have to agree.
You get it, right?
You understand, right?
I don't get it.
Anyway,
This round has to be Agree.
This chopstick right now...
Yeah, we can't say too much.
Right now, it has to be Agree.
I think we can talk more about it later.
Blank board.
For now, it's Agree.
Why are you copying the person before you?
No.
Then how should I put it?
What do you mean by "talk about it later"?
Will we really talk about it later?
Not necessarily.
But for now, it's definitely Agree.
We're in this together.
Xiao Tian.
I feel pretty confident.
Definitely Agree.
Kai, what do you think?
There might be a lot of good options.
But I think this one is Agree.
Well said.
I think that's spot on.
I'm loving this.
One minute for open discussion.
Who do you think has the blank board?
Does Zhu Xudan not have her own way of speaking?
It's just sweet.
Really sweet.
I'm loving it.
You're just repeating other people's answers.
Yang Di, what do you think?
Why do you think so?
I just mentioned two very important keywords.
Yang Di has already given a lot away.
I think he revealed a bit too much.
He basically gave that person a hint.
I regret it now.
Seriously.
No way.
I think it's Yang Di.
Me too.
Impossible.
It can't be me.
Because I think Guan Yue and Zhu Zhu
and even Jia Rui all made good points.
Where did I go wrong?
You're being too vague.
Yeah, your answer is way too broad.
You're just talking in general terms.
He's trying to figure out what we're saying.
Right.
He just gives a rough idea.
I'll go first.
If I get too specific, it might not be good.
I already feel like I gave too many details.
Guan Yue.
That's exactly right.
Absolutely certain.
Totally decisive.
Isn't that true?
Why is Guan Yue always helping him?
The thief.
It has nothing to do with the thief.
It can't be you two, right?
There's only one blank board.
Just one blank board.
Why does she keep helping Yang Di?
And it just happens to be two.
Because she's sitting closer to me.
She heard everything clearly.
But you two are working together.
So if it's you, Zhu Xudan,
do you think that's okay?
No problem.
Are you sure?
Yes.
But if that's the case...
Stop trying to trap me.
You've been protecting Yang Di the whole time.
I think...
I'm not going to get roasted for this, am I?
I really think this is weird.
No, but it's really not me.
Then who is it?
Too many geniuses here.
Tian Jiarui
Today, you were totally outshined.
So many talented people here.
There's nothing we can do.
I'm retiring.
But Tian Jiarui is acting a bit strange.
He definitely thinks this question
has something to do with romance.
He just said, "I'm shipping it."
Then let's ask Tian Jiarui.
Who are you shipping?
Yang Di, you're being a bit obvious.
Honestly,
I think my answer is spot on.
Really.
Right now, I'm shipping everyone.
Do you agree or disagree?
Why are you shipping them?
Why do you care if I ship them?
You—let me describe it.
Describe this question.
Yang Di
No, I'm looking for it.
Xiao Tian
Because I wonder why it's Yang Di.
Even though he spoke up first,
with Yang Di's wit,
he could figure out where this is going.
Which direction is it?
So he mentioned the drama promotion.
I'm really about to lose it.
Am I really that smart?
You guessed it.
You're really clever.
I'm going to recite now.
I feel like reciting something.
I can't take this.
Who could be that smart?
No matter if you agree or disagree with this question,
it's definitely related to the show promotion.
I'm not Einstein.
I'm not that smart either.
So, Zhu Xudan, do you think it's you?
Why are you picking on me?
If it's about the names on that paper just now,
the third person and the second person,
which one do you think is more likely?
The first and the second.
No, the third and the second.
Don't try to trap me.
No problem.
Didn't catch anything.
Then it must be that person.
Yeah.
Who?
Maybe.
Wait a second.
I feel like
I think it's Jiarui, kind of.
Why?
Because just now,
when you were talking to Yang Di,
I saw you looked like you wanted to laugh.
I wasn't trying to laugh.
I'm just naturally smiley.
I just—
You have a smiling mouth.
Yeah, I have a smiling mouth.
Could it be Xiwei?
No way.
Why are you so quiet?
Because I think Yang Di has a lot of loopholes.
He talks too much.
He’s already let a lot slip.
No, I haven’t.
Yang Di.
Zhu Xudan or Tian Jiarui.
Hurry up and pick one.
Yang Di.
I think it’s Yang Di.
It can’t be Yang Di.
I really feel like crying.
If it’s Yang Di, I really...
I’ll do the fear box challenge again.
I’m just too smart.
I might be a little too smart.
Alright, everyone put on your goggles.
Three.
Two.
One.
Go!
Zhu Zhu, you have to vote.
Zhu Zhu.
Which number is Yang Di?
Six.
Okay.
Let’s verify it.
Did anyone find the whiteboard?
If the vote is correct,
the whiteboard gets sprayed.
If the vote fails, everyone else gets sprayed.
Who?
Zhu Xudan.
Sorry, everyone.
Why did no one pick her?
You all still thought it was me.
She's really smart, Zhu Xudan.
Zhu Xudan.
After Tian Jiarui spoke,
he managed to get two votes for himself.
I think from now on, I shouldn't say anything in this game.
But if you don't talk, you look suspicious.
You have to analyze.
I'm done talking.
Before Tian Jiarui spoke,
Zhu Xudan would have been out.
Once you spoke, you got three votes.
Yang Di got two votes.
Zhu Xudan got one vote.
Thank you, Jiarui.
I get it now.
Now I know how to survive here.
I've figured it out.
A real genius.
So you understand now.
I have no idea how to survive here.
At this point,
I'm always a target anyway.
No matter what I do.
Explaining clearly doesn't work.
Being vague doesn't work either.
It's so tough.
This round, the hidden player succeeded.
So the Laughter Power Team gets a point.
Alright, time to switch players.
Please show the question.
Get ready to choose: agree or disagree.
The answers aren't very consistent.
Let's start with Xin Hao.
I've been observing for a while.
I think the "genius" here—
Especially after seeing their performance last round.
I feel like
I'm really familiar with him.
So I firmly decide to agree.
That's it.
I think so.
He has a lot of ideas when playing games.
And he's always on point.
Yeah.
Just "yeah."
I think everyone made good points.
Alright, then I vote for you.
It's you.
Definitely you.
No.
Because I think I—
Let's hear your weak explanation.
It's gone a full round and you still haven't figured it out.
No.
I think everyone's analysis makes sense.
Thanks for your summary.
I vote for number one.
That's my judgment.
From my perspective.
In the last round, I thought
there were still some flaws.
I'll stop talking.
Go ahead, genius.
Your turn.
I hope I don't steal the spotlight again.
Xiwei, let me ask you.
Is this person—or thing—cute?
Which thing?
You.
You mean the character or—
The character.
The character is cute.
Very cute.
How many characters are there?
Just one.
Are you sure?
I vote for her.
No.
I think Xiwei was just guessing.
But this thing—
Is it an event or a description?
It's an event brought up by a character.
The whiteboard is really tough.
Bro, do you trust me?
How can I trust you?
I don't trust you at all.
Hurry, explain it again.
Because this thing—
Thing.
This person—
Sometimes he does well.
Sometimes he doesn't.
So do you think he's doing well now?
He's pretty average right now.
There are flaws.
Yeah, it's pretty average.
I can see that, yeah.
He always causes misunderstandings.
Suddenly he blurted it out again.
But after this round,
He should know by now.
I really didn't just guess.
I swear I didn't.
Give us a clear direction.
I think it's Chen Xinhao.
Chen Xinhao.
You can even point at me with that description?
You're just accusing people now.
He's a "miracle" person.
No, he's not.
Yes, he is.
He really is a "miracle" person.
Is he a thing?
Do you think he's a thing?
I'm not sure how to judge.
If I say yes, it's wrong.
If I say no, it's wrong too.
Let me decide.
No.
He's human.
I'm done talking.
I'm sticking to my choice, okay?
Alright.
Come on, everyone put on your glasses.
But I'm a little scared.
I feel like
I feel like I don't need to wear them.
Just vote for him and that's it.
What if it's not him?
Seriously, I...
I really need to wear these.
I need to wear them too.
I really have to put these on.
My hairpiece is about to fall off.
Teacher, my hairpiece is coming off.
Chen Xinhao is very confident.
He doesn't wear glasses.
You have to wear them.
Please raise your hand.
Pick who you think is the blank board.
He's number one.
It's him.
One, two, three, four.
With four votes, I don't need to.
Xu Kai.
Four votes.
Five.
Wait a second.
You guys are really going to get roasted for this.
No way.
Three, two, one.
Hold on.
You guys are really going to get roasted for this.
Impossible.
Five.
How is that possible?
Why?
"Genius."
First time meeting.
He has a lot of ideas when playing games.
"Genius."
First time meeting.
Lots of ideas.
Right.
Just the word "right."
I think everyone is right.
Okay, then I'll vote for you.
Who?
Who is it, really?
You.
Yang Di.
Who?
Me.
What?
You finished spraying and still looking for them?
No way.
Why?
Why do you never trust me?
Because you're a genius.
Why don't we trust you?
Why do you play like this?
How did I play?
I already told you all.
You're too indecisive.
You should say it with confidence.
That's just how you are.
I don't want to talk to you.
I think our connection is kind of broken.
Kind of.
You proved this with your actions.
Yeah, he's not clear about himself.
Tian Jiarui.
I'm about to lose my mind.
Thanks.
I didn't spray.
I wasn't sprayed.
I didn't mean to give it to you either.
Tian Jiarui.
Chen Hao mentioned you first.
To him, you're a "legend."
A "legend."
With your performance this round,
you proved it successfully.
Alright.
I've confirmed it again.
Who called themselves the genius of the Spy Game?
I think it was self-proclaimed.
He really is a genius.
We all agree on that.
Because I was trying to figure out
if you were serious or just mocking me.
I was trying to tell.
A bit of both.
There’s some truth.
I thought it was sarcasm.
Would we mock you after you played like that?
It was mocking me.
Jiarui.
That last round
was your last chance
to prove yourself.
So I failed, right?
You didn’t fail.
You got five votes.
If you’re not a genius, who is?
You got the highest votes.
If you voted for yourself, it’d be unanimous.
If you’re not a genius, then who is?
Alright.
I accept it.
I won’t say a word in the next round.
Let’s move on to the final question.
Get ready to choose agree or disagree.
They’re all a bit different.
Just seeing someone raise a board,
makes me want to vote for someone.
No.
I think this is something
that some people would never do, no matter what.
This isn’t something
I can decide on my own.
But
if the price is right,
I’d consider it.
I voted yes because
no matter what they think,
I agree.
I want to see it.
I think we can take it.
Sure.
I’m actually looking forward to it.
I’m fine with it too.
Got it.
He’s pretty excited about it.
Are you okay with it?
My question is: are you okay with it?
Absolutely!
So, can I?
I can.
Will you be able to later?
I’m always good to go.
Maybe I saw it wrong.
Me.
How is that possible?
Kai, who do you think it is?
I think it's Yang Di.
Me?
Yes.
Why?
I was being so careful.
So, can you do it?
Of course I can.
Why can you?
We can do it together.
Of course, I can.
What?
He's still laughing.
What's he laughing at?
This question isn't that funny, is it?
Because I'm doing okay.
I like it.
Don't you like it?
Actually, I don't really like it.
Just now, it was fine again.
Why don't you like it now?
But when everyone's together,
then I like it.
I look forward to it.
Can't any of you tell what I'm saying?
It's because you say it so weirdly.
I can't make it any more obvious, right?
I think just remember what was said in the first round.
The culprit is him.
Who's the culprit?
Give us an answer.
Okay.
Me? What?
Alright, let's get ready to put on our goggles.
It has to be number two.
Definitely number two.
I'm telling you,
it's definitely Yang Di.
Yang Di.
What did Tian Xiwei say again?
I don't remember.
Everyone, please raise your hand.
Yang Di is already making the victory sign.
Tian Xiwei is also striking a very cool pose.
They're all doing victory signs.
Yang Di.
Jiarui, which number are you voting for?
Number two gets five votes.
What's wrong?
It must be number two.
Definitely number two.
Why me?
What?
No.
Who?
Is it you?
Kai, what are you looking forward to?
I said "I'm looking forward to it" and you all pointed at me.
No way.
Why are you looking forward to it?
What are you looking forward to?
You don't seem excited.
Because I'm a regular here.
Can't I look forward to you guys coming?
This round's topic is—
The Midnight Return team wants to try an escape room.
We're pretty confident.
Yeah.
See, I said you were looking forward to it, and I was right.
It's you.
I said I'm looking forward to it.
Me too.
Did you kind of guess it?
No, I didn't.
No.
I had no idea.
But the way you said it...
Tian Xiwai is calm and collected,
but she still needs her teammates' support.
Right.
That was really impressive.
We're moving on to the flower board.
Let's try to get another clue.
Then we'll move to the identification round.
Are you ready?
Night falls, please close your eyes.
The two thieves may open their eyes at any time.
Who is it?
Come on, everyone speak up.
Everyone, say something.
Tian Jiarui, say a tongue twister.
Ba le bai le biao le bing le ben le bei le po.
Pao le bing le bing le pai le bei le bian le pao.
Go ahead.
Little white rabbit.
White and even whiter.
White.
Jumped up again.
Why isn’t Yang Di talking?
I’m here.
Yang Di.
No, you haven’t spoken for a while.
It’s Yang Di.
Listen to me.
Yang Di, say a tongue twister.
This round, it’s Yang Di.
It’s Yang Di.
Listen to me.
This round, it’s Yang Di.
So, have we started moving?
Say something.
Ba le bai le biao le bing le.
White, stone, tower.
Stone, stone, stack.
Stack, stack, white, tower, stone, stone, stack.
White, white, tower.
Stone, stone, stack.
Stack, stack, white, tower, stone, stone, stack.
White, white, tower.
Who’s clapping?
Kai.
Say something.
Okay.
Daybreak, please open your eyes.
Yang Di.
It’s Yang Di.
Let me put it this way.
Our thief didn’t go.
He sent his teammate instead.
You went.
Just sit here.
The pawn has moved.
Very clever.
You’ve gotten smarter, Yang Di.
How’s that?
Did I describe it well?
That’s so Yang Di.
This time, I was here the whole time.
You can’t blame me now.
No one’s blaming you.
I was definitely here the whole time.
You can’t point at me anymore.
If you accuse me, you must be up to something.
Why are you so sure you were here?
Because I kept talking the whole time.
Even after it was over, I was still talking.
Why does he keep defending himself?
Because it’s him.
No one even cares.
No one mentioned you.
Kai started defending himself as soon as it ended.
Laughter Power Team, you can come and choose.
See if you can get a clue.
This one’s a bit crooked.
Alright, let’s pick this one.
Why are you looking at me?
Yang, we...
Just now, I was acting as the thief on my own.
Wasn't that tough?
Your teammates couldn't even leave their seats.
They could only sit in place.
Isn't that what happened?
Are you about to jump in now, Yang?
Okay.
Alright.
Because Yang...
Because Yang already...
guessed it right.
There's nothing we can do.
Yeah, I feel like Yang is accusing me too.
He's still talking about me.
Don't look.
I can't look.
I didn't look.
Why are you holding that?
No.
We're not supposed to take part.
But you already did.
No, I didn't.
I was stopping it.
He started defending himself as soon as it ended.
You know?
This motive for defending himself is really, really...
very reasonable.
Makes sense.
We're reasonable too.
He always does this when he feels guilty.
Exactly.
Alright, let's check this one.
You two, pick one each.
Three.
Number three is for you.
No one picked this one, right?
You take it.
Alright, let's reveal it.
Okay.
Still didn't guess it.
I just knew it wasn't the one.
Why are you so happy?
Exactly.
What's wrong with me being happy?
You just gave yourself away.
What do you mean?
Can't I be happy?
You shouldn't be happy right now.
Xu Kai.
We should be sad at this point.
Because we weren't picked.
Can't I be happy?
It's basically the same as being picked.
Because he's smiling.
Look how happy he is. I'm so mad!
Because your teammate gave themselves away.
I'm really angry.
My teammate just exposed themselves.
I'm so mad.
Help!
Alright, both teams, please make your internal selections.
The Fan Club's pick for the thief is Xu Kai.
The Laughter Power Team's pick for the thief is Di Ge.
No.
And Tian Jiarui.
Hurry up and go.
You two are tied.
Can they give us one vote?
On our side.
Yes.
It's you.
Okay.
Sure.
Why did they all pick him?
Who did you pick?
You.
It's Di Ge.
It's him.
Right.
I think it looks like him.
Xin Hao.
No way.
Du Hua.
Sister Du Hua.
Someone in your company has gone crazy.
What are you doing?
No.
It's Tian Jiarui.
Look, he's right there.
He's laughing.
It's Yang Di.
Xu Kai keeps dragging Yang Di into it.
The person Xu Kai keeps targeting
Could he really be his teammate?
Yang Di just tricked us.
And he did it without batting an eye.
Stop helping.
Chen Xinhao.
This is your last chance to shine.
Hurry up and take a look.
It's him.
Wake up.
It really is him.
Chen Xinhao.
It's really him.
Wait a second.
My brain feels itchy.
How did Yang Di trick us just now?
Yes.
Then we all got sprayed.
It was you.
Yes.
Alright.
I can't argue with them.
Yang Di, let's go.
Don't pull me.
Why are you pulling me?
Hurry up and go.
If even Xu Kai can pull someone,
are they really his teammate?
How about this—
Can we take out Xu Kai first?
I'm innocent.
You won't let me down, right?
Bro, trust me.
Trust me.
The spotlight is only on us.
Alright, I'll spray all of you.
If I'm wrong,
Okay, fine.
Trust me.
No problem.
I've made up my mind.
I hate you.
Why?
Why do you hate me?
I hate you.
You're dragging us into getting soaked too.
No way.
Getting splashed.
You didn't think about this when you voted for me.
You were so quick about it.
All three of you had the same look.
Just now, the Fan Club made it clear
that Xu Kai is the thief.
But there's some disagreement here.
Then let's have everyone
identify the thief among these four.
Great!
If everyone thinks the thief is among these four,
the one who is the thief,
please point them out.
No
You
Guan Yue, trust me
Guan Yue
It's him
Stop struggling
No, it's not
He's secretly laughing
He said stop struggling
It's him
It's Yang Di
Raise your hand
Let's count, come on
Now, number one is Tian Jiarui
Number two is Yang Di, okay
Please raise your hand
Number one
Trust me
Don't get brainwashed, sis
So now Tian Jiarui has five votes
Yang Di has three votes
Thank you, Guan Yue
I'm done with this person
The thieves identified on site are
Xu Kai and Tian Jiarui
If we guess correctly
the thieves get sprayed
If we fail
everyone except the thieves gets sprayed
I won't lose, right?
No way, bro
Three
Two
One
Please spray water
Good brothers.
Brothers for life.
In my heart,
it really wasn’t you.
Of course, it wasn’t me.
Why do you think it was me?
Why did you suddenly pick Yang Di?
I always thought it was him.
Because when you were discussing,
I couldn’t understand any of it.
You know?
Our thief-catching mission
has finally come to an end.
Honestly, in my eyes,
it should’ve gone much smoother.
It was supposed to be easy.
In the end, Guan Yue even had to step in.
and do that.
I don’t know why there were so many twists.
I hope the Midnight Return cast
can come back and play again.
Thank you all for coming.
Alright.
Thank you.
Let’s shout our slogan one last time.
See you next time, friends!
See you next time!
Too handsome for words.