What about the four of you on stage?
You have all gained the audience's love and recognition.
You are representative actors of short dramas.
As for the four male actors from the short dramas,
you haven't joined either of the two producers' teams yet.
Alright.
They're still waiting.
So we've also prepared
for each of them
keywords from their classic scenes.
The chosen male lead
will join the female lead's
team.
Let's make a selection first.
I want to set off fireworks here.
Set off fireworks?
Set them off in our studio?
Yeah.
Alright, alright.
Let's all go outside.
Okay, Mengjie chooses fireworks.
Fireworks.
I choose "Three Sways in One Step."
It suits me quite well too.
I want to sway a bit.
Sure.
Let's sway together.
Okay.
Let's take a look at the fireworks first.
Which male lead does it correspond to?
Let's look at the big screen.
It's so beautiful.
So romantic.
This soundtrack
There's a hug here too
I think I'm starting to experience
the charm of short dramas
I only watched for a few seconds
and I'm already hooked
I really want to watch a few more
I even want to keep scrolling up
As we talk about it
when our emotions reach a certain point
we just have to hug
there's that kind of moment
just
that
moment
that moment is
this is their main
so smooth
yeah
Let's welcome Kaimu
Let's welcome Mengjie
Hello
um
What do we do without fireworks on site?
Yeah, I want fireworks
Are you setting off fireworks?
We'll bloom on the side
and add some sound effects
How about that?
Okay
Alright
"Love of Fireworks"
One take
Start
Such beautiful fireworks
Mengjie
Happy holidays
You prepared all this
Your new dress is so pretty
Thank you
I haven't finished my line yet.
It's okay, you don't need to say it.
It's not important.
What matters is that hug.
This doesn't matter anymore.
This isn't important.
And you two let go too quickly.
Because Youji just came over.
Then you both left.
Let's do it again, then.
Youji, get ready.
"Fireworks Romance"
Second take, same shot.
Thank you, Di-ge.
Action.
Such beautiful fireworks.
They're from the "Yijian" convenience store.
The fireworks set off there.
Mengjie.
Happy holidays.
Did you prepare this?
Your new dress is really pretty.
Thank you.
I want to play with the fireworks.
It's on fire!
Thank you.
The roof might catch fire.
Next, let's take a look at
the "Three Shakes in One Step" move.
What's that about?
Let's look at the big screen.
There are no girls here.
Where is Xu Dongdong?
Is it the one in the back?
The key is to follow the one in the back.
Should I walk next to him?
Just learn this.
The way of walking with a sway every three steps.
Our boss.
Let's walk together.
We can all walk.
Today, we
are all your employees.
Then I'll walk from here.
I'll walk from here.
Dongdong.
How about you two walk together?
Okay.
I'll walk with Sister Dongdong.
Then we'll
join in when we get here.
Alright, no problem.
Let's welcome our
Guanyu and Dongdong.
Thank you.
Okay.
We've been playing for half the day now.
So next,
let's invite
Kaimu and Daotie
to join our
Producer Di's team.
Welcome.
Come, this way please.
You've joined the team.
Next, Guanyu and Zenghui
will join Producer Yue's team.
Here they come.
Welcome to the team.
It's an honor to have you.
Alright, everyone.
Whether it's a long or short drama,
understanding the audience
allows us to better
create and serve them.
Next, I'll announce
whose thoughts you guessed correctly.
The specific rules
Our competition will have six rounds in total.
There will be a boys' team and a girls' team.
One person from each team will participate in each round.
They will answer the key question.
Everyone can
use dance moves to grab a seat.
This earns the right to answer the question.
Then, guess
the key player's choice.
On the field,
there are three answer spots.
They correspond to one, two, and three.
If number one gets it wrong,
then it's number two's turn.
If number two gets it wrong, then it's number three's turn.
Each correct answer per round
earns one point.
When the game ends,
the team with the most points
wins.
First,
let's welcome our dance teacher,
Haohao.
Please play the music.
Pretty simple.
This time's question
Let's invite Sister Dong.
Xu Dongdong.
Which of the following sentences
would make you happiest to hear?
A.
Your English
is as good as Terence Yin's.
B.
Your figure
is really well maintained.
C.
You're that super cool big sister-in-law.
D.
Since I was little,
I thought you were really beautiful.
I've decided.
I can't take the first spot.
The first one often has to
That's right.
It's like helping others eliminate one option.
You guys can fight for the third spot.
Let me be the first one.
Okay, it's yours.
Sister Dong has already chosen.
Next, everyone
please start your performance.
Let's go.
What's going on?
It's fine, you can go.
Get him out of here.
What's going on?
It's okay now.
Then we're good.
Let's leave it like this for now.
I want to ask something.
What's everyone's strategy here?
This one.
Haohao is here.
No one is going.
Looks like only he went.
I said, please have a seat.
It's for you.
Haohao walked around once.
Where did you all go?
I feel bad competing with my younger brother.
No.
It's almost impossible to get the first spot.
Except for me,
no one else has ever gotten it.
Look at that.
Haohao can hit the target in one try.
Or maybe help everyone eliminate an option.
Eliminate one wrong answer.
With my years of experience answering questions,
I think
when there are three long and one short, pick the shortest.
So you choose B.
Right.
Okay then.
Say something nice about Sister Dong.
Alright, go ahead.
Sis, you have a great figure.
You have a nice figure too.
How did it turn into complimenting me?
That's what they said.
I meant you really keep in shape, not like that.
Then I...
You just said "really good" directly.
That's really scary.
Sis.
You really keep your figure well.
Little brother.
You keep your figure well too.
So it might be...
So it would be
Not this one
Oh no
You really helped everyone
eliminate one of the answers
No need to thank me
It's what I should do
I think it's
Your English
is as good as Yinziwei's
You guessed right
None of us guessed it right
Gotta grab the second spot
Why did you choose A
This one makes me happiest
Is it because you're as awesome as Yinziwei
Or do you just want to be good at English
I want my English to have its own style
Got it
Actually, I already have it
I
She wants to hear others praise the two of them
I want to make Northeastern English
a global plan
promote it worldwide, global plan
Okay
Wish you success
No problem
Come on
Next, let's look at the following question
"Book-Transmigration" system ready
The one Xu Mengjie most wants to win over
her ideal type is
"Transmigration into a novel" system
Do you know what that means?
Is it the same as "transmigration"?
Transmigrating into a book
"Transmigration into a novel" system
Yes, "transmigration"
A
Appears to be forceful love on the surface
Secretly makes silent sacrifices
Head of a large corporation
B
Can hear your inner thoughts
All-rounder bodyguard
B is the one I absolutely don't want
C
Won't let you do any work
Henpecked but deeply affectionate man
D
Overflowing with hormones
Loyal dog-type boyfriend
A, I like A
I really can't choose
Ideal type
There's one like this
The head of a big corporation like this
I've made my choice
Okay, I've chosen
So Mengjie has already chosen
Let's start dancing
Then let's set off
No, Dige
Okay.
I, Dige, still have a finishing pose.
Dige.
Why did you just coordinate a tactic?
Right?
The blue team won again.
Do you guys really dislike answering questions that much?
You two spent all that time,
and didn’t get a single chance.
Those two aren’t interested in answering questions.
Um...
Jianxiao Troupe.
They really are here to promote themselves.
Our Jianxiao Troupe...
Dige, you have to act it out.
Come on, get ready.
Mengjie, just bear with it for a bit.
Let’s do it.
I like it.
Sure.
This is...
Let me take a look.
D, dog-type boyfriend.
No.
Is it this one or not?
And you even came over to comfort me.
Alright, it's fine.
Let's keep moving forward.
Okay.
Let's go a bit further and try our luck.
I have to move forward on my own.
Okay.
I can hear your inner thoughts.
What is this?
All-round bodyguard.
With such a bad memory,
and you call yourself an all-round bodyguard?
I originally chose the same as you.
That's me.
Thank you.
So?
So it's not.
It's not that either.
How could it possibly be B?
That's a scary character setting.
Hearing inner thoughts is really scary.
Yeah.
Little brother.
Here's your chance, pick one out of two.
I'm number four.
A and C.
They feel completely different.
I think it's C.
I also feel like it's C.
Come on, little brother.
Act it out.
Why are you standing here?
Sit down, quickly.
Who let you into the kitchen?
Are you forcing your love on me?
This is called...
This is C.
This is...
C.
You won't let me do any work, right?
Not letting you work.
Sit down, quickly.
Where should I sit?
Where do I sit?
Sit on the chair.
You should say, "Sit on my lap."
Alright, then you go ahead.
Go ahead.
Go do your work.
I'm leaving then.
The toilet—the toilet is clogged.
So he's not one either.
Right.
It's A.
Hurry, position four!
Coming!
Quietly.
No, this is hard to act.
Hanyu, act out that one.
The one where the chair turns around.
Got it.
Act like you're fierce to them.
And then be especially gentle to me.
Okay.
Be especially nice to me.
Be fierce to us.
Is that right?
Look at you all,
laughing and joking all day at work,
not acting serious at all.
What are you doing?
Why does the company even keep you around?
If you can't do your job well,
then pack up and leave tomorrow.
Except you.
You even managed to catch a "Qiaozui" for me.
You're really good at acting.
It's him.
He's too good, isn't he?
How can you play this kind of role?
Why are they treating you like this?
I've played it before.
That's right.
Zeng Hui, come here for a moment.
Has Zeng Hui ever played a similar role?
I'm just saying,
finally there's a chance.
Here it comes.
Give it a try.
Then I'll try a different way of acting.
Sure.
Are we still employees?
Yes.
Is this about us?
Okay.
Come on.
Do you know what time it is?
You're late to work every day.
If this keeps up,
you'll be packing your things and leaving.
Come on.
Hurry up.
What's wrong?
Let me tell you all something.
Whoever takes good care of her
will get a raise from me.
So that's how it is.
None of you chose correctly.
You totally don't get it.
That's a clever move.
Okay, um...
So, Mengjie,
the way they just acted it out,
is that what you imagined
for Bubble's character?
It's an answer I didn't expect.
Mengjie,
why do you think
A is the one you most want to pursue?
The head of the group is so rich.
So you have your eye on the head of the group.
You don't care what he did before.
Is that right?
That's very straightforward.
Because one is a bodyguard,
one is a loyal follower,
one is henpecked,
and this one is the head of the group.
You didn't care about the previous parts at all.
What was written before doesn't matter.
The earlier ones really aren't worth much.
In the future, I'll be the next one in charge.
Alright.
Boss lady.
That's right.