Alright, next we'll move on to
the first round of audition challenges.
Each team will send out three members.
They'll draw according to their assigned topics.
You have ten seconds to draw.
One person among you has a different topic and is the undercover.
After the drawing is finished,
you'll each explain your drawing in turn.
Everyone will vote to identify the undercover.
The one identified will be punished by eating a lemon.
We have ten seconds.
Start drawing!
As someone who isn't the undercover,
I suggest that everyone
draw a little more vaguely.
Don't let the undercover figure it out.
Saying that makes you sound like the undercover.
Alright.
Time's up.
I accidentally saw what Chaoyue drew.
Honestly, you could say
we can basically vote right away.
To be honest,
everyone's drawings this round
are astonishing.
They're all different.
Are there four undercovers among the six of us?
Even Da Vinci would cry if he saw these.
Even Mona Lisa would be heartbroken.
Come on.
First, let's take a look at
Bi Wenjun's drawing.
What's this?
I've eaten this before.
Pig's tail.
Telephone wire.
Did you draw a ball of yarn?
Yeah, I drew a ball of yarn.
You drew a ball of yarn in just ten seconds.
Yeah.
This is a ball of yarn.
As long as the shape is about right, it's fine.
It's pretty slender.
It depends on how you interpret it.
Come on.
This is Yuxi's creative concept.
Mine is just this.
It's a bit anthropomorphized.
It's cartoonish.
It's been made into a cartoon.
It's a bit suspicious.
Anthropomorphized.
I've never seen
this thing anthropomorphized before.
Its face isn't even on its body.
It flew out—over there.
Whether it's on top or not is just a drawing issue.
But she can draw it like this in ten minutes.
That's impressive.
Ten seconds, not ten minutes.
Ten seconds.
If it took ten minutes to draw this,
then it's just so-so for ten minutes.
Yeah, ten seconds was plenty for you.
You drew so many things.
Let's take a look at Chaoyue's.
Mine is very realistic.
Bean sprout.
Two clothes hooks.
Anyway, it likes to burrow.
What she drew is
That's what she meant.
What's wrong?
You can't tell, can you?
No.
Because the covered part
You should cover it.
Right here in the middle.
There shouldn't be this solid line.
We're so strict.
Here.
This one is a bit...
Mine looks simple.
But there are still some details.
Where are the details?
There's another layer of black on top of the black.
It's this part of it.
Like the body is segmented.
Centipede.
You're a centipede.
It's not segmented.
The pen was too thick.
It came out thick, can't help it.
That's still a centipede.
He drew it even simpler than I did.
It's not simple.
I did a bit more than you.
I went a little further.
Because I think
It usually doesn't coil that many times, that's true.
Bi Wenjun made too many loops.
After all, Bi Wenjun plays with yo-yos.
Let's look at Dige's.
Dige's is very realistic.
Those who know, know.
Because I
was afraid I was the undercover.
But after seeing yours,
I'm convinced I'm not.
You're not.
Look.
Mine is even clearer.
Mine even
shows the whole environment.
I can't understand it.
Morse code.
This is an electric current, right?
What I drew is
Right.
Okay.
Now you can discuss freely.
You have one minute.
Di, neither of us is the undercover for sure.
Ours are the same.
I think Bi Wenjun is a bit suspicious.
Bi Wenjun seems a bit off.
Kind of looks like it.
Starting to lead the discussion.
Now they're turning it on me.
Boss Li (Bi Wenjun) really does
go in too many circles.
Yu Xi too.
But
she didn't draw what she was supposed to.
She drew some cartoon eyes instead.
What was that about?
I think it's Di.
I think it's Di too.
You two
You two are really playing your roles well.
Come on, everyone.
You can vote now.
Okay.
We count to three,
two,
one.
Please vote.
Yuxi has three votes.
Dige has two votes.
Sorry, Yuxi.
Come on.
Let's eat a lemon.
So if I'm not the undercover,
but I made others think I was,
doesn't that mean I
in this "palace intrigue" game
actually won this round?
What are you so proud of?
You weren't the undercover but still got voted out.
And you think you won?
Just eat it already.
So sour, it made me pucker.
Come on, let's sit down.
Next, we're going to reveal the answer.
I'll announce it.
This round,
the undercover
was not
See,
identified.
Is it Zhang Yanqi?
Why is it me?
It does look a bit like him.
Zhang Yanqi's body is in segments.
Come over and take a look.
Four.
It really isn't me.
Wait a second.
Di Ge has been leading the rhythm all along.
It's definitely Di Ge.
Take a closer look at mine.
Going out in the rain.
Isn't it?
That "going out in the rain" idea was mine.
No, it wasn't.
Me.
Then I
I think—
What?
Then it's Yang Chaoyue.
No, it's a rainy day.
I get it.
You misunderstood.
Isn't there a song? That one—
Qingcheng.
You're very suspicious.
No.
The other one.
It's more for kids.
Don't try that with me.
I'm really not.
Yang Chaoyue.
You're very suspicious.
What's wrong, sis?
What's up with them?
They're accusing me unfairly.
I just suspect you drew it.
They're accusing you?
I'm with them.
Sis, say something.
What are you?
The pond is full of water.
Loach.
Right.
You're a loach.
We're earthworms.
We’re all earthworms.
No wonder she’s so sure she’s not the undercover.
I thought
I thought we were loaches.
And she was the snake.
I was looking for the snake.
I also thought the undercover was the snake.
Look, I drew this earthworm to look so much like a snake.
Hiding over there.
Trying to pretend to be a snake.
But it turned out to be a loach.
Alright.
The undercover for this round
is our dear Chaoyue.
The real hunter
is the one who truly believes they’re the prey.
Let’s move on to the next question.
Come on.
Three, two, one, let’s draw.
They all look pretty similar.
My drawing is really good.
To be honest,
we're just strolling around here.
It really feels like we're at the zoo.
Come on,
let's take a look.
What's in the zoo?
There's this one.
These five are the same right now.
Bro,
when you see this scene now,
Di's looks similar.
Why does it look a bit different from ours?
Because I stopped drawing after ten seconds.
I haven't drawn the key part yet.
If that's the key part,
why didn't you draw it first?
Yeah, why not draw it first?
Very suspicious, Di is very suspicious.
Because I like to draw from start to finish.
It's really not a swan, Di.
It's not a swan.
Because my drawing skills are limited.
An undercover can't lie.
Exactly.
Di,
don't be nervous.
Don't be nervous.
Because
because it's not me.
Look, the mouth is pointy.
There's something on top of the head.
We don't know what that is.
We just know there's something behind it.
Come on, Wenjun.
This is definitely a good person.
This one is way too obvious.
And it's drawn really well, too.
Mine isn't complete,
but I only had ten seconds,
so I could only draw
the most important part.
I don't need to explain mine, right?
Mine should be pretty clear.
The two of us are on the same side.
You can feel it.
Right?
Mine is the front view of that.
What's this in the middle?
That's the outfit it's wearing.
It's not a skirt.
Tang Jiuzhou drew a banana leaf fan.
You all need to pay attention.
Please pay attention.
It's wearing—
It's just a concept, you know?
Tang Jiuzhou.
I don't get it.
Go eat a lemon.
Tang Jiuzhou.
Let's vote.
We, three—
Two, one—
Please point out the suspect.
Okay.
We're tied again now.
Tied again.
Xinhao.
You're number one now.
You just scored a point.
Xinhao.
Which company are you from?
Xinhao, you did get a point.
But you can't go back to your company.
I'll contact Sister Du Hua right now.
Tell her not to vote for Tang Jiuzhou.
You only need to think about one thing.
Your contract with Zhenguoli "Smile When I See You"
How long did you sign for?
How long is your contract with Yuehua?
Senior.
Seniors will help you.
Colleagues will only compete with you.
There are still eight years left with Yuehua.
So let's see
What does Xinhao think
Who is the undercover in this round?
Three.
Thirty-nine years old.
One leg is already...
Two.
Yuehua still has eight years left.
One.
Dige
You're impressive.
Dige is suddenly forty years old.
So this round, we
undercover
identification
The road ahead will be much harder.
Failure.
Did you hear that?
We failed.
I'm going to eat a lemon.
Eat a lemon first, Dige.
Who is stirring up the votes?
Let's all flip our cards.
It's not me.
Male peacock.
There isn't a female peacock, is there?
Why aren't you showing your display?
Yeah.
Because I don't have time.
You two go finish all the lemons.
I just finished and came back.
Why did you draw a goose?
Why didn't you draw the most important thing first?
My drawing skills are terrible.
Next, we'll move on to the audition challenge.
Prosper when encountering water.
Each team will have all five members participate.
While team members balance water on their heads,
they need to spin around with a bucket of water.
Start from the starting point.
Go around the turning point and complete the handoff within the team.
The team with more water left at the end wins.
Both teams' members are ready.
Each team needs to send out five members.
One of their four members will have to go again.
You do it.
You join us.
I've never played before.
Actually, I'll go out.
Then move this over here.
Four and four, that's just right.
That's a great suggestion.
Okay.
Let's stick to our rules.
We'll consider it next time.
Rock, paper, scissors.
The winner decides which team goes first.
You're pretty lucky, you go.
You go.
Girls go against girls.
Come on.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Look at that.
You guys go first.
Let's go.
Accept it.
For our Smile Energy Team,
we have some experience with this.
You want to take off and surpass.
No.
I'm afraid it'll get my back wet.
It hurts my back.
Alright, our Smile Energy Team is ready.
So this time,
who will take the lead in the first round?
Xin Hao will start again.
One, two, three.
Go.
Let's see "prosper when meeting water."
the strength of our Smile Energy Team.
What is it really like?
Three, two, one.
Game start.
Pretty impressive.
Very easy.
Like walking on flat ground.
Why did you start limping while walking?
Take it from below.
Alright, here comes the hard part.
It's reversed.
Hand.
The main thing is to catch this part.
From below.
Zhisheng
Spilling as you walk
Why did you even adjust it?
No matter who you are
Get down from Xu Zhisheng
To be honest
Zhisheng, if I switched channels and landed here
If I suddenly saw you, I wouldn't even dare to laugh
Spin around
Really
It's too tough, Zhisheng
Di Ge is an expert
Even the water falling from above
Was caught back into the bucket
This is
the charm of a thirty-nine-year-old man?
A thirty-nine-year-old man never looks back
He walks backward
That's the end
Yang Chaoyue is about to "lose her life"
Not caring about Yang Chaoyue at all
Take it from above
My arm is about to dislocate
From above
Take it and go
Go, Chaoyue!
You can do it!
Thanks to Teacher Yang Chaoyue for bringing us
a mime performance
Isn't there still one more person?
Wait a second, sis
Let me add some water first
It's not over yet
Should we add some water to the bucket too?
Is it really necessary to "swing" this bucket?
How is your bucket dancing?
What does this mean?
Come on.
We're pouring the blue one.
Looks like we've already lost.
There should still be some left on mine, right?
Not necessarily.
There is.
Each round is worse than the last, bro.
How is it?
Now you know our experience, right?
As long as you avoid playing like us,
you can basically win.
Luckily, we won.
Otherwise, we would have gone first.
Yeah.
The way we played last time
was definitely much better than this time.
Really?
He's so steady.
Di-ge
Di-ge is so cool.
So steady.
Alright, Di-ge, let's give it full marks.
Full marks.
Actually, the results are still pretty good.
Learn from this.
Didn't expect us to get worse the more we played.
But it's a competitive game.
Until the very last moment,
you never know what will happen.
Right?
Mainly, my hairstyle wasn't ready today.
Yeah.
Come on.
All our investor friends,
Let's go.
Why does it feel like
we're back to the days of electric scooters again?
Riding little scooters again.
Let's recall the story from the show.
Thank you all.
Come on.
Let's pour water on each other's heads.
I feel really insecure, you know?
Suddenly, right on top of my head...
It's really scary, isn't it?
Does it have to be so full?
I'm already very familiar with this.
I pour water on my own head every day.
Is it heavy?
"Pouring from the kettle" on the head.
Who goes first?
Huang Xinchun.
Go ahead.
Why is it me?
Because you're smart.
You go.
I'll take over for you, bro.
I'm super smart.
The two of us will be fine for sure.
You got this!
We won't leave a single drop of water for you.
Thank you, I'm begging you.
Don't worry.
When it's your turn, we'll use a bucket.
You just...
Then you go last.
I'll take over for you.
Okay.
The first person our Affectionate Team will send is
Huang Xinchun.
Let's see who's the expert.
Three, two...
First time meeting.
I've never seen anyone get this wet right from the start.
Slow down.
Slow down, Chun.
He's dancing.
We don't have a time limit.
No need to rush.
Take it easy.
Turn that way, yes.
That's right.
Wait a second.
Yes.
Go up.
Don't move.
Come here.
Don't move yet.
I'll follow along and feel my way over.
Not moving.
It's hard for me not to move.
That's it.
No more.
There's more.
Nope, that's it.
There's still a lot.
All done.
There's more.
Leave this part.
There's some.
This bit counts too.
Look.
Take it.
Hurry, take it.
Let's go.
In our competitive games
until the very last moment
you never know what will happen.
Too slow.
With that little water, you can walk faster.
Just keep the water on your head.
There's none left anyway.
Alright.
You're great.
But your expression
Honestly, I don't dare to laugh.
After you get it
you get that feeling where you can't laugh.
You look like a game character.
Jiuzhou is playing this game.
Why do your eyes look unfocused?
Your expression is really inspiring.
Okay.
Next.
Do you really need to shake it that fast?
Do I have to carry this bucket out?
There's no water left.
Are you going shopping? You are...
Bi Wenjun.
You can go very slowly
You can give it very slowly
As long as it looks good, that's enough
Very elegant
So elegant
Not a drop of water spilled from the bucket
Because it's gone
Sis, where's your elegant pose?
Elegant
Sis, you'll do this in a bit
This of yours
Walk out elegantly
Spin it with your finger
It's fine, there's no water left
No
Yes
Really, if you do it like this
Okay, this works
Come on
Show them
Okay.
Alright.
Come on, let's take a look at the final results.
Don't pour it into their bucket.
First, let's take a look inside the bucket.
There's still a little left.
A little bit.
It's really spinning, we are...
Yes, that's right.
No need to pour it out.
It's poured out completely.
Tap it a bit.
There's still some.
You shed more tears than this.
Let me tell you.
Let me put it this way.
The spit I used to roll that towel just now
was more than what you poured out.
Alright, Jiuzhou.
You have a lot.
You need to slow down.
Okay, move forward.
Forward.
Lift up.
Lift.
Raise your head.
Not your butt.
Raise your head, not your butt.
Tilt your head back, don't move.
Good.
Move forward again.
Very good.
Hold it.
Tap twice.
Done.
Everyone, look up.
Don't look.
You're so "bad."
How can you be so "bad?"
You're playing this at thirty-nine.
Not many days left to play.
Okay.
Hold it.
That's right.
We won.
Alright.
Okay, no need to pour anymore.
We won.
There's still some for you, sis.
Just pour it all at once.
Let's just pour it, sis.
Yeah.
Right.
Yes.
Leave a little, don't pour it all.
Give some to them.
Give them two drops.
Okay.
Give us some, right?
I'll divide it.
Don't.
Take this little duck.
Okay.
Alright.
The final winning team is ours.
The Affectionate Team.