You're insane!
If you want to die, die alone.
I don't want to fucking die.
If I die, you're not living either.
Let's go.
That message you sent me earlier.
What do you mean?
I said I can't stay at your place recently.
It means exactly what I said.
Are you trying to get rid of me as a burden?
Can you stop overthinking everything?
Your 'important business' is meeting female servers.
Having candlelight dinners with your wife.
I need to please her now
so she'll let her guard down.
Then when we achieve our goal,
will you dump her?
Of course I will.
Then we can openly
enjoy our life together.
You heartless man!
Let me tell you,
I can't live like this.
Du Lili is at a critical moment now.
If you keep making trouble,
our relationship will be exposed.
I won't be able to protect you then.
You're the only one in my heart.
Then you're not allowed to date your wife anymore.
I swear.
You played this move so cleverly.
In this chess game,
I'm the only player.
Everyone else is just a chess piece.
You heartless man.
You have no conscience.
I, Jin Qiang, won't fall for this.
Du Lili.
If you want to fight to the bitter end,
you can leave right now.
Ping'an, are you all okay?
Remember your wedding night,
when you told Lin Jing
that marrying her was your greatest joy in life?
Now I want to ask you,
do you regret marrying her?
How do you know all this?
Did she tell you?
Let me give you one last piece of news.
Your shares in Lüye Group
have all been confiscated.
The Jin family's business chain has been broken.
Bankruptcy is imminent.
I should have
strangled you back then.
Everything is over now.
Let's go.
Does it still hurt?
It's just a minor wound.
Nothing serious.
Jin Qiang schemed everything
but ended up losing everything.
The same goes for Du Lili.
The law will give them the punishment they deserve.
Jin Qiang has reached this point
with no way to turn back.
From now on,
whatever he does
has nothing to do with you anymore.
Mr. Lin.
What should we do?
Let's get out of here quickly.
Mr. Lin
I'm glad it's nothing serious.
You have no idea
how worried I was.
Don't worry.
I made a wish in front of that ice pillar.
We haven't switched back yet.
How could anything happen to me?
Mr. Lin
the case of Du Lili hiring Li Zhuo to commit murder
has been thoroughly investigated.
They will all receive their due punishment.
Jin Qiang is now charged with kidnapping and extortion.
Plus his marital infidelity,
we're officially divorced.
I'm finally free.
That's wonderful.
Xiaomeng.
Xiaomeng, my dear daughter.
Your father was beaten up.
He's bedridden
and I need to take care of him.
We have no income now
and we're in debt.
Your brother is getting married... Enough!
You still haven't realized
your mistakes.
You're just using this method
to gain sympathy from others.
Yes, I know I was wrong.
Just say I was wrong.
Please take pity on your brother.
Stop pretending.
Su Xiaodong is
a perfectly healthy grown man
who never goes out to work
and just leeches off his parents and sister.
Your situation today
is entirely self-inflicted.
Move aside.
Xiaomeng!
What sin have I committed?
Won't you take pity on your brother?
What have I done to deserve this?
You're an ungrateful child.
Around 2 p.m. today
parts of Shanxi Province, China
will once again be able to observe
a total solar eclipse.
Having this phenomenon occur
in the same location within a year
is truly a once-in-a-century event.
Are you sure about this?
Sure about what?
What if
we can't switch back?
We've been through so much together.
Even if we can't switch back,
it's not such a big deal.
I'll just spend my life
as carefree Su Xiaomeng.
That's fine with me.
Then I'll be
a brave and confident Lin Jing for life.
No matter what happens,
we'll face it together.
Okay.
I used to be afraid of my past.
Those memories of being treated with indifference
imprisoned me like shackles,
making me feel
that I wasn't good enough.
Not worthy of being loved.
Lin Jing,
when we first switched bodies,
I was really panicking.
I didn't know if I could handle it well.
But later I realized
that being able to control my own life
is something that gives a great sense of achievement.
I finally discovered that
I, Su Xiaomeng,
What I want most is confidence,
the courage to face life.
Xiaomeng.
When I first became you,
I felt uncomfortable too.
You have too many people around you.
The noisy social interactions
made me feel exhausted.
I once thought
that relationships between people
were all meaningless.
I thought hiding in a thick shell
would protect me from getting hurt.
But in your body,
I experienced
what it means to actively express love.
To give love.
I realize now
trusting others
isn't such a scary thing after all.
What I want is to break out of this shell,
to love life again,
to bravely trust others.
Thank you,
Xiaomeng.
Lin Jing.