Go to Xiao Meng
Only she can handle everything.
Don't worry.
I won't let anything happen to you.
Secretary Su.
Mr. Lin was taken away by the audit department.
Ono needs you now.
I know.
I need you to arrange a few things.
First,
Let the PR department start an emergency plan.
Second,
the audit department
to sign a confidentiality agreement
to sign a confidentiality agreement.
and confiscated the phone.
Third, there's something wrong with the financial document.
Inform the legal team to gather relevant evidence.
I'm an orphan.
Mr. Lin's father.
Mr. Lin's father
That's why
of the PR department.
was set by Chairman Lin
for his daughter.
It's not allowed unless it's urgent.
Only Chairman Lin and I
know about this.
I am Lin Jing.
Now is the critical moment.
I was right.
Although her appearance has changed,
her behavior habits
are engraved in her bones.
It won't change.
I can't explain so much now.
Save Xiao Meng first.
She is innocent.
Okay, don't worry.
I'm leaving.
You heard that?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to hide it from you.
It's just that this is too strange.
No one will believe me.
No, I have to go to the office.
You haven't eaten anything all day.
Drink this bowl of soup.
I'll go with you.
The flow of funds doesn't make sense.
I knew it.
These cameras are connected to the cloud.
I think we can find something.
No wonder Zhu helped Jin Qiang.
Jin Qiang is really stupid.
The cloud plate
with our company account.
This video
is enough to ruin their reputation.
Ono is my dad's work.
I won't let him
be ruined by these people.
Lin Jing,
how do you explain
The funds that flow overseas...
Hello, I have a few documents.
Please have a look.
Mr. Lin has nothing to do with the illegal investment.
It's Jin Qiang, Du Li Li.
by Jin Qiang, Du Li Li.
They not only embezzled illegal funds,
but also involved in prostitution.
Look at the screen.
Look. It's here. It's here.
[Mr. Zhu, I'm sorry.] [I'm sorry.]
About your investigation,
Let's go back.
We need to check it again.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I knew you'd find a way.
I told you you're not alone.
I'm sorry I messed up again.
Why did you say that?
During this time,
everyone in Ono Group
admire you.
You did a lot.
that I can't do.
After our efforts,
our town
will become
of the industry and cultural tourism.
We can't let Ono
in their hands.
We must work together to cope with this crisis.
There's another tough battle to fight.
You need to face it alone.
It's okay. I'm always here.
Recently,
about the Sand Town project.
is completely groundless.
We have submitted
to the relevant departments.
The future investment plan won't be affected.
The Sand Town
of Oz Town.
We promise
not only will we not reduce the investment,
but also increase the development.
and make it the benchmark of cultural tourism.
Please ask a question.
Mr. Lin.
When the tourism is out of season,
is there any problem
Is there a problem?
Indeed.
Tourism industry will be affected by seasonal factors.
But the Sand Town
is not a short-term profit project.
Not only do we have a complete solution,
we will also make
in the next month.
Now it's the low season of tourism.
How capable is she
three times?
Let's just watch her make a fool of herself.
We will respond
with action.
Everyone.
This is the so-called
you mentioned before.
For a week,
the order of the Sand Town increased.
The tourists will be waiting for half a year.
Do you still think I'm dreaming?
This is just a short-term effect.
Short-term effect?
If you hadn't spread the rumor
and ruined the reputation of the group,
The profit of the Sand Town has doubled.
As for your crimes,
I have submitted the evidence
to the relevant department.
Mr. Lin, we misunderstood you.
It's our pleasure
to have a leader like you.
From now on,
I will take over Ono Group again.
For the sake of the Sand Town,
and to clear the group's name.
Thank you for your help.
No matter who you are,
I'll stand by you without hesitation.
on your side.
Let's go.
Midorio's crisis has been lifted.
The operation of the Sand Town is on track.
Why are you unhappy?
Although Sand Town was successfully promoted,
but also brought
in the industry.
But we need to keep the lead in the industry.
we must have the advantage of differentiation.
The wine in Rong Zi Hotel has high quality.
The management of the chateau is also very professional.
We can cooperate with
with Ono Group.
and make a top wine brand.
Are you officially going to
with Rong Zi Restaurant?
Yes.
But she has to go.
Actually, you two want to go together.
Just now,
Ms. Su sent me a message.
She said
convinced Mr. Lu of Rong Zi Hotel
to sign a strategic cooperation with us.
Really?
That's great.
Mr. Lu is very interested
and Ono Group,
Any comment on this contract?
No.
I look forward to working with you.
Let's go. Let's go.