[English subtitles are available]
[FIRST MARRIAGE]
In this desolate spiritual wilderness,
[Episode 12]
I am alone, tasting the bitterness of being misunderstood.
Even if the Shen family falls,
it's better than being a traitor!
What did you say?
If I remember correctly,
you still haven't finished your studies.
Continue to study.
Hidekawa Kojima is vengeful.
You offended him.
He won't let you go.
I caused the trouble.
I'll take responsibility myself.
How?
Tanqian.
Tanqian!
Brother,
Father said "were it to benefit my country I would lay down my life".
What does it mean?
I will do whatever it takes to serve my country
even at the cost of my own life.
Brother, you're impressive.
Did you hear what I said?
I heard everything outside.
I prepared medicine for you.
Am I hurting you?
No.
When I got hurt,
my sister would always apply this medicine on me.
She said
this medicine
can heal wounds quickly
and can comfort hearts.
So magical?
What medicine is this?
Its name is...
Yuji.
It only works on some people.
I should be one of them, right?
I'm not sure.
This medicine has a side effect.
It might make you addicted.
I'll... leave this medicine to you.
Wait.
I'm sorry, Yuqing.
What's wrong?
It's all my fault.
I
didn't say clearly to Mr. Kojima today
and made him think you're a member of the Volunteer Group.
I even asked Mingzhao
to ask you there
when you were unaware of the situation.
I almost got you into trouble.
I don't blame you.
Come on. Sleep now.
Come on.
Yuqing,
you lie down too.
Hideo Miyazaki is the chief guard of Hidekawa Kojima.
They're both from the Yamato Chamber of Commerce.
What on earth does Tanshu have to do with the Japanese?
Does my sister's death
also have something to do with him?
Tanshu.
Tanshu, do you want some water?
Tanshu?
Tanshu.