♪The night breeze
is swallowing me tonight♪
♪If this can take away my loneliness,
it's still considered gentle♪
♪Someone lit a fire in my eyes♪
♪It's like giving me a guilt-free joy♪
=Meet Love in Chong Qing=
=Episode 15=
Mr. Ao.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
Tian.
I'm here to follow up
on our contract.
This time,
I've come with the full sincerity
of the board of directors.
I want to make this place
a paradise.
No.
Heaven.
Mr. Ao.
We can feel your sincerity.
I wonder if you have any plans.
This place is so old.
It doesn't have
any sense of modern technology.
Mr. Ao.
The antique charm
is our feature here.
It has a lot of charm.
Antique charm?
That's right.
I'll let all our service staff
wear high-slit cheongsams.
Oh, that's good.
High-slit cheongsams?
No.
Tear down this wall
and insert a steel pole
in the middle.
Steel pole?
Yep.
It's practical and artistic.
This compound is quite big.
Here.
Dig a swimming pool.
Yes.
Dig all the way here.
Install stages
at the sides.
Install lights and sound system.
Installing stages are a bit too much.
Mr. Ao, we originally planned
to build a children's
calligraphy teaching area there.
Yes.
Children?
You're a genius.
Cosplay.
Divide this into several rooms.
This is hospital.
That's a restaurant.
This is a school.
Great.
Give customers
a different experience.
No, Mr. Ao.
Your plan sounds a bit
obscene.
How is it obscene?
It's art.
But we're building an ancient town.
Ancient town?
Yes.
Oh.
Ancient Town.
Oh, we wanted to build a stage
for the ancient town,
but Tongnan
is right between Chengdu and Chongqing.
It's the perfect location,
so I decided to open a nightclub
in Shuangjiang Ancient Town.
Universe Nightclub.
Mr. Ao.
Is that what a big company
like yours do?
What's the matter?
You dress so fashionably,
but why are you so conservative?
Huh?
I won't agree to it.
I won't agree either.
Have you seen the contract?
Huh?
I signed it.
Mr. Ao.
Do you think the project is feasible?
Not bad. Good idea.
It's now or never.
Let's sign the contract.
We've already signed the contract.
If it's alright with you,
the contract will be effective
once you sign it.
According to the contract,
I have absolute control.
Mr. Ao.
I think you didn't see it clearly.
The contract clearly states
whoever invests the most money
will have the absolute control.
Yeah.
That's why I brought two million yuan.
I'll
invest in the company right away.
And then,
I'll become the legal representative
and have absolute control
over this project.
Ms. Tian.
You're gorgeous.
How about
becoming the general manager
of my company?
Watch your words.
Forget about it.
I'm telling you.
And you.
Forget about causing trouble here.
Throw him
out of here.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Put me down!
Otherwise, I won't go easy on you.
Ao Daman.
What are you doing?
Tell them to let go!
You can't hit me.
Put me down!
Ao Daman!
You...
Oh.
Protect me!
I'll see if any of you move.
Scram.
I, Shuangjiang's Bruce Lee,
am no pushover.
Come on.
Fight me.
I'm not scared of you. Come on.
Come on.
Fight me.
I'll beat you up.
Scram.
Come on.
Ningmeng, one word from you,
and they can't leave the Ancient Town.
It's a misunderstanding.
We're Tian Ningmeng's business partners.
Ao Daman.
This is between the two of us.
Don't involve others.
If you want the penalty fee,
feel free to sue me.
Ms. Tian.
Because you believed in light,
I will allow you
to fulfill the contract
in these few days.
But you can't afford
the penalty fee!
What did you say?
Run!
Hurry.
Wait for me.
Hurry, Sir.
Get in.
My head
is swollen.
You've worked hard.
Tian
has quite a temper.
I like her.
What about our genius plan
for the nightclub?
Open.
We're opening it.
Alright.
Sir.
I'm waiting to making money with you.
I heard
Ao Daman gave you trouble after all.
Ningmeng.
I'm quite worried about you.
I have a solution for you.
This
is a transfer contract.
Transfer the company
to Mr. Ao, and it'll be terminated.
And everything's settled between us.
Don't hold me accountable
for embezzling company funds either.
Li Ji.
Turns out that's what you
went to all this trouble for.
Ningmeng.
I'm helping you.
Don't do this.
You're broke now.
You brought Ao Daman here, didn't you?
But you signed
the contract.
(Transfer Contract)
Given our years of relationship,
I didn't want to pursue
your embezzlement of company funds,
but now
I've decided to pursue it.
Where did you go?
Ningmeng.
Cheer up.
No matter what happens,
we'll figure it out somehow.
Do you think
life has meaning?
When desires are satisfied,
you'll be bored.
It's miserable when you don't get it.
Is hard work really effective?
We can find a balance
between boredom and misery.
Yeah.
Maybe the balance
is giving up.
Do you want to give up on yourself,
give up on your dreams,
and give up your life?
I can't let anyone get involved anymore.
Especially you.
Whatever happens,
I'm always here.
Ningmeng.
(IOU, Tian Ningmeng
Borrowed 158,000 Yuan From Caramel)
(Caramel.)
(Thanks for your company.)
(I'm thankful for you.)
(I'm thankful
for everything you've done for me.)
(Apart from my grandfather
who raised me,)
(you're the only silly man
who treats me so well.)
(But I admit I'm timid.)
(I'm scared of falling for you)
(just because you treat me well.)
(If you can't continue
treating me well in the future,)
(I don't know how to face it.)
(I'm not worth your efforts.)
(I don't want you to get hurt
because of me either.)
- Ningmeng!
- (So I'm leaving.)
Ningmeng!
(Don't look for me.)
(Go on with your life.)
(Maybe one day
when my problems are solved,)
(we'll meet again.)
(But I can only say)
(that we met at the wrong time.)
♪We will have our own wedding
in the future♪
♪Will she still twist her body
in the crimson light♪
♪Dancing all you want
with the lake water in the glass♪
♪Crazy and depressed♪
♪The darkening dusk
makes people get sick easily♪
♪The heartbroken snow
has begun to melt♪
♪The blue person disappeared♪
♪The blue person just like her♪