[English subtitles are available]
I heard on the phone
that you didn't sign the contract yesterday, right?
Then what are you waiting for?
Pack up.
We're going to apologize now.
We must get this project.
Go.
Go pack up.
Mr. Gu, I'm sorry.
Our chairman said
since Mr. Gu has something more important
than Yiyu Garden,
you're not sincere enough
in our cooperation.
It's because we were really...
Mr. Wang, I know what you mean.
We're leaving.
Mr. Gu.
Are you really not going to fight for it?
There are things we can't deal with.
And it seems the chairman
attaches great importance to integrity.
I broke the contract first.
I can't blame others.
Let's go.
There will always be next time.
Goodbye.
Boss,
I won't go to the company with you today.
Come back early.
Bye.
Boss.
She has gone so far.
As a boss,
you're still standing here,
giggling like a fool.
If you keep staring like this,
I guess our employees will all know
there will be a Mrs. Gu soon.
What can I do for you?
Hello.
I'm the CEO's assistant of Gu Group.
I just came here with Mr. Gu.
I want to see Mr. Wang.
I need to call him first.
Thank you.
Okay. Got it.
Okay.
Sorry.
Mr. Wang can't see anyone now.
Can you call him again?
I really have something important to tell him.
I can tell him myself.
Sorry.
It's really inconvenient for Mr. Wang to meet guests.
Please find another time.
Please.
Please call him again.
Yes, I understand.
Please come in.
Thank you.
Mr. Wang, please.
Mr. Gu didn't mean to break the contract.
He had to leave
because something happened to his family.
So I beg you.
Please let me see your chairman.
The chairman never takes back his words.
I didn't expect that he would break his principles
for Gu Group this time.
You mean
the chairman agreed to cooperate?
I'm not sure.
You should ask him yourself.
Okay. Thank you, Mr. Wang. Thank you.
Please.
Just say what you want to say.
The chairman is listening.
Chairman,
thank you for giving me this chance.
I'm here to tell you
that Mr. Gu attaches great importance to Yiyu Garden.
He broke the contract
because someone didn't want him to sign it.
They kidnapped his sister on the way.
Don't worry.
Everything I said is true.
Because I was kidnapped too.
I called Mr. Gu in the car.
Although I lost my phone,
you can send someone
to check my call history
and see when Mr. Gu left.
Everything will be clear.
Chairman,
Mr. Gu
cares about you and Yiyu Garden very much.
He broke the contract because
he was afraid we would get harmed.
Is it wrong for him
to take on such a responsibility?
In other words,
Chairman,
are you really willing to sign the contract
with a person who doesn't care about
the life of his sister and his employee,
and focuses only on profits?
Do you really trust someone like that?
So please,
Chairman,
please give Gu Group another chance.
Miss Xun,
you can't stand it if you stay in this bowing position.
Don't make yourself suffer.
You may go back first.
I'll let you know if there's any news.
Miss Xun.
It seems that the chairman has something to tell me.
Wait for me outside.
Please.
Mr. Wang.
Miss Xun.
It's done.
Really?
The chairman said
you could tell Mr. Gu
to sign the contract again tomorrow.
Okay.
By the way,
he also said
you have to be there tomorrow.
Me?
Yes, you.
You have contributed a lot to the signing.
Go back and tell Mr. Gu
this good news.
Okay, thank you, Mr. Wang.
Thank you.
Boss, I'm back.
I have a gift for you.
What gift?
Here.
The latest one.
You bought it for me?
Not me but the company.
How can I contact you without your phone?
Thank you, boss.
In return,
I have a gift for you too.
What?
That mysterious chairman
agreed to sign the contract of the Yiyu Garden Project.
What?
Why are you so shocked?
As your assistant,
I'm not only good at driving.
I'm quite good at negotiating too.
Xun Yuxuan, thank you for being with me.
I told you
that as long as you were here,
I would always be by your side.
Thank you.
Mr. Gu.
Mr. Wang.
In the hotel,
judging from the relationship between you and Miss Xun,
I thought
it was only her appearance that attracted you.
But what Miss Xun did yesterday
was full of courage.
I finally know
why you like her so much.
As a man,
I have to say that you are really lucky.
Mr. Wang, it's not like that.
We were in the hotel that day because...
Because she is actually my fiancée.
Mr. Gu, please.
Boss,
didn't you go too far just now?
No. Otherwise,
how do you explain
what happened in the hotel that day?
Do you want him to misunderstand
that we have an affair?
I'm saying this to maintain your purity.
If you said so,
they would think I've lost my purity.
What? You are not satisfied with my explanation?
My purity is gone too.
Don't be shy.
You're young. I understand.
Alright.
The chairman is upstairs.
He wants to see you alone before signing the contract.
I won't go in for the time being.
Please.
Hello, Chairman.
Mr. Gu is here.
Bai Bin?
Why are you here?
Hello, Mr. Gu.
When we parted last time,
I sincerely hoped you could
get the Yiyu Garden Project successfully.
Congratulations.
Your wish has come true.
Have a seat, Mr. Gu.
Bai Bin.
No.
Chairman Bai.
Did you come to the company to experience life before?
Yuxuan, we are still friends.
Call me Bai Bin as usual.
Don't worry, Mr. Gu.
I did not plot anything,
nor steal company secrets.
And I won't do anything
that may harm Gu Group.
After all, I'm a decent businessman.
As a chairman of a company,
why did you deign to be my assistant?
It's just for personal matters.
It has nothing to do with Gu Group.
Bai Bin, why didn't you say you are the chairman?
I was so scared yesterday.
Is this a test you give us?
Sort of.
I just didn't expect
Mr. Gu
would send you, his assistant,
to fight for his last chance.
No, no.
It's not like that.
I came here on my own yesterday.
You know Mr. Gu.
He won't explain anything for himself.
Even if it's not his fault,
he won't say anything.
As his assistant,
and the one who knows the truth,
I need to explain it for him.
Does that mean
I wronged Mr. Gu?
I apologize.
Mr. Bai, you don't have to.
I broke the contract first. It's my fault.
Since we're all friends,
we will sign the contract
for sure.
Of course.
Yuxuan.
Wait for me.
I have something to discuss with Mr. Bai.
Got it.
What on earth do you want?
If you don't
give me a satisfactory answer today,
I won't sign the contract.
Mr. Gu, calm down.
I just want Yuxuan to be happy.
But
please don't refuse to sign the contract.
If Yuxuan knows
her efforts are wasted,
she would be very sad.
I think neither you nor I
want to see her sad.
What do you think, Mr. Gu?
Mr. Gu, glad to cooperate.
Glad to cooperate.
Boss, we've signed the contract.
Why do you look unhappy?
Do I?
I'm not.
Don't worry.
I believe you can do it.
How about a celebration tonight?
Let's have a seafood feast.
May I invite Huixin?
I don't think you really want a celebration.
What you want is me paying the bill.
You know me well.
But you said
you would reimburse me for my payment.
Why don't we do it now?
Okay.
Thank you, boss.
Please, boss.
What?
You said Bai Bin is the boss of the Yiyu Garden?
Surprised?
I looked the same as you.
Gu Yancheng
is the CEO of Gu Group.
He was born into a sculpturing family with a history of hundreds,
no, thousands of years.
And he's good at sculpting.
A sculpture randomly made by him
is worth millions.
The key is
he is really
handsome.
Bai Bin.
The big boss behind the Yiyu Garden.
I heard that in the downtown, there is a new mall
and a newly developed villa,
which are all invested by him.
He also enjoys high social status.
And he is as handsome as Gu Yancheng.
The key is he has revealed his identity
and helped you a lot.
It's obvious that he is trying to win your affections.
Don't talk nonsense.
Bai Bin and I are just friends.
We have no other relationship, understand?
So you mean
you've chosen Gu Yancheng?
Shut your gossipy mouth.
Gossiping is quite interesting.
Come on, let's eat as much as we can today.
Don't waste the buffet price of 380 yuan each.
You asked me to treat you to dinner.
Just a shabby place like here?
Boss, please be down-to-earth
and experience the real life.
Please have a feeling of the consumption level of ordinary people.
Three hundred and eighty yuan.
That's enough for me to buy groceries for a week.
Only in a place like this
can Huixin and I dare to eat with no concerns.
Am I right?
Alright, let's eat.
Thank you.
Boss, why do you only eat fish but not shrimps?
We took so many dishes of shrimps.
If you don't eat them,
we two can't consume them all.
It's too troublesome to peel the shrimp.
Here you are.
She can't hide her feelings for me anymore?
She doesn't even care if someone is there.
Boss,
you've been staring at the shrimp for so long.
I dare not put it in your plate.
Don't worry.
It is clean.
Enjoy it.
I can see it's quite clean.
I've never seen you so virtuous.
I don't like peeling shrimps, either.
Could you peel one for me?
Sure.
It's my boss' treat today.
So we must feed him well.
If you pay for this meal,
let alone this shrimp,
I'll peel all the shrimps for you.
It seems I have to
report on you to your dad, Mr. Xun, next week.
How dare you!
Where are you going?
It's going to be a three-day holiday next week.
Huixin and I plan to go back to my dad's for a few days
to spend some time with him.
Take me back with you.
What did you say?
He asked you to take him back.
You are pushing your relationship forward so rapidly
that you will meet each other's parents.
The company is on holiday.
I want to go and relax too.
No, no, no.
Absolutely not.
About our rumor last time,
my dad...
Anyway, not now.
Not now.
Leave it to me.
Here.
A little heavy.
Done.
Why isn't he here yet?
Mr. Gu didn't follow you?
I was wondering if he would come.
Don't mention him.
He has been nagging me for days,
but I turned him down.
Can't you take me back with you?
I really can't.
Surely you can't take me back with you?
No.
I really can't.
I really can't take you home.
Boss, just focus on your work.
You...
Stop asking.
How many times have I told you?
I really can't.
I am not asking that.
Come back early.
Got it?
He doesn't understand.
My dad
is still mad at
our rumor.
He will definitely stir up trouble if he goes to see my dad.
Right.
He's here.
Sorry.
There was a traffic jam.
You're finally here.
Will this be appropriate if you start work?
None of your business.
By the way, what about your internship?
I had an interview.
But I haven't gotten further information yet.
Are you really not going back with us?
You are already back.
When our dad finds out,
he will scold you for not having him in your heart.
I didn't tell him that I would come back this time.
Don't let it slip.
Fine.
Take good care of the store for us.
Come on, bro.
Here.
Take care of the store.
We'll thank you after we come back.
Remember to lock the door.
Remember to pay me overtime.
You brat.
Go.
-Bye. -Bye.
Bye.
Isn't Xun Yuxuan living with you?
She went back to her father's place.
What?
Are you going to meet her parents?
I see.
So you're in love.
Do you think I'm like you?
It's for sculpturing.
I can't work without her.
Okay, you're here to make sculpture.
You are both pure and serious, okay?
Shut up.
Keep dreaming.
Coming.
Why do you always forget your keys?
Bai Bin?
Why are you here?
I'm investing in the resort here.
I have some work to do today.
I heard from Huixin that you came to accompany Mr. Xun.
So I came to visit you.
Come in.
My shoes...
It's okay.
You are busy but you still came for a visit.
Thank you so much.
I suppose that my dad went to the morning market.
Have a seat.
I'll get you a glass of water.
Make yourself at home.
Bai Bin, could you open the door?
It should be my dad.
Okay.
Why are you here?
Aren't you here too?
What's wrong?
Not my dad?
Why are you here?
What's going on?
Come in first.
We are here to find inspiration.
Yancheng needs to be inspired to make sculpture.
It is not good for him to always stay in the office.
I just took him out for a walk.
We just passed by.
Since you already have guests,
it won't be a burden to have two more of us.
No, no.
Leave now.
You can't be here.
Take him away. Go.
Why can't I be here while he can?
Don't you understand?
You have a "criminal record" from my dad's perspective.
What if he sees you
when he comes back?
Just leave.
No.
I won't.
He can stay here.
Why can't I?
You can't stay here.
Dad.
Why are you here?
Why is Bai Bin here?
He saw a photo from my Moments
that I came back with Yuxuan and asked me about that.
So I told him.
I didn't expect him to come.
I didn't expect you guys to join us too.
What should we do now?
Yeah.
What should Boss do?
Yuxuan.
Dad.
Why don't you introduce your guests to me?
This is
Mr. Gu Yancheng, CEO of Gu Group.
This is the partner of Gu Group,
and my friend, Mr. Bai Bin.
Are you Bai Bin?
Huixin has told me about you.
You helped out
with their flower shop, right?
Thank you.
You're welcome, Mr. Xun. It's not worth mentioning.
You young men don't understand.
It's trivial, but it shows your moral quality.
Mr. Gu, I know you.
My daughter comes from an ordinary family.
But it was because of you
that she hit the headline of tidbits.
Mr. Xun, this is a misunderstanding.
What misunderstanding?
Did I misunderstand that my daughter was your new lover
or that you touched her without permission?
Dad, it's been a long time.
Mr. Gu just helped me up.
The media made it up.
And I'm his assistant now.
This has been clarified long ago.
Can it be clarified?
Every time when I drink with my old friends,
they always ask me,
"When will your daughter
come back home with your rich son-in-law?"
It's embarrassing.
Stop talking nonsense.
Weren't you angry back then?
Why are you defending him now?
I'm his assistant now.
Do you understand?
He's my boss.
Can you be nice to him?
They are all guests.
Could you treat him well?
When did you start working for him?
Since a long time ago.
Got it.
I'll try my best.
Not just trying.
You must.
Otherwise,
I won't make your favorite braised fish for lunch.
What are you talking about?
Just a bowl of braised fish...
Braised fish?
Got it.
Mr. Gu.
I'm sorry to say that.
I apologize.
You don't need to, Mr. Xun.
Since you two are here,
let's have lunch together.
Sure.
You guys may have a chat.
I'll cook with Huixin.
Huixin.
Huixin, come and help.
Coming.
Shao Jie, why don't you stay here
and chat with them?
I...
I think we have common interests.
And I'm very good at cooking.
May I help you two?
Let's go.
Alright.
Okay, you guys continue.
Have a good chat.
Dad, be nice.
Mr. Gu.
Why don't you have a seat?
Okay.
Mr. Xun,
I saw you came back with a fishing rod.
You like fishing, right?
Me too.
I didn't expect that.
Bai Bin, why do you have the same interest
as an old man like me?
I like fishing too.
Let me tell you.
I have many hobbies.
Since you two are here,
I must show you.
Let's go.
Bai Bin, have a look.
I like fishing and playing chess.
And now, when I have time,
I also go to the chessboard room.
Recently, I have been interested in traditional Chinese painting.
You see, I bought painting materials, including brushes, ink and paper,
to learn painting.
What a coincidence.
I can do all of these.
Perhaps there lives
an old man in my body.
That's great.
Mr. Gu, what's your hobby?
Sculpturing.
Isn't that your job?
I'm talking about hobbies.
Collecting antiques, playing golf and diving.
They all cost a lot.
Bai Bin.
You have an old man in your body and I am an old man myself.
It seems that we can be friends.
It's a deal, Mr. Xun.
I'll come often to fish, play chess and play cards with you.
You won't feel annoyed, will you?
No.
I've been practicing painting the shrimp of Qi Baishi recently.
Let me show you.
What do you think?
I think the strokes can be lighter.
You know a lot.
Another one here, right?
Yes.
You are really an expert.
You may draw some water plants.
Boring.
I thought you'd be scared.
Why are you sitting here alone?
Why don't you talk with them?
I don't know anything about Mr. Xun's hobbies.
Does that matter?
I don't know much about his hobbies too.
Are you angry because of this?
I'm not angry.
I'm just afraid that Mr. Xun may dislike me even more.
What matters is that I like you...
What did you say?
Say it again.
Nothing.
Forget it if you didn't hear it.
I won't say it twice.
Wash your hands. Time to eat.
Come on.
Let's eat.
Try it.
So many of you are here to have lunch with me, an old man, today.
We need to have a drink.
Right, Bai Bin?
-I'll get the wine. -No.
They have to drive back.
They can't drink.
They can stay here if they're drunk.
We don't have enough rooms.
They can't drink anyway.
You're not allowed to drink, either.
Alright.
Let's eat.
By the way, I just remembered
I wanted to invite you
to the resort I invested in.
It's facing the sea. The view is great.
It is now under the trial operation.
There aren't many people.
The point is
that I preserve my precious wine there.
Mr. Xun, could you bear it for a while?
We can drink a lot tonight.
You may live there.
It's your precious wine?
That's great.
But I can't stand it anymore.
We must get drunk now.
Don't say no.
I'll get the wine.
Don't you like diving, Mr. Gu?
There happens to be diving projects in the resort.
Mr. Gu, do you want to give it a try?
You can give me some suggestions.
Sure.
After all, I've invested in many projects.
What?
I didn't bring it.
Bring what?
A swimsuit! To go diving.
Don't worry. There are stores in the resort.
Just buy it there.
Yuxuan, how about bikinis?
No.
With your figure,
you won't look good in bikinis.
Yes.
You, playboy, have seen a lot.
My ordinary figure is not your type.
But don't look down on me.
You'd better cover your eyes this afternoon.
Don't let my beauty make you blind.
Huixin, what "beauty" and "blind"?
Of course it's about your good wine.
You have good taste.
Look.
Have a look.
Pure wine.
I'll fill it up for you first.
Boss.
Bai Bin, this is for you.
Mr. Xun, cheers.
Help yourself.
Don't drink too much.
Cheers.
Cheers. Let's eat.
There are many styles.
Yuxuan, which one do you think is the best?
I think all of them are fine.
Which one do you like?
How about this one?
This one?
It looks good,
but doesn't it show too much cleavage?
How could you hide your good figure?
I don't think it suits me.
Okay.
I'll choose this one.
I'll try it on.
Okay.
Hurry up.
I'll wait for you.
Am I too conservative?
This one seems okay.
This doesn't suit you.