[English subtitles are available]
[Fairy From the Painting]
[Episode 13]
This is the first time you've kissed me.
You've taken advantage of me so many times.
Can't I do it once?
As many times as you like.
Then start
fulfilling your first duty
after you became my boyfriend.
What's it?
Drive me home.
I've been your driver for so long.
It's your turn.
Perhaps,
you should move into my place.
No way.
We can't live together now.
Why not?
You lived with me before.
I was just your assistant at that time.
Even if you wanted to do something to me, you wouldn't dare.
If we live together now,
I'll be in the wolf's den.
So that's your concern.
Seems that you can't wait for it to happen.
That's nonsense.
I just want to be with you every day.
After all, you don't work in the Gu Group anymore.
We can barely make time
to see each other.
Then I'll go back to work for the Gu Group.
Not gonna happen.
How can I let my girlfriend
be my driver?
Move into my place, will you?
Not now.
My dad is at my place.
Okay. I'll wait.
I'm leaving.
Wait.
What? When have you become so clingy?
Take advantage of me before you go.
Well...
What if the neighbors see us?
There's no one around us now. You'd better hurry up.
I'll count on you to find Yuxuan a boyfriend.
I've been fretting over it.
No problem.
Yuxuan.
Dad, Aunt Li.
Uncle.
Mr. Gu.
What are you doing?
There was a bug here. I patted it away for him.
Dad, Aunt Li.
Where are you going?
I'm taking your dad
to the community activity center.
Is this handsome guy
your boyfriend?
Hello, Aunt Li. I'm...
Aunt Li, he's my boss.
He ran into me and gave me a ride.
I'm relieved to hear that.
I'm thinking about
introducing my nephew to you.
My nephew is also very handsome.
He is?
He's now the financial director of his company.
Yuxuan,
I've seen that young man.
Very good-looking.
Show me his photo.
I'll show it to my daughter.
Dad, Aunt Li,
why don't you go somewhere else to exchange information?
I need to talk to my boss about work.
Go.
Talk about work.
This one, right?
-Yeah. -Let me take a look.
Xun Yuxuan.
Exchange information for a blind date, huh?
I just wanted to send them away.
I won't go meet that guy.
Why couldn't you just say
I'm your boyfriend?
We can't come clean so early.
It would be too much for my father.
Besides,
rushed revolutions
usually end up being nipped in the bud.
And don't presume too much.
You're on probation.
I can refund you anytime.
A masterpiece like me
is not returnable.
A masterpiece? You mean a weirdo?
By the way, if I put this
on the Internet for sale
and say it's carved by Gu Yancheng,
I can get paid a large amount of money, right?
I dare you!
Why would I not dare?
You've only made it to carve it
with my generous help.
I deserve half the credit.
Go ahead and sell it.
I can carve another one.
Dummy, I can never bring myself to sell it.
I'll take extra care of it.
But I can't help but think
that if you carve something for me
on my every birthday,
I'll become super rich
within a few years, right?
Sounds very ambitious.
You bet.
I have a business mind.
Speaking of which,
it's your birthday this Saturday.
How did you know?
It doesn't matter.
What matters is that I truly care for you.
How about this?
Don't make any plans for Saturday.
Let's go on a date.
Okay.
Well,
find me a new driver.
A new driver?
You haven't made up with Fairy yet?
Yes.
Then just ask her to come back.
We don't want outsiders to work for us.
Making my girlfriend my driver
is not good for our relationship.
It's also not safe.
Wait.
You and Fairy are together now?
Good for you, Boss.
You finally made her your girl.
You should hold a celebratory party.
No problem.
But...
Wait. Nothing good follows behind but.
You have to do me another favor.
Let me make it clear first.
I can do you any favor,
as long as I don't pay out of pocket.
Didn't you say
every date should be a special occasion?
That I need to make preparations beforehand.
This Saturday is Yuxuan's birthday.
Make a schedule for me.
We'll have the whole day.
You're asking the right person for help.
No one knows better than me
about girls' fantasies about a perfect date.
A romantic date
requires only one thing.
Take it to the extreme.
Extreme?
Yes. Extreme.
Either you go up to the sky or go down to the sea.
Recall the past or look into the future.
Go up to the sky?
Yes!
A French revolving restaurant
can let you and Fairy
enjoy delicious food in the clouds.
What about going down to the sea?
See the fantastic sea world without diving in the ocean.
Play with dolphins
or penguins.
Believe me,
girls' hearts soften
when they see those cute animals.
By then, you and Fairy
can pledge your love to each other
and let the sea be your witness.
What is looking into the future?
Ferris wheel.
That's a little far-fetched.
Boss,
although you're a little bit
abler and smarter than me,
I've brought many more girls to the amusement park
than you have.
It's an amazing experience
when it gets dark and the whole park is suddenly lit up.
Dating with me
is such enjoyment.
Do your exes think so? I doubt it.
Shut up.
There was no bad blood between me and them.
You've never been there before,
so I'm sure you don't know about
the romantic story behind the Ferris wheel.
What story?
It is said that couples
riding the Ferris wheel together
will eventually break up.
But if they kiss
at the highest point,
they'll be together forever.
I bet you've kissed numerous times
at the highest point.
This story is not convincing.
It doesn't matter whether you're convinced or not.
The key is that girls believe it.
Just do it
to fulfill your girl's wish.
I won't ride the Ferris wheel.
Then...
You just take her
to the highest point of any amusement facility
and kiss her.
It may work as well.
Go on.
I know that.
You're going to talk about looking into the future next.
Bingo.
You and Fairy
can watch stars and the moon together,
and talk about poems and songs and the philosophy of life.
Then naturally the conversation will turn to the future.
Right?
One more thing.
You'll be grateful to me for telling you this.
What?
What is this?
Camp under the starry sky.
Nothing more romantic than that.
Most importantly,
you must bring only one tent.
You're so conniving.
Why did you bring me here?
It's Fairy's birthday.
You should give her a gift.
Although you've given her a hairpin,
she can't wear it every day.
After thinking about it,
I think this is the most suitable gift.
It's not too expensive,
so Fairy won't feel indebted.
Besides,
put on the lipstick of love
for her
and let her return it to you bit by bit later.
But Yuxuan doesn't seem to like these things.
You really don't understand women, do you?
Haven't you seen that movie?
Breakfast at Tiffany's starring Audrey Hepburn.
A girl can't read that sort of thing
without her lipstick.
So, every woman wants to be beautiful
and no woman
can resist the temptation of lipsticks.
Besides,
before you and Fairy
got together,
she must have felt it improper to let you spend money on her.
Thank you.
Boss, can't you pay for this one too?
Buy your woman gift with your own money.
Boss.
Huixin.
You scared the crap out of me.
What do you mean?
I'm here to apologize.
For what?
Well,
I lost control of myself that night.
I will be responsible for you.
Haven't we agreed
to forget about it?
And I really don't need you to take responsibility.
But...
we were both too eager that day
and forgot about birth control.
I mean,
if what I'm worried about happens,
I will be responsible for you.
You look like a playboy
but are actually quite reliable.
Don't worry.
I've taken care of it.
You have nothing to worry about.
What's wrong?
Are you upset because I'm too considerate?
No.
I'm happy.
Alright. Now that you can rest assured,
you may leave.
Don't come here again.
We're done. Bye.
What else do you want?
It's a gift from my company. I have no use of it.
Take it.
Bye. Good night.
What's the matter with him?
Where are we going tomorrow?
It's a secret.
You'll know.
I'll pick you up at nine tomorrow morning.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
I'm going to bed.
So early?
Did you forget something?
Nothing that I can recall.
Are you sure?
I haven't taken advantage of you today. Happy now?
Boss,
you weren't like this before.
Can't you fill your mind
with something important instead?
For me,
nothing is more important than you.
Since I'm so important,
draw closer to the camera.
Yuxuan.
What happened?
I'm coming in.
What's wrong with your lips?
This is the trendy lip exercise.
They say it can make my lips sexy.
Sexy?
Why do you even want that?
Drink it.
Go to bed early.
Dad, you go to bed too.
I'm waiting to take the cup. Finish it.
Okay.
Good girl.
Sleep tight, Dad.
Using your phone again? It's bad for your eyes.
Don't stay up late.
Okay.
Good night. Have a good dream. Kiss kiss.
Good night. Kiss kiss.
What's going on?
I'm watching a romantic drama.
I know. Kiss kiss.
Good girl.
My girl has grown up.
I'm waiting for you downstairs.
Well, something unexpected happened.
Our plan may have to be canceled.
I'll call you later.
Why did you come up?
What happened?
Come in.
Who are you?
Who is he?
He...
My name is Doudou.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
He's Aunt Li's grandson.
Aunt Li went to travel with her friends.
She won't be back until tomorrow.
She asked me to take care of him.
Sister Yuxuan,
is this uncle your boyfriend?
I thought you were single.
You're right.
I'm her boyfriend.
Are you
going on a date today?
What about our date?
I have a good idea.
What is it?
Can you take me with you?
You're going to have fun anyway.
It doesn't matter where you go.
All right.
We'll take you with us, okay?
You're the best, Sister Yuxuan.
I don't agree.
Fine.
But you have to promise me one thing.
What is it?
Don't call me uncle.
Grandpa?
Have you ever seen any grandpa as handsome as me?
Since you call her Sister Yuxuan,
you should call me Brother Yancheng.
Okay.
Brother Yancheng, Sister Yuxuan,
let's set off now!
He'll be amenable.
Let's go.
[Fantawild Dreamland]
Is this part of the dating plan?
Or you changed the plan for the sake of Doudou?
Part of the plan.
Let's go.
Hello.
Two adult tickets and one child ticket.
Wait. Let me speak to her.
Madam,
we want a family package.
Okay.
It's cheaper this way.
Thank you.
That guy flew out.
So fast!
It's so fast.
Are you dizzy?
Brother, let's play together.
Let's play!
Yancheng, are you bored?
No.
Let's play together.
How about I play something else with you?
It was so exciting.
I'll come again.
What should we play next?
I don't know.
Shall we go ride that?
Pirate ship?
Let's go.
Okay.
Sister,
I want to ride that.
No, that's too dangerous.
Not suitable for kids.
My dad brought me here once.
Brother Yancheng, are you too afraid
to ride that?
Are you?
Not at all.
Then let's go and have fun!
Go. Go.
[Escape from Dino Island]
Was it fun?
Yeah, so thrilling.
Are you happy?
Yeah. I'll come here again.
What's next?
Sister, I want to ride the roller coaster.
No!
Sister Yuxuan, I want to ride that.
Do you?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let's go eat something.
Doudou,
let's have some food before we go on, okay?
Okay.
Sister, I want to eat...
that!
You want to eat that?
Let's go.
Let's go eat.
Let me see... What's on the menu?
Hello, sir.
I suggest you
order the family combo.
It's very economical.
We're not family.
Good idea. We'll have that.
Doudou, order whatever you want.
Boy, you have a doting father.
Dad, I want
chicken drumstick, fried fries, and popcorn chicken.
No way.
Listen.
These are all fried food.
You can't eat too much of them. Do you hear me?
Mom, you're being so harsh today.
Can't you be more like Dad?
Madam, I want all the three things I ordered.
Please serve them immediately.
Okay.
Good for you two guys.
You've teamed up against me, right?
You don't give a fig about my opinion, do you?
Mom has the final say in the family.
Sorry,
forget about the three snacks the boy ordered just now.
Madam, your husband is so nice to you.
Your food will be served in a moment.
In fact, he's not my husband.
Are you two
drama queens today?
You both want to win the Academy Award for Best Actor?
-It's his fault. -It's his fault.
Sister,
let's ride the roller coaster
after eating.
Roller coaster?
Say no.
I thought someone was brave.
Beg me.
Doudou,
if we ride the roller coaster
after eating,
I may feel nausea
and...
Do you understand?
Fine. We can play something else.
Good. We'll play something else.
Doudou,
is this what you meant by something else?
Yeah.
Pirate ship, my favorite.
Doudou, let's ride this next time.
OK?
Let's ride it together.
Let's go.
It is said
that couples
riding the Ferris wheel together
will eventually break up.
But if they kiss
at the highest point,
they'll be together forever.
Yuxuan.
Yeah?
Why am I the only one drinking?
Because I have to drive.
You can find a designated driver.
I'm afraid
the designated driver can't send us where we're going later.
So we have
other plans for tonight?
Of course.
Today is your birthday.
It won't end until midnight.
Doudou,
here, take mine.
Thank you, Brother Yancheng.
Seems that you'll be a good father.
That's for sure.
I'll be a good dad,
but you have to give me a kid first.
Knock it off.
Doudou is still here.
Eat your food.
It'll get cold soon.
Sister, I need to go to the bathroom.
Can you go alone?
Do you need me to go with you?
No. I'm a grown-up man.
Cheers.
What's happening?
♫Happy birthday to you♫
You kept completely in the dark.
Sister Yuxuan,
Brother Yancheng wants to give you a surprise.
happy birthday. I wish you become prettier and prettier.
Thank you.
Yuxuan,
happy birthday.
Thank you.
Sister Yuxuan, make a wish.
Alright.
Sister Yuxuan,
what wish did you make?
I won't tell you.
If I tell you my wish, it won't come true.
You don't have to tell me.
It must be related to Brother Yancheng.
You know too much.
Come and blow out the candles with me.
One, two, three.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday to you.
Thank you.
Brother,
let me take a look.
I can't see anything. Where are the stars?
There are a lot of clouds tonight.
We can't see anything.
It's okay. We can wait for the clouds to disperse.
Let's play cards
while waiting.
Good idea.
Take him to sleep.
Here.
Look.
Is that the Big Dipper?
Yes.
It's beautiful.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I suddenly remembered
that I dreamed this once.
We stood side by side
and watched the stars together.
But in my dream,
you were wearing a red wedding dress.
You were very beautiful.
That was just a dream. I never said I'll marry you.
Admit it.
You want to marry me.
We gotta go.
Wait.
I should have given you this
last night.
What is this?
A gift.
Don't open it.
Remember to use it next time we meet.
Why so mysterious?
We'll go back now.
Bye.
Goodbye, Brother Yancheng.
[Gu Yancheng]
You finally called me, Mr. Gu.
What are you going to do? Expose it?
I'm not that bad,
but I'm indeed after something.
Come pick me up at my workplace.
Let's go out to have a talk.
Why is she in such a hurry?
Where is she going?
Mr. Gu,
aren't you curious about
how I got your medical record?
Now that you've had it,
it's meaningless to ask that question.
I was surprised
that Mr. Gu, who has always been acclaimed as a sculptural genius,
actually can't carve.
If word gets out,
there'll be a big stir.
I've recovered.
You've just recovered.
You're yet not as skilled as you were, right?
Just say it.
What's your asking price?
It's simple.
I want you to leave Xun Yuxuan
and be with me.