[English subtitles are available]
[Fairy From the Painting]
[Episode 20]
I'm with your brother now.
Good for you, Yao Yuan.
I'm your sister,
but you didn't tell me anything about her.
I'm telling you now.
What kind of attitude is that?
You're no longer that endearing boy after you grew up.
What are you doing?
They teamed up against me.
Brother-in-law,
how dare we do that to her?
Just kidding.
I'm relieved
to see you two so close.
Yao Yuan,
you must
take good care of my future sister-in-law.
Got it?
Future sister-in-law?
Xun Yuxun,
let me tell you.
Although I'm dating your brother,
you can't call me that.
Okay, future sister-in-law.
Brother-in-law,
isn't the Gu Group
a sculpture company?
Why did you invest in the theater?
Because I have a business mind,
and
Yuxuan can dance now.
What?
Xun Yuxuan can dance now?
You've overcome your mental barriers?
Yeah.
I had someone to help me.
By the way,
after the main performance tonight,
I'll do a solo dance.
Do you want to watch it?
Brother-in-law,
is it true?
Of course.
Just wait to see
your sister's beautiful and elegant dance.
Beauty is in the eyes of the beholder.
In my brother-in-law's eyes,
you're the prettiest no matter what.
However,
you can't be more beautiful than my Wanning.
So gooey.
Just go eat.
Let's eat.
Are you ready?
Feed me.
I'm a little nervous.
Eat this.
Boss, everything is ready.
We can do it tonight.
If you fail again,
you know
the consequence.
Boss, don't worry.
Nothing will go wrong this time.
I didn't know you were coming back.
Have you eaten?
What are you going to do this time?
What are you talking about?
Running the company has kept me busy enough.
You'd better not do anything irreparable.
I won't cover for you this time.
You...
I only saw you dance when I was young.
It's been over ten years.
Yuxuan,
don't be nervous on the stage.
Relax.
Why do I feel that you are more nervous than me?
That's not true.
I'm happy for you.
-Okay. -Fairy.
What are you doing here?
Fairy,
are you ready for it?
Don't be nervous.
Just relax and dance.
We are the only audience.
We won't laugh at you.
You two are really a perfect match.
You said the same words to comfort me.
Huixin.
I need to use the bathroom.
Huixin, have you made your decision?
Didn't you claim
to know all about women?
What?
Kissing me has made you a coward?
Do you mean you agree?
I didn't say that.
I'm going to the bathroom too.
Yuxuan, wait for me.
What did she mean?
Looks like I stand a chance.
You're leaving already?
Yes.
I need to go back
to sort out the interview draft.
Stay.
It's so late now.
Don't you want to watch
Xun Yuxuan's solo dance?
I'm not interested.
She's my sister.
I'm worried about her.
But you haven't called me sister in a long time.
Call me that now.
You are my girlfriend.
I don't want to call you that.
You sure?
I gotta go.
Wanning.
Sister.
What did you say?
I didn't hear you clearly.
Sister.
Don't be so perfunctory. Say it again.
Fine.
Sister.
Again.
Sister!
Sorry to interrupt.
Yao Yuan,
seems that you enjoy calling her sister very much.
Xun Yuxuan,
don't you sneak up on us again.
You no longer care about your sister after you got a girlfriend.
Xun Yuxuan,
are you sure you can dance later?
Yao Yuan is worried about you.
I'm not.
Don't worry.
I'll be fine. I'm 100 percent sure of it.
Good.
Yao Yuan will film it for you.
It'll be a memorable moment.
Thank you, future sister-in-law.
I told you not to call me that.
Alright.
Go sit down.
-I'll be on stage very soon. -Let's go.
Good luck.
[Dance Drama The Fairy]
Yuxuan!
-Boss! -Xun Yuxuan!
Yancheng.
Gu Yancheng!
Gu Yancheng! Gu Yancheng!
Wake up, Gu Yancheng!
Boss, we made it.
Gu Yancheng, are you alright? Gu Yancheng!
Wake up!
Doctor.
How is he?
We performed the surgery
and he's temporarily out of danger.
But...
But what?
The hit caused certain damage to his brain.
His life is not in danger,
but the rest
depends on how well he can recover.
So you mean
he may not wake up?
It's possible.
Even if he wakes up,
chances are that there'll be damage left.
Thank you, doctor.
Gu Yancheng.
Gu Yancheng, you must wake up. Do you hear me?
You promised
that we would be together forever.
I've already lost one of my closest family.
I can't lose you too.
You...
You can sense it when I'm in danger, right?
Do you know
how scared I am now?
Gu Yancheng,
I beg you.
Please wake up.
Okay?
Wake up, okay?
Muyu,
stay with her.
I'll take care of her, Grandpa.
Muyu, what should I do?
What should I do?
Sir, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Look into this accident immediately.
Find out whether it was an accident or someone was behind it.
Go.
[Entertainment News]
[The heir of the Gu Group was severely injured in an accident and hasn't woken up yet.]
Recently, the famous sculptor Gu Yancheng was injured in an accident.
Our reporter asked for more information from the Gu Group,
but there is no response for now.
Find out
where is the theater where Gu Yancheng got injured.
Yes.
I know you.
You're a neat freak.
You have an obsession with cleanliness.
You should wake up and see yourself.
I'm wiping your hand,
but I'm doing it carelessly.
Please wake up soon, will you?
Here. The doctor said
you should drink enough water.
Come on.
Be good.
Drink it.
Just one sip.
You cared a great deal about
your appearance, didn't you?
You'd better wake up and look at yourself.
You're not handsome at all now.
Today,
I'll help you.
You must wake up tomorrow
and drink the water yourself.
Do you hear me?
If this continues,
before Gu Yancheng wakes up,
she'll collapse.
You're right.
I haven't told my dad about this.
Then don't tell him.
He'd be worried sick.
This accident was a big blow to my sister,
just like the accident that took our mother.
Don't worry.
Gu Yancheng will wake up.
I know him.
He's a strong-willed person.
I believe
they can get through this.
Well,
go back to the company. They need you.
I'll stay here.
I'll come back to help you after work.
I'll ask my dad
to contact
famous brain doctors at home and abroad
to see if there's any solution.
Wanning, thank you.
Dummy.
We're family.
I'm leaving then.
You scared me.
Why did you come back suddenly?
Why didn't you turn on the lights?
If you hadn't done anything bad,
you wouldn't have to live with your conscience.
What do you mean?
Don't talk to your mom like that.
You know why Gu Yancheng got injured, don't you?
[The heir of the Gu Group got severely injured in an accident and hasn't woken up yet.]
It's the headline news.
Everyone knows about it.
You know that's not what I meant.
Shouldn't you explain to me
what you said to that guy the other day?
After the last time I saw him,
Muyu was kidnapped.
Soon after I saw him this time, Gu Yancheng was injured.
Mom,
were you behind it?
How can you question me like this?
I'm your mother.
Answer me!
What if I say yes?
What if I say no?
Mom!
Why can't you just let it go?
For the Wei Group,
you would do anything,
even hurt innocent people?
Is it really worth it?
If it was really you,
turn yourself in.
Then I'll still be your son.
What if I refuse?
Are you going to
cut ties with me for outsiders?
Yes.
You...
Don't you know why I did that?
I did it for you!
You really disappointed me.
For me?
For me. For me!
You've been using me as an excuse since I was young.
When I was a boy,
I didn't perform as well as Gu Yancheng in school.
You said I was too useless
to take over the Wei Group,
so I tried my best to catch up with Gu Yancheng.
I even regarded him as my enemy.
We could have been friends.
Because of you,
we drifted apart.
I like Muyu,
but I have to reject her
and hurt her again and again.
Because of you,
I can't be with the one I love.
Mom,
be honest with yourself.
Are you really doing this for me?
It's for your own vanity and desire!
You would do anything
as long as the Wei Group would benefit from it.
You hurt me.
You also hurt other innocent people.
I hurt you?
All that I've done for the Wei Group
is for you!
If it weren't for me,
the Wei Group wouldn't be what it is today.
the Wei Group would have been in someone else's hands.
I know it's not been easy for you.
That's why I've always done as you said.
But now the Wei Group
is under your control.
No one can take it away.
Be greedy if you want,
but I'll no longer be your pawn.
I like sculpting
not because I want to win prizes.
If Gu Yancheng doesn't wake up,
I will withdraw
from the competition for Golden Sculpture Award.
You...
I dare you!
Let go,
Chairwoman Liu.
Otherwise, you will lose your son forever.
Why can't you understand me?
Why can't you understand why I did all those things?
Did I...
Did I really do something wrong?
Is it my fault?
What did I do wrong?
I did something wrong?
Yuxuan, look what I brought you.
Yuxuan, listen to me.
If Gu Yancheng knows you wouldn't eat,
he will be worried.
I found a beautiful place in the yard.
Let's eat there, okay?
Let's go.
You keep an eye out for him.
Yuxuan.
Are you okay, Yuxuan? Yuxuan!
Go get the doctor.
I'll go get the doctor.
Yuxuan.
Yuxuan, what's the matter with you?
Don't scare me, Yuxuan.
-Doctor. -Yuxuan.
Yuxuan! Yuxuan!
Wake up, Yuxuan.
Grandpa, don't worry.
My sister will wake up.
Yuxuan.
You're awake.
Grandpa.
Yuxuan is awake.
She's awake.
Okay.
Good.
Grandpa.
Silly girl.
Promise me
to take care of yourself.
Yancheng hasn't woken up yet.
If you fall ill too at this moment,
I won't be able to take it.
Sorry, Grandpa.
Sorry for worrying you.
It's okay.
I'll have someone
to keep you company round the clock.
Go back and have a good rest.
Don't come back here
until you feel much better.
Grandpa,
let me stay here and take care of Yancheng.
I'll have my meals
and sleep on time.
I want to be the first person Yancheng sees
when he wakes up.
I've been to the hospital.
The Gu family is very cautious this time.
There are bodyguards inside and outside.
Irrelevant people are not allowed to go near the ward.
I've asked around.
Mr. Gu is still unconscious.
What about Yuxuan?
She has been taking care of Mr. Gu in the hospital.
Seems that she never left.
No wonder she didn't reply to any of my messages.
Gu Yancheng
is the only one in her mind now.
President,
do I still need to contact the Gu Group
and tell them you want to pay a visit?
No need.
Go back to work.
Yes.
I saw the news
and wanted to visit Gu Yancheng.
I was walking by and saw you.
Is he okay?
He's fine.
Sorry.
I haven't checked my messages lately.
Are you okay?
If you need any help,
you can tell me.
I know a brain specialist.
It's time to change Gu Yancheng's dressing.
I have to keep an eye on him.
I'm leaving.
Recently,
reporters visited
the set of The Light Chaser, a movie starring Gu Muyu.
Gu Muyu danced in the rain
and amazed everyone there.
Yancheng,
do you hear how great Muyu is?
After you wake up,
we can
watch her new movie together.
Have you heard that?
That patient woke up just now.
Of course.
He's the heir of the Gu Group.
He's so handsome.
Yuxuan, did you hear what they said?
Wait for me!
Yancheng!
Gu Yancheng.
You're finally awake.
Doctor, how is he?
Now that he woke up, he's fine.
But he needs to stay in the hospital for further observation.
We need to see if there are any residual problems.
Okay. Thank you, doctor.
Gu Yancheng.
You're finally awake.
You...
Miss, don't fling yourself at me like this.
Grandpa sent you here, right?
Gu Yancheng,
are you kidding me?
This joke is not funny at all.
Please behave yourself.
Your mission has failed.
I'm not interested in women now.
You...
don't remember me?
Why would I remember you?
It's me, Xun Yuxuan.
Never heard of that name.
Doctor.
Doctor, please check on him again.
Don't worry.
We'll give him
a thorough examination immediately.
Thank you, doctor.
Okay.
Thank you.
I wanted to ask this just now.
Why am I in the hospital?
What happened?
Yancheng,
can you recognize me?
Grandpa, I'm not stupid.
What about me?
Is this your girlfriend?
You remember?
Miss,
take my advice.
Stay away from him.
He's not a good man.
Miss? She's Huixin.
You had so many girlfriends.
I can't remember all their names.
Think hard. Who is she?
I don't know her.
How could you forget her?
She is Xun Yuxuan.
You...
Huixin.
Forget it.
It's not his fault.
Grandpa,
you guys must have a lot to talk about.
I'm going out for some fresh air.
Yuxuan. Yuxuan.
Yancheng,
are you okay?
Grandpa, I'm fine.
Yuxuan, are you okay?
Huixin,
I'm not fine at all.
My heart really hurts.
I feel so sad.
Gu Yancheng remembers everyone
except me.
It's as if I was completely erased
from his world.
You know what?
I'm so scared
that he never loved me.
That's nonsense.
Everyone could see that Gu Yancheng loved you so much.
He risked his life to protect you.
By the way,
he forgot me too.
Could it be
that he's lost the memories after a certain time?
Think about it.
When he woke up, he thought it was Grandpa who sent you here.
When did that thing happen?
It was before you knew him.
This proves that he only remembers
things before you met him.
The memories after that were damaged
or haven't recovered yet.
You're right.
I don't believe it's all fake.
I will make him remember me.
Good girl,
I support you.
Grandpa.
Yuxuan,
I know you feel heartbroken.
I was worried that you would give up.
Looks like I was overthinking it.
Yuxuan,
how do you want me to support you?
Tell me.
I'll arrange everything for you.
Thank you, Grandpa.
I've figured out what to do.
Okay.
Boss, the discharge procedures are done.
Mr. Gu.
Are you the new driver Grandpa hired?
Yes, Mr. Gu.
My name is Xun Yuxuan.
Are you so hellbent on getting close to me?
I don't need you to be my driver.
Let's get to know each other again.
My name is Xun Yuxuan.
From now on,
I'm your personal driver.
I don't need you to be my driver.
Even if you can't remember me,
you haven't changed a bit.
What did you say?
Nothing.
Mr. Gu,
from now on,
I'm an employee of the Gu Group.
I can't just leave.
I'll go get something from the trunk.
Since you can sense it when I'm in danger,
I'll let you feel
what destiny is.
The Gu Group won't accept
someone who can't even walk steadily.
How could you say that?
Are you trying to blackmail me?
No.
Grandpa hired an idiot.
How is it?
Is everything going well?
Do I look like everything is going well?
It may be hard at first,
but don't give up.
He really didn't rush over to protect you?
It's strange.
He said
he could sense it when I was in danger.
Has that accident
affected the connections between you and him?
What are you going to do next?
I have plan B.
Fight fire with fire.
What's wrong with me?
I'll wait for you outside.
How did you get in?
What do you want?
Have you noticed
that I look a little different today?
Yeah.
What changed?
You are even more unabashed.
Forget it.
I shouldn't push him so hard.
I should do it step by step.
Mr. Gu,
I'm sorry.
I was too rude.
I'll leave now.
Wait.
Anything I can do for you?
As an employee of the Gu Group,
you should always look neat and clean.
Your hair shouldn't be unkempt.
Tie your hair when you go to work next time.
Yuxuan,
don't be sad.
He didn't mean it.
I'm not sad.
I'm very happy.
He has forgotten me,
but
he's still the man he used to be.
I'm confident
to bring back his memory.
I'm relieved
to hear you say that.
Well,
I'll leave and think about
what else I can do.
I'm leaving.
Who is that woman?
Do I really know her?
See for yourself.
These things belong to that woman?
It's very weird
that you loved Yuxuan so much
but you lost your memories
about her.
I found it weird too.
She does look like...
The Flying Fairy?
Yes.
So I think
this must be Grandpa's plan.
It seems that Yuxuan is right.
Although you lost some memories,
you haven't changed a bit.
Maybe
this is a test given to you and her by God.
I never knew you believed in God.
Don't snort.
We'll see about that.
By the way,
the competition for Golden Sculpture Award is approaching, right?
Yes.
Time is running out.
You'd been preparing for it before you were hospitalized.
It's okay.
Anyway, Elegant Gathering is almost done.
Elegant Gathering?
It seems
that you lost more memories than we thought.
Your time stopped before the 7th Golden Sculpture Award.
What's wrong with that?
That was five years ago.
You're going to attend the eighth competition.
Did I win the seventh award?
Yes.
Good.
Anyway, I'll win the award this time as well.
But before that...
The car...
Never mind.
Anyway, be careful when you drive.
What does that have to do with sculpting?
I have a personal driver.
Right. How could I forget that?
You have your muse.
What are you talking about?
I've decided
to spend all my time sculpting.
Start from tomorrow.
Okay.
But boss,
I have to give you a piece of advice.
Be good to your driver.
Otherwise, you'll regret it.
If you don't care about what you put her through now,
it'll be hard as hell when you try to win her heart back.
Mrs. Liu,
long time no see.
Yes, Mr. Gu.
Long time no see.
You should know
why I invited you here today.
My granddaughter was kidnapped.
My grandson and granddaughter-in-law are having a hard time.
You are the one to blame
for these things, right?
Mr. Gu,
there must be a misunderstanding.
Stop playing innocent.
I am innocent.
Do you have any evidence
for your accusation?
Evidence?