[English subtitles are available]
I had a strange dream.
I was worried.
Is it still the dream
of the ancient woman?
Help!
Help me!
Let us out!
It's the girl I told you about.
I dreamed of her.
She seemed to be in danger. She was asking for help.
I don't know if this will happen.
Or why it happened.
After all,
I had once dreamed of a fairy.
Then,
someone who looks exactly like her appeared.
Freud believes
all dreams
are a form of wish-fulfilment.
It's an expression of your inner subconscious.
So this dream
represents my innermost thoughts and feelings.
Maybe you don't want to admit it,
but your heart is reminding you
that you care about her more than you think.
Not bad.
Every picture is good,
right?
Go back and create a copy for us.
I have to edit the photos and take selfies.
This is exploitation of labor.
You punk.
Didn't you buy your camera with my money?
Fine.
I'll go home and edit the photos well.
I guarantee the both of you will be satisfied.
Here.
If there's nothing else,
we'll go back first.
I still need to take him back to pack up.
Okay, go ahead.
I've already told him I'm on leave today.
Why did he call so many times?
What happened?
Who is it?
Who else could make a company's slave sigh like that
but her boss?
Forget it. Let's talk about it later.
Are you done?
We're leaving.
Okay.
Bye.
Take care.
Let's go.
-Bye. -Bye.
Is it heavy?
Of course not.
I'll beat you.
My little backpack.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Let's go. Get in the car.
Let's go. What's wrong?
Nothing.
Get in.
What are you doing, Xun Yuxuan?
Let's go.
I keep feeling
like someone is stalking me.
Stalking you?
Come on.
If anyone is being stalked, it's me.
Look at you.
You have nothing.
Your face is just average.
What's there to follow?
Just average?
Yaoyuan, let me tell you.
Spare the rod, spoil the child.
Go home!
Be gentle.
I'll beat you to death when we get home.
And you still dare to ask for food?
Mr. Gu, what do you need?
Get the car ready. We'll leave right away.
Yes, Mr. Gu.
Do you want to hand it over now
or fight me and then hand it over?
Did Gu Yancheng ask you to take this?
Hello?
Hello, Gu Yancheng, where are you?
In the car.
I'm asking for your location.
The company.
Okay.
Wait right there.
Mr. Gu, where should I drive you to?
Change of plan. I'm not leaving.
You can get off work now.
Don't you owe me an explanation?
Explain what?
The photos.
What photos?
Why did you send someone to spy on me?
I didn't.
Then why is my photo
in your phone?
Then who is this man?
This is my personal privacy.
Why should I tell you?
This is also my privacy.
No comment.
Do you know
taking photos without permission
is a serious invasion of another's privacy?
Do you know that if you're absent from work without reason,
I can fire you according to the contract?
I applied for leave!
I didn't receive it!
Okay.
Then you'd better fire me,
or I'll call the police.
If a man
wants to understand a woman,
then he must like her a lot.
Maybe you don't want to admit it,
but your heart is reminding you
that you care about her more than you think.
I'm really going to call the police.
Calm down.
Give me your phone.
Give it to me.
No.
No way.
What a woman...
We're even now.
We don't owe each other anything.
Let's get off work.
Take me home.
Let's go.
Hello, honey.
You're looking for me at such a late hour.
Is there anything you want to ask me?
You're indeed my little sorceress.
I really need your analysis for something.
Go ahead.
Let me, the All-knowing Eye, answer your questions.
Well.
I have a friend,
she...
Your "friend".
Please continue.
Yes, my friend.
Her boss treats her like any other employee.
But recently he actually had someone follow her and take photos.
And at the end, they even kissed.
But her boss
didn't say anything.
What do you think this means?
Who kissed who first?
This is about my friend.
How would I know?
All I know is they kissed.
Then this is not sexual harassment.
It's...
It's what?
It's that he likes you.
He likes me?
I mean, my friend?
Let me guess.
In those stalking photos,
was your friend
with another man?
Right?
Yes, how did you know?
Isn't that obvious?
A jealous man can't think straight.
I see.
Bye.
He likes you.
A jealous man can't think straight.
He likes me?
I doubt it.
Why would I like
that annoying narcissist?
Calm down.
I need to calm down.
Wenwu.
Boss,
we are definitely not compatible.
How about I move back home?
For my safety,
I have to stay away from you.
No.
Why?
You have a man at home. It's inconvenient.
Aren't you a man?
I'm your boss.
It's different.
Forget it.
I think I should take a few days off and stay in the hospital.
That's even worse.
No one will take care of you.
Well,
at my current state,
even if I moved back into your house,
I can't continue to work.
I can't let you take care of me.
I will take full responsibility
for today's accident.
Boss, let me ask you something.
What?
Don't tell me you like me?
Wait.
I'll ask the doctor if there are any precautions to take.
He doesn't admit or refuse.
What does it mean?
Will it hurt to give me an answer?
Do you need my help?
No, boss. Thanks.
Don't move.
Is your neck okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Come down after you're done.
The food is ready.
Seriously.
What does Gu Yancheng want?
This is crazy.
I've really gone crazy.
Boss.
Did you make all these?
I told you,
I'll be responsible for you.
Thanks, boss.
Here.
Boss, you're a man of your word.
But can I ask you for a favor?
What?
Can you not be so nice to me?
You're suddenly so nice to me,
and taking such great care of me.
I'm not used to it.
I feel bad.
If you feel bad,
then just work hard for me.
Okay.
Don't feel guilty.
Try my cooking first.
This is
stewed spare ribs I made for you.
That is stewed oxtail with tomatoes.
Why are they all bones?
They're good for your bones.
What do you want to eat? I'll get it for you.
No, it's fine, boss.
Why don't I remove my neck brace?
You shouldn't.
The doctor said
you can't get hurt again.
Otherwise, it'll get worse.
Do you want to be paralyzed?
It's not that serious.
Unless
you want me to be responsible for you for the rest of your life.
No need for that.
No, thank you.
Here, have some ribs.
Have a tomato.
Okay, boss.
Don't just give me food.
Have some yourself, too.
Otherwise, I'll be too embarrassed to eat.
Alright.
That's enough.
Boss, you waste a lot of water washing your dishes like this.
The most important thing is to wash them clean.
Didn't you learn that
wasting water resources is wasting your life?
Alright, hurry and go to work. I'll wash them.
Don't move.
You must listen to me for these few days.
If you really want to work,
roll up my sleeves for me.
Okay.
-You... -Me...
-You go first. -You go first.
Boss,
you look handsome when you smile.
You should smile more.
Smile will make you more charming.
You're using the wrong word.
First of all, I'm not handsome.
I am very handsome.
Secondly,
whether I smile or not,
I am very charming.
Yes. Mr. Boss.
You're the most handsome
and charming man alive.
By the way,
what did you want to tell me just now?
I just wanted to say that
you will be late for work if you don't go now.
That's it?
What do you want to say to me?
Nothing.
I should go to work.
Mr. Gu.
Miss Yuxuan. Good morning.
Didn't we agree
not to be so polite to each other.
We are friends.
Look what happened to my neck.
And I need you to take over for me.
You just rest at home.
Don't go anywhere.
Okay?
Yes!
With this collar,
I can't go anywhere.
I'll just stay at home.
Let's go.
What?
Did you see it?
See what?
The latest gossip about me.
No.
Have you seen the first trending topic?
Have you read it?
Yes.
How do you feel?
What do you mean?
Didn't I tell you?
I have no feelings for you.
Who said anything about your feelings?
I'm asking you,
what do you think of this little boy?
I'm going to give him a chance.
I know I am not going to get a answer from you. Bye!
I will have me gossiped every day. You'll see!
Miss. Muyu.
All the other stars regard gossip as a PR crisis.
Why are you so happy?
Special situations
require special means.
Who is it?
Hello, delivery.
Mr. Gu's order.
Are you Mr. Gu's woman?
No!
Sorry, I went to the wrong door.
I am sort of.
That’s not right.
Mr. Gu said
the recipient should be his woman.
Then you can see me as his woman!
Give it to me.
I can't do that!
Yes means yes. No means no.
I'd better make a call to confirm.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
I’m Mr. Gu’s woman.
Just give it to me.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
Hello.
Gu Yancheng!
What woman of Mr. Gu?
How dare you take advantage of me!
I'm doing this for your safety, okay?
And I thought you took advantage of me.
I'm not angry. How come you are angry?
By the way, I have something to do tonight.
You can have dinner by yourself.
I'll be back as soon as possible.
Come in.
Mr. Gu, this is my resignation letter.
Boss.
Boss!
I feel better now.
I can work.
How about I take it off and show you?
No.
But I haven't been out for a week.
I want to go out for some fresh air.
Fresh air?
You can get some fresh air in the yard.
Boss,
please.
I love work.
Please let me work, okay?
No.
Why?
Just stay at home.
Don't go anywhere.
Do you hear me?
Yes.
Hearing is one thing.
Whether I can do it or not is another.
Huixin.
Do you know?
Gu Yanchen has been acting like a psycho these days.
He wouldn't let me go out.
And he would check on me from time to time.
He even asked the delivery man
to confirm my identity.
It's really scary.
Are you two going this far?
Are you really my best friend?
How can you say that when I'm already like this?
Of course, I am your sister from another mister.
So,
what exactly did this vicious Gu Yancheng
do to you?
Tell me.
I'll teach him a lesson for you.
No matter what,
I think he's my nemesis.
My patience for him is almost at my limit.
Then you and your friend
really live in different worlds.
Which friend?
The friend you said
was kissed by her boss.
Look, she was kissed.
Yet you're being abused.
There are no different worlds.
Let me tell you the truth.
The one who was kissed and the one who was abused
were all me.
You're finally telling me the truth.
I'm thinking about how long you can hide it from me.
After that,
what happened between you two?
What happened after makes me even angrier.
Can you believe it?
Later I asked him
if he really likes me.
But him!
He didn't say anything at all.
What does he mean?
Isn't he just acting like a rascal?
Stop laughing.
Xun Yuxuan.
Do you know how the dinosaurs died out?
A comet hit the earth.
It was because your reflex is too slow.
Do you still need to think?
Of course he likes you.
Really?
Think about it.
Since you met him,
he made you his driver,
and his assistant.
And finally, he let you live in his house.
What do these mean?
These mean he already likes you so much that he can't help it.
But...
are these special?
These are obviously
pure business matters between us.
You don't understand.
Gu Yancheng could actually do these
for you.
He really takes great pains.
I have changed my view on him.
Huixin.
I think
you don’t know Gu Yancheng well.
But I know men well enough.
If you don't believe me,
just see if he always tries to
stop you from being alone with other men.
Also,
you can provoke him in front of other men.
If he's competitive,
he definitely likes you.
Mr. Gu,
Mr. Wang's company hasn't advanced
the Yiyu Garden Project.
We called to ask about it.
They said that
Mr. Wang has communicated with you about the project,
and is waiting for your reply.
Is that right?
Yes.
Boss, you may need to make a decision as soon as possible.
Otherwise, the Wei Group has been eyeing us.
The longer we hesitate,
the more unfavorable it is to our company.
Go on.
Okay, let's take a look at
the case studies of landscape design,
site characteristics, and challenges.
The entire garden is about 32 kilometers
which is surrounded by high-intensity development cities.
With Shiliang River on its west...
Sorry,
the number you dialed is busy now.
Please try again later.
Sorry.
The subscriber you called is busy now.
Please redial later.
Sorry,
the subscriber you dialed...
Xun Yuxuan!
Boss, what brings you here?
I should be asking you.
You didn't answer your phone
and fooled me with your lame English.
You sent someone to follow me again!
I was trying to protect you.
Bro, this is a society ruled by laws.
It's not as dangerous as you think.
Do you think you are in a movie?
You are being ridiculous.
You're injured.
You can't act on your own.
Also,
why did you take off your neck brace?
What if you get hurt again?
If you want something to eat,
you can tell Steward Du.
If you want to go out,
you can tell me.
I don't care what you...
Master! Master!
Please stop nagging.
I'm sorry.
I'm going home now.
I'll put it on as soon as I get home, okay?
-Please, please! -No!
Is it that serious?
Do you have any treatment plan?
You must choose the best plan.
I'll pay, no matter how expensive.
Sir,
I mean,
you're making a fuss.
She's recovering well.
She's fine.
See? I told you I'm fine.
It's all your fault.
Miss,
you have to understand your boyfriend.
He's just too concerned.
Doctor, he's not my boyfriend.
Doctor, you're right.
It is me, her boyfriend,
who is being too concerned.
We'll be more careful next time.
-What are you talking about? -We'll leave now.
Go.
Gu Yancheng.
Say it!
Why do you always take advantage of me?
I'm doing this for your own good,
so that the doctor won't misunderstand you as frivolous.
This is a hospital.
They won't ask you to show your personality.
A man and a woman came to a hospital together.
And they are not together.
This is frivolous.
No.
He's so good at it.
I can't get distracted.
It was you who insisted on bringing me to the hospital.
I think you're the one who wants to flirt with girls.
You sound like you're in your energy.
Quite resonant.
Then I'll grant your wish.
You can get back to work now.
Now?
Mood swings.
Truly scheming.
What are you mumbling?
I said I love work.
Work makes me happy.