"Heart Stain"
(Episode 3)
(Kim Ji Oh as Yoon Woohyun)
(Hamin as Park Doha)
(Kang Yeon Jae as Nam Jeongmin)
(Shin Siye as Lee Sori
Yoo Hosoo as Park Taemin)
(Kim Leegon as Kwon Junsu)
- What to study first?
- I don't know.
- Not sure. Math?
- Is it not English?
Can we skip math?
So sleepy.
- You're here.
- Mm.
- You're cold?
- Yeah.
I thought it'd be hot in the afternoon,
so I didn't wear a gym uniform.
But I should have.
Want to wear my gym uniform?
Is it okay?
Why do gym clothes smell so good?
I washed them yesterday.
Why does it look so big on you?
No, it's not!
You just want to believe that.
The semester just started and
you two are wild already.
Honestly, how many days
have you two dated?
Huh?
You can be honest with me,
little brother.
What are you talking about? Scram.
I understand everything.
Even if you guys said you're going to
the U.S. to get married,
I'd still attend.
What are you saying?
Just don't throw a fit here because
you're not in a relationship.
It's not that I'm unable
to find someone,
I'm just not looking for one.
I'm just holding back because
we're in grade 12.
Thinking that a friend is "holding back"
is sad.
Even a dog knows that
you're unable to find one.
What are you saying?
Come on, just admit it.
- What?
- When you're jealous,
just say you're jealous.
Ugh. This is so annoying.
Was it obvious?
He's always talking nonsense,
just ignore him.
And
it's the truth isn't it?
Huh?
We're actually dating.
You...
Don't want to make it obvious?
No, it's not like that.
Then should I go around telling
people you're mine?
- Hey, Park Doha!
- What?
You're getting more shameless.
What?
How can you say things like that
so casually?
Hello, students.
Good morning.
I want to announce it that
even the teacher finds out?
EMX2.
From EMX2 to X2.
From the experiment choice one,
place the reaction vessel for MX and W,
and let them react.
Choice two. Measure the mass of MX,
Choice three. Measure the volume of X2.
Then the experimental result
shows the mass of MX.
Then
the atomic weight of MX
is the answer, which is option three.
Next, let's solve problem number four.
Who will try to solve question
number four?
Alright. Class is over.
See you during home room time.
- Yes.
- Where are you going?
- I'll go see the teacher for a bit.
Teacher.
Yes, Woohyun?
The books you gave me were really good.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'm glad to hear that.
Did you have something to say?
Teacher...
I didn't hit Lee Sori.
I was trying to stop her,
but it turned that way.
I didn't mean it at all.
- I know.
- Huh?
I don't really believe
that you hit Sori on purpose.
You said you were trying
to stop it, right?
And I also know you're not
that kind of person.
Even so why did you...
Even so,
it's not right to fight in school.
Because you're the class president
I trust the most.
That's why this made me
even more disappointed.
I'm sorry.
I also have a younger sister like Sori.
There were so many times
I felt unfairly treated.
- Really?
- Of course.
Especially every time I get scolded.
But I always feel this way,
giving up to the person we love
means we have won.
I don't treasure Sori that much.
Woohyun, you've grown up so much,
but you're still just a kid.
Alright, see you later.
Park Taemin, switch seats with me.
- Suddenly?
- Next period is self-study.
I like sitting here and study.
Alright.
Did you hear? Kim Jinsol and Lee Hana…
Really?
Yeah, but turns out Kim Jinsol
liked Lee Hana first.
And then it turns out,
Lee Hana has always liked Kim Jinsol.
Seriously?
That's so crazy, isn't it?
They already liked each other
the whole time.
Yeah.
Haa... I'm so jealous.
When will I have a love like that?
Having someone I like
like me back
is like a miracle.
What?
Are you saying I shouldn't even hope
for that kind of miracle?
Hey, Park Doha!
Wait for me! Dammit!
Yoon Woohyun, let's go to karaoke.
No. I'm not going.
Woohyun, seriously, just once.
- Sori, let's go.
- No, not going.
Yoon Woohyun, just today!
Just sing three songs. Let's go.
You useless guys. Is no one
coming to karaoke with me?
We're seniors, we don't have
time for karaoke.
Seniors should go, that's exactly why!
We need to relieve stress from studying.
You should actually study first
before saying that.
I don't care, let's just go.
Let's go, Doha.
I'm not going.
I know, if Yoon Woohyun's not going,
you won't go either.
It can't be helped.
Shall we go just the two of us?
- Sure!
- Really?
Mm.
Yeah. I've been feeling stressed
about forgiving Yoon Woohyun,
so I need a change of mood.
That's just an excuse.
It's not an excuse!
Hey, you two enjoy your date!
Mind your own business.
Doha,
wait for me.
You should go with Taemin.
Properly make up with Sori.
Those two would probably
be happier going alone.
And...
And what?
When I go home,
I have to go back with you.
Do you have something on your mind?
No.
You've been acting strange
since yesterday.
What's wrong?
Could it be that
I did something wrong?
It's not that. I'll go home first today.
Bye-bye.
Doha!
(Time sale)
(The reason why your
ISFJ partner avoiding you)
Oh!
Park Doha is an ISFJ.
(Because you're ugly)
(Tired of the other person doing the
same thing over and over again)
(Regret that you two are dating)
No way.
Is Doha regretting dating me?
So tired.
Hey.
The handsome Taemin is here.
So noisy.
Why are you sighing so much?
- Hey.
- What?
- Am I ugly?
- No.
Really?
You're seriously so ugly.
Not just ugly,
- but extremely ugly.
- Hey!
Honestly, what else is there to look at
in our classroom besides me?
Ah, these foolish mortals…
Scram.
- Where are you going?
- The teachers' office.
Again.
Teacher.
Oh, Woohyun. What's up?
Are you worried about something?
How did you know?
It's all over your face.
Sit down.
Well,
When you want to make up
with a friend, what do you do?
Did you fight with a friend?
No, it's not that.
They keep avoiding me.
Even when I ask, they don't answer me.
It's frustrating.
If it's something that needs to be said,
they would have spoken about it.
But if you keep asking just
because you're frustrated,
they might not like it.
There must be a reason
they're not saying anything.
How about waiting for them?
Yes.
Is that friend the one
you said you liked before?
No, it's not.
It's someone else.
Oh, I see.
I'm jealous of that friend.
Huh?
Because Woohyun cares
about them so much.
Park Doha, where are you going?
Hey, well...
Can you not go to the teacher's office?
What do you mean?
If no one calls you or
there is no business there,
can't you just stay with me?
Or go with me instead?
Are you
jealous by any chance?
What? Are you serious?
Don't come.
Park Doha.
Don't tell me,
was the reason you were
in a bad mood yesterday,
was because of the teacher?
Well...
What? Is it so funny?
That's all it was?
Why are you getting closer?
I'm relieved.
Huh?
I thought it was something serious.
Since it's nothing major,
that's a relief.
Nothing major?
Was I too sulky?
Still, it's really annoying.
Hey, Doha.
I have something to say.
With me?
Doha,
are you seeing someone?
Well, you see...
I...
Like you.
Sorry, I already like someone else.
I see.
I'll be going, then.
Was I just as nervous?
Oh, Park Doha!
I don't know why, but I
just felt like going that way.
I didn't expect to see him
getting confessed to there.
That girl confessed so amazingly,
And Park Doha just went,
"Sorry, I already like someone."
Enough already.
So, Park Doha,
who is it that you like?
Park Doha.
Huh?
Let's talk after school.
I'm sorry.
I really messed up.
I shouldn't have done that.
Now do you understand my feelings?
Mm.
So...
Can I not eat it?
You don't seem all that sorry.
No, I really am.
If you're really sorry, eat another one.
I can't handle spicy food.
That's exactly why
I'm telling you to eat it.
This reduces my stress.
I'm getting more stressed.
- Park Doha.
- What?
If nothing special comes up,
I won't go to the
teacher's office anymore.
I wasn't thinking properly.
I'm sorry.
And I'm also sorry
for saying it was nothing.
I don't think that your liking me
is worthless.
I'm sorry.
If you do it again, you have to
eat it three times spicier.
I won't do it again.
But...
About dating me,
you don't regret it, right?
Huh?
I mean, since you got confessed
to today and all…
- Just wondering.
- Eat it three times spicier now.
No, I was just...
I'm afraid that you might regret it.
Why?
What if I say I regret it,
would we break up?
No.
It's too late for regrets.
Resetting things in the middle
is cheating.
I won't regret it.
Do you know how nervous I was,
worried that you might
say you regret it?
I won't.
You really can't regret this.
I said I won't.
Promise me.
Geez...
I suddenly regret this.
Park Doha!
- Go inside.
- Mm.
You too.
Woohyun, I have something to say.
Come closer.
What is it?
Hey!
Hey, take care, Yoon Woohyun.
(Woohyun, I would like to upload
the photos today...)
Oh, you answered right away.
I just finished taking a shower
and you called me.
Really? Mm...
Woohyun.
I have a favor to ask.
A favor?
Can I upload those pictures
on Instagram?
What pictures?
I just sent it to you. Look.
What is this?
I cropped you out a bit.
Why did you crop me out?
Just upload it as it is.
No.
I was worried someone might notice.
You want to hide it?
Half and half.
I want to hide it,
but I also want to let people know.
Actually, I'm a bit worried
about what people will think.
One of my brother's friends is gay,
my brother beat up those guys
who were criticizing his friend.
I'll beat them, too. Don't worry.
What's with you?
But if I get taken in,
you have to come visit me.
Haa... This is why I like you.
Huh?
Never mind. I'll upload it, so check it.
I'm hanging up.
Okay.
(Happy to eat together)
What? Park Doha met the girl
who confessed to you?
(junseo_k sent a request to follow you)
Kwon Junseo?
(Next Episode)
Are you a heartbreaker?
Did you see this card?
Your cards say you'll have two
romantic interests at the same time,
and you'll be super confused.
What nonsense is that, Lee Sori?
No.
Hwatu
never lies.
Hey, why are you avoiding me?
Don't be like that.
It's all in the past, anyway.
- What's going on?
- Woohyun.
Hello. Are you his boyfriend?
No need to say hello. Scram.
What's your relationship with him?
A super strong relationship.
Not bad, Park Doha.
Where are you going, Teacher?
I'm at the age to get married.
Getting married?
Maybe I'm sentimental because it's fall?
- Teacher.
- Yes?
I said I liked someone before, right?
Mm.
That person is you.
"Heart Stain"