ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE
Professor He, have you eaten?
Yes.
My mom made beef noodles.
I added two fried eggs.
I see.
My uncle told me everything.
How is Mr. He now?
Shall I take leave and visit him?
It's fine. Maybe next time.
Okay.
Tomorrow is our store's anniversary.
I can take leave,
but my supervisor will scold me.
Right. We have a dance
for the store's anniversary.
Let me show you!
I said stop. Can't you hear me?
Stop dancing!
Cai Minmin.
Even my son can do these moves.
What are you practicing for? Come with me.
Seriously.
I can dance without the head.
Didn't you hear me?
Come with me! Hurry!
My phone!
Professor He, I have more surprises!
-I'm not done yet!
-Come with me!
Sir, your delivery.
PLEASE DRAW A HAPPY MELON FOR MY BOYFRIEND
Is he diagnosed with Alzheimer's?
Yes.
I'll do this.
I'll search for good local specialists.
Or how about this?
I'll take time off to visit Fanxing's dad.
It's fine if we didn't know he was sick.
But now that we do,
we should definitely pay him a visit.
What?
Wouldn't you be meeting her parents?
It's like a forced marriage.
What do you know?
Fanxing's dad has Alzheimer's.
If we don't visit him and meet him now,
do we wait until
he can't tell people apart?
That's true.
I'll talk to Fanxing.
Of course. We can't just show up.
By the way, how is Minmin's part-time job?
I didn't think
that she would actually work.
This daughter of mine,
I'd still worry that she'll starve
even if I hang food on her.
Caiwei, don't worry.
Everyone knows how to grow up.
HE FANXING
Ms. He looks pretty as well today.
Don't you have work?
There's no hope for you, kid.
Forget it.
I didn't do anything.
Can't I be in a one-sided love?
An open one-sided love
is also moral coercion.
-Yuan Song, here!
-Hey.
What?
Nothing.
Come on.
Sit here.
Qingqing has left.
The seat next to mine is yours now.
-Should I kneel to thank you?
-No. People might think you're proposing.
I'm taken.
Are you still dating that taxi driver?
What taxi driver?
He's an elegant and chic chauffeur, okay?
They have uniforms.
He looks really sexy in it.
Since you're all here,
I'll tell you now.
Initially,
I planned to resign
before we move offices.
But my dad is sick.
I spoke to Mr. Li today.
Next Monday will be my last day.
I'm almost done with the handover.
So Bai can handle it alone now.
Mr. He is sick? What's wrong?
Alzheimer's.
Early stage.
We'll look for experts in this area
and see how things go.
So I have to spend more time
with my dad now.
Are you leaving already?
Qingqing just left.
Every department has someone leaving.
Now that you're leaving,
it feels like our big family
is breaking apart.
That's right. We're breaking apart.
But Ms. He's dad is sick.
She won't be in the mood to work.
Get through this first.
We're still in the same city.
Let's meet up when we're free.
That's right.
You're Ms. He's favorite. Say something.
I...
I can't be of much help.
Don't be too sad.
Why are you so nervous? You're stuttering.
My goodness. Seriously, Bai.
What face is that? What did I do?
Nothing, you fearless warrior.
Two days ago,
you searched for my dad with us
the whole night.
I saw your attendance.
You still came to work yesterday.
Thank you.
Someday, I will...
I will let Canyang treat you to a meal.
If you want to thank me,
buy me a meal yourself.
I know very well
that my unrequited love is moral coercion.
You're feeling very down
and have problems at home.
Yet I can't do anything to help.
The only thing I can do now
is not causing trouble.
But I don't want our final memory
to be a fight again.
Think about it.
Sure.
I'll buy you a meal.
I also don't want to remember us
fighting until the end.
How about this weekend?
Let's play badminton
and have a meal after.
Okay. See you then.
-All right.
-I'll get back to work.
Dad.
-Mr. He.
-Yes, Song Xue.
My friend knows an expert
from the military hospital.
But he's booked until next Wednesday.
By then, I'll go with you.
Thank you, Song Xue.
Actually,
this disease isn't easy to cure.
But compared to our previous guess
of a nerve-compressing brain tumor,
this is better.
I don't have issues with it.
I'm just worried
that I will trouble all of you.
-Dad.
-What?
When your mom and I were your age,
we had two clueless kids
and elders to care for.
We also had to work.
We were working like clockwork every day.
We had to feed a big family.
Every penny earned was carefully spent.
It's different now.
You're in your 30s,
but you still behave like kids.
Now that I'm sick,
what are you going to do?
What else?
My salary isn't low.
I can support you.
That brain of yours
can only think of money.
-Eat up.
-Thank you, Mrs. He.
Eat some fruits for your brain.
Money is important,
but a patient needs to be cared for.
You're a bachelor.
You can't even look after yourself.
Who can you care for?
Is He Canyang your only child?
What about me?
I have resigned earlier anyway.
While I'm home, I'll take care of Dad.
Don't.
Your dad is not at that stage yet.
There is still me at home.
I just won't let your dad go out alone.
I'll follow him wherever he goes.
Just do what you have to do.
Everything will go on as usual.
Your mom is right.
Now that you're sick, you agree with me?
If I had I known,
I would have wished
you'd gotten Alzheimer's ten years ago.
When have I not agreed with you?
You're so forgetful.
Chances are high
that you'll get Alzheimer's too.
You're the one with Alzheimer's now!
-Seriously.
-Mom.
Stop saying the word "Alzheimer's".
It's horrible. I'd get Alzheimer's too.
You said it, not me.
Look. You got scolded.
In our family,
no one can defeat your mom.
Song Xue, you go.
I'm just worried about the kids.
Especially Fanxing.
Look.
It's because you treat them like kids.
You support everything they do
and think for them.
That's why they don't grow up.
Before you talk about others,
you should think about your own problem.
Don't you pamper them?
You don't even let them
wash their own socks!
The only thing Fanxing can make
is fried eggs!
They just seem so busy with work.
I always do it, so it has become a habit.
Next time, I will try not to do so much.
I'll let go, all right?
If this disease continues to develop,
I won't be able
to tell people apart, right?
Listen to me.
One day, Fanxing will get married.
Other dads walk their daughters
down the aisle.
But I...
I probably won't be able
to recognize my own daughter.
If she gets bullied after she's married
and tells me about it,
I won't understand anything she says.
Even if I want to help,
I won't be able to.
This is so...
Qingfeng.
Don't think too much.
Didn't we contact the hospital
to get you treated?
Besides, Fanxing has a boyfriend now.
At this rate,
she might get married in a year or so.
You're right.
I beg you. Please don't rush her.
I won't rush her.
I'm just helping her.
Don't you also think
that Luming is pretty good?
That's true.
Hurry up and sleep.
You think too much.
That's why your brain degenerated.
Let's sleep.
Hurry up and sleep.
What took you so long?
You're still watching anime?
I can't watch it anymore.
Did you cry?
No.
No?
You can't hide it from me.
Song Xue.
I wish to get married.
You want to get married
because your dad is sick?
I don't want to, I wish to.
That means I already have such a plan,
but it just hasn't been fulfilled.
Ye Luming is indeed a good man to marry.
We get along well.
My family likes him too.
It sounds like
you're trying to convince yourself.
Don't be silly.
Don't force yourself to do things
that you don't want to do.
I'm not!
I'm just speeding up
the dating process with Ye
while working towards marriage.
I will like him a lot
that I want to marry him!
Have both of you kissed?
Yes. Over here.
Anyway, I've resigned.
I have a lot of time to spend.
The first mission
is to see doctors with my dad.
The second is to develop
my relationship with Ye.
The third
is to prepare to open a store!
You're the most enthusiastic person
in the world now.
Friend, oh, friend
Drink up this glass of wine
Get lost. I won't go crazy with you.
Come on.
Now that I think of it,
all the things we despised
and thought that we would never do,
we have all done it now.
Xiaoyu hates women
who know of their husband's affair,
yet refuse to divorce because of the kids.
As for you,
you only wanted to date out of love
and not just anyone compatible
just to get married.
As for me...
I know.
You're the only one who stayed the same.
I'm pregnant.
Pregnant?
I know you two don't want kids.
You're pregnant?
Apparently, condoms
have a two percent failure rate.
If I didn't get pregnant,
I wouldn't believe it.
You didn't drink?
I'm pregnant, so...
When I feel like drinking,
I'd just smell it.
Didn't Xiaoyu do the same?
-How long has it been?
-Almost three months.
So this was why you threw up
at Xiaoyu's house?
No.
That time, I really puked out of anger.
He has been good.
I haven't been feeling much
of the pregnancy symptoms.
I can't help but feel
that this accident
is the destiny that God has for me.
So,
you plan to let destiny run its course?
That day, I held Malty
and he looked right into me.
Suddenly, it felt like letting destiny run
its course isn't such a bad idea,
although the world doesn't seem good now.
But since he wants to come to this world,
I'll let him.
Since you let destiny run its course,
his nickname should be Tiantian.
Not bad.
No. What is this?
Does Dongyang know?
I broke up with him yesterday.
You know Dongyang dislikes kids.
I broke our promise.
I can't ruin his life either.
I will change.
No more business trips. I'll be with you.
No more socks in between the sofas.
No armpit shaver for my mustache.
Shake out the laundry before drying.
-I--
-Dongyang.
The sensor light at home has been broken
for almost a month.
Please fix it.
If life was an exam,
we might be the worst students.
Everyone is seated
in the classroom for the exam of life.
Time is the strictest exam invigilator,
though it just stands outside the door
and doesn't make a sound.
Students are chased by time.
They answer in a rush.
Some would copy someone else's answers.
Some would toss coins.
Some would submit a blank paper.
Some would think so hard,
but still end up choosing
the worst answer.
There are also some
who would give their pen to someone else.
There are
no right or wrong answers.
There are only multiple-choice questions
in our life.
And it's you
who marks the paper
and finishes your lifelong journey.
By then,
how many points would we grade our lives?
Let's eat if the food is ready.
Okay.
Are you in a bad mood today?
Why did you want to cook here?
I'm not.
Aren't you
on a break today?
After I go to the office
to pack my belongings today,
it will be officially over.
I've worked so hard for ten years.
Today is my first time
doing grocery shopping during office hours
and eat at my boyfriend's house.
It feels quite complicated.
Complicated?
So are you happy or sad?
It's not that.
It's like trying so hard
to think of an answer in an exam.
But when I turned around,
the tree outside bloomed.
So I stopped to look at the flowers.
Using exams as a life metaphor.
It's quite like you.
What about you?
Life is like a casino.
If you have chips, you have hope.
That is really quite like you.
Right.
Here's the thing.
My sister wants to visit Mr. He.
She just thinks that
we should visit him since we're dating.
Nothing else.
If you find it inconvenient,
then forget about it.
Of course, you can.
Sure.
Why?
You know my family so well.
I would like to know yours too.
Is that wrong?
It smells so good. I'm so hungry.
What did I say?
They'll wake up when the food is ready.
Fanxing, you're here.
You're awake.
Minmin, your friend is here too.
Right, let me introduce you.
My best friend, Liu Zhanni.
This is He Fanxing,
my uncle's beautiful girlfriend.
Just call her Fanxing.
-Hello, Fanxing.
-Hello.
You two, wash up and eat.
Okay!
Yesterday was the store's anniversary.
Zhanni and I worked until 2:00 a.m.
Our supervisor was so stingy
that he didn't give us any tips,
just one meal.
How many staff are there?
It'd cost a lot.
If one meal will do,
why give tips?
Profiteer.
Fanxing.
Don't you think that
my uncle's mindset is problematic?
From an employer's perspective,
your uncle is right.
Did you hear that?
Fine, just side with him.
Here.
Do I look like a squirrel?
Yes, you're a squirrel.
Here, one more.
Right, remember to like my new post.
I'm screwed!
A 20-year major bad luck!
I'm Taurus and my uncle is Libra.
We're the main victims!
We're both dead!
The last one was 10 years.
And now it's 20 years?
Why are you staring at my uncle's photo?
Don't tell me you like him.
Please! Don't worry,
your uncle is my uncle.
I'm looking at your uncle's girlfriend.
Why does she look so familiar?
Like I've seen her before.
That's normal.
All good-looking people look similar.
No.
I've definitely seen her before.
I know her voice too.
It's just like...
What kind of monster are you
to be able to remember a person
after one meeting?
I can't remember faces well.
Melon!
Look!
Don't they look alike?
Like what?
Big eyes?
A few months ago, at Yuan Song's house,
we thought she was the cleaner!
-Don't they look alike?
-No way!
What are you saying?
They don't know each other!
You could have just called
for advice on decoration.
You just want free coffee, right?
What's up?
You're not going to confess, are you?
Yuan Song.
Is He Fanxing your ex-girlfriend?
Your uncle told you?
I knew it.
On the way here, I thought
Zhanni and I made a mistake
and the girl we mistook for the cleaner
just happened to look like my aunt.
How can this be?
Our friends and colleagues
only found out after we broke up.
Are you unhappy?
Shouldn't that be you instead?
I said so many dumb things
in front of you.
I even boasted about
how my uncle got the girl he liked.
I'm so embarrassed now.
Don't worry.
You and your uncle are different.
I'm not mad at you.
The more you do this,
the more guilty I feel.
I'm so sorry, Yuan Song.
Can I repay my uncle's debts in return?
I'll break up with my boyfriend
and you can take me. All right?
Of course not.
You don't like me.
Forget it.
Then let me buy you a meal.
I'll be your on-call lackey.
If you like anyone in the future,
I'll help you out.
How's that? Do you accept my apology?
If I don't accept it,
are you going to keep talking?
I'll apologize until the café closes
and then continue at a bar.
Smiling means that you accept it.
If you had always been this shameless,
you could have taken down ten of me.
All men are liars.
You say nice things,
but you choose empathetic and sensible
girls like Fanxing in the end.
She's sensible?
She aged for nothing.
She's just like a little girl.
When something happens at home,
she would just panic.
Beauty lies in the eye of the beholder.
Do you still like her?
Does it matter?
Your uncle suits her better than I do.
Why are you full of adults' bad habits?
Love is not about being compatible.
It's love!
Liang Shanbo and Zhu Yingtai.
Romeo and Juliet.
Lovely and tragic love stories
are the result
of challenging feudal ethics.
I guess you paid attention
in Professor He's class.
Of course.
So do you want me to get her back for you?
I...
My uncle is almost 40.
My mom yearns for a nephew so much
that she's going crazy.
Those who challenged feudal ethics
have all died.
You're right.
Normal people should just find
someone suitable.
"Full of adults' bad habits", right?
EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
Ms. He.
Keep in touch.
Of course.
We don't work together anymore,
but we're still friends.
I am no longer your director.
Just call me by my name.
He Fanxing.
Fanxing!
I suddenly feel like a free slave.
Why is that?
Fanxing, be sure to visit us.
Don't worry. We won't be strangers.
She's going to be a florist,
so she needs us as her customers.
That's right.
I'll treat you to a meal next time.
Look.
Even if she has resigned,
Ms. He is still Ms. He.
She still buys us meals.
Be sure to call Qingqing.
She's so free now.
She keeps bragging
about having fun on social media.
That's relaxation.
Everyone has agreed
to visit your dad someday.
Sure.
Okay, get back to work. Stop chatting.
Bai, take note of those
who are late and lazy.
Don't let them off.
I got it. Seriously.
You're leaving,
but you're still like this.
All right.
-Then I--
-I'll see you off.
-I'll get going. Bye!
-Bye!
Be sure to visit us!
This must be the end.
The curtain closes.
That's right.
A sad ending.
Please. What ending is this?
We want a happy ending.
It will be a happy ending!
Get to work or I'll deduct your pay!
Go!
While the cat is away, the mice will play.
She'll be the cat from now on.
A bad cat.
You!
What's this?
My classmate's grandpa
also has Alzheimer's.
I asked him for some tips in daily life.
He wrote this.
I've sent you the digital copy.
You can print it out.
How nice of you.
Thank you.
If you have time,
do you want to visit my dad?
I'll pass.
I'll see you at the badminton court
this weekend.
Okay.
Shouldn't you be with your dad?
I can't just stay with him every day.
You miss me, right?
I can't stand it. It's so hot.
I'll ask for leave and buy you milk tea!
I'm serious.
Your family is having issues now.
We can go on lesser dates.
Don't miss me too much.
You wear this every day at work.
I feel hot for you.
Why not change to another job?
Being a waitress is easier.
This one pays well and I get paid daily.
My mom's birthday is coming soon.
I want to buy her a scarf
with the money I make.
Why? Do you feel sorry for me?
Silence means agreement.
It's so hard to deal
with old people like you.
You won't say it
when you miss me or feel sorry for me.
I heard you used to be
very good at dating.
Maybe my intelligence dropped
after I met you.
People who are in love
tend to have lower intelligence.
If so, does that mean you like me a lot?
Perhaps.
Right,
I met Yuan Song today.
-Is the renovation done?
-Not yet.
Almost.
Do you know
who Yuan Song's ex-girlfriend was?
I don't know.
I didn't even know he broke up.
That rascal!
Did he tell you?
I don't know.
He refused to tell me.
How mysterious.
I wonder what kind of beauty she is.
That's right.
By the way, next semester,
I'll transfer to the art institute.
What?
Why?
Because of you.
Are you dumping me?
Why would you think so?
You have to study for another two years.
If people find out, they will gossip.
I'd better leave.
I'm not afraid of gossip.
They used to think
that my uncle was my sugar daddy.
Though they're not exactly wrong.
I know, but I want to protect you.
I didn't know
that you would think that far.
Not exactly.
The art institute offers higher pay.
By the way,
my mom will visit Mr. He tomorrow.
You know it, right?
No. Nobody told me.
Visiting him is one thing,
but it's also to meet your parents.
I see.
I got it. I won't go back.
It's fine. My mom doesn't know you anyway.
If you see her, leave a good impression.
For your meals,
eat more beans and fish
to increase your intake
of soft phospholipids
and unsaturated fatty acids.
You should also exercise!
Exercise. Line dancing would be ideal!
"Line dancing can help prevent dementia."
This is good! Hey.
Qingfeng, are you listening?
I'm reading it to you.
I've always carried my keys with me
since I was young.
I'm used to it.
I disagreed
when Canyang wanted to install
the keyless door lock.
The things left behind by our ancestors
are slowly disappearing
and becoming outdated.
That's right.
Subtitle translation by
Jane Ng Sweer Jieng