Hey.
What is it?
If you have any clients,
keep them for me.
Aren't you tied up with other projects?
I have time at night,
so I can design them.
No more games?
I've had enough. I'm tired.
Okay.
Thank you.
What?
Are you two mobsters
exchanging information?
Shut up.
What's going on with you?
What?
You resigned, but you came back.
Last night,
Ms. He's boyfriend bought us dinner
and you insisted on going.
Someone was buying dinner.
Why wouldn't I go?
I'll be honest with you.
They seem to be doing well.
Don't ruin their relationship.
Well, you can be as generous as you want.
But do you have to make others
do the same?
What do you mean by that?
I meant it literally.
I'll see how long you can pretend.
Why do you keep saying weird things?
My baby is due next month.
I haven't been sleeping well lately.
Look at my leg.
Whenever I press it,
it leaves indentations.
At my last checkup,
I was told the baby is positioned wrongly.
I might need a C-section.
Since it's not under my control,
I should listen to the doctor.
Shen Fanfan only took half a day off
when you gave birth to Peanut.
Ask him to stay longer this time.
There's no need for that.
You, Song Xue, Canyang
and both our parents will be there.
That's already too many people.
It'll be so noisy.
Besides,
the ward can't fit so many people.
Are you giving birth to our kid
or Shen Fanfan's kid?
His pay will be deducted
if he's absent from work.
Adults don't have much freedom.
We all need to make a living.
You're such a good wife.
No, I'm not.
It's just because we're poor.
We have two kids now.
I'm a housewife.
If he has no income,
should our whole family
count on our parents
or starve on the streets?
I told her I'd take a half-month leave,
but she objected.
I've already submitted my leave request.
But I have no choice
since she objects to it.
Otherwise, I'd be staying with her
and nagging her daily.
All right. I know you're good to me.
Dad, I want to play on the slide.
Okay.
You guys eat up.
I'll take Peanut downstairs.
Leave everything here.
I'll clear the table when I get back.
Impressive, Shen Fanfan!
I never thought you'd become
a good family man.
My wife is pregnant.
I have to be a good husband.
Eat up. I'll take her downstairs.
-All right.
-Go ahead.
I was filming a show the other day
about a cheating husband.
He has two sons.
A three-year-old and a six-month-old.
That's not something new.
You're still focusing on those men?
It is indeed not something new.
But whenever a lady accuses
her husband is having an affair,
the ratings soar.
If you invite a health expert,
the ratings get even higher.
Honestly,
if your husband cheats on you,
would you ever forgive him?
I don't think so.
No way. I won't get over it.
It's like someone secretly
using your toothbrush
to scrub the toilet bowl.
Even after a long time,
I'll still feel gross.
Enough. Scrubbing the toilet bowl
with a toothbrush?
It's so gross that
my baby wants to come out.
You're a married woman.
Shen Fanfan is so playful.
What do you think?
Actually, I can accept an affair
if I don't know about it.
To me, not knowing means it doesn't exist.
Not knowing is one thing.
But it's escaping reality.
Let's forget about this affair talk
and talk about love.
You don't truly know
if your husband actually loves you.
Because it depends on what he tells you.
If he says he loves you,
but thinks about someone else,
that's not even love.
So, it is up to you to believe him or not.
But love is a matter between two people.
An affair involves three people.
You can't objectify love.
But when the third person
comes between the two,
they're an obstacle no matter what.
That's why I said
this is under the condition
that you found out about the third person.
It'll be tough when you do.
Which part would be tough?
The kids.
Look at me, I have two kids.
They are my priority
when I make decisions now.
It doesn't matter if the adults suffer.
But it'll be very tough for the kids.
They can't survive
without their parents' care.
You're right.
A loving and happy couple
is the best role model for children.
You're too naive.
Love no longer exists
after being married for over ten years.
Just live well.
If he had an affair,
it doesn't exist if I don't know about it.
Why be so hard on yourself?
Isn't it better to live a simple life?
We have to move on anyway.
I guess.
You're married, you have the say in this.
Peanut is back already?
Dongyang, you're so early.
-I came right after work.
-Come in.
You're all here.
I hope you're not waiting for me.
Dongyang, how long have you
not paid your respect to me?
Greetings to Your Highness.
I bought these presents for Your Highness.
That's a lot.
I haven't even finished the formula
you got us last time.
Look, these are all for your baby.
It is due soon, right?
Yes.
Honey.
There's so much food!
I'll finish everything up.
I can't stand you. This is for you.
You even took my seat. Hand that to me.
He Fanxing,
you've really changed my opinion of you.
I heard you dated two guys
in three months.
Don't listen to Song Xue.
Tell me if it's true.
It is.
Incredible!
-What's wrong?
-What's going on?
I'm fine.
I'm going to the toilet.
-I'll go with you.
-There's no need. You eat up.
Be careful.
Eat up.
Well,
it's a good thing
we insist on not having kids.
Why not?
You two are so loving. Just do it.
Forget it.
Raising a kid is so troublesome.
I don't want Song Xue to suffer. Right?
That depends.
Look at Xiaoyu.
She looks so happy with the kids.
Shen Fanfan is also very caring.
You're right.
Her Highness is going to have a good life.
Your style has changed.
You're more stable now.
My girlfriend specially trained me.
She's a great player.
She's not only good at pool,
she's also great at badminton.
-And--
-All right.
You've been showing off all night.
Enough. Cut it out.
Haven't you been boasting
about how awesome
and capable your wife is?
So you're not fighting anymore?
Which couple doesn't fight?
Right, I have something important
to tell you.
Tomorrow is my daughter's birthday.
Bring your girlfriend.
I'll introduce her to my wife.
You're only telling me
such important news now?
I'm not sure if my fairy can come
to the mortal world.
She's an employee of mine after all.
I can call her manager and arrange things.
No need.
Who doesn't know you're the boss?
I'll handle it.
I want to find out how you won her over.
You weren't together
when we met at the hotel.
We were close.
The point is,
her ex is much younger than her.
Young people get agitated so easily.
Even if he can keep his cool,
he can't beat your servile manner.
You're truly my buddy.
You're always so kind.
By the way, we had a bet.
If I could get her within two months,
you’d add 20 percent to the ad budget
for the next quarter.
When will you draw up the contract?
When was that? Why don't I remember?
Don't pretend.
I have a recording of that.
All right. I remember it now.
Did you really need to record
a friendly wager?
That's why I didn't.
When will I receive the new contract?
Hey, we agreed on a two-month time limit.
But you took longer than that to get her.
It really was around two months.
All right, I'll give you a discount.
15 percent.
Five percent.
This is too much. A boss like you
shouldn't bargain that much.
I'll meet you halfway.
-Twelve percent.
-Ten percent.
Deal!
But something feels wrong about this.
A bet is a bet.
I remember our bet
was originally just ten percent.
Really?
I remember it was 20 percent.
Now I'm sure it was ten percent!
You!
Do you have a cold?
You look under the weather.
Are you in a bad mood
because of Shen Fanfan?
I was so scared that
you'd tell everyone about his affair.
Song Xue, I think we should let it go.
They're husband and wife.
We're close to Xiaoyu,
but we're just friends.
We're still outsiders.
You want me to act like I don't know?
What if Xiaoyu actually knows about it?
Impossible.
She'd have told me and Fanxing right away.
Fine. I know the chances are slim,
but it's not impossible.
If Xiaoyu doesn't want a divorce,
then it's a possibility.
People have their pride.
She doesn't want a divorce
as long as her husband
makes a clean break.
But if you expose it,
she'll be in a dilemma.
She doesn't have the courage
to divorce him.
But it's shameful if she doesn't.
It's very hard to separate
when children are involved.
Blood is thicker than water.
They're connected by blood.
It is a deep entanglement of life.
It's a horrible thing.
Hurry up. She has school tomorrow.
Got it.
Peanut, what sound does a duck make?
Quack.
What about a goat?
Bleat.
I was filming a show the other day
about a cheating husband.
He has two sons.
A three-year-old and a six-month-old.
You're a married woman.
Shen Fanfan is so playful.
What do you think?
MS. KOU
Let's go. Our clean little kitty
is going to bed.
-Let's find Mom.
-Mom!
Mom is sleeping.
Come in.
You were looking for me, Mr. Li?
Fanxing, I'm giving you a chance
to meet your boyfriend
during working hours.
Send this supplemental agreement
to Minglu.
Ask Mr. Ye to sign this.
A supplemental agreement?
Didn't we sign a contract with Minglu
a few months ago?
We've been acquired by Aijia.
It's all cut and dried now.
We're now a subsidiary of Aijia.
There were some problems
with the old agreement.
So we've made amendments
based on the headquarters' order.
Don't delay. Go now.
I have work to do. Can I ask Bai to do it?
I'll tell Mr. Ye.
No, you must go.
I won't be at ease if it's someone else.
All right.
Wait.
Fanxing.
I heard Mr. Ye courted you
for a long time.
Does he like you very much?
We're still
at the stage
of getting to know each other.
I see. As long as you're doing good.
Okay, go now. It's fine.
Bai.
I have to go to Minglu
to have a document signed.
When the delivery arrives,
open it and check the contents.
The forms are on my desk.
Verify everything.
Sure, no problem.
You're really in love.
I can't believe a boss
is doing trivial work.
I remember not too long ago,
someone didn't want to go there
and deceived me into doing the legwork.
Sorry.
Ms. He.
I have to check some furnishings
with a client.
Can I share a ride with you?
Sure.
Did you change your perfume?
What?
Yes.
I read online
that a woman cuts her hair
when she has a breakup,
and changes her perfume
when she has a new lover.
I'm kidding. Don't be mad.
We're friends now,
but I still can't help but speak my mind.
Be honest with me.
Why did you come back?
When Mr. Li asked me to get you
to reconsider, you refused.
Then you applied for a job at Aijia
and was transferred back.
Why?
What do you think the reason is?
Don't answer my questions with questions.
All right. I'll stop teasing you.
I had to come back.
Meiyin insisted that I work at Aijia.
I didn't want to work at the headquarters,
so I came back.
Wu Meiyin?
I can't go against her.
You and her...
Forget it.
Didn't you hand over all your clients?
You're viewing furnishings
with a new client already?
I handed over everyone but this.
I have to follow through
with Cai Minmin's project.
She's my junior after all.
Cai Minmin?
She just liked your post.
Fate works in funny ways.
Right.
Then, will you...
accept her in the future?
Do you know what this agreement means?
It means,
after Aijia has completed
the acquisition of Amazing Decoration,
the original agreement will be invalid.
For branding,
Aijia will liaise with Minglu directly.
Amazing Decoration doesn't have
an independent department for that.
Aijia will take charge of it.
It is cost-saving and efficient.
That's not a bad thing.
You'll save money, but I'll earn less.
Your boss accepts anything but a raw deal.
SONG YIFAN
Hello, Luming?
Mr. Song.
Goodness, why are you so polite today?
It's business.
I've got to be polite to Party A.
I just received an agreement from Aijia.
Do you know about it?
What agreement?
Simply put,
I finally got a ten percent raise
for the advertising budget.
But I have to return it
after I sign this agreement.
You know I don’t deal with small matters.
My wife is in charge of these things.
Why don’t you call her?
Forget it.
I didn't know her when you married her.
Just take the money as a wedding gift.
All right, I have to go.
I have an agreement to sign.
Okay.
Now you know
why Mr. Li asked you to deliver this.
Why don't you fight for it?
Why don't...
you fight for it?
I’m in no position to do that.
Besides, Mr. Li has limited options
regarding this.
Of course not with Mr. Li.
You have a chance
to talk to your big boss tonight.
What do you think?
What?
It's his daughter's birthday party
tonight.
He keeps saying that
he wants to meet my girlfriend.
I've even prepared a dress for you.
Isn't this the dress I gave you?
I've always wanted to give it back to you.
You look great in it.
Besides, you have no reason
to reject my gifts now.
I bought this with my own money, okay?
Gift?
Let’s go. I’ll buy you lunch.
I’ll pick you up after work.
You buying me lunch makes me uneasy.
Why is that?
Don't worry.
I don't like you anymore.
This isn't some kind of tactic.
I’m not like my uncle, that old loach.
He's devious and cunning.
But he really was successful this time.
He must be so happy.
Yes, he is. Too happy, in fact.
He's putting his girlfriend
before his niece now.
I asked him out to dinner last time,
and guess what happened?
He sent me a red packet
with 88 yuan in it.
He brushed me off with just 88 yuan!
He must watch out.
Since he stole someone's girl,
he might lose her the way he got her.
Stole? Didn't he snatch her away?
That's if he competed fairly.
But he bonded with her as a friend
and swooped in on her.
That's stealing.
It sounds nasty but true. You’re right.
Enough about my disgraceful uncle.
I have something to ask you.
We have similar situations,
but you're more experienced.
Go on.
I'm dating a guy who is more than
ten years older than me.
More than ten years?
After having crushes on guys of my age,
I realized a mature guy
is more suitable for me.
I wish you happiness.
Aren't you surprised?
He's more than ten years older.
Aren't you curious about him?
I'm quite surprised,
but I'm not that curious about it.
Shouldn't you talk to
your female friends about this instead?
You have indeed been around the block.
You're so calm.
I wanted to tell Zhanni,
but I can't.
Because we're keeping our relationship
in a greenhouse.
A greenhouse?
A sprout will die from frost in winter.
It should be kept in a greenhouse.
When it's strong enough
to brave extreme weathers,
we'll take it out.
Our relationship is based on this theory.
We'll hide it at first like you did.
Hide it?
Even from your closest friends?
It's a secret?
It's also quite exciting
to keep it a secret.
Are you being tricked by him?
Didn't you do the same as well?
She did trick me!
For your money?
No.
Anyway, a secret relationship is taboo.
It's unacceptable.
But I think this is quite good.
Is this your first love?
If you don't count my previous crushes,
then this is actually my first love.
If you hide it until you break up,
then congratulations.
Your friends and relatives will think that
your next boyfriend is your first love.
No one will acknowledge
your real first love.
Isn't that very exciting?
I don't know how to educate my son now.
He's only 12.
He has good grades and seems well-behaved.
He also never breaks any rules.
But it turns out
that he has been criticizing everything
and his teachers online.
-Like having a split personality.
-Kids.
They can't be too obedient.
My daughter is 16 this year.
She's like a monkey.
Always jumping up and down all day.
She said after she graduates high school,
she wants to learn how to fly a plane
at the air force academy.
We haven't met Mr. Song's son.
I heard he's outstanding.
He's remarkable.
So remarkable that I seldom see him.
I'd rather have a daughter than a son.
Yes.
Here you go.
We only stay here on the weekends.
We grow some fruit trees in the yard.
My daughter and I picked
the hawthorn berries and made this wine.
It's nice.
Meiyin, you're amazing.
You can make anything.
You're totally a superwoman.
Both your career and family
are well taken care of.
Superwomen are rare to find.
My family hoped that I would have a kid
right after we got married.
I spent over ten years building a career.
But to them,
having a child is more important.
We all have different values.
We can't force them.
When Tangtang was little,
I was so busy with work every day.
Sometimes, when I got home,
I'd cry so much.
Really? Why?
I had never taken care of a baby before.
I was exhausted.
Your dad's last name is Song,
but yours is Wu.
Were you adopted?
No, I took my mom's last name.
My mom asked me to.
We all listen to everything she says.
She's the boss.
We listen to my dad in my family.
He's the one making money.
My grandma said
the one making money is the boss.
Your grandma is wrong.
So what if someone makes money?
My dad also makes a lot of money.
You guys are lame.
Let me take you to my brother.
He knows what's fun.
He's a know-it-all.
Really?
You'll find out. Follow me.
What's wrong?
Don't you find it a bit weird?
How so?
You're introducing me to your friends now.
So?
Wait. Let's make it clear.
Our current status is that
we just decided
to try to build our relationship.
It's only been a few days.
But we've already met
my family, your sister,
my colleagues, and your niece.
Now I'm meeting your friends.
I think
the pace is a little weird.
How so?
I don't think I should be here.
Just go home then.
Since I'm already here,
where else can I go?
I was just grumbling a bit.
Don't misunderstand.
Please tell me
if I've done something wrong.
If you shouldn't be here,
where should you be?
We are developing our relationship,
but you are my girlfriend.
It's my friend's daughter's party.
Shouldn't you come?
I should.
I didn't know you'd get angry so easily.
It's bad for your skin.
Do you know where you were wrong?
I do.
Where?
I was wrong because you said so.
I won't do it again.
If you say that,
then you don't really know.
What do you even mean by that?
You're wrong because I said you were?
It is your fault
for making me sound unreasonable.
No.
You're angry. So it must be my fault.
Tell me then.
What part of it is your fault?
Excuse me, did you forget your invitation?
What?
Sir, your car isn't parked yet.
Could you park just in front?
Is this okay?
Sir, please park in the parking lot.
Didn't you say just in front?
-Is this okay?
-Why not back up a little?
Is this okay?
WELCOME TO MY BIRTHDAY PARTY
Do all rich kids
celebrate their birthdays like this?
When I was little,
my sister would make me some noodles
and two fried eggs.
It shouldn't be fried eggs,
it should be hard-boiled eggs,
skewered with a chopstick.
Why? What's the reason behind that?
A chopstick and two eggs
symbolize 100 percent.
Superstitious.
Are you not angry anymore?
If I was really mad at you,
I would have gone nuts.
Watch your step.
Mr. Ye!
-Mr. Feng.
-Hello.
It's been a while.
I heard you got a promotion.
What promotion?
-It was a normal transfer.
-I see.
Congratulations.
I'll say hi to Steven.
-Sure.
-All right.
Talk to you later.
Steven.
There you are.
Excuse me.
Both of you have met before,
but allow me to officially introduce you.
My girlfriend, He Fanxing.
Executive Director at Amazing Decoration.
Hello, Mr. Song.
-Nice to meet you.
-Just call me He.
You're Luming's girlfriend
and an employee of Aijia.
No matter what, you're family now.
Right.
Even though we're family,
cough it up when you should.
By the way, He,
Luming said that
you're worried about your company.
Well, Aijia has acquired
Amazing Decoration.
You're not only looking at our brand,
but also the staff who built the brand.
But until now, Aijia still hasn't
given clear instructions
on whether we'll operate independently
or merge with the headquarters
for unified management.
So,
many in our company feel insecure.
There's a high turnover
in all departments.
Because of Aijia's rigid policies,
even some old employees
have also resigned.
So I think employees should be
more important than the policy.
You're right, employees are important.
But He, have you heard of
the Pareto Principle?
It states that in most companies,
20 percent of the staff
creates 80 percent of the business.
Those who only think about themselves,
have no confidence or fool around,
will be eliminated.
True.
Different company cultures
is also our concern.
But new blood needs time
to adjust and blend in.
What you said isn't wrong.
Amazing Decoration still wishes
to remain as a warm family.
That is understandable.
But they have to respect Aijia's culture,
follow the rules
and earn respect with your own abilities.
Of course, Aijia is also willing
to grow with the staff,
provided that
they want to grow instead of backing away.
I see.
It's the survival of the fittest.
Even if we keep those who are unfit,
when we dismiss them,
we still have to pay them
severance pay, don't we?
What's this?
Is today a good day to discuss work?
He, just add me on WeChat.
Sure.
I hope you don't mind.
About what?
You're the boss. You're always right.
-Mr. Ye.
-Mr. Sun.
How are you?
May I know where the washroom is?
Go straight and turn left.
Thank you.
-Why is he here?
-Why is she here?
Yuan Song, your clothes.
Why is she here?
He Fanxing, we've met before.
Did Yuan Song invite you?
-Have a good chat.
-No.
I came with someone else.
I see.
Yuan Song told me that
you often take care of him.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Are you Yuan Song's sister?
Sister?
Yuan Song, what did you tell her?
I told her that you're a family member.
How could she understand
if you put it that way?
Fanxing!
I've been looking for you.
You're...
Why is he here?
Meiyin.
I came with Mr. Ye.
Luming, Ms. He...
Let me introduce you.
This is my girlfriend, He Fanxing.
She'll be Aijia's employee soon.
Please take care of her.
The boy is also here.
Is this boy your friend?
-He is--
-You're all here.
Tangtang is about to cut the cake.
Come on.
Dad.
He just called him...
-Are you kidding me?
You haven't made the introductions?
Let me officially introduce you.
This is my son, Yuan Song.
This is my best friend, Ye Luming.
Call him Mr. Ye.
This is his girlfriend, He--
-I know.
-You know?
I interned at Amazing Decoration.
She's my boss.
I didn't have time to tell you.
Subtitle translation by Cheah Fong Yee