WELCOME TO MY BIRTHDAY PARTY
Come make a wish, Tangtang.
You're staring at him.
I'm just feeling a little awkward.
I used to think
that Wu Meiyin
was Yuan Song's ex-girlfriend.
She bought him branded goods
and even cooked for him.
Never have I thought
that she'd be his stepmom.
But why isn't Yuan Song
using his dad's last name?
At least we could have linked him
with Mr. Song from that.
Both of Steven's kids
follow their moms' last name.
His ex-wife's child has her last name.
Ms. Wu too asked for her girl
to follow suit.
So to be fair, Steven consented.
Is that so?
If Steven finds out
I snatched his son's girlfriend,
what would he think?
I'd have to leave Amazing Decoration.
It's okay. Resign and live off me.
-Why should I?
-This is poverty alleviation.
Even if I lose my job,
I still have my brother to depend on.
I thought you would depend on yourself.
Depending on my brother means the same.
What logic is that?
Why can you depend on your brother
but not your boyfriend?
Boyfriends can be
someone else's boyfriend.
But siblings are forever.
I think you're right.
We must talk about it on our way home.
-Really?
-Mr. Ye.
Hey. Let's go.
-You're a dad now.
-Mr. Ye.
-Have fun!
Hurry and go.
-Luming!
-Yes!
What's the matter?
Let's talk inside.
Try Meiyin's hawthorn wine.
Come on. Let's go.
I don't drink.
When Steven and I just got married,
Yuan Song refused to call me Aunt,
saying that I'm young and pretty.
So he calls me Meiyin instead.
Time has changed.
He has grown up. He is out of reach now.
He never answers my calls
or tells me about his condition.
He studied the same field,
but he refused to join Aijia.
I don't know what he's up to.
Dad, must you lecture me
with my boss around?
I'm not lecturing you.
I'm just lamenting
the fact that you're much cuter
when you were a kid.
He.
How's his performance at work?
Well...
He was weak at time management
and was always tardy.
But not anymore.
He's adaptive
and has a nice sense of design.
Now, he can complete a project on his own.
Clients are mostly pleased.
Really? That's great.
He Fanxing always wants her staff
to obey the rules.
She never praised me.
Mind your manners.
How can you address her by her name?
How rude!
Not really.
We're close friends apart from colleagues.
We address each other by our names.
Right, He Fanxing?
That's right.
Yes, that's right.
Fanxing said her company
adapts family-style management.
There's no obvious hierarchy.
They often hang out for a meal or karaoke.
-Really?
-That's right.
We often walk our dogs together too.
Walk dogs together?
You have a dog?
My mom's Braised Meat. It's with me now.
I live near He Fanxing,
so we go to the same park.
But we haven't been there for a long time.
My brother is taking care of it.
So he'll walk the dog.
Right. Her brother was my lecturer
who's close to me.
He recommended the internship
at Amazing Decoration to me.
So you have such a relationship.
Yes. Yuan Song told me
that He Fanxing often looks after him.
Of course.
It's also because of her brother.
So, he eats at your house
and is close to your parents?
Yes.
Is that so?
I didn't know you were so close.
What a coincidence.
I didn't know that Yuan Song was your son.
Maybe you're not close enough
unlike He Fanxing and me.
It's not that.
Ye and I are very close.
We drink and play pool together.
By the way,
when He was seeing someone else,
Ye has liked her already.
He went out of his way
to court her, right?
What a strong wine.
Yuan Song.
Have you seen Ms. He's ex-boyfriend?
I heard he's young.
I have.
I bet he isn't as good as Ye, right?
-What's wrong?
-Your back is dirty.
-It's clean.
-It's okay now.
-No.
-No. This...
What are you saying?
How could he be better than me?
Don't get too confident.
I should go now.
My dad will wait for me if I'm late.
Right? What time is it?
Hello?
Yes, I did.
The driver I hired is here.
-You're leaving now?
-Greet the others. Don't mind us.
We'll take our leave.
-We won't see you off then.
-Okay, see you.
See them off, Yuan Song.
They said no need.
Let me give you a quiz.
A rare steak
and a medium-well steak met each other.
But they didn't greet one another.
Why?
Because they're not close enough.
Steven and his son
are like a rare steak
and a medium-well steak
meeting each other.
You and Mr. Song
are like a medium-cooked steak
and a medium-well steak
meeting each other.
You and your ex are the same, right?
That's right. We're not close.
You and I are also medium-cooked steaks.
Not close either.
But at least, we're the same.
I shouldn't have come.
Had I known...
I wouldn't have invited you too.
-Okay, drive safe. Bye.
-Thanks.
Dad, Meiyin.
-Yes?
-Tangtang is asleep. I'm leaving.
You're leaving?
Hey, it's late. Why are you leaving?
Why don't you stay?
I'll send you home tomorrow.
It's okay, Dad.
The last bus is at 11:30 p.m.
I can still make it. I'll leave now.
Okay, text me when you've reached home.
-Okay.
-Bye. Be safe.
Hey, he...
Does he hate me?
Rather than hate, he feels uneasy.
What do you mean? Why would he be uneasy?
He's not close to you.
Love needs to be nurtured.
He won't even stay. How can I nurture it?
Besides, I give him everything he wants.
Why won't he listen to me?
Yuan Song has never asked
anything from you.
Anyhow, I brought him up.
No, you didn't.
It was his grandparents.
Do you think you can give money
to a baby and let him buy
his own milk?
Or do you think that Tangtang
is planted in a bank
and showered with money?
Of course I know
I have to care for the kids.
But I had to make money.
We can't live without money!
Why can't he understand?
His grandpa kept the money you gave him.
He gave him the money and assets
on his deathbed.
So your son has never used your money.
To me...
it's good enough that he calls you Dad
and thinks that you're a good man.
Others reap and you sow,
yet you despise what you sowed.
You're sick.
Hey.
We were just chatting.
Why are you angry?
No matter what,
I'm still better than most dads, right?
Tell me. How are you better than them?
I...
At least, I found him a nice stepmom.
That's because I'm nice.
It has nothing to do with you.
What else?
I'll give him my company.
Tangtang can stay home and live off him.
Yuan Song won't accept your company.
Tangtang won't live off him either.
Steven.
Why are you so childish?
You want everyone to live
according to your will.
Your son...
doesn't hate you.
He wants to be close to you.
But he has to stay away from you
to not hate you.
If you don't change yourself,
Tangtang...
might become like her brother.
Understand?
What?
Yuan Song's dad owns Aijia Decoration?
Yes.
That young and pretty Ms. Wu
from the investing department
is his stepmom.
She's only seven years older than me.
Who could have imagined that?
I've seen her.
She's young and pretty indeed.
Where did you meet her?
At his house with his sister.
You never told me.
I thought you knew.
Your dad is funny.
Yesterday,
he forgot to add water to barley.
Today, he forgot to add salt
to the noodles.
When he met Mr. Liu the other day,
he actually forgot his name.
Maybe someday, he'll lose himself.
That's an exaggeration.
Do you have a good memory?
Better than you.
Do you remember that episode
in The Love Clinic?
There was a guy
who went on a date with a bike.
He pretended to be poor
so that people wouldn't know he's rich.
Yuan Song is not like that.
He is not close to his dad
and he grew up with his grandparents.
Now that his dad is controlling him,
he is starting to rebel.
A left-behind child?
Something like that.
Yuan Song and his dad
don't seem to be close.
They were quite polite to each other.
I think Yuan Song is fine.
He just lacks love.
Why don't you invite him over for dinner?
Bring Minmin too.
They're schoolmates.
They know each other, right?
Yes.
That's great.
Young people will have mutual topics.
Yuan Song is not bad.
So is Minmin. Maybe they can...
Cai Minmin needs to study
or she'll fail again.
That's right. Yuan Song just
became a permanent staff.
He has a new project.
He doesn't have time for that.
What's with you two?
-I--
-Okay.
Keep your matchmaking passion.
Eat up.
Bai, come here.
Help me with the boxes.
The courier is coming at 11:00 a.m.
I thought you were Bai.
Sending festive gifts to clients?
Yes.
-Let me help.
-It's fine.
What is it?
Nothing major. I just want to apologize.
What for?
I didn't tell you that my dad
is the boss of Aijia.
I didn't mean to hide it.
He wanted me to join Aijia, but I refused.
So I hid from him
and only contacted Meiyin.
After that, Aijia acquired
Amazing Decoration.
All the more I had to keep it a secret.
I was worried
that everyone would judge me.
It's okay. I understand.
Your dad does not define who you are.
You can keep it a secret.
You're not mad?
If I had asked about your dad and his job,
would you have told me?
I would.
So, it wasn't being
kept secret deliberately.
You just didn't make yourself clear.
I didn't ask either.
Maybe, deep down inside,
I don't think it's important.
In that case,
you don't have to explain.
The client said he's stuck in traffic.
Okay.
Four shots of espresso?
Did you work all night?
I completed Donghai Mall's project
last night.
So fast?
Yuan Song and I will go
on a business trip tonight.
A business trip?
Who sent you?
A client saw our work
from our previous client online.
Yuan Song and I were in charge of it.
So Mr. Li sent us to do the measurement
and discuss with them.
It's a remodeling
of a 2,000-square-foot chalet.
A 2,000-square-foot chalet?
You'll work until next month.
Yes.
By the way,
you can continue giving me new projects.
Give me all you can.
Can you handle it all?
There are eight days of weekends
per month. I can use them.
What's wrong? Stomachache?
Had too much coffee?
It's fine.
Maybe it's just a stomach spasm.
I'll get another cup.
No!
You still want to drink coffee?
Use this.
Here.
Come in.
Ms. He, I have a favor to ask of you.
What is it?
I'll go on a business trip for three days.
Something came up with a friend
who agreed to take care of my dog.
Can you keep Braised Meat for a few days?
Let He Canyang take it.
I've asked him.
He's busy and will be back late tonight.
Please.
It will pee on the sofa
if it's mad and hungry.
-Okay, I'll go after work.
-Thank you so much.
Same password.
I owe you a meal. Bye!
You scared me!
I almost had a heart attack.
Serves you right for not locking your car.
Why aren't you at the West Gate?
I'm too tired to walk there.
Here, your milk tea.
So I can go anywhere I want today?
Yes, as long as we don't break the law.
Then we'll go save the animals
trapped in a cage.
One more time.
-It's fine.
-Go for it!
-This...
-It's rigged!
You wanted to save them.
-Next one.
-Let's continue.
Almost there!
Not again!
Last two tokens.
Do you really want to save them?
Did you have to take it that far?
Of course.
Don't you like it?
We've saved the animals. What's next?
Something exciting.
Something that'll fire you up
that you can't stop yourself.
Braised Meat.
Why are you here?
Come. Up you go.
What's that smell?
Did you poop, Braised Meat?
My dear Braised Meat.
Why did you poop everywhere?
Good thing you didn't do it on the rug.
He?
Mr. Song?
Why are you here?
Yuan Song is on a trip.
I'm here to take Braised Meat
to my place for a while.
It pooped on the floor,
so I cleaned it up.
I'm leaving soon.
He.
Can we talk?
I'll be straightforward.
I don't know much about my son.
Seeing that he trusts you a lot,
I think you two must be close.
Can we talk?
Sure.
Have a seat.
-Is tea okay?
-Sure.
What kind of chair is this? This child.
-Have some tea.
-All right. Thanks.
Take a seat.
He.
Do you come here often?
You're very familiar with the kitchen.
I came here before.
Looks like you took care of him
outside of work too.
My son is not sensible.
Did he trouble you?
No, he didn't.
He's quite independent
and he has a good character too.
He gets along very well
with his colleagues too.
Everyone likes him.
Really?
He's not a mess? Does he wash his cup?
He doesn't piss people off when he speaks?
No.
This boy...
"Song Yuan"?
What a nice handwriting.
He, my wife told me that
he just broke up with his girlfriend,
so he has been feeling down.
Have you ever met her?
Yes.
Once in a while.
I heard that she's older than him.
What does she look like?
What does she do?
I'm not sure.
These are private matters.
You should ask him directly.
My son
doesn't talk to me.
Boys are different from girls.
They won't talk much with their parents.
My parents don't know
what my brother is up to either.
But they will always be our parents.
Parents don't get to choose.
He hates us.
I can't change that.
Don't misunderstand. He doesn't hate you.
He thinks that
you're working hard in your expertise.
You're amazing and he's proud of you.
Did he say that? Did he say that himself?
Yes, he mentioned it before.
But I don't know about the others.
This child seems closer to you.
Not at all.
He, how about this?
You're his senior.
In the future,
if he makes any mistakes in the company,
educate him for me.
Not to that extent.
Well...
Okay, then.
Please help him out.
It's so spicy.
How did you know about this place?
My aunt brought me here.
She loves the super spicy version.
How is it? Is it super spicy?
It is.
Why do you eat like a hamster?
Are you saying that I'm cute?
Cute? You're a troublemaker.
-But you like me.
-Don't get cocky.
Watch your behavior in public.
Again?
I can call you a cab
if you want to be a nun.
Aunt?
This is...
I don't quite know him.
We're sharing a table.
Don't tell my mom.
Especially my maternal uncle.
Isn't your aunt your dad's cousin?
-Why would she know your maternal uncle?
-That's right.
She's his assistant.
Family business.
He's your boyfriend, right?
Hi, I'm Su Li, Minmin's aunt.
Sorry, Aunt.
We're secretly dating.
We can't reveal anything.
What do you mean?
It means
we'll keep our relationship a secret
until it's stable.
Why?
You can date older guys.
No. It's very complicated.
I can't explain it.
Anyway, time will prove everything.
Eat up.
We just began. We're starving.
All right. Continue your meal.
Don't tell my uncle!
You know them?
That's my niece. She got a boyfriend.
Where are they?
They left when you came here.
You must still be hungry.
Have some nuts.
Three Squirrels.
You know me.
My aunt is a spy.
My mom and uncle will know
that I have a boyfriend now.
And an old one too.
As long as I keep quiet
and my aunt doesn't see your photo
in my uncle's social media,
no one will know.
What if he takes a family photo with us
and posts it online?
If my uncle did that,
that means I'm destined to be a nun.
Not again. It's not that serious.
It is!
My uncle is very selfish.
He can become ruthless for his happiness.
Doesn't your uncle treat you well?
He even bought you a house.
That was before.
There's no kinship
in business and love life.
It's not a good situation.
Right.
I'll send you to the campus.
We must be careful.
Yes, now that I'm moving out,
we can't let our guard down.
You brought Yuan Song's dog home?
Where's Dad and Mom?
They're testing a new massage chair
at Mr. Zhang's house.
You two are quite something.
You're at the forefront of society.
You still care for his dog
after breaking up.
Is Ye Luming fine with that?
You're the one who is taking care of it.
I'm only in charge of bringing it home.
Aren't both of you
in an awkward position now?
A little.
But we can manage.
Will you two get back together?
Have you forgotten? I'm taken.
So you mean
that you and Ye Luming are dating
with the premise of marriage?
I said we're only giving it a try.
A try. I see.
Did you eat hotpot?
It's super spicy and super good.
Let's go next time.
You went there with Cai Minmin, right?
I went with my colleague,
but I met her there.
She must have gone there
with her classmate.
He's a handsome guy.
We greeted each other and left after that.
Why are you staring at me?
Don't tell her anything
about me and Yuan Song.
I won't. You were talking about this?
What else?
We have to be careful
when posting photos online.
Yes, we should.
A boyfriend?
Minmin never told me.
Su Li said,
if she didn't meet her yesterday,
Minmin wouldn't let us know about him.
What's wrong?
There's nothing to be shy about.
That's right.
Su Li said he's a working man
who is a lot older.
I'm really worried.
Why don't you check on her for me?
All right. Leave it to me.
Right, how are things with Fanxing?
Not bad.
Prepare a wedding house then.
My house is fine.
You're a bachelor. What do you know?
Your current house is okay for now.
But when you get married and have kids,
you'll need a baby room and a playroom.
If you hire a nanny, she'll need a room.
Why are you so anxious?
We can plan that
when we're getting married.
How can you not be anxious?
You'll have to wait
for at least a year
to get the house and renovate it.
If you two are not married by then,
everything will turn sour.
Okay. You're right.
Just buy a house first.
I'll think about it.
I'm at my office. Let's talk later.
-Hi, Mr. Ye.
-Mr. Ye.
Come in, Su Li.
Boss.
Luming.
My sister said
you met Minmin's boyfriend last night.
What is he like?
He looked a lot older than Minmin.
I couldn't tell his age.
Perhaps 27, 28, 29 or 30 years old?
Miss.
You might as well say
that he's ten years older.
I couldn't tell.
He's quite good-looking.
Looks like he charms every girl he sees.
What's with Minmin?
Why won't she let us know?
I don't know. She wouldn't tell me.
Didn't she say she liked her senior?
What now?
Luming.
Do you know there's a group of loan sharks
that targets college students now?
They have a dedicated plan.
They send handsome guys
to date their victims
and ask them to lend money
from the loan sharks
on the pretext of needing the money
for their business or family.
The victims will sign a fraudulent IOU.
They'll give their boyfriends the money
and it'll be returned to the loan sharks.
The victims don't get any money
and will be in debt.
If they can't pay up
and the interests accumulate
until it hits a million yuan,
they would be done for.
Do you think that guy is such a person?
He's not a simple man.
Minmin is innocent
and inexperienced in love.
She's going to be hurt
if she dates a player.
Okay, I get it.
I'll talk to her later.
No.
I'll go now.
Luming!
It's Boss.
You're awake?
We're here.
What time did you sleep last night?
You slept soundly
after you got in the car.
The quarter assessment is here.
Everyone's looking at me with teary eyes
and waiting for me
to pay them their bonuses.
When will your company move?
Next month.
To an office building below Aijia.
The renovation is almost done.
So fast?
A decoration firm is decorating the firm.
Professionals work fast.
"A decoration firm
is decorating the firm."
Interesting.
Is the administration on its own?
Maybe. We don't know.
If you can't stay in Amazing Decoration,
come to Minglu.
Be my executive director.
Just like your boss and his wife.
We can be a formidable duo.
Spare me.
Your cousin is your assistant,
and your girlfriend
is your executive director.
Are you really making it
a family business?
A family business? So be it.
What about it?
We have good benefits.
Foot spa basin?
Health pot?
Walking shoes?
When is Minmin coming?
I have to be back before 2:30 p.m.
I have lots of things to do.
Soon, I guess.
Fanxing.
Minmin.
I'm sorry. Does it hurt?
It's all right. I'm fine now.
Thanks, Fanxing.
You're not a kid anymore.
Still playing pranks.
Serves you right.
I like it!
That was a nice punch.
I wouldn't eat with you
if Fanxing wasn't around.
You're being rude.
Call her Aunt.
That was before I met her.
Look. She's such a young and pretty girl.
Even I would hit on her.
How can I call her Aunt?
I should call her Fanxing.
I think that is just nice.
Aunt means your uncle's wife.
It's not right.
Then from now on, I'll call you Fanxing.
Subtitle translation by
Jaynne Tan Jie Ying