Darling!
Xiaoyu!
-Darling.
-What?
Are you all right?
Let go!
-I'm sorry, let me go!
-Scum!
Scum!
You reap what you sow.
Thank goodness it's not me this time.
-Why are you here?
-Stop!
Why?
-Hey!
Are you sick?
What?
The baby is born?
Gosh!
It's a boy?
That's great, Xiaoyu is blessed.
She has a boy and a girl now.
Take good care of her.
All right!
That's great!
They're both safe.
-That's great.
-Gosh.
I wonder when we can have
our own grandchild.
I don't care if it's a boy or a girl.
Our Fanxing has such great qualities.
Luming is handsome.
They will definitely have
a clever and beautiful baby.
Looks aren't that important,
as long as the baby is healthy.
-Yes, the baby just has to be healthy.
-Hey.
I'll make some northern snakehead soup
and have Canyang take it to her tomorrow.
All right.
-I'll help you.
-Hurry.
It's so weird.
He seems to like you very much.
He stops crying once you hold him.
Song Xue is his godmother after all.
Here.
Malty.
Hello there.
I'm your godmother.
You look like you really like babies.
You should have one soon.
Mom!
Okay, I'll stop.
Here.
I don't want it anymore.
What?
Ms. He and Yuan Song were an item?
That's old news though.
Why didn't you tell me?
I even had a meal with them
and made fun of them.
It's so awkward.
They didn't tell anyone.
How could I spread the news?
Moreover, Mr. Ye managed to interfere,
and Yuan Song has yet to give up.
They're fighting dirty now.
Yuan Song!
I'm giving you this cactus.
Thank you. When are you leaving?
Once I have finished tidying up.
-That soon?
-Yes.
Won't you wait for Chang Huan?
Why should I?
I have gotten back with my ex-husband.
Ex-husband?
I have been rewatching Naruto recently.
Kakashi is my true love after all.
Bai.
Didn't you say you liked my table set?
It's yours now.
Okay.
Were you fired?
It's the opposite.
Aijia's admin department
only allocated one vacancy.
Ms. He gave it to me.
What about her?
She resigned.
It has been approved
and she is already handing over her tasks.
What's the matter?
Did you quit?
Yes.
You were absent yesterday,
and you're suddenly quitting today.
Is it because of what I said?
Do you hate seeing me?
My best friend gave birth yesterday.
As for my resignation,
I had thought about it for some time.
I can't be an administrator forever.
Look me in the eye and tell me
that it's not because of me.
What are you doing?
Tell me that it's not!
It's not because of you.
You won't see me ever again?
Yes, I won't.
Am I not even allowed
to love you one-sidedly?
You'll meet someone better for you
in the future.
Okay.
I get it now.
No one can see us here.
Here, have some water.
It's so refreshing.
How long have you been here?
Take this off. I'm getting hot
just from looking at you.
I can't. I'm still working.
Did you ask me to come here
to watch you work?
Since I have a job now,
we don't even have the time to date.
We're dating, and I miss you.
Give me your hand.
What's this for?
This is the first 200 yuan
I have ever made.
I'll give you and my uncle 100 yuan each.
Please don't mind.
I have thought it through.
I'll stand behind both of you
and back you up.
It's fine if either of you wants
to take a rest for a day.
I will be here.
Don't worry, I'll make lots of money
and buy both of you lots of things.
I have to get back to work.
Please put the head on me.
Okay.
-Gosh.
-I'm okay.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
-Is everything all right?
You can go home now.
I'm going back to work.
-All right, get going.
-Bye.
Tangtang, have some more broccoli.
Don't just eat meat, okay?
Okay.
We're eating together,
but you look so unhappy.
No, I'm not.
Are you not happy?
Right, have you read the book I bought?
No.
Don't slack off.
You might have to take the exam soon.
Don't talk while you're eating.
You're being long-winded.
It's because I rarely get to see him.
How about this?
Move back in with us.
My room is big, so Yuan Song can have it.
I'll use the small one!
You love your brother the most, don't you?
Yes, he's the best!
I want to be like him when I grow up.
What are you talking about?
He's so disobedient.
Yuan Song is the best!
The teacher said that if we can pursue
our dreams without troubling others,
that's something admirable!
He will definitely build
a lot of beautiful houses.
Tangtang, I have a question.
What if your brother becomes poor one day?
I'll study hard
and start a business like Dad.
I'll make lots of money
and take care of him.
Tangtang, you're amazing!
Did you hear that?
Even your sister is worried that
she'll have to take care of you for life
if you do end up being poor.
That Uncle Ye you met
came from a poor family.
He fought very hard for a good life
and he is only finally getting married.
I have to leave. I have to go to the site.
And Dad,
I won't read the books you bought.
Tangtang, I'll pursue my dream
without troubling others.
I'll build pretty houses for you one day.
You're the best in the universe!
What was that about?
Was he challenging me?
Even Tangtang knows
we shouldn't cause others trouble.
Why can't you be more sensible?
Couldn't you see how upset he was?
You still mentioned Ye Luming.
That's strange.
Why can't I ever mention Ye Luming?
He Fanxing has resigned.
She resigned?
Is she getting married?
She should work at Luming's company.
That's even weirder.
How does this affect Yuan Song?
Why was he so agitated?
Yuan Song likes He Fanxing.
Doesn't he still like his ex?
Are you stupid?
Say something.
This is making me very awkward.
What should I say?
Do you want me to recommend him
some hair growth serum?
I have done my best,
but he has too much hair.
He's only partly bald.
Professor Song, look.
Malty has his mom's eyes!
Darling, look!
He has your eyes and my nose.
Is that so?
Isn't it time for you to go to work?
I feel disgusted whenever I see him.
-Xiaoyu.
-Fanxing, let me.
My dad made you some soup.
He's the best.
Is there a lot? I want some.
-He made you some as well.
-Thank you!
That's great.
When will you go to the care center?
They'll be picking me up tomorrow.
-Nice.
-Try it.
Well then, I'm off to work.
It's good.
This one is yours.
Careful, it's hot.
The moment I came in, I immediately felt
the tension in the air.
Why should we be the ones
who feel awkward?
That's because he is shameless
and we are not.
Right, Fanxing.
Have you consulted a lawyer for me?
I have asked my client who is a lawyer.
She specializes in divorce cases.
According to her, for your situation,
it is difficult for you
to get the custody of Peanut.
It's because you're unemployed.
But don't worry, I have a plan.
My resignation has been approved.
We can open a flower shop.
Did you really resign?
Yes.
I can't be an administrator forever.
I should start a business
while I'm still young.
I also have quite a bit of money
saved over the years.
Moreover, Mr. Li promised to apply
for a severance package for me.
This plan is pretty good.
You used to work as a florist
back in college.
Yes.
I have even signed up
for a florist course.
It will start next week.
You can attend the course
after you have recovered.
You really have everything planned out,
even for me.
Of course.
I can't just support
your divorce verbally.
How about it? Does it sound good to you?
Of course...
I have no problems with it.
It's just that
I've spent a lot of money on the kids.
I don't have much savings left.
Hey.
You forgot about me.
I'm the one with the most money
among the three of us.
Just count me in your business.
The two of you will work
while I'll be a silent partner.
How about that?
You're so rich!
It's just so-so.
What are you talking about so happily?
-I could hear you from outside.
-You're here, Ye.
Fruits for a beauty.
Thank you.
Hey.
Goodness, it's really thick.
Isn't it improper to open it
in front of the giver?
Ye isn't an outsider.
Ten thousand yuan!
And one yuan.
Your baby is one in a million,
hence the amount.
Really?
Yes.
Did we really get the homestay project?
It is thousands of square feet!
Yes, it is.
Here.
Be careful of the stitches.
What a fool.
Pain is good.
Or else, I would think I was dreaming.
We actually outperformed
the renowned designers from Shenzhen.
Looking at it from another perspective,
it could be due to our low price.
Thank you for the red packet.
Don't mention it.
There's no need to be courteous
with each other.
While we're dating each other,
you have spent plenty of money.
You bought me gifts
and gave my friends money.
You have given too much.
Therefore, as a way to return the favor,
you should quickly fall
madly in love with me
and declare that
you can't live without me.
Okay, I understand.
I'll try my best.
Okay.
Keep it up then.
Yes, I'll work hard.
Aren't you visiting another friend
on the 14th floor?
I should go.
I have to meet an important client
at the office.
Okay, bye.
Ms. He!
Mr. Ye, you're here too.
Hey.
Her best friend just gave birth,
so I came to visit.
I have to go.
Let's have a meal another time.
-Okay, bye.
-Bye.
Why are you being so awkward?
You didn't do anything wrong.
But it feels like I did.
I never would have imagined
that you and Yuan Song dated.
We weren't a good match, right?
I'm nearly hitting middle age,
while he's still young.
That's what I thought at first.
Then I realized
there was nothing wrong with that.
If men can find girls
who are 10 or 20 years younger than them,
why can't women do the same?
But you're seeing Mr. Ye now.
You don't have any feelings left
for Yuan Song, right?
I knew it.
We don't have a choice.
Women have to be realistic.
As for Mr. Ye,
in every aspect regarding marriage,
he is better than Yuan Song.
All right, let's go.
You look too calm.
Are guys like you this pretentious?
Gosh, this is my first time
getting such a big project.
I can already feel the money rushing in.
I'm happy as well.
Then try to smile, at least.
When I saw you, I thought we screwed up.
Right.
For the reconstruction,
we have to work with an architect.
We can hire someone first.
After I have completed my studies abroad
and become an architect,
I'll do it myself.
If you're going to study abroad,
how can you court Ms. He?
Forget it.
She has resigned.
Resigned?
Yes.
She won't see me anymore.
This is the room.
I'm going to the site.
Are you feeling better?
Yes, it's nothing serious.
I can leave tomorrow.
That's good.
-Ms. He.
-Yes?
Yuan Song said...
that you have resigned.
Resigned?
Why?
I didn't make the decision just recently.
I've thought about it for a long time.
I am done with being an administrator.
I plan to open a flower shop
with my best friends.
That's good.
You do like flowers a lot.
Yes.
But it feels too sudden.
We will be without
your supervision and discipline.
It feels like our strict class teacher
has suddenly announced her retirement.
Don't worry.
I may have resigned,
but it doesn't mean we won't meet again.
You have to visit my shop often.
All right.
Although I need to save money
to buy a bigger house,
I'll still sign up for a membership.
Thank you, my dear customer.
Why do you want to move to another house?
Are you getting pompous?
A two-room house can't satisfy
an active monkey like you anymore?
I heard you would only stay
in a 2,000-square-feet house.
So I have to be better than her.
That's just a rumor.
I have never said that.
My requirements have never changed.
The guy has to be rich and likable.
The standard of wealth
is actually pretty vague.
If I don't like him,
I wouldn't marry him
even if he was a billionaire.
If I like him, I would marry him
even if he only has tens of thousands.
I do have that much!
But I don't like you.
Then why do you keep visiting me?
I like your mom.
She's nice.
I am here to chat with her.
Although we're no longer colleagues,
as your friend,
I'll be sure to attend your wedding.
I am not marrying him!
Then why are you trying
to be closer to my mom?
I don't even have a brother.
You talk too much!
I'm injured. Be careful!
It hurts!
-I'm warning you.
-I'm done.
Yes.
That's right.
I have prepared a transfer report.
All right.
Thank you for your help.
Thank you very much.
You were doing so well.
Why are you transferring?
The art institute pays more.
-Mom.
-What?
Would it be bad if I had a girlfriend
who is younger than me?
You talk as if the girls you dated
were all older than you.
That's not what I meant.
I'm talking about someone
who is 12 years younger than me.
Save it.
Is it not good?
What do you think?
We have enough issues.
Your dad and I are old.
We won't be able to handle it.
But doesn't our family
value personal freedom greatly?
Our family upholds
public order and social norms.
But having a younger girlfriend
doesn't break the public order
or social norms, right?
Have you really found someone this young?
No!
No, of course not.
That would be for the best.
If you really did,
then don't even think of coming back here.
Your dad went for a walk.
Why isn't he back yet?
Give him a call right now.
What is he doing?
He forgot his phone again.
Your dad
might really get himself lost one day.
Goodness.
This is just an illusion you feel
after falling out of love with discontent.
It's the aftermath of love.
Think about it.
You don't actually like her.
You just want to get her back.
It's like having beers.
You don't really want to drink.
You just want the beer snacks.
Whenever I drink,
it's because I really want to.
Not necessarily.
Try giving it more thought.
If you win her back,
she might look pretty now,
but how about two years later?
When her collagen levels are depleted,
she will be an old lady.
Can a young man like you handle it?
If you're going to dump her eventually,
you should just let her go now.
I like the fact
that she is an innocent woman
who stood the test of time.
Her soul radiates such brightness.
Even when she is old and full of wrinkles,
she will always be beautiful in my eyes.
You are disgusting.
What's the use of telling me that?
She's dating Ye Luming,
and he has my parents' approval.
And she has resigned now.
You won't see her as often.
I'm telling you this as a friend.
Let go when you should.
Don't dwell on it.
Hey...
That's enough.
You're acting like a girl.
Even if you're right, I still like her.
So what if I like her?
All right.
Do as you please.
You're a young man who cries for love.
How admirable.
Mom, I'm back.
You're back.
Xingxing,
your dad is not home yet.
-Did he go out?
-He did.
He went out this morning
and forgot his phone.
He's not back yet.
He's not?
-No.
-Did he call?
No, he didn't.
Things should be fine.
Maybe he went somewhere else for a walk.
But he still hasn't returned.
He should at least call.
Could something have happened to your dad?
Did he say where he was going?
I'll look for him.
He said he was going to the park.
I'll change and go with you.
Mom, you should stay here.
Wait here in case Dad comes back.
Call me if he's back.
Calm down, he'll come back.
-Call me once you have found him.
-Okay, I'm going now.
Hello, Canyang, where are you?
Stop.
That's my dad.
He was there around 1:00 p.m.
He always uses the south gate.
Please check when he left.
Can you fast forward?
Mr. Liu, have you seen my dad today?
-No.
-You haven't?
Thank you.
Why are you here?
I was with Professor He when you called.
-Where is he?
-He's checking the CCTV footage.
Something must have happened.
Calm down. No news is good news right now.
Okay?
There are drowning incidents here
every once in a while.
My dad likes to walk by the lake.
He can't swim.
Don't worry. There's no such news yet.
Don't think only of bad things, okay?
-How did it go?
-So?
The dog is with security.
The CCTV footage at the south gate
showed that Dad never left.
Calm down!
The CCTV at the west gate is out.
Dad might have left from there.
But he always uses the south gate.
Something must have happened.
Something must have happened!
Let's go to the police.
-The police!
-All right, let's go.
You have to file a report.
-Okay.
-This way.
He Fanxing.
How can you go home looking like this?
I'm scared.
If something happened to him,
what's going to happen to my mom?
What will I do?
Mrs. He is alone at home.
She must be scared too.
Go back to her.
She needs someone with her right now.
You need to keep it together.
We have to prepare for the worst.
If...
If something happened,
you have to be there for your mom.
Have you found him?
Don't worry, we'll find him.
I'm here. Don't worry.
Go be with Mrs. He.
I'll wait here with Professor He.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
You're back!
Mom...
We'll find Dad. Don't worry.
-Look over there.
-Over there.
Something is floating here.
It looks like a body. Come here!
Come on.
Gosh.
No.
Wait.
Hello, Canyang?
In the lake...
It's not him?
Okay, come home first.
Someone fell into the lake a few days ago.
The body
only emerged after a while.
Mom!
You haven't slept.
Don't think too much.
We must be mentally prepared.
A big man
vanished just like that.
I want to see him,
dead or alive!
That's nonsense. Am I not here?
Luming, you're here too.
I'm hungry. Is breakfast ready?
Qingfeng!
Where have you been?
Are you trying to make us go crazy?
-Dad!
-My dear daughter.
Where were you?
We looked for you everywhere!
It's all right now.
Canyang is looking for you by the lake.
We thought you fell in the lake.
It's all right. I came back alive!
Call Canyang. He can stop searching.
Right, I'll call him.
-There, there.
-I'll call him.
Slow down.
I told you that
you'd get yourself lost someday.
And you really got lost.
Mr. He, slow down.
Goodness.
I have no idea what happened.
I just couldn't find the way back home
no matter what.
I even forgot my own name.
I was confused.
I couldn't even talk.
I kept on walking and walking.
I was looking for my way home.
Then, I got sleepy.
So I went to sleep
in the boathouse.
Mr. He, you should get some rest.
I'll register him at the hospital.
I'll take him for a checkup
this afternoon.
There's no need.
You stayed up all night. Go back and rest.
Canyang is home anyway.
That's right.
You should rest as well
and go to work if you can.
Canyang doesn't have work today.
He'll handle it.
All right.
If you need anything, just call me.
-Okay.
-It's fine.
Don't worry.
If I'm sick, then so be it.
I'll listen to the doctors.
Let's eat. Eat up.
Dad!
Dad, where have you been?
I was so scared
when they said someone fell in the lake!
Don't cry!
Which heartless monster
threw a mannequin in the lake?
Don't cry!
Come on, stop crying.
Don't cry.
Why are you crying too?
I couldn't hold it in!
All right, don't cry.
Stop crying!
You're making me cry as well!
Goodness!
Look at you!
It's all right, get back inside.
That won't do.
I have to thank you.
I'm glad you were here.
My mom could be at ease for a bit.
So? How did I do as your boyfriend?
You were excellent.
Don't worry.
If you haven't picked out your house,
I'll accompany you.
Are there any real rewards?
What would you like? I'll buy it for you.
I'll help myself.
I'll go now.
Give me a call after the checkup.
All right.
There are no bruises on the head.
Your symptoms meet
the early signs of Alzheimer's.
The progression differs from
person to person.
It might take years or decades
to reach the later stages.
Some just take months.
Doctor.
At later stages,
will he not recognize
or remember anyone anymore?
Yes, but that's not the worst.
He will lose the ability
to look after himself.
Doctor, can you
give me any medication
so that I'd turn senile slower?
Of course, sir.
Early medication can control the symptoms.
No matter what disease it is,
a good mentality is the best medicine.
Yes, you're right.
The doctor said
it can be controlled.
Then again,
it progresses differently
from person to person.
Don't worry.
When I was 12 years old,
I experienced growing pains.
My body grew too fast,
and my skin stretched itself thin.
My muscles and bones
felt like they were being torn.
My body resisted rapid growth with pain.
We're now 32 years old.
We grew up overnight.
We're facing severe growing pains again.
It's 10,000 times more painful
than when I was 12.
The pain is simply unbearable.
It reminds me that
as we are willfully wasting our time,
our parents
don't have much time left
to be wasted.
Subtitle translation by
Charlie Chai Chang Lim