How could you do this?
You didn't tell me after you found out!
I said so many silly things unknowingly!
How could I tell you?
Ms. He wanted to hide it.
I couldn't just announce it, right?
Besides, I only found out a few days ago.
Like you,
I said a lot of silly things too.
This is ridiculous.
How can I, the Queen of Gossip,
miss out on such news?
This is too ridiculous.
Don't spread it.
I know.
What's going on between
Yuan Song and Ms. He now?
Not long ago,
Yuan Song still liked Ms. He.
Now,
I think they're really just friends.
Friendship between men and women?
There must be something going on.
What can there be?
Think about it.
If Yuan Song and Ye Luming both liked you,
who would you pick?
Me?
Are you feeling giddy?
In terms of dating,
I'd pick Yuan Song for sure!
As for marriage,
I'd pick Mr. Ye!
That's right.
Think about it.
Ms. He is already in her 30s.
No matter how you think about it,
she should choose Mr. Ye
for a better future.
Can't you live life in a more
capricious and reckless way?
A reckless life is only
for those with financial freedom.
Normal people like us
have to plan wisely.
After all,
life is like walking on thin ice.
It's tough to be human
and even more as a woman.
But being a 30-year-old unmarried woman
is even tougher.
-Drink up.
Hey. Are we going to sing or not?
Of course!
I want to sing "Ten-Minute Romance!"
A ten-minute romance
May be a little short
Your smile takes away all the regrets
I have in my heart
Class is over
A ten-minute romance
All of me belongs to you
I hope that we will never part
If you win,
I'll be your girlfriend.
How about that?
You're way off. That's great!
Why are you so silent?
Are you still thinking about
how you missed the last shot?
No.
Then why do you seem so disappointed?
Aren't you happy working with Luo Wenyue?
Says who?
You.
Whatever she does, you follow her.
I do not!
You said that if I won, you would date me.
It was a joke, right?
Who would joke about that?
You could have just told me
you were kidding.
Then I wouldn't feel so bad.
Now I think I've ruined my life
with my own hands.
Never mind.
I should earn more money
and buy a house first.
Let me be clear.
Wishing to live
in a 200-square-meter house
is just a rumor.
I didn't say it.
It's not for you.
Don't be so full of yourself.
Say that again!
-You hit me?
-Say that again!
Can't I state the truth?
What's wrong? Did I hit your wound?
Let me see. Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Today, I couldn't win.
Maybe, this is how our lives go.
We didn't win,
but we didn't come in last anyway.
Don't worry.
I will be more successful in the future.
Mrs. Chang told me that you have a switch.
It's true indeed.
Fine.
Since you looked cool
while you were bowling today,
I'll take that you've won.
You'll take that I've won?
What does that mean?
What do you mean by that?
What do you mean?
It means you look cool when you bowl.
What do you mean I look cool?
Do you want to have tea at my place?
Tea? At this hour?
YUAN SONG
Today's progress...
Amazing! You got a strike!
Yuan Song, eat up.
Thanks for teaching me how to bowl today.
He's a really good player.
Dad.
What are you doing here?
I...
I don't know.
Did you forget what you were doing?
Yes.
What was I trying to do?
It's late. Did you want to go
to the washroom?
Yes. I remember now.
The washroom.
-Washroom.
-Be careful.
You...
Why are you here?
Aren't you going to bed?
What's wrong?
Dad.
I'm sorry.
What are you saying?
Why are you sorry?
I'm sorry, Dad.
Don't cry, child.
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
What's wrong?
In this world, I realized
that there are things that I can't do
no matter how hard I try.
There are things that I can't control
And there are things that I can't change
no matter how hard I try.
Let's meet tonight.
-Slow down.
-Sorry, I got caught in traffic.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
It's not a big deal.
Look. Tiantian is all good.
Are you really naming him Tiantian?
Tiantian is good!
It means being happy every day.
Why not name him Happy then?
Happy?
Happy is good too. I can do that.
No, Tiantian is better.
Tiantian, our Tiantian, little Tiantian.
He kicked me!
Are you crazy? He kicked you?
What are you going to do later?
I want to go shopping and have lunch.
Are you free? Join me.
Have you forgotten? I'm unemployed.
I have nothing but time to spare.
They sell dresses.
-This one's nice.
-It's fine.
Let's take a look.
Welcome!
It's nice.
I don't wear this kind of dress.
It suits you more.
Try a new style.
When your belly gets bigger,
wear it with a jacket and you're all set.
Buy it for me then.
Is this how you exploit
an unemployed middle-aged woman?
I'm about to raise a child alone.
I need to save up.
I really think that you should tell
Tiantian's dad about this.
After all, hiding things
and having others hide things from you,
both feel terrible.
If Dongyang knows that you call him
Tiantian's dad, he'd go crazy.
He really hates kids.
But you're right.
As the biological dad,
he has the right to know.
I'll consider it again.
I've been thinking.
It's always easier to make decisions on
other people's problems.
You may feel sympathetic
because you've had a similar experience,
but things like empathy
just doesn't exist.
Yes.
I've been reflecting on myself too.
When I was mediating relationships before,
did I speak as if I were God?
I spoke the facts.
Yes, onlookers see things more clearly.
As an onlooker,
I have to remind you.
They always say that
women in love are prettier.
Look at you.
If you put on a wedding dress,
you can be a real-life Corpse Bride.
Do I look that haggard?
Even though I don't have
the right to judge you,
I still want to remind you.
You should stop lying to yourself.
Love has always been
something that comes effortlessly.
What you need to work on
is keeping it and not let it slip away.
I just think
that many people have also dated
because they're compatible.
And they live a happy and loving life.
Well, I am also a normal person.
If they can do it, I can do it too.
You're wrong.
How can the same thing have
the same result on different people?
Everyone has different
principles and limits.
There is a saying that goes,
"Your personality decides your fate."
Yes, your personality decides your fate.
Before this, I thought I was so mature
to end the relationship
between me and Yuan Song.
We clashed like Mars and Earth.
I don't want him to derail from his path.
But now, when I see him with other girls,
I can't help but get jealous.
Since you know that you're jealous,
then I won't say anything else.
But if you still want to lie to yourself,
then do whatever you want.
Actually, I feel very sorry
towards Ye Luming.
I think Ye Luming
has probably noticed it too.
How can he not know
that your focus isn't on him?
He's also lying to himself.
Right now,
you're like a crow perching on a boar.
You can see others but not yourself.
Why are you attacking me?
I just don't want to see you
get any uglier.
Okay, I got it.
I'm already extremely ugly inside and out.
I can't get any uglier.
Even though I'm not sure
what I really want,
I know very well what I don't want.
You can do this.
That day,
I really shouldn't have
let Luming rest in Fanxing's room.
If that's the case,
then I shouldn't get this illness either.
What are you saying?
Who wants to be ill voluntarily?
You didn't have a choice.
That's enough.
Don't overthink.
Fanxing must have forgotten
about this already.
Other people don't need to worry
about their kids.
Look at our kids.
They hide everything from us.
They only tell us good things,
so that we won't worry.
That's why we have to keep trying
to figure things out by ourselves.
I feel so anxious.
That's enough. Stop feeling anxious.
The kids are all grown up.
There are many things
that we don't understand
and can't help with.
We will only trouble the kids more
in the future.
We won't be of much help.
Take me for an example.
I will only become more useless.
You're talking as if
you used to be helpful or something.
You always refute me.
-See?
-Fine.
I get it.
You're ill now.
In the future, I'll go wherever you go.
I won't let you get lost.
I'll ensure that
you will be taken care of.
It would be great
if humans
never grow old.
If we don't grow old and die,
we'd be like tortoises.
Looks like it will rain soon.
I'll shut the windows.
Hello? Where are you?
It will rain soon. I'll pick you up.
Sure, I'll wait for you. See you later.
I should have picked you up.
You're all wet now.
The weather forecast didn't say
it would rain.
I'll lend you Minmin's clothes. Come in.
What a feast.
Steven gave me this wine.
I couldn't bear to drink it.
Sit.
This is sumptuous.
This is nothing.
Your parents always invite me over
whenever they cook nice meals.
My parents' way
of showing their affection
is through food.
This language of love is very precise.
Every time I visit an elder's home,
I can't stop eating.
Have some.
Try the steak I made.
I've thought about it for a long time.
-We--
-Wait.
Can't you try the steak I made first?
He Fanxing.
Let's break up.
What?
Let's go back to being friends.
I told you that I'd give you a month.
Forget about it.
Don't force yourself.
I can give myself a break too.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
I broke up with you.
I should apologize.
How can love be forced?
I was the one pushing it.
You're just the victim.
Thank you
for consoling me.
But you don't have
to make yourself the bad guy.
If I were a victim like you said,
I didn't lose anything either.
You helped me
and treated me well.
I helped you because I wanted to date you.
You shouldn't think too highly of someone
just because he was nice to you.
When a man is pursuing you,
it's normal for him to treat you well.
You're right.
But for someone to give so much in vain
yet I can't give him
the same amount in return,
it feels like I've dined and dashed.
Dined and dashed?
It's nice to dine and dash
once in a while.
Also, nothing was given in vain.
In the process of giving,
I felt good too.
Basically, it was just a give and take.
Okay.
I accept that.
Regardless,
thanks for dumping me.
You still had to be the bad guy
in the end.
You're so funny.
You're thanking me for dumping you?
Do you want to be nominated
for next year's Nobel Peace Prize?
Bottoms up for me.
Do as you please.
Drink slowly. That's expensive!
Drink slowly.
It's all inside.
Okay.
Professor He, you're amazing!
With your method,
I reconciled with my uncle easily!
Did it go well for you too?
My mom changed the password.
I couldn't get in.
I see.
Why am I so unlucky?
That's true.
You and Fanxing share the same issue,
but not the same luck.
How did He Fanxing manage
to hide it so well?
There were no signs or hints at all.
Your sister didn't hide it well.
You all just thought
that she was very naive.
She doesn't look like
she would date her brother's student.
What did I just say?
You said He Fanxing looks too naive.
She doesn't look like
she would date Yuan Song.
But in reality,
I think Yuan Song made the first move.
You...
You knew?
Yes.
To put it simply,
my sister only dated your uncle
after she broke up
with the person you liked.
Our relationships are so complicated
that even dramas wouldn't have such plots.
I don't think we should care
about other people's problems.
Like how my uncle
didn't bother to find out
who Fanxing's ex was.
Otherwise, he would have felt
very awkward.
Do you have some misunderstandings
about your uncle's shamelessness?
What about him?
He already knew when He Fanxing
was dating Yuan Song.
What?
I think it's easier
to be friends with you.
It's more comfortable and carefree.
Tell me.
Love is not some bacteria.
How can it grow?
I've been so tired and anxious.
Every day, I repeatedly ask myself,
"Why do I not like you yet?
Why?
Could it be that
I have some sort of heart disease?"
Your heart is fine,
but your eyes aren't.
Lately, I also think
that I'm just like a beggar.
And you are a poor passerby.
You're the poor one. I'm not poor.
-You are poor!
-I'm not poor!
In my savings account, I have...
I have hundreds of thousands!
I'm not talking about money!
-What then?
-I'm talking about feelings!
I was too confident.
I thought you had them,
so I waited for you to give them to me.
Then I realized that you don't have them,
yet I kept waiting.
How pitiful.
I don't have them?
-You don't!
-I just...
If I had them, I'd give them all to you!
Then I started to ask myself.
Why am I making myself so miserable?
Ye Luming.
Do you really like her?
Or are you just refusing to accept defeat?
When there's a problem,
don't always blame yourself.
You can also find the answer
from someone else.
Right! You're so right.
-That's right.
-So I'm not the problem.
I'm so good.
Why would you like Steven's son?
Steven has ended his friendship with me.
He won't play pool with me anymore.
Steven!
Yuan Song is your best friend's son.
It's all your fault!
Fine. It's my fault.
Blame me, okay?
Let me tell you a secret.
It's going to be hard for you
to find another man
who is as good as I am.
You will surely regret this.
Regret?
Steven's son isn't as good as me.
Nonsense!
He's better than you.
-He's nice too.
-Nonsense!
You're still defending that wild man?
Nonsense! You're the wild man!
-Nonsense!
-I'm not nonsense!
-What are you?
You're right.
I am nonsense. That's why you let me go.
Nonsense Ye Luming.
Nonsense He Fanxing.
Here.
Your niece!
I've met her! I know her!
Come.
This is my niece.
Isn't she cute?
You...
Of course you've met her, she...
She went to your house.
No.
It was Yuan Song's house.
She thought I was the housekeeper.
Like this.
Housekeeper? You more look like an alien.
They called me Ma'am.
I was so sad!
Ma'am.
Why are you two drinking so much?
Put it down!
Kids can't drink!
Let me tell you a secret.
I dumped her.
What?
This is what happened.
I was going to break up with him.
But he brought it up first.
I won!
So I got dumped!
You got dumped.
But we are now best friends!
Best friends.
Nonsense Ye Luming!
Drink, Nonsense He Fanxing!
You're a mix of nonsense.
Hello?
Professor He, don't leave first.
Come to my house now.
What?
Are they drunk?
Okay, I'll come now.
Let me recap what happened.
Fanxing came to break up with my uncle,
but my uncle brought it up first
and dumped her.
They are now back to being friends
and had this breakup dinner.
Now, they're drunk.
Episode Two starts now.
I just feel
so sorry for my dad.
I know he really wants
to see me get married.
Every time I visit my grandma,
she asks him so many questions.
Do you know my second aunt?
Every time we meet, she would tell me
that I can't do whatever I want
and live as I please.
I have to think about
my parents' feelings.
Every time she says that,
I just feel
very sad.
-Very sad.
-I get it.
I get it.
It's hard for a woman.
If humans
all live the same way,
it would be boring, right?
I just want
to meet someone I like
and date him.
When we're stable,
we'll naturally get married.
When our marriage is stable,
we'll have a kid.
But even if I don't have these things,
it's fine too.
It's fine.
It's fine if I don't have them.
I wish I could live until I'm 200.
What? 200 years old?
That's nice.
Fanxing, let's go home.
Canyang.
My brother.
Let's go home.
Canyang.
Are you here to see his niece?
You know what?
Once, at Yuan Song's house,
she thought I was the housekeeper.
Apologize to her, Cai Minmin.
-Apologize to her.
-There's no need.
Cai Minmin!
There's no need.
Uncle, you're drunk.
I'll help you to your room.
No, I'm not done drinking yet.
Let's go home.
What's with your sister?
She can't forget her ex,
but she still dated my uncle.
Where are her morals?
What about my sister's morals?
Your uncle pursued her so closely
like a stalker.
How is my uncle like a stalker?
She could have called the cops on him.
So everything is her fault?
Doesn't it take two to tango?
You can't blame my uncle for everything!
You're doing the same thing
towards my sister!
Fanxing, let's go.
Where's your bag?
No.
I still want to play
with Nonsense Ye Luming.
-Let's go home.
-Nonsense He Fanxing, drink up.
-Nonsense He Fanxing.
-Nonsense Ye Luming.
Nonsense Ye Luming.
-Nonsense He Fanxing, drink up.
-Horse!
Horse, go!
Go!
Good morning, everyone!
Good morning?
You're late again. Come and help me pack.
Why are you so angry in the morning?
Chang Huan.
Why do you like her?
Can you be polite to your superior?
I'm sorry. I got a notice
from human resources.
I just got promoted!
I'll report to the headquarters
in two days.
I'll be the manager of Marketing Team Two!
Congratulations!
The previous manager of that team
was promoted to marketing director,
so there was a vacant position.
I'll count on you in the future,
Manager Cong.
Of course.
You are all my family and friends.
I will treat you well.
Thanks, Ms. Cong!
Hurry, help me pack.
Okay, Ms. Cong.
The marketing manager's salary
is affected by the department's
sales performance.
Chang Huan, you'll have to work
extra hard then.
Shut up.
How else can he work hard?
He's already working overtime every night.
What about his health?
Don't sleep late because
you think you're young.
Do you know how many people died
because they sleep late?
Didn't you see the news?
All right. I'll listen to you.
What a stench. The stench of love!
Say that again!
Yuan Song, your annual leave
has been approved.
Seven days.
Remember to bring us some souvenirs.
All right.
-Where are you going?
-Suzhou.
In two days, my favorite architect
is having a talk there.
I want to learn from him.
You're going alone?
I'm going with Luo Wenyue.
Both of us admire that architect.
No wonder you look so happy.
Don't misunderstand,
I don't like Luo Wenyue.
You don't like her,
but she likes you.
It's easy for girls to pursue guys.
You seem pretty happy now.
Not long ago, somebody looked
so depressed every day.
When Luo Wenyue appeared,
you got all perked up again.
Men always say one thing but mean another.
Young man, good luck.
What luck? I told you I don't like her.
Okay, you don't like her.
The door is open.
Is there no water at home?
Here.
I peeled a pomelo for you.
Eat it with sugar
to get rid of bad breath.
Look at the time.
It's 4:00 p.m., Fanxing.
Do you think it's fine
to get so drunk at night?
Don't be like this.
It feels like something
is about to happen.
It scares me.
-He Canyang.
-Yes?
Help me out.
If Mom passes out,
call the ambulance.
What?
Subtitle translation by
Jane Ng Sweer Jieng