The Taoism Grandmaster
Episode 16
Lady Jiang.
You're not thinking straight.
The God of Deity won't stand by your side.
Lord Cui.
Lady Jiang.
Why are you here?
I'm here to offer incense.
Lord Cui.
I have something to tell you.
Lady Jiang, please.
They all say
I used your heart to make my dream come true.
They say I'm a lowly woman
and have a high-spirited heart.
They're talking nonsense.
Everyone comes and goes alone.
The so-called top-class family looks glorious.
But it's normal to be defeated.
If I didn't take advantage of the family affairs,
what kind of man am I?
But I made a mistake.
You really don't mind?
What mistake did you make?
Your uncle was more reluctant to marry you than you were.
He had no choice but to marry you.
They were the ones who made the mistake.
You have too many difficulties in this world.
Buddha said,
I'm the most ordinary woman.
I'm willing to do everything to help you.
Please forgive me.
Everyone is suffering.
Why do you have to forgive me?
Because you've hurt everyone.
Buddha is above.
If your heart wants to succeed,
you can't forget it.
Of course.
I'll send you back.
Okay.
It's not yours.
You can't get it no matter how hard you want to.
I've never seen a woman like you.
A woman who is like a woman.
She's beautiful and elegant.
She's fearless.
She doesn't need to be afraid.
In your life,
are you living a free life?
Of course.
That's great.
I've never left this city.
It's hard to live here like a human being.
Don't blame the bad environment.
Sometimes,
you have to think about yourself.
Are you kind enough?
Do you always help others?
Because I'm not kind enough to be bullied.
Interesting.
I want to see
how you can use kindness to change others.
I'm scared to death.
This subordinate is too cruel.
Kindness reminds you
that this is not a game.
If you lose,
you will die.
If he does this to the consort,
he will harm more people.
I'm scared.
I'm scared of more people.
Sister, eat.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Ji Yuan Lang,
you dare not pay
my gambling debt?
You're not a man.
I'm a man.
You dare not pay?
When my sister enters the house,
I'll give you money.
Come on.
How much gambling can the house
let this poor uncle?
Listen.
I've calculated.
Your sister and my son are in love.
Let her marry my son.
Gambling debt is very effective.
Otherwise,
everyone will know
your ugly things.
Your son?
Isn't your son already...
dead?
What are you thinking about, brother?
Nothing.
He's been acting impolitely and boldly these days.
He's not like my sister.
Why don't you hand him over?
Sister,
I saw a game outside.
Do you want to go and have a look?
Yes.
Of course.
I'm so bored.
Go.
If I go out of this door,
I'll be tied to a wedding.
My dear brother.
You...
What do you mean you?
Call me sister.
Sister.
Sister, you have to save me.
Sister, open the door.
Sister, do you know?
That woman seems to be good at gambling.
She's probably a witch.
And she said
she wanted Li Yuanyuan to kill me.
You have to save me.
Get out.
I'm not a witch.
I'm a man.
Wait.
She took the money in your money house
to please the people of the Prime Minister's Mansion.
You don't care about that?
Where is she?
What a beautiful bride.
Who are you?
Bridegroom.
Li Yuanyuan.
Tell the witch to sell me out.
Women should have a family
to decide their marriage.
Your brother has agreed.
I'm a man.
I'm not a wound.
You sold a lot of money.
You're contented, right?
You're really like a woman.
What a pity for my son.
Madam, we're both women.
Let me go, okay?
Shut up.
What are you?
It's your bad luck to serve my son.
Madam, the time has come.
Let me go.
Go back, go back.
Hurry.
Amazing.
It seems you really
have bought money.
Please let my brother go.
So he can earn more.
He threw away a sacrifice.
Let's go.
You're such a liar.
You took a prick for the wedding.
Go back to find our bridegroom.
Okay,
call me.
Go.
Come inside.
Wait.
This room this big
is what you deserve.
Don't blame me.
Bow to each other.
Jiu Jiu.
What's wrong, my lady?
Go prepare the carriage. I'm going out.
It's late at night.
Go.
Yes.
What are you laughing at?
On my wedding day,
shouldn't I laugh?
I should call you two eunuchs and aunts.
It's good that you've thought it through.
It's a blessing to be able to become a family with you two.
Enough.
Continue.
Don't waste time.
Enter the bridal chamber.
Let go.
I'll do it myself.
Master,
Shen Quezi came to the capital to get the wedding dress.
His name is the enemy of the border.
He's actually a spy.
The Third Prince and the Prime Minister are very worried.
It's a wedding.
You don't have to mind it.
Master.
Cui Youan.
You're awake.
How dare you!
Cui Youan.
You're so anxious.
Go away.
My wife is not very obedient.
Shut up.
You know the rules.
She's a girl.
You can't coax me.
Life is short.
Why don't you do something interesting?
You're drunk.
Cui Youan.
You're so pretty.
You're like the moon in the sky.
But you're pretty.
But you're a little cold.
Please be careful.
Cui Youan.
I want to tell you a secret.
What?
This is my first kiss.
Shi Jiao.
Take her back.
No.
I...
Go.
I won't go back.
Cui Youan.
Let me go.
Where are we?
I'm in a hurry to see your dead husband.
We're in the north street.
Sangqiao.
Get out of the way.
Who dares to stop our Li Yuan's family's wedding?
Are you a soldier?
I want to ask for help.
The situation is good.
Who would care about a woman at this time?
Of course I don't care.
But...
North street.
Purple stone.
Soldier.
Right now.
Guards.
It's time to go.
Tang Tianyi's son.
Li Tiandan's son.
The world is in danger if we kill him.
You want to die?
What kind of magic is that?
You want to kill us?
Shut up.
Father, mother.
Don't you miss your son?
I'll send you to see him now.
The king's son is dead.
We must find him.
Open the door and let him shut up.
Hurry up.
Come on.
If you want to die,
die together.
Don't think about living.
Shut up, you bitch.
Guards.
Rebellion.
You read it correctly.
Yes.
What's your crime?
According to the law of our country,
those who rebel
will be beheaded.
You're not afraid of death?
I am.
But I'm more afraid of my enemy.
General.
This woman is crazy.
She has nothing to do with me.
I'm willing to be the judge.
I'm willing to prove my innocence.
Li Wu Zheng.
You don't remember me?
I've been looking for you for many years.
The night of the letter box three years ago,
I found you.
You were running away,
and someone was sneaking into our rear.
The guard at the gate of the imperial gate was killed.
You...
You've got the wrong person.
I remember the face of the enemy
after many years.
Kill him.
Master.
Shen Juan.
Your eyes
look like an old friend of mine.
General Wang.
For the sake of you,
and the old stone,
I'll let the woman live.
You want to live?
Yes. I want to live.
For living,
can you sacrifice everything?
Why?
Nothing is more important than me living.
Yes.
This
looks like her.
My life
is in your mind.
Please show me your face.
If you don't go,
the old friend you look like
will have a grudge against me.
Master.
Mr. Cui.
I didn't see him.
General Shen.
Just kidding.
Sorry.
You just returned to the capital.
You know it.
Please be careful.
Yes.
I'm a man of my word.
I have no roots.
You are the most important person in the world.
Thank you for your consideration.
Unduechuckling
leave now.
I'm fine.
It's not my blood.
I'll give you a ride home.
Okay.
The truth ANYONE,
and anyone ever cares about,
be sure to find it yourself!
Childe Cui didn't stay
with the last General.
Have you ever heard
Cui You'ai!
Shi Jiu, let me go!
Why don't you go back?
Cui You'ai,
I just kissed you.
Why are you hiding?
I was careless.
What?
I was the one who took the initiative.
What's wrong?
You...
It's the first time
I've seen you angry.
I'm not.
I met him at Guan Yin Bridge.
I found him drunk.
So I ordered Shi Jiu to send him back.
So you're câmera
treatment.
You're program treatment.
It's Hall of Mercurnial removing loved ones?
You really specialized to
emerge from hold-up
and receive leaders withkell the struggles of life?
Now I'm your Miss's
loyal secretary.
He treats me like
your most special character.