's
run
.
Behind the unboxing,
the
England
ings
So I didn't think
that
I would
have known
until now
and
Not me.
It's your brother.
Why do you want to know?
Because I can make up for the past.
How is that possible?
How is that impossible?
Two of your sisters have appeared.
What else is impossible?
I also know
the test for the Spring Festival Exam next year.
You went to gamble
just to get money
to buy the Spring Festival Exam?
You know that?
I told him that
it was just to protect myself.
How did I know that he let me go
and sold you to get married?
It's none of my business.
I'm not like you.
I have a bottom line.
What are you doing?
Yao Zu.
He wants to sell me to get married.
It's Yao Zu's fault.
But you're his sister.
He has always loved you since he was a child.
He will change
if you teach him more.
Jiang Su.
Okay.
I'll teach him.
Yao Zu.
What are you doing?
I'm not doing anything.
I'm just trying to help you.
What are you doing?
Someone reported that he tried to bribe the examiners.
We'll arrest him.
I didn't.
You're wronged.
My son is an educated man.
How could he do such a thing?
Cut the crap.
Arrest him.
Yes.
No.
What are you doing?
My son.
Mom.
Yao Zu.
Help me.
Mom.
You're the one who arrested him.
Jiang Jiu.
Go and tell them
that Yao Zu is wronged.
Go.
Mom.
I'm wronged too.
Yao Zu.
Don't be afraid.
The whole family
will get you out.
Yao Zu.
My son.
Don't be afraid.
Mom.
Don't touch me.
Yao Zu.
Yao Zu!
The mortal is still an immortal.
I'm fine.
Only my son can't forget.
Your Majesty's sons
are all great.
They are the best in the country.
What do you know?
Shen Que.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your adoptive father sent you to find me.
You An.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your father has been the chancellor many times.
He wants to make you the crown prince.
Your father
is for the country and the people.
But I have something to do.
I can't think of anything else.
I'm willing to share your worries.
Okay, Zhun.
Your Majesty.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The crown prince has a long life.
How long have you been single?
I'm worried for
I'm not the one who came to pick you up.
Very good.
Three, two, one.
Wait.
I'm hungry.
You dare to play tricks on me?
Do you believe that I'll kill you?
I was the one who was hungry before.
No matter how hard life is, it won't be short for you.
You should have some self-respect.
Is it my fault that we're married?
Do you think I'm not a big shot?
You're hiding at home every day.
Don't you know that the people outside are talking nonsense?
Which sister is not a big shot?
You're not a big shot.
You're too selfish.
General Chen.
What are you doing here?
Why are you running away?
We meet again.
I still like the way you dressed last night.
Greetings, General.
That's your brother.
Guards.
Drag him down.
Yes.
General,
did you see it?
I don't know what you mean.
I was blocking the arrow for you last night.
A man would die for a woman.
I was touched.
If this woman is indifferent,
how can she be honest?
You're right.
Yes.
I should take good care of your love for me.
The one that unites you.
The one that unites you
is you.
Director Kang,
you're Witeng Ringmaster.
Finger~~~
I'll strike according to command.
Hunian,
I'll accept if it's out of context.
Your Majesty has explicit instructions on this matter.
I don't understand what you mean,
please give me your comments.
If he tells me anything, I'll kill your brother.
Speak.
I don't want to.
Please go ahead.
If I might zip out your谢谢,
then enough.
Hurry up.
I'm long ago into a many- będziemy inches-long book.
That is me.
I went through the fire
and was saved by the ancient goddess.
I married the man she ordered
and fell in love with her.
The life of the Nixi is perfect.
Except that
the ancient goddess is not dead now.
Will this change the plot?
The next plot should be
Cui You'an sent a invitation to Jiang Jiaojiao.
The Prime Minister's banquet.
Where is my invitation?
Mr. Cui.
Why are you here?
I heard that your brother was in prison.
Do you need help?
No need.
I should let him suffer.
By the way,
my aunt will come to my father's birthday banquet tomorrow.
She said she wanted to see you.
I...
My lady,
that is the Empress.
This is the invitation.
Thank you, Mr. Cui.
My lady will come.
My lady,
we should dress up well
when we go to the Prime Minister's mansion.
This one.
A little butterfly
flies over the Banyin Bridge.
Little butterfly
flies...
Here.
I've been crazy for so many years.
I feel so pitiful.
It's okay.
I have my wife and you are always by my side.
Eat slowly.
There is more.
koorakor infantry
Tongidula
Angry child!
Here you are.
Yes, hit it.
You are so easy to deal with.
Jiang Song
really sent the red rain-baker
in my behalf.
I should be the heroine.
Come on.
Yao Zu.
Yao Zu is the only child of my family.
Mother.
How can I let Lian Zu and Lian Zu down?
It's all over.
He hurt you so much.
It's all because of my mother.
Mother.
It's not a game.
If you lose, you will die.
What should I do?
He is so cruel to his own brother.
He can't stay at all.
He will be in a mess if he doesn't stop.
I can't be soft-hearted anymore.
Come on.
Second Young Master.
Yes.
Come on.
This is really a beautiful girl.
Right?
She is a beautiful girl.
Master.
Mr. Li and Mr. Wang are here.
Congratulations.
Please come in.
Come on.
Congratulations.
Mr. Li.
Please come in.
Please.
His Majesty is getting worse.
At this critical moment,
he wants to find the future of the Crown Prince.
He doesn't want to make another crown prince, right?
Don't worry, Your Highness.
The third prince succeeded the throne.
It's the destiny.
Cui You'an.
A businesswoman.
She is a bitch.
She even dresses up as a noble woman.
She is so rude.
She can only make a few people look good.
According to the plot,
if I can get the experience,
I can make Cui You'an fall in love with me.
Why are you here?
Where is Mrs. Jiang?
She can't come.
I'll come for her.
No one can replace her.
No one can replace me.
You'an.
That's the woman you mentioned.
Let me see her.
Aunt, she...
Cui You'an.
Do you want Her Majesty
to know that there are two strange things about Jiang Jiaojiao?
I've been a Buddhist since I was a child.
I'm afraid that she will become a nun.
I'm relieved to see you.
By the way,
what birthday gift did you bring?
Show us.
You didn't bring anything, did you?
Don't make it difficult for me.
I've never seen such a rare treasure.
You're right.
But you should know some etiquette.
It's important to be polite and kind.
Your Highness,
I'm afraid that my etiquette
will be unnoticeable to you.
OK.
Bring it on.
Let me go.
Mrs. Jiang.
Since you know it,
you can't go.
Let me go.
Don't scream.
Why are you so stubborn?
Let me go.
Be good.
Mother.
I told you not to scream.
Don't meddle in my business.
Or I'll kill you.
Mother.
Get out of here.
Will you cry if I die?
Will you regret running away because of fear?
I understand.
I need you to protect my child.
I'm sorry.