The Taoism Grandmaster
Episode 18
General, bad news.
The scout is here to report that
Cui You An is having another wedding.
It's... it's with Lady Jiang.
Could it be that Lady Jiang
really wants to marry into the Prime Minister's Manor?
Why are you doing this to me?
Let go of me!
Master said
that this is a play for Jiang Song.
It's a live show.
If you can't stand it,
leave the white cloth.
I'll let go. You pretend to be dead.
Shi Jiu!
It hurts, Shi Jiu!
Without my wisdom,
it's not important.
It hurts, Shi Jiu!
It hurts!
As long as you beg me,
you can take revenge.
How do you feel?
Not bad.
But not enough to take revenge.
I want to kill her myself.
Okay.
Jiang Song, I beg you.
Don't kill me.
I'll do it myself.
Okay.
Jiang Song.
I beg you, don't kill me.
No.
Jiang Song, I beg you, don't kill me.
Jiang Song, I beg you.
Let me go. Don't kill me.
No.
Jiang Song.
You want to die?
Let her go.
Cry.
Hate me.
Who said I was your creator?
Why are you laughing?
My creator.
You must have a way to take me out of the city.
Right?
I made you so miserable.
You don't cry or make trouble.
How can I find a way to take you out of the city?
Tears are useless to hurt yourself.
Hatred is blind to the mind.
No eternal enemy.
Only companions of the heavenly and earthly power.
You and I are half of the world.
Don't compete with each other.
Why don't we make a deal
before we die?
You have nothing.
What can you bring me?
Have you ever thought
you don't need Cui Youan's armory
but your own weapons?
I only need Cui Youan.
He has everything.
But that's his.
You can only get it
if he gives it to you.
Why don't you try
to take it all in your own hands?
Enough.
Don't try to fool me.
You just want to trick me
and replace me.
The role of the character in the story is selected.
Will you make an effort
to change the ending and become the main character?
Where did you get the confidence
that the story you designed
will be better than my own life?
You...
You are so arrogant.
You can't win me over.
You can't learn
how to deal with people
without falling down.
Put down your sword
and come here.
Isn't it good for you
to take revenge on me?
I can't even
take the love
that you gave me
to be your pet.
I won't take it from you.
I don't need your reward.
He is afraid of your power.
He is a fool.
But using this power
is the most hateful thing.
What did you say?
Zhuxu.
Dad.
Get up.
I'll take you away.
Are you okay?
That way.
You...
Jiang Qixiao.
Are you still not awake?
No.
He didn't really want to kill me.
Otherwise, he wouldn't let Shijiu tell me
that it was just a joke.
You ask me what I can give you.
The first one
is to give you only one.
Can you take it from me?
I'm just giving you
a way out of the prison.
The way is right in front of you.
You go or not go.
You think
it's not a prison
when you run away?
Let me tell you
what is the prison of a beautiful woman.
It's the appearance.
I'm not guilty.
I'm not guilty either.
A ugly guy,
a fox,
they're all in our class.
What a coincidence.
Xue Miaoli
is ordinary and guilty.
Not ordinary and guilty.
What's wrong with my bedroom security?
I'm your guardian.
You're a big girl.
I have to care about you.
You're not obedient when you're a big girl.
You have your own opinion, right?
Look at what you drew.
Age,
age,
and age.
You said I was biased.
Just an egg.
How old are you?
What's wrong with you?
What did you learn in school?
The more you learn, the more ignorant you are.
Our prison
is a pair of eyes that judge us.
We seem to have a lot of choices.
In fact,
we have no choice at all.
Then don't wait for others to make a choice
and walk out of a way by yourself.
I'm not afraid.
How to go?
Just trust me.
Shen Que will come to save us.
Little Nine.
It hurts.
I'm in his hands.
Run!
Little Nine.
Since you are not good,
I can only send you to the netherworld.
It's a pity that
I haven't played enough.
Be careful.
Jiang Song.
Shen Jun.
I'm sorry.
Jiang Song.
Shen Jun.
Are you okay?
Jiang Song.
Master.
Mr. Cui.
Wait.
She is the criminal who escaped from prison.
She will be punished tomorrow.
General Shen and I
are under the supervision of the police.
Eunuch De.
My son.
Premier.
I understand.
The criminal escaped from prison.
Mr. Cui saw her being pitiful and kind.
He didn't expect
she was a criminal.
Yes.
Thank you, General Shen.
Mr. Cui.
Miss Jiang.
I didn't see you at home today.
I didn't expect to meet you here.
What's the matter?
A few days ago,
I was in the netherworld.
I saw you.
I'm sorry for the trouble at the restaurant a few days ago.
I can't remember it clearly.
But I must have been confused.
I came to the Prime Minister's Mansion yesterday to propose a marriage proposal.
I'm really ashamed.
Isn't this what you want?
I mean,
this marriage can help you get rid of your troubles.
Isn't it?
Yes.
But I'm so sorry for you.
It's not a big deal for me to marry a married woman.
Are you in a bad mood today?
Maybe it's the reason for the good reputation.
Yes.
The world is full of good reputation.
People on the road want to break off their marriage.
Each lamp is a letter to the people who have passed away.
We're lighting the lanterns for my father.
Do you want to light the lanterns too?
So you won't have to worry about your own death.
No need.
I'll leave you alone.
Mrs. Jiang.
If a close person has passed away,
but she doesn't feel sad,
do you think this kind of person is heartless?
Not really.
Oh?
People's sorrow
may be as short as a storm
or as long as a storm.
But there's another kind of person
who is ignorant and unrivaled,
but at some point breaks out of the earth.
This is what makes her so amazing.
She's been growing up in the dark.
Is this kind of person worth being understood?
It's worth asking yourself.
Thank you.
This is the lotus soup fish cake I made.
If you don't mind,
please try it.
Goodbye.
Mrs. Jiang, you're also here to light the lanterns?
Yes.
This smell.
Those who don't light the lanterns are like a single light.
There are thousands of lanterns.
Those who are bright are bright.
You're as bright as a grass,
but you're not as beautiful as a Bodhisattva.
Why can't I do it?
Why?
General Shen,
I know that you're forced to
do this for the Cui family
because you're the daughter of the Cui family.
I'm helpless.
I won't be able to win.
Thank you for your understanding.
In the official field,
there's me and you.
I just hope that you can take care of me in the future.
Eunuch De Ming,
I'm sorry.
Eunuch De Ming, it's time.
Wake up.
I was provoked by a man.
But my family didn't help me.
I'm innocent.
I was a widow for 15 years.
The county committee said that they would give me a piece of the needle and a needle.
I made him change it to food.
He blamed me for being disrespectful.
Am I guilty?
I'm innocent.
I killed my man.
He hit me.
I beat him.
I'm guilty.
But I don't admit it.
I dressed up as a man to attend the imperial examination.
I was exposed.
I died of laughter.
It's not a pity.
I'm innocent.
They didn't catch up at the last minute.
fatuous
My god.
Thank you.
seedlings now.
Court Lady department,
after the malt capability of Ninth Lord
ended,
you can come back and repeat my request.
Leave all of her
to me.
A'Mo.
Wait.
As a beloved servant,
I'd better let them
settle.
It's okay.