The Taoism Grandmaster
Episode 16
Doctor Li, how is General?
I'll give General a few shots first.
Okay.
Look at my skills.
I really forgot to bring it.
Please go to the clinic and get me the needle.
Okay.
As a doctor who saves people, how can you kill people?
I killed the person I should kill.
How dare you be so impudent!
Zhang Chao, do you still remember?
When someone in the village of Tuolin
was hiding the scouts of the Lake,
you actually killed the whole village.
The whole village was in shock.
My daughter is among them.
And her eight-year-old son.
And so many innocent people.
Do you remember what happened?
I killed so many people.
I don't care about them.
Good and evil are always rewarded.
Even if I can't take the responsibility today,
your body won't last for a few days.
At least you'll die before me.
Shen Quan, kill him.
Do it.
Father, he's a doctor.
Why don't you charge into the army?
Do you also think I should die?
No.
I gave my life to him.
Not only your life.
If it weren't for me,
would you have the achievement today?
Now this person wants to kill me.
What should you do?
Kill me.
Zhang Chao, you can't die.
You can't die.
If you're not out of the tribe,
our tribe will be in danger.
Zhang Chao, will never be put in this mess.
Your Majesty!
Wan'an.
Let him go.
Father.
How is the Prime Minister?
His Majesty ordered him to be sent to the mansion
under the order of Xiuyang
and sent people to keep an eye on him.
I'm in the capital.
Li Dacheng is training in the Eastern Camp.
They won't be able to get away with it.
If we don't have any time,
we must find the commandant of the Clouds as soon as possible
and make them a punishment.
Tomorrow is the Spring Festival.
Keep an eye on them.
Yes.
Father.
After the Spring Festival,
I want to get married.
I'm afraid that I'll be a burden to you.
Since you've made up your mind,
I have nothing to hide.
In fact, he was the one who asked me to save you.
What?
He stabbed you with a knife
and my reinforcements
ran away from those rebels.
He ran with you and my team
all day and night
asking me to save you.
He also said that you know some martial arts
and knelt down to beg me to keep you.
He said that you can't
and asked me not to mention him in front of you.
Why are you here?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just want to see you.
I won't let you go again in the future.
Don't think about the future.
It's good to have now.
Tomorrow is the Spring Festival.
I hope nothing will happen.
Stay at home these days.
Miao Hua will take care of you.
I'll feel more at ease.
But I'm still a little worried.
Don't worry.
They haven't found the Clouds of Courage yet.
They can't touch the Night Star Pavilion.
I can hold on.
What's wrong?
I'm afraid that I'll be a burden to you.
Nothing.
With him by my side,
it's like you're by my side.
Let's go.
Shen Que.
I'll wait for you.
Wait for me.
They've been playing chess these days.
It seems nothing is wrong.
No one is coming in or out.
They didn't say anything.
No.
It's not æ.
What's that smell?
The smell seems to be around.
It's a odor.
What is this?
General.
Yuan Hua.
What happened outside?
I don't know where many people came from.
They are going to the palace to kill.
Is Ye Xing Ke?
General.
The general said to protect you.
I'll go and have a look.
Ah.
Yuan Hua.
We've finally got to the end of the story.
Jiang Jiao Jiao.
I'm not Jiang Jiao Jiao.
You are soon.
You don't even know the seven-seven.
Ye Xing Ke is divided into two.
Half of them follow the order of Yun Yong.
The other half follow the order of Feng Qi.
Right.
The order of Feng Qi
is in the hands of the prime minister.
You mean
only half of the Ye Xing Ke
is in the mess now?
Yes.
When we find Yun Yong,
Cui You An will be safe.
It's up to you.
What does it have to do with me?
Jiang Song can't find Yun Yong.
But Jiang Jiao Jiao knows where he is.
Don't you remember anything?
What!
I don't remember
anything at all.
Can't you remember anything?
In fact, you know me.
How could I possibly know you?
You've known me for a long time.
I was born into this life.
I'm leaving.
A little butterfly
flew over the Guanyin Bridge.
Are you running for the bride?
After I escaped from the city,
I still had nowhere to go.
God Bi saved me.
I had a new life
with this mask on.
You once killed yourself
to exchange for a dog's life.
No wonder you insisted on me being a Jiang Jiaojiao.
Isn't it good to be a Jiang Jiaojiao?
Look.
So many people died.
A city was destroyed.
A dynasty was destroyed.
Just to fight for you.
Just to break through your love story.
So many people died
because of me?
No.
This is not real.
This is a nightmare.
No.
Look.
This is the world of the heroine.
No killing,
pain,
ugly.
Only flowers.
The man who loves you
is covering for you.
He is protecting you.
You just have to be a Jiang Jiaojiao.
You have a choice to be oppressed by the cruel truth.
You have to choose not to learn
something hidden from this flower beggar.
The guest who sets off 먹을
has not just the truth,
but there is pleased between us.
And the person who leaves his lovely home
and goes that way
can once again become a cool and precious more to you.
I spend the rest of them
Why can't you live with yourself?
Jiang Song.
Jiang Jiaojiao.
Very well.
You are Jiang Jiaojiao.
Think about where the Yunyong Order is.
I will be there.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
I will take care of my grandson.
Cheng Ze, you were born in the royal family.
I hope you can live a safe life in the future.
You can't let anyone else take the throne.
Maybe when the Yun Kai Wu San is over,
he can help you.
I remember it now.
Where?
The Yunyong Order
is on the throne of Zhao Cheng Ze.
So fast.
The sun, the clouds and the clouds are all empty.
Losing you is a lot of work.
No matter how busy I am, I have no worries.
I can't live up to my love.