[Park Min Young]
[Ko Kyoung Pyo]
[Kim Jae Yeong]
[Love in Contract]
[All characters, businesses, groups, locations, products, and incidents are fictitious. The use of animals was filmed safely under the supervision of experts.]
How dare he get angry at me?
If it's not a drunk habit, what is it then?
It's not a drunk habit! Forget it.
At least I'm not cowardly like you. I'm devoted to my feelings.
No, I am!
- You are? You were never sincere—
- What's the point you're trying to make?
Are you saying I felt tempted in front of my ex-wife?
Are you denying it?
Think about it one more time.
Of course, I was caught off guard.
You forgot to drop me off at my place.
I was there to confess my love to you, but you were with my ex-wife.
How can any man stay calm in that situation?
I was nervous and afraid to ruin everything. Gosh!
Fine, I'm sorry I couldn't drive you to your place.
- What did you say?
- I said I'm sorry.
No, not that.
You said you tried to confess your love to me?
Otherwise, why would I go there?
It would have been nice if you told me sooner!
I wouldn't have felt so worthless then...
How is that for an answer?
♫ Open the door; knock on our time ♫
♫ You shone on me, and I'll be like springtime for you ♫
♫ You became light and shone on me ♫
♫ You're the only one for me ♫
[Love in Contract]
[Episode 10]
Geez! You scared me!
Yes.
Did you get home safely?
It's late. Why aren't you sleeping?
But you still drove me home.
I thought I should at least check if you got home safely.
Yes, I got home safely. Why don't you go to sleep now that you've confirmed?
Pardon?
Yes, I'll hang up then.
- Sang Eun.
- Yes?
Well, I'm sorry.
About what?
It's just that...
you looked tired.
You said you didn't sleep due to me. So I said that out of worry.
I see.
So this is the charm of a straightforward man.
You must be more tired than me. You should go to sleep first.
Yes.
Why don't you hang up first?
No, you hang up first.
No, I'll go to sleep if you hang up first.
No! You go first.
No, you should go first...
Also, you have to work tomorrow.
You go to work tomorrow, too.
You should go to bed since you must be Kang Hae Jin's wife tomorrow.
Well, yes. I should. Bye then.
[Client Jung Ji Ho]
[Let's meet after you finish work tomorrow.]
Wednesday feels too far away.
Does he like me that much?
A family introduction dinner?
Ms. Jamie and Kang Hae Jin?
To be accurate, it's Eena and Kangjin.
Both companies are in crisis.
They're probably too desperate to save face.
Also, they already announced marriage. What's the problem?
Whenever I saw Ms. Jamie,
she always expressed hatred toward the conglomerate world.
Are you sure she's okay with that?
She just got polluted because she was left alone.
I'll turn everything back now.
I don't think it would be easy...
I've been too easy on her.
Noona.
Hey, Noona.
Noona. Noona!
Hey!
Noona, we have a problem.
Madam Yoo is weird.
She's really weird right now, I said!
Get up right now. Come out!
You got up. Very good.
Irregular sleep isn't good for your skin.
- What's all this?
- Breakfast.
I prepared your favorites.
I have business to attend to.
Have a relaxing meal.
- What's wrong with her?
- It's so strange, isn't it?
She never even ate a tomato unless I washed and served it to her.
Wow, this is great.
You won't even touch her food, right? I'll take care...
Why would I get into petty fights with her?
I should take whatever I can.
She was making it since early this morning.
Does she feel guilty toward you?
Is she apologizing?
Hey, you really don't know how to read people.
Right, did you clean my room yesterday?
Did you clean my clothes and scarves?
No, I clean every Wednesday.
How am I supposed to eat this sandwich?
How should I eat this?
What a beautiful day.
Hey, this isn't so bad.
Thanks for all the hard work.
Yes, hello.
It's my first time seeing him smile.
You're right.
Hello.
Thanks for your hard work.
Good morning,
it seems.
He smiled... right?
Aren't you making it too salty?
What do you mean? My wife is my handicap.
If they combine a couple's scores, she will half mine.
Come on, you made four birdies (1 under par) last time.
Didn't you see her shoot double par?
Her golf bag is full of onions (sounds like double par). She can start selling onions.
Anyway, it's the third Sunday. It was hard to book.
Yes!
The third Sunday sounds good.
I'll attend.
Excuse me, but who are you?
Judge Jung Ji Ho told me not to invite him to couples' gatherings.
From now on, please invite us to all couples' gatherings,
including Sundays, of course.
He does look like him, but he's surely not Judge Jung Ji Ho.
Okay, but not for golf.
You can only play golf together if you're on a similar level.
But you can't even score 100 (72 is good).
I can play a good single's game.
Then just send your wife.
This is not good.
I won't put up with it if you oust me like this.
Well then.
I've never been scared of people.
But he's kind of scary lately...
a lot.
Did Jamie say that herself?
That she is seeing Kang Yoo Jin?
Yes.
She's the one in the tabloid photos.
By the way, didn't their youngest son leave home a while ago?
It is an issue that he's having conflicts with his father.
Kangjin's Chairman always brags about his youngest son whenever we play a round together.
He says he resembles him the most.
He can't stop bragging how he fights head on
and takes good care of his business.
Just wait and see.
He will become the powerhouse of Kangjin.
The older sons are just full of greed.
They lack brains to compete with him at all.
I'll have Ms. Jamie move back to the residence.
Is that really necessary?
- We can just get her a new house.
- That day...
if you treated her to a warm meal instead of forcing her
to an arranged marriage meeting on her return to Korea,
it might not have been such a disaster.
I raised her perfectly inside and out.
I told her that she was one of the Eena family.
I never told her that she was a hired robot.
If you want an obedient daughter,
you should be good parents first, right?
Along with you too, Ms. Yoo?
No.
What she needs is a family,
no more of a nanny.
So did you contact Kangjin?
The rumor of them becoming in-laws with Sunghan has spread everywhere.
I'll contact them myself.
- You came, Hyung.
- Yes.
These are from overseas fans.
Deliver them safely to my house.
Make sure not to forget any, not even one.
Do my fans know
that even Kang Hae Jin gets dumped by a woman?
Do you know what hurts more?
I kissed her, then got dumped.
I'm famous for being a good kisser.
How could I kiss her and... geez...
Yes, she might be playing hard to get.
She might be embarrassed she initiated the kiss.
She's a very proud woman.
Is it my turn to approach her?
Does she want me to do that?
Are you sure your arm is okay?
Yes, I'm fine since I'm still so young.
Anyway, where is that b*stard?
What b*stard?
You mean the new bodyguard?
Why are you being so touchy?
To pick a new project, you know I analyze the director's face instead of reading the script.
He's a good guy.
You should get along with him, okay?
Geez, I should gain success quickly.
[Kanghan Entertainment]
I can't believe I'm put on the same level as an inexperienced punk.
I should have gotten his number yesterday.
How great was he anyway?
- Couldn't you get his number?
- No.
He left while I was on the phone.
He's apparently the bride's friend. I should ask her.
He has a great, stylish voice,
and his face was not bad, either.
But most of all, his eyes are... Wow, they're so melodramatic.
I guess they're kind of deep.
Let me try to explain it.
Yes, exactly like those eyes.
What? What are you doing here?
- Hello, Hyungnim.
- Hey, you came.
This is the one I mentioned.
- This is my manager...
- Well...
Hey.
Why are you staring at him like that?
He is the one I meant.
Is he that b*stard?
- B*stard...
- Really?
I was going to introduce him to you, but you've already met.
Apparently, he saw you at the wedding yesterday.
He has a crush on you.
So the guy you hired after analyzing his face is...
Don't you have any sense of loyalty?
I worked with you for so many years.
I heard they hire young talents as managers these days.
You hired him to go on a variety show as your manager, right?
You're certainly imaginative when you get angry.
Anyway, follow him around and learn the job from him for now.
Okay.
He's the same age as you; try to be friends.
I'll stop by home and go to the shoot myself. Bye.
What did you see in him to hire him?
Did you even get his resume?
How do you know what he's been up to? What if he's a scammer or a thug?
I almost forgot.
Should I tell him?
Yes.
He's gay, apparently.
He wants to be open about it at work.
He hates work romance so don't worry.
- It's out in the open now.
- Yes.
Hyung!
I'm Woo Gwang Nam.
I didn't catch your name.
Your first impression wasn't that great, either.
You probably don't remember.
How dare you talk casually to me, Baby Hoobae (Junior)?
Why am I your hoobae? You're a manager, and I'm a bodyguard.
I heard we're the same age; let's get along.
I heard you injured your arm. Give me the key. I'll drive.
How dare you try to grab my knife in my kitchen?
He's a good slapper.
I'll be in touch!
[Benuee]
Thanks for all the help today.
I'll bring coffee and tasty pastries next time.
Geez. It's like he's starting out his acting career.
Thank you!
Move!
Gosh, you have to do it like this.
Like this! That's better.
All right.
Let's go.
I told you not to show off.
[CEO Choi Ran Hee]
Ha Young, you were... my life insurance.
Gosh.
Whose son is he? Gosh...
No technology will be able to create someone like that.
- Ha Young, I...
- Seriously...
My heart aches.
Yes?
Who?
Eena Group's... management support office?
She must have felt guilty.
That's why she made breakfast and cleaned.
Geez, my head hurts.
What should I tell Hae Jin?
Should I just be honest?
Face him head-on?
You came.
Hello.
Come in.
Hello, we meet again.
Yes, hello.
She apparently wants to tell you something.
Have a seat.
First, I'm aware that Mr. Kang is Kangjin Group's son.
Since he wants strong privacy,
I'll prioritize that.
Since the media is mostly talking about his marriage,
I think I should understand your background, Ms. Choi.
I'd like to get your permission.
Would that be okay?
N-No.
I rushed the marriage announcement since
I was trying to stop rumors and avoid a marriage arranged by my family.
We won't rush to get married.
I don't think it's necessary to dig deeper.
It's also about my girlfriend's privacy.
You two seem a little distant.
It's easy to get into fights while preparing your wedding.
You get sensitive to each other as there is a lot to worry about.
How was it for you?
Preparing for your marriage?
Me? Well...
It was very hard for me.
But you're a good man, Hae Jin.
I can tell you love and respect Sang Eun.
Some men trap women in the world they created
and hurt them in every little thing.
They treat you like a puzzle piece.
Would you like to read the document?
I never thought I was immature,
but I realize I was back then.
I realized later.
You quit your job as a lawyer,
and you bought this apartment that I've always wanted to live in.
By chance... Did you wait for me?
I'm getting hungry.
Would you like a bagel?
Jung Hwan got me some...
Here.
I'd like to apologize one more time.
Our kiss the other night...
That was kind of an accident.
You know, an accident?
She got me, after all.
She's making sure I'm dead.
Pardon?
No.
I expected this.
She only says what she means.
I understand.
So... you want a bagel or not?
Also, I'm not sure why, but I thought I should be honest with you.
I'm thinking of going out with Ji Ho.
I wasn't ready for that one at all.
What do you keep muttering under your breath?
That b*stard!
I mean...
That man, do you love him?
Do you mean it? Are you sure?
If you ask me like that...
It's hard to say for sure,
but I'd like to take the next step if there is one.
Our contract won't be affected, right?
Of course not. That's a separate issue.
But you're aware that we don't have much time left, right?
Could you give me some time, too?
The same amount of time you gave to Jung Ji Ho.
I started the contract late.
So you might change your mind.
Hae Jin.
I want to live my life now.
I want to be someone who has nothing to do with Eena or Kangjin Group.
But if we start seeing each other as you said,
the 13 years I spent escaping them,
and everything you've achieved will be
destroyed by them.
But... I don't think I can stand it if that happens.
Of course, that's definitely not the biggest reason.
Also...
Is there more?
Can you hurt me more?
I'll take that bagel.
Go ahead.
[In one piece (dryer sheets)]
What were you doing?
I was doing the laundry.
You do the laundry yourself?
It's easy to wash clothes nowadays.
I'm used to doing it on the days you're not here.
In five years, I guess it's our first time meeting on a Tuesday.
Well...
A plan came up that I didn't get a chance to mention to you.
So I...
got you some...
clothes in advance. I'm sorry.
It must be a place with a dress code?
Yes.
I had perfect scores many times in life,
but I was never called Mr. 100 before.
I need some training.
Then isn't this considered more of a job than a date?
No. I got cut from the couples' golf club due to my inability.
Should I just let it happen?
I shot an under-par that day.
We're a couple, aren't we?
It's a special gathering we joined as a team.
It's monumental.
We can't just let this happen. Let's start.
Okay.
♫ Boom, boom, Baby, goes my heart ♫
♫ When we're in the dark, I'll never let you go, no ♫
I'll try again.
♫ Boom, boom, Baby, goes my heart ♫
♫ When we're in the dark, I'll never let you go, no ♫
Here's the ball, right?
Squint your eyes, glance at it like this,
and slap it elegantly.
Slap it on its cheek.
I squinted too much.
Let go of your greed.
And then...
slap elegantly without forcing it.
♫ When we're in the dark, I'll never let you go, no ♫
That's much better.
Sang Eun, I made a reservation at a place with amazing salmon.
We'll arrive just in time if we leave now.
I'll consider this our first date going to this restaurant then.
Mr. Jung!
[The Swing: Black]
Gosh, Sang Eun is here, too.
Hello!
Of course, she's been giving him a lesson because he's falling behind.
Yes... Well, then...
Why don't we get dinner together?
We're going for something tasty.
No.
We're going to a salmon restaurant.
You all know how harsh Mr. Jung is.
That's why it's so awkward.
But his wife is the real deal.
His reputation at the court improved greatly, thanks to her.
You're coming with us, right?
Yes, let's do it.
Behave yourself.
Okay, let's go.
Get in, get in.
All right, the seventeenth round!
Help yourselves.
I brought a cool card with me today,
a Christmas card.
That was a joke.
Sang Eun, have some of this...
and do your best, please.
Sang Eun, have some eel soup.
They put only heads in it.
They didn't put anything like loaches in it.
It's good for you.
Also, Sang Eun loves to drink, too.
The more air the beer cocktail gets in contact with, the smoother it gets.
Let's put a lot of air into it.
All right, take a glass.
I was craving alcohol today anyway.
Do not force her to drink.
Here we go again.
We're trying to have a baby.
I'll have a glass instead.
No, don't drink it.
You're impossible to handle when you're drunk.
How much juice will you drink this time?
Drink water. Don't drink too much of it, though.
You'll get drunk from the water.
Let's drink without them.
Chief.
You have to eat eel regularly.
I'm starting to feel heated.
You guys are still full of energy.
I never tell my wife if I had eel.
Sleep, wake up, and leave the house quietly.
You live so diligently.
Mr. Jung, eat more, eat more.
Hey, Mr. Jung, just thank me for buying you eel if good news arrives.
You can do it.
Chief.
All right, let's go digest then.
Beer is the best bubbly drink.
Of course, that's our protocol.
- Let's drink something nice and cool.
- Sounds good.
You're coming, too, right?
We judges don't have a chance to get things off our chest at the court.
We build friendships by sharing a beer together.
We don't invite just anyone.
That's right.
We're okay.
We'll get going.
Why don't you try joining them?
I don't want to.
The court should look into it more...
Isn't this the first time your sunbaes invited you to a gathering like that?
I'm not interested in making an impression.
You should still go.
But it's our first...
If the children can't confirm that the parents' committee agrees,
they'll never get the verdict. Don't you think, Mr. Jung?
The court should make them get their children a psychologist.
I was going to tell you that anyway.
Maybe this is the perfect opportunity to discuss.
I'll just leave you to it.
I'll get going.
Well...
But I have a big card.
Where should we go then?
Sang Eun has left.
Let's just go to a convenience store.
Thank you!
[Client Jung Ji Ho]
You should focus on the meeting.
I said goodbye to them.
Already?
Yes.
I just told them what I needed to say and left.
I'm sorry.
It became work again.
Not at all.
What's important is that we hung out on a Tuesday for the first time.
But that's not enough. How about this?
What?
When we meet tomorrow for work,
we should go on a real date.
Let's.
Did he always have such a nice voice?
I should have recorded it. Did it record?
[CEO Choi]
Hey! Open the door!
Geez!
I know you're in there!
Seriously!
You b*stard!
I rang the bell at least thirty times!
Turn the music off!
Turn the light on!
Why are you here?
Your mom is freaking out because she can't reach you.
- Why don't you pick up the phone?
- There's probably a reason for that.
Everything's a mess right now!
Is the woman you're seeing really Eena Group's daughter?
She is.
Did Hyung say that?
What are you talking about?
He freaked out and said no.
Eena Group called.
She apparently told her family that she's seeing you.
She made me all upset earlier.
Is she playing with me right now?
What is it? Tell your uncle.
People only use me at times like that.
They use me and try to get what they want.
They only want me for that.
Talk to me so I can help you think!
This might not be her idea.
Eena Group might be using her.
Why would they use their daughter?
What the heck are you talking about?
[Jamie]
I want to live my life now.
I want to be someone who has nothing to do with Eena or Kangjin Group.
[Jamie]
Whatever...
The meal is good for detoxing.
It reduces puffiness too.
Enjoy yourselves.
She really must feel guilty toward you.
People who seem cold are actually tender inside.
When did she get new dinnerware?
It's unnecessarily pretty.
Wow, this is how it feels to be treated like royalty.
Is it good?
Eat, eat. Hurry.
Help yourself.
Geez!
Cut!
- Okay!
- Director.
Let's do it again.
That's what I'm saying, okay to do it again.
Let's go one more time!
I did action scene body double work before.
I learned Taekwondo so I have the form.
I have a good kicking form.
- Isn't that bodyguard so cool?
- I know, right?
- He's so cool.
- He seems quite a cool guy.
- Totally.
They pick on me all the time.
It's my first time on location.
Me?
Excuse me for a second.
What?
You must not know as a newbie.
Do you know how much they disdain management company employees if you let your guard down a bit?
They're really nice people!
You'll become a pushover.
Stop smiling at the wardrobe studio, shop, or film location!
You're really... ugly.
How could you call me "ugly"?
Not ugly looking, but ugly inside.
Let's have fun. Have fun.
- Let go, geez!
- Fun.
Wait for me!
Geez!
Don't come in here, I said!
How many times did I tell you not to come in?
It says "Filming" right here!
Who do you think you are?
You could have hurt someone.
Step back.
- Don't cross this.
- Okay.
Hey, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Hyung!
Geez.
It seems Eena and Kangjin are in a hurry.
The management support office apparently already discussed a family introduction.
Geez!
How scary.
But isn't that a good thing? I thought you really liked her.
I actually feel relieved.
You said she has roots.
And you get to be a good son, too!
But if we start seeing each other as you said,
the 13 years I spent escaping them,
and everything you've achieved will be destroyed by them.
But...
I don't think I can stand it if that happens.
The woman Hae Jin is seeing...
Have you met her?
Yes, a few times.
You know she is Eena Group's daughter, right?
Didn't Hae Jin tell you?
No, not yet.
How do they seem as a couple?
Please ensure I'm the first to know how they're doing.
Why?
Am I burdening you?
No, I don't like being paid in advance.
If something worthy of reporting comes up, I'll give you a call.
Why don't you reward me then wholeheartedly?
You're smart.
Why don't you check out the department store now that you're here?
- I'll tell the secretary.
- It's okay. I like being alone.
I have grocery shopping to do too.
I'll get going then.
Okay.
Yes, Son.
Schedule a meeting with Sunghan Group's daughter.
What?
I'll date their youngest daughter or whatever.
We broke up.
So don't get me involved with Jamie Jung.
Distance yourself from Eena Group.
What are you talking about?
You used to flip out since you didn't like Sunghan Group's daughter.
I don't dislike her. I'll date her.
If you bother me about this again, I'll forget Sunghan and everything.
You know I'm serious, right?
Hey! Hey!
Gosh! Seriously!
They say your mortal enemy in your past life becomes your child.
Don't apologize.
Today, I had time during the day, and you didn't.
But still,
I made a big deal of it, but I made you go shopping alone.
But instead,
no matter what you get, I'll try making something delicious with it.
Wow, what are the odds?
She's the daughter of an elite family?
How about gambas?
I just found the best shrimp in the universe.
Can you make creamy shrimp too?
By chance, can you make both?
How romantic.
Okay, Ji Ho. Yes.
Why are you bringing up Sunghan's daughter suddenly?
Hey, do you have schizophrenia or something?
You're driving me crazy.
Hey, hey! Makeup, makeup!
Geez...
Yes, Attorney Jung.
Did you know your girlfriend is having an affair with your neighbor?
Did you have no idea?
- It's not like that.
- What do you mean?
By chance, did you know they're dating?
There's a reason for it. You don't have to worry.
Kang Hae Jin, I'm your lawyer.
If this situation is leaked to the public, it'd be critical to your image.
Can't believe you announced marriage with a woman like this.
It's a contract-based relationship.
I'm the one who hired her.
All the rumors, pressure to get married...
I had to avoid the situation I was in.
We both agreed to a contract so there's no problem.
Please just protect my privacy.
But how about Oppa...
How about Jung Ji Ho?
She divorced 12 times. Her job is to get married.
You mean a woman who makes money through marriage
is taking advantage of Jung Ji Ho, too?
Please watch what you say.
Sang Eun didn't use him.
Jung Ji Ho hired her himself.
She wanted to retire, but he and I begged her not to, okay?
Where are you, Sang Eun?
I'm about to go to Ji Ho's. Why?
Never mind.
It's nothing.
Uncle, I mean, CEO.
Give me my car key.
- "My car key"?
- Hurry!
Kang Hae Jin!
Don't go now.
Why?
Well...
I need to tell you something. It'd only take a moment.
Is it urgent? I need to get going now.
I need to tell you right now.
- Must it be now?
- Yes.
Okay. What is it?
Why are you being so rude?
A man who hired his wife...
How funny.
Kang Hae Jin wanted to stop the rumor.
What could have been your reason?
Did you want to hurt me?
My wife will be here soon. Leave.
To be honest, I was quite shocked last time.
I was hurt by Jung Ji Ho.
- Leave.
- By chance, did you hold onto her
waiting for this moment? To cause me pain?
I said leave.
Why, do I like it?
Was your hatred toward me that much?
Geez, what should I say?
Well, Hae Jin. If you can't remember, let's talk tomorrow.
No, it's something really important.
Well, how do you say it?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Oh, my gosh! Where are you going? Where are you going?
Leave.
I told you. My wife will be here soon.
You're Kang Hae Jin's lawyer.
So you must know to keep quiet.
You're extremely professional.
I'm not interested in complaining about my wife's job.
So you should focus on your job, too.
How cool.
I heard she is Eena Group's daughter.
You despised me for obsessing over success.
But you're fine with one born with a silver spoon.
It was perfect revenge toward me, who was desperate to have anything.
She has a sick hobby since she has too much money,
bored with her life. How do you stand someone like that?
It's possible as you have no feelings for her.
I know you, Oppa.
The two corporations are really pushing Kang Hae Jin to marry her.
Quit your sick game
and call me.
I'm not the same anymore.
What are you doing? Put me down!
- I have to...
- Gosh!
My gosh!
- Well...
- You crossed the line!
So what are you trying to tell me exactly?
It might be difficult for you to understand now, but...
I'm sorry, Sang Eun.
I don't know what it's about,
but I'll see you tomorrow.
Ji Ho!
Sang Eun.
Where are the shrimps?
Well, they didn't... I...
I forgot to get them. I'm sorry.
Ji Ho.
Was someone here other than me today?
No, not at all.
Why do you ask?
Never mind.
The place felt unfamiliar for some reason.
It's strange that you feel unfamiliar in this place.
Well, I've been thinking, and...
I realized I don't know anything about your life.
My life isn't that special.
Also, you've been to my place once.
You said you have a roommate. What kind of person is your roommate?
My roommate?
Right, you've met him once.
He's the one who picked me up when we ate out the first time.
But he's... a man.
Well, yes, he is, but as a roommate,
he's more like a woman.
Yes, he is.
So...
But why do you ask all of a sudden?
I heard she is Eena Group's daughter.
Some men trap women in the world they created
and hurt them in every little thing.
They treat you like a puzzle piece.
Ji Ho.
I hope that you can accept
Choi Sang Eun as she is.
I'll do the same, too.
Yes!
I...
am planning to accept you
just as you are. Yes.
Well...
We don't have shrimp.
Should we order something in?
Yes, I love delivery food.
Let me look into it.
It's obvious.
- What?
- Husband No. 2.
He wants you to end things with Kang Hae Jin.
He can't ask directly or he'd sound petty.
So he's asking about your life and who your roommate is.
It's typical.
But it does seem wrong. They even live in the same building.
It's too much to ask him to understand.
But it's work.
- No?
- It is.
Also, the contract expires soon.
I know!
The contract expires soon. Why is he stopping you?
You helped him by pushing back your retirement too.
He's prioritizing his ridiculous rules over a person.
I'm going to work.
Okay, see you.
(court files)
Yes, Sang Eun.
Are you busy?
No, I'm okay.
I'm on my way to meet with Kang Hae Jin.
Oh, it's Thursday, right?
Yes, see you later then.
I'll terminate the contract with him.
I could tell you everything, persuade you and sort things out,
but right now, I want you to like me.
For some reason, it wouldn't bother me at all.
So I want to try my best and focus on only you.
Sang Eun.
Yes?
For real, let's go get something tasty tonight.
Okay.
- Can you put this next to that?
- Sure.
Please check the camera location!
Can you grab it from this angle? Because...
I'll move it to the left a bit.
Ask the camera crew to check the monitor.
- Yes.
- Please check the props.
Production Department, please check the props!
- Look (silently).
- What?
Hyung.
Yes?
I said you don't have to come to work because my schedule is full today.
But at least you visited me at work once.
- Eat before you go.
- Well, Hae Jin.
Yes. Got it.
I'll tell you the order of the breakup.
Even if we break up now, we must drag it out before the media notices.
That's how we do it in this field.
If you don't do anything with me from now on,
they'll write how our relationship has gone south, and rumors of our breakup will spread.
That's when we'll admit that we broke up a long time ago.
If an article says we just broke up, things will get kind of annoying.
They'll follow me all day and guess my facial expression
and every little action.
Your face won't get known, but
I don't think I can pretend to be fine.
♫ I'll always be there♫
I will take care of Kangjin.
I... want you to be happy, Hae Jin.
♫ Still always be there ♫
♫ I'm going to stay ♫
♫ Longing for you in my dream ♫
It hurts a bit.
♫ I'll wait for you tonight ♫
Hey.
Take a look at this.
Why would I look at your phone? Geez...
I want you to look at this right now.
What are you saying?
Yes.
What?
Yes, yes... Now? Yes. We're screwed.
That's why I told you to look at this!
Hey.
[Kang Hae Jin's fiancée's face revealed]
What?
[Kang Hae Jin's fiancee's face revealed]
Sang Eun.
H-Have a look at this.
Don't be shocked.
[TSEN: Kang Hae Jin's fiancée's face revealed]
[Kang Hae Jin's fiancée's face revealed]
[Accident? Planned? Kang Hae Jin revealed his girlfriend's face.]
[Kang Hae Jin's woman has finally been unveiled.]
What?
Look at this.
A reveal! A beautiful non-celebrity girlfriend.
It's Kang Hae Jin's fiancee.
[Was the face reveal a mistake? What is Kang Hae Jin's agency's reaction?]
[How does Kang Hae Jin feel about this?]
- No way!
- What the heck!
We're screwed.
Incredible.
What is this?
Wait...
I should make a reservation at the salmon restaurant.
I...
[Epilogue]
She recently lost her entire family and became an orphan.
I'll take care of her myself.
I'll leave the country and raise her as a perfect bride
Mom!
I'm a consultant who'll turn you into a perfect lady.
It's your job to stop acting cheaply.
Wow, it's really Korea!
I'm thinking of becoming a buyer.
I want to support Eena's weakness.
Before that, I need to meet my parents.
They'll probably like me, right? Do you think I can do a good job?
Have I assisted you for 13 years now?
It was all for today.
Your ambition and dream,
it's all good. But there's an important test before you get there.
You'll meet with the Kangjin family.
You'll meet the Kangjin heirs, whom I've always talked about.
Our target is the oldest son.
You must captivate him.
But this is my first time in Korea. Shouldn't I say hello to my parents?
Of course, they'll be there, too.
Do you... have a reason to meet with them separately?
♫ You shone on me, and I'll be like springtime for you ♫
Don't forget that you're the main project of the Eena Group.
I devoted my life to you.
Please prove that... it wasn't a mistake.
♫ You're the only one for me ♫
They just... use me.
They use me and try to get what they want.
That's the only thing I learned living as Jamie
for all those years.
With all your sons...
you must feel so secure.
♫ Like seasons that never change ♫
At age 18, she was able to...
Even if I send her off to Silicon Valley right now, I'm sure she'll be on top in a year.
She's the perfect bride material, isn't she?
She can support her husband's business perfectly behind the scenes.
♫ And I'll be like springtime for you ♫
♫ You became light and shone on me ♫
Hey.
♫ You're the only one for me ♫
♫  All the pain from before ♫
Hey!
♫ I want to shine on you ♫
Jamie!
Do you know how much you cost us by canceling this marriage?
If I had wed into Kangjin Group as planned, would it have secured your future as well?
I'll let you keep using that car.
Take it.
I'm planning to more efficiently use skills you taught me, Madam Yoo.
♫ I'll be like springtime for you ♫
Please marry me.
I really need you.
I've never
received anyone's true love.