♪Should we forget yesterday's sorrows♪
♪And the dazed confusion♪
♪Should we let go of♪
♪The stubborn madness♪
♪And naive recklessness now♪
♪Those years, those faces♪
♪Those old scars we can't erase♪
♪Tears streaming, facing the light♪
♪Piercing the sorrow within♪
♪The road ahead's long,
stumbling all the way♪
♪The wounds we've borne
are medals hidden within♪
♪Standing alone on an open plain♪
♪We gaze at the stars♪
=The Dream Maker=
=Episode 24=
(Bold Exploration, Courageous Practice
Work Hard, Build Yuehai Together)
My head hurts. What liquor?
Aged liquor?
No, it's...
(Cooperative Development Contract)
Yes, aged liquor.
You scared me! I took the wrong seat.
You sit here.
There's no need.
You sit there.
I'll speak less.
Changyuan will speak for me.
Today,
- Why?
- I'll be talking.
Why?
Don't ask.
Look,
I haven't mentioned this to my husband.
I'm not afraid of him...
Understood.
Sit down and relax.
I can help you out a little.
What's that?
Don't touch it.
Let me see.
I'm doing my homework. Don't bother me.
Be quiet.
May I speak?
Did you drink? Smells awful.
He drank.
I didn't drink.
You ate chive pancakes?
Thank you.
(Cooperative Development Contract)
(Conference Room)
Okay.
Thank you.
Come on.
Secretary.
Mr. Zheng.
Ms. Li.
Hello.
Mr. Lin, Mr. Tan.
Have a seat.
Today, I'll be the main speaker.
Everyone is present.
Then...
Where is Xie?
Mr. Xie has gone to handle a dispute.
You'll be the speaker.
Well,
let's start.
Let's begin.
Well, the contracts in everyone's hands
are exactly the same as the sample
in Xuemei's hands.
We've reviewed it.
Yes, we have.
Good.
Let's go straight into it.
We'll definitely build public toilets.
At most, we can only build three.
How can three be enough?
Yes.
Ten people are
building nine modern factories.
On average,
each factory employs 300 people.
One public toilet per 300 people.
That's not excessive.
True.
You can't expect us
to waste valuable production time
waiting in line for the toilet.
- Yes.
Wait, Ms. Gao.
Why should we build toilets
for your workers?
We build toilets on municipal roads.
True.
I think we must build a guesthouse.
- Right?
- Yes.
You mean
the government builds the guesthouse
- and gets the profits?
- Yes.
Yes and no. No, not exactly.
We can negotiate this.
Yes, that's negotiable.
Don't forget.
Take note.
- What?
- We also need a freight station, right?
Yes.
Freight station.
That's not a problem.
But the cost will be borne by you.
Forget the toilet.
Come on.
Help us widen the road a bit too.
We can't do it arbitrarily.
Look, how much
will it cost to widen it by one meter?
(Today's Revisions)
All the terms are laid out.
Listen,
a word of advice,
don't push your luck.
Our town government
has borrowed several million
to build the industrial park.
We should work on it together.
How can you expect us
to shoulder everything?
We can communicate about this.
It's negotiable.
Mr. Tan.
I've said it before.
We have good officials.
Alright.
If everyone has no objections
to the terms,
let's just sign the papers today, okay?
- Good.
The new contract has been printed.
One copy for each.
Can we sign?
Sure.
Sign it!
Sign it?
Sure.
You can refuse.
Why?
I'll sign it first.
You came to work
without even bringing an inkpad!
Huh?
Thank you for your assistance.
We'll work hard
- on this project.
- Done.
Are you done?
Nice.
What a harmonious atmosphere!
Xie is back.
Xie.
Perfect timing.
We'll be busy.
Ms. Gao.
Xie, perfect timing.
You know.
Come on. Eat something.
Pass it around.
I won't disturb you.
Are you in a meeting?
Go on, please.
You're so nice, Xie.
- Good news?
- Very nice.
Of course.
Do you remember the plot in Gaopu?
We've all decided
to jointly develop an industrial park.
The contracts are already signed.
All signed?
Sure.
You signed it?
Yes.
Wonderful news.
We should celebrate.
- Here.
- The issue of Afang Bakery
has been settled,
right?
Did you buy these cakes
with your own money?
Don't be silly.
They gave these cakes to me.
They said I handled the issue well.
There is one less.
Right here.
Bring it over.
Guess what?
Today's issue was resolved perfectly.
Right here.
Good.
They said I deserved cake
since I handled it so well.
I said I couldn't eat it alone
and would share the cake with others.
Take this.
Resolving disputes is your specialty.
It's a piece of cake for me.
I just resolved it
effortlessly, you know.
Go ahead and eat.
Come on.
Try this.
Don't waste food.
You eat too.
It's fine, really.
What's wrong?
What?
What happened?
Nothing.
If you didn't decide for yourself,
you wouldn't be Gao Xuemei.
Don't you think so?
It's fine.
You're you, and I'm me.
When it's your call to make,
you make it.
You don't want to?
Even if you don't want to, you must.
You're the boss.
Well,
it's fine. I'm used to it.
I mean it.
Relax.
There's good news, isn't there?
Must be good news.
Let me ask you.
Did you
join the industrial park project?
Me?
Many hands make light work.
- I contributed a little.
- You did?
Yeah.
I feared you hadn't joined in.
You did the right thing.
You must do it without hesitation.
You scared me.
Also, you need to take the lead.
Otherwise,
it means there's a problem
with our attitude.
I'll leave it at that.
You make the call.
You made it.
Good.
Look how reasonable Xie is!
Sure.
Look!
Yes, he is.
Stop flirting.
Good cake.
Go ahead and eat.
Have some cake.
Show me the contract.
Let me see that contract.
No need, it's signed.
Try this.
I won't see. I was kidding.
You've made the decision,
right?
It's right here.
On the top is the biggest deal.
(Cooperative Development Contract)
Go ahead.
Stirring things up?
I'm not looking.
Well...
Ms. Gao decided.
Give it to me.
How's the flavor? Good, right?
Very sweet.
Unexpectedly,
the cake is very delicious.
Very good.
Eat.
Go ahead.
Second to last page.
Ms. Gao's signature.
What's wrong with you?
Feeling unwell?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I suddenly felt a bit... Nothing.
Eat your cake.
I...
Are you okay?
Thirteen...
Where did the 13 million
come from?
A loan!
The town government took a loan
to build the road.
They took a loan to build the factory.
Good. What did you use as collateral?
Well, I have
mortgaged our printery.
I've mortgaged it.
What's wrong with you, Xie?
Are you okay?
Ms. Li, tell me.
Did you deliberately send me away?
And you, Mr. Tan!
Are you putting on a show?
You sent me away
and then signed the contract?
No, Xie, you've misunderstood.
We really didn't.
It was just a coincidence.
How could we be tricking you?
I'm just asking.
I see. I happened to leave
while they happened to come here, right?
I'm going to the bathroom.
I need toilet paper.
I really...
don't feel well.
Listen, Xie, let me explain.
You can't blame anyone else.
Honestly, I didn't dare tell you
at first.
I feared you'd make a fuss about this.
Now, look,
you're getting a stomach ache,
feeling unwell.
Well,
besides, I thought as soon as you came,
you'd figure it out right away.
I didn't expect you to go off
to the Afang Bakery.
As a result, you misunderstood me.
I'm telling you,
taking loans for business
is a common practice now.
It's really no big deal.
There's no risk.
We've put all our family savings in
and borrowed so much more.
We put it all in. No risk?
There's no risk?
Not like that.
Let's talk about this at home. Come on.
Xuemei.
We're leaving first!
You stay.
All of you stay.
We'll talk right here.
Stop it!
Eat your cake.
This concerns them, so we'll talk here.
Why go home?
Are we going to argue?
Would we even argue?
Come on.
The town officials are right here!
We're not arguing.
- We're talking.
- Yes.
We're fixing things.
Xie, we're leaving first.
Your stomach aches?
I have medicine for diarrhea.
Take some medicine.
Give it to me.
- Come on.
- Here.
I'm killing you.
What are you doing? Get down!
Get down!
Are you crazy?
Look where you are! Not your home!
This is the town government!
Watch your manners!
S-Sorry about this.
I...
Shut up!
Don't blame everyone else.
I was rude.
I decided to burn my boats.
I'm telling you,
if we don't build an industrial park,
we'll be left behind by this era,
you know?
Then, why didn't you tell me?
I'm the deputy mayor.
I'm also your husband.
Don't I have the right
to know about this first?
If you had told me,
I might have agreed.
I said might.
It was all negotiable,
right?
I don't agree.
This contract
is canceled.
You signed this contract.
That's your business.
Agreeing or not is my business.
I disagree.
Xie, be reasonable!
Xuemei has made the call.
Why did you object?
Give us a reason.
She and I are one,
right?
After all, we're husband and wife.
She is me, and I am her.
If I say no, it means she says no. Okay?
Mr. Xie, I understand how you feel.
But we must build the industrial park.
Yes.
We must do it! Did I say I wouldn't?
But some can do it, while some can't.
No.
What are you doing?
I've had enough of you!
Enough.
I'm telling you,
if you dare tear up this contract today,
from today on, you're you, and I'm me.
Go ahead, tear it.
I've had enough of you!
What if I tear it?
Go ahead.
Fine.
What do you mean?
You go home.
Back off!
I'm telling you.
Go home.
Since we moved here,
have you managed our home
and the business?
Go home.
Talk right here!
Let's make it clear here!
Talk at home.
Why?
Go home and talk.
Do you feel humiliated?
Xie Chunlai.
I've been providing you
with food, drinks,
clothes, and daily articles.
I've shown you respect
in public and private.
I've been quite nice to you.
How about you?
When I do business,
everyone treats me politely.
How dare you order me around?
Just because of a marriage certificate?
Yes,
exactly that.
Then, I can do without it!
(Cooperative Development Contract)
That's all for today.
We'll talk another day.
Let's go.
We're leaving.
Xuemei.
Let's go.
Take your stuff.
I can't believe this.
I underestimated you, Gao Xuemei.
You're really something.
How did you do it?
How could you do this?
At home, anything goes.
But in front of so many people,
you just can't disrespect me.
You acted without telling me first!
Very clever of you!
What are you doing?
Is Xuemei inside?
Yes.
Sounds like they're fighting.
You've gone too far!
Are you in charge of it all?
I...
Xuemei.
Don't be impulsive.
Why don't you come out?
Look,
it wouldn't be right
for either of you to hurt the other.
Honestly, Xie couldn't beat you.
It wouldn't be good if you hurt him.
So, come out and talk?
Get out!
All of you, get out!
He's putting on an act.
Shameless!
I'm not surprised at all.
Eavesdropping on me?
Get out!
You scared me to death!
What are you doing?
Mr. Zheng? You finally came in.
I was holding my breath,
afraid to speak.
When did Ms. Gao leave?
She never showed up.
What? Xie, what's wrong with you?
You scared me.
You crazy woman!
I want a divorce, right now!
I'm telling you,
I'd rather be widowed than divorced.
Good for divorcing!
Hurry up and divorce.
I wish all the homeless men well.
A real man
should live alone.
Right?
Tofu.
How are you and Sun Xiaoyan?
We're doing fine.
I think everyone should have a family.
Mr. Xie.
I've talked with Mr. Zheng.
We'll leave the project alone for now.
We'll hold another meeting
to discuss specifics.
I didn't tell you
about the industrial park beforehand.
I feel I must formally apologize to you.
I'm sorry.
I hope it won't
affect your relationship with Xuemei.
If needed, I'll talk to Xuemei.
It's okay.
Dad.
Dad, where are you going?
Going to learn.
Did Mom know?
Mom's eating at Mr. Dong's stall.
Mr. Xie, you're here.
Ms. Gao is over there.
Noodles.
Okay.
Mom, you talk to Dad.
What's he up to?
He took a lot of his clothes from home.
And personal belongings.
He even took the thermos.
What happened?
Whatever.
I don't care.
Dad, just give in a little.
(Just Do What You Want)
Mr. Xie, your noodles.
It's too late, you loser.
Sir, do you have a pen?
Yes.
Divorce agreement.
First, the business goes to me.
Second, the money goes to you.
Third, Xiaoyu,
a question mark.
Xiaoyu, a question mark?
No matter what, you're mine.
Question mark.
Go!
Come on!
Dad.
This won't do. It's not formal.
Tell your mom.
If she really wants a divorce,
write a formal one.
You go with me.
Dad?
Just eat the noodles.
Dad.
Eat the noodles.
Dad?
Are you starving?
Come on.
There's plenty more.
Go get some more.
This is really delicious.
Here.
Thank you.
Eat more.
Braised pork!
What's the occasion?
Too much.
There's braised pork!
Ms. Xiao must have been crazy.
Thanks.
What a surprise!
Keep your voice down,
or she'll hear you.
Want some veggies? They're good.
The food's good today.
Extra braised pork.
Okay, I'll get extra.
Thanks.
Braised pork, please.
Okay, Dongfu.
Ms. Sun.
Yu.
Why are you here?
Mr. Xie asked me
to cover Ms. Xiao's shift.
What's wrong?
Well,
listen to me,
you can't be here.
Why?
You're taking advantage
of the town government.
What?
You're taking advantage
of the town government.
The meat isn't cheap!
The government didn't take advantage.
Wait,
Ms. Sun, I haven't gotten my food yet.
Have Wu get it for you.
I mean, you are
taking advantage of the government.
I'm taking advantage?
I started prepping vegetables at three,
and service starts at five-thirty.
Two and a half hours. I haven't
even had time to drink water.
Where am I taking advantage?
Cooking here isn't volunteer work,
is it?
You'll get paid, right?
Yes.
I'm providing labor!
Getting paid for that is normal,
isn't it?
What about permanent employment?
I didn't bring it up.
They did mention it to me.
See? It's a little bit of nepotism.
What do you mean?
You think I came here just
to get a permanent job?
You're making me abuse my power.
Don't you understand?
No, I don't!
I'm here to cook.
How did I make you abuse your power?
Well,
if it weren't for our relationship,
would they have let you work here?
Use your head!
I'm telling you, you can't work here.
Understand?
Why did Ms. Sun leave?
Xie.
Tofu, I was about to talk to you.
I'll go first.
Okay, you go first.
She can't work in the canteen.
Fire her today.
Who? Sun Xiaoyan?
Don't play dumb.
Why fire her?
I'm going to talk about this.
I tried so hard
to get her here to cook for us.
This is a good thing.
Why fire her?
I said she can't work here.
I'm seeing her now.
If she works here,
it's a little bit of nepotism.
I can't make this mistake.
I have principles.
I know you do.
But...
But you're not making mistakes.
What are you thinking?
Well,
listen,
she...
Why are you using my toolbox?
Just keep it simple.
I'm in charge of the canteen, right?
So, if Sun Xiaoyan makes any mistakes,
it'll be my responsibility.
Is it clear,
isn't it?
Let me borrow this, okay?
Let me use it.
Sun Xiaoyan is my girlfriend.
So, before you hired her,
shouldn't you have told me?
Sure, but you wanted to speak first.
You only told me after hiring her.
Quite clever.
Quite clever, aren't you?
Why are you being silly?
She's doing well,
yet you're firing her. Why?
Can Sun Xiaoyan make her own decisions?
Can she or can't she? Answer me!
Listen to me!
You've made a mistake.
You can decide on everything, can't you?
Like using my toolbox.
You even decided for Sun Xiaoyan!
She's my girlfriend.
How could you hire her
without telling me?
Gao Xuemei decided to build the factory.
You knew that, right?
Yet you didn't tell me,
making me look silly.
You're being unreasonable!
Am I?
Two different things.
Same thing.
You have a problem.
I just can't get through to you.
What's exactly in your head?
Unreasonable.
Whatever. I'm not talking
to you.
I'll find someone else.
Ms. Li.
Yes?
Come here.
What's going on?
Did you hear us?
You did, right?
Listen,
Lin Tofu
has no issues.
I have a problem.
It's all my fault.
I can't
manage my home.
I can't manage the canteen either, huh?
I'm incompetent. Fire me. Do you agree?
You...
Mr. Lin, what's going on?
No, I...
Well...
I disagree
with Sun Xiaoyan working here.
Well...
Mr. Xie is responsible for logistics.
He can hire anyone,
including Sun Xiaoyan.
But she's my girlfriend.
As deputy mayor, so that looks...
I can't make an error of principle.
What error?
Explain clearly.
Mr. Lin, right now, besides you,
nobody thinks
Sun Xiaoyan is taking advantage.
Sun Xiaoyan
is an independent individual.
She's not your property.
She's good at cooking.
You know what? Since she cooked here,
more people have gone to the canteen.
You heard her, didn't you?
Then,
she knew she would
become a full-time employee one day.
Isn't it nepotism?
See?
So what?
If she's willing to stay,
I'll give her a permanent job.
Come on.
Whoever does well will become permanent.
What does it have to do with you?
Male chauvinism.
No.
It's not acceptable.
Mr. Lin, you can't be so selfish.
You know Sun Xiaoyan well.
Do you think
she loves to take advantage?
Why do you think
she manages her wonton stall
while working in our canteen?
It's exhausting!
She does it
because she knows you're unwell.
She knows you eat meals erratically.
She wants to take care of you.
Listen, when I went to ask her,
she refused to come.
She wanted to focus on her stall.
I persuaded her.
I said Mr. Lin didn't eat properly.
If she cooks, he'll have an appetite.
Hearing that,
she was about to cry.
She agreed eventually.
Why does she work so hard?
What for?
Isn't it for you?
How could you ask me to fire her?
You fool!
I was deeply moved.
You're just stupid Tofu.
Take it back!
Knock on yourself!
Go on!
You use it!
Use it!
Take it back!
Go ahead.
Well done!
I'm praising you.
Good for you.
Mr. Xie, are you resigning?
Who said I'm resigning?
I'm doing a great job.
Why would I resign?
Fine, I won't fix it then.
It's okay.
It's fine if a vehicle gets old.
Just get a new one.
If a brain stops working,
it'll be a big problem.
What a surprise, Ms. Li.
I'm off.
Mom.
What's so urgent
that you have to rush to Yuehai?
A patient I operated on a few days ago
has some abnormal readings.
He might need a second surgery.
Am I delaying you?
No, not at all.
Mom,
when was the last time
you went to Shanghai?
The last time to Shanghai?
I remember before I retired,
I went to Shanghai
to attend a conference for surgeons.
Why do you suddenly ask about Shanghai?
Nothing, I just feel
I'm already over 30
and haven't even been to Shanghai.
That's true.
Why don't you take Qiuping
there for a honeymoon?
Mom, what are you talking about?
Don't play dumb.
You two have been together
for so many years.
Your wedding should
be put on the agenda.
Well,
we've both been extremely busy lately.
There is no rush.
Still delaying?
How much longer will you wait?
I'm already retired now.
I've been a bit busy recently,
but I won't be this busy
once things settle down.
I'll have time to handle your wedding.
You haven't seen her for a while, yes?
How about this?
Just drop me off in a bit,
and go find Qiuping to discuss it.
No time like the present.
Mom, just leave this matter alone.
Qiuping and I know what we're doing.
Fine. I won't interfere.
(Yuehai Town Steps into the New Era)
I planned to visit you this weekend.
I didn't expect you to come today.
I've been incredibly busy lately.
Today, I happened to drive my mom here,
so I came to see you.
The town government looks really nice.
There are flowers.
I planted them.
I've been tending to them.
We'll live here in the future, right?
Let me show you something.
What's this?
Just open it and see.
(Marriage Application)
Aren't you happy?
Sure.
Well,
when did you write this?
Why didn't you tell me?
I wanted to surprise you.
Your look tells me
it's an unpleasant surprise.
It's pleasant.
It's just that I feel
I should be the one
to bring it up first.
Don't be old-fashioned.
Girls can also propose marriage.
When I get back,
I'll write an application too.
Ms. Li.
Isn't this Liu's house?
Yes, she rented it to us.
By the way,
when will your house be built?
Very soon.
We've been quite busy.
Okay.
Look.
Your hands have calluses.
Probably from writing too much.
Mr. Lin,
wait a bit. The food isn't ready yet.
No, I...
Well...
What is it?
Where's Yan?
She quit.
This is our new cook, Dong.
Dong.
This is Deputy Mayor Lin.
Mr. Lin.
Hello.
Finish checking it before eating.
Mr. Tan.
Tan.
Yes.
Actually, Xie,
I wanted to discuss something with you.
Time to eat.
I know
Dong doesn't cook better
than Sun Xiaoyan.
But she is not a terrible cook.
That's what I wanted to say.
To be honest,
you did a good job.
Sun Xiaoyan's cooking is excellent.
I really don't understand
why Lin must fire her.
Missing nice food is frustrating, huh?
No.
It was a win-win situation.
I think
Lin might just be overthinking it.
He thinks it was nepotism.
After all, it's his girlfriend.
So, Lin can still have the good food
Sun Xiaoyan makes.
Let's not interfere, okay?
We have to respect Lin, right?
Look, it could be a win-win result.
Let's try again.
How about I talk to Lin privately?
And you talk to Sun Xiaoyan.
You sure?
- Well...
- You talk to him?
You need to...
Mr. Lin,
Mr. Tan wants to talk to you.
Go ahead.
Lin, have you eaten?
I...
Well...
Why didn't you talk?
Lin acted like that.
How was I supposed to talk to him?
Yan, I...
Mr. Lin,
you shouldn't come here anymore
to avoid misunderstandings,
in case I'm taking advantage of you.
No...
Well, Yan...
(Yan's Wontons)
Yan, I-I didn't mean it like that.
Actually, Ms. Li and Mr. Zheng
have talked to me.
They all really
like your cooking,
including Xie and Tan.
Everyone in the town government
loves your cooking.
Actually, I like your cooking too.
If you want,
keep working in the canteen.
You asked me to quit, and I did.
Now, you ask me to go back,
and I'll do it?
No, that's not what I meant.
I just...
I just thought...
I've figured it out.
As long as your salary isn't higher
than anyone else's,
you're not taking advantage.
What do you think of me?
You think I'm venal?
Guess how much
the town government paid me?
Cooking two meals a day
for dozens of people.
70 yuan a month.
True,
I don't make much selling wontons.
But I don't care about 70 yuan.
I'm such a fool.
Actually, Ms. Li told me.
She said you took the canteen job
mainly to look out for me.
Yan, I'm sorry. I was wrong.
Liu!
My chain is off! Help me fix my bike!
Okay.
Careful!
Hello, please page 660901 for me.
My surname is Li. Tell him
to call back as soon as possible.
Thanks.
Ms. Li,
why are you working so late?
I still have some things to handle.
You may leave.
Alright.
♪Gently holding your face♪
♪To dry the tears from your eyes♪
♪My heart will always be yours♪
♪Tell me you'll never be alone again♪
♪Gazing deep into your eyes♪
♪No further words are needed♪
♪Tightly holding your hand♪
♪The warmth has never changed♪
♪We share the joy♪
♪We share the pain♪
♪We hold the same hope deep inside♪
♪We brave the storm♪
♪We share the quest♪
♪We cherish this love we share♪
♪Whether we've ever met before♪
♪Be it near or far away♪
♪My heartfelt wish for you♪
♪Is for your peace and happiness♪
♪We share the joy♪
♪We share the pain♪
♪We hold the same hope deep inside♪
♪We brave the storm♪
♪We share the quest♪
♪We cherish this love we share♪