♪Should we forget yesterday's sorrows♪
♪And the dazed confusion♪
♪Should we let go of♪
♪The stubborn madness♪
♪And naive recklessness now♪
♪Those years, those faces♪
♪Those old scars we can't erase♪
♪Tears streaming, facing the light♪
♪Piercing the sorrow within♪
♪The road ahead's long,
stumbling all the way♪
♪The wounds we've borne
are medals hidden within♪
♪Standing alone on an open plain♪
♪We gaze at the stars♪
=The Dream Maker=
=Episode 25=
(Ms. Li: Please call back soon)
(Marriage Application)
If you really want to go to Shanghai,
you must have an impactful report.
What are you looking at, Du?
Nothing.
W-What's up with you?
Du, I'm going to Guangzhou.
To Guangzhou?
Good for you.
Good.
When are you leaving?
Just in two days.
Is your girlfriend going with you?
We broke up.
Broke up?
Just an hour ago, we broke up.
Du,
do you also think I'm quite heartless?
Actually, I think...
I'm telling you.
I think you're pretty awesome.
Although you're younger than me,
you act more decisively than I do,
more courageous than me.
Weren't you just asking
what I was looking at?
What?
Don't touch it. You can't touch it.
I was looking at this.
It's a good thing, Du.
You two are finally getting married
after all these years.
It's just a shame
I'm going to Guangzhou.
I can't make it to your wedding.
You...
Do you really think it's a good thing?
Listen up.
I've been thinking
about it for days now.
I think a man
must prioritize his career
above all else.
Morality, feelings, etc.
None of them is important.
They matter, but not that much.
Nothing should become
a roadblock on your path
to career success.
Are you going to Shanghai with Mr. Xiao?
You know he is leaving?
Heard about it.
I'm not afraid of you laughing at me.
I'm not afraid of you laughing. I...
You can go to Guangzhou now.
I'm just one step away from Shanghai.
I'm still one step short.
A whole step.
Du, you can definitely do it.
With your talent, that one step
won't take long, right?
Yes, I will surely make it.
- You'll definitely make it.
- I definitely will.
This great era
has given us
a once-in-a-century opportunity.
And we are always ready to welcome it
and embrace it.
Embrace it.
Come on.
To the future, to our careers!
To Guangzhou, to Shanghai!
(Zheng Decheng)
(Yuehai)
(If Yuehai)
(High-Speed Development
or a Hotbed of Corruption)
Du.
Did you break up
with that female town mayor of Yuehai?
No.
I have to be honest with you.
This article of yours
is indeed impactful.
But once published,
it's likely to affect
the whole of Yuehai.
It might even affect
Yuehai's entire leadership team.
Let alone your relationship
with your girlfriend.
Everyone,
at some point in life,
will arrive at a key juncture
in their life.
At that time,
what seems like an insignificant choice
could well change
the direction of your life.
Du, let me be clear.
I'll understand
whatever choice you make.
If you choose not to publish,
I'll act as if this article
never existed.
Mr. Xiao.
I...
choose to publish.
♪Should we forget yesterday's sorrows♪
♪And the dazed confusion♪
♪Should we let go of♪
♪The stubborn madness♪
♪And naive recklessness now♪
♪People come and go,
rushing east and west♪
(New City Life)
Ms. Li sends her
congratulations to you all.
(Cooperative Development Contract)
Let's review the contract once more.
If everything looks fine,
let's wrap this up quickly.
Come on.
- Come on.
- Okay.
♪Those years♪
♪Those faces♪
♪Those old scars we can't erase♪
♪Tears streaming, facing the light♪
(Binhai 1st Road)
(Environmental Protection,
Benefits today and the future)
♪The road ahead's long,
stumbling all the way♪
(Regulate Traffic Order,
Ensure Road Safety)
♪The wounds we've borne
are medals hidden within♪
How did it go? Smoothly?
Yes.
Eight million is no small amount.
But I saw Ms. Gao took ten million,
and she looked quite calm
when she signed at the bank.
That's just Xuemei's normal state.
We have no way back now.
Let's work hard together.
High-Speed Development
or a Hotbed of Corruption?
Nonsense!
Lin, see that?
No, what's wrong?
Take a look.
What corruption?
Mr. Zheng, take a look.
W-What corruption?
The headline in New City Life.
Look, what nonsense is this?
High-Speed Development
or a Hotbed of Corruption?
Reporter Du Tao.
Guided by the principles
of Reform and Opening-up,
taking rural reform as an opportunity,
township and village enterprises
have sprung up like mushrooms.
They have become a crucial force
driving rural economic development.
However,
alongside the rapid growth of TVEs,
corruption has gradually surfaced,
becoming a focus of societal concern.
A certain leader in Yuehai has always
been strong-willed and decisive.
At the city's founding,
he pushed through opposition
and proposed a city construction fee.
In a few days, nearly ten million yuan
in city construction funds was raised.
Afterward, relying on his own prestige,
he adopted a dictatorial approach.
While it fueled Yuehai Town's
rapid economic growth,
it also planted the seeds
of serious risks.
Another leader in Yuehai Town
has a wife who is one of Yuehai's
largest self-employed individuals.
To help his wife build her factory,
the town government
made a baffling decision.
They took out an eight million bank loan
to build a Class IV highway.
What nonsense is this?
It's turning black into white!
It's sheer lawlessness!
Is it the fact?
This is insane.
It's insane.
You didn't see the rest yet.
The part about the city inspectors
is also harshly worded.
In the town's early days,
the city inspection team
was formed as a temporary response
to maintain order.
However, years have passed,
yet the inspection team still exists
without true law enforcement authority.
This inevitably raises the question.
Does its existence serve the needs
of the people or the leaders?
What kind of talk is this?
Ms. Li,
we built
the city inspection team together.
You know the reason best, don't you?
We did it for the sake
of Yuehai's residents.
And this.
Building a modern hospital
is inherently a good thing
that benefits the local people.
However, in Yuehai,
this matter has sparked controversy.
The wife of Yuehai Town's top leader
once passed away due
to delayed medical treatment.
Afterward, he resolved
to build a modern hospital.
He coined the phrase "no budget cap".
During the construction,
they purchased large quantities
of expensive medical equipment.
D-Does this Reporter Du
even write like a human?
Anyway, I think this report
is utter nonsense from start to finish.
It's slander and defamation.
He's not basing his report on the truth.
Du Tao, I have a message for you too.
You have overwhelmingly become
the enemy of Yuehai Town.
I truly never expected
Du Tao to be such a person.
Alright.
Calm down, okay?
This article wasn't written by Ms. Li.
Why take it out on her?
Are you still into collective punishment
after all these years?
Moreover,
Ms. Li is just his girlfriend,
not his mom.
Even if she were,
she couldn't control
an adult's actions, right?
As deputy mayors,
this is all you can take?
You said it's not true.
So what are you afraid of?
(City Construction Archives)
Li...
Can't you all just talk a bit less?
(New City Life)
I've already seen this report.
Yes.
Mr. Zhao is away on an inspection tour.
Don't worry.
We will fully cooperate on this matter.
Okay. Goodbye.
You received whistleblower letters too?
They all are.
Take a look.
I think it's all because of this report.
Yuehai collected
the city construction fee ages ago.
They bring it up again.
Don't you understand yet?
(Conference Room)
The key to this report
is not about the city construction fee.
That's just a cover.
I understand.
Isn't this article
just insinuating that Zheng Decheng
has financial issues?
This is total slander!
I've known Zheng Decheng for decades.
I know him well.
If he were greedy,
he could've left his post
and gone into business long ago.
With his talent,
I wouldn't be surprised if he turned
into a lion, let alone some 'monkeys.'
Yes.
Yuehai has developed
remarkably these years.
His achievements
are also evident to everyone.
But when it comes to work,
to put it nicely,
he doesn't sweat the small stuff.
To put it bluntly,
he has no regard for others.
Yuehai is unique.
Since its establishment,
apart from handing over tax revenue
proportionally every year,
the remaining funds are all
self-collected and self-disbursed.
Look.
(Whistleblower Letters)
I compiled these whistleblower letters.
Guan,
absolute power
likely leads to absolute corruption.
Can you guarantee
that over all these years in Yuehai,
Zheng Decheng hasn't made fatal mistakes
out of negligence or carelessness?
What's more troublesome now is
these letters
weren't just sent to us.
They were also sent to the city level.
This
has already gone beyond our control.
(Silence)
Hello, is Director Jiang on duty today?
In that room.
Okay, thanks.
Tell me.
What's the deal with those articles
you wrote about Yuehai?
What?
You processed the paperwork
to go to Shanghai?
Did you discuss this with Qiuping?
Tao,
how can you be so impatient for success?
Did you write articles like that
to get into that magazine?
I'm so disappointed in you.
(New City Life, High-Speed Development
or a Hotbed of Corruption)
Hello?
It's me.
Dad.
What are you doing?
Watching TV.
You little punk.
Gaokao's coming, and you're watching TV?
Just kidding. I'm doing homework.
That's more like it.
I've got something.
It's just
that I might not be able to go back
to the county for a while.
But no matter what happens,
you have to believe me.
Got it?
Wait. Are you saying
you're going to get arrested?
You really don't wish me well, do you?
No, I told you before,
don't make enemies out there.
You don't know a thing!
Stay out of adults' business.
Just firmly believe
that your dad's a good man.
And also,
I'll buy some eggs and walnuts later
and send them to you.
Remember to eat.
Got it.
Okay.
Dad.
Go on.
You'll always be a good man.
That's it.
Li.
Come here.
Okay.
Have a seat.
I called you over
to discuss a few things with you.
Mr. Zheng, I'm sorry.
I called Du Tao many times,
but he didn't answer.
But regarding this matter,
I will surely
give everyone an explanation.
That's not what I to discuss.
Li.
I know you're upset.
But this situation
might be even more serious
than we thought.
I'm worried
that very soon
they will investigate me.
Investigate?
But this is just a hunch of mine.
However, we still
need to prepare for the worst, right?
Mr. Zheng,
everything about Yuehai
was decided by all our colleagues
in the town government.
They can't just
investigate you alone, right?
Of course, it's too early
to discuss this now.
What if...
I mean, what if...
If I'm taken away for investigation,
Yuehai's work must not stop.
Yuehai's goals must not deviate.
That's why I called you here.
Mr. Zheng.
I won't go into minor details.
I trust you
and the three deputy mayors of Yuehai.
Even if I'm not here,
you can still carry on the work.
But there are several
important matters I must mention.
First,
our overall goal
for Yuehai must not waver.
Yuehai must reach a population
of 100,000 by year-end.
With more people come,
housing, job demands,
and school facilities
must be upgraded accordingly.
Second, Yang Xiaohai and those kids.
I calculated the timing.
They should be getting out soon.
I've thought it over.
Just finding them jobs isn't enough.
We must help them change fundamentally.
Help them find
the right purpose in life.
That's your specialty, right?
Okay.
Third, and most critical
is...
Build the industrial park.
Seems my worries are unnecessary.
Then I am at ease.
One more thing.
Keep this
for me.
What is it?
How do I put this?
It's my life's work.
You asked to meet me here.
What? Afraid to face me?
I'm sorry.
You must've been treated unfairly
in Yuehai lately.
Why did you write that article?
Qiuping, I came
to ask you not to let this article
affect our relationship.
Then why didn't you answer my calls?
Tell me, what does journalism
mean to you?
What do you mean?
Answer me.
Journalism means reporting the latest
valuable information as quickly
as possible from a unique perspective.
No!
Journalism's essence is pursuing truth,
fairness, and objectivity.
That's what you told me.
Your article insinuates
that Zheng Decheng took bribes.
Are you objective? Are you fair?
Did you seek truth from facts?
Now you want to talk
about seeking truth?
When I wrote columns in Yuehai,
I was factual, wasn't I?
But you never admitted it.
Don't give me
that "for Yuehai's development" excuse.
I think
sacrificing Yuehai to make the nation
think Reform and Opening-up is worthy.
Make the whole nation think?
It's your ticket to Shanghai, isn't it?
Du Tao, you wrote that sensational piece
chasing success and fame,
ignoring truth
and betraying your ideals.
Is this still the you I knew?
Yes!
I chase success and fame.
I want to go to Shanghai. What's wrong?
Times are changing.
Who isn't chasing success and fame now?
When you and Zheng Decheng
blocked my article,
weren't you after fame and fortune?
You see me that way?
You think I acted for personal gain?
What else? For Yuehai's people?
To serve the people?
Exactly! I serve the people.
The people's interests come first.
Can't you drop the hypocrisy?
Can you be real?
Have you considered that you changed?
I remember back in university,
you used to read People's Daily
on the campus lawn.
You said,
"This is an era
of wild growth and vitality."
requiring great navigators."
"An age needing great surfers."
That's exactly when I fell for you.
All these years,
I've kept every article you ever wrote.
(Scrapbook)
Du Tao,
when I gave you
the marriage application,
did you think I was ridiculous?
I know nothing I say to you now matters.
Let's break up.
(Scrapbook)
(I chase success and fame.)
(I want to go to Shanghai.
What's wrong?)
(When you and Zheng Decheng
blocked my article,)
(weren't you after fame and fortune?)
(I think)
(sacrificing Yuehai to make the nation
think Reform and Opening-up is worthy.)
(Can't you drop the hypocrisy?)
(Can you be real?)
(Yuehai Town People's Government)
Mr. Zheng!
Ms. Li, they are taking Mr. Zheng away.
What's wrong?
You are Ms. Li?
Yes.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Liu Weimin from the Municipal DIC,
the head of this investigation team.
We are now asking Zheng Decheng
to accept our investigation.
Please also notify all Yuehai cadres
to remain
in Yuehai Town at all times
during the investigation.
And we will temporarily freeze
all of Yuehai Town's accounts.
Take a look.
Any other questions?
You can't freeze these accounts.
They must be frozen.
This protects the people's property.
I'd like to ask
what specific issues are being
investigated regarding Mr. Zheng?
No comment.
Ms. Li,
with accounts frozen,
how can I continue the project?
Enough!
All of you, calm down.
We must cooperate fully
with the investigation.
While I'm away,
all Yuehai matters
will be directed by Ms. Li, alright?
That's it.
(Due to Du Tao's report
and the public's whistleblower letters,)
(to avoid wrongly accusing any cadre,)
(the city and county
formed a joint investigation team.)
(They took Zheng Decheng.)
(Yuehai)
(was plunged
into an unprecedented crisis.)
It's over.
Bad news!
Listen, something's happened!
Taken by people from the city!
Be clear! Who took him away?
Mr. Zheng
was taken away by the Municipal DIC.
What?
The Municipal DIC?
Yes! People from the Municipal DIC.
No.
Was Mr. Zheng taken alone?
Or were there others?
Here's the thing.
The others aren't important.
What's important now?
The government's accounts are frozen!
What?
What did you say?
Accounts frozen?
Yes! They are frozen.
So is the industrial park happening?
Happening what?
Accounts frozen means
Yuehai's government can't move
a single cent in or out now.
Can the industrial park function?
I've ordered the machinery.
If the industrial park can't function,
what happens to my loan?
Maybe pay me back first?
How... How can I pay you back?
You ask me? Who do I ask?
- Enough.
- You can't...
Stop talking.
Yours is loans? What about mine?
Mine was real silver and gold,
put up bit by bit!
Mr. Qian, you have a call.
For me?
Yes.
Are you sure it's for me?
Why would a call for me come here?
Hello?
I'm Qian Changyuan.
Who is this?
Hello, sir.
What's the name?
Anyway, two cars.
Two cars in total.
How many people?
Let me think.
1, 2... And the drivers.
Well, I need to go out.
Where to?
The investigators want to talk to me.
What? Why do they talk to you?
What did I say?
- It's starting.
- Wait.
- Listen.
- Why are they
investigating him?
What do you know?
The investigators come here now
just to sound things out, right?
I think,
this time, Mr. Zheng
is really in trouble.
Nonsense!
You didn't read the papers?
The whole nation
is cracking down on corruption.
Several have already been caught
in other provinces.
I'm telling you.
Mr. Zheng is not here.
I just want to check things out.
All of you, go back.
Mr. Xie, handle this.
Okay.
Okay, I'll handle it.
You can interview him
when he gets back, right?
A leader is here.
Mr. Zheng, are you in?
- Quiet!
- I saw you inside.
(What is this?)
How do I put this?
It's my life's work.
Entrusting something
this important to me?
Is it appropriate?
Yes.
(Town Mayor's Office)
(If)
I really don't come back,
burn it.
What is this, Mr. Zheng?
Don't betray my trust.
(People Build Their City,
and the City Serves Its People)
No cooperation? Fine!
What's the big deal?
Seriously!
The news spread way too fast.
From six until now, how long is that?
I've already gotten calls
from three partners.
They heard Yuehai had problems
and want out of the contract.
Three? That's nothing.
I've taken seven calls canceling orders.
When elephants fight,
the grass gets trampled.
Xuemei, say something.
We all took out loans
to start these factories.
We have to pay interest every day.
Where's Dog? Dog!
I drank you out of booze.
I'll drink your most expensive stuff.
But I don't have money to pay you now!
I owe you, okay?
Skip the math. Come.
Let's go! Drink!
Drink! Let's go! Stop calling!
Go! Drink! Come on!
Xuemei, forget the math, okay?
Forget it! Come on!
Let's drink! Come on!
I bought it.
This round is on me, okay?
Come on. Get glasses. Come on.
Come on. Let's drink.
You're drinking at this moment?
I...
What's wrong with drinking?
We all invested together.
Can't we drink together?
I put every penny I had into this.
I didn't save a single cent.
It wasn't easy for me.
Like you're the only one?
Who here hasn't
put everything on the line
for this industrial park?
Who had it easy?
I think
we must stop construction
on this industrial park right now.
Why looking at me?
You fool.
Let me tell you.
Why did we start building
this industrial park
and the new factories?
Wasn't it to make money?
Now, look!
Mr. Zheng has been arrested.
How to make money?
How?
Yuehai is about to change.
I think our first step
is to take whatever money we have now
and return it to the bank.
Second,
go and return the land
for the industrial park.
Just swallow the loss.
In these special times, we must cut
our losses to save the bigger picture.
Okay.
I agree to stop it for now.
We should wait for confirmation
from Mr. Zheng
before constructing.
Otherwise, we're really finished.
Disperse for now.
Give me some time.
I'll figure something out.
Mr. Liu.
Mr. Liu!
You're finally here.
Great! Come on. Have a seat.
Let's hurry up and investigate.
I'm sorry. Come on. Please sit here.
I don't have many other strengths.
But I'm highly cooperative.
I guess you want to ask
about the city construction fee?
I'll confess.
At that time, there was less
than a week left before Yuehai's launch.
Honestly, it was quite
a dark and windy night.
Zheng Decheng.
Please put away
this liberal attitude of yours.
If you are cooperative
as you claim to be,
please follow the rules here.
That means I ask, and you answer.
Understood?
No problem at all.
Mr. Liu Weimin
from the Municipal DIC, ask away.
What is your monthly salary?
118.
How about that?
It's a lucky number, right?
So you want to investigate
my financial matters?
That won't be a problem.
As for money,
I absolutely can't have any issues.
Ask and investigate whatever you want.
I'm totally clean.
Is that so?
Mr. Liu,
I think
you could spend more time reading books.
Study Das Kapital.
Get clear on what productive forces
and relations of production are.
Since Yuehai's city construction,
I've been begging others for help.
Why would anyone give me money, right?
That makes no sense.
So, financially, I absolutely
can't have any issues.
Then why did we receive reports
that you own multiple properties there?
And these properties aren't registered
under Zheng Decheng,
but Secretary Zheng.
What's going on?
That's impossible.
I'm up to my neck in debt.
How could I have money to own houses?
Zheng Decheng.
Since 1981,
I have
investigated nine cases.
These nine cases
were completely unrelated.
But one thing was the same
for all of them.
What was it?
All of them, at the very beginning,
when undergoing my review, told me
that they had no problems
and could definitely withstand scrutiny.
Yet in the end,
I still uncovered problems.
So, Zheng Decheng,
I hope you will be
the first exception in my work.
Hey, what's going on here?
Why is there no one on the site?
I just got back. I know it clearly.
The workers heard the government's
accounts are frozen. There's no money.
They all ran off.
So what are you doing?
Aren't they under your watch?
Isn't this on you?
How can I handle it without money?
Workers need to eat too!
No money, no management!
What's that attitude?
You...
What awful manners!
Don't touch it. It's for me.
Hello?
Mr. Wang, I was just about to call you.
Go on.
Yes.
Yes. Listen.
Mr. Zheng will be fine.
This temporary situation
will pass quickly.
The accounts are frozen.
But...
How about this? Let's meet and talk.
Hard to explain here, right?
Super Dog Restaurant, right?
Let's set a time. Meet...
Who are you?
Are you even human?
What were you like
when Mr. Zheng was fine?
He isn't in trouble even now.
What kind of fool are you?
Who are you? I'm asking you.
I was just letting off steam.
He hung up ages ago.
Well... Xie. Lin.
I think we should calm down first.
Don't panic.
I think that very soon,
the investigators
will talk to us individually.
I mean,
when we answer their questions,
we should just stick to the facts.
Don't add our own opinions.
Don't cause unnecessary trouble, right?
You think I don't know?
Tan, do you have any money?
With accounts frozen,
how could I have money?
Mr. Wang said the money has to be paid
the day after tomorrow.
If we don't pay the Power Supply Bureau,
they'll cut Yuehai's power.
The workers also said they won't work
until they get their wages.
The site is empty now.
Yelling at Tan is useless.
It's not his fault, right?
Should I yell at you?
Go ahead.
You'll have the money if I do?
L-Let's control our emotions, okay?
Control it.
Mr. Zheng isn't here right now.
We should be more united.
We need to figure out a solution
to this problem as soon as possible.
For example, could we approach
some self-employed individuals?
W-We could discuss it.
See if they can lend us some money.
Help us get
through the current difficulty, right?
For example, Xie,
could you talk to Ms. Gao?
I'm sorry.
What do you mean?
What do you want, Tan?
No, Xie, I really didn't mean it.
- I...
- If I had money,
would I even ask you for it? Am I crazy?
I'm sorry. I panicked just now.
I was thinking of a solution.
It just slipped out. I...
Sit down.
Just sit down.
No matter what,
this road must be built.
When Mr. Zheng left,
he didn't say
to stop construction, did he?
Go find him then.
Talk to him properly.
He said "as usual" when he left, right?
Yes.
What is "as usual"?
Lin, "as usual".
I don't know you,
but I think
we should try our best
to keep the daily work.
Make it...
What does "as usual" mean?
It means we can't stop!
Will I be blamed when he's back?
Enough! Stop arguing!
If I had money,
I could access it, right?
Mr. Zheng, when are you coming back?
Look at your people.
Look at this mess! All chaos!
Come back now.
Xie, stop being sarcastic, okay?
I don't want it this way.
Small families are like that,
and big families like this.
(Town Mayor's Office)
Hello? Mr. Xia?
Here's the thing.
Yuehai's accounts have been frozen
by the investigators now,
and won't be unfrozen
until the investigation is over.
But many projects in Yuehai
are still ongoing.
Can't stop.
Yes.
I'm wondering if the county
could advance Yuehai
some funds.
For specific use.
♪Gently holding your face♪
♪To dry the tears from your eyes♪
♪My heart will always be yours♪
♪Tell me you'll never be alone again♪
♪Gazing deep into your eyes♪
♪No further words are needed♪
♪Tightly holding your hand♪
♪The warmth has never changed♪
♪We share the joy♪
♪We share the pain♪
♪We hold the same hope deep inside♪
♪We brave the storm♪
♪We share the quest♪
♪We cherish this love we share♪
♪Whether we've ever met before♪
♪Be it near or far away♪
♪My heartfelt wish for you♪
♪Is for your peace and happiness♪
♪We share the joy♪
♪We share the pain♪
♪We hold the same hope deep inside♪
♪We brave the storm♪
♪We share the quest♪
♪We cherish this love we share♪