(All characters, places,
and organizations are fictional.)
(Children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Episode 1)
(Surgery in progress)
Call 911! Hurry!
- Momo, stay with me!
- What happened?
What do we do? Manager Oh!
It isn't love if it changes.
You have to stay...
by my side forever.
- Momo!
- Momo.
- Yes, we need you here right away. Hurry.
There was a scuba diving accident!
Director Shin.
Momo has lost consciousness on a boat.
- Did they call 911?
- Yes, they called for help.
(International Arrivals)
(New York: Arrived)
What's taking so long?
- Here they come!
- Finally.
Here they come!
I wish they would come out soon.
I hope they come out soon.
Come on, why aren't they coming out?
Welcome back.
Who is all this for? Is it a celebrity?
Looks like it.
But they won't tell me who, though.
It can't be for Momo.
Hello.
We met once before
at an exhibition with Momo.
I'm with the culture desk
at Sungwoo Daily.
- Oh, yes...
- I'm Geum Ba Ra.
That's right. You have a unique name.
Are you here for me?
TEN.CO is arriving
a day ahead of schedule.
"Tango?"
It's TEN.CO, the popular idol group.
I see.
I'm having dinner with Momo tonight,
but her phone is off.
Her manager isn't picking up either.
I'm going to be about an hour late
because of TEN.CO's arrival.
With Momo? Just the two of you?
Yes. She said she had an exclusive for me.
If you can reach her another way,
could you ask her to delay dinner an hour?
- It's TEN.CO!
- Where? Where are they?
I'd really appreciate it.
Let's get some pictures!
The person you have called is unavailable.
Leave a message after the tone.
Is she filming something?
Ever since she got engaged,
she can't even be bothered
to text me once a day.
(Manager Oh)
It's ringing, but he's not picking up.
Why isn't anyone answering?
Do you happen to know
Momo's schedule today?
No, I don't.
(Director Choi Do Il)
Yes, CEO Hyun. It's been a while.
Why isn't Momo's manager...
answering my calls?
And I don't have
the road manager's number.
Really? I'm in Taiwan right now.
You're a busy man.
Anyway, I just met a reporter
from Sungwoo Daily,
and she said Momo promised her
some kind of surprise scoop today.
I'm worried she'll announce
the engagement.
She's close to that reporter.
Exactly. It's too soon.
The wedding isn't until next year.
Right. I'll look into it.
Isn't she with Director Shin Ju Shin?
Director Shin? Free at this hour?
Hello?
My battery died.
Yes?
Is Momo home?
No, she's not.
What are you doing?
She went scuba diving.
Not Momo. What are you doing?
Me?
- Cleaning.
- You sound like you just woke up.
I haven't said a word all day.
Are you back already?
I thought you weren't arriving
until 9:30 p.m.
I'm on my way. I'm hanging up.
(Manager Oh)
- Yes?
- It's me.
Where's Momo?
Isn't she with you?
She should be on her way to Seoul.
I heard she went scuba diving.
There's been a problem.
- We're at Gangwon Hospital.
- What's wrong?
Is Momo hurt?
(TEN.CO arrives a day early
for domestic schedule.)
They said something had suddenly come up
with Momo.
- The A course, please.
- Okay, and coffee to go with it?
Yes, a latte today.
Got it.
Does CEO Ha come here once in a while?
Which CEO Ha?
- James?
- CEO Ha Yong Joong.
Yes. He was here earlier today.
Aren't you scared?
You once said...
that there was nothing left
for us to be afraid of.
I'm sleeping over tonight.
Is that okay?
You don't want me to?
So is Momo at the director's hospital?
If a story gets out, it'll be a disaster.
Yes, this is Kim Jin Ju.
(6 Months Before Momo's Accident)
CEO Ha...
Yong Joong?
Right.
Is the terrace okay?
- This is our cameraman.
- I see.
I'm Lee Jin Ho.
- I don't have a business card yet.
- I see.
You must be new.
I joined the company the year before last.
You live in a nice neighborhood.
I like being near the water.
But I'd rather not take any photos.
It's for an interview,
so it's a bit difficult without a photo.
I made it clear to CEO Lee Myeong Woo
that I didn't do photos.
That wasn't relayed to me.
Don't you know CEO Lee personally?
He's close with a senior colleague.
I've joined them for a meal before.
How about a caricature?
I'm not a politician.
So, drinks first? Coffee, maybe?
Ginger ale, please.
- I've had an iced coffee this morning.
- Okay.
Does everyone just drink coffee
by default?
Sorry. But to be honest, yes.
Most people I meet,
and all my colleagues do.
If you don't want it to be just text,
how about an image of the Karuan Serpan
from the game?
Hey, why are you crying?
Where's your mom?
Did you lose her? Are you all alone?
Don't cry. I'll help you get home.
Did you come here to buy a snack?
(Neighborhood Supermarket)
What's your name?
Ba Ra.
Ba Ra?
Your name is Ba Ra?
How old are you? Five?
Six?
First, let me buy you something.
(Neighborhood Supermarket)
Let's go!
- What are you doing here?
- I came to see you.
You never said you had a younger sibling.
Draw your parents' faces accurately.
- Okay.
- Yes, teacher.
All right, you may begin.
Gosh! Look at that.
You did a great job, Beom Tak.
Good job, Ha Neul.
What is this?
Geum Ba Ra, you can't leave
until you finish your drawing.
She has to stay after and finish.
- Won't that emotionally scar her?
- I think so.
Your homeroom teacher did that,
even though he knew?
Are you done?
Are you being defiant? To your teacher?
You must've had caregivers
at the orphanage.
But they're not my mom and dad.
You're always talking back.
You learned only bad habits there.
Are you crying?
What good is crying?
Does it feel unfair?
That bastard...
How could someone like him be...
- Go on and have some.
- What, you don't have hands?
What are you, a baby?
She is a baby.
Who would think she's a fourth grader?
I thought she was in kindergarten.
(Apprenticeship Training Center)
(Shin Ju Shin)
Stop for a second.
(Apprenticeship Training Center)
Get in.
- I'm not going home.
- You wouldn't be.
Why isn't Ji An Hee coming to school?
What's he up to?
You shouldn't be hanging out with him.
Can't you tell?
He's not the punk you think he is.
Just go.
(Seongsil Hall)
Aren't you going to college?
Okay, thank you for your hard work.
Just be quiet and listen.
That was one of the parents, wasn't it?
The young woman you were dining with
at Mangyeongru.
I just took a wild guess.
Everyone knows
you shouldn't accept gifts like that.
Are you the only one who doesn't know,
Mr. Kim?
Just give me one answer, and I'll go.
What kind of educator are you
to these kids?
I asked, what kind of teacher are you?
I like the kids, and I love them...
- I do my best to...
- You do your best to discriminate?
You need to change, starting now.
No more discrimination.
Treat every kid equally,
whether they have wealthy parents
or come from nothing.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
- Do you?
- Yes.
How can you, a homeroom teacher,
hurt your students?
You're raising two daughters yourself,
So Young and Hye Young.
I wonder what would happen
if I sent this to the school board?
I got a clear shot of the parent's face
and of you accepting the gift.
This looks like
some very expensive liquor, too.
So?
What about the game's format?
It's a side-scrolling platformer.
Have you never played one before?
This is for our readers
who might not be familiar.
Could you briefly explain the plot for us?
You acquire powers
hidden across the continent...
to save the princess.
Yes, sir. Alright.
The game's protagonist, Karuan,
is a very charming character.
Does he resemble you,
the developer, at all?
Do you think so?
Have you seen comments...
from fans asking
if Karuan is your avatar, CEO Ha?
No, I haven't.
He was just created to be a fun...
and cool character.
Three and a half million sold worldwide
in a month is a record...
no one in the country has.
How does that feel?
It deserves a grand finish.
Would you say you're ambitious?
Is there anyone who isn't?
Have you met anyone who isn't?
It's admirable, as long as it's not greed.
I did some research,
and it says you dropped out
of high school.
- That's right.
- May I ask why?
I just wasn't into studying.
And was there any particular reason
you weren't interested?
Just like you don't need a reason
to like something,
I just didn't want to do it.
You seem very straightforward and cool.
I like to keep things simple.
Is it because game development
requires so much brainpower?
That's part of it.
How do you relieve stress?
Do you work out?
Do I look like the type?
You're in great shape. I'd say you do.
Yes. I work out at home too.
I run for one hour every morning.
Here at the Han River Park?
Yes. I sometimes catch the sunrise, too.
You're so disciplined.
Is working out...
enough to give you your dopamine fix?
Are you asking
if I do anything else for fun?
It's just that...
it's rare for people to work out
just for the fun of it.
Some people genuinely love to study,
but most of us force ourselves
to work out just to stay healthy.
So I was wondering...
if you did anything else
to blow off steam.
People throw that word "dopamine"
around a lot these days,
but what is it exactly?
It's a precursor hormone to adrenaline.
It's released when you eat good food
or do something you enjoy.
And in your case?
When do you...
For me,
it's when an interview is going well.
When a short question gets a long answer,
my dopamine spikes.
But too much of it isn't a good thing.
You're a new face.
- Special Forces?
- UDT, sir.
You've got a good look about you.
Thank you, sir.
- Hey.
I'm not late, am I?
Manager Kang, the Chairman's watch is off.
Is it five minutes off?
- What about Su Ah?
- She got back yesterday.
I heard she has a boyfriend?
Yes, but she says he's a guy friend.
What's all this "guy friend,"
"boyfriend" nonsense?
As opposed to what, dating an animal?
Kids these days are so different
from when we were young.
She really cleaned me out.
That one runs circles
around her older brother.
The Ha women are a tough bunch.
- Stronger than us men.
- That's not true for you, Mr. Chairman.
Come on.
And lastly,
could you tell us about your future plans?
I'll be continuously developing DLC...
to keep providing our players
with great new content.
But first,
I'm going to take a trip to recharge.
DLC?
Downloadable content.
Thank you for your time.
Is that it?
- Yes.
- You're a very fast typer.
I bet you're good at video games.
Can I ask you a personal question?
Sure.
Since you work mostly by yourself,
don't you ever get lonely?
I don't have time to be lonely.
How many close friends do you have
that you can confide in?
They're all busy, I guess.
I guess you could say everyday happiness
wasn't meant for me.
Now, I'd like to try living
like everyone else.
Where are you traveling to?
Europe, starting with Italy.
Do you have a favorite place in Europe?
I'm not sure.
Personally,
I've always wanted to go to Paris.
You haven't been to Paris yet?
No.
The two of you have such a great vibe.
Do you mind if I get a shot of you two?
It's not for an article.
Just to remember the interview.
By the way,
for the Head of Strategic Planning
at the holding company,
I'm going to recommend Bae Seon Gil.
I...
was thinking of Min Kang Woo.
Bae Seon Gil.
Chairman, Min Kang Woo's the best
in all aspects.
Why are you so...
protective of Min Kang Woo?
It's not that I'm being protective.
Think of Bae Seon Gil's accomplishments,
like landing the Dubai contract.
He dedicated his life to this company,
and it cost him his marriage.
He didn't dedicate himself to the company.
He got divorced because
he dedicated his body to a younger woman.
And he got caught red-handed.
Are you spying on our executives?
Informal?
What is this, political scheming
or corporate manipulation?
You cut me off while I was speaking...
I apologize.
It's just like last time
with Woojin Shipping.
Your right-hand man took the position.
Stop with the "right-hand man" talk.
- What?
- If that's how you label it,
then Bae Seon Gil is
your right-hand man, Mr. Chairman.
Team Leader Bae may be a great salesman,
but this position requires a strategist.
Are you lecturing me now?
In terms of contributions,
performance reviews,
and every other evaluation standard,
Min Kang Woo is the right choice.
Why, you little...
Brother.
Just because you studied abroad,
you think you can talk down to me?
You have no sense of propriety!
What could that smell be?
You've gotten so thin.
They say our bodies just rot when we die.
But don't you worry.
I'll make sure you're preserved perfectly
so you won't rot.
Your stomach is completely empty,
so you must feel nice and clean.
Today's the big day.
The glorious day you pass on.
Should I show some mercy?
I thought about letting you
starve to death peacefully.
But that takes too long.
And life clings on so stubbornly,
doesn't it?
Besides, you need to feel at least
a fraction of what I went through.
Don't you think?
It's only fair.
These last eight days
have been pure bliss.
How should I send you off?
How would you like to depart
from this world?
You're going to beg me
to put you out of your misery.
You know the saying.
"If you can't avoid it, enjoy it."
So enjoy it.
I'm about to become a monster.
So watch this masterpiece unfold.
And try to hold on to your sanity.
Stop.
Please! Don't kill me!
Bring a few dishes. Your pick.
We have to get the eggplant lasagna.
Of course.
CEO Hyun looks so young now.
Did she say where she got her work done?
- She looks so young in her photos.
- Tell me about it.
I didn't ask. And I don't care to know.
How could you not be curious
when you're an actress?
Then again, you're still young enough
not to need it.
How come there isn't a single crease
on your clothes?
I changed before I left.
I was meeting you, Momo.
I'm dying to see your beautiful place
that people have told me about.
I moved.
- To where?
- You wouldn't know if I told you.
It's a residential-commercial spot.
Momo, do you believe in fortune-telling?
Should I?
I kept getting sick and hurting myself.
Something felt off, so I got a reading.
Apparently, I'm not supposed to live
in a big, luxurious house.
It's a pain, but that's my fate.
- Oh my.
- So, what else could I do?
Are you feeling better now?
- Strangely enough, I am.
- Goodness.
(An Hee)
- Hey, An Hee.
- Why do you sound so down?
I'm not down.
Actually, I just stopped by your place,
but the lights were out.
Why didn't you call first?
You shouldn't have come when you're busy.
I just figured you'd be home.
Perfect. I'll treat you,
so bring Jin Ju and come on over.
She usually doesn't get off
until 10 p.m. or so.
- Hey.
- Yes?
Never mind. I'll tell you in person.
Where are you?
I got a special bonus from the chairman.
Use it to get yourself a car.
All the other reporters have cars,
you know.
Plenty of reporters don't.
Then at least get a sofa
for your apartment or something.
It's a palace even without a sofa.
You'll never guess who
I interviewed today.
Ha Yong Joong.
Did he recognize you?
I was filling in for a senior reporter.
And he just pretended to look at my card.
You've both done well for yourselves.
You should reach out to him.
- "Done well?"
- You're not doing too badly yourself.
It's good manners not to bother friends
after they've made it big.
I'm so sick of Peoples.
There's just nowhere else decent to go.
What do you mean there's nowhere to go?
You like Japanese food.
Today, I'm treating you, Momo,
but my clients usually pay.
So how can I suggest we go
to some expensive omakase place?
Besides, we're done talking business
in 20 or 30 minutes.
And you can't just sit there on your phone
in silence for 2 or 3 hours.
Confirm the facts tomorrow,
add some details, and run it.
Understood.
And this isn't like you, Geum Ba Ra.
You should've gotten a picture.
I heard Ha Yong Joong is
quite a looker, too.
It felt like he would've just walked out
if I forced the issue.
He's that touchy?
He said he wasn't comfortable
with being recognized.
All right. You can go.
Yes, sir.
It's torture.
And why are the explanations
for each dish so long?
- Especially at fine-dining restaurants.
- I know, right?
I wish they'd just stop.
But it would be awkward to tell them to.
Ba Ra!
That last shoot was disappointing.
Can't we find a better photographer?
I'm so sorry.
I must have the wrong room...
Hello, Reporter Geum.
You remember me?
Of course. You're from Sungwoo Daily.
Come on in for a second.
Please.
You didn't recognize me?
How could I possibly not recognize you?
I was at the last press conference too.
I know.
Then why didn't you say hi?
I didn't want to interrupt.
This is our director, and my manager.
- I'm Choi Do Il.
- I'm all out of business cards.
I'll get one next time.
I've been meaning to contact you.
You wrote such a wonderful article.
I just wrote what I honestly felt.
You should be an actress
instead of a reporter.
Right, Director?
You say that as if you really mean it.
And you're taking my sincerity as a joke.
My friend is here.
I'll buy you a meal to thank you.
I could treat you instead.
I tend to walk into the wrong rooms.
I've even walked into the men's restroom.
Oh, my gosh. Me too!
I've walked into the ladies' room twice.
You should stop by our company sometime,
like for a party or a formal event.
I'll doll you up.
I can already picture
the perfect outfits for you.
(Sungwoo Daily, Geum Ba Ra)
That's very kind of you to say.
He doesn't make empty promises.
Sometimes I do.
Hold on, your outfits...
Look, we're twinning.
This outfit was originally hers,
but we swapped.
You two look great together.
And she's an incredible writer.
To use an old-fashioned phrase,
you've got both style and skill.
And what's your personality like?
- I'll get out of your hair.
- No, wait...
I'll text you.
Please do stop by.
An answer, please.
Okay.
She's a breath of fresh air. So unique.
Isn't she?
Yes.
At the press conference for "Magic Fog,"
she nailed the key points of the project,
and she wrote about me so beautifully.
You could feel her respect for actors.
And to think, she was just typing quietly
and barely asked any questions.
You know what they say,
still waters run deep.
Is that a real saying?
Half of what he says are old sayings.
Don't differentiate between old and new.
That's all just judgment.
Do you know what happens
when you let go of judgment?
What?
Manager Yoon, you're really knocking them
back tonight.
- Enlightenment.
- You've reached enlightenment?
I'm on the verge.
That's why I don't get stressed.
I just shake everything off.
- Compliments of the chef.
- Oh, my.
- But I'm so full.
- There's always room for dessert.
- Please thank the chef for me.
- Will do.
Gosh, this looks amazing.
I should come with you more often, Momo.
We even get freebies like this.
When I come with other people,
they don't even give me a cabbage heart.
A digestive.
Thank you.
And what's a "cabbage heart?"
- Do you know?
- No?
You can search online for it.
It's the sweet core of the cabbage.
It's actually pretty tasty.
- We're going to have leftovers.
- Says who? My pouch.
You can't let food go to waste.
- Are you getting a doggy bag?
- This will last me two days.
- You're so thrifty.
- Call me Mr. Thrifty.
Teacher, whoever marries you
will be a very lucky woman.
In what way?
In every way.
You're so considerate and funny.
Enough with the lip service.
Set me up with someone.
But all I know are other actors.
What's wrong with actresses?
I'd be grateful.
They're pretty and they make good money.
As if you don't know
way more actresses than I do.
And they're all trying to get
on your good side.
- A barber can't cut his own hair.
- So looks are important to you?
For him, it's looks first,
and looks second.
You're wrong. First is looks, second is...
My little brother is a watermelon fiend.
In his heyday, he could eat
almost a whole one in a single sitting.
- You have a brother?
- He's young enough to be his son.
Not with a 17-year age gap.
By the way,
there's actually someone
who wants to be set up with you, Momo.
And I can vouch for him.
He's the Noir Hospital chairman's son,
the chief surgeon.
And there's the Noir Foundation,
so he's the total package, in every way.
Oh, goodness.
I'm not really into doctors.
Why not? He's a prime catch.
Who said anything about marriage?
Just meet him, for now.
I've got my reputation to think about.
Apparently, he was completely smitten
after watching "A Maiden's Prayer."
Tell him I'm nothing like that
in real life.
Prospect-wise, his younger brother
might be an even better catch.
He has zero interest in women.
So he's just a man on the outside?
He must quit his video games first.
Only then might he start noticing women.
(Sungwoo Daily, Geum Ba Ra)
What?
Did you eat fish cakes?
Can you smell it?
Don't you brush your teeth after you eat?
Thank you.
Don't be late.
Thanks for finding the time
when you were busy.
The pleasure is all mine.
The Noir Foundation...
Yes.
I've heard it does a lot of good work.
Not me personally...
It's the foundation that does the work.
When things free up a bit,
I'd like to volunteer my talents, too.
- That's very generous of you.
- I have to apologize.
Alright.
I just got a call for a sudden reshoot,
so I won't be able to stay for dinner.
I'm so sorry.
Do you have to leave right now?
I can stay for one drink, though.
- You're filming a period drama?
- Yes.
It's just an over-the-shoulder shot.
I only need to deliver my lines.
I already spoke with the manager
on my way in.
If I'd known,
I would've had a decent lunch.
Oh, no.
I was busy, too, though.
I understand.
Because when I get paged for an emergency,
I have to leave immediately, too.
Anyway, at least...
I got to see you.
"Got to see you?"
Not "It's an honor to see you?"
I like this champagne.
I'll send a few bottles to your place.
I know the address.
No, that's okay. I already have some.
So when can we reschedule the dinner
we missed tonight?
I don't make personal plans
when I'm working on a project.
- Is that a no?
- It's not a no.
This is just how I live.
A normal life is impossible for me.
You can always make time.
No matter how busy you are,
everyone has time for a meal or two a day.
Am I that bad?
Is he dropping the formalities?
I haven't had the chance to find out.
That's my point.
You should get to know me.
Do you make a habit
of being so condescending?
- To people in general?
- Yes.
Well...
Did you feel like
I was talking down to you?
These days, people even speak politely
to preschoolers.
I wasn't using casual language.
I was being polite.
My debut was in a medical drama,
and the doctors who were our consultants
were incredibly busy.
And yet, you've seen my show?
Only "A Maiden's Prayer."
I stumbled on it while flipping channels
and got completely hooked.
I binged the whole thing in one day.
And not on fast-forward.
Doctor...
This might sound a little forward, but...
Your looks are kind of wasted
on just your patients.
Have you ever been scouted?
You have, haven't you?
- I'm not the type at all.
- You never know.
Being in front of a camera
can bring out a hidden talent.
I'm supposed to take over the hospital.
This is a much better fit for me.
Let me guess, you picked a stethoscope
at your first birthday party?
From the pictures,
it looks like I picked a dictionary.
- What did you pick?
- A microphone.
Although...
Go on.
If there had been a model of a skull,
I would've picked that.
Come on.
You can't be serious.
When you operate,
you find every brain has its own feel.
They're all different.
Really?
Yes.
You don't want to open up my head, do you?
Of course not.
Let's hope that never has to happen.
You look good when you smile.
You should smile more often.
Your first impression was a bit stiff.
That's a first.
Really?
I've been called arrogant
a few times, though.
By who? Your friends?
Then give me a chance.
A chance to show you my smile more often.
Playing my role in "A Maiden's Prayer"
was honestly brutal.
But I got way too invested
in the character.
From a man's perspective,
did you relate to the older man at all?
Are you asking if I'm a pervert?
No.
I was just curious
what male viewers thought of him.
His inner thoughts? His base instincts?
I suppose a very small minority
might have related.
People like that do exist, after all.
But people should live
like decent human beings.
To behold you in the flesh...
Oh, my gosh,
did I really just say "behold?"
I must have shattered your fantasy.
I looked pure in "A Maiden's Prayer,"
thanks to the director.
This side of you is charming too.
What's the role?
- The queen of the social scene.
- So you're playing yourself.
Are you a social butterfly?
- I'm not so sure.
- About me?
Or about women in general?
Do you know a lot about men?
I'd like to think so.
I should get going.
I'll give you a ride.
- Where's the set?
- No, thanks.
The van's more comfortable.
So when are we having
this dinner we couldn't have?
Would a meal taste any good
if it feels like an obligation?
If there's one thing
you should know about me,
I'm a total mama's girl.
And?
Just thought you should know.
I'm not as charming as the characters
I play in dramas.
In that case,
I'm an only child, and a daddy's boy.
(6 Months After Momo's Accident)
(Hospital Director, Shin Ju Shin)
(Kim Jin Ju)
You're here.
I heard the surgery was over.
(Should I prepare your dinner?)
You should have some dinner.
This is enough for me.
I don't have the appetite.
Don't bother.
Do you still have rounds?
Do you have to go see your patients?
I think it was about a month...
before your father passed away?
I heard about it.
I didn't tell anyone.
I heard...
a brain swap is possible.
You've done one, haven't you?
I've thought this through,
and it's the only way.
It's only a matter of time
before the world finds out.
How long can we hide this?
And I can't...
bear to see this anymore as her mother.
I'm sure you feel the same way,
Director Shin.
You must have considered the option,
haven't you?
We'd need a subject.
Me.
I've considered every possible option,
but dying isn't the answer.
I can't just die alone.
Am I supposed to poison my sweet girl?
Could I give Momo a lethal injection?
I'm not giving up.
I'll take care of any problems or issues.
I will handle everything.
Just do the surgery.
Just because it was successful once...
Things can still go wrong.
There's always a risk with surgery.
That's why you have us sign consent forms.
But what if something goes wrong,
and you don't wake up?
Could it be any worse than this?
Just being awake and breathing
is already torment for me.
I haven't gone a single night
without crying myself to sleep.
I don't care if I end up like Momo.
Just do it. We'll leave the rest to fate.
Your engagement isn't public knowledge,
so I can just live as Momo,
and you'll be free to meet someone new.
People's feelings change, after all.
Some feelings don't change.
I doubt that.
If I collapse from the stress of all this,
who will take care of Momo?
You know what they say.
"When illness comes in, love flies out."
The feelings you've developed
in just over a year?
It wasn't love.
It was just an infatuation.
- We...
- The ocean may never run dry,
but fire always burns out.
What fire burns forever?
I loved Momo more than anyone
in the world.
My love for her is no less
than your love as a mother.
Are you comparing a mother's love
to romantic love?
Okay, sure. Let's say it was love,
up until now.
But you'd just leave her in this state?
If you were in Momo's condition,
what would she have wanted for you?
Is just being alive the same as living?
Let's just think about Momo.
Let's think about what's really
and truly best for her.
All you have to do is transplant
her brain into my body.
Her eyes, her nose, her mouth...
They'll all be the same.
The damaged brain?
If it's in her body or mine,
what's the difference?
This is what a parent...
This is a mother's love.
Chairman Hwang of Bada Group.
The body is Chairman Hwang's,
but the brain is his son's.
The father had a terminal brain tumor,
while his prized only son was paralyzed
in a motorcycle accident.
After your father told me,
I watched him closely.
The way Chairman Hwang talked,
and his whole demeanor...
Only his face looked like
he was in his 60s.
Leave it.
Skin needs to stay moisturized.
Hey.
Thank you for all your hard work.
You've worked hard.
It's time to take a vacation.
You've never been to Hong Kong, have you?
You should go. It's nice.
I'll book you a business class flight.
But I'm not planning on leaving.
You told me I could stay
for as long as I wanted.
I've been diagnosed with depression.
So I need to do something.
I'm thinking of trying to do
some housework myself.
Something physical.
But how could you, ma'am?
(Current time, Surgery time,
Anesthesia time)
One thing's missing.
The candles.
The wind blew them out.
This is more than enough.
So, is that necklace special or something?
You're just now asking?
It protects me.
From now on,
I'll be the one to protect you.
But I thought you were afraid of water.
It's for when I'm underwater.
I'm going to take up scuba diving.
Really?
I want us to do everything together.
Who gave it to you?
- My instructor.
- Your scuba instructor?
Yes.
Take it off.
Take it off. I'll have a prettier one
made for you, with a diamond.
Are you jealous?
Then don't give me a reason to be.
What did I do?
My buddy...
My diving partner.
Your buddy must be a man, right?
She's a woman.
I first thought
you had great manners at Crystal.
We were talking about acting,
and when I raised my champagne glass,
you raised yours with me to drink.
That's just common courtesy.
It wasn't just manners.
It came from the heart.
I love how thoughtful you are
about the little things.
I want to be just like my dad.
He could easily meet younger women
and remarry,
but he only ever thinks about my mother.
He's always been that devoted.
Do you believe in a next life?
I wouldn't rule it out.
If there is a next life,
he says he'll find my mother
and marry her all over again.
But missing someone is different
from being lonely.
Don't you think he'll get lonely
when he's older?
He'll have his grandchildren to dote on.
It isn't love if it changes.
You have to stay...
by my side forever.
(Doctor Shin)
What happened to Momo?
Who told you?
Someone made 100 million dollars
just by developing one game.
This is Ha Yong Joong.
I was wondering if you were...
the Geum Ba Ra at Minjin Elementary
16 years ago.
You have a boyfriend, right?
What makes you think I do?
I made a point not to ask you the same.
Why didn't you ask on purpose?
I think I want to get married.
- To me?
- Just give me a chance to prove myself.
- He's actually not bad.
- If he contacts you, shut him down.
So he doesn't get his hopes up.
Don't lead him on.
My mother left this for me
to give to the person I fell in love with.
He's really determined, isn't he?
I want to share my whole life with you.
But I don't.
Then I'll become your everything.
I can promise and swear to you.
I know I can be a responsible husband.
How about an engagement first,
rather than marriage?