=Love at Night=
=Episode 2=
Director Xu.
Remember to pay me for the room.
( Director, Department I)
( Products Introduction of Lemi )
Director Xu.
Remember to pay me for the room.
(Sending friend request)
For the room charge.
(Mo Lingze)
Still remember what happened last night.
I hope we're quits
and let it go as soon as possible.
Excuse me.
Could you please give this to that man?
Who's "that man"?
A member in the band.
Sa...
Could you tell me where Lingze is?
He's yours.
Not mine.
How could I know where he is?
He never answers my calls
or texts me back.
He was purposely ignoring me?
Girl.
You have to hurry.
Mo is particularly popular.
Sure enough, a playboy.
I'm not in a hurry.
Sorry to bother you.
You're the white-collar, aren't you?
You also come to Mo?
No.
I just come to return something.
Thank you.
See?
The fourth girl in this month.
What a playboy!
I have to write it down.
Even such a trifle?
It's what I should do as a mate.
What did she ask you to hand over?
How can I know?
(Fan Yunxi)
Youyou.
I'm waiting for you in the bridal chamber.
Let's talk calmly.
How can we give up the ten-year relationship?
I won't leave until you come.
What do you want to talk?
You told me, right?
You want to marry before you're 30.
You want to move out.
I've imagined numerous times the life
after we live together.
Our dream is coming true.
Please forgive me.
I can't.
Youyou.
It's just an incident in our life.
Believe me.
It's gonna be over soon.
Fan Yunxi.
It's not an incident.
Not everything's gotta to be over.
Maybe you can make it.
But I can't.
No one can promise
he will never make a mistake.
I'm just hoping you give me a chance.
Look at everything in this house.
They're your favorites.
We've been looking forward to the day for so long.
Are you really willing to give up?
You're right.
Life is so long.
Once I accept the false beauty,
I may live in the sham all my life.
Like your lie,
it broke with a simple touch.
I won't break up with you.
Is there any follow-up of Fan Yunxi?
Yes.
He told me a lot.
But it didn't work.
Well.
Let's go for something exciting this weekend.
Roller Coaster
or Room Escape?
Stimulus is called for.
Go to Room Escape on your own.
Don't worry. I'm here.
So what?
And I just feel bored.
Precisely why you need to go now.
The more exciting, the...
Good morning, Mr. Mo.
Come in.
Go ahead.
What's up?
Mr. Mo.
Let's get straight to the point.
I hope you can forget what happened before.
Otherwise, it will affect our work.
Forget what?
Forget what you shouldn't remember.
What if it's too impressive to forget?
Mr. Mo.
We're just for fun.
Don't take it serious.
It seems you're quite a dab hand.
Takes one to know one.
Your ears are hot already.
Why not come in, Director Xu?
Hello, Shangger.
Leader is a promising enterprise
after preliminary screening.
Its business includes amusement arcades and parks,
cinemas and situational games.
A complete product line.
A promising prospect.
Amusement parks are small.
Facilities are stale.
The target acceptors are not made determinate.
Cinema profits are passable at the first glance.
But in this area
it's much lower than nearby Wanda and Stellar.
Attendance is poor.
Target sales are lower.
Is this the result of your due diligence?
The poor attendance
is because they haven't updated the decoration.
Advertising has failed to keep pace.
I think these disadvantages are potentialities.
We can improve them one by one after our investment.
I don't care about your standard
before I get here.
But I have to tell you.
Shangger is an investment firm
not for charity.
Tapping and cultivating potential projects
is also one of the businesses of us.
If 80 percent of our projects
are hard to handle,
I wonder how we can get our annual profits.
But...
Give me a new
due diligence instruction in three days.
No problem.
Miss White-collar is generous!
Mo is worth so little?
It seemed she received poor service.
A bad experience.
No wonder she said
she didn't want to get involved in your business.
Go to Room Escape on your own.
Don't worry. I'm here.
So what?
Precisely why you need to go now.
The more exciting, the more interesting.
You said there were situational games in Leader?
Yes.
The situational game
is the most popular Room
on social networking websites now.
The ace project of Leader.
Style?
It focuses on real scene restoration and thrill.
I'll conduct field research if you want more details.
Leave it to me.
It may be inappropriate if you go to finish it, Mr. Mo.
The more exciting, the more interesting.
Right?
Qingyou.
Here's the proposal of Meeting Your Match.
Please look it over.
If there are no problems, please sign here.
Great progress, Meng.
OK.
Let's follow this plan first.
(Mo Lingze, Themed Room Escape)
Come here.
Mr. Mo.
Text the wrong person?
We're even if you come.
I've paid for the room.
Director Xu.
It's from Shangger.
Thanks.
What do you want from me?
Don't you want to let it go?
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry.
My bad. My bad.
My bad. Please.
It's me.
Mo Lingze, why do you choose this place?
I thought Director Xu wanted to make it clear
with nobody listening to it.
I do like quiet places
but not here.
So? You're afraid?
I thought you were good at playing.
Speak up.
What do you want me to do?
To beat the game.
Then I'll let it go.
Do you think I'm idle
or you're idle?
Of course I'm idle.
I haven't met such an interesting woman for so long.
It is understandable.
OK.
No problem.
You'll forget it if I beat the game, right?
You got my word.
Go ahead.
You.
Fine.
Don't try to test me.
I will not give other women
any chances as the princess of Gold Sun.
Lingze's car.
Don't try to get rid of me.
You nearly caused a crash!
Where's Lingze? Are you his driver?
I'm the investment manager.
You're the fangirl of Mr. Mo.
His girlfriend in the future.
Golden Sun Capital.
The same trade.
But
your title is a little low as a trainee.
(Wang Ji, Shangger)
Did Shangger let anyone
be the manager these days?
Although I'm an intern,
Mr. Lin of Golden Sun is my Dad.
You're Miss Lin.
Shall I call my Dad?
No no.
Nice to meet you.
How's Lingze doing?
Did he eat well?
Did he sleep well?
Is there any woman badgering him?
Miss Lin.
These are Mr. Mo's privacy.
It's nothing serious.
I mean we go way back.
You're Mr. Mo's...
You've finally realized it.
No wonder he's smiling a lot lately.
Really?
It's true to overcome firmness by gentleness.
To overcome firmness by gentleness? How?
It's not late to quit now.
I won't.
Do you need any help?
No.
Keep your hands off me.
But you never kept your hands off me.
It was totally a mistake that night.
Forget it
if I beat the game.
On the premise of beating the game.
OK. No problem.
OK.
Dear players.
Time's up.
The exit will open for you.
Challenge failed.
Welcome to come here again.
Mr. Mo.
Actually you're enjoying making me look like a fool.
I didn't expect you have such a strong prejudice
against me.
Prejudice?
I don't think so.
You had an urge to let it go?
Yes.
Because it should not have happened.
But it happened for sure.
We can erase it.
There shouldn't be so many connections between us.
But the challenge failed.
It would let you down, Director Xu.
I'll kill you. I'll kill you. I'll kill you.
Hey, hey, hey!
It's me.
Xu Wei, you're killing yourself.
You're not supposed to be so faint-hearted.
Afraid of darkness, ghosts and Dad.
I'll wring your neck.
Qingyou.
Qingyou, my bad, my bad.
It's all my fault.
Now I see that I was wrong.
Because of what?
What's wrong with your luggage?
Go home.
Go home?
You quit school?
I've graduated.
You're talking nonsense!
You should spend five years on college.
I, your younger brother, am a genius.
It took me four years to finish the five-year study.
And I got the first prize.
Really?
You're not cheating, are you?
Art will never tell a lie.
You said you would become a master before.
What happened? You gave up your dream?
I came back for inspiration
because of my dream.
Are you artists so metaphysical?
I refused all admissions of MFA.
I'm not kidding.
You won't get an MFA's degree?
Do parents know about it?
No.
Never tell them the truth.
If they know about it,
I will die undoubtedly.
Then you'll lose
your cute and attractive younger brother.
They'd better throw you away.
You're so cruel.
Do you know
my dream since my childhood?
What?
To be an only child.
How can you say that to your brother?
All right.
Dad and Mom will be back in two weeks.
Keep your secret.
Don't spill the beans.
OK.
Qingyou.
Can you do me a favor?
Please help me find out if your firm
or my brother-in-law needs someone
to draw decorative paintings.
I'll go to work with Gu Dayan.
He deserves to get some businesses.
Don't bother Fan Yunxi.
I will help you with what you said.
But your efforts are the most important.
What's wrong with you?
He'll become our family soon.
Isn't it natural to ask my
brother-in-law to help me?
Why are you so independent?
Don't guess what women think.
OK. I can't read your thoughts.
Any follow-up?
Who?
The white-collar.
She didn't hit your fancy?
That's natural.
Not your type at a glance.
What type should I be attracted to?
Sago cycas seldom blossoms.
Hello, Sa.
I want to book the whole bar for a party this weekend.
Weekend?
How many people?
Mask party.
About 60 people.
Will the Sad Band
perform at that time?
Pay extra for it.
Money is not an issue.
It's enough that the band can perform.
Especially the good-looking guitarist.
OK.
That's settled then.
OK. Thank you.
Keep your place for me.
There will be an event?
A girl will have a party.
And you're asked to be present.
I'm busy.
You have to come.
No way.
Who's it?
What are you doing?
Xu Wei.
You've been back.
You still have one year left, right?
You still remember the date I come back.
You were expelled from school
or repatriated?
Don't jinx me!
I've completed my credit
and graduated one year ahead of time.
Fine. All in all, it's great.
What is the smell?
You're killing me.
Where's your elder sister?
She's sleeping.
Who is it that you drew?
Just a person.
Tell me the truth.
A girl.
You have a girl in your heart.
Kid.
I'm not a little boy.
Fine.
Princess Xu.
Time to get up.
No no no.
Just a disappointment in love.
You're decadent now.
Hurry up. You've slept for so long.
Don't look down upon me.
I'm too tired and busy at ordinary times.
Come and sleep with me.
I must get my beauty sleep.
Your words don't matter.
Hurry up.
I'm going to dress you up and
go to a party today.
Come on.
Every time we go to a party
you're looking for handsome guys.
Then I'm looking for you.
I won't go.
So boring.
Who told you that?
You have to be with handsome guys
so that you can get rid of
the memory about Fan Yunxi.
I don't have to.
I need sleep.
Youyou, look at me.
Charming, attractive but weak.
Who will take me home if I'm drunk?
You? Charming and weak?
You would be Mulan
(*A strong girl who disguised as man in the army)
if you were born in ancient times.
-Go with me or not?  -I'll go.
I'll go.
Take me with you.
I can take you home
if you're drunk.
Stay out of it.
We won't take a child.
Get out.
Can you move quickly
since we've reached the door?
Are you sure I should dress like this
to come to the mask party?
Are you questioning my taste?
Besides,
what are you afraid of since we'll wear a mask?
I worry that you're sad alone at home.
I'm telling you.
There's a special event tonight.
Just for once.
Let's go.
I'm the VIP here. No queuing up.
I'm telling you.
All present today are social elites,
investment leaders
and financial celebrities.
You have to take one
since I've dressed you up.
Otherwise
you'll never rise to the very top.
I've long stopped daydreaming.
I think it's better to get a promotion or a raise.
You've depended on yourself for 30 years.
I hope this isn't too much.
How about you?
You!
The two o'clock position.
Elegant and moderate.
A high-flyer deserves your investment.
You can see him clearly even he's with such a big mask?
Of course.
Hurry up!
Go!
What's this?
Lottery.
Everyone has one.
Hello.
I'm Sa, the boss here.
Welcome to Sad Bar.
Have fun tonight
and enjoy the mask party.
Now let's give a round of applause to
Miss Lin, the protagonist today.
Lin Siyu, the daughter
of the chairman of Golden Sun Capital.
Let's have a good time
and enjoy ourselves tonight.
My treat.
Terrific!
Average-looking.
Not as pretty as you.
-Miss Lin...  -Stop teasing.
She prepared a special surprise for you.
You've got your number plate.
After a while, we will draw two lucky ones.
They'll become the special couple tonight.
You didn't tell me that.
I didn't know, either.
I was thinking
why I got a plate of public baths.
It was for this.
You told me it was for lottery.
Yes.
The special couple is the prize.
Boring.
It may not be you.
Come on.
What I got was No. 99 and No. 17.
I'm No. 99.
What a coincidence!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
It is too fake.
Where's my No. 17?
Where's my couple?
Who did it?
That's all for your marriage.
Plate lottery for you.
Where's my No. 17?
Where's my couple?
Lin.
You're not No. 99.
It's No. 66.
I'm not No. 66?
You're No. 99.
Congratulations! Hurry up!
Where's the No. 99?
Here!
She's the No. 99.
Are you crazy?
I'll give the opportunity to you, girl!
-You're welcome. Go ahead.  -Fang Qi.
Fang Qi.
Come on!
So unreliable is Bobo.
He even confused No. 99 and No. 66.
Where's No. 17?
-Here!  -He's here!
-He's here!  -I won't go!
I'll help you take off the mask.
Come on.
Hold out your hands.
Your hands, please.
It doesn't matter.
She needs practice.
You can make it!
Now that our guitarist has been drawn,
shouldn't you perform for us?
Performance! Performance! Performance!
Come here.
What are you going to do?
To play the guitar.
I can do nothing. What should I do?
Don't move. Follow me.
Hold it tight.
Are you ready?
(Fang Qi)
Do you want me to pick you up?
I'll give an opportunity to you.
It's on the way after dinner.
What do you want from me?
I just want to help you solve the problem.
If you really want to do that,
then forget what happened.
You're good at flattering yourself.
What did you think
happened to us that night?