=Love at Night=
=Episode 6=
What are you doing?
I want to explain it.
I don't like to be misunderstood.
I don't want to know.
What's there to say about the things
that haven't been sent out?
Because of my mom.
My mom used to love making hairy crabs.
I stopped eating after she died.
I'm sorry.
I don't know your difficulties.
Are you all right?
I'm okay.
Just don't get me wrong.
French DDS Media Company
owns the copyright
of 124 top international sports events.
According to our research and evaluation,
DDS is valued at more than US $1.2 billion.
Many large companies
including Golden Sun Capital
will participate in DDS acquisition.
Lawyer Fan thought of Shangger
at the first time.
Thanks to Lawyer Fan,
we Shangger can also
participate in major international projects.
Never mind.
Lawyer Fan
gives us a big deal.
He has his own purpose.
He acts as a contact in the middle.
Do you know how much commission he can get?
Conservative estimate,
tens of millions.
As far as I know,
the copyright of sports events in Europe
is not a permanent license.
The contract is signed
every three to five years on average,
and will be cleared automatically upon expiration.
In this way,
the valuation of 1.2 billion
is a little high.
Mr. Mo,
I'm sure you've heard about that before.
The previous offer was 1.8 billion.
Now it's 1.2 billion.
It is already the lowest price.
DDS let go this time
because their financial situation is extremely unstable.
A loss every three years,
the risk is very high.
Mr. Mo.
What's your opinion?
Very simple.
Make a supplementary agreement
on the basis of the agreement.
If DDS fails to meet the standard
at the expiration of the agreement,
the investment money will automatically
be converted into debt.
DDS is the leading company in the industry.
After many rounds of negotiation,
Lawyer Fan won the acquisition index.
Coupled with the convertible debt
is extremely distrustful of the company,
even an insult.
Mr. Han,
are you talking about feelings?
The DDS acquisition case
is a major event in the industry.
Many companies are watching.
I think it's an opportunity for Shangger.
No matter what the result is,
we should have a try.
Of course,
the inflated valuation mentioned by Mr. Mo
is also a problem.
Lawyer Fan,
why don't we try convertible bonds
as Mr. Mo said?
OK.
Xiaofang,
do as Mr. Luo said.
Connect with DDS again.
Youyou,
why are you here?
I'm coming to...
Do you come to return my suit?
Director Xu.
Please don't have any problems with the clothes
next time you shoot an advertisement.
Okay, I see.
Thank you, Mr. Mo.
Thank you
for helping Youyou.
Never mind.
It's just work.
Youyou,
my mom made pig's trotters soup for you.
It's in my car.
Let's take it.
Remember to drink it while it is hot.
Take a picture after drinking
to make her happy.
OK.
Tell your mom not to do it.
I'm afraid she's tired.
If you're afraid she's tired,
you'd better marry me earlier.
She'll be happy as long as she sees you.
Yunxi,
I need some time.
OK.
I know you need time.
I believe this day will come soon.
All right.
I have to go to work.
Go upstairs.
Be careful on the road.
Bye.
Director Xu,
why did you feel guilty just now?
Nothing.
I just don't want to make trouble.
I've helped you so much.
Don't you thank me?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Isn't it always
Director Xu's demand to keep secrets?
I hope you can pay attention to what you say.
Pay attention to what?
Pay attention to our relationship.
Fan Yunxi is my boyfriend.
So?
So I said
don't cause unnecessary trouble.
You think I'm a problem.
Yeah,
a big trouble.
Do you think
I'll bring you more trouble?
Fang Qi,
I wait for you to send Moments every day.
I saved all your photos
and drew this picture album for you.
I want to give it to you.
Why are you here?
What are you doing?
I'm preparing clothes for tomorrow's blind date.
I just take out the garbage. It's smelly.
Blind date?
Why do you want a blind date?
Don't you like someone?
Who says I love someone?
From my observation.
Don't you like someone in secret?
Unrequited love at such age?
I'm not eighteen.
If I like someone,
I will tell the world.
I'm afraid of being taken away by others.
What the hell is this?
I bought it by the side of the road.
Please help me to pick one.
Which looks better?
Neither looks good.
Come on. Bye.
Mr. Zhai.
Youyou,
Lawyer Fan
sued Lemi.
I don't know.
Maybe he wants to surprise you.
You have a good talk with him.
I can't afford to offend him.
Okay, I'll talk to him.
(Civil Procedure)
What's going on?
I want to help you.
They want to lay off employees improperly.
Then I'll put some pressure on them in my way.
Sue my company in my name.
Have you discussed this matter with me?
I said
I just put pressure on them.
I'm not really going to sue them.
I was going to tell you.
I forgot because I'm busy.
Are you angry?
Things have passed.
Drop the lawsuit as soon as possible.
What's wrong with you today?
I just think
you should discuss with me
before you do everything.
I didn't discuss with you before.
Are you still blaming me
for that?
I need some time to get used to it.
Then you adjust yourself as soon as possible.
I really don't hope our feelings
stand still.
Okay?
I have to go.
Look at these pictures.
So handsome.
He's so cool.
Is this a good shot?
Extremely perfect!
How about this one?
They all look good.
This one.
Right?
Do you think
I'll bring you more trouble?
I don't know how to choose.
I don't think so.
You don't think it's good.
Do we need to remake it?
Youyou.
Youyou,
are you asking too much?
This is quite nice.
The commercial film of Meeting Your Match
will be online soon.
Work hard to check all.
What about the live broadcast and filming?
Leave it to me.
Look at it again.
OK.
What's wrong with being so handsome?
It's nice. Very cool.
She's too strict. Yeah.
Mr. Mo, are you in the company?
I want to talk to you about something.
He thought I'd back down.
The subscriber you dialed is busy.
Please redial later.
All the information about
the impromptu meeting next Monday
should be sent to Mr. Mo's mailbox this Friday.
Have you sent it yet?
I forgot if you didn't remind me.
I'll get ready.
Director Xu,
why are you here?
What's the matter?
Can I eat you?
Where's Mr. Mo?
He is not here.
Not here?
Really?
I swear.
(Schedule)
It doesn't matter if he's not here.
I'm not looking for him anyway.
Don't look for him?
Yes.
I'm looking for Fang Qi.
Bring her something.
It was here just now.
Why can't I find it?
Give me a hand.
Hold it for me.
Quickly.
Where was it?
Where?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
(7AM-8AM: swimming)
Mr. Mo likes swimming.
We are in the investment business
and must have good physical strength.
We need to do sports.
OK.
Got it.
I'm leaving.
Director Xu,
what about your things for Fang Qi?
Mr. Mo.
Why are you here?
You're so strict with yourself
besides work.
We should learn from you.
You're not coming to talk to me about work, are you?
Every second counts.
Let's talk here.
You don't care about the popularity of advertising.
Why do you care about me?
You are the heat.
We saw the commercials
and did data analysis.
Between twenty-two and thirty-four seconds,
it reached the peak of data.
And these twelve seconds are the time when you appear.
Mr. Mo,
the data analysis of Meeting Your Match
has come out.
You are the favorite of netizens.
It is very important for Lemi.
I hope you can do us this favor.
Do a favor?
You're not afraid of trouble now.
That's my job.
Yeah.
This is your job.
What does it have to do with me?
Mr. Mo,
you can just say
how on earth can you help us.
Then I'd like to ask you.
What are you willing to do
to get my help?
Thank you.
I seem to hear this sentence often.
This is what I owe you.
I'll pay it back.
Xu Qingyou,
do you have to tell everything so clearly?
This is my principle.
What about the live broadcast?
Aren't you afraid to owe me more?
I...
Answer cautiously.
Your reply may decide whether I answer or not.
I know.
But I made a pledge.
This promotion
is really important to our team.
I don't want to affect my team
because our personal affairs.
I will definitely pay back the favor
in my own way.
It's impossible.
My observation is absolutely correct.
Do you know how sad I am to lose hope?
It's better to have no hope in the first place.
This is
worse than waiting in Paris
for four years.
I see.
Let's figure out how many years
you have had a crush on her.
One year, two years...
You have loved her for so many years
and haven't confessed.
She doesn't like me.
How to confess?
She doesn't like you.
Then you should try your best
to make her like you.
That's what it's like to chase girls.
Do you want to
watch her blind date succeed,
then have a wedding,
but the groom is not you?
What should I do now?
Destroy her blind date,
of course.
Miss Fang,
do you mind if I have a child?
I read your information just now.
You are also divorced.
But it doesn't matter.
I don't mind.
You see,
we have a common experience.
Then I'll go first.
Think about it.
Hello.
I'm in a hurry.
Let me get this straight.
You don't  need to do dishwashing
and cooking in my family.
Nanny can do these.
What I need now is someone
who can give birth to children.
Two children in three years.
It would be better if they were all boys.
I'll give you one of my two villas.
Think about it.
Mom, let me show you this girl.
I like this one very much.
I've been watching her for a long time, mom.
Come on.
This is my mother. Hello.
Hello. Can she cook?
I haven't asked yet.
Mom, I'll ask for you later.
I got it. I got it, mom.
I see.
You must know about her family background.
Wait a minute, mom.
You need to make it clear.
Hello,
here are my various certificates.
Have a look.
This...
I'm sorry about that.
This, this is...
What are you doing here?
I'm on a blind date.
What are you doing?
My sister called me here
because she was worried about you.
She's afraid you are fooled. Come on.
Fine.
You're so good.
Why do you come on a blind date?
Go away.
This one...
This is my brother.
Go quickly. It's not suitable for children.
Hello,
I'll introduce myself first.
I have six properties now.
Hello,
what's your name?
You don't have to worry about
the financial situation at all.
What do you do?
You just need to
enjoy life at home.
What's the difference
between this and the unemployed?
And then...
I think it's quite good.
Right?
And then
my mother cares more
about education.
Hello,
I'll introduce myself first.
I'm a Ph.D. student at Medical University.
It takes a long time to
learn this major.
So it delayed finding a lover.
I am a doctor she trained.
Like primary school level.
You are too disrespectful!
No.
Then
let's go out and have a chat.
OK.
This way.
Go.
It would be nice if you didn't mind I have children.
I like children.
This project is really wonderful.
I like this one.
This project was born for Mr. Mo.
Qingyou.
What are you looking at?
Our advertisement
can be put on tonight.
Qingyou,
why don't you invite Yunxi
to make a guest appearance?
He is very busy.
To tell the truth,
it's really good.
The first round of launch will start tonight.
Fighting.
Don't worry.
OK.
See you.
Bye, Mr. Zhai.
Qingyou,
I was going to
check the advertising with you
this evening.
But it suddenly occurred to me
that I had a classmate meeting.
So...
Well.
I see.
Thank you, Qingyou.
By the way,
here's a tip for you.
The viewing platform opposite
has a much clearer view than ours.
OK.
This restaurant is delicious.
Let's come again next time.
We'll eat it another day.
Don't invite me to your house?
I live alone.
We don't know each other very well yet.
Maybe next time.
You've been married to someone.
Is it necessary to pretend to be pure?
What are you talking about?
You really think of yourself as a little girl?
Are you crazy?
I will absolutely beat you!
Just leave the trash to me.
You...
Xu Wei.
Leave it alone.
I thought I met Mr. Right.
I didn't expect him to be a trash.
I'm almost thirty.
Why can't I meet a good person?
It doesn't matter.
You're so smart and beautiful.
You have a good job, high income,
and your own house.
You can buy bag for yourself.
Your value
is beyond your age.
Why do you care if you have a boyfriend?
What you just said
is absolutely right.
So
ever since I got divorced,
I never thought about getting married again.
But
Qu Kai is getting married.
Qu Kai,
your ex-husband?
He found a young and beautiful one.
Then I have to find one, too.
I have to find someone
who is more handsome, richer
and better to me than him.
So
this is why you...
Have one.
I just got pills and can't drink.
I finally got off work. I have an appointment today.
Qingyou,
I'm leaving first.
OK.
Bye.
Go back early.
Bye, Qingyou.
Go home early.
Bye.
Please check this data again.
Look here, let's compare it.
(Meet Your Match)
Why is the power out in the building opposite?
I heard that Director Xu is
checking the advertising.
Make a phone call and ask her.
OK.
Hello, Yunxi.
Are you off now?
Not yet.
What's wrong with you? Where are you?
I'm on the viewing platform opposite the company.
I'm checking the company's advertising.
Unexpectedly, there was a sudden power failure here.
Hello?
The subscriber you dialed is powered off.
Who is it?
Me.
Mr. Mo,
why are you here?
Check advertising.
If there's anything wrong with the ad,
I'm the one who lost.
It's power cut suddenly.
But the ad is OK.
Thank you.
What's wrong with your foot?
I just tweaked it.
Nothing.
I'm fine.
Don't move.
It doesn't matter.
Go back and put some ice on it.
It will be okay the next day.
Okay, I see.
What's going on?
I'm doing Power Point.
Why is the power out suddenly?
I'm really sorry.
We are repairing the circuit now.
It will be all right soon.
Hurry up!
I'm really sorry.
Hello, what's going on here?
Suddenly, the power went out.
The elevator didn't work either.
Where is the viewing platform?
The twentieth floor.
Thanks.
Never mind.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Hello.
The subscriber you dialed is powered off.
Please redial later.
Be careful.
It doesn't matter.
Go.
Mr. Mo,
stop here.
In short,
thank you today.
Is there anything else to say?
Come to me tomorrow
to check the live broadcast process.
Thank you.
Never mind.
Let's go.
Yunxi.
Youyou,
are you all right?
I heard there was a power failure and came right away.
But your phone has been disconnected.
The phone is dead.
It's all right now.
Mr. Mo,
why are you here?
Why can't I be here?