=Love at Night=
=Episode 22=
What's up?
Things about Taikang have changed.
I'm waiting for you at Shangger.
Be there in thirty minutes,
or this project will be lost.
OK, I'll come over now.
As soon as the waiter came up,
he changed his attitude.
I'm sorry.
There is something urgent in the company.
I have to go back.
Please take care of her.
I'll be back later.
There is something urgent.
I'll pick you up when I'm done.
Come on, eat more.
Qingyou, eat some noodles.
Come on, let's eat.
Let's keep eating.
Watch the news.
(Shangger invested in Taikang
and reached cooperation)
They leaked the news deliberately,
trying to use public opinion
to force me to sign the contract.
Be careful of asking for trouble.
It seems that besides you,
Taikang also has insiders in Shangger.
Let's see who is more patient.
In this case, the psychological tactics you prepared
are completely useless.
The reason for releasing such public opinion news
is to tell everyone,
if there is no conclusive evidence,
there is no way to turn around.
How about cooperating with me?
It's not that I want to cooperate with you,
but you want to cooperate with me.
Ruiying Technology, an affiliate of Taikang,
is your company with the largest investment share.
If something goes wrong with Taikang,
Ruiying Technology will definitely not be able to escape.
At that time,
I will resign at most,
but you will go bankrupt.
How many surprises does Mr. Mo have for me?
Sure I do.
Excuse me.
In theory,
the serial number of the last receipt before closing
minus the serial number of the first receipt
when opening
is the sales volume of the day.
Look here.
Here are internal actual sales data and receipts
on the 21st,
the serial numbers of two consecutive receipts
are disconnected.
The serial number of the previous receipt was 26,
but the next one jumps directly to 28.
In other words,
the statistical sales data is higher than
the actual sales data.
However, if they want to cheat by skipping bills,
there must be a cooperation
with the third-party stakeholders.
For example...
The Auditing Department.
That's why I was sure
they would show the cloven foot.
Because once they hear the news,
the audit will be anxious to cover up.
So now we have enough evidence
to suspend
Shangger's investment in Taikang.
Next, it can be regarded as a reason.
We can ask a third party to intervene
in the legal process
and investigate the audit problems.
I'll inform the third party to be ready to intervene.
I'll help you with it.
Are you full?
Mo hasn't come back yet.
Qingyou, let's take you home first.
Don't bother, I'll bring Lingze something to eat.
You two go first.
That's okay, bye, Sa.
Bye bye.
Bye.
Are you all right?
I'm OK.
Lingze has a sense of propriety. Let's go.
You know what,
I've known Lingze for a long time
but I haven't seen him fall in love with any woman,
except for you.
He's the kind of person
who won't change easily once he's determined.
I see.
It's done. I'll print it.
You can go now.
Hard work.
Lingze.
What's wrong with you?
Asthma?
Where's the medicine?
I don't have any medicine.
I'll get some.
Lingze.
It's too slow to untie the buttons one by one.
This is more direct.
I thought
you would have some clever means.
Unexpectedly, that's all.
Showing weakness to redeem the relationship.
If you want to make me angry,
you made it, congratulations.
But it's still far from redeeming his heart
by these means.
The stage is for you. Go on acting alone.
Are you staying here for the night?
Fire away. I'll speak without reserve.
When were you together?
If I remember the anniversary with my ex
so clearly,
someone will be unhappy.
Definitely not me.
When did you break up?
Eight years ago.
Who mentioned it?
She left without saying goodbye.
She appears again now.
Is there mood swing in your heart?
Yeah, there was.
Well,
you're so unsure of yourself.
Don't change the topic.
I just appreciate her working ability.
Aren't you curious about the details?
What details do I have to be curious about?
That would make me unhappy.
What I care about is that
you won't be connected with her now and in the future.
Of course.
If we break up in the future,
no matter who you contact,
it will have nothing to do with me.
Xu Qingyou, you thought about breaking up?
What if you have an affair?
Don't worry. You're attractive enough.
I won't be interested in others.
What if
I fall in love with others in the future?
Xu Qingyou, are you crazy today?
Anyway,
I won't leave you without saying goodbye in the future.
Of course, I won't have an affair.
Good night, Mr. Mo.
Go to bed early.
Xu Wei, this is your first formal date
in 22 years.
Don't be cowardly.
Xu Wei.
Fang Qi.
Come on, carry it please.
Let's go.
Why not have some popcorn first?
No, I haven't finished
reading the financial statements yet.
Hurry up.
Thanks.
Fang Qi,
this is our first date since we were together.
It's precious.
I know you are busy with your work.
But you promised me yesterday, didn't you?
Just give me two hours.
Can we concentrate on dating?
Date costs money, but work can make money.
Which is more important?
Work.
How about
going skiing and enjoying a hot spring this weekend?
I really can't.
Many projects have not been finished yet.
It's not the time to relax.
Help me put it in.
Xu Wei, others are intermittently crazy.
You are intermittently timid.
How do you feel, my boyfriend? Are you happy?
Youth is good.
Am I really that good?
You're silly and easy to cheat.
Let's go.
Look!
Fang Qi, this movie is too scary.
Since you're afraid,
why do you watch horror movies?
I knew this is our first date.
Gu Dayan said
horror movies
help promote the relationship between couples.
Did you see that?
Watching horror movies
to promote the relationship between couples
is only applicable to girls under 25 years old.
Then what scares you?
I think no money is the scariest.
Except for this.
It's especially scary that slides are not saved.
Give it to me.
Give me.
You...
Since we're watching horror movies,
I need to give you a little scary atmosphere.
Xu Qingyou and I are really poor sisters.
We fall in love with
a Poker Face and a naive fool respectively.
My sister is in love, right?
With whom?
The...the popcorn is delicious.
Who?
Eat it.
This is horrible.
I feel so horrible, too.
Hello, a glass of whiskey.
As usual, no ice.
Sa.
It's too little, isn't it?
Add more.
You made that call just now, right?
I thought things are gonna change as long as he came.
And then?
He's gone
with her.
Give up.
Never mind.
They are like
eggs and stones.
They are clearly not the same kind of people,
but they have to get together.
They will fall apart
without my external force.
What about after falling apart?
Can you accept
Mo Lingze
when he loved other women?
But I loved someone else, too.
I've hurt him before.
So now I'll treat this
as a little revenge on me.
It's fair. I can accept it.
You are still so self-righteous.
Am I?
Don't you have a drink with me?
I will keep my promise
about Taikang.
You have three days to prepare to quit.
Shangger
will delay the contract over legal issues
to avoid leaks.
I don't want these.
When Mr. Luo came to me,
he asked me to make a request.
I didn't ask for a penny.
I just asked for this access card.
Do you know why?
Because no matter who I want to approach,
the initiative must be in my own hands.
What's up?
Qi,
that woman came again.
Why has she been pestering Mr. Mo?
You,
go in and ask the boss
how to solve the problem of Taikang.
They are obviously in conference now.
It's not appropriate for me to go in now.
You just go in and ask.
Is it completely solved?
Does he need our help?
Isn't that more important than
the two of them staying in a room?
(Lin Siyu)
Qi,
I still have something else to do.
I'll leave first.
Do you have a minute?
Go shopping with me at noon.
Hey, what's the matter?
Are you available tomorrow?
Tomorrow,
I should go to work normally.
You take a leave
and go somewhere with me.
I have something important to tell you.
OK.
Ms. Tang,
where you want to go is your freedom.
But I kindly remind you
choosing the wrong target
is likely to lead to a dead end
and wasting effort.
You think you know me well, don't you?
I admit that
I agree with consequentialism.
If I find that the front is a dead end,
I won't waste a bit of effort.
And before the age of thirty,
I think there were only two ways to choose,
either right or wrong.
And I must be the one
who always chooses the right way.
But I have experienced a lot
over the years.
I gradually understood a truth.
In fact, right and wrong are not important,
what you want in your heart
is the most important.
Ms. Tang,
don't put things
in wrong place,
especially things that don't belong to you.
Do you have to treat me like an enemy?
As long as we are in a pure working relationship,
we won't be enemies.
If you insist on crossing the boundary,
then I have to obey my rules.
I gave you the confidential data,
because you are Mo Lingze.
But if
the person standing in front of me is a stranger,
everything will be different.
I thought
I had the biggest crisis
of my career.
I didn't expect Poker Face to solve it for me.
He hasn't blamed Wang Ji and me.
Are you still upset?
No, I'm happy.
That's why I asked you to come out for a big meal
to celebrate it.
But,
but...
this green dress is so beautiful.
(*Green sometimes means being cheated）
It suits you a little.
Isn't this color too tender?
Not for me.
This pair of shoes.
These two match well.
Great!
Fang Qi,
take it.
I wonder
why is this hat not green?
I didn't notice it.
I...
just want to give you something.
Pay more hearts to it, please.
Thank you.
What do you mean?
Tang Xi came to Shangger, right?
You know her?
Of course I know.
I've dealt with her before.
Are you bullied?
I won completely.
Is it true or not?
Of course it's true.
She is the queen of our investment industry.
She is cold-blooded.
How can you win her?
So you want to come out
to buy clothes during your lunch break.
Then prevail over your rival in love.
I bought this for Tang Xi.
I tore her shirt.
What?
You're so tough now.
Did you learn it from Poker Face?
Forget it.
I have to remind you that
boys will never forget
their first crush.
So you have to be vigilant if there is any trouble.
Stop it at the beginning.
Do you read too many romance novels?
As soon as first crush appeared, the world is turbulent.
Never mind.
And I believe Mo Lingze.
If you love someone, don't doubt him.
What you just said
is the same as what Xu Wei said.
You two are absolutely...
Why did you suddenly mention Xu Wei?
You two?
What's wrong with us?
It's unacceptable,
unimaginable.
Tang Xi has sent a message.
Take a look.
(See you in the archery range at 7PM)
Miss Xu, I'm sorry.
I can only ask you here.
Because my training time is fixed.
No problem.
Miss Tang,
I broke your clothes last time.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
But clothing is like armor.
People will judge you by what you wear.
I only wear my own clothes.
Is it?
But the things sent out
are old things.
If Miss Tang doesn't like it,
just throw it away.
Miss Xu, you surprised me a lot.
It's better to be open and honest.
I asked you here this time
because I wanted to talk something with you.
Go ahead, please.
If ten is a perfect mark,
you're beautiful.
Appearance scores 8.1 points.
IQ,
five points.
EQ is 4.5 points.
As for your means,
three points.
On average,
you haven't passed yet.
I just want to know
why Mo Lingze fell in love with
a woman like you?
It seems that Miss Tang's opinions on women
are not so objective.
You judge the situation and weigh the pros and cons.
What is the result?
What you have gained and what you have lost,
you know better than me.
Excuse me, your coffee.
Thank you.
Delicious.
Miss Xu has good taste.
The beans in this café are baked very well.
The taste is particularly delicate.
When I brought Lingze here for the first time,
he loved it.
I said this cup of coffee is delicious.
It has nothing to do
with you and Mo Lingze.
I won't say it tastes bad
because it is recommended by you.
Because I never
lie to myself.
The reason is pretty good,
but does Miss Xu really not mind at all?
Do you know
why Lingze always wears black suits?
Because I chose this color for him,
which suits him best.
Lingze was created by me.
Is my aesthetic good?
It's really great.
But since he is with me,
he will have his own appearance.
What I love is the real him,
not the formula that has been worked out.
The real him,
do you know the real him?
Do you know why Lingze
never believes in long-term relationships?
Miss Xu,
why not wait for me to win him back?
Miss Tang,
if you can handle Mo Lingze,
why bother to tell me this?
The result is already clear.
I still have something else. I'll go first.
Thank you for the coffee.
Why are you out?
I made an upgraded caramel cake,
waiting for you outside.
I'll try it.
Why did you change your suit?
You didn't wear this in the morning.
Do you remember so clearly what I wear every day?
Of course.
I remember what you wear every day.
Reward a bite.
Wait a minute.
You answer me first.
Why did you change your clothes?
I went shopping with your sister.
Then why don't you take me when you go shopping?
Why should I take you?
Will you pay me the bill?
Do you have money?
I do.
My money is in Gu Dayan's pocket.
He hasn't given it to me yet.
I'm joking with you.
We talked about adults' things.
It's not adults' business.
It's girls' topic.
Gossip about rival in love.
You can't understand.
Rival in love?
Who?
It has nothing to do with me.
Then it has something to do with my sister.
Who is the rival?
Can you let me have a bite first?
You can talk while eating.
It's a long story.
Take a bite and tell me.
Hang it up. Don't drop it.
All right, let's go.
(We wish each other a long life
to share the beauty in life, even miles apart)
You look so formal today.
You also wear perfume, right?
Do you want to attract attention?
I'm trying to
prevent mosquitoes.
Although it's a little artificial,
it's okay
as a farewell ceremony.
Farewell ceremony?
Since I have given up Mo Lingze,
our cooperation is coming to an end.
So it's over?
You still want me to hold on, right?
You really want me to be a mistress, don't you?
No.
How could I make you a mistress?
So from today,
Wang Ji and Lin Siyu's love-chasing alliance
has officially ended.
But I believe that
you, as an excellent Party B,
will definitely fulfill Party A's last requirement
before the contract expires.
What requirements?
Come with me.
Miss Lin,
why do you want to play this?
Are you scared to walk so slowly?
I just want to try your courage.
I walked behind you to protect you.
Really?
If you're not afraid, just take two steps forward.
Don't hold on to it.
You leave it first.
Why should I leave it first?
You're a man, so you leave it first.
What does this have to do with men?
You...
It seems that I have to take measures
to exercise you.
Wang Ji.
What's the matter?
I have a stomachache.
I seem to have appendicitis.
Let's go to the hospital.
Go.
Are you looking for your sister?
For you.