=Love at Night=
=Episode 24=
(Tang Xi)
Hello, Lingze.
I know you're still awake.
This trip is an overnight stay,
so remember to pack a change of clothes.
I am on the coffee beans.
I know your preference.
Okay, Ms. Tang.
I'll pack for him.
Miss Xu.
Could you please tell Lingze
that this business trip has been brought forward?
We're going to leave at this weekend.
Mr. Mo.
Why didn't I hear
that you are going on a business trip
with Ms. Tang?
I planned to
tell you tonight.
I promise
it is just a business trip.
Of course,
if you mind,
I won't go.
Go.
Why not?
Or I will be regarded as less sensible.
You must go.
Okay.
Here's to our sensible Director Xu.
Here's to Mr. Mo for keeping his nose clean.
We are the warriors of the office.
We've gone through lots of difficulties
to get the position.
We can't quit!
Work gives me
the strength to face difficulties in life.
Sorry.
That's all right.
Here.
Take it easy, lady.
Thanks.
It's so hard for the young nowadays.
Working overtime so late.
Some are working hard for a better life,
while some achieve nothing.
Why do you hurt my soul in this beautiful morning?
Are we still brothers?
There are at least 1,000 months in a person's life.
Fang Qi persisted in her fight
for the first 120 months.
On the contrary,
for the past 240 months,
I have achieved nothing.
Do you feel ill?
Fang Qi has overcome countless such breakdowns
to persevere until now.
What breakdowns?
What are you talking about?
Now that I have achieved nothing,
I am not good enough for Fang Qi
who is working hard.
Where are you going?
I'm going to make my name.
No way.
I want to take part in
this year's Pompidou Youth Art Exhibition,
so I'm looking for Mr. Peter Huang.
Mr. Huang is not here. Please come back.
Who hung this painting there?
The style is not matching!
It's horrible.
Anyone,
take this painting away!
Okay!
Mr. Huang.
Hello.
I'm Xu Wei.
We met before
at the Pompidou Masters of Modern Art Exhibition.
Who are you?
Get this painting out of here.
Okay.
Mr. Huang.
I admire you.
I have a collection of your curated works,
especially the one in 2017
called The Unity of Contradiction and Confrontation.
I graduated from
Ecole Nationale Superieure des Beaux-Arts.
I know
that you are dedicated to
discovering young artists at home.
Please have a look at my works.
I want to participate in
this year's Pompidou Youth Art Exhibition.
Young man,
why should I choose you?
I graduated with top honours.
I won three gold prizes in the school art exhibition.
I know
I'm not good enough now.
But I'll prove myself.
You said
art is for all ages,
for all who are willing to work hard.
There was a premise to this quote
that was cut out of the media.
The premise is "in the world of genius".
I can prove myself.
If I could change the painting
that you were not satisfied with,
could you recommend me to the exhibition?
Young man,
if you could do that,
I would recommend you to the exhibition.
Thank you, Mr. Huang.
Mo Lingze.
Hey, hold it!
I'm not here for you.
Where's Wang Ji?
He's back to his home town.
Where?
Yuanji.
Darn, Wang Ji went home without saying a word.
What are you doing?
You've disappeared for two days.
I have some special things to do.
But I can't tell you now.
Did you hit someone on a skateboard
and have to escape?
It's impossible.
Tell me the truth.
I won't give in.
You won't?
Give in or not?
It hurts.
What's wrong?
I haven't even made the effort yet.
You're trying to kill me.
I am now nominally your boyfriend,
but in reality I am your mobile sandbag.
Some even don't have the opportunity
to be my sandbag.
Anyway,
it's okay that you want to be disconnected.
But you come and tell me in advance.
Are you looking for this?
I think
I'm getting to know you better now,
so I want to be a better man.
That's why you disappear?
Just two days.
Two days later,
I'll tell you everything.
What's wrong with you?
By the way,
there's food in the fridge for the next two days.
Remember to eat it on time.
And you'll see me when you're done.
Who cares about your food?
How dare Xu Wei
play the disappearing game with me?
As his sister,
you should give me an explanation.
What?
What's wrong with you?
Forget your sister after having boyfriend?
I'm going to leave.
Let Mo Lingze play in mud with you.
No, no, no.
My...
Mo Lingze, he's away on business.
I was going
to do something nice for his birthday,
but all my plans went down the drain.
Right.
I heard from Wang Ji
that he went with Tang Xi.
So what?
It sounds like you are happy to hear that.
No.
I just want to ask you
are you worried?
No, I'm not.
We have made some rules.
First, no physical contact.
Second, no alone time.
Third, no recollections of the past.
How can you say you're not worried
under such strict rules?
I am busy!
I have a birthday present to prepare.
Are you kidding me?
You get him a cup for his birthday?
("Cup" and "tragedy" are homophone in Chinese.)
A cup means
we'll be together forever.
("Cup" and "forever" are homophone in Chinese.)
Don't talk nonsense if you don't understand.
In my opinion, don't prepare any gifts.
Just show up
in front of him
and tell him,
"Honey,
I'm your gift,
enjoy."
I'm not interested in that.
It's just a birthday.
It's okay not to be together.
Why are you so unromantic?
Only you are romantic.
So bad you are.
Hello?
I'm in the Maldives.
The sound?
It's the yacht.
I'm going to go diving.
I'd better hang up now.
Talk to you later.
Bye.
This is as far as I can take you,
you walk the rest of the way yourself.
Okay, thanks.
Go now.
The peanuts grow well this year.
Yeah.
(Yuanji Village)
The peanuts in my field grow well either.
There's a good harvest this year.
(Moments of Wang Ji)
Yeah.
Look.
Have a look.
This one's getting a nice tan, too.
Hello uncle.
Could you tell me
does Wang Ji live around here?
He's in that alley right there.
You can come in this way.
Okay. Thanks.
You're welcome.
Wang Ji.
Don't leave.
How could you do this?
Come here without a word.
I ran out of my fuel tank.
And my shoes are broken to find you.
Our contract was over.
Who told you that?
Last time...
I'm here
in the spirit of contract
to say goodbye to you.
Is this the attitude
you want to take towards your first party?
What do you want?
Help me.
In fact, I come to you
to invite you to start a business with me.
Our contract was over.
I want to sign a new contract with you.
No, thanks.
It's a precious opportunity.
Are you sure you want to reject me?
I'm good in Shangger.
Wang Ji.
To see you,
I've driven 547 miles
and walked for over three hours.
And my shoes were broken.
Now, you're going to reject me.
Your shoes are costly, right?
It's just a pair of shoes.
I'll throw it away when I get back.
Look at mine.
What do you mean, Wang Ji?
I don't care about these things.
We live in different worlds.
Don't come to me again.
What do you mean?
Come back.
Living in different worlds is okay.
I don't care.
Lingze.
Chen Ziming's greatest taboo
is the relationship with his mother.
So, it's not easy to persuade him
to help us with the Hua Group event.
I'll try my best to support you later.
Thank you, Ms. Tang.
It's been a long time
since we've worked side by side like this.
The Flat White here still tastes the same.
I still remember...
Sorry, I need to answer this.
What's up? Somebody misses me?
Who misses my boyfriend?
I'll beat her.
How's your work?
Is everything going well?
Not bad.
I just feel a little bored
without Director Xu.
I just want to finish my work quickly,
and get back to stay with my girlfriend.
Since you're so eager to return,
work hard
and finish early
so you can see your girlfriend.
When I get back,
I'll have dinner with my girl.
Bye.
Have calls with your girlfriend
during work hours.
Mr. Mo, you never did personal business
during work hours before.
Ms. Tang, you never
judged others' affairs before.
Mr. Chen.
Ms. Tang.
Long time no see.
You've changed a lot.
You're prettier.
This is
your...
This is Mr. Mo, Mo Lingze of Shangger Capital.
Mr. Chen.
Fengtang Capital and Shangger Capital are partners.
So, Ms. Tang and I
are partners, either.
Of course.
Let's walk and talk.
Please.
I've heard a lot about Mr. Mo.
I'm expected to cooperate with you.
Thank you, Mr. Chen.
Shangger is expected to cooperate with you, either.
Right, Mr. Chen.
Excuse me.
I'm going to leave for a while.
My girlfriend is here.
You are here to check up on me?
You have an overactive imagination, Mr. Mo.
I'm just here on a company assignment
and happened to meet you.
That's quite a pity.
I was going to have dinner with Director Xu
when work was over.
I'd consider
having dinner with you
if I finished work early.
Okay.
Mr. Mo.
Mr. Chen has a tight schedule.
Let's get down to business first.
Okay.
Come back early.
Wait for me.
Mr. Chen.
Miss Xu.
Kindly remind
surprises can easily turn into scares.
Mr. Mo.
Bell Company has nothing to do with Hua Group.
If Bell Company and Hua Group are really not related,
then why does Bell shift 20%
of its annual profits to Hua Group?
How do you know that?
Bell Company and Hua Group are
in fact a parent-subsidiary relationship.
They wax and wane simultaneously.
The reason why Ms. Hua
refused to sign off on the M&A
was she felt that Bell Company is your effort.
But Hua Group is her effort, either.
If you continue to do so,
sooner or later, Hua Group will
have to do a bankruptcy filing.
Mr. Chen.
If you can persuade Ms. Hua to sign,
Shangger
will be able to save both companies.
I believe
it's also what you expect.
I can help,
but you two have set me up for a trap today,
so shouldn't you apologize to me?
Mr. Chen.
At your disposal.
I've heard that Ms. Tang is good at fencing.
I'd like to take this opportunity
to have a good sword fight with you.
Mr. Chen.
How about having a sparring with me?
What?
Mr. Mo, are you trying to
take advantage of the situation
and take me down in swordplay as well?
Mr. Chen.
Don't mind him.
Come on.
Look.
Ms. Tang can't wait
to spar with me.
I can't wait to cooperate with you.
Okay.
Ms. Tang, I lost to you,
this time,
I must win.
Ms. Tang.
Please.
-Hello.
I've heard that customers can choose their own songs
for birthday party, right?
Yes.
You can tell us what you want to sing
and we'll arrange for the band to rehearse.
You will be able to sing live in the evening.
By the way,
could I rehearse with the band in advance?
Of course. This way, please.
Thanks.
Ms. Tang.
You're not sincere enough.
Solicit business for Mr. Mo.
You should make all your efforts.
Okay, as you wish.
Right.
Come on.
Tang Xi.
Ms. Tang.
What's wrong?
Where's your medicine?
I ask somebody for a favor.
Okay.
Tomorrow's meeting is rescheduled for the morning.
Remember to send me the plan in advance.
Ms. Xu, hello.
Our band has waited for a long time.
Do you...
I'm sorry.
Just give me a minute, please.
It's an important person.
I understand.
Please wait for a while.
Sorry.
Thanks.
It's me who should say thanks.
Thank you for everything you did for Shangger.
You know what I did was not for Shangger,
it's for you.
I need thanks from you.
It's not from Mr. Mo.
It's from Mo Lingze.
Tang Xi.
You don't have to do this.
Do you remember
the winter of my first year in the business?
We went to meet a client together
and I had a sudden asthma attack.
You were the same back then as you are now.
It was you who took me to the hospital.
And then you stayed by my side
as you do now.
Take your medication with you.
Not every time you will have someone by your side.
Stay with me tonight,
can you?
Lingze.
Excuse me, Ms. Xu.
It's very late now.
Do we have to wait any longer?
Just a moment, please.
He will definitely come.
Then how should we deal with the cost?
About the cost,
I'll pay by the hour.
Thanks.
I'm so sorry.
Please wait for a while.
Thank you very much.
No problem.
Qingyou.
Sorry.
I'm late.
You must be getting impatient.
No, I'm not.
I was just about to leave.
Just now Tang Xi was admitted to hospital
with an asthma attack.
I left in a hurry
and didn't check my phone.
I came to see you as soon as I saw your message.
Will she be okay in the hospital alone?
She has someone to accompany her.
Don't worry.
Instead, it was my girl,
who was alone and sulking.
I must hurry back to be with her.
It's not
too late for you to come.
A present for you.
Come on.
Do I make a progress?
My little fairy
must sing flawlessly!
Thank you.
Happy birthday, Lingze.
Happy birthday to you.
Qingyou.
I feel tired.
I want to go back and have a rest.
What's the matter?
Leave me alone.
Miss Xu.
Kindly remind
surprises can easily turn into scares.
Tomorrow is your birthday.
What kind of gift do you want?
I want you and Mum
to come to my piano competition tomorrow.
Hello.
Qingyou.
Where are you?
I'm at your door.
Mr. Zhai called me
and said there's a meeting tomorrow.
So, I have to go.
Okay.
Where are you?
I'll take you back.
No, thanks.
I'm already in a taxi.
Okay.
Then wait for me to complete the current business.
I will definitely give you an explanation
when I return tomorrow.