=Love at Night=
=Episode 1=
Hello.
This is hotel reception.
Mr. Mo has booked
a wake-up call for you at eight o'clock.
Mr. Mo?
( One day ago)
I am Xu Qingyou,
the Director of the Operation Department Ⅰ of Lemi.
I'm going to be 30.
It is said that
time will put an invisible shackle
on 30-year-old women.
It makes them obsessed with keeping young forever.
It makes them careful about every choice.
What should a 30-year-old woman look like?
My answer is...
Any look that satisfies yourself.
(Fan Yunxi)
What's the matter?
Why did you call me so early?
You started to work so early.
Since you work so hard,
why don't we hold the wedding in advance?
You can quit your job and be Mrs. Fan.
And I don't have to stay in the hotel anymore.
You are the breadwinner
and bear a heavy burden.
I earn my own living to share the responsibility for you.
Isn't it wonderful?
At the mention of quit, you will change the subject.
Isn't it women's dream to enjoy the fruits of others
without having toiled?
No.
That's men's erroneous assumption.
( Long Jin, Dept II)
Hello.
Xu Qingyou.
The external advertising
is clearly the responsibility of the Department Ⅱ.
Why was the plan of the Department Ⅰ chosen?
Because the exposure of your channel is low
but the cost is too high.
Who approved it?
Who made you to do these
messy gimmicks?
Let's talk about it in the company.
See you later.
( Wang Ji calling）
Hello, Mr. Mo.
Our project
was robbed by Zhao Lei
of Golden Sun Capital,
your former employer.
He is going to Jia Weisi
with the investment agreement now.
Don't worry. He can't do it.
To meet at the location.
Mr. Mo.
We searched the whole street for Jia Weisi,
but failed.
He is a genius coder.
But, in life, he is a super otaku.
He has breakfast in this street
at 8:30 every day.
I confirmed it.
Hello, Mr. Zhai.
Qingyou, you asked the Technical Department
to temporarily change the plan into
your plan today, right?
Do you know
-the people in the Department Ⅱ...  -Hello, Mr. Zhai?
I seem to be in a bad reception area.
Hello? Can you hear me?
Hello?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Did I just step on your foot?
No.
-I'm sorry.  -Jia Weisi.
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
Let me deal with it for you.
That's okay.
So let me buy a new one for you.
Give me your Wechat  number.
Drama queen.
It's too old-fashioned.
I'm sorry.
(Cards)
Enjoy yourself.
Thank you.
Guys,
I only
care about one thing now.
Which of you can
give me the investment funds first?
Do you know what situation it is now?
It's capital winter.
For startups like ours,
every minute is very important to us.
You are right.
Have a look, Mr. Jia.
This is the investment agreement
of Golden Sun Capital.
There is absolutely no imparity clause in it.
As long as you stamp it,
we can complete the whole process soon.
Sign the agreement without due diligence?
Are you sure the investment can be paid?
Of course.
It only takes one month,
one and a half months at most,
and the funds will definitely arrive.
Your products are highly homogeneous
and over-reliant on
a single third-party distribution and payment channel.
You have no awareness of risk diversification at all.
How can I give you
my investment with confidence?
Umm...
Wang Ji.
( Project Cooperation Plan)
Just a piece of paper?
Mr. Mo, I have to say that
you are fooling him.
I think you misdirected your energies.
Just come to the point.
There is no need for nonsense.
This plan contains everything you need.
It is enough to represent
the sincerity of Shangger Capital.
Mr. Mo.
You are not what you used to be.
You think you can be a partner
because Mr. Lin's daughter likes you?
What I didn't expect is that
you still make a living in a small company.
You are overqualified for this job.
I am not interested in
being a partner,
but interested in leading Shangger to surpass Gold Sun
to become the best investment company of TMT track
in the shortest time.
Mr. Zhao.
Don't be too nervous.
You...
Mr. Jia.
Take your time to read the plan.
You can contact me at any time.
See you later.
OK.
Mr. Jia.
This is...
Your favorite cartoon.
Mr. Mo specially asked the author to sign for you.
He said you'd like it.
Please thank Mr. Mo for me.
I like it very much.
Ninety percent of accounts
receivable in the current period.
Seventy percent of prepayments.
Director Long.
As long as we finish one more order,
our performance in this quarter
will definitely surpass that of the Department Ⅰ.
Good job.
Director Long.
We have a meeting in the meeting room at ten.
How much longer do you need?
It will take a while.
And,
for your performance this month,
it won't take long for you to meet.
Xia Meng,
Director Xu
seems to be resigning as a lawyer's wife soon.
She's going to enjoy herself.
Why don't you follow me
and do chores for me?
That's a good idea.
You...
Just  keep daydreaming.
Don't laugh out loud.
Or your face will hurt.
As for advertising,
it is because your department's plan
failed the online test,
while ours passed.
What's the matter?
Are you so eager to pass the buck?
I'll revise the plan if it fails.
It's none of your business.
The plans of the DepartmentⅠand the Department Ⅱ
have been given to the Technical Department.
The Technical Department said that
whoever passes the online test
will be adopted.
Any problem?
Right.
It was decided at the previous meeting.
There is a recording of the meeting.
We can replay it to confirm.
So the misunderstanding between us is caused by
the untimely transmission of information.
Director Long.
You are really good at shirking responsibility.
Remind you that
we will have a meeting in the meeting room at ten.
Please hurry up.
By the way.
Garbage should be classified.
Thank you.
Take some time to get this done.
Our employer, Shangger,
has a new vice president.
He has been in the investment field for nearly ten years,
with keen insight and market control.
I heard that he will be responsible for
Lemi's round C financing.
I wonder if he is handsome.
Do you know what his character is?
Strict? Gentle?
A bossy president or a warm man?
Both are fine.
None of your business.
Let's worry about our performance first.
Let's get to work.
Qingyou,
Long Jin
is getting more and more arrogant.
He took it for granted
that he was the general manager.
Doesn't he know that you may also become general manager?
That pisses me off!
Don't be angry.
Qingyou.
They all said you were going to quit your job
and be a rich lady.
Really?
I will be a rich lady,
and I will continue to work.
I'm greedy.
I know you hate to part with me.
That's it.
-OK.  -All right.
( Fake cosmetics of Lemi)
Qingyou, something terrible happens.
What's the matter?
There are fake cosmetics of Lemi.
Weibo published dozens of
online famous cosmetics inspection reports of Lemi.
After inspection, they are fakes.
(They are so malicious)
Look.
(This kind of websites should be banned)
I bought cosmetics in Lemi for two years.
(I even recommended it to friends)
Today's news said there were fakes in it.
(Yes,)
You know,
(I regretted buying lots of cosmetics on it)
something happened to Lemi.
Don't reply.
Before the official announcement,
no one is allowed to disclose any negative information
about the company to the media.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
Hurry up to get this straightened out.
Hurry up.
Mr. Zhai.
As we approach the mid-year sale,
rumors of fakes are sure to
affect sales by generating negative emotion.
At this critical time,
it must have been done by our competitors.
Beauty makeup has always been handled
by our department.
I will contact the whistleblower soon
to solve the crisis of public opinion.
Shangger just changed the vice president
in charge of us.
At this critical time,
nothing can go wrong again.
I see.
Xu Qingyou, look.
Let me tell you that
Fan Yunxi is a playboy.
(Calling Honey)
(Honey calling)
Hello.
Let's have dinner together in the evening.
I booked the couple restaurant
you always wanted to go to.
Youyou?
OK, see you tonight.
Dong Bao.
Contact the whistleblower.
Then try to communicate with him.
OK.
Xia Meng.
Verify the purchase records.
Yu Ming.
Prepare a lawyer's letter.
OK.
Xiaopang.
Contact the brand department
to prepare PR.
OK.
Youyou.
Why don't we hold the wedding in advance?
You can quit your job and be Mrs. Fan.
Youyou.
I don't make excuses for myself.
Although I drank too much that day
and couldn't remember anything,
I was really wrong.
Youyou.
My heart only belongs to you.
I will give you a happy life.
Trust me.
You cheated on me three months before marriage.
Trust you?
Look.
I saw it.
That woman is great.
Let me have a look.
Hello.
Director Xu.
I have submitted the company's delivery plan
for next month to the Technical Department
and copied it to Mr. Zhai.
Please give me a break.
Lady, con...
The company is in such a big crisis.
You still have a party?
You don't care
because you are going to marry a rich man, right?
I'll open a bottle of champagne
to wish your Department II
to be back in the saddle.
Xu Qing...
What's the matter?
Miss,
you
broke the record
of our bar since it opened.
You are the God of War.
Really?
Do I look like Athena?
You're Athena.
Let me tell you,
there is a rule in our bar.
The record-breaker has the right
to make a request
to the previous record holder.
You
broke Mo's record.
He's here, a handsome guy.
The new God of War. Your record was broken.
You're weak now.
Sorry.
You can make a request.
Anything is OK.
Miss, we're closing.
Please settle the account first.
OK, just a moment.
Miss,
can I call your honey
and ask him
to pick you up?
No, you can't.
Umm...
You threw it.
It has nothing to do with me.
It's okay.
It's okay if it is broken.
Mo...
It's okay. Leave it to me.
Thank you, Mo.
You're number two.
Miss,
please behave yourself.
Where's my lip print?
You bosses like to find something to carp about.
Don't worry.
Let me get you another one.
Perfect.
A perfect new lip print.
A new lip print.
Ouch.
Don't forget that
I have the right to ask you
to do anything.
Right?
Don't look at me.
I can't help you.
The rule of the bar is that bet is bet.
Bet is bet.
Tonight, obey my order.
Where do you live?
Let me take you back.
Why do you ask this?
If you don't tell me,
I'll have to hand you over to the police.
Well.
Let me tell you a secret.
I, Xu Qingyou,
learned today that the perfect boyfriend
I've loved
for ten years
cheated on me.
I used to think
I wouldn't lose
what I had.
But now I realize that
actually people
are not so lucky.
Right?
Miss Xu.
I don't care about your relationship status.
At this moment,
all I care about is your personal safety.
Let's flip a coin.
If it's face up, I'll take you home.
If it's upside down, I'll hand you over to the police.
Upside down.
Hand you over to the police.
Face up.
The side with numbers is the front.
The patterned side is the reverse one.
This is common sense.
I don't understand.
I don't wanna go home.
It's a deal.
Take your time.
Hello, Director Xu.
Morning.
Good morning, Director Xu.
Director Xu.
Morning.
Qingyou.
There is feedback from after-sales service.
They said that the invoice and authorization code
provided by the whistleblower had confirmed that
his purchase record was true.
Contact the whistleblower
to see what he wants.
Be safe when negotiating.
Let me know as soon as something bad happens.
OK.
Go for it.
( Youyou, please listen to my explanation.
I really love you)
I need to break my bad habits.
Princess Xu.
Your takeout is here.
You had a showdown with Fan Yunxi?
You broke up?
You were persuaded by Fan Yunxi's
superb negotiation skills again?
No.
I just need a little time
to let me leave him firmly.
Xu Qingyou.
If a man betrays you once,
he will betray you countless times.
As long as he makes one mistake,
he will keep making mistakes.
He'll be addicted to
betraying you.
If they hadn't posted
photos of the party in the WeChat group,
I wouldn't have
happened to see it.
Hello, Meng.
Hello, Qingyou.
The whistleblower said that he had to
meet with the leader.
I really can't communicate with him.
I really can't help it.
Wait for me.
Sorry, I really need to go now.
Don't you eat?
No.
Enjoy yourself.
Are you all right?
Is this your condition?
Delete the video.
Apologize publicly.
Why should I listen to you?
You have 16 Weibo accounts.
Since 2015,
you have been using
these 16 seemingly unrelated accounts
to do one thing
that is to disclose the products of various enterprises
and ask them for compensation.
In these years,
you disclosed the news about nearly 20 companies.
If I'm not wrong,
you rely exclusively on
blackmail for profit, right?
They are willing to pay compensation,
which shows that they have a guilty conscience.
I'm enforcing justice on behalf of Heaven.
It's not shameful.
Really?
It seems that you have chosen the wrong company.
Lemi has a clear conscience.
I have recorded
all of our conversations.
When the time comes, I'll hand it over to the court along with the evidence.
Regarding the issue of fake products,
Lemi is willing to accept all investigations.
You must follow the news
to monitor us
if you go to jail.
You...
This coffee tastes good.
Don't waste it.
Meng, let's go.
OK.
Take your time.
Mr. Zhai,
I believe he will accept my terms
to clear Lemi's name.
The new vice president of Shangger is very strict
and pays close attention to this matter.
Come back quickly
and give him a report.
OK.
I didn't expect that he specialized in blackmail.
But to be honest,
his unboxing video
is really good.
Meng.
You found out earlier that
his purchase records were true, right?
Yes.
He filmed the whole process
from unboxing to inspection.
Well.
You go back to the company
to ask colleagues in the Technical Department
to check the authenticity of the unboxing video.
I have a place to go.
OK.
Sir.
Please pull over.
OK.
Welcome.
Welcome, Mr. Mo of Shangger.
Manager Wang, Manager Fang.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
I'm sorry.
I'm busy dealing with
the negative news of the company these days.
Very upset.
I heard that all the staff of Lemi
are dealing with this matter urgently.
As the investor in Lemi,
we will certainly do our best to help you.
You said you'd give me feedback in three days.
How's it going?
We are duty-bound to pay our concern about this.
Mr. Mo, well.
Let me show you around the company first,
and then we'll talk in detail.
Please.
This is the core operation department of our company,
including the Department Ⅰ and the Department Ⅱ.
This is the reception area and leisure area.
That's the Technical Department.
This is Director Xu's office cubicle.
Director Xu?
Right.
She is in charge of this fake crisis.
Bet is bet.
Tonight, obey my order.
Come on, Mr. Mo, this way.
OK.
Mr. Zhai.
The reason why Shangger invested in Lemi
is the development potential of Lemi
in the e-commerce industry.
As the investor,
I am concerned about risk.
Now the negative news of Lemi
has seriously affected its market valuation.
So I think
the investment value of Lemi
should be reevaluated.
Why haven't you come yet?
Our new vice president is waiting for you
to give a report.
Mr. Mo.
Please believe that
Lemi will save the day.
We have drawn up three verification schemes this time.
Director Xu suggested starting with the person who disclosed the news.
This is
the most straightforward and efficient way.
Sorry, I'm late.
Let me introduce her.
This is Director Xu,
the person in charge of this fake crisis.
Hello, Director Xu.
Hello.
Xiaopang.
Play the video.
Please watch the video.
This is the video released by the whistleblower.
This is...
Look at this surprise.
It has no lid.
What a surprise.
Lemi's product?
After verification by the Technical Department,
this video has not been edited.
So it's true.
Since there is no problem
from unboxing to inspection,
there is only one doubt:
warehouse.
This is the surveillance video of Lemi warehouse
restored by the Technical Department.
Please have a look.
The whistleblower
seems to have done a good job.
The purchase record and item number are authentic.
But this video
shows that the warehouse keeper changed the products.
The whistleblower also admitted it.
I asked him to make a statement
to apologize to Lemi publicly,
otherwise we will take legal action.
Mr. Zhai.
Wang Dachuan, the warehouse keeper, has an employment relationship with the whistleblower.
He secretly changed the product.
His previous poor consumption record
caused him to incur heavy debts.
In order to repay his debts,
he chose this desperate way.
Now he has brought
great loss of interests to the company.
As for what to do with him,
it's up to you.
He apologized.
The whistleblower apologized.
He has apologized to our company
by posting a video on Weibo.
Qingyou, good job.
Thank you, Mr. Zhai.
Thank you all.
Qingyou, see Mr. Mo off.
OK.
Mr. Mo, this way, please.
Director Xu.
You look familiar to me.
But I don't know where I've seen you.
Really?
You got the wrong person.
Maybe... Have you seen me?
No.
Director Xu.
You haven't paid me the fee
for hotel accommodation yet.