♪In the airport lounge
at the break of day♪
♪A page of dust beneath my fingers♪
♪Filled with stories♪
♪That others never got to tell♪
♪We stand where the law draws its line♪
♪One foot in homeland,
one foot in another land♪
♪With every single stamp we bring down♪
♪The world is split an inch wider♪
♪Raise your eyes, face the light♪
♪See the truth, and see the fright♪
♪Guard the crack within this door♪
♪Keep the way back home
always burning bright♪
♪The camera pans
across the boarding crowd♪
♪Some wear a smile,
some have their eyes adrift♪
♪A red suitcase♪
♪Tied with faded pasts
and broken prayers♪
♪We stand where the law draws its line♪
♪One foot in homeland,
one foot in another land♪
♪With every single stamp we bring down♪
♪It's the heartbeat
echoing the call of law♪
[Gimlet Eyes]
[Episode 16]
I know what you're about to say.
Just head back.
I want
to be alone for a bit.
Alright.
I'll get going then.
After my mentor passed,
I couldn't shake the feeling
that I'd let him down.
So I didn't dare slow down,
didn't dare stop.
Like if I just held on a little longer,
maybe the guilt would ease up.
Mr. Chen.
Yeah?
It's our day off.
And you dragged us
out here this early?
You're young. Why sleep so much?
We're picking up trash.
The fish out there need it.
It might look like
we're just cleaning up garbage,
but in a way,
we're saving a life in the ocean.
Same as the work we do
in Passenger Inspection.
Look.
Up ahead.
See that? We're not doing this alone.
Plenty of people will join us.
So I believe
as long as we keep going,
one day,
this whole beach will be clean.
And
if I can't come out here much later on,
you all need
to hold your post.
Come back often
and pick up what you can.
Looking out at this endless ocean,
I finally understand
why my mentor brought us here
to clean the beach.
There's only ever been
one thing we're meant to do.
To guard the country's gate.
It takes a whole team
to keep it going.
Even if there are regrets along the way,
we still shouldn't rush it.
Just keep going.
♪Turn around and look♪
♪That door's still open♪
♪Waiting there for you♪
You're back, son.
Cong.
You're back.
Where have you been?
Look at you.
Go change your clothes.
Leave your shoes outside.
Mom,
can I get a glass of water?
I'm parched.
Look at him.
Still like a kid.
Don't you think
he's in a much better mood?
Oh, right.
That singing in the hallway,
was that him?
Sounded like him.
If that's the case,
I can
finally relax.
Here.
Thanks, Mom.
Cong,
did you just get back from Fei's place?
I cleaned up trash on the beach.
Clean the beach?
Why?
To protect the ocean.
My mentor's last wish.
Right.
Passport, visa, all sorted.
Here.
I can't go.
What?
Customs didn't approve it?
It's not like that.
The trip was never really my idea.
Sometimes you just want some quiet.
To be on your own.
You suggested Australia,
saying it's far
and good for me to make a fresh start.
I thought
it made sense,
so I said yes.
But now, I've thought it through.
I don't want to go anymore.
I'll go talk
to Customs
and withdraw the application.
You're not going abroad?
I need to get back to work.
Cong,
did you forget your mentor's last wish?
He told you to leave.
Good thing I didn't hear that
from him myself.
I've thought about a lot.
I recalled many things from before.
Recalled how he pushed me
and had my back.
He used to tell me all the time
I had to guard
this country's gate for him,
stand every post in his place,
and never disgrace this uniform.
And the thing is,
when I was quitting,
he didn't give up on me.
When he told me to quit,
I don't think
that's what he really meant.
You know how he was.
He must be confused again.
Clear one minute, confused the next.
We couldn't always tell.
That makes sense.
Also,
even if the illness wore him down,
made him lose hope,
and he did want me to quit,
I still wouldn't
because I truly
love this job
in Passenger Inspection.
Not just for you
or my mom,
but for all those families out there.
I must hold this line.
Right?
I'm gonna take a shower.
Son,
well said.
I almost want to clap for you.
Cong,
if you've really made up your mind,
then go do it.
Alright.
Hey.
Have Cong put his passport
and visa away.
I've been tied up with his stuff.
Look at the good weather.
I haven't been fishing these days.
That's a real loss.
I'm gonna go wet a line.
- Alright, take care. - Yeah.
Yu,
it's been days.
Mr. Guo still hasn't come back.
Does he really…
No.
He just needs time.
Then analyze it for me
from a psychological angle.
What's going on with him right now?
From a psychological angle…
He's in that phase
after a belief system collapsed.
His sense of identity shakes,
and he is rebuilding it.
So going to Fei's place
or leaving the country
is just a kind of withdrawal
resulting from his defense mechanisms.
But pulling away like that
might let him come back stronger.
I don't get it.
Stronger or not, it doesn't matter
as long as he comes back.
Um,
she's not
coming over here for us, is she?
That doesn't look good.
Tao, where are you flying today?
Zhang Yu,
are you trying to take Guo Cong from me?
I know you like him.
You've been sneaking around.
I look down on people like that.
Hold on, Shen Taotao.
Say it straight.
What do you mean, sneaking around?
He'd already decided to travel,
but after you went to see him
at the fish farm,
he canceled everything.
Zhang Yu,
what did you say to him?
He canceled his trip?
Who told you that?
Guo Cong.
He told me himself right here.
Mr. Guo's at the airport?
Sorry.
I'll get going.
Zhang Yu, I'm not done yet!
Tao,
good luck.
If you hadn't come back,
Shihuo would be making
a whole tribute video for you.
That's not true.
I trust him.
[Binhai Huayan Airport Customs]
He knows Passenger Inspection
Section I needs him.
[Binhai Huayan Airport Customs]
You're back.
Yeah, I'm back.
Will you leave again?
Not anymore.
Mr. Guo, you're really back.
Yu was just telling me earlier
about you pulling away and coming back.
You totally called it.
You're amazing!
So you really ran off?
Now you've come to your senses.
That's a good thing.
Alright.
The briefing's about to start.
Hey.
What?
Seriously.
Why didn't you tell me
Mr. Guo was going back?
I just found out, too.
I'll let this slide.
Next time, give me a heads-up.
Give me that pen.
First, I owe everyone an apology.
Because of my personal situation,
I held up the team's work.
Shihuo said just now
that Section I needed me.
But honestly,
I'm the one who needs Section I.
It's been eight years.
I went from a clueless rookie
to who I am today,
someone who's found
his place and purpose.
That's because of my mentor
and
all of you.
So, thank you.
Thank you.
We can reuse
that welcome line for Zhang Yu.
This time,
let's welcome Guo Cong back home.
Come on.
Welcome back home!
Welcome back!
Over here.
Hello, may I see your passport?
Alright, this way, please.
Right this way.
No additional duty needed.
Cong feels different today.
He's smiling so much.
Hi, how do I get to the restroom?
Over there.
Okay. Can we take a photo together?
Sorry, no photos allowed here.
Thanks. Bye.
Mr. Guo seems a little off today.
Why is he so happy today?
Yeah.
Looking sharp, kid.
Thanks. Right this way, thank you.
Muyang, come on, let's go.
Hello. I need to inspect your suitcase.
Sure.
Mom, look.
A soldier!
He's a Customs officer.
Just like soldiers, he protects us, too.
Hi, officer.
Hey there. How old are you?
Six.
Six already?
- You're all grown up. - Mom,
when I grow up,
I want to work at Customs, too.
Then you'd better study hard
so you can get in.
When you join us,
we'll be guarding the gate together.
Okay!
Okay.
I'll be waiting for you at Customs.
Alright, thank you.
Bye, officer!
Bye.
How is it? Everything clear?
All clear. Looks good.
Mentor,
you've been smiling a lot today.
That's because
I finally feel like I'm needed.
Before, all I ever thought about
was catching smugglers.
I missed a lot of the simple,
good moments.
But today,
I saw all of it.
Hello.
I need to inspect your suitcase.
Thank you.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No worries. Go ahead.
Alright.
Excuse me,
how much salt did you use?
Feels like you went all out.
Hey, hey, hey…
It's… it's me, San.
Hey,
we were in the same detention center.
it's me.
Oh, San.
Have a seat.
When'd you get out?
A couple of months ago.
Thought it was you,
so I came over to say hi.
How about we grab a bite together?
Yeah.
Thanks, man.
Excuse me,
two beers and five kidneys.
Got it.
Thanks, man.
We've been through it together.
San,
I've got something to do.
I'll take care of the bill.
I'm heading out.
No, no, no.
Sit, sit.
Please, sit.
I
came to see you
for something serious.
You've got business with me?
I've got something good.
It's fresh.
Need to move it fast.
Since when
did you start dealing in that?
I just got out.
I'm not touching that stuff.
Hey,
weren't you doing import-export before?
Help me find a buyer overseas.
Ship it out. That's it.
I'll give you 20 percent.
Import-export?
You're making me sound legit.
Truth is,
I haven't touched
that line of work since I got out.
Find someone else.
Come on,
I don't know anyone like that.
How about this?
If you really don't want in,
just put me in touch with someone solid.
I'll give you
ten percent for that.
Leave me your number.
If I find someone, I'll let you know.
Forget the referral fee.
Thanks, man.
Let me repeat it again.
I'm not getting involved in this.
If things blow up,
don't drag my name into it.
Don't worry.
I know how this works.
I'd never set you up.
Alright.
Wait for my call.
Got it.
I'll be waiting for your news.
Game over.
Everything sorted?
Yeah, all sorted.
Sit, let's talk.
It's a Yuan dynasty painting.
So what's your next step?
I'll pass the info up the chain
and see if they take the job.
How are you passing it up?
Once you do,
how long before you hear back?
No clue.
I normally just send it up
and wait.
If you pass it up,
then it becomes their job.
What do you even get out of that?
Come on, I'm just a henchman.
Something this big,
it's not my call.
If I were you,
I'd take it straight to the top.
Otherwise, you'd stay
at the bottom for life.
Alright.
Think it through.
Don't forget
to tell me if you hear anything.
Of course.
You can count on me.
Go.
Alright, I'm heading out.
See you.
Keep playing.
Call me if something comes up.
Cong.
You're back.
Where have you been?
Look at you.
So when he told me to leave Customs,
I don't think
that was what he really meant.
Good thing I didn't hear that
from him myself.
Because I truly love this job
in Passenger Inspection.
Not bad, bro.
You've already
hooked a few so soon.
Look at me.
Nothing.
You kept switching spots earlier.
It could be the fish showed up
right after you left.
That makes sense.
I'll stay put this time.
Got one!
Nice size, too!
My rod!
Forget it. Don't go after it.
The water's deep and freezing.
Not worth it.
No way.
I just bought that rod.
If I lose it
and have to ask my wife for money again,
I'm done for.
Money's replaceable.
Lose your life,
and that's a different story.
What kind of crap is that?
Lose my life?
I'm not a kid.
This little bit of water?
I can walk through it blind.
Help!
I'm tangled in weeds!
I'm stuck!
I warned you.
You didn't listen.
Help!
Hello?
Police?
I'm calling it in.
Someone's drowning here.
Yeah, I warned him.
I told him the water was deep
and cold.
He didn't listen.
He even snapped at me.
When you saw he was in danger,
why didn't you help?
I can't swim.
Is that wrong?
That's not what I meant.
I called the police right away.
It's just that this place
is really out of the way.
Is everything okay now?
If there's nothing else,
can I go?
You can go.
If we need anything else,
we'll reach out.
Alright.
Found him!
We found the body!
Your Uncle Xiang brought this.
He just caught it today.
Came all this way to give it to us.
Cong,
you're back
at Customs now, right?
Perfect timing.
I caught this fish earlier.
I figured I'd bring it over
for you to try.
Thanks.
Perfect way to celebrate being back.
Xiang,
I need to say this.
The way you're thinking is dangerous.
You're basically excusing smugglers.
Since you brought them up,
let's talk about those smugglers.
All these years,
you've been catching mules.
So why did they become mules?
Because they got fooled
by smuggling rings.
They chased a little easy money,
and it ended up ruining their lives.
Sounds like you pity them.
How could I not?
They were just tools,
used to move contraband.
Most don't know the law.
Some don't even know the truth.
Tell me that's not tragic.
Choice.
Chen, it's a matter of choice.
Just like you chose to join Customs,
they chose to be mules.
They chose to become tools for crime.
They don't deserve pity.
You're cold-hearted.
I'm not cold-hearted.
I'm rational.
I understand them.
They have desires.
Unrealistic desires.
They
don't want to put in the work.
They want shortcuts.
Then, someone
shows up and hands them a ladder.
Exactly.
We need to catch the ones
handing out those ladders.
Especially the handlers
inside these smuggling rings.
They're the kind of monsters
who devour people whole.
You…
[30 Minutes, Manual Measurement]
Chen,
do you remember what I asked you?
Can you really hold the line?
And for how long?
You can't.
No matter how long you try,
you can't hold it.
Not just you.
Cong can't either.
And that trainee of his.
None of you can.
Enough.
I'll go get a doctor.
[Dolls → Poisonous Perfume, E]
Hurry…
Today,
you've asked so many questions.
Looks like
this
might be
our last
conversation.
So let's just
be honest.
Chen,
that Group E
you took down three years ago
was never wiped out.
They've started moving again.
And that doll,
it showed up, too.
I'm sure Cong told you all this.
But
you can't remember anymore.
How…
how
do you
know?
Guo Cong
would never
tell you.
This is internal…
infor…
Chen,
you're still so conceited.
Always so sure
you're the smartest guy in the world.
Listen, what I know
goes way beyond what's written here.
Who…
who…
- Who am I? - Who…
are you?
Who am I?
That doesn't matter.
None of that matters.
What matters is this.
Everything you've done
amounts to nothing.
Look at yourself.
Right now,
you're like a helpless old dog.
You can't even find your way home.
And you still think
you can hold the line?
Don't worry.
Guo Cong
won't end up like you.
I'll save him from Customs.
You don't deserve that.
Fine.
I don't deserve it.
I've looked out for him for 15 years,
and I don't deserve it?
Look,
you said it yourself.
He's like a son to me.
I'll make sure he gets a different life.
Please…
don't…
Xiang,
there's something I need to tell you.
Go on.
Chen is showing signs
of terminal lucidity.
What does that mean?
It's something
even medicine can't fully explain.
Some Alzheimer's patients,
right before they pass,
suddenly regain clarity.
They can talk like nothing's wrong.
In the medical field overseas,
it's called
Terminal Lucidity.
A final moment
of awareness.
Like a last burst of clarity?
More or less.
Don't get worked up.
I'll go get the doctor.
Xiang.
Easy, easy.
- Don't get worked up. - Don't go.
I'll get the doctor.
Xiang.
Xiang, don't…
don't go.
Doctor!
Don't go!
Goodbye,
old friend.
[Yuan Dynasty Painting]
Zhang's already taken a look.
The painting dates back
to the Yuan dynasty.
As for whether it's an original
by Zhao Yong,
we'll need
a proper appraisal once it's out.
Zhang says it's worth
at least a million dollars.
Got a buyer lined up?
That's the easy part.
I sent the photos out,
and people started asking right away.
I think
we can get it out first
and have it properly authenticated
before making the deal.
Since when do you make those calls?
Li, I was just trying to read your mind.
So how do you plan
to get it out?
Look.
It's a bit large,
so I had Zhang
split it into three pieces.
We'll send them out with three mules.
Even if one gets caught,
the rest still have value.
Alright.
Go arrange the flights
and handle everything on the other end.
The sooner, the better.
All set.
Li,
after all these years,
if nothing else,
my cooking's still got it.
See that?
Heat's perfect.
Looks good, smells good, tastes good.
[Mr. E]
Mr. E,
it's me.
I know.
I got the photos.
These are all mules?
They're all people who can become mules.
[Shen Taotao, Flight Attendant]
On the back of the photos,
[Eager to Prove Herself with Money]
I wrote short notes
about their current situation
and weaknesses.
When you need people,
go to them.
Need me to tell you what to say?
No.
I know what to say.
What's wrong, Li?
This Mr. E
is acting off.
He's always been capable
and mysterious.
He's never been normal anyway.
What's off about that?
It's just normal for him.
Think about it.
He used to handle
finding the mules only,
but he never asked who we used
or how.
But when I brought up the painting,
he specifically picked Chen Wei,
Lawyer Song,
and that guy dealing the painting
to be the mules.
And out of those,
only Lawyer Song
is someone he actually found.
He's never even met the other two.
So what do you think
he's after?
If I knew that,
I wouldn't be here thinking.
Something's not right.
Have you noticed
he hasn't asked
about the doll in a long time?
What if he already knows something
and just doesn't tell us?
Very likely.
Li,
I probably shouldn't say this.
He's not in this with us.
Not me.
I've always had your back.
We're on the same side.
Remember those dolls
and how Sa Ziyi went down?
He knew all about it
but never told you the full story.
That alone
tells me we need to watch him.
We should find a chance
to see what he's about.
You'll never catch me.
[Ancient Painting]
This doll is clearly a warning.
Mr. Shen,
any updates lately
on cultural relics moving in or out?
Nothing so far.
Cong, have you noticed something?
This one and the last don't seem
especially for us.
Three years ago,
the doll was pretty low-key.
Only Customs knew about it.
No one else did.
But these last two feel staged.
Like someone wants attention.
Like it's not just
meant for Customs,
but for someone else, too.
Dayu told me this.
Whoever did this is trying to use it
to pull our attention away.
They want to use Customs
to take down Group E.
Whether it's criminals
turning on each other
or something else,
it doesn't change our job.
As long as we guard the border,
that's enough.
Yes.
[Creepy Doll with Eerie Looks and Voices
Found in the Airport Restroom]
Li,
the doll showed up again.
It just won't go away.
This is clearly tied to the painting.
Something about this deal feels off.
It's been off since Mr. E got involved.
Li,
someone must've leaked the word.
We should pause this deal.
If we keep going,
we may walk straight into trouble.
I agree.
We can't afford to lose on both fronts.
Li,
you're pulling out fancy phrases now?
How do you not understand that?
I mean,
we can't take a loss here.
We can't lose the goods
and get busted with them.
Got it.
We can't screw up and lose everything.
Alright.
I'll call Ken.
Have him hold the shipment.
Wait.
Let me call Mr. E first.
Him again?
He's not stupid.
He must be thinking
about the same thing.
First of all, this is huge.
I need to inform him.
Besides, I've got a feeling.
I want to see how he reacts.
Mr. E.
Du Li.
This is him.
The doll showed up again.
Do you know that?
I do.
You don't sound surprised.
I've been waiting for it.
I'd be surprised if it hadn't shown up.
What do you mean?
Its appearance
proves my theory was right.
I already know
who put the doll there.
Who?
Long Shuo.
Long Shuo?
Du Li,
I've been telling you to find him.
But you end up being found by him first.
Did you know
he's already working
with Chen Wei?
That's impossible.
The footage from the exhibition
was shot by Long Shuo.
And if I'm right,
he's the one
who connected Chen Wei to this painting.
I asked you
whether the source
of this painting was clean.
What did you tell me?
♪There's a place of simple,
everyday warmth♪
♪A door left open
for the wandering soul♪
♪A humble table still warm with love♪
♪After you've tasted every high and low♪
♪Come home, I'll keep you warm♪
♪Where the days begin and end♪
♪A light still on for the ones
who've lost their way♪
♪An embrace waiting just for you♪
♪Through every passing season♪
♪Even if you return with nothing at all♪
♪Turn around and look♪
♪That door's still open♪
♪A light still burning♪
♪Waiting there for you♪
♪Turn around and look♪
♪Someone's still waiting♪
♪Watching the dusk settle in♪
♪Waiting for the break of dawn♪
♪It's always there♪