♪In the airport lounge
at the break of day♪
♪A page of dust beneath my fingers♪
♪Filled with stories♪
♪That others never got to tell♪
♪We stand where the law draws its line♪
♪One foot in homeland,
one foot in another land♪
♪With every single stamp we bring down♪
♪The world is split an inch wider♪
♪Raise your eyes, face the light♪
♪See the truth, and see the fright♪
♪Guard the crack within this door♪
♪Keep the way back home
always burning bright♪
♪The camera pans
across the boarding crowd♪
♪Some wear a smile,
some have their eyes adrift♪
♪A red suitcase♪
♪Tied with faded pasts
and broken prayers♪
♪We stand where the law draws its line♪
♪One foot in homeland,
one foot in another land♪
♪With every single stamp we bring down♪
♪It's the heartbeat
echoing the call of law♪
[Gimlet Eyes]
[Episode 17]
If I'm not mistaken,
this painting
was also brokered to Chen Wei
through Long Shuo.
I asked you before
whether this painting was clean.
Remember what you told me?
Did you actually check it out?
If you had,
you would've traced it back
to Long Shuo.
Why would he do all this?
He was Sa Ziyi's lover.
Sa Ziyi's cause of death
is still unknown.
You think he doesn't want to know
who killed her?
Whoever took over Sa Ziyi's turf
is the prime suspect.
Who else would he come to but you?
He couldn't find you himself.
So he used the doll to get Customs
to find you for him.
Now you get it, right?
But
Chen Wei doesn't even know who I am.
He's never even seen my face.
What about Ken?
Ken was directly
involved in moving the painting.
What if Long Shuo's already found him?
Probably not.
Du Li.
Looks like life's been
a little too easy for you lately.
You're starting to look
just like Sa Ziyi back then,
spoiled and careless.
Take my advice,
don't follow in her footsteps.
Or death'll be staring you in the face
before you know it.
Understood, Mr. E.
I'll send someone to look into Ken.
We'll dig deep.
So, should we stop
moving the painting for now?
No.
It has to go.
Why?
To protect ourselves.
First,
Chen Wei is already
Long Shuo's eyes and ears.
You still want to keep him around?
Second,
Lawyer Song failed to frame Guo Cong.
You think Customs
won't start digging into him?
Third,
this painting is
a Yuan Dynasty artifact.
You think anyone
dealing in something like that
has clean hands?
Any one of these three
could bring trouble to our door.
They're already expendable.
Letting them move the painting
is basically giving them a way out.
If they make it out,
they can live it up overseas.
If they don't…
Du Li,
then you'd better
start worrying about Ken.
Mr. E, if you knew all this,
why didn't you tell me sooner?
Because it was only a theory.
I needed the doll to confirm it.
How could I have told you before that?
But your theory cost me a lot.
You cut off an arm to save your life.
Understand?
Right now, we've only
lost a few fingers.
If we keep dragging this out,
we'll lose the whole arm.
If you make it through this,
keep looking for Long Shuo.
He's the real problem.
Useless.
What now?
What do you think?
We keep going and hope for the best.
Finish the job.
But Li!
What if they really get caught?
Then that's their fate.
Fine.
Mr. Long.
What's up?
About the painting,
I reported it to the higher-ups.
They put me in charge of this job.
They're giving me this much.
Congratulations.
Looks like you're moving up.
Not really.
It's all thanks to the chance
you gave me.
So, Mr. Long,
can I ask you something?
What exactly are you trying
to find out from me?
Nothing major.
Just a personal score to settle
with your boss.
If we could sit down face to face,
it'd all blow over.
But I can never get to him.
So I had to go the long way around
and work my way up through you.
Mr. Long,
if I handle this deal well,
I figure
I'll get a chance to meet the top brass.
I'll pass your message to them.
I appreciate that.
When are you planning
to make the move?
Honestly, I don't know yet.
Usually, the seller
gives us the flight number
a day in advance,
and we head straight there.
Being cautious is a good thing.
Well, here's to a smooth run.
Thanks, Mr. Long.
I booked us a private room up ahead.
Uncle Xiang.
What are you messing with?
Here.
Let me help.
Where does this go?
No.
I put it here
just now.
Just moved it over.
Set it down properly.
Listen, don't move
my stuff around.
Or I can never find anything again.
You've got more and more stuff
piled up in here.
How long has it been
since you last came by?
When you were a kid,
you'd come straight here after school.
Couldn't get rid of you.
And now what?
You're at Customs,
and you don't even
bother stopping by anymore?
Come on,
of course I want to.
The problem is, every time
I come here,
I feel like pocketing something.
But Customs has rules.
We can't do that.
You know how painful that is?
So, out of sight, out of mind.
That excuse sounds well-rehearsed.
If you don't want to come, fine.
Spare me the excuses.
Let me tell you,
half the stuff here
belonged to your father.
That means half of it is yours.
Taking your own things is totally fine.
Fine, I'll come by more often.
Just don't blame me
if I mess the place up.
Uncle Xiang,
what did you call me over for today?
Why is a young guy like you
stuck at home all day?
Go ask a girl out.
Wait…
Did my mom get in your ear too?
She nags me every day about
finding a wife.
I came here to get some peace.
Your mom didn't have to get to me.
We've been on the same side all along.
Seriously.
Tao!
Tao? Come on…
Guo Cong's here!
Where is she?
Coming right down!
Hi there.
Come on in.
Uncle Xiang…
Look,
your mom assigned me a mission.
I tried to get out of it,
but I couldn't.
Uncle Xiang,
she's not right for me.
Anyway, spend more time together first.
People have a lot of sides to them.
You need different settings,
different situations
to see different sides.
Maybe you'll like one of them.
So I'm just here
to fulfill my mom's mission.
Then at least buy me lunch.
When she gets here, smile.
Don't make things awkward.
But I…
Guo Cong, you're here.
I'm here.
Tao, sit.
You remember this?
I was just chatting with Mr. Xiang,
and he told me so many stories
about you playing here
when you were little.
It sounds like a dream.
You're too kind.
This place is basically a junkyard.
Only he cares about all this stuff.
They may be old,
but every piece here carries history.
That's true.
My uncle's got all that history
in his head.
Uncle Xiang,
why don't you
show Tao around
and tell her all about it?
I don't have time for that.
I promised a regular customer
I'd help find a matching pair
of old window lattices.
I asked you to come
because I want you
to teach Tao photography.
I'm an amateur myself.
That's fine.
Just teach her the basics.
The camera and film
are all ready to go.
Go take some shots,
and when you get back,
we'll have lunch together
and develop the film.
Well,
thanks in advance, Mentor.
Don't call me that.
Customs has rules,
no small cliques.
But Zhang Yu calls you that too.
Zhang Yu's different.
Alright, what are you waiting for?
Get going,
while there's still daylight.
Go on.
Go, go, go.
Alright.
Make sure you've got everything.
Got it.
We're heading out.
Mr. Xiang, we're off!
Cong, take good care of her.
Got it.
Thanks.
Guo Cong,
my feet are killing me.
Can we sit down for a bit?
Sure.
Let's sit here.
Mr. Guo told me
to call him in five minutes
and say it's an emergency.
If I'm guessing right,
he's in the middle of a tough date.
A tough date?
I've been
flying to Australia a lot lately,
and I saw this neck massager
selling like crazy.
I want to get one for your mom.
No need.
Her neck is perfectly fine.
You just don't know it.
When we watch TV together,
she's always rubbing her neck.
And your couch is way too hard,
it's really not great for older people.
Okay, fine.
Go ahead and get one.
Let me know how much it is,
and I'll send you the money.
Can you stop
making everything about money?
I want to give it to her as a gift.
Guo Cong,
can you stop drawing such clear lines
between us?
That's not it.
Customs has rules,
you know that.
Customs rules
won't let you make friends?
Or fall in love?
That's not what I mean.
Who's calling?
Work.
Hello? Zhang Yu. What's up?
Something happened at Customs?
What is it?
Okay.
Be right there.
See you soon. Bye.
Sorry,
I've got to get back.
Something came up at Customs.
How about this,
if you still want to take pictures,
go to the park up ahead.
You can shoot there.
And when you're tired,
go rest at my uncle's place, okay?
Gotta go. Call me.
Shouldn't I bring your camera back?
Right.
The camera.
Thanks.
See you.
Guo Cong.
You're pretty good at reading people.
But your acting
is really terrible.
Well… What acting?
Just now,
you were clearly texting someone.
You had Zhang Yu call to bail you out,
didn't you?
At least you've got some conscience.
You went out of your way to lie to me
just so I wouldn't look like a fool.
Actually,
Tao, I wanted to tell you…
Guo Cong,
we're not kids anymore.
Whatever you have to say, just say it.
I think
you're a really kind person.
I just don't think
we're the right match.
Why do you say that?
I've always felt that
even though
we haven't known each other that long,
you're a genuinely good person.
If you think I'm a good person too,
then why can't you give me,
give us,
a chance?
When it comes to relationships,
it's not as simple as
you think I'm a good person,
and I think you're a good person.
It comes down to whether it feels right,
right?
So,
you like her then?
Who?
Zhang Yu?
She's my colleague.
Okay.
Good.
Guo Cong.
I like you.
And I'll make you like me too.
I'm willing to wait.
I believe
feelings can grow.
[Herbal Tea
Clears the Liver, Sharpens Vision]
This is really bitter.
[Herbal Tea
Clears the Liver, Sharpens Vision]
But kinda addictive somehow.
Do you think people are just like that?
Always drawn to things
that make them suffer?
Are you talking about yourself?
Or someone else?
Who else? Shen Taotao.
Why'd she go after
a hard nut like Mr. Guo?
Mr. Guo didn't say a word
about it on the phone.
Think about it.
Who else could make Mr. Guo
call for help like that?
I still don't think it was her.
He's not that kind of person.
If he wasn't into her,
he wouldn't have gone off alone
with her.
Sure, he wouldn't.
But what about his mom?
And Mr. Xiang?
Mr. Xiang?
He wouldn't
get involved in something like this,
would he?
He cares so much about Mr. Guo.
If you didn't know better,
you'd think he was Mr. Guo's father.
Of course he'd get involved.
Alright, enough guessing.
Just call him and ask.
Again?
Of course.
What if he's still stuck there?
Then your mission failed.
Call him.
Hurry up!
One call and you'll know.
Speaker.
Speaker!
Hello, Zhang Yu.
So… did you manage to get out?
Yeah, I'm out.
Good. Glad you got out.
Was that Shen Taotao just now?
How did you know?
Just guessing.
Wait, Shen Taotao
doesn't know I called you, right?
She knows.
I showed her.
Otherwise,
how would she believe
it was really a work call?
Mentor, you got me in trouble again.
How did I get you in trouble?
Last time,
you canceled that Australia trip,
remember?
She thinks I got in the way
and made you cancel it.
And now you're using me
as your cover again.
She's definitely coming after me.
You were the only person
I could think of, okay?
But…
Wait…
Mentor…
I…
I mean,
if you're not into her,
stop being alone with her all the time.
Or she's going to get the wrong idea.
I wasn't planning to.
Uncle Xiang tricked me into it.
Mr. Xiang is involved in this?
Back then,
my mentor was always worried about this.
He's looking out for me
for my mentor's sake.
So that Australia trip
with Shen Taotao
was Mr. Xiang's idea too?
I was planning to go to Australia
by myself.
Uncle Xiang brought her to see me.
She overheard us.
So it was his idea after all.
What? Didn't catch that.
Nothing, never mind.
Glad you're out. Talk later. Bye.
You were the only person
I could think of!
Stop it!
You're in trouble, Yu.
Nonsense!
I was just thinking,
don't you think
Mr. Xiang's pushing
Shen Taotao
toward Mr. Guo a bit too hard?
If not her,
then how about you?
How about you? Seriously!
Tao, you're back?
Where's Cong?
He got a work call.
Something came up. He left.
That kid,
he just left you there by yourself?
This is on me.
I shouldn't have just
sent you two off together like that.
This…
Well…
I…
I know
you really like Cong.
But honestly, I never thought
he'd just leave you there
and run off by himself.
So what are you thinking now?
Honestly,
getting rejected really hurts.
But
this is my own happiness
we're talking about.
I want to try a little harder.
Otherwise,
I'm afraid I'll regret it later.
Good.
That's what I like about you.
But even though I've made up my mind,
I don't know what to do next.
You know Guo Cong better than anyone.
Can you give me some advice?
Advice, huh?
Okay.
Here, hand me the camera.
You poor thing, come here.
Come on.
Li,
what brings you here?
You could've called ahead.
If I didn't come now,
Customs would beat me to it.
What do you mean?
Can that computer pull up
all the security footage
from Yating's cameras?
Yeah.
Pull up the footage from the day
you passed the message to Chen Wei.
The cameras facing the gallery.
Stop.
Zoom in.
Who is that?
Long Shuo.
Customs doesn't answer to you.
I've got things to do.
Save the lecture.
Stay where you are.
I don't remember saying you could leave.
That's Long Shuo?
No question.
I saw him once at Sa Ziyi's place.
It's definitely him.
How did he know where to find us?
He's been working with Chen Wei
this whole time!
You brought a wolf in
and didn't even know it!
Can you make him disappear?
Li, you scared me.
I-I can't handle something like that.
How about
letting Dabao handle it?
He's ruthless enough.
I knew you didn't have the guts.
Li.
Long Shuo probably didn't see me.
I came to pick up the message at night.
Let's hope so.
From now on,
stop everything you're doing.
Don't go anywhere.
Stay right here.
Wait for my call.
Right now,
all you can do is pray Chen Wei
doesn't mess up the run.
If he gets caught
and gives you up,
I can't protect you.
Chen Wei.
I sent you out to photograph people,
and every single shot is of him.
Tao,
I honestly don't understand
how you young people
deal with relationships these days.
But one thing I do know
is Cong doesn't understand it either.
He's never even been in a relationship.
He's been walking barefoot
his whole life.
How would he know
what kind of shoes fit him?
But here's the thing,
that boy always has his guard up.
He was only 15 when his father passed.
It took me a lot of effort,
nearly a whole year,
before he finally called me uncle again.
If you really want my advice,
it's simple.
Just one word.
Persist.
Persist?
Exactly.
Like water wearing down stone.
Use all your time
to slowly get closer to him,
and all your energy
into letting him see how good you are.
Once he starts coming to you on his own,
you won't be able to shake him off.
I get it.
Let me think about that.
If you need me
to help behind the scenes,
just say the word.
Will do.
Honestly,
I've got my own selfish reasons too.
I've always had a dream.
I want to
sail around the world on a boat.
But I never managed to.
This business keeps me tied down.
Ever since I met you,
I started seeing hope.
I figure
if you and Cong
make things official soon,
and get married,
you can help me convince Cong
to leave Customs.
Then the two of you
can take over my business.
Wouldn't that be nice?
That's exactly what I was thinking.
Customs work is way too demanding.
I don't want a husband
who's never around.
Exactly.
That's the right call.
Oh,
let me show you something.
See this photo?
After that photo exhibit,
I kept looking for this photo of you.
And I finally found it.
This is just a sample print.
You captured it so well.
Look,
back then, your eyes were full of life.
Actually,
I'd just started as a flight attendant.
I was seeing so much around me,
and I was stuck
in this place of inner conflict,
constantly torn inside.
And somehow,
you captured
exactly how I felt back then.
But after that,
I made a lot of wrong choices.
Let's see what we're having tonight.
Sounds good.
Zihan.
Tao!
Come on, I'll take you to the airport.
See you then.
Okay, bye!
Nice one, Tao.
Showing up in a luxury car now?
Better to rely on yourself
than on anyone else.
True.
Alright.
Whatever happened in the past,
let's leave it there.
When I was young,
I made way more mistakes than you.
But remember this,
if you want a future with Guo Cong,
don't make any more mistakes.
Don't worry.
I promise I won't.
Tao.
Be careful on the way.
Goodbye, Mr. Xiang.
Bye.
Li.
You've got a mule named Shen Taotao.
Yes.
The flight attendant.
She's not moving cargo anymore.
Right.
She's never handling cargo again.
I've got
other plans for her.
This time,
I'm going to make sure
you win Guo Cong over.
We just received critical intel.
A smuggling ring is planning
to smuggle the Yuan Dynasty painting
Layers of Mountains
out of the country today.
Headquarters' order is clear:
Stop that painting
before it leaves the country.
Almighty Lord.
Please bless me.
Hello, China Customs.
Please cooperate with the inspection.
Excuse me, sir.
This way, please.
Hello.
China Customs.
Please cooperate with the inspection.
Mr. Zhang.
That man in the gray jacket,
something's off with his luggage.
Copy that.
Excuse me, sir.
China Customs.
Please cooperate with the inspection.
Please open your luggage.
Too warm here?
It's okay…
Not at all.
What's in here?
Nothing…
Let go.
Stop him!
- Stop! - Don't run!
Stop!
Move!
I heard
Section III already caught two of them.
Based on the scans so far,
there should still be
one more piece missing.
My wife
already went with Hu to back them up.
They won't get away. Don't worry.
Yan Bowen,
want to go check it out with me?
I've never seen
a Yuan Dynasty painting before.
Mr. Guo, I'd like to take another look
at the painting.
Just a quick look, be right back.
Come right back.
Don't get in anyone's way.
- Understood. - Go ahead.
Mr. Zhang,
I heard
they caught the suspects
in the painting smuggling case.
Mr. Li,
we got two of them.
One's still missing.
He could've run
when he saw his partners get caught.
Or maybe
he's still waiting it out.
My guess is
he'll take one last shot.
Otherwise, once the anti-smuggling
gets his information from his partners,
he'll have nowhere left to run.
Hard to say.
Those two mules were obviously rookies.
Whatever they know
probably isn't worth much.
But the one who got away,
I'm guessing he's the handler.
Doesn't matter.
They're not getting past us.
Trust me.
- Liu. - Liu, over here!
Come on.
Thanks, Mr. Zhang.
Thanks, Mr. Li.
No problem.
Good work.
Just doing my job.
Mr. Li, I'm heading out.
Alright.
Leave it to me. I've got this.
Sure.
Liu, what's wrong?
Why are you so nervous?
N-Nothing.
I'm just a bit tired.
Wanna get home and rest.
Liu, what's going on?
- Liu! - Liu!
- Stop! - Stop!
- Stop! - Don't run!
Stop him!
Grab him!
Liu?
Call Anti-Smuggling.
Liu just came at us
like he'd lost his mind.
If it wasn't for Yan Bowen,
that boiling water
would've been all over me.
Bowen, are you okay?
This is all my fault.
I shouldn't have gone over there
to see the painting.
Are you okay?
- That burn looks bad. - I'm fine.
Liu did it.
Which Liu?
Liu Kai?
But…
Hello.
Mr. Li, go ahead.
Got it.
On my way.
Liu says he wants to see me.
Gotta go down there.
Get that burn treated.
Put something on it.
Dayu,
go to the cafeteria, bring me
Liu's favorite dishes.
He's being sent
to detention this afternoon.
Let's get him a good meal
before he goes.
Grab some soup.
His stomach isn't great.
You really can't judge a person
by appearances.
Did you find the handler?
We questioned Liu for a while.
He wouldn't say a thing.
He finally started to crack,
but he insisted on seeing you.
We found the last piece of the painting
in the bag on Liu's cleaning cart.
And at the time,
he was heading toward an outbound lane.
So I'm guessing
the handler already
made it through customs,
and is waiting for him outside.
If we can't get Liu to talk,
the handler's about to cross the border.
After that, he's gone for good.
Alright.
Let me try.
Mr. Guo.
I…
I'm sorry.
You don't owe me an apology.
You let yourself down.
And your family.
If I end up in prison,
I…
How am I supposed to face anyone?
Now you're scared?
Then why did you do it?
I did it for the money!
Ten years ago,
someone paid me
to stay at the airport,
keep doing my cleaning job.
I was told
to take the money,
do nothing,
and only act
in case of emergencies.
Liu,
when I started at Customs,
you were already here.
You always told me
you were doing this for your family,
for your son.
No one wants to see you like this
more than your wife
and your son.
They don't know anything.
Don't drag them into this.
If the neighbors find out,
it'll be a lifelong shame.
If you tell me the truth,
maybe I can still help you.
Hello, welcome aboard.
Boss,
the package is gone.
But I'm already on the plane.
Excuse me, coming through.
Glad you're safe.
Don't come back for now.
Chen Wei.
A distant relative of mine.
He sent me money every year,
but never asked me to do anything.
This
was the first time he ever used me.
So Chen Wei was today's handler.
He's the one
who gave you the pants, right?
Yes.
Justice has a long arm.
None shall escape.
No one gets away.
After Chen Wei came to me,
I started helping them
keep tabs on Customs.
I took that photo
of Zhang Yu.
♪There's a place of simple,
everyday warmth♪
♪A door left open
for the wandering soul♪
♪A humble table still warm with love♪
♪After you've tasted every high and low♪
♪Come home, I'll keep you warm♪
♪Where the days begin and end♪
♪A light still on for the ones
who've lost their way♪
♪An embrace waiting just for you♪
♪Through every passing season♪
♪Even if you return with nothing at all♪
♪Turn around and look♪
♪That door's still open♪
♪A light still burning♪
♪Waiting there for you♪
♪Turn around and look♪
♪Someone's still waiting♪
♪Watching the dusk settle in♪
♪Waiting for the break of dawn♪
♪It's always there♪