♪In the airport lounge
at the break of day♪
♪A page of dust beneath my fingers♪
♪Filled with stories♪
♪That others never got to tell♪
♪We stand where the law draws its line♪
♪One foot in homeland,
one foot in another land♪
♪With every single stamp we bring down♪
♪The world is split an inch wider♪
♪Raise your eyes, face the light♪
♪See the truth, and see the fright♪
♪Guard the crack within this door♪
♪Keep the way back home
always burning bright♪
♪The camera pans
across the boarding crowd♪
♪Some wear a smile,
some have their eyes adrift♪
♪A red suitcase♪
♪Tied with faded pasts
and broken prayers♪
♪We stand where the law draws its line♪
♪One foot in homeland,
one foot in another land♪
♪With every single stamp we bring down♪
♪It's the heartbeat
echoing the call of law♪
[Gimlet Eyes]
[Episode 4]
[Four Years Ago
2019]
Besides the one I just mentioned,
Flight KM997,
please pay attention
and see if there are any passengers
wearing red or carrying items
featuring red from other flights.
Keep it in mind.
As easy as finding a needle
in a haystack.
Quit whining.
One mistake can cost everything.
I found nothing
on my shift.
It's all yours now.
Same as always.
Got used to it.
Mr. Shen.
Heard you're getting promoted.
Hey, Zhang Dayu.
You always remind me of your dad.
What does it have to do with my dad?
Both are chatterboxes.
Mr. Chen won't leave the front line.
Otherwise, it wouldn't be me.
Learn from him.
And also from Guo Cong.
Alright?
Don't bring shame on China Customs.
You guys are the future here.
Look how pudgy you are!
I'm working on it.
Are you?
Go.
Excuse me, sir. Passport, please?
This way.
Excuse me.
Our target might be red,
but not everyone wearing red
needs to be sent to inspection.
Look how busy it is now.
Thanks for your cooperation.
You need to judge first and screen.
Can you?
In the world,
no smuggling is perfect.
-There's always something with their looks
and their movements.
Observe, and you'll see it.
Yes, sir.
Don't get trapped by red.
Understood.
This way.
Please open it.
This is Passenger Inspection Section I.
This way.
Hello. We need to check your clothes.
Okay, thank you.
Attention, everyone.
Flight KM997
has landed.
Passengers will be here soon.
Guo Cong, copy.
Dayu, copy.
Deng Hongxia, copy.
Sir.
I've got someone suspicious.
He's been using his phone's front camera
to look behind him.
Short-sleeved white T
and black sleeveless hoodie.
Blue jeans.
Black and white sneakers.
Black suitcase
and black backpack.
Over and out.
Deng, go help Guo Cong.
Okay.
Dayu, follow him.
Copy.
Sir, please help me with this.
Hello, China Customs.
We need to check it.
Hello.
We need to check your suitcase.
Please open it.
Came from Europe with so many stamps?
It's my hobby.
Gentle!
Sorry.
Are they expensive?
It's not about the money,
okay?
These stamps might look small and thin,
but these tiny pieces
carry a country's history and culture.
Take this set, for example.
This set
was specially issued
to commemorate Mozart.
The 20 stamps here
tell all about his life
and achievements.
I just landed.
The trip was really worth it.
Quite a faw stamp collectors.
I'm a stamp collector.
Need those from every country.
Can't miss them when having the chance.
Do they cost much?
I might buy some, too.
Not too much. Affordable.
These look quite new.
And they're odd.
Doesn't matter.
Their value will increase.
Not really.
The appreciation of stamps
depends not just on time
but more on their artistic
and research value.
Mister,
did I use your money?
The small bag, sir.
Hi, officer.
Can I go now?
Of course.
Thank you for your cooperation.
This bag
exceeds the limit, I think.
Got the receipt?
Yeah, but it's within the limit.
It only cost 355 euros.
That's less than 5,000 yuan.
And plus the stamps?
Come on.
The stamps aren't worth much.
All within the limit.
Go check if you don't believe me.
Sorry, please come with us.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Liu.
Allow me.
Why did you bring me here?
I didn't do anything.
Miss, are these stamps yours?
Yes, they're mine.
Then, on behalf of China Customs,
I'm telling you,
the test shows
these stamps contain
illegal drug ingredients
and are prohibited from entry.
The Criminal Law stipulates
that smuggling requires the offender
to have subjective intent
with knowledge.
If
you were deceived into carrying these,
unaware of the nature of the act,
it does not constitute smuggling.
But
if you knew
what you were carrying
and were aware of the nature of the act,
then you are suspected of smuggling.
I'll ask you one more time.
Are these stamps yours?
Think carefully before you answer.
They are not mine.
A man approached me earlier,
saying his items exceeded the limit,
and asking me to help bring these in.
Then he gave me 1,000 yuan.
I really had no idea
these stamps were prohibited items.
Was it a man wearing a white T,
a black sleeveless hoodie,
and blue jeans?
Yes, that's him.
Dayu, are the anti-smuggling men here?
They are.
Look carefully.
There are drugs on the stamp back.
Officer,
I really didn't know.
I was deceived.
He told me to meet him
at the Big Bowl Noodles.
You need to go get him!
Okay, it's alright.
Miss,
when the anti-smuggling officers
get here,
tell them everything you know.
It's gonna be okay.
Hello. These are her belongings.
She's still so young.
Mr. Chen,
that man also had stamps.
Why did you let him go?
He knew his stamps very well,
while this girl knew nothing.
Could it be that he knew
carrying stamps looked suspicious,
so he did some homework
to learn all about those stamps?
Did you hear his ringtone?
Some classical music.
Mozart's Serenade.
You know that?
In our line of work,
you need to know
a little bit of everything.
So, it makes sense his luggage
had a high concentration of Mozart.
Just think.
If he wanted to smuggle drugs,
he couldn't be so meticulous
as to set his ringtone
to Mozart, right?
And look at that girl.
She knew the price of her bag very well,
but not so much about the stamps.
This bag
exceeds the limit, I think.
It only cost 355 euros.
That's less than 5,000 yuan.
And plus the stamps?
Come on.
The stamps aren't worth much.
All within the limit.
So obviously,
she's just a temporary mule.
But Mr. Chen, there's one more thing.
Yes?
The suspect
needed someone to be the carrier.
Why did he choose
a girl wearing pink?
And we happen to be looking
for a smuggler
who is related to red or pink.
Is it just coincidental or intentional?
You are asking
the right question.
I think it should be a coincidence.
Anyway,
Shihuo,
you've reminded me.
That suspect
is probably new at this,
giving little information to his helper.
And he used his phone
to keep track of the girl behind him.
That was exactly what exposed him.
It was an obvious flaw.
What do you mean?
I got it.
He did that on purpose.
Fan, let me.
Sure.
Cong,
how many from KM997 have gone through?
Only a small number.
Those with little luggage.
Those with checked luggage
are still in there.
This way, please.
Sir,
that girl in pink
whom you just checked.
How did it go?
Find anything?
Drugs in stamps.
You should know,
it's gonna be a long day.
More drug smugglers?
I think the big one is yet to come.
Seriously?
This way, please.
Now, all be quiet.
Quiet.
Quiet. Come here.
Let's take a group photo here, okay?
Okay.
Let's scooch closer
and take a group photo. - Larry?
Who?
Larry.
You know him?
One of the best esports players
in China.
It looks like he just
got back from an overseas competition.
He's red-hot now.
Look at all those fans.
They were probably with him
at the competition.
The Hangzhou Asian Games
will have esports events.
Cong, well done.
Go.
Find a pen and paper,
and join me here.
Hurry.
Don't push.
One at a time.
Okay, that's all for today.
We're running late. Until next time.
Here.
Pen and paper.
Come on.
What's going on?
Larry's here.
Which Larry?
How many do you know?
The Larry?
Get me an autograph.
We need to check it.
I was just joking, sir.
Hello, China Customs.
Please, this way for inspection.
Officer,
we have a livestream to attend.
We're running late.
Don't worry, as long as you cooperate,
it won't take long.
Zhang.
Over here.
Larry and I will go now.
You stay here
for the luggage inspection.
Take a taxi and join us later.
Got it.
Sorry, rules require
the trophy to be inspected, too.
It's Larry's interview
after the championship today.
You know how many people are waiting?
Please calm down.
Please calm down and cooperate with us.
Calm down.
Listen to me.
Let's not fight.
I'm also a fan of Larry.
I'm also so happy seeing him
with the trophy.
I share your feelings.
No photos.
But here's the thing.
This is the Customs.
Customs has its rules.
You wouldn't want some trolls
to attack and accuse Larry
of not following customs rules, right?
He is a public figure, right?
Can't tarnish his image, right?
Let me handle this, okay?
I'll handle it.
Mr. Chen.
Let him skip the line, okay?
Make an exception.
Make an exception, right?
Yeah!
Just be more understanding.
I'm helping you, right?
Yes, you are.
Keep moving. Keep going.
Since I'm helping you,
I hope you can also help me, okay?
Okay.
Now, the fans
can exit through here.
Alright?
Okay.
Wait outside, okay?
Thank you.
Thanks for your cooperation.
Okay, Larry.
This way, please.
Here, this way.
Please put your luggage
through the X-ray machine.
Well, you see,
I'm really a big fan.
Could I have your autograph?
Sure.
Thank you so much.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
One of us is a huge fan of you.
I was signaling Chen to get him here.
Seriously?
Are your people always
this casual at work?
Well, we've got an idol here.
Oh, excuse me.
This trophy needs
to go through the X-ray.
Here, let me.
Its weight feels wrong.
For a solid trophy this big,
it should
be about two or three kilos.
This is only around one kilo.
Step back!
Cooperate with our inspection.
It's an international championship trophy.
Cause any damage to it,
and I will file a complaint.
Did I say damaging it?
I only said
it felt a bit lightweight.
Didn't I?
Never mind.
You take care of the trophy.
I'll wait for you outside.
Sure.
Please cooperate
with customs inspection.
I've been cooperating,
and you've been holding me up here
with various excuses.
So you competed in world-class events.
Got some nerves of steel.
Then cooperate with us one more time
in the inspection room.
This way.
Shihuo,
the luggage is clear. Let go.
This way.
- This way. - Sorry.
Larry!
Larry has a livestream to attend!
This trophy didn't come easily, right?
Quite prestigious, isn't it?
Of course.
It was the World Elite Invitational.
Only the top 20 players in the world
could participate.
Officer,
please hurry up.
We really are running out of time.
Relax. I'll be quick.
Cong,
hand me the hammer.
Now.
What do you want to do?
Take it easy.
What are you doing?
Wait.
What's this smell?
A sourness typical of drugs.
Drugs?
Dayu.
Get anti-smuggling guys here.
You didn't know he's been using?
I… I didn't.
Look at the scar on his palm.
It's a burn scar left
by a heated glass tube
when he was in a daze,
with his senses dulled,
after using drugs.
Right?
I saw it before.
I thought it was
from his mouse handling.
Larry,
how could you be so foolish?
Why did you touch drugs?
Mr. Chen, anti-smuggling men are here.
Zheng, he's all yours.
Larry!
I'm here for you!
Are fans all this crazy now?
Larry!
Those esports players
are like movie or TV stars now.
Those must have been his fans for years.
Dayu is also like them.
He could watch his competition videos
for an entire afternoon.
Aren't you also
one of this Larry's fans?
I was just pretending to be.
You told me to get a pen and paper.
I figured you must
want me to ask him for an autograph
so you can check
for any drug-use marks on his hands.
Good, you're quite smart.
Fan, let me.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Sir.
How did he get your attention?
Jiang Shihuo made me realize
the stamp case was too easy
and too small.
It was likely just a diversion.
So I thought the big one
was still to come.
This way.
Then I saw this champion.
You'd think he'd be excited
with his fans around.
But him?
He was holding that trophy tightly.
It was a defensive posture.
Also, the AC here is freezing.
He wasn't wearing much,
yet he kept wiping his sweat.
And he yawned frequently.
With so many of them traveling together,
he could easily go through unnoticed.
Most importantly,
you told me he was red-hot.
It looks like he just
got back from an overseas competition.
He's red-hot now.
It seems the doll provided
accurate intelligence.
The thing is,
why not just tell us directly?
Yeah.
Why not?
Who is this man?
Chief of Passenger Inspection Section I,
Chen Sanhe.
He's the one who got Larry.
You said nothing could go wrong.
Who would know?
Our stuff was sealed inside the trophy.
Why would anyone check there?
You go put this picture
inside the locker
at the transaction site.
We shall also give this Mr. Chen
a little reminder.
Should we put a pause
on our operations?
We can't.
The money has already been paid.
We have to get the cargo in.
I don't think
we'd always be this unlucky.
This time,
they just got lucky.
[Self-service Locker]
[Press to Deposit]
[Password Slip Here]
Please take the password slip.
Please deposit in Locker 14.
Close the locker.
Please retrieve from Locker 14.
[Case Summary]
Last week, we seized
[High-level Mule of an Esport Champion]
a drug smuggling case
[Case Summary
High-level Mule of an Esport Champion]
involving Larry,
or Tan Xiaoming, an esports player.
But on the day of the seizure,
many of his fans were there,
resulting in the immediate exposure
of the case.
Following this, we must
be really careful
and prevent information leaks.
As Tan is a world champion,
the case has drawn widespread attention,
causing an extremely negative impact.
The Binhai Customs
immediately reported this situation
to General Administration of Customs.
The anti-smuggling investigation
has revealed
Tan accidentally took some soft drugs
at a party last year
when he was abroad for a competition
and gradually became addicted.
When he was
buying drugs at high prices
through a middleman in Binhai,
he caught the attention
of a drug-smuggling ring
and later became
their high-level mule.
And the reward was
enough drugs for his own use.
Tan confessed that
the plan was
he would place the trophy drugs
in a locker at this supermarket.
As the case was exposed,
the anti-smuggling unit saw no need
for surveillance there.
But they still investigated the scene.
Unexpectedly,
they actually found something.
Why did they pick such an ugly one?
Take it easy.
I've even received bullets before.
It's okay. Please continue.
Chen,
you have to take this seriously.
This photo was taken
on the day of the seizure,
which means
the ring was there that day,
monitoring Tan.
It could be one of his fans
or some other passenger.
Anyway, this shows
the ring operates very meticulously.
I see.
They are so brazen, Chief.
We had just seized their drugs,
and they
taunted us with this photo.
Sir!
Yes.
It's a woman.
The red cross was drawn with lipstick.
[Found in the Locker for the Trophy]
The shade could be 420.
The mark looks smooth, so it might be
one of the Serafini Floral series,
whose users are
mostly women in their 40s.
I have finished.
Very good.
Which section are you from?
Jiang Shihuo
from Passenger Inspection Section I.
One of us…
Sit down.
Yes, sir.
Jiang Shihuo is doing great.
At least we know
there is a 40-year-old female leader
in this ring.
[Chen Sanhe's Photo]
Besides this photo,
we also found other things that day.
[Dolls]
The doll on the left
was delivered to us
on the day of Tan's case.
The doll on the right
was found in the locker.
The note before
helped us catch Tan.
[Notes; May 7, Drugs]
This time in the locker,
[Clown Mask: Found in the Locker]
besides the doll,
there was also a clown mask.
Got any ideas?
The doll last time
couldn't tell much.
As for the word 'drugs',
what does it mean?
Taunting? Warning?
We can't know for sure.
It seems they were using incomplete
and unclear messages to toy with us.
It means
their next move
may have something to do with this mask.
Then we can follow this lead
and keep investigating
until we get all these clowns.
Right.
Zhang, pull up those two dolls.
[Notes]
[Dolls]
I looked up
the two dolls on the Internet.
[Dolls]
Let's take a closer look.
These brooches
should have been pinned afterwards.
They look like the scepter of Hermes,
the God of Commerce,
in our customs emblem.
So these people
must have done their research,
and they're quite ritualistic.
I have finished.
[Dolls]
Besides the God of Commerce,
Hermes
[Dolls]
also represents the God of Thieves,
protecting all illegal acts.
Using his scepter as their symbol,
to be frank,
makes some sense.
Since they relate themselves to Hermes,
let's use the letter E,
the first letter in Hermes in Greek,
to name them
Group E.
They are not gods.
They are vipers lurking around,
always ready
to breach the customs defense line.
Therefore,
we must catch them.
This is the third doll we've received.
[Perfume Is Poison]
And there's a note along with it.
Three words.
[Perfume Is Poison]
Everyone, use your imagination.
Why is 'perfume' in black
and 'poison' in red?
So many bottles of perfume.
Is it possible
[Perfume Is Poison]
there's a new type
[Note: Perfume Is Poison]
of liquid drug
that's harder to detect?
Sir,
please come with us
to the inspection room.
It seems they're using incomplete
and unclear messages to toy with us.
It means
[Clown Mask: Found in the Locker]
their next move
may have something to do with this mask.
[Face Mask]
Miss, you've got too many face masks.
They exceed the limit, I think.
It's been a while
since we got the last doll.
Have they
backed off now?
It's basically all mules
we're bringing in.
Can't get to the core members
of the ring.
But I am intrigued by that person
who placed the dolls.
Though I can't figure out their purpose.
For example, "Perfume is poison."
That's just too easy.
Perhaps
they think they're so clever.
I don't think so.
Then let's wait
until they slip up.
Shuo.
Open another bottle.
You should stop.
You're already drunk.
Just do as you're told.
I want to get drunk.
That's it?
That's enough.
Using children to move cargo.
Can you reconsider it?
You wanna get on my nerves, too?
You think I want to do that?
I also want to bank some good deeds
for myself down the road.
I'm gonna be a mother someday, alright?
But I have no other choice now.
It's all because of that Chen Sanhe.
How many times has he seized my cargo?
And cargo is money.
I have to earn that money back.
Otherwise,
how can I travel overseas?
How can I visit the Alps?
How can I have your child?
Since we're using children,
let's make it more secure.
I'll get rid of Chen Sanhe.
Have you lost your mind?
We only do smuggling.
We don't kill people.
I'm not that stupid.
I just want to teach him a lesson.
Put him in the hospital for a while.
Sir,
do you think one day
all the criminals and smugglers
in the world will just disappear?
Humans have desires.
Desires result in selfish motives,
which lead to secret agendas.
And that would make people take risks.
I wish for that day, too.
Then I could retire from this job
and be free as a bird.
Is that so hard?
I am free as a bird now.
Why not
join my Fools' Dock?
I'd love to,
but on one condition.
No smuggling in the world.
Are you just making excuses
for your workaholism?
How could there
be no darkness in this world?
Where there are days, there are nights.
Where there is light, there are shadows.
That's why
Cong and I still have lots to do.
Anyway, I'm always here.
I don't have anything fancy.
But if you are tired or hungry,
just come.
There are always noodles for you.
I know.
This...
Is this string about to break?
Hold still.
Don't get burned.
There.
Don't worry. It's gonna be okay.
More drinks?
Want more food?
No.
I'm already full.
We were just chatting.
Hello?
Hey.
No, I'm good.
I just had dinner with my mentor.
Well, is there anything you wanna eat?
I'll bring it to you.
Tell him to come eat here himself.
Why should we bring it to him?
Alright, go ahead.
I'll wait for you in the car.
We'll be your delivery guys.
Hey, what do you want to eat?
Fei.
Some food to go.
Thanks, Fei.
Gotta go. Bye.
Sir!
Sir?
Come here.
Easy, sir.
Sir.
Chen!
Fei, call 120!
Sir, hang in there.
Just hang in there.
Sir.
Hello?
Is it the emergency center?
I'm at Haixian Street,
Xunfeng District, Binhai City.
There's a car accident here.
Sir.
Please come quickly!
Cong,
you've been up all night.
You need to rest now.
Your mentor is awake now.
The doctor said he's okay.
You should go home and get some rest.
Cong, your mentor is injured now.
You have to stay strong.
We need you in our work.
The doctor said
there were more tests to run.
Deng Hongxia and Wang Wenlei
are at the hospital.
Now,
do as I say.
Go home and sleep.
- Chief. - Mr. Zhao.
Have they got the offender?
Not yet.
Guo Cong, fortunately,
you weren't in the car.
Do not panic.
You should learn this from your mentor.
At the scene, besides the suspect truck,
there was another car.
But I don't know
if it had anything to do
with the car accident.
But one thing is certain.
The accident was Group E retaliating.
I saw that doll
with my own eyes at the scene.
Probably.
An investigation has been launched.
You may get questioned in a few days.
Take a look at this.
Yes, this is the doll.
Shen and I have examined it.
Unlike previous ones,
this doll carries no message.
Yeah.
So we believe
this might just be a warning.
Guo Cong,
your Section I has made
the most seizures in these doll cases.
Group E must have their eyes on you.
So,
you must be careful and stay safe.
Yes, sir.
Shen, take good care of them.
I will also send reinforcements
to fully support Section I.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Cong,
we all feel so sorry
for what happened to your mentor.
But no matter what,
you can't bring your emotions into work.
I believe your mentor
would expect the same.
Got it, Deng.
Hello, China Customs.
♪There's a place of simple,
everyday warmth♪
♪A door left open
for the wandering soul♪
♪A humble table still warm with love♪
♪After you've tasted every high and low♪
♪Come home, I'll keep you warm♪
♪Where the days begin and end♪
♪A light still on for the ones
who've lost their way♪
♪An embrace waiting just for you♪
♪Through every passing season♪
♪Even if you return with nothing at all♪
♪Turn around and look♪
♪That door's still open♪
♪A light still burning♪
♪Waiting there for you♪
♪Turn around and look♪
♪Someone's still waiting♪
♪Watching the dusk settle in♪
♪Waiting for the break of dawn♪
♪It's always there♪