[English subtitles are available]
[Luoyang]
[Episode 7]
-Mister, don't leave.
-Lady.
Lady.
-Mister, don't leave. Mister
-Lady.
Liu Ran.
Did Hongyi
do anything inside?
No.
Did he get the answer
to what he wanted to ask?
Not yet.
We'll have to wait for a while.
There'll surely be results.
Let me tell you.
People in this kind of place
are only looking for benefits.
If they don't talk when asked,
they might when bribed.
Hongyi.
Mister, please come in.
Please come in.
I spent some money and got the answer.
Hongyi.
Hongyi, where are you going?
Shen Fei, send Liu Ran home.
Yes, sir.
Your Majesty.
Liu Xiang is still kneeling out there?
Duke of Mount Wind wants to
ask a favor from Your Majesty.
He hopes that Your Majesty will grant respite
[Secretary: Yang Huan]
so that the Bali family would keep some properties
for Baili Hongyi.
Would he be so kind?
Help me understand.
What is Liu Xiang
actually trying to do?
In my humble opinion,
Duke of Mount Wind is doing this
for Chuiliu Corporation.
Half of the properties in Chuiliu Corporation
belong to the Liu family.
The yearly profit accounts for
more than half of the Liu family's income.
[Palace of Immortality]
When Lord Baili was convicted after his death,
Chuiliu Corporation was closed down immediately.
Duke of Mount Wind was not happy about it.
Agent,
we found the mole.
Who is it?
Jianfeng from the Intelligence Services
named Zhao Yang.
He's the owner of a meat shop.
He trained the Intelligence Services'
Saker Falcon to deliver letters to the mole?
You're right.
How about the trained Saker Falcon?
Did you manage to find the person behind it?
It was poisoned to death.
When we found him,
he was about to take the poison.
I am Han Dongqing,
agents of the Intelligence Services.
[Agent of the Intelligence Services: Zhao Yang]
Zhao Yang, from Luzhou.
You moved to the capital during the second year of Chunxiao.
Both parents have died.
A widower.
And you joined the Intelligence Services during the fifth year of Chunxiao
to become part of the agent.
Don't waste your time.
Just kill me.
You alone can't create chaos
in the Intelligence Services.
Tell me who your superior is.
I'll spare your life
and send you out of the capital.
I'll keep my promise.
Is your superior Agents
or Buddha?
Kill him.
Yes.
[The Interior Guard Services]
Why did you summon me here?
What's the order?
Has your body
recovered?
I'm fine.
I asked someone
to prepare some snacks
which you liked to eat when you were small.
Try them.
Want me to feed you?
Look at how you eat.
If father were still alive,
he would have beaten your hands badly.
Drink some water.
Siyue,
both of us
are the last descendants of the Wu family.
After all, we bear
the good name of "Wu".
So act
like a member of the Wu's.
Sometimes, your actions
are totally unacceptable.
I'm an Interior Guard Services.
I don't want people to know
I'm from the Wu family.
You...
The Wu family.
Because of these three words,
no matter what you do,
if you do it well,
that's because you are of the Wu family,
someone must have helped you.
If you don't do it well,
the Wu's is useless.
I don't want to be on par
with those idiots.
Do you mean that the empress is the idiot?
No.
Or King of Jin and the consorts?
You know who they are.
I think you've been an Interior Guard Services
for too long.
You've gone wild.
A few days later,
it will be the Princess Yongchuan's birthday.
You must go.
Sure!
As an Interior Guard Services,
protecting the nobles of the capital
is our duty.
Don't try to be innocent.
Dress up.
Let Princess Yongchuan
find you the right man.
I don't want to get married.
If you don't,
I'll choose a man for you.
I told you, I'm not getting married.
I'm busy
with my job.
You're just
being capricious.
Your marriage
was not decided by me.
It was the empress' idea.
The investigation of the informer
was also instructed by the empress.
You never dared to go
against me in the past.
Is it because of Gao Bingzhu?
Nothing to do with him.
Let me warn you.
Gao Bingzhu is wanted.
His background is questionable.
He's framed!
Framed?
You've interrogated so many criminals.
All of them claimed to be innocent.
He is different.
[Private Mansion of Zhang Silang]
Lady Zhai.
When did you come?
The dishes are still warm.
These two people
have just died.
They both died of stab wounds,
and their time of death is close.
They must have been killed by the same person.
To silence them.
The man is Zhang Silang,
the shopkeeper of Chuiliu Corporation.
He was involved in the theft of the copper in Mount Lian.
Hence, his death
is not a surprise.
But the lady...
She is Lady Zhai,
the concubine of Huang An, the supervisor of the Ministry of Works.
Huang An worked under my father.
Last month, Lady Zhai spilt
a pot of sweet soup.
Then she was chased out of the house by Huang An.
Not long after that,
Huang An died in an accident.
So,
Huang An knew that
something would happen to him.
So he sent his wife,
Lady Zhai, away in advance.
Then, Huang An...
must have told Lady Zhai
something.
That's why she was killed.
One more possibility.
Huang An
could have entrusted something to Lady Zhai.
The instinct of a mortician.
[A Report to the Empress]
I was foolish and ignorant.
For being appointed a supervisor, I am much obliged to the empress.
I shall repay the empress' grace
with my professional skills.
Huang An wrote this.
He knew from the accountant in Mount Lian
that the operation of the copper mine was abnormal.
Lin Zhong.
So this is what
they were trying to inform.
They were trying to feather their nest.
They wanted to embezzle the copper mine in Mount Lian.
And the mastermind
[Liu Xiang]
is Duke of Mount Wind,
Liu Xiang.
[A Report to the Empress]
According to this letter,
the greedy person in the copper mine in Mount Lian
is Liu Xiang, Duke of Mount Wind.
I'm afraid that your marriage
has been a conspiracy since the beginning.
Although our family
is one of the noble families in Heluo,
[Happiness]
the world is unpredictable.
We're in a dangerous position.
One wrong utterance
might get ourselves killed.
He degraded himself
and proposed a marriage to your family.
He gained your father's trust
and got the copper mine in his name.
Now that he's been exposed,
he killed your father.
Why do we have to bootlick the Liu family?
What did you say?
Are you sure that you're not using this marriage
to help you advance in your career?
And made your father a scapegoat
of stealing from the copper mine.
As the Liu family is such a powerful family
that can protect us,
I will be relieved.
Liu Xiang
was really making a good plan as he wished.
My father
died because of me.
This has been planned.
It's not your fault.
You should think of...
how to revenge for your father.
One more thing.
You were the first to arrive here.
It would seem that
you are the one who killed
both of them.
Just like when I was
in your father's study room.
That's why
what you see
might not be the truth.
I need to enter the well for an urgent interrogation.
Lord Gao from the Grand Court said that
anyone...
[Behest]
Open the door.
Yes.
Madam Wu.
Why are you here this time?
[the Well Officer: Wang Dengcheng]
I'm looking for Gao Bingzhu.
You must be kidding.
I'm looking for
the Gao Bingzhu five years ago.
The household registers
have always been managed
by Mr. Unsightly.
He would be the best person
to ask about the past.
Mr. Unsightly.
Where is he?
Wake up!
[The Manager of the Household Register of the Unwelcome Well: Mr. Unsightly]
Who is this lady?
She smells good.
You are the person
who manages the household registers?
I'm here to see you.
This is Madam Wu from the Interior Guard Services.
She has something to ask you.
Please answer truthfully.
Help yourself, Madam Wu.
All the archival documents
are here.
Madam Wu,
help yourself.
For the past few years,
has anyone left the Unwelcome Well?
In the Unwelcome Well,
there are a total of 419 families.
77 people are dead.
There are 23 families
who do not have any descendants.
No one
has left the Unwelcome Well alive in these years.
How about Gao Bingzhu?
I don't know him.
Mr. Unsightly.
I have nothing against Gao Bingzhu.
I'm investigating to find out
how someone who used to
protect the capital
would become like this.
Li,
from what you've told me,
I'm really jealous of you.
[Wine Seller: Bai Lang]
You must be
meeting a lot of dignitaries every day.
It's nothing great.
Let me tell you.
I've been to the palace.
That's great!
Tell me,
is Duke of Mount Wind so busy
that you have to send him everywhere?
It's fine.
It's all about the dignitaries.
Why do you want to know this?
My sister
admires Duke of Mount Wind very much.
She's been curious
how he actually looks like.
She's been wanting to see him.
She can't eat or sleep but thinking about him.
How's Duke of Mount Wind's itinerary
for the coming days?
Can I let my sister
see him secretly?
A jar of old wine after it's done.
Two jars.
Two jars?
Sure!
Great!
Have you got it?
It's not easy to get
Duke of Mount Wind's itinerary for the coming days.
I bribed
his stableman
with three jars of old wine.
Three jars.
Remember that.
Thank you.
Why are you sharpening your blade?
You want Duke of Mount Wind's itinerary...
Bingzhu,
don't be impulsive.
Duke of Mount Wind...
Duke of Mount Wind is not any ordinary man.
He has countless
private soldiers.
Before you can even touch
the corner of his clothes,
you would have been killed.
Do you know that?
What's wrong?
What do you mean?
Thanks for your effort.
I...
You...
You're well-rounded.
Worth it.
Things like this
must not be done by someone else.
I'll do it for you.
The core secret of the Intelligence Services was leaked.
The mole is either Agents or Buddha.
Agents?
Agents and Buddha are the cores of the Intelligence Services.
For the rest of Agents' life,
he will never leave the Palace of Nature.
He can be trusted.
Be careful of what you say.
There have been thefts in the copper mine in Mount Lian.
The coppers for the the Supreme Buddhist Temple project have been changed.
Recently, Baili Yan was killed.
The Intelligence Services
failed to make any prediction regarding these incidents.
They didn't even notice
any clues.
The mole is either Agents or Buddha.
To enter the Palace of Nature,
the procedure is complicated,
and there is record keeping.
If the mole were to contact the outside world,
[Guard of Intelligence Services Lord Chu: An Baitan]
there must be a secret agent.
Zhao Yang.
Zhao Yang is the secret agent.
In public, he was
the owner of the nearby meat shop.
However, upon inquiry,
ten years ago,
he used to be an outstanding Falcon Tamer.
He was the person
who used the Saker Falcon of the Intelligence Services
to leak the secrets.
However,
the mole can't be
just Jianfeng in the Corps,
a Falcon Tamer.
They must have
infiltrated into the Intelligence Services for quite some time.
Master.
Agents and Buddha are the cores of the Intelligence Services.
Now that it has been infiltrated by a mole.
This is an emergency.
Shall we...
Shall we activate the Reclining Buddha Order?
Agent Han.
Once the Reclining Buddha Order is activated,
the Intelligence Services will no longer function.
If we don't get rid of the mole,
the Intelligence Services will be in a difficult situation.
The Reclining Buddha Order?
The Intelligence Services are the empress' spies.
The empress can't be without her spies.
Hurry up.
Be quiet.
Got it.
Follow me.
What are you afraid of?
Great!
Great! Great!
Good job!
It's really bustling in the capital.
Lower your voice.
It's so much better than the Unwelcome Well.
Of course.
Bingzhu.
The red one...
That is sugar-coated haw.
It's delicious.
When I go out later,
I'll buy it for you to try.
We are all the empress' people
earning a living in the capital.
Why do we from the Unwelcome Well
are not allowed into the capital?
Let me tell you.
One day,
I'll make sure
all people from the Unwelcome Well
can live freely in the capital.
They can do whatever they want,
buy anything they want,
just like the people in the capital.
Let's go take a look.
How did you know that I'm here?
There are no tombstones on these seven graves,
and there are no names.
After I went to the Unwelcome Well,
I found out that
the people buried here
were your companions.
It's fine.
When you collect my body in the future,
at least you know the place.
Why didn't you put up a tombstone?
Trying to stay away from calamity?
I've told you.
Stop following me.
In April, the first year of Daqing period,
Gao Bingzhu, the Well officers,
broke the rule with seven people from the Unwelcome Well,
leaving the Unwelcome Well without permission.
They died.
In the same month, the Grand Court locked the Well.
Gao Bingzhu, the Well officers.
died...
Stop investigating me!
This has nothing to do with the case.
I've gone to the Unwelcome Well,
and met Mr. Unsightly.
Apart from the record
which was written
on the file,
no one else knows
what happened that year.
Why are you not saying anything?
You can't say it?
Or you don't dare to say it?
I know what you're afraid of.
All people from the Unwelcome Well
are not allowed to leave the Unwelcome Well without permission.
Seal the well.
Yes.
As a Unwelcome Well officer,
don't you know
the consequences of breaking the rules?
You're right. I'm investigating you.
But I'm not just investigating the case.
I'm curious.
A person who used to protect the capital,
an officers,
how could he turn into someone
who is in a mess!
This has nothing to do with you.
Gao Bingzhu.
What happened when
Xiaowu and the rest died?
You still remember, don't you?
Wait for me.
Bingzhu, wait for me.
Bingzhu, wait for us.
Wait for me.
-Bingzhu, wait for me.
-Wait for me.
Bingzhu, wait for me.
Wait for me.
Higher.
-Higher.
Good!
The wind out here is sweet.
He broke the root.
Help me!
I brought you out
-not to mess things up.
-Help.
Help me!
Bingzhu, help me!
Bingzhu, someone's there.
Go back.
I'll have a look.
Bingzhu.
Listen to me. Leave now.
Meet you at the main gate.
Go.
King Tongyang of that year,
the current crown prince,
was assassinated at the outskirt of the capital.
The crown prince once said that
if it weren't for some people who saved them,
they wouldn't have lasted till aid arrived.
But the people who saved him
vanished into thin air
and never appeared after that.
Gao Bingzhu.
The people who saved him
were you and your brothers
who are buried here.
Right?
Stop it!
I don't know what you had gone through.
I also don't know
what makes you feel difficult to disclose.
You are the only person
who knows what happened that year.
You should tell the truth.
The truth?
Who cares?
Do you care?
You only want to investigate the case.
The Grand Court
and the Interior Guard Services
are just fighting for merits.
They don't care.
But they are also the people of Luoyang.
They shouldn't be dead
for no reason.
Xiaoqi,
someone said you're the people of the capital.
Brothers,
are we the people of the capital?
Brothers...
This is the first time someone said
we were the people of the capital.
But we don't deserve it.
We can only live forever
in darkness in the Unwelcome Well.
Who are the people of Luoyang?
I won't let them sacrifice for nothing.
I will never ever
let them sacrifice for nothing.
This is my business.
What if you die?
If you die,
who will know
these people in the deserted grave?
Who will revenge
for them?
Gao Bingzhu.
You're so selfish.
You have no rights
to allow them to become
nobody.
You'll be wondering,
who cares.
Today,
I swear
in the name of Siyue.
No matter what happened that year,
I'll reward the men of merit punish the felons.
Be it innocent or guilty,
I will give you an explanation.
Protect His Highness!
[King Tongyang: Li Dun]
Father, I'm scared.
Who sent you here?
For Bingzhu, charge!
Mother.
Evacuate this place!
We managed to stop some of the assassins.
While the soldiers were escorting King Tongyang,
they were eager to evacuate
and did not care about us.
♫It's raining in Luoyang♫
My brothers
♫Cruelty is amidst the thunderstorm♫
collapsed one after another in front of my eyes.
I'm left alone
all by myself
♫Bingzhu wants to see the building♫
surviving in this world.
It was my fault
♫Hidden identity♫
for bringing them out from the Unwelcome Well.
I was presumptuous
♫Patiently waiting for his fate♫
and naive.
It's me, Gao Bingzhu!
♫Fog is scattered in the countryside♫
Why did they die
♫Causing the figure to be blurry♫
but I survived?
♫Talking about merits and demerits♫
I should
♫Who will be relieved?♫
face the retribution!
♫The stupa is motley as before♫
Wait for me.
Wait for me. Bingzhu.
Go, Bingzhu.
♫What does this tell us all?♫
Wait for me.
♫Suddenly it says it all♫
Come on.
Go.
They won't blame you.
You are the one
who blames yourself for everything.
They won't be at ease seeing you like this.
Let me tell you.
They've never
left me.
I see them every day
in my dream.
I've seen Xiaowu.
One day, Xiaowu...
was riding a big white horse.
I asked him, "Why are you here?"
When I turned back,
I saw that he brought a mysterious lady.
He told me,
"Bingzhu, I'm getting married soon."
I said, "Great!"
"It's great that you're getting married."
He said,
"I came to inform you."
I said,
"I'm going to attend your wedding."
He said, "Bingzhu,
it's too cold at my place.
You can't take it."
Gao Bingzhu.
I don't want to wake up from my dream.
When I wake up,
it's really hurtful.
I've never had a good day for the past five years.
All of them died because of me.
If they were still alive,
they would have had kids,
and wives.
I'm left alone
surviving in the capital.
I really hate myself.
Stop it.
Please don't...
I...
Gao Bingzhu.
To them, you are a hero.
What you should do now
is to pull yourself together
and revenge for them.
Don't let them sacrifice for nothing.
They shouldn't be
dead for no reason.
The reason I'm still alive
is to revenge for them.
Thanks for talking to me.
It has been five years
since I talked to anyone
about this.
Be strong after this.
This is the closest I've been
to the clues.
You saved them.
No, it's you.
I have nothing to do with it.
But you saved me.
I'll keep my promise.