[English subtitles are available]
[What happened to my fingers?]
[What's with these plasters?]
♫ The falling light ♫
♫ Leads to a road ♫
♫ Longing for you ♫
♫ To be at the end ♫
♫ If the wind started to ♫
♫ Stop chasing the rain ♫
♫ How would the eyes ♫
♫ Fog up? ♫
[I guess things are still the same]
♫ Listen to ♫
[in Pangu and in the real world.]
♫ All the diversity in the world ♫
[I'll never get my first trophy back.]
♫ But time ♫
[My very first]
[AR fighting champion trophy]
♫ Is still flying ♫
[is broken too.]
♫ How many reunions ♫
♫ Does it take ♫
♫ To understand ♫
♫ A touch? ♫
♫ The sea chants for the sky ♫
♫ With the raging of the waves ♫
♫ Make a wish ♫
♫ On an ordinary night ♫
♫ Praying that the red eyes ♫
♫ Are no longer blurry ♫
[The essence in giving gifts
is sincerity.]
[The best gift comes from the heart.]
♫ Look up and watch ♫
♫ The starry sky ♫
[What's so great about
that star moonstone?]
♫ I hold you ♫
♫ With all my love ♫
♫ Can you hear my wish ♫
♫ In the noise? ♫
♫ Perhaps you can understand it ♫
♫ Only if you are ♫
♫ Closer to me ♫
[Episode 15]
[Eight Hours]
You're playing chess?
There you go again.
Why are you back so early today?
I've fully recovered.
Did you notice something at home?
Something?
No.
It must be a pain in
making that vintage trophy.
Of course.
It took me two days
to find the original manufacturer
to customise the wood.
Then, I carved it myself.
You carved it?
What an effort.
The font looks the same
as the original version.
Yeah.
It's exactly the same, right?
I told you.
Some manufacturers said that
the font looks old-fashioned.
They refused to carve it.
Do you know how long I took to...
I only practised carving it
during my free time.
Do you always do this
for other girls too?
Of course not.
Are you sure?
Of course.
You know what?
Back then when my trophy broke,
I cried for so long.
I dropped out of medical university
and insisted to become
a professional gamer.
I had a huge fight with Mom.
She accidentally broke my trophy.
I know
she must have felt bad.
So,
she helped me to
put my trophy back together.
After that, she told me that
she had made up her mind
to support my career in Esports.
But when I finally made it,
she wasn't around anymore.
So this gift
means a lot to me.
Ye Tian.
Thank you
for this precious gift.
I'm glad that you liked it.
Okay.
Guess what I prepared for you?
Have a bite.
See if I improved from last time.
You know what?
When I was little,
I followed Dad to Celeste Group everyday.
Every morning, we'd have
a poached egg for breakfast.
At that time,
he would share
his words of wisdom to me.
He said the more capable you are,
the greater the responsibilities.
Don't be corrupted by wealth.
Don't be subdued by power.
Now I know that
he was trying to motivate me.
He wanted to tell me that
no matter how wealthy you are,
all you need is a poached egg
every morning when you wake up.
I'll give it a taste.
This is the taste I longed for.
Actually, I don't get it most of the time.
I don't understand
the meaning behind Dad's words.
Now I realised that
it was not just about
the taste of poached egg that I like,
but the atmosphere
and memories.
Thank you, Bai Wei.
I found that feeling again because of you.
You're welcome.
In the future,
I'll make this for you everyday.
[Vice Bar]
What's wrong?
Are you upset?
He must be mad at me.
[Le Le, our collaboration ends here.
I will contact you if I can.]
He wouldn't text me first.
I underestimated the enemy.
Le Le.
Don't say it.
I know what you're thinking.
It won't work on me.
Is he really that good
and worth your time?
Do you believe in fate?
I do.
Me too.
Do you know why I came back?
Tell me about it.
I want to live for myself.
I want to get what belongs to me.
I'll help you.
What's next?
Run an investigation on someone.
Sure.
Zhang Hao Cheng.
He eagerly wants to find Ye Tian
before the police.
I want to know why.
I want to know what's the deal.
You want to threaten him?
Of course not.
I want to help him.
I have things to do.
I'll get going first.
Okay.
Call me if something happens.
[Today is the annual tennis tournament]
[of Celeste Group.]
[We welcome your active participation.]
[Celeste Group]
Thank you.
Wei Wei.
Are you participating today?
I don't play tennis.
Why should I?
I'll be rooting for you.
In that case, please cheer me on
as loud as you can.
I've been preparing for a year.
Today is my time to revenge.
Do you have to go that far?
Of course.
It's about pride.
Planning department's pride, get it?
Fine.
Go Mr. Lin!
I didn't expect that
Mr. Lin can play so well.
When Mr. Ye was still around,
it was always a tight competition
between them.
He's good in tennis?
Thank you.
Stay still.
I'll do it.
Thank you.
Miss Zhang is next.
She's good too.
Anyone from planning department?
No one?
Why isn't anyone going?
Because other than Mr. Lin and Mr. Ye,
she's the best.
Me.
Wang Ying Qiao?
You want to enjoy the limelight?
Come here.
You can do it!
Go for it, Xiao Qiao!
You can do it, Xiao Qiao!
Go for it!
What happened?
Is she okay?
Wang Ying Qiao.
Are you okay?
You're not as skilled as me.
Don't blame me.
Swap her out!
Let me do it.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Bai Wei.
Do you know how to play tennis?
How can you swap players
in the middle of the game?
Do I know how to play?
You'll find out soon.
You don't have to do this.
Listen to me.
Go rest.
You forgot what we did back then?
If we were bullied by the seniors,
what would we do?
We'd go against them.
But you're no match to her.
That's a different story.
But I won't let her bully my friend.
Go for it!
You can do it, Bai Wei!
You can do it!
I won the first set.
You'll serve this round.
Sure.
Bai Wei.
Do you even know how to play tennis?
Why don't you forfeit this game?
It's none of your business.
Master of AR Games,
you're just a beginner in tennis.
Beginner,
just give up this game.
I never gave up in anything.
Let's do this again.
[She's good.]
[I underestimated her.]
Referee,
can we take a break?
Why?
I'm having a stomachache.
Bai Wei.
There are no breaks in competitions.
Unless you're injured.
That's right.
Yes, I injured myself.
Where?
Didn't your ball hit me just now?
Are you blind?
Forget it.
I don't want to be calculative.
You may take a break then.
Wait for me.
I'll show you what I got when I'm back.
Please help me.
Please...
Can you help me?
I'll give you some tips.
Okay!
[Your problem now is that]
[you're underestimating yourself.]
[It's not about how well
Zhang Yun Er plays.]
[Remember this, you're a genius in games.]
[You're the only opponent that I respect.]
Can I change court?
Sure.
You can't win anyway.
Go for it!
You can do it, Bai Wei!
You can do it!
Beginner,
you have 15 more minutes.
What do you mean?
Our office canteen will be
opening in 15 minutes.
So you mean
you can beat me in 15 minutes?
Ten minutes will do.
The other five is for you to cry.
Five minutes.
I'll beat you in five minutes.
[I've analysed Zhang Yun Er's
weakness in techniques]
[and defence with you.]
[Firstly, you need to
treat this competition]
[as your usual AR video games practice.]
[Apply the same focus,
speed and strength.]
[Secondly, pay attention to the ball's
underspin, point of fall and angle.]
[If you still lose to her
after giving your very best,]
[maybe I overestimated you.]
She's getting better!
Impressive!
She powered-up!
Wei Wei!
You can do it!
You're doing great, Bai Wei!
She's better than I thought!
Nice one!
Bai Wei!
Way to go, Bai Wei!
What's going on?
She's like a different person now.
Nice one!
Impressive!
Way to go!
She's like a different person.
That's right.
Be careful.
[Remember the time you beat me]
[in that AR video game?]
[If I can beat Zhang Yun Er,]
[you can too.]
[Stay focused.]
[Stay hungry for victory.]
[Come meet me after beating her.]
Is she injured?
Are you okay?
[Ye Tian.]
Wei Wei.
How did you manage to run so fast?
Bai Wei.
You played so well just now.
There's a script meeting later.
Join us later.
Sure.
Wei Wei.
Mr. Lin looks after you a lot recently.
Is something going on
between the both of you?
What?
You're out of your mind.
No I'm not.
Didn't you see his eyes glowing
at the court just now?
You even beat Ms. Zhang.
You were a different person
after the break.
What happened in between?
Mr. Lin wants me to
attend the meeting.
I'm late.
I'll get going.
Wei Wei.
Our initial storyline is about
the disagreement between
King Qiu Yi of Autumn City
and the Sergeant Major.
In the end, they fought
against each other
and caused a turmoil.
Why are we talking about reconciling,
walking hand in hand
and happy reunion now?
Bai Wei is in charge of
this change of storyline.
Please explain yourself.
Mr. Zhang.
Bringing human kindness
into the storyline,
reminding users to cherish
friendship, appreciate loved ones
and promoting positivity.
Is there a problem with that?
The problem is
we're lacking of rivalry.
No sides will be taken,
no battles
and no shops
to purchase weapons and armors.
That means there won't be trades
and profit model.
We can organise online activities.
When I apply a user's perspective
and an objective angle
in preparing this proposal,
brotherhood is more
interesting to me.
It will attract more users.
We think about our loved ones more
during festival seasons.
What do you think?
High in the mountains,
my brothers will miss me
like I'm only missing Cornel
in the greenery.
We can organise a Cornel Festival.
You're right.
We can reconnect long lost friends
so they can reminisce the good old days.
Isn't that great?
Linda.
Are you okay?
Just an old problem.
I'm okay.
I agree with Bai Wei.
Through this Cornel Festival,
we can organise related
theme based activities
and go on a tour.
In that case,
we'll achieve the topic-worthiness,
popularity and profit
that Mr. Zhang wants.
At the same time,
we can promote positivity.
It matches the spirit of the times.
Mr. Lin.
There are no weak troops
under a strong general.
I'm flattered.
Okay.
We'll go as your plan.
Bai Wei.
Let's have a meal together
and talk about the details
of Cornel Festival.
Mr. Lin.
We're done for the day.
Are you trying to exploit your employee?
That's not right.
I'll get going.
You gave her a stone
but she returned it?
You asked her out for a meal
but she refused?
Don't be a busybody.
Are you feeling well?
Yes.
Great.
Why isn't she here yet?
Why is she offline
for so long today?
What is she doing in the office?
Why isn't she here?
What's wrong?
I'm exercising.
Playing hopscotch?
You're bored because
you waited too long?
What are you thinking about?
Why are you so late today?
I'm busy today.
Moreover, Lin Feng asked me out
for a meal just now.
You can't go.
Why?
You're a newbie.
You just joined the company.
You should keep your distance
with the authorities.
If not, people will talk.
Just because of that?
It's for your own good.
We're colleagues.
It's normal to have a meal together.
It's normal.
Come to the Cornel Festival with me.
I designed it.
Let's go.
[Hulu Prefecture]
Hurry up!
Look!
Happy Cornel Festival!
Sir.
Here you go.
There's wine.
It's chrysanthemum wine.
Thank you.
Happy Cornel Festival!
Why are you drinking so much wine?
You're upset?
No.
Really?
Is it because Lin Feng asked me out?
You're jealous?
Are you out of your mind?
I'm just thirsty.
You're lying.
Tell me.
If Lin Feng asks me out
in the real world,
what will you do?
[Cornel Festival starts now!]
What's happening?
Let me take a look.
They're becoming sworn brothers?
Sworn brothers?
Interesting.
Let's see.
They're becoming sworn brothers.
From now onwards, we're sworn brothers
and shall walk hand in hand.
We swear to the Heavens, Earth,
Mountains and Rivers.
We'll stay by each other's side,
and never go against each other.
Interesting.
[Look!]
[This is the Newbie Village.]
[We'll build an assembly hall]
[in the middle of it.]
[Users can come to the assembly hall]
[and become sworn brothers]
[to get a buff.]
[I've already came up
with an affidavit.]
[Come here.]
[It goes like this.]
[Today, Ye Tian and Lin Feng]
[become sworn brothers.]
Great!
[Ye Tian]
The main purpose of
having this festival is
to remind you that
other than the game,
don't forget about your best buddy.
You'll only
appreciate something
when you lose it.
Very well.
That's all from me.
Enjoy yourselves.
Good speech!
Nice one!
Okay.
Don't be upset.
You're hiding this from him
for his good sake.
Am I right?
I planned this Cornel Festival.
You'll love it.
I love it a lot.
I'm at loss for words.
Really?
Tell me.
In the real world,
if Lin Feng asks me out,
what will you do?
[Does this mean that]
[he won't let me go?]
Don't move. Someone from
Heavenly Society is here.
[I see.]
[Great.]
[This is a good assist.]
They're gone.
You're not Bai Wei's assistant,
Zhao Jia Liang.
Who are you then?
Move aside.
President.
I got it.
Magical Marriage Contract?
Will this make things work?
Of course.
This is
the legendary Magical Marriage Contract.
It's a reward I received
after completing a global mission
with three guilds.
Even if users already have
a specific partner,
their marriage will be
automatically cancelled
after signing this contract.
They'll be able to
remarry someone else.
Good job.
You'll get a pay rise.
Thank you.
When you meet that guy later,
let him sign this contract.
What do you think, Dai Dai?
It's a great move!
Bai Wei will be pissed off!
But...
President.
I'm not sure if I should say this.
Spit it out.
You've never seen
his face before.
Why do you like him?
He's a mystery because of his mask.
It's interesting.
It's cool.
I can be imaginative.
What a great speech.
President.
You are the most
admired and respected person.
People are talking about it.
You're the one pursuing him.
Don't you feel sorry for yourself?
What do you mean?
I do what I want.
I enjoy as I please.
Do you think I'm afraid of
people talking about me?
He'll figure it out one day
and stay by my side.
You mean based on
Ye Tian's current situation,
it's unlikely that
he can go online in Pangu?
Yes.
But...
One of the test results
is suspicious.
Tell me.
We found that there's
an abnormal neuron reaction
in his cerebral cortex.
That means his nerve centre
is being controlled.
He also has some anesthesia reactions.
You think someone
gave him anesthesia?
It's just a prediction.
Okay.
You may get back to work.
Li.
Go find the prescription medicine
that stimulates nerve centre
and its purchase history.
Okay.
What's the progress?
Uncle.
To find his exact location,
we need to crack his account's
highest limit of authority.
I need some time.
How long?
A conservative estimate,
I need half a month.
Hurry up.
If he
makes a move inside
and reveals the truth,
none of us will be spared.
I can't do much here in the hospital.
To ensure everyone's safety,
he must be gone.
If that can't happen here,
make it happen in the AR world.
Got it?
Okay, Uncle.
I got it.
I'll try my best.
[What's the progress?]
[To find his exact location,]
[we need to crack his account's]
[highest limit of authority.]
[I need some time.]
[Hurry up.]
[If he]
[makes a move inside]
[and reveals the truth,]
[none of us will be spared.]
[Okay, Uncle.]
[I got it.]
[I'll try my best.]
Zhang Hao Cheng is the one who caused
the misfortune of Ye Tian,
the president of Celeste Group.
The reason why he's going
all out to find Ye Tian
is to destroy his body
and make him disappear completely.
He's keeping it from you
because he needs your help.
He'll push you into the fire pit.
He's hiding the truth from me
because he doesn't want
to drag me into this.
You always find excuses for him.
This is not the point.
No matter what it is,
I don't want him to
make the same mistakes again.
Bai Wei.
I'm going to the nursing home
to visit Tian.
Do you want to come along?
[If I go with him,]
[it means I'm giving him a chance.]
Bai Wei.
I underestimated you.
You joined the company
because of Xiao Lin Lin, right?
Listen here.
Don't try to set your mind on him.
If not,
I'll torture you everyday.
Mr. Lin.
Let's visit Mr. Ye.
I'll drive.
Xiao Lin Lin.
Bai Wei.
You...
Tian has been recovering
in the nursing home.
We haven't announced this
to the public.
I brought you here to take a look at him.
These records are no longer
available in the market.
I purposely
brought them here from his house.
Mr. Lin.
I've prepared everything
as per your order.
Actually,
you don't have to come here everyday.
It's okay.
I'll feel at ease
after visiting him.
Doctor.
I heard there were some employees
who came to visit Mr. Ye.
But they were stopped and
that caused a commotion, right?
Mr. Ye is very close to his employees.
In terms of this, I hope that
you'll be more understanding
and considerate.
That's for sure.
Thank you.
Mr. Lin.
You're so thoughtful
when it comes to Mr. Ye.
People might think that
you're his brother.
[It does seem safer here]
[compared to Bai Wei's house.]
I'll do it.
Leave it to us.
You may leave.
Okay.
Pardon me.
Since I'm here,
I want to do something for him.
You seemed to care about Tian too.
Pangu's second generation
portable connector?
This is just a prototype.
We produced it in a small quantity.
Not in mass production.
By the way,
how did you know about this?
[What a big mouth I am.]
I heard it from Linda.
Tian was the one who
developed this idea.
It works together with
the brainwave monitoring system.
Tian.
An old friend came to visit you.
Do you still remember her?
Do you visit him frequently?
At least three times a week.
I'm afraid that he'll be upset
if he doesn't see me.
Can I visit him frequently too?
Of course.
I guess I was right.
What is it?
I know why you returned
the Star Moonstone to me.
Tian always spoke about you.
I didn't think a lot at that time.
I thought you were rivals,
that's why he acted like that.
You like Tian, right?
Yes.
I've always treated Tian as my brother.
No matter what I do,
I look up to him.
If I want something,
I'll compete with him in fair way.
If I lose,
I'll be happy for him.
But I won't give up easily.
If not,
he'll look down on me.
Am I right, Tian?
What are you trying to say?
I like you, Bai Wei.
I heard from the other colleagues.
Xiao Lin Lin went to have a drink
with her at the food stall.
They were so close.
I heard they even went
to meet Bai Wei's father.
Hi, Uncle.
[You have a boyfriend?]
[Why didn't you tell me?]
[You're disrespecting me.]
[You've never told me that]
[you like me.]
[Yet you don't allow me to
fall in love with someone else.]
[Why did you do that today?]
[Who are you to do that?]
[My friend?]
[Someone I'm seeing?]
Or my lover?