[English subtitles are available]
[Drunken Bamboo]
Try it.
Your favourite is still
the Drunken Bamboo wine.
This wine is so good.
Did I really make it?
I can't believe I'm so incredible.
Sorry.
If I hadn't gone to Greenwood Lane
on my own,
you wouldn't have ended up like this.
[Episode 22]
[Eight Hours]
[Sea of Flowers.]
[Your current session is about to end.]
[You have 15 more minutes
until you have to log out.]
I almost forgot about that.
You sleep.
Wait for me to be back.
I'll come back tomorrow.
Where are you going?
[His consciousness hasn't recovered.]
[If I leave him by himself in here,]
[he might go outside]
[and get caught by elite monsters.]
[That would be troublesome.]
[Sea of Flowers.]
[Your current session is about to end.]
[You have 10 more minutes
until you have to log out.]
[But I can't keep accompanying him.]
[While I'm away,]
[I'll have to find someone
to look after him.]
[But who should I ask?]
[Invincible and those guys]
[might not be able
to take good care of him.]
[I need to find someone with power.]
[It's worth a gamble.]
[She's the only one who can do it.]
[Heavenly Society]
President, you've been offline
for some days.
Now that you're online,
you won't let us catch those two.
This you don't know.
The Heavenly Society almost disbanded
because of them.
Everyone is frustrated.
Like I said, don't bring that up again.
President.
Surprise, surprise.
Speak of the devil.
They just came knocking on the door.
Don't just stand there. Beat them!
Halt!
You're all dismissed.
President, I'll protect you.
Leave.
Leave!
You go.
I go?
Go where?
Impressive, Madam President.
I'm sure you didn't come for nothing.
Just get straight to the point.
I came here
to ask you for a favour.
We're on an epic-level mission.
But it's almost time for me to log out.
So I'm wondering
if it's convenient for you
to help look after him for the night.
I worry that
before I could come back online,
he would already be beaten.
He's skilled.
He doesn't need my protection.
What are you two scheming this time?
It's better to be safe than sorry.
After all, this place
is the safest place in Pangu, isn't it?
So I hope you'll agree to help.
You made me lose face in Pangu.
Now you come asking for a favour.
With no backup at that.
What if I retaliate?
I wouldn't be here if I was scared.
I admire you for your forbearance.
You wouldn't begrudge me
over petty matters.
Am I right?
Fine.
I can help.
But on one condition.
What is it?
He can stay here for one night.
But if he doesn't want to leave,
you can't force him.
Okay, that's a deal.
Be good. Come here.
Stay here and wait for me.
She is our pretty president friend.
I'll come and get you tomorrow.
[Sea of Flowers.]
[Your current session is about to end.]
I don't want to.
[You have 30 seconds
until you have to log out.]
Be good.
Trust me.
I won't leave you by yourself.
Bai Wei.
Bai Wei?
She's gone.
Come sit down.
What's your problem?
We're no strangers.
Do I know you?
Wei Wei.
You're zoning out.
You've been out of sorts
since coming out of the cabin.
What's the matter?
You didn't finish the mission?
I can help you.
It's not that.
It's rare for us to get together
on a weekend like this.
But you
won't talk and just look gloomy.
Very good.
Okay, I was wrong.
That's better.
If only I had a boyfriend like that.
Although each time you wake up,
you don't remember him,
he will profess
his feelings to me every day.
Isn't that romantic?
Yes, it's pretty romantic.
But if one day,
this actually happened to you,
the person you love stands before you
but doesn't recognize you,
you wouldn't find it romantic then.
Sometimes, even if you
stand right in front of a guy,
he doesn't know you.
I think it's better
not to know each other.
I know who you're talking about.
But destiny
cannot be forced.
[Regarding the handover of B1 tomorrow,]
[you don't have to come to the office.]
[I'll go take it.]
I think Xiao Guo is pretty good.
I thank you.
I'm being serious.
Think about it.
Last month, when you forgot
to handover the character update proposal,
he was the one
who secretly did it for you.
Also,
every time you liaised
with the programmers,
you always forgot to mark each character.
He's the one who marked each one for you.
Everyone in the department
knows about this.
No one told you?
I wasn't told.
That's why,
the amount of attention you give
to Zhao Jia Liang
is the amount of attention
Xiao Guo gives to you.
You can't see the gem
that lies before you.
Alright, let's not talk about that.
Accompany me out for some fun
this weekend.
We haven't had an outing
for a long time.
I can't. I don't have time.
I can't accompany you.
But I have something for you.
What is it, Wei Wei?
Remember to use it by this weekend.
It's expiring soon.
A voucher for Muse?
This is very expensive.
Is it?
The restaurant gave it to me for free.
This is a couple set.
If you don't go with me,
who will accompany me?
That's up to you.
Qiao.
When someone loses their memory,
they can recover it back, right?
I don't know.
That's how they play out in the movies.
Are you serious?
You and your wife
aren't pranking me, are you?
It's 2019.
Are you still using the amnesia trope?
We came without notice.
Sorry about that.
Have a drink.
Looks like you really forget everything.
I used to always
make trouble for you and her.
Now that we're sitting here quietly,
it feels a little surreal.
I don't know why.
From the first time I met you,
I've felt
a peculiar familiarity.
You know what?
There are two kinds of people in Pangu.
One wants to forget reality.
The other wants to live a different life.
I'd put myself in the first type.
I wish to forget reality,
and forget about who I am.
In the real world,
I manage my family business alone.
I always have to size up the situation
and know what to do and when to do it.
So to me,
Pangu is a luxury.
At least I can live more recklessly.
But when I met you two,
I realised I was wrong.
Us two?
Yes.
You and Bai Wei.
I realised
I had brought the same stuff
from the real world
into Pangu.
I believed money to be everything.
Before, I thought being a pay-to-win whale
was something to be proud of.
Thank you both
for letting me know more about Pangu
and myself.
Are you feeling sad?
Although I don't quite understand
what you're saying,
I want to believe you're a good person.
I've said a lot about myself.
What about you?
Why did you come to Pangu?
I don't know why I'm here.
Recently, in my mind,
strange voices keep popping up.
They seem to be reminding me.
The world of Pangu and I
have this or that form of connection.
Actually,
I think you are
just like a childhood friend of mine.
With you,
I keep seeing traces of him.
An unknown person keeps appearing
in my mind too.
Really?
Who is that person in your mind?
You're so weak.
Do you have calcium deficiency?
[From today onward,]
[I formally appoint
Bai Wei as my guardian.]
[Any of my affairs outside of Pangu]
will be handled by her.
I will bear all responsibility.
Bai Wei does not need
to bear any legal responsibility.
Bai Wei.
I want details on Bai Wei.
Ms. Wei.
Morning.
Bai Wei.
Wei Wei, good morning.
Morning.
Mr. Lin called you.
Why didn't you answer him?
Never mind it.
Guo Yi Da.
What's the matter?
Why are you going around me?
I... I didn't go round.
Are you free this weekend?
Yes.
I have a voucher for a couple set meal.
Would you like to go?
Yes.
See you this weekend then.
Yes!
Le Le.
Your cousin is in trouble.
What's wrong with Jia Ping?
Ms. Le Le, you must think of something.
Jia Ping and I came to stock up.
We then went to the Internet cafe
to play Pangu.
Now he can't log out.
I dare not tell his father.
Catch your breath.
What do you mean he can't log out?
Where is he?
He's in Pangu.
Jia Ping.
Jia Ping?
We logged out together.
But he said he couldn't do it.
He's waiting anxiously inside.
I don't know what to do.
Where is he in Pangu?
In a forest.
Not far from the main city.
Jia Ping.
Le Le.
What's going on?
Le Le, I can't log out.
What is that supposed to mean?
Where's your bracelet?
Le Le, please don't tell my dad.
You have ideas.
You have to help me.
Save me, Le Le.
I don't want to die here.
How did this happen?
Wait for me here.
I'll look for help outside.
Le Le, come back quickly.
I'll wait here.
Why wasn't the player named
Hero of Jia Village
not discovered sooner?
Sorry, boss.
Where is he currently?
They're in Black Pine Forest.
I'll go and catch them right away.
But, sir,
there's one problem.
What?
Ms. Ding has also gotten the news.
They might have gotten a head start.
That annoying lass.
We can't let her find out
about 2021.
Or else we can forget about
getting Ding Group to invest.
Here's what we'll do.
Find a way to delay her.
And then look for that Hero guy.
To be safe, you'll do it personally.
You must get rid of the witness
before Ding Xiang gets there.
Yes, sir.
Ms. Ding, are you still thinking about
the masked guy?
Ms. Ding.
The company saw a post
on the Pangu member forum.
Supposedly a player
couldn't log out from Pangu.
The name is Hero of Jia Village.
They're still verifying the details.
I knew Zhang Hao Cheng
wasn't telling the truth.
Surely he's hiding something
about Pangu's security risks.
Dispatch the Heavenly Society immediately.
Find that player named
Hero of Jia Village
to verify the situation.
Ms. Ding, we can't dispatch anyone
from the Heavenly Society.
Pangu just released a notice.
Recent violations will be given
severe punishment.
Due to the ruckus
in the main city recently,
the Society has been barred
from any public activity for 24 hours.
Did that just happen?
Yes.
Zhang Hao Cheng.
Jia Ping.
Jia Ping!
I just went offline to look up
Pangu's technology.
How did you...
Jia Ping, wake up.
Wake up.
Jia Ping...
Jia Ping.
Call an ambulance, quick.
Do it.
Go.
Hurry.
It's done.
I was looking for you.
But you weren't in.
Just tell me what it is, Mr. Lin.
I wanted to say,
after we get off work,
perhaps we can go somewhere
to have a chat.
I've been moody lately.
I feel like
in the whole company,
you're the only person who understands me.
I'm sorry.
I think someone else
is more suited to keep you company.
Please excuse me.
Bai Wei.
Mr. Lin.
I think we should keep a certain distance
in the workplace.
If there's anything related to work,
you can get Linda to talk to me.
As for what you said about
me understanding you,
it's probably just a misconception.
Between humans,
it's almost impossible
to fully understand the other.
You and I are no exception.
Bai Wei.
I see you're a pro at playing
with other people's feelings.
I'm not sure what you're saying.
Xiao Lin Lin has given you his heart.
But you broke it, smashed it
and threw it on the floor.
I won't let you
bully the man I like this way.
Yun Er.
Stop talking.
Mr. Lin.
I really think
you don't know yourself very well.
Yun Yun!
I forgot to tell you something.
The proposal you made on the spokesperson
for Pangu's new advertisement
has been approved by the board.
From today onward,
you can carry out your plan
and choose the spokesperson you want.
So from now on,
you have to be more careful
of your reputation.
We are in a professional setting.
Not a place for you to date.
Understand?
What?
Is my courting of Xiao Lin Lin
annoying you, Mr. Zhang?
Is it bothering you?
I don't care about you fooling around.
But I have to remind you.
Don't fall too deep.
You and he won't have a happy ending.
Who said I'm fooling around with him?
I'm not interested
in your power struggle.
Here's a reminder to you.
Whether or not we'll have a good ending,
it has nothing to do with you.
I like Lin Feng!
I love him!
My condolences.
The company
will take responsibility for your son.
We have made
arrangements for his funeral.
Please take a look.
The corneas and pupils
were not responsive.
There weren't
any physiological reflexes either.
He won't wake up anymore.
The test result
said it's due to brain fatigue
that resulted in impaired consciousness.
Celeste Group will pay
for all the medical costs.
Why?
Why are they asking the family
to sign a confidentiality agreement?
The problem wasn't with Jia Ping.
I saw Zhang Hao Cheng's man
in Pangu.
I reminded you.
Do not delete the audio recording
like he asked.
Now it's clear.
There's something wrong with Pangu.
Zhang Hao Cheng is hiding something.
I'm sure he has his reason.
Even now,
you're speaking up for him.
Le Le.
You can go.
I'm fine.
Hao Cheng.
I want an explanation from you.
I was there when Jia Ping was attacked.
Was it your man's doing?
Why couldn't he log out?
Even if he was killed in Pangu,
in real life, he...
Le Le, I'm sorry.
I can't give you
an answer about that right now.
All I can say is,
I'm truly regretful
about what happened to Jia Ping.
You know there are multiple factors
that caused the error.
If I hadn't done what I did,
I
as well as the whole of Celeste
will be doomed.
We have compensated his family.
Consider it...
Consider it my sincere apology.
So Ye Tian's incident
is related to this too.
And that audio recording.
Why?
Why did you lie to me?
Le Le.
I really didn't want to lie to you.
I'm in charge of a huge company
that is Celeste.
I have to ensure the livelihoods
of thousands of employees.
I am responsible to them.
If just because of your cousin's incident,
the whole Celeste collapses,
then...
Le Le.
Here's a question.
If you had to choose one side
between me and Celeste
or your cousin
to be responsible for this matter,
who would you choose?
I just don't get it.
A distant relative
who you've not met in years.
For him,
you'd risk the livelihoods of thousands
of employees.
Would you do that?
I know.
You've suffered these past years.
So have I.
I also know
you're very close with Yun Yun right now.
She trusts you and relies on you.
I plan to come clean with her.
You know it.
In our relationship,
I've always been the weak one.
I don't dare to face it
and I am clueless as to what to do.
I want to be brave for once.
For us, and for Yun Yun.
This way.
Watch it.
Be careful.
Okay, it's connected.
[They even took down Ye Tian's ad.]
Hey, hold on.
Are these things being cleared too?
Yes.
Come on.
I'm planning to turn this
into a resting area for the staff.
Some things are like this record.
To some, they carry meanings.
But to others,
they are merely outdated things.
But even if it's outdated,
Ye Tian's record will always be there.
No one can replace it.
No one.
Even if he never wakes up,
his place in your heart
can't be replaced either, right?
Bai Wei.
I'm the one who approved the renovation.
Sorry.
I forgot the gaming room
was your favourite.
You won't be able to spar
with Xiao Lin Lin
in this place again.
That's great.
Lest someone get the wrong idea.
Xiao Lin Lin.
She doesn't see your good,
but I do.
Don't be upset.
Let's go.
Here.
I'll put it on for you.
You know what?
I had bought this
before you went abroad.
But somehow,
I missed the chance to give it to you.
So you left
for five years.
Le Le, now that you're back,
I promise to make up for our past.
I'll make it up to you.
Please give me a chance.
Help me secure Celeste together.
Okay?
[Heavenly Society]
Ye Tian.
Bai Wei.
I'm back.
I did my part. I'm giving him back to you.
Is that all?
Yes.
We talked for a long time last night.
Even when he's lost his memory,
the only thing he remembers is you.
I have to say I admire you.
In order to keep your beloved safe,
you were willing to hand him
into the enemy's hands.
I'd never be able to do the same.
I've been utterly defeated
in the "stealing your couple" game.
However,
I won't lose without consequence.
You can have this top quality divine ring.
Take it.
Consider it a wedding gift.
Be good to him.
Thank you, Ding Xiang.
When can I take off the mask?
I've been wearing it a long time.
Keep it on for now.
Master, we're here to visit you.
I've mastered the moves
you taught me.
Let me show you.
What are you doing?
Master, you attacked me
with a hidden weapon.
Was it to test
the speed of my reflexes?
Just you wait.
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
You...
Don't be scared.
Are you all right?
I'm okay.
Release it, okay?
Even if you're my master,
you can't simply hit my wife.
Release it.
Ouch!
Show me. Let me see.
It hurts.
It hurts?
It's just a boo-boo.
Let me blow it for you.
Is it better?
Don't be scared.
What's wrong with your master?
It's okay.
It's okay now.
Water-fried egg.
You remember?
The most important person.
Water-fried egg.
Most important person.
What's the matter?
It's okay.
Don't think anymore.
No need to remember.
Don't think.
It's all right.
Give it a rest.
[Tracking location]
The account you are monitoring,
GM 001,
is no longer in Misty Mountain.
No activity is detected.
He managed to escape
from the recycle bin.
Not bad.
But it's useless.
I will find you no matter where you go.
I'll show you
that no one is irreplaceable.
Sorry, Dou Zi.
I hope he didn't hurt you both.
It's okay, Ms. Wei.
I understand.
But Master doesn't remember you.
You must be heartbroken.
But don't let it get to you.
This is how it is looking after
a sick person.
I'm used to it.
When a person is sick,
they become agitated.
While Ah Xiu's doing his rehabilitation,
he had trouble with certain moves.
Then he'd take it out on me.
Dou Zi.
You truly are a kind young lady.
Just he waits.
Ms. Wei, we'll keep a record
of all their faults.
Once they're better,
we'll make them pay.
Yes, we'll make them pay.
Ye Tian.
Don't be scared.
I won't let anyone hurt you.
Even if the whole world
can't be trusted,
you still have me.
Your condition may improve.
But you could also
never recover your memory.
But no matter what,
I will stay by your side forever.
Even if you never remember me,
I'll find a way
to make you fall in love with me again.
[I will find you no matter where you go.]
[I'll show you]
that no one is irreplaceable.
[Once this whole thing is settled,]
[I'll tell Yun Yun about us.]
I trust that Yun Yun
will support our decision.
[I, Wang Le Le,]
am not going to die by a man's hands.
[Be it the real world,]
[or the world of Pangu,]
[as long as we're together,]
[that's all that matters, right?]