[English subtitles are available]
[This is a gift for you.]
[Oh, no!]
[If I die here]
[and can't go offline,]
[so the ending will be…]
[Who is it?]
[Who sent them here?]
[Zhang Hao Cheng.]
[Episode 29]
[Eight Hours]
Ding Xiang.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to do this.
However, I know
your personality.
I'm pretty sure you wouldn't
have a sit-down with me.
Not to mention
the fact that you are now
a victim of 2021.
[I really have no choice.]
[Goodbye.]
[I hope we have the opportunity]
[to work together again in the next life.]
How are you?
I told you I had a bad feeling.
Who are you?
Her blood count is depleted.
We can stop the attack on her.
Retreat!
-Ding Xiang.
Zhang Hao Cheng.
They are Zhang Hao Cheng's men.
He has found this out.
They are all his men.
You must stop him.
Don't let other victims of 2021
in Pangu be like me.
You must keep Pangu
perfect all the time.
Why
didn't I recognize you at first?
Ding Xiang.
-Ding Xiang.
It's all because of me.
I have been thinking
if we had both gone there sooner,
would Ding Xiang be saved?
You are not to blame for this.
Moreover,
she's not actually dead yet.
However, she couldn't go offline.
Isn't dying in Pangu the same as...
It's true that she couldn't go offline
but
she was online in Pangu.
This means that Pangu's server system
will automatically record
her online information.
I'll get out of here
and solve the issue of 2021 completely,
then come back
and complete her chain of information
so that she can be resurrected in Pangu,
then we can save her.
Really?
Yes.
By tomorrow, as planned,
I'll be able to enter the core area.
[Even if I don't use
the company's intranet,]
[I still can't access it]
[using other common methods.]
Lin Feng,
what are you hiding?
[After so much preparation,]
[I can finally enter the core area.]
Hello, Bai Wei.
Bai Wei.
Where are you going?
Let's go.
Get on the bus.
Where… Where are we going?
Hurry up and go.
No.
No way.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
Get on the bus.
I still have something to do.
Let's go.
No way.
Where are we going?
There is a gag order from the company.
I can't tell you.
Bai Wei, where are you going?
Have a seat.
Sit here.
Sit down.
[This is probably a team building]
[for members of the core team.]
[I can't believe I forgot about this.]
[I wonder where we are going this time.]
[Oh, no.]
[If we're going to Paradise Island,
it will be troublesome.]
[I don't think there is
a Pangu experience cabin there.]
[If I can't go online in time,]
[Bai Wei will be in danger.]
Where are you going?
I have something to do at 8pm.
I have to go home.
You can't.
You're one of the main figures this time.
No way.
I really have something to do.
It's not up to you.
I hardly got a chance
to dress up like this.
Yes.
It must be fun over there.
I think so too.
You are so reluctant to
go on a team building trip?
I didn't have anything ready.
You don't want to make everyone unhappy
just after you've joined
the core team, do you?
Celeste is a group.
It has its own measure of loyalty.
You will understand
when time goes by.
But as time goes on,
we can understand those
we didn't understand before,
while those we thought we knew well
gradually become harder to understand.
Ms. Zhang,
when is your wedding day with Mr. Lin?
Has the date been set?
Will the company throw a party for you?
Lower your voice.
Ms. Zhang,
why did I hear that
Mr. Zhang doesn't approve of
your relationship with Mr. Lin?
Whether he approves or not,
he can't stop me from
being with Xiao Lin Lin.
There will be a mystery party
on the island tonight.
You must all attend.
There will be a great show.
What show is that?
It's a secret.
You'll see what happens then.
He didn't give me any clues.
There are so many firewalls.
Who knows what you wanted to show me?
However, you're always like this.
You always kept everything from me.
You bought me milk,
but you didn't ask me if I liked it.
[Zhao Jia Liang]
Hello, Zhao Jia Liang. What do you want?
I… I just… I just want to tell you that...
You… Don't just...
Don't just focus on
taking care of Guo Yi Da,
you should eat when it is time to eat,
and sleep when it is time to sleep.
Alright, I got it.
I've got to hang up now.
Bye.
[I'm leaving.]
[See you when I see you,]
[Zhao Jia Liang.]
[Didn't he say we wouldn't
be seeing each other again?]
[It used to be so ferocious.]
[Why does it hide
when I see it this time?]
[I remember the last time it saw me,
it immediately avoided me as well.]
[Is it really true that I can beat it,]
[as Xiao Liang said?]
Brothers,
come on and carry it on!
Later, I will give you a raise.
Alright.
Xiao Qing,
this area is our world
that I have developed for you.
When you come to Pangu, you will find out
that your husband
is a successful man.
Ordinary but great.
Bai Wei?
Bai Wei!
Don't you ever bother us again!
We don't want to play with you anymore.
We are all ordinary workers.
Stop!
Bai Wei, what are you doing?
Hurry up and get away!
Look at the ground.
What is this?
What… What is this?
Is it a pet?
It's so cute.
No.
Listen.
Don't fool with me again...
[How could this happen?]
Get over here
and stand behind me.
This… This is…
Try and see if you can go offline now
Offline?
I am asking you to try and go offline now.
Hurry up.
Where is my bracelet?
Why can't I go offline?
This is not scientific.
You're in hot water.
We have arrived.
Everyone, pay attention.
We are about to reach Paradise Island.
Let's
enjoy the sun and sand then!
That's great!
Let's go.
Linda,
are there experience cabins on the island?
Supply is tight even in urban areas,
not to mention the suburbs.
I'm sorry, I have a stomach ache.
I'm having my period.
I'll go back first.
You have asked for leave
every week this month
because of your period.
What's going on?
I'm really having a stomach ache.
I forgot to turn off the stove
in my house.
I really have to go back.
The road back to town is so jammed now.
It's too late even if you go back now.
I'm sorry.
I am really not ready
for the team building.
I'm not going.
Goodbye.
Hold on.
Don't come back to the core team
if you leave now.
This is just a team building
but you can't even get used to it.
The core team doesn't need such people.
Bai Wei.
You don't have to worry
about the experience cabin.
I promise you,
I'll definitely get a few over.
Okay?
Xiao Lin Lin.
I have something to tell Bai Wei.
Let's go.
Bai Wei,
I want to surprise Lin Feng.
Get straight to the point.
When the time comes,
I would like to ask you a favour.
What is that?
Actually, I always know in my heart
that Xiao Lin Lin likes you.
I told you that…
Let me finish my sentence.
Xiao Lin Lin has always liked you
and it's the same even now.
I have no feelings for him.
It's you who has misunderstood.
A woman's intuition is very accurate.
I could tell you're his type of girl
from the first moment
he laid eyes on you.
That's why
I've been against you all along.
I've made it clear to you.
I don't have any thoughts about him.
It's you who's overthinking it.
Actually, what I want to say is,
even if you like him,
Xiao Lin Lin still won't choose you.
Because he is the kind of person
who separates his feelings
from his career very clearly.
He will only choose someone
who is beneficial to him.
For example,
me.
However, I hope
that one day he will look at me
with the same sparkle in his eyes
as he looks at you.
As long as there is no interference,
I will definitely succeed.
If it goes well for me,
it will go well for you at work.
Do you understand?
Okay, I got it.
I will stay away from him in future.
Can you please do me a favour?
I want you to urge them
to get the experience cabin
here sooner.
If you can guarantee it,
I can tell you one more secret.
Alright.
What is the secret?
Lin Feng may like a dominant girl.
[I don't like gentle girls.]
[they must be indecisive and sloppy.]
[My girl must be sassy,]
[independent, assertive and intelligent.]
[She has to be unique in this world.]
[Aren't you afraid
that you two will fight?]
[I'm not afraid.]
[I will certainly]
[tolerate her and spoil her.]
[I will spoil her to the max.]
[I'll make her realise]
[that there is no one in the world but me]
[who can tolerate her]
[so that she can't leave me.]
A dominant girl?
Is that so?
How did you know about it?
I guessed it.
You guessed it?
Xiao Lin Lin.
What's wrong?
What are you talking about?
It's a secret.
Secret?
Go for it!
Zhang Yun Er.
Bai Wei.
Why don't you get in the water
when you come to Paradise Island?
I don't have a swimsuit with me.
Tell me about the experience cabin.
It's okay if you don't have a swimsuit.
The company has provided it.
It's all free of charge.
I'm asking you about the experience cabin.
I don't know.
However,
I know someone who knows about it.
Lin Feng.
Lin Feng knows about it.
You can ask him.
[Horse's owner, Ye Tian]
[Horse information]
[Horse's owner, Lin Feng]
Lin Feng,
when will the experience cabin arrive?
8pm.
What's wrong?
Nothing, I'm just asking.
This horse is generally
not close to anyone,
except for me and Xiao Tian.
When we were in the old mansion,
Simba also seemed to be familiar with you.
This is strange.
Why does it seem like
all of Xiao Tian's pets
are close to you?
Maybe I have a connection with animals.
I'm leaving.
Bai Wei,
I always feel that
there is an inexplicable closeness
between us.
It's like I've known you for years.
Is that so?
I don't feel that way.
Can you ride a horse?
Let's race.
The loser will accept
one condition from the other side.
Alright.
Whoever reaches
the starting point first wins.
I'll give in a bit.
I'll say one,
you say two,
I'll say three.
Your way of competition
is exactly the same as Xiao Tian.
Really?
What a coincidence.
One, two, three, run!
Hey!
I won.
I also missed it a little bit
in my previous match with Xiao Tian.
I didn't expect you
to be such a good rider.
I practised it when I was a kid.
I lost.
You may say the condition.
My condition is
get away from me.
Did I do something wrong?
Nothing.
Bai Wei.
What do you think of Paradise Island?
Not bad.
This island was first discovered
by Xiao Tian.
He bought the island
as a site for the core team.
We probably don't even come here
once a month.
In fact, I couldn't understand
his decision at that time.
He probably didn't know
where to spend his money.
Perhaps it's because he was born
with a golden spoon in his mouth
and was living a wealthy life,
and I am
the exact opposite of him.
I grew up in a poor family.
My parents saved money
to pay for my education.
If I had not received a full scholarship,
I would not have been able
to study abroad.
So sometimes I think that...
So are you jealous of him?
Jealous?
Maybe it's because of jealousy.
That's why I want to be
the person in charge of Celeste
in my own way.
I want the whole world to know that
there is not only Ye Tian in this world,
but also me, Lin Feng.
You did it.
You got what you wanted.
Bai Wei,
you will support me, right?
Do you forget
that you lost?
My condition is that
you are to stay away from me.
I'm sure you'll manage Celeste well.
But after Ye Tian wakes up,
what will happen to you?
I believe that even when Ye Tian wakes up,
he will not be able to change anything.
Really?
I'll keep Celeste
under my control very well
and you
will be my woman.
Lin Feng,
Celeste has the surname Ye.
And you, Lin Feng, has the surname Zhang.
[Bai Wei,]
[I must get you.]
In fact, the situation is not so bad.
I don't want to die.
Why me?
Ms. Wei,
if you know this stuff,
you must have a way to save me.
Ms. Wei,
I'm just a security guard.
I'm nothing out there.
I've changed jobs
about four or five times.
Pangu is the only joy in my life.
Unexpectedly, great joy
begets great sorrow.
Ms. Wei,
it's all my fault before.
I shouldn't give you a hard time.
Please save me.
You are a man. How can you cry?
Hold it back.
I can't control it.
If you keep crying, I won't save you.
Stand up.
Hurry up.
For your condition,
you still can be saved,
this is the first thing.
Second,
you are always so arrogant
in Pangu.
Your technique and control aren't bad.
Why do you always
work as a security guard?
Is there any other way out for me?
Of course.
Wait until it's over,
just join my team.
You can start by joining C Echelon.
If you work hard,
you should still be able to win
an intercontinental tournament
and win glory for the country.
Thank you, Ms. Wei.
Get up!
Ms. Wei,
I'm in such a situation.
How can I get back to normal?
You can certainly be saved.
It's just that the person
who can save you is not me.
The person who can save you
will go online in a moment.
He is also an acquaintance of yours.
He should be online soon.
Now you can rest easy.
It is Mr. Li's idea
to make the Paradise Island clubhouse
the 42nd experience store of Pangu.
I've heard there's a
welcome ceremony tonight as well.
Welcome ceremony?
Welcome the new members of the core team.
This time, it will be held in Pangu.
This is creative.
This is a surprise for the new members.
[Cracking the code]
200708.
[Password is correct, entering the system]
[Celeste Group]
20070821 Wang Ying Qiao.
My date of birth.
Your password is my birthday.
Guo Yi Da,
you are such an idiot!
Big fool.
Guo Yi Da is a big fool!
All ready?
All accounts on the experience cabins
have been locked.
As soon as the banquet starts,
whenever someone goes online,
the account's activity
will be permanently recorded
by the experience cabin.
In other words,
everyone on the island
is already within our monitoring range.
Can you be sure that the person
who did the operation
was from within the group?
Not only that,
his authority and skills are quite high.
It's very easy to track him down.
No wonder you've adjusted
the list of people coming to the island.
Those who are highly skilled
and authoritative
are all present at this banquet.
Good.
As soon as the banquet starts,
let's get them all in one go.
Well, we'll see.
It's opened,
but there is nothing important.
Another group chat of engineering geeks.
CCTV?
Paradise Island.
It's Paradise Island.
I knew
Lin Feng took them
to Paradise Island with bad intentions.
Wei Wei.
Wei Wei is on Paradise Island.
[Wei Wei.]
[Do not log into Pangu
with the experience cabin.]
[Lin Feng is monitoring.]
[The trip to Paradise Island is a trap.]
Thank you.
[Do not log into Pangu
with the experience cabin.]
[Lin Feng is monitoring.]
[The trip to Paradise Island is a trap.]
[Did he read the message?]
I really didn't see anything.
Bai…
[No phone calls.]
[Crack the code immediately.]
[I managed to delay]
[the time limit
for the shield anti-cheat system.]
[However, I must log into Pangu
by 12am at the latest.]
[Otherwise, Bai Wei will be in danger.]
Bai Wei.
What a coincidence.
Let's go.
It so happens that
we are going online into Panga.
Let's go.
[I managed to delay]
[the time limit
for the shield anti-cheat system.]
[However, I must log into Pangu
by 12am at the latest.]
[Otherwise, Bai Wei will be in danger.]
Crack the code. Crack...
How do I crack it?
Didn't you keep saying that
you wanted to log into Pangu?
How come you're not
in a hurry now?
[Going online now means
throwing myself into the trap.]
[I need to think of a way.]
My stomach aches.
I have to go to the restroom.
There is a restroom downstairs.
You can use the restroom there. Let's go.
Just in case my stomach acts up
and I can't control myself,
this won't be nice, will it?
Then you shall
walk slowly.
I'll walk by myself.
[Looks like I'll have to
play a sympathy trick.]
What's wrong?
Are you alright?
Don't touch me.
Bai Wei.
Are you alright?
Get up first.
Call the doctor.
Are you alright, Bai Wei?
I'm fine.
Call the doctor to the playroom.
[I have gone too far this time.]
Mr. Lin,
Ms. Bai Wei's foot
was only slightly contused.
It is nothing serious.
She will be fine after taking a break.
Alright.
Good work.
Thank you.
I'm sorry
to spoil everyone's fun.
What are you talking about?
It doesn't have to be today.
We'll make it up for you tomorrow.
Right, Lin Lin?
Alright.
Bai Wei is fine now.
I know you care about her.
Thank you for today.
Get back to your work.
Wei Wei, have a good rest.
Why don't you all go back first?
I'll just rest for a while.
Alright then.
Have a good rest.
We'll get going now.
Alright.
Let's go, Xiao Lin Lin.
Xiao Qiao, how is it going?
Stop rushing.
I'm working on it.
You haven't broken through
the inner defences yet?
[Your private message is now being sent]
[I'm sorry.]
[Private message receiver is not online.]
[Please be patient.]
[He should have been
off work a long time ago.]
[He's going to the core area today.]
[Has something happened to him?]
[Don't scare yourself.]
Ms. Wei,
who are we waiting for?
Will he go online?
You may
go offline and ask him.
This is a matter of life.
If he doesn't go online for one night…
Stop talking rubbish.
I didn't say anything.
Isn't it normal for him
to not be online for a night?
I dare you to say that again?
[Dear player,]
[your online time ends in three hours.]
[Please be ready
to go offline in advance.]
Anyone can be offline,
but not him.
[Dear player,]
[your online time ends in three hours.]
[Please be ready
to go offline in advance.]
[Wei Wei.]
[Look what I've brought you.]
[You're finally back.]
[What time is it?]
[9pm.]
[What is the time you promised to return?]
[8pm.]
[Are you wrong?]
[Yes.]
[It's good that you know you're wrong.]
[Sit down.]
[You're not angry anymore?]
[How can I not be angry?]
[I've cooked a table full of food]
[and it's getting cold.]
[What time did you promise to be back?]
[You must keep your promise
in future, okay?]
[I got it.]
[Remember what you said.]
[You're so good to me.]
[What are you doing?]
[It's time to eat.]
[Let go.]
[I don't want.]
[Naughty boy.]
[Do you like it?]
[I remember you telling me that]
[you haven't had a delicious cake]
[in a long time.]
♫ Inviting the moon to drink with me ♫
[It turns out that]
[you were…]
♫ And asking the sky ♫
[That's right.]
♫ About the come and go of sorrow ♫
[I have generated it with holography.]
♫ With a frown on my face ♫
[Today is the one month anniversary]
♫ My heart and soul are broken ♫
[of our meeting in Pangu.]
[How can I forget it?]
♫ The autumn wind can't disperse ♫
♫ The fire ♫
[That's more like it.]
♫ Of the border pass ♫
♫ From the land of war ♫
[I'll feed you.]
♫ I wonder how many people
will be able to return home ♫
♫ Some people are jealous of my untamed ♫
♫ High-profile attitude ♫
♫ They say ♫
♫ I'm a big talker and ♫
♫ Mock me ♫
♫ The ancients, however,
said that young people are awe-inspiring ♫
[Is it tasty?]
♫ And that young men ♫
♫ Can achieve great things ♫
♫ I want to fight with my sword ♫
♫ To pacify the chaos of the world ♫
[You take a bite too.]
♫ Wait until ♫
♫ The world is peaceful ♫
♫ Let's drink and have fun ♫
♫ That's what I really want ♫
♫ Under the moon with wine ♫
♫ Awaiting you in the flowers ♫
[What are you laughing at?]
♫ An invitation card ♫
[Nothing.]
♫ Is inferior to the moon in the cup ♫
[I just laughed at myself]
[because I felt that I was like
a resentful lady today.]
♫ Lilies bloom and fade ♫
[I cooked a full table of food]
[and waited for my husband
who came home late.]
♫ Humans are born and die ♫
[I think that's good.]
♫ Watch the sword in my hand ♫
[That's how I can feel secure.]
♫ As it slashes through the bright sky ♫
[Feel secure?]
[Are you a masochist?]
[How can you call me a masochist?]
♫ Under the moon with wine ♫
[It makes me feel at home.]
♫ Awaiting you in the flowers ♫
[To be frank,]
♫ An invitation card ♫
[I haven't felt this way in a long time.]
♫ Is inferior to the moon in the cup ♫
[Wei Wei,]
♫ Lilies bloom and fade ♫
[actually, what I want to tell you
is that]
♫ Humans are born and die ♫
[you don't have to worry about me.]
[No matter how long I'm away,]
♫ Slash a brighter world ♫
[I'll be back on time.]
♫ On my behalf ♫
[You don't have to worry about me]
[because I always remember that]
[there is someone who loves me]
[waiting for me at home.]
Ms. Wei,
how much longer do we have to wait?
Be patient.
He'll be here for sure.
Anyone can be offline,
but not him.
Because he knows
someone is waiting for him at home.
[If you do see him tonight,]
[please tell him]
[not to blame himself.]
I don't blame him.
[And please tell him that]
[I love him.]
[I love him very much.]
Yun Er,
will you marry me?
[If you and Yun Er
have a child in the future,]
the surname of that child
must be Zhang.