[English subtitles are available]
This one's good.
This looks intricate.
Thank you.
Little Lin Lin.
I prepared a birthday cake
specially for you.
Let's go eat the cake.
Nice.
Bravo!
♫ Happy birthday to you ♫
Happy birthday!
Make a wish, Little Lin Lin.
Thank you, everyone.
Mr. Lin must have made a wish related
to Pangu, right?
No way. He probably wished
to get a girlfriend sooner.
Now, now.
What about we play a game?
Something thrilling.
How about Mafia?
We can play while we eat the cake.
What about it?
-Good idea.
-Sure.
Sure.
I'm really happy
you came today.
Don't you want to know
what I wished for just now?
A wish won't come true if you reveal it.
Even if I said nothing,
you probably would've guessed.
My wish
is related to the day
we visited Xiao Tian.
You like him, don't you?
Yes.
I will compete with him fairly.
If I lose, I will give him my blessing.
But I won't give up so easily.
I guessed it long ago.
Right after Xiao Tian got hurt,
you applied for a job at the company.
It wasn't because you wanted
to do cross-border learning.
It was because of him.
You wanted to be in a place
where he stayed for a long time.
So that you could maybe feel his presence.
Am I right?
[Maybe it's time I told him.]
[Episode 20]
[Eight Hours]
It's so trendy.
It's night time, close your eyes.
"Killer", please open your eyes.
Tonight, you have to kill him.
Close your eyes.
Lin Feng.
Actually...
[You are the Killer.]
It's not me.
It's definitely you.
Who else could it be but you?
Linda.
Linda!
Miss!
What happened?
Is she alright?
Why did this happen?
What's going on?
Linda.
Get the doctor, quick.
What happened?
She fainted.
Dr. Luo.
Mr. Lin.
Please clear the space.
Why did she suddenly faint?
Call an ambulance.
The doctor is here. She should be safe.
Linda.
What's happened?
We were over there playing Mafia just now.
We heard a scream.
We then rushed here
and found her unconscious.
She suddenly fainted.
She's under too much stress
and has not been sleeping well.
It resulted in temporary loss
of consciousness.
She needs immediate treatment.
But I don't have my doctor's bag.
Hold on. I have something.
We should get her to the hospital.
What's going to happen?
What's this medicine?
This is Colami.
Try and use it.
It should help.
This drug can activate the hypothalamus.
It will stimulate brain activity
in the nerve center.
But if misused,
it may become addictive or cause numbing.
Mr. Lin.
This drug is not available on the market.
How did you...
When Pangu was undergoing
prototype testing,
in order to test
the user's EEG while connected,
I asked a friend to procure it.
I see.
Give it a try.
Okay.
[He's lying.]
[During Pangu's prototype testing,]
[he and I were the only ones present.]
[We did not use]
[any drugs related to neuro-suppression.]
[I get it now.]
[My experience cabin]
[had a voltage overload,]
[but I managed to come alive in Pangu.]
[It's because someone]
[had injected
a nerve-inhibiting drug into me.]
[Although the cabin malfunctioned,]
[it became a blessing in disguise]
[because my consciousness was paralyzed.]
[I became a piece of code
in the system]
[and managed to stay alive.]
[Lin Feng, why did you lie?]
[It's all wrong. I was wrong.]
Here.
Careful does it.
She was fine a minute ago.
Now look at the state she's in.
Hopefully she's okay.
It's fine now.
Don't worry too much, guys.
Bai Wei, what was it
you wanted to say just now?
Okay.
Let's all go in and continue the game.
Come on, let's go.
It was nothing.
Let's go.
How about
we go in and play Mafia too?
It's fine.
I'll pass. You guys go ahead.
Let's go.
Do you enjoy "killing" that much?
[Boss.]
[Previously,]
[when we did a physical check on Ye Tian,]
we noticed he was injected
with anesthesia.
[The lab did further testing.]
A certain chloral hydrate
and propofol deposits were found
[in the subcutaneous tissue
of the left arm.]
[I've checked.]
[Someone from the group
secretly procured ]
[anesthetics used only in laboratories.]
[That person was...]
Lin Feng.
[That's right.]
Things just got more interesting.
[Boss.]
Has he been trying
to disrupt our plan this whole time?
[That's why Ye Tian didn't die for good.]
No.
There is another possibility.
We happened to...
Collide.
What?
Lin Feng lied to you?
Why would he do that?
I don't know.
But there's no good reason.
Is it because
of the Colami he had?
That's why you think he's the culprit.
The drug cannot be bought on the market.
Moreover,
nobody else but me
has free access to the testing hall.
If it wasn't him,
why did he lie?
I know where to procure Colami.
If I can prove
that he did not buy the drug
before the incident,
will you then believe he's innocent?
I'll do it right away.
He is your closest friend.
The only thing I can do now
is to reassure you.
I know
this is very important to you.
I don't want you to doubt the whole world
just because of this matter.
Over here.
Watch him.
Got it.
Go to Haohan Street.
Meet me there. It's urgent.
Sorry.
That darn Xiao Liang.
Why isn't he here?
[This should be the place
we visited before.]
Ms. Wei.
This is not a place you should be at.
Promise me
you won't come here by yourself.
This Shencao Pharmacy
dares to sell drugs
that is banned everywhere else?
Of course not.
They're selling them disguised
as health supplements.
Moreover,
they also have
the synthetic drug, Colami.
Colami?
[Shencao Pharmacy]
I think I've heard of it before.
[It's a record of their sales.]
[Colami.]
[Lin Feng.]
[Ye Tian was right.]
[It really was him.]
We saw you entering the shop
and something seemed fishy.
Speak. Who sent you?
Why are you here?
Does this place have a toilet?
You look like a toilet to me.
There's none.
I'm sorry. I got to the wrong place.
Hey!
Open up!
Open the door!
Which one of you leaked information?
Both ends of the supply channel
are kept secret.
The other party must have sent the spy.
She looked suspicious
so we followed her.
If she gets the records,
we'll be in trouble.
Sir, was it okay to jab her with this?
If she can survive it,
then she's got a long life.
If she doesn't,
let's just say she's got a weak heart.
She seems somewhat familiar though.
You call any pretty lady familiar.
Come on. Let's go get the key.
We'll check on her later.
[2nd generation Pangu portable connector.]
Bai Wei!
Bai Wei.
Are you all right?
Bai Wei, talk to me.
I was injected with something.
I'm so sleepy.
You can't sleep. You must not sleep.
Stay awake.
You were probably injected with narcotics,
so your form cannot
be materialized in Pangu.
You must not sleep.
If you sleep,
you'll disconnect completely.
I'll think of something.
Listen. Think carefully.
What other buildings are around?
I'm in the southwest of Haohan Street.
Shencao Pharmacy on Greenwood Lane.
Haohan Street...
Southwest, Greenwood Lane.
Look. Those two people.
Don't they look familiar?
Invincible!
Guys.
Who has time right now? Help me!
It's urgent.
Log off and help me call the police.
Call the police?
Members of the Heavenly Society
are still locked up in prison.
I was only spared because
I couldn't log in that day.
I'm not joking around.
This is life and death. I'm begging you!
Log out and call the police!
Are you nuts?
Why can't you log out yourself?
Guys, beat him until he logs out.
I'll deal with you guys later.
Ye Tian...
Yes, do that, Bai Wei.
Hang in there by your own will.
♫ The falling light ♫
I'll save you.
♫ Leads to a road ♫
Bai Wei, don't sleep. Listen to me.
♫ Longing for you ♫
♫ To be at the end ♫
You've overcome so many obstacles.
This time is no different.
♫ If the wind started to ♫
I've done many wrong things.
♫ Stop chasing the rain ♫
I'm sorry about that.
But I want to do you good.
♫ How would the eyes ♫
I believe we'll be able
to have a wonderful future together.
♫ Fog up? ♫
♫ Who's waiting ♫
Yes, I'm jealous of Lin Feng.
But I wish to give you something better.
♫ To be touched softly ♫
I will change if I get out this time.
♫ Promises shouldn't be like ♫
So don't leave me, okay?
♫ A gust of wind ♫
Ye Tian, I'm not blaming you.
♫ How many times ♫
♫ Shall I whisper ♫
And I won't leave you.
♫ Is enough to describe ♫
Trust me.
♫ Love? ♫
I feel like my world suddenly changed.
♫ The sea chants for the sky ♫
It no longer revolves around me.
♫ With the raging of the waves ♫
♫ Make a wish ♫
Rather, all my happiness and sadness
♫ On an ordinary night ♫
♫ Praying that the red eyes ♫
are connected to you.
♫ Are no longer blurry ♫
You could use what we've gone through
♫ Look up and watch ♫
♫ The starry sky ♫
as inspiration for your next design.
♫ I hold you ♫
The main male and female protagonists
will be you and I.
♫ With all my love ♫
♫ Can you hear my wish ♫
♫ In the noise? ♫
How we traverse
between two worlds.
♫ Perhaps you can understand it ♫
♫ Only if you are ♫
[I'm just afraid.]
♫ Closer to me ♫
[Afraid that the story would end]
[right after it started.]
No, I won't have that.
Since it's our story,
we will be the ones to write it.
Hang in there, Bai Wei.
Don't you sleep.
I will get you out of here.
[We'll go out there]
[and enjoy the world.]
[I won't have to wake up from the cabin]
[all alone again.]
[I won't have to look forward to]
[the next time I see you
in another world.]
[While you won't have to wear my clothes,]
[or hide yourself.]
[I don't have to go along
with your actions.]
[We can just be ourselves.]
♫ Perhaps it's enough to describe love ♫
[We can go and eat the food you like.]
♫ Only if you are ♫
[Live together.]
♫ Closer to me ♫
What is this place?
This is a thunderstorm scene
that hasn't been completed.
Players who come here will encounter a bug
where their consciousness is separated
from the Pangu system.
This is the only way.
What do you plan to do?
Jump into it.
Is this the only way?
Yes.
You're crazy.
No.
Normally, when a player
is disconnected by force,
the system will deem it as offline.
They will then wake up in the cabin.
But my account
is bugged.
If I become separated...
You'll die.
There will be a small probability event
where the system misjudges
my disconnect by logic.
The small probability in the logic
is my chance to return to the real world.
No, that is not a chance.
You're making a bet with your life.
I won't let you.
But it's worth it.
I won't...
For you, everything is worth it.
I'm not going to let
anything happen to you.
Even if it's a minute possibility,
I'm willing to give it a try.
No, I won't let you do it.
I just have to jump.
No...
This is the only chance.
No, I won't...
I won't let you.
Ye Tian.
Ye Tian!
Where am I?
It's really me.
I did it.
[No, my consciousness is not stable.]
Mr. Ye?
Mr. Ye.
Mr. Ye is awake. Get help!
Hurry. Take Mr. Ye back to the room.
Leave me be. Let me go.
Go to Greenwood Lane, Haohan Street.
Someone needs saving at Greenwood Lane!
Mr. Ye.
Mr. Ye!
Are you okay?
Dr. Wang.
Check over there with Xiao Qin.
Okay.
Mr. Ye!
Atenolol.
It's used to treat irregular heart beat.
It should help Bai Wei.
Mr. Ye! Mr. Ye is here.
He's here!
Mr. Ye!
Quick!
Come down here.
Hold on.
[Mr. Lin, Mr. Ye is awake.]
Little Lin Lin! Where are you going?
Tell me where.
Okay.
I'll be right there.
That looks like Ye Tian.
Bai Wei!
Ye Tian, I am here.
Ye Tian...
I'm here.
Bai Wei!
Bai Wei.
Wake up.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, I came late.
I love you.
I love you, Bai Wei.
You're awake.
It's really you.
It's me.
Hang in there. I'll get you out of here.
Let's go.
Hang in there.
This lady has an accomplice.
He barged in here alone? Very bold.
After them! Quick!
Ye Tian!
Stop!
Get lost.
It's Xiao Liang.
He's buddies with the big gun
of Haohan Street.
Let's go.
Does it hurt?
No.
I don't believe you.
How long will you be able
to stay out of the game this time?
The system currently acknowledges me
as offline.
This time, I should be able
to stay with you for a long time.
Really?
Yes.
That's great!
Ouch...
Sorry. I...
I'll be gentle.
Not so hard.
Okay, I'll be gentle.
Don't move.
Come closer to me.
Be gentle.
Blow on it.
So childish.
Childish?
You're just despising something
you cannot get.
You're still young.
When you're older,
you'll know the good of having a wife.
Wifey, come.
Okay, giant baby.
Sit down.
Come here.
Done.
Kid, even if I have Ye Tian,
I'll always be your Ms. Wei.
Alright.
I'll go and cook for you guys.
Wait here.
You're going to cook?
Forget it.
I bet
you'd only be able to make instant curry.
Let me do it.
You can be my assistant.
Ye Tian is right.
Stupid Xiao Liang.
♫ My yearning is like an ocean ♫
♫ Have you ever thought
of rowing to the other side? ♫
♫ I think there's a girl there ♫
♫ Waiting for me
to take her to the future ♫
♫ My longing is like an ocean ♫
♫ I wish there was someone chilling
on the other side ♫
♫ So I wouldn't be alone ♫
Put it down.
Wash your hands.
♫ He will appear one day ♫
♫ Falling in love makes someone ♫
♫ Become like a kid ♫
♫ You're always adorable ♫
♫ Missing someone is a great pity ♫
Say, you're pretty amazing.
♫ Can you show up ♫
What if my tummy got used
to being spoiled?
♫ To my side quickly? ♫
If I'm the only one here,
I'd feel out of place.
♫ How can I find love? ♫
♫ I am your love ♫
♫ How do I keep you with me? ♫
Then I won't leave.
♫ I will stay ♫
You said it yourself.
♫ You are my only desire ♫
I take it as a promise.
♫ Finding Love ♫
♫ Be my boy ♫
♫ How can I find love? ♫
♫ I am your love ♫
♫ How do I keep you with me? ♫
♫ I will stay ♫
Yes, I said it.
♫ Give you all my love ♫
From today on, we'll never be apart.
♫ Love you hard, I am your harbor ♫
But it still feels like a dream.
♫ How can I find love? ♫
♫ I will stay for you ♫
♫ You are my only desire ♫
Does it feel real now?
♫ Finding Love ♫
♫ Be my boy ♫
Geez.
♫ How can I find love? ♫
I'm going to make the eggs.
♫ I am your love ♫
♫ How do I keep you with me? ♫
♫ I will stay ♫
♫ Give you all my love ♫
♫ Love you hard, I am your harbor ♫
Meatballs, fishballs,
Southern Fried meatballs,
braised pork balls, Three Delicacies
meatballs, dried fishballs,
deep-fried meatballs, tofu balls,
boiled meatballs.
We'll make it one by one.
[Oh no.]
[Looks like my logging out by force
is problematic.]
We can eat very soon.
[I don't think I can remain much longer.]
[I'm sorry, Wei Wei.]
[I have to break the promise.]
Since this is a happy occasion,
I'll go down and buy some beer
to celebrate.
I'll be back quickly.
Okay.
I...
I think that's Mr. Ye.
Mr. Ye?
Mr. Ye is out of the hospital?
Mr. Ye is awake.
When did he wake up?
[Just a bit more.]
[I have to get as far as I can
from Bai Wei's apartment.]
Where is Ye Tian?
He went to buy beer.
Why did he go himself?
We can get it delivered.
You're right.
I'll look for him.
What's wrong?
Zhao Jia Liang,
I can't remain here further.
My consciousness
is about to return to Pangu.
Return to Pangu?
Didn't you successfully log out?
I don't have time to explain.
I've already been seen.
If people from Celeste Group find out,
they will surely investigate the matter.
Promise me.
Don't let Bai Wei appear at the scene.
Be careful of Zhang Hao Cheng.
Make sure Bai Wei is safe.
Got it?
Now go.
Look after her for me.
Time to eat, two giant babies.
Right, they went to get some beers.
They should be back by now.
Why didn't you pick up the phone?
I didn't hear it ring.
Where's Ye Tian?
Why isn't he back yet?
I don't know. I didn't see him.
Oh no. It's people from Celeste.
We have to find Ye Tian.
Is that Ye Tian?
Ms. Wei...
Ms. Wei.
Don't go, Ms. Wei.
Ye Tian!
[I'm sorry. I just promised you]
[I wouldn't let you wait for me alone.]
[But I...]
Let me go.
[Broke it right away.]
Ms. Wei.
Let me go.
What just happened?
Ye Tian did it for your sake.
Mr. Lin, the report isn't out yet.
Why don't you take a rest first?
Rest assured.
Despite the erratic EEG,
Mr. Ye's vitals are relatively stable.
He went to Haohan Street when he woke up.
The police showed up
after being tipped off.
They cracked down on
an underground drug factory
on Greenwood Lane.
Xiao Tian fainted near Yibin Square.
No one knows why he was there.
My men
are cooperating with the police
to find out more details.
It's all right.
At least he's alive.
That's already very fortunate.
By the way,
why aren't we
conducting intracranial screening surgery
on Xiao Tian?
It's not the right time.
He just experienced a violent awakening.
He comes in and out of consciousness.
We can't pinpoint the reason.
So maintaining the current state
is our only option.
We'll wait for more detailed test results.
I'm setting up a foreign panel
of specialists to review his case.
You really know all the ins and outs
of Ye Tian's condition, Mr. Lin.
A rarity.
Ms. Wei.
Ms. Bai Wei.
You can't go in.
Why?
Mr. Ye needs
recuperation.
You're not allowed to disturb him.
You're doing more harm than good.
Ye Tian doesn't want you to...
Xiao Liang, it's dangerous for him
to be alone in there.
I must see him.
Even just one glimpse.
-What are you doing?
-Ms. Wei.
Stop...
Let me go.
Ms. Bai Wei.
What are you doing here?
I heard Ye Tian is awake.
Can I go in and see him?
Mr. Ye just underwent testing.
He needs rest.
Come with me.
I'll wait here.
You really care about Xiao Tian.
When the accident happened,
you came too.
You even left
a commemorative coin
from the AR Fighting Championship.
We made a pact.
The one who lost
will take the coin as a memento.
It will be returned when they win.
But he hasn't woken up.
Hence I've been keeping the coin.
I'm waiting for him to wake up
and return it to me himself.
In the past few days,
I've been watching over him like this too.
I too, hope that he'll wake up soon.
Do you really want him to wake up?
Don't bring up Xiao Tian.
Be it Xiao Tian or Zhang Hao Cheng.
I don't need anyone's permission
to do something.
I'm the group's
CEO!
He got too close to the furnace.
Part of his character data was erased.
That's why he doesn't remember me.
Do you actually want him to wake up?
And disrupt your life again?
Ye Tian, watch out!