♪You are my world♪
♪Never leaving through all seasons♪
♪I wish I could hold you tight
in my arms♪
♪And turn into the wind to be with you♪
♪You are my air♪
♪I breathe you in,
yet get lost in the wind♪
♪I wish we could get closer♪
♪So you could fill my whole world♪
♪As you draw near♪
♪I hold my words inside♪
♪I'm lucky to have met you♪
♪I send a love sign♪
♪With a playful expression♪
♪But you pretend not to respond♪
♪Butterflies in my stomach
as I decipher your words♪
♪A love confession is bound
to happen in the next second♪
♪You are everything I anticipate♪
♪Hurry and shorten
the distance between us♪
♪You are my world♪
♪Never leaving through all seasons♪
♪I wish I could hold you tight
in my arms♪
♪And turn into the wind to be with you♪
♪You are my air♪
♪I breathe you in,
yet get lost in the wind♪
♪I wish we could get closer♪
♪So you could fill my whole world♪
=Their Wonderful Time=
=Episode 25=
Lingling.
Lingling?
Do you like them?
Did you prepare all this?
Yes.
Look.
This was taken when we attended
the press conference.
This
was taken on our first date.
This is you at work.
At this one.
It was when you were home.
When did you take all these photos?
Some were taken openly,
and some
I took when you weren't aware.
Tell me.
Did you like me
for a very long time?
You liked me earlier than I did.
In case you forget me
while I'm away,
so
I have put up
all the photos here.
So
they can remind you
of me.
And you
won't feel lonely.
Even without these photos,
I won't forget you.
Thank you for your gift.
I like it very much.
Sure.
We will take a lot more photos
and fill this wall.
And also
that wall.
Let's fill the walls with our photos.
I think
this house isn't big enough.
We need a bigger house.
Maybe we can take a few photos now
as a memory.
Sure.
(Ms. Song,)
(this may sound weird,)
(but I think)
(the current situation has proven)
(that the memories
of both you and Xing Tian)
(have reshuffled and intersected.)
(You designed Xing Tian)
(and wrote the code)
(of his memory.)
(But who can guarantee)
(that we humans aren't
a composite code)
(written by beings of a higher level?)
(As Xing Tian's code)
(is absorbing your energy rapidly,)
(you will end up)
(becoming a dormant Xing Tian,)
(while he will become you
drifting in the void for good)
(without being discovered.)
(At this point,)
(there's nothing I can do.)
(Please forgive me, Ms. Song.)
(Thank you, Mr. Xue.)
(Please don't tell Xiao Ran about this.)
(If all my memories disappear,)
(does it mean)
(that everything never existed)
(in my world?)
(I won't even have)
(a chance to say goodbye to Xiao Ran.)
I'm Song Lingling
and the person in charge
of Lan Yao Studio.
Metaverse of Love
is a game
I spent four years creating.
Liu Yiyi and I
met in college.
We are
the best friends.
Dad,
what brings you here?
Since Lin Qiao isn't planning
to inherit the Shanhai Group,
you can't marry him.
Dad,
I don't want my marriage
to become a chip in your business.
My child,
I'm doing this for your own good.
It can help you in inheriting
the Shen Group
more easily.
You need to know
that given your experience,
none of those astute shareholders
will accept you.
I'd rather not inherit anything.
Let someone else take it.
This is absurd!
Dad.
Fine.
If you don't want anything,
I will pull off
the game investments
in the Shanhai Group.
Dad,
you can't do that.
I promise Xiao Ran
I will support Lanyao
until the fixings are done.
I made this mistake,
and I have to make amends.
You diluted your shares
in his company
for this reason, didn't you?
If you hadn't secretly sent Steven
to help Vic,
things wouldn't have turned out
as bad as this.
What makes you think that way?
You ordered Steven
to report any of my movements to you.
I was wondering why Steven helped Vic.
And he wouldn't answer me
no matter how I tried.
But you transferred him away
the next day.
Why would you react that way
if you had nothing to do with this?
I just wanted you to see
who the right choice is
for you.
I know very well
who's right for me.
Then you should calm down
and think it through.
Call me when you come around to this.
Are you trying to lock me up?
I didn't want to do this either,
but there are principles and boundaries
you mustn't ignore.
Keep an eye on her.
Don't let her out
before I'm back.
Yes.
Why are you looking at me
like this?
I just want
to take a good look at you.
I will be back very soon.
Wait for me.
When did you return from overseas?
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I could've sent a ride for you
from the airport.
Old man,
how much longer do you plan
to hide this from me?
If I hadn't come back this time,
when were you going
to tell me?
Lucky you.
You have two sons.
I have only one daughter.
I'm counting on her to help me
after she got married.
You have known about this all along.
Why didn't you do something?
You just let these young people
mess around.
You always have a short fuse.
Calm down.
How can I calm down?
Come on,
just tell me already.
What's your plan?
Let me be frank with you.
I came back
for this matter.
You must give me a satisfactory answer.
Honestly,
I talked to them.
Xiangyu
likes Lin Qiao.
Nonsense!
How can that be?
Do you think you can let them be
when you are satisfied?
No way.
Listen.
This doesn't count.
Don't be mad.
We can talk nicely.
Let's have some tea.
Calm down.
The kids have all grown up,
and they have ideas of their own.
We were all young once.
We argued with our parents
over relationships, too.
You can't force someone to be together.
Cut your crap.
Are you planning to
go back on your words?
I didn't say that.
The thing is,
they don't always listen to us.
Don't try to brush me off. Call Xiao Ran.
I want to hear what he has to say.
All right, then.
Zhang.
Give Xiao Ran a call
and tell him to come back.
Please.
(What has he been busy with these days?)
(Liu Yiyi is my best friend)
Coming.
Lingling?
You have the keys.
Why did you knock?
You can come in directly.
I...
What?
Don't just stand here. Come on in.
Let me show you what I've packed.
Come on.
This is
a rare trip for us.
I have to prepare well.
I'm going to pack
all of our beautiful clothes.
Then
we can take amazing photos.
Look at this.
What do you think about this piece?
What are you looking at, Lingling?
It's nothing.
You haven't been back
for a long while.
You miss this place, right?
You are living in a big villa now,
but
don't forget
this is the place
where our dreams began.
I won't forget this.
What's wrong?
Are you moved?
If you miss me,
just come back to see me.
If Xiao Ran ever mistreats you,
move back here.
This will forever be your home.
All right?
Yiyi,
let's take a photo.
Sure.
Let me fix my lipstick.
Okay.
Let's do it.
One, two, three.
(Lan Yao Studio is
where you strive for your dream)
(Everyone here is the best staff
and the most reliable partners)
Check this again.
Boss?
Wu.
Boss.
Boss,
what brings you here?
Just visiting.
Be honest.
Do you miss us?
I have missed you very much.
Boss,
let me tell you this.
While you were away,
they have been working all night.
You always tell us
to get enough sleep,
but they
never listen.
Xiong,
you also work late every night.
You said
you could work from down to dusk
for the game.
Boss told you to work out,
but you gave up.
Jeez.
I won't argue with you.
You guys have been working
all this time.
It's fine, Boss.
This is a small matter.
You don't have to worry.
We settle it
with ease.
Get back to your work.
I'm going to my room
to fetch something.
All right.
Wu,
don't you think
something's wrong with Boss?
Is it?
She seems a bit down.
I don't see it.
Back to work.
Mr. Xiao,
why don't you
take a look around the office?
I can't focus
with you sitting here.
Have some tea.
Dad.
Mr. Shen.
Have a seat.
I called you here
because Mr. Shen
has something to ask you.
I haven't seen you in years.
You have grown into a fine man.
I can rest easy
after handing over
the Shen Group to you.
Sorry, Mr. Shen.
I can't marry Xiangyu.
Why?
Both of you have been close
since childhood.
Why?
You don't like her anymore?
To be honest, I have been seeing Xiangyu
as a sister over the years.
Besides,
I have someone I like.
And Xiangyu
is with my brother now.
Is this the attitude of your family?
I told you.
They have their own ideas.
I was furious when I first found out.
I scolded them a lot.
I understand
you are planning for the future
of Xiang Yu.
I asked Lin Qiao.
He said he likes Xiangyu very much.
I also believe
he can make Xiangyu happy.
Why don't we
give them what they want?
That's easy for you to say.
I know you
quite well.
If you could let go of the past,
Lin Qiao would've achieved nothing
in the Shanhai Group.
He's now an outsider
in the company.
If that's the case,
Xiangyu might as well
marry an ordinary man.
This is enough.
Stop it.
So you do have a temper.
Listen.
I don't care if you listen or not,
I say what I have to say.
If you can give Lin Qiao
equal status and power as Xiao Ran
and let him take full charge
of the company's affairs,
then I might consider this.
Otherwise,
I will tell everyone that the Xiao Family
broke their promise.
By then,
your family's credibility
will be ruined.
If you make a scene out of this,
you will put Xiangyu to shame, too.
It would be better than her suffering
after the marriage.
Listen,
if you can't handle this well,
I will take matters into my own hands.
I will withdraw all the investments
of the Shanhai Group.
You have time to think it over.
I expect a satisfactory answer.
You!
Dad, calm down.
I will see him off.
Mr. Shen.
There's one thing
I need to talk to you about.
I have already made myself clear.
There's nothing left to talk about.
I know what you are thinking.
To you,
my brother's a stepson who isn't valued
and holds no power in the company.
You are worried that his lesser
influence in the Shanhai Group
won't be helpful
and supportive of Xiangyu
and will also affect
future collaborations
with the Shanhai Group.
That's why you think
he doesn't deserve Xiangyu.
But I have a way
to ease your concerns.
What do you plan to do?
I will take care of that.
But I believe
you will see it soon.
I believe you are well aware
that my brother and Xiangyu
are truly in love with each other.
You don't have the full confidence
to convince Xiangyu to marry me.
Nothing turns out well
if the situation doesn't improve.
So, could you give me some time
to resolve this?
Do you really have a solution?
Absolutely.
But could you please not withdraw
your investment first?
This fund
is very important to us.
All right, then.
I give you my word on this.
But
you need to show me the results
as soon as possible.
You have my word.
Ms. Song, you are back.
Mr. Xiao,
Ms. Song is back home.
(I'm in the hospital, and Liu Yiyi came.
I'm so touched.)
(I'm Song Lingling and the person in charge
of Lan Yao Studio)
Mr. Xiang said
you went out earlier today.
Where did you go?
I...
I was out for a walk.
Right. Getting fresh air outside
can help improve your mood.
Yes.
I'm feeling particularly well now.
By the way,
do you remember
the white dress you wore
during the press conference?
I do.
You were there too,
right?
Do you remember
what happened on that day?
It has been a long time.
I can't remember that.
Why are you asking this?
Nothing.
Do you remember
the name of this jellyfish?
Yes.
It's called...
It's called the immortal jellyfish.
Yes, right.
That's its name.
It's a luminescent creature
in the ocean.
Besides,
it's immortal.
It can be reborn
repeatedly.
I didn't know that.
Do you still remember
why you named your game
Metaverse of Love?
I...
You spent four years on this game.
Lingling,
tell me.
Did you forget everything?
♪I see you now, I've taken you lightly♪
No. Not at all.
I...
♪Flame on my palm♪
♪I see it clearly, I see my fate♪
I didn't forget.
I don't want to forget.
♪We passed by each other♪
Not this.
It's all right.
Not that.
I want to remember it.
No, not this.
- Lingling.
- Not this.
Stop it.
♪Seeking amidst illusions♪
♪The unknown river of love♪
♪Across the empty sky♪
♪A star scurries past, is it you?♪
♪I turn back time to search for you♪
Sorry.
♪I stand on tiptoe to reach you♪
I can't remember everything.
I'm sorry.
♪I pass by sunset and run into dawn♪
♪Roaming in secret through time♪
No need to apologize.
It's fine.
I can't remember anything.
No matter how hard I have tried,
I know I have forgotten something
very important.
It's like
walking a path alone,
endless,
dead silent,
pitch black,
and with no way out.
I'm terrified.
I feel like I have lost myself.
Sorry.
I should've noticed it sooner.
I have put you through
all of this alone.
♪The night breeze fears
it's too late to kiss the stars♪
♪I can't find your response♪
♪Thoughts of you never stop traveling♪
♪Like a cloud passing by♪
♪That stays firmly by your side♪
♪How lucky do I have to be♪
♪To catch your attention♪
♪I wish to leave a trace♪
♪Sadly, we are far apart♪
♪Will you believe
in the promise we have made?♪
♪The moon isn't afraid
to stand alone among the stars♪
♪Tides swell in my heart♪
♪Because you are getting close♪
♪I can't help but respond♪
♪The moon isn't afraid
to stand alone among the stars♪
♪Ripples fill our eyes♪
♪Never explored by anyone else♪
♪This love needs no declaration♪
♪It's meant only for you♪
♪The moon isn't afraid
to stand alone among the stars♪
♪Ripples fill our eyes♪
♪Never explored by anyone else♪
♪This love needs no declaration♪
♪It's meant only for you♪
♪The moon isn't afraid
to stand alone among the stars♪
♪Tides swell in my heart♪
♪Because you are getting close♪
♪I can't help but respond♪
♪The moon isn't afraid
to stand alone among the stars♪
♪Ripples fill our eyes♪
♪Never explored by anyone else♪
♪This love needs no declaration♪
♪It's meant only for you♪