[English subtitles are available]
[Once and only]
[Episode 8]
Well.
You're the only one
that makes me concede defeat.
Do you have any unfulfilled wish?
I've been arrogating power in court for years
and I've enjoyed the dignity as an emperor.
I have no pities.
Is there any family member
you need me to take care of?
I have a son.
I'll have him escorted back to Pingcheng
so that he can escape this misfortune.
Before His Majesty was born,
the late emperor had an eldest son
who wasn't born to the empress.
But he died at three.
In order to find the truth out,
I offended Empress Gao.
But Liu Yuan begged for leniency
and saved me.
In my childhood,
I was on good terms
with Liu Yuan.
That's why you buried wine together?
Yeah.
Then,
have you ever buried some wine with any woman?
What do you mean?
Nothing.
You walked on every inch here
in your childhood?
Yeah.
Zhousheng Chen.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't matter.
I'm just not used to
hearing you
call me by my name.
Your family is in the Western State
and you will live in the Western State later.
You just said
it's enough for you to have ten orphans
and one disciple
in your mansion.
Yeah, it's enough.
Miss Cui,
The Prince of Guangling
is waiting for you outside the hall.
I'm going to ask him back.
My bedding hall
is also in the imperial palace.
How can you stop the Prince of Guangling?
Ask him in.
Yes.
Wait.
I don't feel well.
I'm afraid I can't deal with him if he comes in.
If so, we can only ask him to go back.
Yes.
What's wrong?
I'll be better after having a rest.
Your Highness,
she is...
Advisor Xie,
summon an imperial doctor.
Your Highness, can't you
feel her pulse?
I'm unfamiliar with it
as I haven't done this for long.
Let me do it.
It's more reliable
to summon an imperial doctor.
Your Highness, you know
my medical skills.
I can...
OK.
I'll summon an imperial doctor.
Advisor Xie,
please feel my pulse.
Let me do it.
You feel a pain in the chest?
Sometimes you feel depressed?
You had ringing in the ears?
A little.
It's not serious. You'll be better after a rest.
Then I go to rest immediately
and won't meet any visitors.
Suit yourself.
The maid said
Empress Dowager wants to send the nun
to the Western State
to give the junior Prince of Nanchen a favor.
Second,
if she gives birth to a baby,
the baby can be sent back to the palace
to be raised as a hostage.
Are you sad
that you're being forced to stay here by me?
I'm just tired.
I know
you feel so restless
because she is in the palace.
Since you came here,
I've been with you,
haven't I?
That's just your helpless action.
She is my fiancée.
I'm worried about her since she is ill.
Is there anything wrong?
After marrying me,
she will be your sister-in-law.
You can't dislike
her like this.
If she is good to you,
I won't dislike her.
Don't worry.
Your Highness,
Princess.
What's up?
By order of Empress Dowager,
some of the Cui family directly drove a carriage from the palace gate
to her bedding hall.
Did you see who got off the carriage?
Many of
the Cui clan.
If you want to see me,
I can go to your mansion.
Why do you come regardless of your condition?
I'm afraid I can't wait any more.
You come
for the Crown Princess' engagement?
Now that His Majesty has concubines,
he'll have sons soon.
You won't allow the Prince of Guangling
to be the Crown Prince,
right?
Yeah.
The Prince of Guangling will be unqualified.
So Shiyi won't be the Crowned Princess.
I'm sorry.
But...
Please cancel Shiyi's engagement.
My son Feng.
I want to ask for an engagement
for him.
Which girl do you think suits him?
Tell me.
Princess of Xinghua.
My son has been guiding Shouyang for many years.
With many battle achievements,
he is worthy of Her Highness.
In the palace,
only she
reaches marriageable age.
But...
If she marries my son,
the Cui clan and your family
will be united through marriage,
which will be good
for you only.
Empress Dowager.
OK.
I'll certainly agree with this marriage
to make up for what the royal family
owe your family.
Thank you, Empress Dowager.
[Jiafu Palace]
Shiyi.
Your Highness, please behave yourself.
I won't definitely cancel our engagement.
Your Highness,
as a favored prince,
it's not hard for you
to have a better marriage.
Now that Empress Dowager has cancelled our engagement,
don't give your heart
to me.
Shut up.
You called her in public like this.
Aren't you afraid of offending the Cui family
and Nanchen Royal Mansion?
You're a prince,
but the Cui family's daughter
is not humbler than you.
Your Highness, My Lady,
please calm down.
Your Highness has loved Miss Cui since childhood.
He doesn't want to
and won't hurt her.
I'm sorry.
Uncle, please forgive me.
Go out of the palace
to stay in the Residence of Cui
with your mom for a few days.
And spend some days
with your uncle.
Yes.
Aunt, I don't want to marry him.
Aunt.
I don't want to marry him.
The marriage between the Cui family and us
is imperative.
Now we just let it be.
So you must marry him.
But, but I don't like him.
Who do you like?
I...
I grant you the status of princess
is not to make you enjoy yourself.
You can choose to marry Cui Feng of the Cui family,
or marry a ruler in the border areas
to make peace.
[Residence of the Grand Mentor]
Cui Xiu is dead,
and I'm dying.
The Cui family doesn't have anyone influential in the court.
Wenjun,
remember.
Don't mourn for me for three years,
but ask the Princess to marry in as soon as possible.
Dad,
I don't want to marry her.
Please cancel the engagement.
You,
you unfilial son.
Dad.
Unfilial son.
Dad. Dad.
Cui Feng,
your dad gave up his dignity
to ask for this engagement for you.
Do you really want your dad
to die in anger?
Dad,
I always
listen to you
and have never gone against you.
This time,
I beg you to cancel this engagement.
I would rather remain single all my life
than marry the princess.
Beat him.
Don't stop until he promises.
Mom,
stop them.
Your uncle is the clan chief.
Who dares to disobey him?
Chief! Chief! Chief!
Dad.
Brother.
Favored by
the late emperor,
I was promoted to such a position.
I should have gone without regrets,
but I'm loath to leave the descendants
of Wushui.
Dad.
Do you still treat me as your dad?
Promise your dad.
You unfilial son.
All of us
get married for the Cui family.
Promise him.
Wenji.
I know you dislike it.
But, Feng,
each of us
should sacrifice for our clan.
When Shiyi was 10 years old,
her dad's clan
offended Empress Gao.
To prevent the Cui family
and Shiyi from being implicated,
I wrote the divorce agreement
to divorce him.
I was more reluctant
than you are.
Feng,
I beg you.
Let your dad
go without regrets.
I promise.
Dad.
Dad!
Brother!
-Brother. Brother.
-Dad.
Brother.
-Brother.
When did you come back?
Master.
I want to go back to the Western State.
Here you are.
Your Highness.
Cui Wenjun comes.
[Chonghua Palace]
Your Highness.
Is Shiyi here?
She is not feeling well.
Give me some days
to persuade her.
You're her master,
but you're not her family after all.
Let us take her back.
You're...
Cui Wenji.
As a member of the Cui family,
you should know
Shiyi has lived in my mansion
for long.
What she gained
and learnt
all come
from here.
So I know more about her
than you.
Brother just died.
Wenji and I indeed are busy
with internal and external affairs.
So we have no time to talk things out with Shiyi.
Back then...
Your Highness, please explain it to Shiyi for us.
Thank you.
Your Highness,
isn't
Cui Wenji...
Even the Empress Dowager respects him.
You were so rude.
You wanted to see your own daughter,
but he stopped you.
Can't I
speak for you?
For me
or for yourself?
The late Prince of Nanchen
is gone.
Don't be
resentful to his nephew.
You think too much.
It has been years since my uncle's death.
I didn't expect that
she is still
dwelling on the past.
They were not destined to be together,
so she can't let it go.
In the palace that day,
Cui convinced me
to take Shiyi
as an apprentice
with the affair of my uncle with Cui Wenji,
so as to resolve the hatred between the two families.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't have agreed
with him easily.
I'm sorry
to embarrass you.
Shiyi.
If I had known that
you didn't want to take me as an apprentice,
I wouldn't have stayed in the Western State.
If not,
where can you go?
Come with me.
Who is she?
She is from the Cui family.
Cui Shiyi.
She is the daughter of Li Qilang?
Yes.
Another blood debt
that the Gao family owes.
In the Taiji Palace back then,
considering the complicated relations
in the court in the Central State,
I just didn't want to connect with any family.
So back then,
no matter
who you are,
I couldn't
take you as my apprentice.
You smile finally.
Mind your words as a senior.
I'm less than ten years older than you.
I'm not a senior.
But as an uncle,
you rank as my senior.
Your Highness.
Wait for me here.
I'll come back to you
after meeting her.
It's late.
Why does she want to meet you?
What brings you
here this time?
May I talk with you
on our own?
There are no outsiders here.
Go ahead.
Please help me.
The Empress Dowager
let me out of the nunnery
to finish a task.
What did she want you to do?
Be your wife.
What if
I can't promise you?
At any cost, even if as your maidservant.
There is only one maidservant
in my mansion
and she came with Shiyi.
The rest are bodyguards.
Moreover,
I need no maidservants.
The Empress Dowager hates the Gao clan.
The reason why
she didn't kill me
is our misleading past.
If you don't take me in this time,
she'll think that I'm useless
and will kill me.
Get up first.
I really can't
promise you this time.
Although I can't marry you,
I can take you away.
I have an adoptive brother,
the Prince of Pingqin.
I can pretend to take you away
and secretly send you to him to avoid trouble.
What if she is provoked
and sends men to kill me
when finding that
I'm not in the Western State?
As a vassal king
not from the imperial clan,
The Prince of Pingqin is less restrained by the imperial court.
As Pingqin County is the farthest from the Central State,
the people and soldiers there
all respect him.
Even assassins sent there by her
may either die halfway
or never return.
OK, I'll go.
The Royal Army of Nanchen will leave soon.
Go back and get ready.
Miss Cui,
would you come out and see me?
Her uncle just passed away.
She is sad
and asleep.
Then I'll say it here.
I apologize
to you for my clan
killing your father's family.
I accept it for her.
You can leave.
My dad...
As a gentleman
from a famous family,
he was
known for his noble character
among his peers.
He loved your mom
and proposed many times,
but he was refused
for his humble origin.
At last, he chose to marry into the Cui family
and lived in the Residence of Cui.
How did that happen?
Why do you know it?
On the day he took you as his apprentice...
Why did he leave?
Is he hiding something from me?
No.
Perhaps
he wants me
to tell you without his presence.
On the day he took you as his apprentice,
your mom told him that
you got aphasia
because of your dad's matter.
Thus he got to know
the Li and Cui familys
and every detail
of what happened
to your dad.
His Highness is quite
attentive to you.
Advisor Xie,
what was the Gao's clan like
back then?
I know
it's a forbidden subject.
If it's not appropriate...
The Gao clan had two empresses,
so it had its heyday,
dominating the court
and overwhelming the royal Liu clan
and the Cui family.
However,
consequently,
few people today
remember the Gao clan.
Her Lady wants to return to the capital as soon as possible
to send the clan chief back to Qinghe County.
The condolence from ministers
will be over today.
I see.
So you must
be careful at night.
General Hong.
What can I do for you?
Both you and I
are generals
of the equal status.
Please don't say so.
I was ordered to
guard the peace of the Residence of Cui.
Here
I'm a guard
and you're the master.
Certainly you can order me.
I remember you were friendly to each other.
Why do you
have a conflict right after
his dad passed away?
It isn't a conflict.
It's public affair.
Well...
I'm in pain these days.
Perhaps what I did and said
have offended her.
Tonight,
may I see you
to apologize to you?
Tonight...
Sure.
I'll guard tonight.
What makes
the Royal Army of Nanchen invincible
is our united morale.
You two should
patch things up.
Today,
you must talk about it over.
I've kept some words
in my heart for years.
Let me say first.
Because of your status,
you need to consider
manner and reputation
whenever you talk.
But I'm an orphan
without any constraints,
so I'll say first.
That day
when you first went to
the Western State
with your sister,
I stopped you
under the gate tower,
but you made
a strong impression on me.
♫I don't seek glory of the multitude♫
I thought you
♫I only want to have a quiet conscience♫
couldn't stand the hardships in the army.
However,
you guarded Shouyang for years
♫With a pot of liquor, I travel all over the world♫
and resisted the enemy there.
Though you were in danger
when being besieged for several times,
you never retreated,
♫The horse's hooves sound on the battlefield♫
but guarded the south gate
for the people.
I'm flattered.
♫I am griping a great ambition in my hand♫
I really
admire you.
♫I don't fear the rain and wind and have an inflexible will♫
I, I also...
Xiaoyu, it's my turn.
No.
Let me say first.
♫As a general, I may forget any wound on the shoulder♫
Perhaps what I want to say
is more than your words.
♫I am willing to stick to a ray of light for a lifetime♫
This is your news of victory.
I've kept it for years.
You've made greater achievements
than I've done.
You've long been famous in the Central Plains.
I love you,
♫The moon knows my heart♫
but I dared not say.
From beginning to end
♫Forgive me as I never retreat on the battlefield♫
I always love you,
but we can never be together.
♫There will be a grand scene of prosperity♫
♫I don't expect people to praise me, and I just want to have a clear conscience♫
I've heard of you,
Xiao Wen.
Xiao Wen is dead.
I'm Xiao Yan.
You changed your name?
My uncle believes you,
so do I.
I've drawn up an edict
to make you the Prince of Fengyang.
You'll stay in the Central State
and be protected
by Beichen in this life.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I don't want to stay in the Central State.
Where do you want to go?
Sure enough,
people prefer following uncle.
Your Majesty,
Xiao Yan wants to join the Royal Army of Nanchen
to get a chance
to avenge his parents.
Don't bother to explain.
I don't mind.
I promise.
I'll still give you
the title of Prince of Fengyang.
I'm already a monk.
Prince of Fengyang,
although you've got tonsured,
you still attach to the world.
When you avenge,
come tell me
whether you want this title or not.
I...
Just follow the edict
of His Majesty.
Don't disobey it.
Yes, Your Majesty.
That's right.
When will you leave, uncle?
Tomorrow.
When will we meet next time?
We'd better not meet again in this life.
What's wrong
with me, uncle?
Whenever I come back,
there will be great events in the court,
so I'd rather
not see you again in this life.
I'll guard the Central State in the Western State.
I hope that you'll be a wise emperor.
I envy you
having these able men around.
I want someone of them.
Who?
I'd like to invite Advisor Xie
to help me in the Central State
like how he taught the late emperor.