[English subtitles are available]
[One and Only]
[Episode 7]
[Central State]
Stop!
General,
where did you come from?
That's not a question
You're entitled to ask.
We are escorting a major criminal to the capital city
according to His Majesty's decree!
Forgive me, General!
General, please.
Feng Qiao is so bold.
She's holding a fake decree
as if it were real.
[Central State]
Is the Chief of State Finance in there?
Yes.
I've brought some desserts from Jiangnan.
Your Highness, please.
You actually don't trust me
though we meet every day?
I can take the box in myself.
Does that works for you?
The Chief of State Finance already had dinner.
You wait outside for me.
Yes.
Chief of State Finance.
I wanted to bring you
some desserts from Jiangnan
but was unfortunately stopped outside.
Thanks for Your Highness' kind offer.
Don't mind.
I'll punish them
for you later.
Thanks for taking the trouble.
Chief of State Finance.
His Majesty is still worshipping the Buddha.
His Majesty likes to chant scriptures,
which is just like the Empress Dowager.
I think I'm enjoying the honor
that no other eunuchs
have ever enjoyed.
I have my own living palace
with palace maids.
And the imperial family members like you
chat with me.
We discuss political affairs
around the state.
I'm sure that
you can't keep the title of Crown Prince.
Look.
His Majesty is in the prime of his life,
and he will have his own sons.
So how could he possibly
make you the Crown Prince?
But don't worry.
I will surely help you to
marry the lady from the Cui family.
Just count on me.
Thanks, Mr. Zhao.
I'll do it.
Don't take the trouble.
It's no trouble.
Royal Army of Nanchen is outside the city.
Help me.
Or you won't be alive.
Your Highness.
The guilty eunuch Zhao Teng has admitted his guilty
and committed suicide.
He's dead,
so who are you serving?
Just admit your guilty now.
Let's kill him and escape.
Who dares to do it?
Here's the royal token of the junior Prince of Nanchen.
[Nanchen]
We aim to protect Beichen.
You'd better give yourselves in here,
or you will be dead.
Pardon me, Your Highness.
Find an adopted son of Zhao Teng.
Tell him that
Zhao Teng has suddenly caught a severe illness
and is dying.
Ask Liu Yuan to immediately come into the imperial palace
to watch Empress Dowager and comfort His Majesty.
Yes.
Do you know who I am?
I'm General-in-chief of the dynasty.
If you dare to kill me,
your families and relatives will be eliminated!
Who are you?
Who actually are you?
Who are you on earth?
Tell me!
The court session is cancelled today.
All ministers,
you may go.
Cancelled?
What's happened?
All ministers are here.
Exactly.
Yes.
Isn't he the Prince of Guangling's chamberlain?
What are we supposed to do?
Let's go out first.
Go.
What's going on?
Why is this happening?
Why was His Majesty absent from the court session?
There they are.
The court is in bad order now.
How can we not being worried?
Counselor-in-chief.
Who are you?
You're Cui Wenjun from the Cui family.
You're right.
You rarely left Qinghe County before,
why are you in the capital today?
My elder brother is severely ill
and dying.
However, he didn't want to part with
His Majesty, his peer ministers
and Counselor-in-chief.
He decided to come back to the Residence of Cui in the Central State,
and I came back with him.
So why are you here now?
I'd like to invite all of you
to the Residence of Cui
after the court session is over.
[Residence of the Grand Mentor]
Lord Cui.
Everybody, please be seated.
I've heard that
Zhao Teng is badly ill
and is dying.
I've also heard that
General-in-chief Liu Yuan went to see Empress Dowager.
He admitted that he had arrogated power in court
and killed loyal ministers.
At the time you arrived here,
the guilty minister Liu Yuan handed over his military power
and gave himself in.
Refreshments are ready.
Have a taste, everyone.
These are specialties of Qinghe County.
Counselor-in-chief,
didn't you hear of this?
You go in and out of the imperial palace every day.
You should have known it earlier than me.
I heard of it before.
Liu Yuan kept maids and whores,
killed ministers indiscriminately
and turned common people into slaves.
I guess you've been tolerating that
and have waited for this result for a long time.
You're absolutely right.
I'm badly ill now,
I'm powerless though I hope to do something.
At such a time of turbulence,
please help His Majesty.
It's my duty.
I knew that
you would ground me
sooner or later.
Your Majesty.
The outcome is certain now.
You should be happy.
Why are you still praying?
From beginning to end,
I've always thought that we would win.
What worries me most is that
His Majesty doesn't trust him.
I worry that His Majesty thinks he has other purposes.
If that's true,
everything he does for His Majesty
will be a joke.
Why are you crying?
Did you kill Zhao Teng?
Zhao Teng
died of illness.
What about Liu Yuan?
He confessed his guilty
and has been deprived of military power.
What I say
will be announced to the state
and recorded in history.
Well...
Will I be recorded
as dead today in history?
I'm afraid not.
You need to have several sons.
Otherwise, there will be more rebellions
if you don't have descendants.
I haven't brought weapons into the palace today,
just the wooden sword granted by Your Majesty.
I'm your uncle,
and you are more important
than the throne to me.
Uncle.
Thanks for saving me.
I once said that
you never need to kneel down in front of me.
After being grounded by my disobedient son and eunuch
for three years,
I've long lost my dignity as the Empress Dowager.
Without you,
I wouldn't have been set free.
I was wrong.
I will not see you as my son anymore.
I believed in slanderous talks
and wanted to come into throne as soon as possible,
But then…
But then
I just couldn't break away from Zhao Teng.
I knew I was wrong earlier
and couldn't eat or sleep well every day.
However, I didn't dare to go against them
because I was afraid they would kill you.
I was wrong.
I really was wrong.
Mother.
[Shiqian Palace]
Your Highness.
Have you thought of many things in the past?
The late emperor was just in his thirties
when he passed away,
but he died as an emperor anyway.
It's hard to come by that
we've made it without much trouble.
Exactly.
It's really hard to come by.
Then why is Shiyi going to cry?
Your Highness.
No one likes to joke about his disciple
as you do.
I can't stand seeing this.
I thought that
you must have been imprisoned by His Majesty.
His Majesty did order to
imprison me.
He ordered to
imprison me in the palace
for a period of time.
What will happen after this?
I'll go back to the Western State.
The Shiqian Palace is an emperor's living palace,
but why is it vacant?
The late emperor passed away here,
and His Majesty had his bedchamber moved to the Xianyang Palace
for fear of feeling sad.
[Shiqian Palace]
I was brought up by the late emperor here
when I was young,
so I lived here too.
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at the place
where you lived in childhood.
They don't know us.
That sounds right.
During this rescue,
except a few people,
no one else knows that
the junior Prince of Nanchen is back.
Therefore,
we need to hide our real names in the palace.
That sounds right.
So I can't call you “Master”, right?
We would be exposed in that case.
That makes sense.
Zhou…
Your Highness.
The Empress Dowager asks Your Highness to her living palace.
Go to the military advisor.
After all, it's not my mansion.
Don't go around.
The lady is in the palace.
If Your Highness wants to meet her,
I will invite her here.
I'm feeling pitiful.
Pitiful?
For what?
If we want to eliminate uncle,
tonight will be the best time.
That he came to the capital to save the emperor
has been known by no one else
except several close ministers.
Therefore, Royal Army of Nanchen would not complain
even if he died here.
If we kill Liu Yuan and him tonight,
it will be a double kill.
Pitifully, His Majesty values kinship
more than the throne
and doesn't have the heart to kill uncle.
Change clothes for me.
Yes.
Are you seeing Miss Cui?
Princess.
No.
Actually, I'm going to thank uncle for
saving His Majesty.
The Empress Dowager has invited him over
a moment ago.
[Jiafu Palace]
Congratulations for getting the power back.
You think I ask you here
to kill you?
Guess
who is back in the palace?
I haven't been concerned about worldly affairs for long.
The guy from the Western State.
You're finally back.
In this living palace,
we're family
rather than an emperor and his ministers.
You're my sister-in-law in the future?
Sorry for visiting abruptly.
Please don't worry.
I'm here to see him.
Are you Xie Chong,
the military advisor of
the junior Prince of Nanchen?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, don't do that.
I can't receive this.
You can.
Get up.
Your Majesty.
You taught the late emperor
and support my uncle,
so I should bow to you.
I need to bow twice more.
You were engaged with the late emperor
but you didn't marry him at last,
so why did you do this?
After the late emperor died,
Empress Gao forced me to be a nun.
When she died later,
I wanted to leave the palace at first.
Then I heard that you made a severe promise
at the Taiji Palace that
you would never get married,
so I stayed here.
After all,
this was the place where we met.
Your Majesty don't come here
just to bow to me, right?
I'd like to ask about a person.
Have you ever heard of
a lady named Huaiyang?
Gao Huaiyang?
Yes. Her surname is Gao.
Your Majesty,
what do you want to know about her?
What's her relationship with uncle?
Your Majesty,
why do you think
she has anything to do with your uncle.
I asked you first.
I will tell you
after you answer my question.
Your Majesty,
she's a cousin of Empress Gao
and has lots of chances to come into the palace.
The late emperor saw her
and took a fancy to her soon.
However,
the one she wanted to marry
was your uncle.
Did my uncle like her?
I didn't dare to ask.
So she must be very sad
when uncle left after that.
Maybe.
All I've heard is that
Gao's clan forced her into the palace
so that she could serve the late emperor.
After all, it was always
to Gao's advantage
if they had
an adored concubine.
However, Empress Gao didn't want her to share the late emperor's love
and tried all means to stop that.
Finally, she couldn't marry the late emperor.
After the late emperor passed away,
I've never heard about her.
She has been in the palace as a nun with hair
until today.
She's still alive?
I thought that
I would see you sooner or later
if I stayed in the palace.
Did it have anything to do with me
when you left the palace back then?
No.
[Chonghua Palace]
You like this place?
Master, you must have been tired
after seeing an old acquaintance.
Get in the palace and sleep.
Where are you going?
I'm going out of the palace.
The gate was closed earlier.
A powerful minister can go out
if he has important affairs.
Like you said,
a powerful minister can go out only if he has important affairs.
Do you think this place is like the Western State
where you can go anywhere arbitrary?
I've sent someone to
inform the Residence of Cui,
so you may stay here tonight.
Your Majesty is here too.
Yes.
I almost fainted after crying today.
I just chatted with your military advisor
and I'm back to myself now.
Why don't you
pay respect to His Majesty?
As a noble lady from the Cui family,
where are all your good manners?
He has been here for two hours.
He?
His Majesty.
I told her that
she didn't need to treat me as an emperor
in this living palace.
Please don't blame her.
Uncle, please be seated.
Sit down.
You eat.
Uncle.
You've done a deed of merit this time,
so what reward do you want?
I don't need that.
Jewelries?
A rank?
Or a land?
Or is it marriage?
I can't get married.
Even though you can't actually get married,
you can be with a lady
if you love each other.
His Majesty is wise.
A wedding is useless.
That you truly love each other
is the thing that matters.
I don't want you to be childless.
If you have a child,
you can bring him into the palace.
I'll personally bring him up.
No one would dare to say anything bad.
Your Majesty,
I'm not childless.
So,
I have cousins?
When did that happen?
There are ten orphans
and one disciple
in my mansion.
I'm contented.
My military advisor is old.
I hope Your Majesty won't blame him.
It's OK.
Your Majesty!
How dare you!
I told you that
no one should come in.
Please don't be angry.
I heard a noise
and was afraid that Your Majesty was in danger.
They are my honored guests
in the living palace,
so how could I be in danger?
Get out!
Yes.
I have nobody to trust
except you.
Your military advisor just told me that
Liu Yuan and you were close when you were younger.
Would you like to ask for leniency for him?
I can give him a way out.
Your Majesty,
please be fair and just.
I have only one request.
Go ahead.
Don't get my descendants involved.
If you're hungry,
you may ask someone outside the palace.
I'm not hungry.
I'm just not used to it
since this is my first time to sleep in the palace.
Master, are you worried about something?
Well.
You seem to be worried about something too tonight.
I'm young
without many past stories,
so I don't have the chance to be worried.
I found that you were not in the mood
as soon as you came back.
What's actually going on?
The wine I'm drinking
is called Sangluo.
It's usually granted to
meritorious officials.
My father once granted it to
a general who claimed to
drink lots of wine without getting drunk.
However, he was drunk for half a month
after drinking several liters of it.
The wine is strong
and I've drunk much tonight.
So if you have any worries,
just tell me.
I won't remember anything tomorrow.
Did His Majesty bring it here?
We buried it here before.
We buried it in many places in the palace.
Who buried it with you?
Several friends.
In childhood.
Was the person with you?
Yes.
He's really drunk
and tells me everything.
So will you take the person out of the palace this time?
The person has committed a severe crime,
and I have no reason to save him.
Your eyes are red.
I haven't slept well,
so my eyes are red.
Shiyi.
We've known each other for such a long time that
you can't cheat me.
The person knows you for a longer time.
Did my military advisor tell you this?
When His Majesty was here,
they chatted about this
and I heard that.
His Majesty just asked me
whether I would ask for leniency for the person just now.
Why would you ask for leniency?
Because of the surname Gao?
Liu Yuan's surname is not Gao.
You...you've been talking about Liu Yuan?
Who else should I be talking about?
Let this go.
Go to bed early.
Master, where are you going?
There's curfew in the palace.
You could be taken as an assassin.
Why are you following me?
I'm afraid you would be in danger.
Why?
You've drunk a lot tonight.
Actually, I can drink a lot.
That's right.
What's right?
Mom once read me several lines
about you.
“Lying on the beach with numerous corpses after getting drunk
indulges in singing”
I should have realized that
you can drink a lot.
The crazy things I did at a young age
was actually written down.
There were not enough soldiers back then
and we didn't know if we would survive,
so I could indulge myself.
Just put this on.
You put it on.
I'm not cold.
Come here.
Master, what are you digging for?
Wine.
I'll see an old friend in a while.
He buried the wine with me.
We promised to
get it out
and celebrate my victorious comeback.
Who are you?
Let me go!
Do you still want to be alive?
Do you hear me?
Let me go!
Aren't you afraid of getting your families and relatives killed?
Hurry up and let me go!
Who are you?
Tell me!
Who...who are you?
Who actually are you?
You!
That makes sense.
Only you will come to see me.
I've dug this jar of wine out
to meet you for the last time.
I should have
asked Empress Gao to
kill you back then.
Thanks for caring about me when we were young.
I cared about one who wants my life now.
Give me some wine.
My throat is sore.
Well.
You're the only one
that makes me concede defeat.
Do you have any unfulfilled wish?
I've been arrogating power in court for years
and I've enjoyed the dignity as an emperor.
I have no pities.
Is there any family member
you need me to take care of?
I have a son.
I'll have him escorted back to Pingcheng
so that he can escape this misfortune.