.
I want to stay in Xizhou.
Like you, Senior Brother.
Like you, Senior Sister.
Just one more step.
I can stay in Wangfu.
I'll take the next step.
Don't come.
Episode 16
Mother, are you still blaming me for what happened back then?
No.
I just don't understand you.
You and I are biological mother and son.
Why do you always believe in what others say and not me?
Your grandfather was not even a year old.
The Empress Dowager was a court lady.
They were very close.
Why can they do that?
You and I are biological mother and son.
Why can't you do that?
These years,
Mother used all kinds of means in the palace.
She has been hard to convince.
I didn't see her.
But after Zhao Teng's death,
I didn't want to be involved in Mother's bedding.
But Mother,
she took over the treasury and used it to make a living.
And the money is more important than the money.
It's also very important.
I can't leave it alone.
Hui'er,
if it wasn't for me,
you would have died.
Without the money,
there would be no me.
What can you do if you let your uncles be so arrogant?
I don't want to let the people down.
What do you mean by that?
Come.
Why are you not drinking?
Are you afraid that I will poison you?
Drink it.
I didn't poison you.
I can't bear to leave you.
You are my biological son.
I am the most
in the position of your father.
You'd better stop drinking.
Why?
The doctor said that you shouldn't drink these days.
I am willing to leave.
I will take my leave.
Hui'er,
since you are filial,
why don't you drink this for me?
Have you ever tried this wine?
I have.
Give this wine to His Majesty.
Empress Dowager.
Your Majesty.
Leave us.
You are so clever.
You poisoned the wine.
Drink it.
Your Majesty.
Your Beilun
has decided to rest
in the ancient palace.
Your Majesty.
Mother.
I beg you.
Let His Majesty see his child.
Mother.
Empress Dowager.
The child is not alive.
Mother.
Take the child away first.
Yes.
Mother.
Please.
Give my child back to me.
Mother.
My child.
Empress Dowager.
Is that the grandson?
Yes.
I am happy to have a grandson.
Send out the news.
His Majesty is happy to have a prince.
Zhongzhou City is now free from the Xiaojin.
The palace is on fire.
It will be closed for 15 days.
Yes.
Empress Dowager.
Please.
General Qin has gone out of the city.
He went south.
He is lonely.
He ran away.
He is short-lived.
He is not worth it.
Where is Concubine Jiang?
She died.
What is your name?
Empress Dowager.
I am Yuan Wuchu.
I am the vice commander of the imperial guards.
From now on,
you will be in charge of the imperial guards.
Thank you Empress Dowager.
Kill the palace guards,
eunuchs,
and the imperial doctors
who gave birth to Concubine Jiang.
If you leave
one alive,
you will not live either.
Yes.
Empress Dowager.
Qin Yan is a member of the King of Nancheng.
If he tells the emperor that he died...
He wouldn't dare.
He is not afraid of me.
He is afraid of his old master, King of Nancheng.
I think
he went south
to learn from Liu Changshan
and run southward.
I congratulate you.
In 15 days,
the crown prince will be conferred.
Yes.
This is the divorce letter I wrote.
Keep it.
Once the aunt
gets the Empress Dowager's approval,
she will give it to the princess.
If she does so, she can leave the mansion
and not be comforted.
Okay.
You must protect yourself in the palace.
Who just left the city?
General, it was the imperial governor.
He...
Miss, go back to the mansion first.
Yes.
You guard the door. Yes.
Come with me.
Look.
This is the gift of Grand Tutor Xie.
It's from Grand Tutor.
Why do you have it?
Someone wrapped this in a jimpa
and threw it into the Cui mansion.
He said it was his personal gift.
As long as you see it, you will recognize it.
The letter says
there is a change in the palace.
Okay.
I felt strange
at the gate.
The people were celebrating.
The general was waiting for me.
I didn't want to be in the way.
Third Miss, a eunuch
came to the mansion.
He said he would take the princess and the girl to the palace to congratulate the prince.
The princess came to the palace.
Why did she let Shiyi go with her?
The eunuch said
Prince Guangling grew up in the palace.
He has a deep relationship with the emperor and the empress dowager.
The empress dowager has always
treated Prince Guangling as her own son.
The prince was born.
He will let the future princess
come to the palace to congratulate him.
Please take my greetings
to the palace.
This is the imperial edict
from the empress dowager.
Don't worry, I will do it.
Sister,
why don't you come with me?
I will go with you.
Bravo!
The people are celebrating the birth of the new prince.
I have long forgotten
that Brother Ziqian is the new prince.
Life is full of ups and downs.
Shiyi, he has suffered a lot in the palace.
He has not won the throne
and he has not married you.
Be good to him.
As long as you are good to him,
I will do my best to take care of you.
I have never heard of these words.
You are not allowed to say it again.
Even if you are the princess,
you can't say it.
The palace
Prince Guangling, Your Highness.
Princess, Shiyi
I will take you to the palace.
The empress dowager is having a banquet with the concubines.
I will not be able to attend the banquet.
I will send you in and then I will leave.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Have you ever seen the new prince?
The empress dowager is very nervous
about the birth of the new prince.
She personally reported to the palace to take care of him.
She has never seen the new prince's birth mother.
I will go with you.
Every palace has died before.
The luck is hard to disperse.
It is much colder than outside the palace.
I am the one who took care of Li's family.
It is just that Li's family
is only born for me.
And will always be like this to everyone.
Let's go.
Do not let the empress dowager wait.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do this.
If the relationship between people
is really unpredictable,
your brother is the governor of Taiyuan County
and you are watching my father.
But you and I are drinking in the palace
at the banquet.
It's you, Imperial Concubine Jing.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
I have a question in my heart.
I want you to answer it.
Imperial Concubine, please ask.
His Majesty sent Cui Feng to the Taiyuan County
to be the governor.
Is there a saying that
I can kill my father at any time?
Governor Zhou has the duty of monitoring
and also the duty of transporting troops
to suppress local feudal lords.
Not only my brother,
but all the 13 governors of our country
are the same.
I think as long as General Jing
is loyal to His Majesty,
my brother will never use military power.
Thank you for your understanding.
Episode 11
Have an early rest.
Imperial Concubine has drunk a lot tonight.
How can she see His Majesty?
His Majesty adores Imperial Concubine Jiang.
He rarely calls other concubines,
especially Imperial Concubine.
Everyone in the palace knows
that he and His Majesty are not compatible.
Since Imperial Concubine Jiang gave birth to a son,
there has been no concubine who can see His Majesty.
facing the battlefields personally.
What are you looking at,
not afraid of being seen.
What happened?
A big thing.
Your Majesty,
the family is dead.
My son
is dead.
Your Majesty.
We shaved our hair.
Let's go to the palace
and pray for His Majesty.
I don't want to shave my hair.
I guessed that
only you would disobey me
in the palace.
I also guessed that
the Empress Dowager
would not dare to touch me.
The 13th Army of the court
is the most powerful in Xizhou.
Taiyuan Army is the most powerful.
My father never let anyone do anything.
You want me to shave my hair
is to make me
locked in the palace and threaten my father.
You are the most intelligent
in the palace.
It's a pity
that your man, my son
is already dead.
Send the Empress Dowager and the concubines
to the palace.
I will go to the palace.
Let's go to the palace.
Your marriage with Zixing
will be delayed.
His Majesty is the Emperor,
and the people are all his.
How can Shiyi talk about marriage?
Then, let's stay in the palace
and accompany me for a while.
I will obey your order.
You are not a concubine.
You are the only daughter of Cui Sanniang.
Prince Guanglin's wife is not married yet.
Brother is the heir of Taiyun County.
Master is the king of Xiao Nan.
This is the reason
why I want you to stay in the palace.
Shiyi guessed it right.
Your Majesty is six years old.
I held his hand
and walked into the Taiji Palace.
Now, I am lost.
He has left,
but I am still here.
If you are sad,
you should go back to the palace and rest.
The Emperor died
because of your uncle and three royal relatives.
They worked together
to make you wait for him all night.
I am so worried.
I have told you
that it is dangerous at night.
If you are not careful,
the game will be over.
Tonight, there are people
who are with Cui.
I am sure of it.
I will go to the palace.
This is the place
where the previous emperors
used to deal with political affairs.
Your Majesty.
Write three letters for me.
Yes.
This letter
tells him
that the Emperor died
and his grandson is going to be crowned.
The situation in the court is complicated.
He asked if he could
enter the capital alone
as he did before
and confess his feelings
in front of the officials.
Why didn't you write it down?
I can't write it down.
Why?
Please find someone else.
I can't write this letter down.
Tell me what you are afraid of.
Just one letter
makes you afraid of what?
You are afraid that
Zhou Shengchen will see
your handwriting,
worry about you and risk your life to enter the capital.
Are you two
really like the rumors
and have a secret relationship?
Master treats all his disciples like family.
If today,
my senior or senior wrote this letter,
he would come to save me.
But if today,
my senior or senior were here,
no one would do this
and put the master in danger.
You are not afraid of death?
I will let the Empress Dowager decide.
You
are a man of love.
You are a man of love.
But you are very secretive.
This Prince of Nanchen
is really crazy.
Shiyi,
your uncle saved me twice.
I won't kill you.
Guards.
If my father knew you treated me like this,
he would have killed you.
Concubine Gu,
the rest of the concubines have been sent to Ni Guan.
Only Concubine Gu is left here.
This is enough to show the Empress Dowager
how she takes care of you.
How she takes care of me?
She is afraid of my father.
Father.
I'm afraid you don't know how old Concubine Gu was.
She was older than your father.
What happened in the end?
She didn't die in the palace.
She died in the palace.
It's the same path you just walked.
You are all noble people.
As long as you don't hurt each other,
no one can hurt you.
Close the door.
How did the older brother
of Empress Dowager Gao die?
After His Majesty ascended the throne,
Gao Guo was tricked into the palace
by Empress Dowager's edict.
Xiao Lu was surrounded by soldiers in the palace.
She was killed by the
fire of the fire.
Did Empress Dowager want to
kill her father
or your master
for the sake of the common good?
Empress Dowager.
How is the outside of the palace?
The ceremony is still going on.
It's very lively.
Prime Minister hasn't arrived yet?
He is on his way.
Close the gate.
Without my order,
no one is allowed to enter Zhongzhou City.
Yes.
We are sorry.
Bye.
Stop.
Push it! This is the carriage from the city!
This is our people.
You are?
The King of Nancheng.
So boring.
Imperial Concubine is not like a person who has no husband.
She doesn't like me. Why should I be sad for her?
But you have been to heaven and earth, and had a couple's ceremony.
Won't you have a different feeling from others?
I have been to heaven and earth because I value him as the King.
I have been to heaven and earth because I want a prince and want to be the Empress Dowager.
I have feelings between Liu Hui and Concubine Jiang.
I don't have feelings between her and me.
Sooner or later, the East Capital, the Central Capital, the West Capital, and the West State will belong to my father.
By then, your father will die soon.
It seems that we can only have the friendship of tonight.
Yes. We are destined to be enemies in the future.
But before we become enemies, we have to get out alive.
Your Highness.
Why did you come back?
I...
I finally got you back.
I have a friend to save me.
I was so angry that I tried to kill the prince.
No.
Actually, the child is fake.
He is not a prince.
Concubine Jiang didn't have a prince.
She did.
But the child was gone that night.
The Empress Dowager was afraid that this would be exposed.
She killed 29 people in the Imperial Palace, including the imperial physician, maid and maid maid.
And Concubine Jiang.
I was threatened.
I shouldn't have said anything.
Prime Minister's family is in the mansion.
How can you threaten them?
No. She...
My master didn't mean to investigate this matter.
If you do as he said,
you will have the chance to atone for your crime.
I am willing to listen to your order.
From tonight,
they will follow you step by step.
Okay.
What's next?
What is he going to do?
The new emperor will ascend the throne.
He will listen to the government.
Since he wants the new emperor to ascend the throne,
you help him to accomplish this.
Let an unborn prince ascend the throne?
Yes.
Do you remember how Liu Yuan was punished?
Of course.
Do as I said.
Don't think about anything else.
Otherwise, you will be the first one to be buried for the emperor.
I will definitely make up for my mistake.
I will listen to your order.
Liu Yuan
So
I am your uncle.
From now on, you don't need to be a servant.
You don't need to be a servant.
You are worthy of being a servant.
Today, I only brought
the wooden sword from the imperial palace.
I am your uncle.
To me, you are more important than the imperial palace.
Uncle.
It's all my fault.
I didn't protect you well.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
your Majesty
Your Majesty
Your Majesty.
The country cannot be without a king.
Although Your Majesty has returned to heaven,
you left us a prince.
I think
the prince should ascend the throne immediately
to stabilize the court and the people.
Your Majesty.
This concerns the safety of the country.
The prince has just been born
and he has already ascended the throne.
He is afraid that the people will not obey him
and the country will be in chaos.
Your Majesty, please be careful.
It is a custom for our young children to ascend the throne.
The five-year-old Emperor Gaozu ascended the throne
and the six-year-old Emperor Xianli ascended the throne.
It is all decided by Your Majesty.
Why can't we do it today?
You are wrong.
Your Majesty.
The six-year-old Emperor Gaozu ascended the throne
is a wise decision.
Back then, the Gao family was in control of the country.
If the Emperor does not ascend the throne,
Zhongzhou will be in the hands of the Gao family.
Now, there is no danger of that time.
Why don't we choose a man
who is just the right age
to take over the throne?
The Emperor's bones are not yet cold.
The young son is still crying in the palace.
Cui Shizhong can't wait to take over the new crown.
I am not thinking about it.
I have no selfish motives.
You don't have to explain to me.
Explain to the Empress Dowager.
Empress Dowager.
Prepare to ascend the throne.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The Cui family's objection
makes me very uneasy.
After ascending the throne, everything will be settled.
Even if Cui family
opposes with the Yizhong Wang family,
it is useless.
But this child can hide for a while.
He can't hide for a lifetime.
The late King of the Lingtao
has a five-year-old son
named Liu Zichen.
Do you remember him?
Except for Zhou Shengchen,
this is the closest
to the blood of the previous emperor.
Tomorrow, I will take him to the palace.
After this,
Empress Dowager will order the world
to say that she was deceived by Concubine Jiang.
It turns out that the prince is a fake.
Push all this on Concubine Jiang.
But Concubine Jiang died early.
The outside world doesn't know.
After that, the Empress Dowager ordered
Concubine Jiang to die four times.
Liu Zichen will be the emperor.
Then you can explain to the officials
and the kings.
A five-year-old child
is not up to the Empress Dowager.
It's so absurd.
I'm afraid the officials in the court won't believe it.
I'm here.
Zhao, Liu Zichen enters the palace.
I obey the decree.
Master is worried about Junior Sister.
Junior Sister is in the palace.
The Empress Dowager knows
she can control many people.
She doesn't dare to do anything.
Since Master is so determined,
why are you still worried?
Go to Cui's Mansion.
The Empress Dowager is worried about Junior Sister.
She is worried about the Empress Dowager.
The Empress Dowager is worried about the Empress Dowager.