Talk about finding joy in the mundane.
Having a drink with a friend after work.
Isn't it just perfect?
It'd be even better
if it was with a boyfriend.
I don't agree.
Then give me your boyfriend.
I'll give you this in exchange.
Hey, Yeong-ju. Seriously!
Hey!
EPISODE 1
Hey, do you still have
the kimchi you gave me last time?
I'm bringing it now.
I hear a phone vibrating. It's yours.
-Mine?
-Yes.
-Hi, Gi-seok.
-Hey, are you still there?
No, I'm at Yeong-ju's place
for another round.
I see. When are you going home, then?
In a bit, I guess? I'll just sleep here
if I end up staying late.
Do you have an afternoon shift tomorrow?
Yes. But it's Saturday,
so I have to be there before lunchtime.
-Okay.
-Is your team dinner over?
They want to go elsewhere for more drinks,
but I'm playing basketball tomorrow,
so I'm going home.
I got invited to the basketball club
started by my fellow college alumni.
Oh, really? You should go, then.
All right. I'll talk to you tomorrow.
-Okay, bye.
-Bye.
What?
You guys are in a relationship.
Don't all couples say things like
"I love you" to each other
before hanging up?
Cut it out.
This is why
long-term relationships are bad.
Hey, it depends on the person.
We were never lovey-dovey
even at the beginning. You know that.
Right, you two have always been
like a middle-aged couple.
We're not that bad.
I've never envied your relationship.
You told me to hand him over.
You can keep him.
-Jeez.
-Cheers.
Cheers.
-Good. That was great.
-Great job.
You guys did well. Okay.
-Good job.
-Well done. Good shot!
-That was good. Great job.
-Thank you.
Oh, boy.
-Keep it up. For just a few more minutes.
-You did well.
You're doing great. Keep it up.
You're playing man-to-man defense?
Slow down, okay?
Remember to set a solid off-ball screen
and move faster.
-That pass was good.
-Yes, okay.
Guys. The defenders keep moving, you know.
-Yes.
-You need to keep up with them.
-I have to go.
-You're leaving?
-Good job.
-Get going, then.
-I'm off.
-See you. Great job today.
-Bye.
-Good job, guys.
-See you all next week.
-Focus on the game, okay?
I'm off, guys.
-Bye.
-See you next week.
-Come next week.
-Hey, I'm leaving.
Hey, wait. This is Gi-seok.
I've told you about him before.
He helped us rent this gym today.
-This is the friend I told you about.
-I see.
You probably don't remember him.
I feel like I've seen him before,
but why don't I remember him?
Did you also start your undergrad in 2004?
Yes, that's right. I'm Yu Ji-ho.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kwon Gi-seok.
Jeez, look at you. He's younger than you.
Don't be so polite during the games.
Just crush them down.
Especially this dude.
When it comes to basketball,
he's such a snob.
You are no match for me.
Look at that.
This is exciting.
Let's play together next time.
Yes, of course.
I won't go easy on you though.
You shouldn't.
-I'll be off, then. Bye.
-Bye.
Let's go, Gi-seok.
WOORI PHARMACY
-Hello.
Do you have any medicine for hangovers?
I need something strong.
This will help too. You can have a sip.
Okay, thank you.
If you have any rubber bands
lying around, could I please get one?
-This is all I have.
-That's exactly what I need.
Thank you.
Oh, here.
What's my total?
-It's 6,000 won.
-Okay.
Where's my wallet?
Where did it go?
-Did you lose your wallet?
-No. This is so weird.
Last night, I...
Never mind. Just a second, please.
Well, it looks like I left it
at my friend's place. What should I do?
Where is your friend's place?
She lives over there.
-Are you sure your wallet is there?
-I'm pretty sure...
No, I know that it's there.
Just a moment, please.
-What's my total again?
-It's 6,000 won.
Gosh, why isn't she picking up?
I'm in a rush now.
So I'll come back in the evening and...
Actually, my friend is still asleep.
-As soon as she wakes up, I'll tell her--
-You can just go.
No, I need to settle up.
Give me your account number.
Then I can send it to you right away.
No, just go. You said
you'll settle up next time. Just do that.
I'm sorry.
I promise I'll come back and settle up.
Actually, excuse me.
It's not like I opened it.
-Pardon?
-You opened that new bottle.
I never said I wanted to drink it.
You asked for a hangover remedy.
Right, I did.
But I never asked you
to open the bottle and mix it for me.
Right, I made a mistake.
You said you're in a rush.
Shall I give you my number?
I mean, just in case.
I'll definitely come back and settle up,
but just in case you don't trust me.
It's hard to trust people these days,
so I understand.
Zero, one, zero.
Four, five, nine, three...
Hey.
Oh, you don't have to do this.
Do you need more?
I'm not giving you this money.
Pay me back.
What is your name?
I'm Yu Ji-ho.
I'm Lee Jeong-in.
Be safe, Ms. Lee Jeong-in.
It's in the bag
from the convenience store.
You bought the beer last night.
I guess that's when you put it there.
Hey, I'll either pick it up after work
or if I get off too late...
Anyway, hold on to it.
How will you pay for the taxi ride?
I'll call Ha-rin and ask her to come down.
Hey, if you pass by the pharmacy...
Never mind.
Pharmacy? Why? Are you feeling sick?
No, I'm fine.
Anyway, hold on to my wallet, okay?
Bye.
ADD NEW CONTACT
I memorized it.
The elevated levels
of fine particulate matter have dropped,
so you can enjoy being outdoors
this weekend.
However, you should still wear a mask
when you go outside
for your health's sake.
That's it for the 12 p.m. news update.
Thank you all for watching.
-Good work.
-Thank you.
-Great job!
-Good work, everyone.
-Great job.
-Well done, everyone.
Don't touch any of my stuff.
What a cheeky...
This is getting rid of my hangover.
It's not getting rid of mine.
I think I drank way too much last night.
Really?
I wish meeting people
could be like this too.
I want to meet people who continue to grow
on me even though I had no expectations.
The first encounter could be all you need
to be smitten by someone, like destiny.
My goodness.
You don't even believe in horoscopes.
What's gotten into you?
Well, that makes me feel
as if I'm being brainwashed.
"Don't do this. Don't go there."
I don't like it.
But it's not like you enjoy adventure.
Hey, who even gets a chance
to be adventurous?
You go to school, get your degree,
and get a job.
After that, all you do is work
and hang out with friends here and there.
Why leave out dating?
It's the cause of all sorts of problems.
Thankfully,
even that aspect of my life has been
relatively problem-free.
I don't like to be in a relationship
that is too boring.
-"Boring"?
-Yes.
I don't like it.
Just a second.
-Hey.
-What account number?
What?
Your message.
You asked for my account number.
Oh, that. It was for someone else.
I guess I sent it to you by mistake.
I'm sorry.
-For whom?
-What?
Who was it for?
One of my clients. A publishing firm.
Thank you.
PHARMACIST
YOUR BANK ACCOUNT NUMBER!
Hurry up.
-This is...
-What?
-I'm like this too though.
-What did you say?
Don't worry. It looks fine.
Security activated.
How's the new department?
It's the evaluation team,
so the workload is high.
And I'll be away
from the office quite often.
I thought you worked at your desk all day
since you work for a bank.
Anyway, that means you'll be even busier
from now on.
That being said...
Yes?
Shouldn't we start talking
about getting married?
-Why are you surprised?
-I'm not surprised.
I mean, we should get married.
Why are you all quiet?
What do you want to hear?
What now?
What do you mean, "What now?"
Did you tell Yeong-ju to come out?
I texted her just now.
You two can have dinner together.
What about you?
I was going to go home
and get some work done if she's free.
I need to get the hang of my new tasks.
Then just go home.
I don't have much of an appetite anyway.
I'm not saying I don't have time
to have dinner with you.
Let's grab a bite together.
-It's okay.
-What is okay?
I said it's okay.
Jeez, forget it.
What?
Why are you sulking over nothing?
Who's sulking?
I know you well enough, okay?
Seriously.
WOORI PHARMACY
-Hello.
-Thanks.
-You seem a little down.
It'd be nice to grab dinner together.
I already got food
from the convenience store.
Why are you downcast?
-Did you two fight?
-Should we fight?
I hope you win.
I'm off.
-I'll call you later.
-Okay.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm coming.
You're so slow.
Dude, you always lose
when we play basketball together.
He's boasting
after winning just a few times.
Hey, you've met Gi-seok.
If he joins my team, you'll be done for.
Game over.
Who is he?
I told you one of my co-workers
is our fellow alumnus.
He helped us rent the school gym today.
His father is the chairman
of the foundation.
-I envy him.
-Oh, right.
His girlfriend's dad is the principal
of that school. I heard she's hot.
Hey, seriously. How can life be so unfair?
-It pisses me off.
-You've never seen her?
No, never.
But I want to arrange something soon.
After that, I'll set you two up
with girls. That's the plan.
Hey, I have to study.
Oh, right.
As for you, we'll wait
until you pass the civil service exam.
But you're on board, right?
I'll figure it out myself.
What?
You're so busted. You'd better tell us.
Tell us already.
You're seeing someone, aren't you?
No, not at all.
I should go bring some beer.
Hey, you're stuck in the pharmacy all day.
And all you do on weekends is play
basketball. What is wrong with you?
You should meet girls
whenever you get a chance. Date anyone--
Gosh, he said he'll figure it out himself.
I'd love to see him figuring it out.
I mean,
it's not like he committed a crime.
Hey, please.
What? We're friends.
Hey, did I offend you?
Whatever.
Hey, the meat will burn.
There's more beer, so drink up.
Here.
I said we should have dinner together.
How stubborn.
Don't put the blame on me.
We should move in together soon.
This won't happen if we live together.
We'd eat, sleep,
go home, and go to work together.
It'll be convenient.
So, you want to marry me to avoid hassles?
Why do you keep putting words in my mouth?
Then what is it?
What can I do?
How can I make you feel better?
You said you know me well.
What can I do?
Get out of my sight at once.
I will if you get out.
All right.
Okay, I heard you.
I'll make it up to you next weekend.
Think of what you want to do.
Just go.
Sweet dreams.
My gosh.
Is that you, Jae-in?
-Jeong-in.
-What's going on?
When did you get here?
What's up with this...
Does Mom know you're here?
Can we talk inside?
Gosh, I'm so cold and hungry.
You're unbelievable.
-Let's talk inside.
-Okay.
I was such a great photographer
even back then.
Both of you look amazing in this photo.
Come here and eat this.
Okay!
Thank you.
It's so good.
First, tell me what happened.
Hold on. Let me have some kimchi first.
What? It's not Mom's kimchi.
Come on. Tell me.
Not much happened.
I had chased a guy for a while,
but he reported me
to the police as a stalker,
so I got a restraining order.
-You?
-Yes, me.
Stalking is considered a serious crime
in France.
I was afraid I'd keep
going there to see him.
So I thought, "I should go back to Korea
to avoid becoming a criminal."
That's why I'm here.
So, you actually stalked him?
I just asked him to marry me
a few times, and he overreacted.
Marry you?
Jae-in, have you lost your mind?
Love incapacitates your logical brain.
You call that love?
You're seriously crazy.
Love makes you crazy.
How's your relationship?
Not bad.
What?
This is delicious.
CHATS
LEE JEONG-IN
YOUR BANK ACCOUNT NUMBER!
ALARM WILL GO OFF IN TWO DAYS
ALARM IS SET FOR 7:30 A.M.,
MONDAY, MARCH 11
GI-SEOK
Don't eat the whole thing.
You'll gain weight.
CHATS
PHARMACIST
YOUR BANK ACCOUNT NUMBER!
-Drive safely.
-Thank you. Take care.
-You're still up.
-Yes.
-What brings you here this late?
-I was in the area.
-Have you eaten?
-Yes, I have.
You'll sleep here, right?
I have to leave early in the morning,
so don't mind me and go to bed.
Daddy.
What are you doing here?
I came to see you
because I suddenly started missing you.
-Did you not miss me?
-I missed you.
Oh, boy! Gosh, you'll beat me soon.
-I'm stronger than you are.
-You are?
Really?
Why are you so strong?
Here's your ox bone soup.
-Enjoy.
-Hey.
I went ahead and ordered to save time.
Good call.
Why did you have to go there?
It's about the same thing
every single time.
"Transparent management"
of the foundation and so on.
So, how's the new department?
Well...
Not bad.
Some at the executive level
used to work in the evaluation team.
Start thinking about getting married.
It'd be nice to focus on work
with your wife's support.
Word has it that Assemblyman Jang
will be appointed Director of the FSS.
His youngest daughter
is so successful.
It's not easy to become a professor
at such a young age.
She's very impressive.
Cut out people that you don't need.
Jeong-in is a good girl.
She's not the only "good girl."
It's just not easy to find
the right one to marry.
Don't leave it to the last minute.
You should end it now.
I'll figure out what to do.
You'd better make the right decision.
I'll arrange something
with Assemblyman Jang's family.
Maybe later on.
I told you that I'll figure it out.
-I'll think hard about it.
-About what?
Well, it's about my marriage.
I need to do some thinking.
Marriage isn't some kids' role-play game.
It's a part of the business.
Just remember that.
SUYEONG HIGH SCHOOL
PRINCIPAL LEE TAE-HAK
ANYONE CAN EARN 5 MILLION WON A MONTH
WITHIN 5 YEARS OF RETIREMENT
Come in.
Mr. Kwon.
I'm just stopping by on my way back.
Have a seat.
-All right. Did you have to step out?
-Yes, to the Teachers' Pension Office.
And I saw Gi-seok too.
He works in that area, you know.
Right. Come to think of it,
I haven't seen him in quite a while.
Is he doing well?
-He's well.
-Good.
Gi-seok is a guy, so we're not in a rush,
but shouldn't you rush
your daughter a little?
Well, frankly...
We are getting anxious.
I think it's high time for us
to start discussing the topic.
Does she want to get married?
Yes, of course she does. They've been
together for a while, you know.
They must be quite attached to each other.
I don't think it's that serious.
I wouldn't say they're "attached."
Your eldest daughter married
a great guy. Jeong-in will do the same.
I heard she's a great catch.
Well, yes.
Let's go for lunch tomorrow
or the day after.
-Do you not want to?
-I do, of course.
-I'll call you.
-Okay.
WIFE
You don't know what it's about?
No, I'm not annoyed. Why does he
want me to come by out of the blue?
Mom, tell Seo-in to come as well
so that she can join us for the meal.
No, you do it. I'm busy now.
Okay, bye.
You look like you're going
to fight someone today.
Hey, you're going home
right after work, right?
Why? Shall I get booze ready
and wait for you again?
Get a lot of booze.
Gosh, I'm already scared.
I should stop by the pharmacy
and get something for my liver.
Do you go there often?
The pharmacy? Which one?
The one in your area, on your way home.
Right, there is a pharmacy.
You sound as if you're a regular there.
It was a slip of the tongue.
It didn't sound like that.
What do you want?
Did you run home to tell your mommy?
Your mother asked me to come over.
Then come.
And be dragged to hell with you?
Seo-in, what are you
trying to achieve by being cheeky?
You seem scared.
That smart brain of yours
must be on the fritz,
but you're the one
with everything to lose here.
-Whether you come or not is your choice.
-But...
What am I going to do with her cheeky ass?
-You're here.
-How could I not come when you asked?
You're the best. Why weren't you inside?
I had to take a call.
-What do you think Dad wants?
-Who knows?
Still, I can probably guess.
Just being with you girls only
makes me miss Jae-in more.
Seo-in, dig in already.
You seem gaunt on TV these days.
Are you on a diet again?
No.
Are you sick then?
We should see a doctor tomorrow.
Her husband's a doctor
and her in-laws own a hospital.
You're overstepping.
I'm not sick, Mom,
so please don't overstep.
Is your husband busy?
He hasn't been over lately.
He just started his night shifts.
I heard he couldn't make time.
He's back at 11 p.m. at the earliest
and I should be home by then.
Should I tell him to come?
So how's it going with Gi-seok?
It's pretty much the same.
So you'll just stick to dating him?
Maybe, or I could even end it. Who knows?
Are you kidding me?
Why date someone you'll break up with?
Should I call it quits then?
Why are you being this way?
Aren't you going to marry him?
Who knows what will happen?
What's going on?
Did you say something to her?
I threatened her to stay unmarried.
I don't care. Talk with Gi-seok
and set a date for this year.
Stalling will only
make you lose out in the end.
Seo-in, sorry about this.
I won't be pushed into it like her.
I want to weigh my options
and get married on my own terms
when I'm ready.
I don't know when it'll be though.
Pushed? By whom?
Seo-in, you tell me.
Did I force you into this marriage?
Did I?
Yes.
I'm not blaming you for it all.
It's partly my fault as well.
Are you two kidding me?
Is marriage a joke to you?
It seems to be to you.
I'm an adult, Dad.
Please respect my wishes
when it comes to my marriage.
I'm sorry.
It's true that your marriage
gave me clarity though.
I know.
Thanks for understanding.
There's something I want you
to understand too.
I'm...
getting a divorce.
Not any time soon,
but we're no longer living together.
Will you be all right though?
Rumors spread fast these days
and this will hurt your image.
That's been holding me back all this time.
The divorce...
Did Si-hoon agree to it?
I'll have to make sure that he does.
Are you all right?
Yes, for now at least.
Can I help in any way?
Just take my side when the time comes.
I've always been on your side.
Are you really all right though?
Call me whenever you need to.
I'll always be on standby.
-You know that, right?
-Of course.
We're all in such a mess.
Jae-in is at my house.
No news is never good news with her.
Tell me about it.
Let's get together soon.
Unbelievable.
Just so you know, we're in this together.
It must be a sister thing.
Goodness.
Seo-in, you've got this.
Thanks.
Unbelievable.
It's snowing!
If only I had a date tonight. Damn it.
-Why are you upset?
-Because it's snowing.
I'm not going home early
on a day like this.
-Is that a rule?
-When it's snowing, yes.
Good night then.
-Have you already made plans?
-I will on my way home.
-See you tomorrow.
-Bye.
You're here.
Why didn't you text me
your account number?
I asked you a question.
So I can see you one more time like this.
Can I get my change?
Have you had dinner?
If not, we could grab a bite with this.
I don't like eating with strangers.
What is it?
You memorized my number,
so how am I a stranger now?
I have good memory, that's all.
You're getting ahead of yourself
if you thought it meant something more.
It's not like we'll cross paths again.
Take care then.
So both your parents and his parents
are starting to talk about you guys
getting married?
I want to marry because I want to,
not because I'm at that age.
For you, logic always wins
but not when it comes to love.
Charming, aren't I?
That must be our chicken.
-I'll get it.
-Thank you.
How did you know I was here?
Did you follow me?
I don't need the change.
Up here.
Leave already!
I'll call the cops.
Thank you.
-Bye.
-Goodbye.
What took you so long?
It's nothing.
I can smell the chicken. Hurry up.
-I can't wait.
-Hey.
Do you know your neighbor upstairs?
In which unit?
The one above.
A woman around my age
and a married couple.
A married couple?
Or they could just be living together.
And...
I don't know.
I don't cross paths with them.
And I only moved here recently.
Why do you ask?
I just saw someone heading upstairs.
It was a young guy.
Not bad looking.
How handsome is he?
I only got a glimpse of him.
Have you seen the guy
who lives with his girlfriend
in the unit above?
Was he that handsome?
Do you want me to go and check?
You know,
being curious about someone
is an important sign.
Your mind keeps wandering back to him.
It means you're interested.
If you weren't,
you wouldn't care about his whereabouts.
Just know this though.
That qualifies as cheating too.
LEE JEONG-IN
I apologize for the misunderstanding.
Get in.
-Go back in. It's cold. See you!
-Bye.
It's snowing heavily.
Have a safe trip home.
Thank you for the concern.
The next time it snows,
we should meet outside the pharmacy.
We?
WOORI PHARMACY
You didn't have to run.
You must be cold.
This is probably the best place.
It won't take long.
I just have something to say.
But it's cold out here.
Security deactivated.
Please have a seat.
Thank you.
I should have stuck to texting.
I feel like this is a mistake.
I have something to say too,
Jeong-in.
I have a boyfriend
who I'm planning to marry.
I have a kid.
You're married?
Then so what?
It doesn't make you
less decent or anything.
Is that what you wanted to say?
Of course not.
Well, I guess I would have told you that
at some point.
What I actually wanted to say is this.
I've been curious
about what kind of person you are.
I have been thinking about you
since I first saw you here.
I even thought of the possibility
of you being taken.
Still, just once...
Just once more...
Well, it led me here today.
It wasn't my intention,
but I did make it confusing for you.
-I apologize.
-Why would you?
It didn't last long, but I was happy.
That's probably burdening to hear.
Forget I said it.
As if that's possible.
I must have put you in a tough spot.
Not really.
Anyway,
let's be friends.
You don't meet people like this every day,
so we can be acquaintances from now on.
I'm sorry,
but I won't be comfortable with that.
Come on, let's go.
I've been cooped up inside
ever since I got back to Korea.
You're the one who secretly came back.
But I'm bored, Jeong-in.
It's my day off and I'd rather rest.
Your boyfriend will treat me
to a welcome back dinner anyway.
You've gotten more shameless.
Besides, why would we go there?
For fun.
Fun is something you find,
not wait around for.
Just don't tell people
that you're my sister.
Are you really not going?
I'm not.
I'm holding you to that.
Wait, it's snowing.
It was sunny this morning though.
It'll be the last snow this winter.
I should find someone to hang out with
since you're not interested.
Let's go out.
Just like that?
Why the sudden change of heart?
What is it?
-Jae-in.
-Yes?
What is it?
Can you hang out with a friend?
Hold on. Seriously?
Are you ditching me? For whom?
Well, suddenly...
Forget it. It's nothing.
Here comes a taxi.
You sure are fearless.
This is Dad's school you're at.
If you're caught, he'll kill me too.
But it's a Sunday. Come on.
Hey. Behave and
don't run your mouth, all right?
Are you Mom? Goodness.
Jeong-in, let's go over there.
There are no seats here.
Jeong-in,
isn't that Gi-seok?
-Come on.
-Pass.
-Shoot.
-Nice.
-Okay.
-Here we go!
Take your positions.
Stop him.
Get him!
All right, nice!
Keep it up!
Defense!
Watch it. Referee!
-Hi.
-Gosh, it's been a while.
You look happy and well.
I was born to live in the wild.
You're quite good at basketball.
I haven't shown all of my skills yet.
I find him attractive.
Isn't he attractive?
You said you'll start dating again,
didn't you? Don't be so sheepish.
Both sisters are gorgeous.
I think Jeong-in is the prettiest one.
Take care of Jeong-in instead.
She's very opinionated.
It's probably about us getting married.
Is it marriage you hate, or just me?
They say most get cold feet
when the idea is presented.
But your reaction is more than that.
Gi-seok, I think we need a break.
I want to tell you to be selfish.
You have the right to live a happy life.
This is top secret.
Actually, he has a kid.
If I had known,
I would've been nicer to him.
Everything else is fine.
Who cares if he's a single dad?
How is that fine?
What woman would like that?
I've moved on,
so you don't have to worry so much.
We can be friends then.
What would your boyfriend say?
Let's give it a shot.
Let's be friends.