(Nothing Uncovered)
(Production sponsors)
(Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, KOCCA)
(All locations, characters, organizations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(74M 4272)
Did he...
follow me here?
A knife from your place...
was left at the home of the person that was supposed to be framed,
so we know who will be the next target.
But what if it affects me?
That will not happen. I'm sure of it.
Let me pour you one, sir.
Try and imagine what could happen...
the moment your filth splatters on me.
(74M 4272)
What are you doing?
How dare you tail a police detective?
Assemblyman Mo! Your aide tailed me in Mueon.
Shall I question him at the precinct?
Or shall we talk at your place?
Goodness. You're naive.
Did you think you'd never get caught for tailing a cop?
(Episode 8)
I'm really sorry.
I apologize.
Mr. Na. Did hearing...
that I was headed to Mueon make you that anxious?
I heard you were digging up an old case...
Assemblyman Mo was in charge of,
so I wanted to figure out what was going on in advance.
We don't want another controversy,
like the one about politicians and the media.
This will probably cause a bigger controversy.
Why do something I never told you to do?
You didn't order him to do it?
No, I assure you he did not. That's far-fetched speculation.
"Far-fetched?"
It's a reasonable speculation from his perspective.
The other detective told me...
that Ms. Jin's ex-husband...
was Park Jin Soo, the manager of the Bongto plant.
Yes.
So that was why she approached my family...
and collected all the articles about me.
Yes, that's what I think too.
Do you think I'm connected...
to the murder of Cha Eun Sae as well as Ms. Jin's case?
Is it true that you were Cha Eun Sae's sponsor?
You're a police detective.
You shouldn't let such trashy tabloid stories...
confuse you, right?
In the upcoming local elections,
I'll run for Governor of Gangwon Province.
Both cases have nothing to do with me,
so I hope this doesn't affect...
my campaign schedule.
And you have nothing to do with Cha Geum Sae?
This is from Eun Sae's collection.
She wanted to drink this with me on my birthday.
You see,
Eun Sae and I got along more often than not.
We were the only family to each other.
Had I known it was you,
I wouldn't have done such a stupid thing, you know?
I know everything,
so just confess what you did.
- What? - This is nuts.
What I did? What do you mean?
You killed them all!
Jin Myung Sook and my sister too.
(My Honey)
The phone is turned off. Please leave a message...
Hello, Ms. Yang. Are you with Jung Won now?
What? Jung Won left earlier. She said she was tired.
What time did she leave?
Around 9:30pm? Why do you ask?
Well, she's not home yet, and her phone is off.
Really?
She'll be home soon.
Yes, please let me know if you hear from her.
Were you waiting for me?
I'm waiting for my wife.
Did you...
see my wife today?
Do you suffer from delusional jealousy? Ask her directly.
Her phone is off, and she's not home yet.
Her colleagues said she left at around 9:30pm. I can't reach her.
So, you didn't see my wife today.
Clearly, you seem relieved.
It's so obvious that you're still hung up on her.
Jung Won promised me...
that she'd keep her distance from you.
Jung Won and I will never split up,
so don't get your hopes up.
The phone is turned off. Please leave...
Hey, you! Darn you.
However much you freak out,
no one can hear you. Why?
When you passed out,
the guard made his last round.
So let's not waste each other's energy, okay?
Do you think no one will look for me?
What you're doing is a crime.
Don't you care about your crimes?
Darn you!
Hey.
I know everything.
The same person killed Jin Myung Sook and my sister.
Darn it.
And that it was you.
So...
quit acting out.
I'll record everything, so confess.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you convinced it was me?
You're trying really hard not to get it.
I'll show you, then.
You know...
what this bag is, don't you?
(The day of Jin Myung Sook's murder)
Hello, Mr. Song.
I'm watching her.
The woman stays indoors...
once she returns from work.
You can't dock my pay even if I don't get anything.
Okay, then. Bye.
No one else went up there.
It's me.
Jin Myung Sook seems to have a visitor.
If I find out who it is,
I want double.
Deal?
What the heck?
Lady.
What's this?
Darn it. Lady.
What's this? What's all this money?
Help...
What do you want me to do?
Darn it.
Help me.
That's why when you visited me,
you recognized this bag.
Because you were hiding right there.
Ms. Jin...
was still alive then?
The person who was hiding. It wasn't me. I...
I went in after Ms. Jin had died.
Don't you lie.
How did you recognize this bag, then?
I'd taken it and ran by then.
Anyway,
I didn't know you'd been at the scene.
What you're saying is,
you realized that just now...
because I told you?
Don't play any tricks.
Admit that you killed her.
Before I go down for it.
(Call)
(Reporter Seo Jung Won)
The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Seo Jung Won's phone has been off since last night.
Find out where it last was.
I'm at the place where Seo Jung Won's phone was turned off.
Her car's here with the door open and the dashcam memory card gone.
What? What about traffic cameras?
There aren't any. Something happened.
Who would try to hurt her?
Someone who'd hurt her on purpose...
I know you're a reporter, but can you try to play it safe?
What if Cha Geum Sae turns out to be the culprit?
Then you were alone in the house with a murderer.
I have to go.
Stop, right there.
Cha Geum Sae's car was spotted near where Seo's phone went off.
Locate the jerk now. Hurry!
Goodness.
Darn it.
Since you won't confess,
I must avenge my sister's death in person.
Okay.
I'll do it.
You should've said that sooner.
Where is it? Hang on.
Go.
The person who killed Jin Myung Sook.
It was you, Cha Geum Sae.
If you'd called for help right away,
she would've survived.
Why did you steal from your sister and beat her?
Why avenge her when you don't deserve to be a brother?
Do you have a death wish?
Darn it.
Shoot.
Open the door before I bash it in!
I'll kill you. Open the door.
Darn it.
The psycho witch.
She wants to go all the way, doesn't she?
Fine, then. Let's do it.
Just like you said, I found Jung Won's car at this location.
The memory card for her dashcam is gone.
Where's Detective Kim now?
I'm still looking into that.
(Gangha Felice Apartment)
That's Cha Eun Sae's house.
Sir, I just located Detective Kim.
Why isn't this breaking?
Darn it. Come on.
I kept telling you to behave, didn't I?
Okay?
Come here.
Come out.
Darn you.
Gosh.
Come on. Seriously!
Hey, look at us. What are we doing? Seriously.
Look at this mess. Okay? Darn it.
You should just die.
You...
You... Darn it.
Just die.
Die.
Hey.
You have the right to an attorney.
You'll have a chance to tell your side of the story.
But I clearly saw you choking her like this.
You...
Hey.
Tae Heon.
I'll cuff him. You should help Ms. Seo.
Hey, I'm the victim here.
Are you okay?
Darn it.
I'm sorry...
for taking so long.
Jung Won.
I'm sorry.
I should have gotten here faster.
What on earth happened?
I'm fine now.
You don't look fine at all.
Who did this to you? Who is this jerk that hurt you?
Let's go to the hospital first.
The police officer who found the victim...
must accompany her to the hospital and check her medical condition.
You're her guardian.
Why don't I drive all of us to the hospital?
You drove here. I'll see you at the hospital.
Let me see.
It stopped bleeding.
What did you bump into?
Do you feel dizzy or dazed?
Any headaches?
Tell me if you feel nauseous...
or if you think you're going to get dizzy.
Okay?
(Jihyang University Hospital)
(General Ward A)
- Could I get some water? - Okay.
She's a victim who just got examined and admitted to the hospital.
Must you interview her now?
I'm not an ordinary victim. I'm a journalist.
Go ahead.
The victim agreed. So please leave the room.
No. I'm her guardian. So I'll stay.
I will feel relieved only once I check your condition.
Let me stay by your side.
Your cell phone was turned off around 10pm yesterday.
Is that when you were abducted by Cha Geum Sae?
Yes.
I lost consciousness, and when I woke up,
I found myself in Cha Eun Sae's office.
Cha Geum Sae threatened me with a knife.
I thought I was going to die there.
I used the wine opener...
to attack Cha Geum Sae and tried to run away.
I can't watch this. Let's stop here.
Ms. Seo, look at me.
You're safe now.
Should we stop here if this is too much?
No.
Let's keep going.
Why did Cha Geum Sae abduct you?
He was certain that I was the one who killed Jin Myung Sook...
and Cha Eun Sae.
He wanted me to confess.
Go.
One.
Nice.
Getting updates on something while shooting? It must be urgent.
- Is it about work? - First, let's go ahead and fire.
My goodness.
That's embarrassing.
(Mr. Song)
Cha Geum Sae has been arrested...
for abducting and assaulting my daughter-in-law.
You're too tense,
for your own good.
I heard you had him keep tabs on the housekeeper.
You should just take care of it...
as an embarrassing mishap, don't you think?
Before you lose everything, that is.
The killer was hiding in there when Cha Geum Sae...
left with the bag full of cash, knowing Jin had been stabbed.
And he thought you were the killer.
That's what you mean, right?
- Yes. - Like he said,
it's possible that you were hiding in there...
before you came out and called it in,
pretending to be the first witness?
Are you asking my wife...
if she's the killer?
I thought you dropped your phone again, like the time...
when you found the housekeeper.
Was he...
watching me that night?
I will prove that it wasn't the case.
How?
That day, I was on the phone...
with my informant who gave me the location of a stock scammer...
when I found Ms. Jin Myung Sook.
But I think my informant...
was watching me at that moment.
That informant is Zeus, right?
Do you know who he is?
I must find out,
no matter what.
You can't go on like this.
That's enough.
You must think this world is a joke.
You think you can frame anyone by planting a knife at their home...
and that you can just abduct people...
and threaten them to say what you want to hear.
You have some nerve.
How dare you abduct and threaten someone?
Oh, you didn't just threaten her. You choked her,
which is considered attempted murder.
Were Jin and Cha your doing too? Just like Seo Jung Won?
I...
I did what I did because I knew this would happen, okay?
Jin Myung Sook and my sister. I knew they'd try...
to dump it all on me to destroy me! Do you hear me?
Mr. Cha Geum Sae, the late actress Cha Eun Sae's brother,
has been arrested for abducting and assaulting...
Reporter Seo Jung Won. The police are questioning him at the moment.
Reporter Seo Jung Won is resting to recover...
I'll go home tomorrow and go straight to work.
You don't need to come back here.
You're hurt. You should stay here longer...
Go home.
I want to be alone.
Why do you want to be alone?
You make me uncomfortable.
I understand why you feel that way,
but how do you think I'll feel if I go home alone,
knowing you're in the hospital all by yourself?
I couldn't come to your rescue and can't even stay by your side.
So what am I supposed to do as your husband?
I'll sleep at a hotel nearby.
Call me if you need my help.
Help...
What's this? What's all this money?
Darn it. What do you want me to do?
So, Jin Myung Sook died because you left her there to die.
How was I supposed to know she'd die?
You clearly heard her asking for help!
This was what Seo Jung Won said about the moment she found Jin.
"Her upper body was hanging off the balcony."
You didn't even think to call it in and just ran off,
so she got herself up with all her might...
and stood there to call for help...
and died eventually. She must've really wanted to live.
So, the same person killed Jin Myung Sook and Cha Eun Sae.
Who told you that? Was it Song Hyo Sung or Mo Hyung Taek?
Who ordered you to keep tabs on Jin Myung Sook?
It was Mo Hyung Taek, right?
He knew...
all about you framing Kim Min Chul, didn't he?
Was it your idea? Or did Mo Hyung Taek tell you to do it?
I...
If you feel...
even just an ounce of guilt as a human being,
tell me the truth.
I was going to ask you for it.
You must've been offended.
- Why? - You know, earlier in the day,
when I asked you if you were hiding in Jin Myung Sook's home.
I would've asked the same question too.
The day Jin Myung Sook was found dead,
you told me while being questioned...
that you found her while trying to track down Lee Yi Jin...
after receiving information about his location.
According to some tip-offs we received recently,
Lee Yi Jin stowed away at the end of August.
You were told he was pinged in Owol-dong on September 2.
It was a lie.
So, I was led there to see Jin Myung Sook...
on purpose.
And how I was given the report on the Bongto plant case too.
They're both...
connected to Mo Hyung Taek.
How Cha Geum Sae framed Kim Min Chul too.
Mr. Song knew all about it.
And Mr. Song was the one who told him to keep tabs on Jin.
Cha Geum Sae confessed to everything.
And the orders...
all came from Mo Hyung Taek?
If you want to know the truth,
- write an article about it. - Can I do that?
You must do it,
to officially summon a party leader for an interview.
Anyway, go back to sleep.
I woke you up.
No, I woke up because I was hungry.
What do you feel like eating?
You should have porridge. An ice pop, seriously?
Are you a kid?
My dad always said the same thing too.
I miss my dad.
Ever since Cha Eun Sae died,
everything's been weird, as if it's all a dream.
From how my husband betrayed me...
and how I'm running around trying to find the culprit...
to how we met again.
I should stop eating this.
Yes, it's not good to eat cold stuff when you're not feeling well.
See? Your hand is so cold.
It's chilly.
It all feels like my fault.
When you left to see Cha Geum Sae,
I should've stopped you.
If something worse had happened, I'd have...
You could've gotten badly hurt because of me.
This isn't working.
I was warned not to feel any emotions for you.
I can't do that.
Now that we've met again,
I'll do as my heart says.
I must take it all the way.
(Jihyang University Hospital)
You're leaving already?
Why are you here?
My patient got admitted. Of course, I should visit.
I have nothing else to say to you.
But I do. And I have something to show you too.
You know I tape my consultations, so I'd like to ask you directly.
What's this blood?
You went to Unit 1401 that day, didn't you?
Did you kill Cha Eun Sae,
then talk to me to create an alibi?
Do you really think so?
Yes.
I'm convinced you're the culprit.
If we test the blood on the shirt, we'll know the truth.
It shows up even after it's washed.
If the shirt you wore that day is gone,
that would be even more suspicious.
I took care of that shirt.
I threw it away in case Jung Won got in trouble.
She'd had a nosebleed.
I doubted her at one time for no reason.
Sorry about that.
How silly of you.
Do you think that will erase the fact that your wife's guilty?
- Listen. - Woo Jae.
It's a lie that I briefly liked him in school.
I still like him.
I think of him, miss him, and want him all the time.
Hey. Are you out of your mind?
I told you.
I'm worried and afraid you live with a murderer.
I realized as we talked...
just how unstable, volatile, and dangerous you were.
Enough to kill someone.
The photo of your bloodied sleeve and my opinion as a doctor.
I'll submit it to Detective Kim Tae Heon.
That's how I'll save Woo Jae.
Since we're all here,
why not invite the detective?
Do you want to lose your doctor's license?
Shall I tell the detective first?
That I asked you to get me propofol,
and you prescribed it to me illegally.
I quit after I met you.
And got hooked again after meeting Eun Sae.
I'm trying really hard to stay off it now.
Now that Jung Won knows I was addicted,
you have no more weakness to wield over me, do you?
If you want to report Jung Won at the risk of losing everything,
go ahead.
Thanks for the visit.
Goodbye.
When I was studying abroad,
I got hooked when sleeping pills stopped working for me.
There was no turning back.
I did all sorts of things to get myself clean but failed.
So I went to the sea determined to kill myself.
That's when we met.
It's okay to look at the sea as you walk,
but it's dangerous to stare at it standing still.
Yes, I'm reporter Seo Jung Won from "Nothing Uncovered."
What were you thinking about...
that you didn't notice your shoes were wet?
I was thinking it would be nice if someone...
would talk to me.
I didn't miss the drugs at all when I was with you that day.
When just the day before,
I hadn't wanted to live.
That's when I realized that not wanting to live...
actually meant that I wanted to live really well.
That I wanted to spend the rest of my life with this woman.
I managed to break free after I met you.
You saved me.
Why couldn't you sleep...
even though you took sleeping pills?
A girl I liked died in an accident.
What accident?
I don't want to talk about it.
Let's go home.
Jung Won. I'll zip it up for you.
My dear beloved Reporter Seo, welcome home.
(Two months ago)
Did you watch my show today?
Of course, I did.
The novelist...
Ko Dae Chul who violated his students.
I exposed him on my show.
You did great.
Did I really do great when he helped you get published?
This is why I love you.
You don't weigh your options or hesitate.
- What is it? - Something stings.
- Is it your shoulder? - No, the necklace.
- My hair. - Oh, hang on.
It must've gotten tangled up.
It's off.
It's done.
(Chief Kang In Han)
After your article came out,
Mo Hyung Taek called an emergency press conference.
It's on TV now.
(National Assembly)
Regarding me...
and the late Cha Eun Sae,
I'm well aware of the rumor that I was her sponsor.
It's true that...
I did sponsor Cha Eun Sae.
When I was a prosecutor, each time I moved to a new region,
I asked for a list of teens from broken families...
and I sponsored them.
Cha Eun Sae was one of them.
(Assemblyman Mo, "I sponsored the late Cha.")
Since she was 15 and until she graduated from high school,
I covered her tuition and living expenses.
As evidence,
I will disclose the handwritten letters...
Cha Eun Sae sent me on Parents' Day.
- Really? - Handwritten letters?
So he just helped her financially?
(National Assembly of South Korea)
Whether as a prosecutor or now as a politician,
I have always held the same goal.
("Good Deed Doer Mo Hyung Taek")
I wanted to give the privileges...
I had received from society back to the people.
Being firmly committed to my goal...
helped me endure all kinds of rumors...
and attacks.
In the upcoming regional election,
I plan to run for governor in Gangwon Province.
I will allow myself...
to be put to the test once again.
This is driving me crazy. Even Mo Hyung Taek has an alibi.
Then it means everyone on our suspect list...
has an alibi.
Among the people related to this case,
whose alibi haven't we confirmed?
Mo Soo Rin's alibi.
(The man delivering Jin Myung Sook's cash donation)
Oh, right.
Remember the organization with the factory fire's victims?
A man supposedly delivered Jin's cash donation in her place.
I got his composite sketch. I'll send it over to you now.
This face...
What if Yoo Yoon Young took the necklace that day?
(Yoo Yoon Young)
It's me.
I couldn't stop feeling bad...
from the way we said goodbye earlier.
Are you free tonight?
She's driving me crazy.
I told you I was coming to see you in the hospital after work.
What are you doing here?
Gosh. Seriously.
I told you to rest up since you were in the hospital.
You really might pass out if you don't rest.
If I stop working with the excuse of going on a break,
I might pass out for real.
I can't let that happen.
After reading your exclusive report, I thought...
you were going to pick Mo Hyung Taek as your target for the next episode.
What a surprising turn of events. You and Mo Hyung Taek...
must've been each other's archenemies in previous lives.
Gosh.
If he were sponsoring Cha Eun Sae for solicitation,
I would've been 100 percent sure that he was the culprit.
Mo Hyung Taek has an alibi for the day...
- of Cha Eun Sae's murder. - What?
Seriously?
In my opinion, your promise to expose...
the real killer on our show within a month was impossible.
You should take care of your health first.
You can't even think straight...
in your condition.
- Where's the newbie? - The newbie?
He's taking a sick day which is unusual.
Is he feeling sick because you're not well?
I'm on the outdoor terrace of the TV station.
Spare me a moment.
Doesn't the composite sketch match your newbie reporter?
I think so.
Where did this sketch come from?
Jin Myung Sook withdrew cash every month...
and donated it to the victims' organization of the factory fire.
He delivered the money in her place.
It proves that he was very close to Jin Myung Sook.
Is he in the office right now?
No. He's taking a sick day today.
If you also thought he resembled the newbie reporter,
I was going to question him.
What is it?
My chief called for a team meeting at the station.
He's probably going to nag us to catch the killer.
I'll drop you off.
Please go home and rest up.
I'm not done talking to my team yet.
I'll go home soon.
I'll call you to check as soon as my meeting is over.
Bye.
Ae Na. Find Ba Reun's home address and send it to me.
There's a house in a place like this?
Ba Reun. It's me.
Are you inside?
(Arson Case)
(My husband, Park Jin Soo, isn't an arsonist.)
(Prosecutor Mo Hyung Taek...)
(This is the location of Detective Kim Tae Heon.)
(Can you talk?)
It was you?
Zeus was you?
Lee Ba Reun.
What an honor this is.
I don't have anything on you anymore.
But you're spending time with me.
Yoon Young.
Why do you like me?
I have never been kind to you.
I always pushed you away.
Don't you hate me?
Always.
There hasn't been a moment when I didn't hate you.
But the problem is...
I never stopped liking you.
You're quite a determined man.
You stopped medicating yourself when you began dating Seo Jung Won.
I kept throwing myself on you, but you never crossed the line.
Am I not attractive as a woman?
You could have given in at least once, couldn't you?
Giving false hope is the most painful act...
one can do to another.
I had no intention of dating you, so I thought giving in...
to your advances wasn't a nice thing to do to a friend.
Who cares about being nice?
So what if it comes with a bit of pain?
Love and pain always go hand in hand.
After all, you're hurting now because you love your wife.
As for me,
you've never been mine. So naturally, I'm still hung up on you.
But why are you so obsessed with your wife?
I'm afraid she'd leave me.
That she might...
abandon me.
Between never making something yours...
and forever losing what was once yours,
what do you think would drive you more insane?
Neither of us...
knows how to love properly.
I...
want you to be lonelier...
and more miserable.
I hope the days you shed tears...
outnumber the days you smile...
so that...
you'll keep coming to me.
(Enter passcode)
(Recents)
(You and Me, White)
(Seo Jung Won)
It was because of me.
It was all because of me.
That's why you set Jung Won up.
Hello, Detective Kim.
You must be wondering why I'm here.
I'm here because of Ms. Seo Jung Won.
(Nothing Uncovered)
She left your necklace at the scene...
but has a confirmed alibi. That means...
She either has an accomplice or hired someone to kill her.
You felt insecure because I never liked you back,
so you committed murder.
I didn't know you were such a monster.
Do you think you have the right to say such a thing?
Seriously, do not contact or meet Reporter Seo for the time being.
Are you out of your mind?
She asked me not to have any feelings for her,
but I couldn't do that.
Jung Won did nothing wrong.
Don't cry.
It was my fault that the article got published.
Don't worry. I'll protect you.
Yoo Yoon Young gave me some pictures yesterday.
They were photos of Jung Won next to Cha Eun Sae's dead body.
That said, help me.
You're going to arrest me for murdering Cha Eun Sae?
I'll handle them. Just don't get hurt.
Let's stay like this for just a minute.