(Nothing Uncovered)
(Production sponsors)
(Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, KOCCA)
(All locations, characters,
organizations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Episode 9)
When I saw them, I was so surprised too.
They're Cha Eun Sae and Jung Won, right?
These pictures. Where did you get them?
I found this envelope under my windshield wipers.
Where was your car?
I drank last night, so I left it parked in an alley.
The thing is, it's a blind spot with no cameras around.
Whoever did this must've known Jung Won was my patient.
I think this was planned.
- You must have a dashcam in your... - I'm sorry.
I don't have a dashcam in my car.
Anyway, I'll take these.
To ensure a speedy investigation,
please do not tell the media about these photos.
Okay, I won't.
(Investigative Planning Team)
(My Husband)
I was swamped at work yesterday,
so I couldn't go home.
I'm in front of the broadcasting station now.
Let's talk. Now.
I found this picture on a flash drive Yoon Young had.
This necklace was in my old studio.
Yoon Young took it.
- Are you sure it's mine? - I checked the serial number.
It is the necklace I bought for you.
After all, my instinct...
was not wrong.
(Secretary Gong)
(Seo Jung Won In Inappropriate Relationship With Detective...)
What's that picture?
It's not true, right?
Why can't you say it's not true?
Did you want to get back at me the same way?
Is this what you wanted?
(Seo Jung Won In Inappropriate Relationship With Detective...)
(Father)
(Seo Jung Won In Inappropriate Relationship...)
(With Detective In Charge of Cha Eun Sae's Case)
(Reporter Seo Jung Won is in an inappropriate relationship...)
(with Detective A, who is in charge of the Cha Eun Sae case.)
- Hey. - Hey, did you read the article?
Did you find anything?
They already took all the hard drives,
but that's not important right now.
We might find something there,
so comb through all the documents you see there.
Don't leave anything out, okay?
Okay, I heard you.
But seriously,
do not contact or meet Reporter Seo for the time being. You got that?
Seriously, no more.
No more what?
You know what I'm talking about.
She's married.
If you do not stop, your life will be ruined.
"Ruined?" So be it, then.
Hey, Tae Heon!
(Seo Jung Won In Inappropriate Relationship...)
(With Detective In Charge of Cha Eun Sae's Case)
(They met when A visited her in the hospital.)
Look at this now.
Hey, Seo Jung Won.
Nice scoop, right? I bet you're jealous.
That article. It's not true.
It's not true?
Then how will you explain that photo?
The HR Committee is already discussing disciplinary measures,
so just know that.
Oh, really?
So they'll cancel the plan to resume "Nothing Uncovered" next week.
Then the show...
We should do it this week, then.
Hey, forget about the show.
You're on the chopping block right now.
I have a suspect.
Really?
I bet you're just saying it to mislead me.
It's Mo Hyung Taek, isn't it? I knew it.
So, what I heard was true.
What did you hear?
Forget it.
How did you manage to dismantle his alibi?
It's not Mo Hyung Taek.
It's not him?
Then who is it?
Hey, do you have objective evidence?
My necklace found at the scene of Cha Eun Sae's murder.
I found out who took it in the first place.
I have a picture to back it up.
Okay, so who is it?
I will tell you everything,
so please hurry up and get a slot for the show.
Hey, seriously.
You want to do the show because you feel it's unfair you were accused?
Yes, I have to do it because I was falsely accused.
I did not kill Cha Eun Sae,
but my necklace was found at the scene,
and the prime suspect is the person who tried to ruin me.
Can't I go public with it through the show?
We must tell the truth,
including who the suspect is and what I did wrong.
What you did wrong?
Please secure a slot for the show.
I'm not even curious.
It can't be done, so get out.
Have you lost your mind?
I told you to cheat on him too, thinking you'd never do it.
I can't believe you actually did it!
It's not true,
but I couldn't say that to my husband.
So you're not having an affair?
Then why can't you tell your husband it's not true?
Because Detective Kim has feelings for you?
And because you like him too?
Oh, dear. What are you going to do?
Knowing you, you must've tried your best to push him away.
Nothing drives you crazier...
than not being able to follow your heart.
I have to pull myself together.
I will snap out of it.
Ba Reun.
He missed work, didn't he?
Oh, right.
Did you talk to him last night?
What were you going to say?
I had an informant who got me information illegally.
- It was Ba Reun. - What?
Wait. Are you saying...
Ba Reun approached you...
and double-crossed you?
Oh, my gosh.
What on earth is happening?
The day you got kidnapped.
Ba Reun said...
he cared about you...
because he suffered the same way.
- He suffered the same way? - Yes.
Can you tell me if these were Photoshopped or retouched?
It looks like it was taken from inside the room.
If they weren't Photoshopped,
they're from a hidden camera.
That's why I need them analyzed.
You said it's an unofficial request, which means...
you didn't show these photos to the police experts.
I read the article about you and Ms. Seo.
Are you all right?
- Professor. - No one will know.
I've known you for too long.
Don't worry.
(Seol Woo Jae)
How dare...
the likes of you covet my wife?
Are you out of your mind?
Why must I explain myself to a cheating husband?
That's enough.
What's enough, punk?
It's not enough.
Darn you.
Let go.
(Reporter Seo Jung Won)
I'd rather die than divorce her for you.
Jung Won's my wife and you're just...
a shameless fool who coveted a married woman.
That's all you are.
How long do you think your pathetic love will last?
Will it feel good forever?
Before you do,
Jung Won will get tired and give up.
I know that.
And until then,
I'll just wait.
For her feelings for you to disappear.
For her to come back to me.
Why hurt her if you're so desperate for her love?
Jung Won did nothing wrong.
She asked me not to have any feelings for her.
But I couldn't do that.
I clung to her and I kept hitting on her.
Have Jung Won...
get a restraining order against me.
That will clear her name.
You scumbag.
Do you mean that?
I'm a shameless fool who coveted a married woman.
I should pay for it.
(Reporter No Ji Ho)
It's Seol Woo Jae.
I'd like to explain things...
in an interview.
I couldn't control Ji Ho and the article got published.
It was my fault.
We were photographed because I couldn't control myself.
Did you come here to apologize?
My necklace that you found at Cha Eun Sae's scene.
I know who put it there.
Yoo Yoon Young?
She left your necklace at the scene...
but has a confirmed alibi. That means...
She either has an accomplice...
or hired someone to kill her.
If you're right, a hitman...
or someone close murdered her.
One person committed three murders, and if that were Yoo Yoon Young,
and she hired a hitman three times, that would be just too risky.
Plus, she was just 19 at the time the factory burned down.
You're right.
My husband would be the person closest to her.
He has an alibi.
Her clinic's registered in someone else's name. Mo Soo Rin.
I looked her up.
She's Mo Hyung Taek's daughter.
- Could it be... - What is it?
Never mind.
I'll tell you when I'm sure.
- Jung Won. - Tae Heon.
There's something...
I lied to you about.
I'll do...
whatever it takes to expose Yoo Yoon Young on air.
I'll explain everything myself.
Bear with me.
(Ae Na)
(Seol Denies Affair Rumor, "Will Get Restraining Order")
What restraining order?
That's stupid.
It was my idea.
I'll handle them.
Just don't get hurt.
Let's stay like this...
for just a minute.
Let me do this...
for just one minute.
I was furious when I saw the article.
If I'd actually had an affair,
I wouldn't feel bad at least.
I hate that I can't control myself.
I hate that...
this could hurt you.
I've been suppressing my feelings all this time.
I've tried with every ounce of my will...
to push these feelings away.
Give me a minute too.
Considering how you took my stuff without my permission,
you know this is a small price you're paying.
- Why did you do it? - I want to ask you the same thing.
Why did you kill Cha Eun Sae?
Why did you commit such an act?
After killing Cha Eun Sae,
you framed Jung Won as the culprit.
Is sending her to prison your goal?
My goal...
is you.
Because you know you can't win my love,
are you trying to win my hatred?
Is that the kind of love you want?
What you're doing isn't love. You just want to take me from her...
because I was never yours.
Education, career, money, and friends. You've got...
everything you ever wanted.
But I was the only thing you couldn't have.
Despite that, we've known each other for a long time.
You were a bit too much,
but I never thought deep down, your nature wasn't evil.
I had no idea how broken you were.
You felt insecure because I never liked you back,
so you committed murder.
I didn't know you were such a monster.
You're calling me a monster?
I wonder if you have the right to call me a monster.
Do you think I'm clueless about you?
I know everything.
Like what you've done.
What do you mean?
Don't talk to me in code.
I'm sure you understood me.
Must I really spell it out for you?
Don't worry.
Because I'm going to protect you.
I read your interview with Mr. No in his article.
I didn't get much sleep last night.
Let's talk about this later.
Woo Jae.
I need to talk to you.
I know you didn't cheat on me.
Kim Tae Heon told me that.
You told him...
not to have any feelings toward you.
But the truth is that you were tempted to have an affair.
That's what you wanted to say, right?
That's why you pushed him away, right?
It's completely understandable.
You guys dated before you and I met.
And I ended up hurting you.
If he was determined to seduce you,
feeling tempted would be natural. Of course.
I would have deserved that too.
It's okay.
No.
To be honest, it's not okay.
But I'll accept it.
It's all my fault.
And...
thank you...
for not caving into the temptation.
That's not true.
I tried not to cave in,
but I couldn't.
I...
Don't say it.
Don't say anything. Not a word.
Don't cry.
You're not sad because of me.
You're sad because of that jerk!
I...
like him.
You are...
so cruel.
When I found out that you had an affair with Cha Eun Sae,
if you hadn't lied to me,
it would have hurt me less.
So...
I'm telling you the truth.
No.
I want you to lie to me. I don't need your honesty.
Please, Jung Won.
Tell me it's not true.
I'm begging you.
Please?
I expressed...
my feelings to him.
I can't go back to how it was before.
I'm sorry.
(Chairman Seol Woo Jae)
Sir.
(Mujin Welfare Foundation)
How dare you show up here?
Get lost before I kill you.
Yoo Yoon Young gave me some pictures yesterday.
They were photos of Jung Won next to Cha Eun Sae's dead body...
in Unit 1401 of Leaders Palace.
- That means... - Jung Won was at the scene.
There's no way Jung Won killed her. I'm sure of it.
She probably saw the body and ran out.
Those photos actually confirm...
that hidden cameras were set up in advance...
and that Jung Won was lured to the scene...
because of the text message with the wrong address.
Then Jung Won's necklace was left in Cha Eun Sae's hand.
It was a premeditated murder.
That said,
you're the only one I can turn to right now,
so help me.
If Yoo Yoon Young planned everything,
but if someone close to her committed the murder...
And what if that was Mo Soo Rin?
I heard this coffee was the reason Ms. Yoo Yoon Young...
decided to move into my husband's old studio space.
Your employee told me...
that you two were very close.
Jung In, you should take a break and grab a bite to eat.
Sure.
I also know...
that Ms. Yoo's clinic is in your name...
and that the two of you were classmates...
in your senior year of high school.
My husband too.
You look like you know everything too,
including why I'm suddenly telling you all this.
You know Ms. Yoo Yoon Young very well, right?
My necklace was found at the scene of Cha Eun Sae's murder,
but Ms. Yoo had that necklace. Did you know that?
You must also know that she was at the scene too.
You know everything,
don't you?
But Yoon Young has an alibi.
An alibi? You mean, the video of the waiting room?
They've concluded that it was manipulated.
Pardon me? That can't be.
Also, her fingerprints were found in the AC plant room...
in Unit 1401 of Leaders Palace.
It means she was hiding in the scene...
the day Cha Eun Sae was killed.
That room is tiny. No one can hide in there.
And how do you know that?
Tell me.
How do you know the layout of Unit 1401 so well?
I have nothing more to tell you.
Please leave.
- Ms. Mo. - I asked you to leave.
(Cha Eun Sae, 3 months pregnant)
- Hey. - The person who did the job.
I think it was Mo Soo Rin.
Mo Soo Rin? You mean, Mo Hyung Taek's daughter?
Yes, I met her earlier in the day.
She knows the layout of Unit 1401 like the back of her hand.
I'll send you what I jotted down on her relationship with Yoo...
and the video of Yoo's last session with Cha Eun Sae.
Go through them.
All right.
(Yoo Yoon Young, Seol Woo Jae, Mo Soo Rin)
(Went to Mueon High together)
Yoo and Mo were classmates in their senior year of high school?
The fire at the plant broke out in the same year.
Hello, Detective Bong. It's me.
The Bongto plant fire case.
Who was in charge of the crime-scene investigation?
Detective Bong briefly told me about the situation.
That old case is suddenly getting all this attention.
This feels weird.
I went through all the case reports.
Were any of the details from the ignition analysis...
omitted or simply not reflected in the reports?
We were sure of one ignition location at the scene.
Another fire ignition location was suggested, so we analyzed it.
The probability was about 60 percent.
But at the time, Prosecutor Mo said it was irrelevant and covered it up,
so we had to leave it out.
So, Mo Hyung Taek forced you not to include it in the reports?
It's odd.
Politicians who took bribes in the past...
have no problem making a comeback,
but it's nearly impossible for reporters.
I guess that could be why...
you're still bending over backwards for me to this day.
I hear she still doesn't know her place and insists on doing the show.
We will have no problems, right?
It was scheduled for next week but has been canceled altogether.
She can't do it.
Good work.
Should I just give up since it won't happen?
(Zeus)
They're photos from Mo Soo Rin's phone.
These photos are from Mo Hyung Taek's daughter's phone?
The show got canceled altogether because you keep digging like this.
So, you're saying Mo Hyung Taek pulled some strings, right?
Will you keep letting the higher-ups...
drag you around when you're the head of the department?
When you were at Mueon KBM,
you took bribes from Prosecutor Mo...
and worked for him, didn't you?
Well, that's right. I did.
But I got chewed out by a senior colleague who was just like you...
and stopped doing it.
That's right. It was Reporter Seo Sang Gyeon, your father.
You're so persistent, just like his father.
If people find out about it, my career is over.
I get what you're saying.
Swapping out one of the interviews on "News 9" was the only way.
You only have three minutes.
I got an interview on "News 9."
I'll expose the suspect and the possibility of an accomplice.
Once the interview airs,
you'll have to question Yoo Yoon Young right away.
- Can you do it? - Don't worry about that.
But do you have evidence to back up that there might be an accomplice?
Ba Reun sent me some evidence.
You should comb through everything in that house too.
Ba Reun was investigating Mo Hyung Taek and his family,
so you might find something important.
Yes, I'm combing through everything now.
Good luck with the interview.
Thanks.
I would like to...
take this opportunity...
to tell the viewers something.
I am here...
to expose myself...
for one last time.
I told you not to even call Reporter Seo for the time being.
You never listen to me.
Shut it.
Don't be distracted.
See if you can find anything on Mo Soo Rin or on the fire case.
(Bongto Factory Fire Case Report, Not Accepted)
(Arson, Suspect: Park Jin Soo, Male, DOB Feb. 4, 1958)
(Aiding and abetting, grievous harm...)
(Current stance)
(Considering the possibility of an accomplice)
I can use this to put pressure.
On whom?
You're interviewing someone else.
Seo Jung Won will come on.
What?
(KBM News 9)
On today's Focus Interview,
I'll speak with reporter Seo Jung Won.
- Hello. - Hello.
A month ago, you publicly announced...
you'd reveal who killed Cha Eun Sae.
Yes, and I'm here today to keep that promise.
Necklace photo, on screen now.
This is a photo from the scene of Cha Eun Sae's murder.
The serial number showed the necklace was mine,
and that's why I was questioned by police.
(KBM News 9)
I'd left it at the studio...
belonging to my husband Seol Woo Jae,
and I recently found out someone had taken it.
Cha Eun Sae and I weren't my husband's only visitors.
His high-school friend whom I'll call A for now...
had also been there.
Photo, on screen now.
This is a photo of my necklace that was in A's possession.
The serial number confirms it's a photo of mine.
Why did she have my necklace?
And why did that necklace go from being...
in her possession to being found in the hand...
of dead Cha Eun Sae?
There's one more thing.
A has an alibi for the time of Cha's murder,
she she wasn't named a prime suspect.
Now we must turn our attention to someone else.
It's B, someone very close to A.
On B's phone...
were photos such as these, taken in secret, of Cha's office...
which was also the murder scene.
Why on earth did B take photos of the scene?
If B doesn't have an alibi,
can't we suppose they could be an accomplice?
The two of you who might be watching right now...
must know the answer to all these questions.
- Cooperate with the police... - Okay.
- and tell them... - I'll do that now.
the truth.
What are you doing? Cut the transmission.
- What? - Take them off the air.
Finally, to the viewers, I'd like to say...
Ms. Seo, thank you.
Here's the next report.
It's a summary...
of cultural events happening nationwide.
- Please watch. - She was still talking.
You're going to arrest me for murdering Cha Eun Sae?
Because of a photo of a necklace?
You made illegal prescriptions for propofol.
You're under arrest for breaking the Narcotics Control Act.
You can keep quiet,
and what you say can be used in court against you.
You can hire a lawyer too.
(Search and Seizure Warrant)
We'll search your office and home and take everything that's relevant.
(Interview with Reporter Seo Jung Won)
Assemblyman Mo...
instructed me to buy you a plane ticket to New York.
Would 2pm suit you?
You'll also pay the price for taking...
illegally prescribed medication.
I'm not stupid enough not to know that.
This photo was on a flash drive that was in your possession.
You took it, didn't you?
Aren't I here...
for writing illegal prescriptions?
I care more about this case than that one.
The day Cha was killed,
did you go to Leaders Palace Unit 1401?
- Yes. - At what time?
Was it around 4pm?
Seol Woo Jae was there too,
so I didn't stay for long.
Congratulations on becoming a dad.
I'll retire and move abroad.
(The day of Cha Eun Sae's murder)
I'll wait until you get a divorce.
Eun Sae.
Did you think I wouldn't know...
you're seeing other guys too?
What do you mean?
Sorry.
I was hoping to have a coffee with you.
You two seem to be talking. I'll come by another time.
- See you later. - Okay.
(Good luck, Eun Sae. Wish you only the best.)
No, Woo Jae.
The baby is yours. It is.
It's yours.
Is it?
Even if you insist it is, our relationship ended long ago.
I was with Cha Eun Sae that day,
and Yoo Yoon Young did drop by.
Then after 4pm,
did you visit Unit 1401 again?
- No. - Then how did...
Seo's necklace that you had...
end up in dead Cha's hand?
According to Seol Woo Jae,
you took the necklace that had been in his studio.
I didn't take it. Woo Jae gave it to me.
In return for not telling anyone about his affair with Cha.
That's a lie.
She did know about our affair,
but she stole the necklace.
When and how did you find out about Seol's affair?
Early August, was it?
Eun Sae told me during a session.
After hearing about the affair,
did you blackmail Seol Woo Jae?
No.
Why would I blackmail him?
On hearing my wife couldn't sleep after finding Jin Myung Sook's body,
she pressured me to bring Jung Won to see her.
She said she'd go public about the affair if I didn't.
I bet that's when...
she started to form a plan to trap my wife.
I just started questioning you,
and you lied twice already.
Yes.
Just as you thought,
Seol Woo Jae's watching in the next room.
Since there's no point in lying now,
how about I ask point blank?
Why are you lying? What is it that you want to hide?
Perhaps, your feelings toward Mr. Seol?
How did you feel after finding out about his affair with Cha Eun Sae?
The man you had a crush on for a long time...
was involved with two women.
"How come he liked Seo Jung Won and Cha Eun Sae, but not me?"
Has this thought ever crossed your mind?
You confessed your feelings to him 14 years ago,
but he turned you down.
Back then, he was dating...
a girl named Lee Na Ri, not you.
(14 years ago)
You know what's interesting?
There was the same signature from the culprit...
at both of Lee Na Ri's and Cha Eun Sae's murder scenes.
On top of that,
it was also found at the murder scene...
of Jin Myung Sook, Mo Hyung Taek's housekeeper.
Aren't you curious about the signature...
that was found at all three crime scenes?
Are you going to tell me?
Detective Kim, I have an alibi.
Yes, you do.
What if you were the mastermind behind the murders,
and B, the individual Ms. Seo exposed in her interview,
executed the deeds?
So what if Mo Soo Rin committed the murders?
Just like it was mentioned during the news, did you know...
Mo Soo Rin had photos of Unit 1401 of Leaders Palace,
the very place the murder took place?
Even if those photos...
were indeed from her phone,
she was just one of my many patients.
What do her photos have to do with me?
She's more than just a patient.
You two have known each other since high school senior year.
You guys are quite close.
Jin's murder, Cha's murder, and the fire at the factory.
You guys conspired together to commit them, didn't you?
On the grounds that we graduated from the same high school?
Do you think your reasoning makes any sense?
Here's what I heard from the leader of the forensic team,
in charge of the fire incident at Bongto Factory.
He included in his report the possibility...
of the arsonist having an accomplice.
But Then-Prosecutor Mo Hyung Taek buried it.
Considering all the connections,
You as well as Ms. Mo Soo Rin have something to do...
with the three cases.
Do you think this makes any sense?
You put Seo Jung Won's necklace...
in Cha Eun Sae's hand after she had been killed.
Didn't you?
Did she smile just now?
- What? - Did you find anything useful?
We're searching everything here.
Yoo Yoon Young isn't even scared. She's completely unfazed.
Bring me evidence that she instigated the murder.
- We can't arrest her without that. - Got it.
We need to find the evidence from the raid.
Detective Kim.
What happened to the photos I gave to you?
Ms. Seo's photos taken next to the dead body...
of Cha Eun Sae at the crime scene.
What photos? What's she talking about?
I'm conducting a thorough analysis on them.
Because they could be manipulated or Photoshopped?
I was worried for nothing.
I read in an article that you had an affair with Ms. Seo.
I was concerned that you might bury the evidence.
You know, I've been thinking about those photos.
Assuming that those are original copies,
based on the angle of the camera,
the photos were taken inside the unit.
If there wasn't a third person at the scene,
a spy cam must have filmed that.
That's what you think too, right?
Right.
I kept a folder of Ms. Seo's therapy session videos...
on my office computer.
You should watch the video from the day of Cha's murder.
There's blood on Ms. Seo's sleeves.
In my opinion, that blood belonged to Cha Eun Sae.
So...
when I asked her if she still had the shirt at home,
Woo Jae stepped in and said he threw it out.
It means that...
even her husband suspected her of being the murderer.
You should ask Woo Jae...
if he indeed threw it out.
If you're done questioning me, you should release me.
You were going to question me on suspicion of the murder.
But seeing how you arrested me for writing illegal prescriptions,
there's no smoking gun.
I will find that smoking gun soon.
More than anything,
I can clearly prove that you wrote illegal prescriptions.
So you won't be getting released.
You know what?
Woo Jae is falsely accusing me. His accusation is one-sided.
I expected this. You know?
I knew Woo Jae would report me for writing illegal prescriptions...
and you would try to frame me as the accomplice...
with Ms. Seo's necklace.
You can raid my place all you want.
But you won't find anything.
What do we do?
You didn't get anything at all?
There's no evidence that she issued unlawful prescriptions.
I didn't find any leads that...
could prove she instigated the murder or was an accomplice.
It was squeaky clean.
- There weren't any spy cams either? - No.
I thought we would find something from the raid.
This is bad.
By the way, I heard from Captain Jung.
What are these photos Yoo Yoon Young gave you?
Let's talk about that tomorrow.
Father, please forgive our sins.
Please save us from the fiery pit of fire.
Please watch over the souls in purgatory.
Watch over the soul, burdened with the most tragic...
abandonment.
(The day of Cha Eun Sae's murder)
Cha Eun Sae...
suspects you and the assemblyman as the culprits.
She said she had to do something about it.
She said she would tell everything to the police.
If Cha Eun Sae exposes everything, it will be over.
The truth about Jin's murder and the factory fire...
will come out.
What do I do?
Oh, no. It's all because of my diary.
Don't cry.
It's a blessing that we found out before she did anything.
We can fix it now.
This is the last time.
This...
will end it...
for good.
They will start installing the security cameras...
all over the building tomorrow.
We only have today to do it.
(Father)
- Yes. - I know the police let you go.
Come home now.
So, I hear that woman, Yoo Yoon Young,
is connected to the Bongto Factory fire,
the Jin Myung Sook case,
and the Cha Eun Sae case too.
That's right.
She's helping us.
It means the Lord has already forgiven you for your sins.
The Lord will take good care of you from now on.
As soon as the case is closed,
join the team in charge of the second Mujin resort.
It'll take a while for the case to be closed.
Yoon Young...
has an alibi.
They arrested her without even checking her alibi?
Yoon Young planned everything, but someone else executed it.
Yoon Young set up spy cams at the scene in advance,
ordered someone to commit the murder,
and lured Jung Won to the scene,
but the investigation will go nowhere without solid evidence.
There were spy cams?
I'm suspecting Yoon Young had an accomplice,
and it's someone you know, Father.
If this person really was her accomplice,
then our plan to build the second Mujin resort will be affected.
What should we do?
Seeing how the Lord...
keeps on testing you...
tells me...
that I will never be forgiven for my sins,
Father.
Hey, what's up? You want to go to work with me?
I booked a small banquet room at a hotel.
My goodness.
For a party to celebrate?
I must say, that interview yesterday was very cool.
Hey, I read some of the comments.
Once the show resumes next week, we'll get such high ratings.
Hey, can you tell Chief Kang and Reporter Joo...
that I'll hold a press conference at 2pm today?
A press conference? Why?
Is there something you forgot to say at the interview yesterday?
There's something...
I must expose, for one last time.
After my press conference at 2pm,
I'll go to the police station to be interviewed.
I want you to interview me.
- Tae Heon. - Yes.
The analysis team said they didn't have those photos.
What is going on?
Hey, Kim Tae Heon!
Have you lost your mind?
I lost the photos Yoo Yoon Young gave me.
- Please wait until I find... - You punk.
You lost them? You deliberately hid them!
Look at this.
You are dismissed from your position as of this moment,
so hand over the cuffs and your police ID. Now!
What's going on?
The police suddenly barged in.
What is going on?
We're on duty at the moment. Please give us a few minutes.
Sir!
Did you find something?
We found blood on the sole of these shoes.
Ms. Seo.
You're under arrest for the murder of Cha Eun Sae.
(Nothing Uncovered)
How much do you love her that you did such a thing?
Because I trusted her.
It sounds like you feel betrayed now because you trusted her.
I'll take a hit too.
We must catch the real culprit. It is the only way.
Please help me so Jung Won can be released.
I'll do anything.
Soo Rin, I need you to do something before you leave.
They found blood on the sole of Reporter Seo's shoes, but...
Cha Eun Sae's blood?
Will you divorce her and marry me?
Have they issued an arrest warrant on me?
Do you know what you can do to get out of your situation...
when you're at the end of your rope?