[The Demon Hunter's Romance]
[Episode 35]
♫The beginning of love♫
♫The return is yet unknown♫
Banxia,
have you ever wondered
what your life would be like
if you couldn't see demons?
♫Through endless days and nights♫
Maybe things would be a little easier.
I'd be closer to my family,
go to school,
♫Where my heart leads me to♫
learn to ride horses,
and even study martial arts.
Isn't that He Quelian?
You want that kind of life?
Not really.
♫Who is talking about never letting go of the memory♫
Because that way,
I'd never be able to meet you.
♫Dreaming about the intertwined joy and sorrow♫
♫Who knows the river of life winds through with twists and turns♫
♫A fleeting memory, yet love endures♫
What's going on?
W-What happened?
My Lady.
Should we call for a physician?
What's going on?
She pulled her out of the river.
[Xingxian]
She's waking up.
She's alive.
She's awake.
Are you alright?
Go away!
Go away, go away!
Go away.
You stupid woman!
Stupid woman!
What are you doing?
Why did you kick her?
[Zhang Pu]
I just scolded you a little,
and you tried to kill yourself.
Why are you still alive?
Are you alright?
Come.
Come home with me!
You can't take her!
Be careful.
You again.
Who are you to step in?
I'm disciplining my own wife.
What's it to you?
Come with me!
Don't
embarrass me further!
Well done!
Your wife isn't embarrassing.
The one who's truly embarrassing
is you,
a lazy, good-for-nothing fool!
Touch her again,
and I swear
I'll drag you to the authorities.
Take him to the authorities!
The authorities?
Do you even know where
the government office is?
You little wench,
you think you can scare me?
Try me,
and you'll find out.
I can tell you this:
my dad works at the government office.
I know all the constables there very well.
If you don't believe me,
just come with me.
When you're in jail,
we'll see if you
still dare to act out
and beat your wife.
Put him in jail!
That's right.
Have him arrested.
Report him.
Out of my way!
Move aside!
Get lost.
Miss Duan.
This isn't
the first time he's hurt you.
I helped you once, twice,
but I can't
be there every time.
If you always wait for someone to save you,
what will you do
when no one shows up?
Not every time will someone
appear
to be your guardian angel.
My Lady, you got into a fight again.
If Madam finds out,
she'll be furious.
Ms. Xingxian
is really quite foolish.
You've
helped her so many times,
yet she'd rather stay and get beaten
than leave her husband
to seek a better life elsewhere.
If you ask me,
even if you help her 10,000 times,
if she remains weak-willed,
it won't change anything.
My Lady,
are you even
listening to me?
Tingzhou.
When I went into the river earlier,
did you hear
a man's voice on the bank?
There were so many people on the bank at that time,
both men and women.
My Lady, who are you talking about?
My Lady,
what exactly did you hear?
I didn't hear anything.
My Lady,
you must have had hallucinations again.
If you ask me, this is all Master's fault.
You were already frightened
by the Human-faced Owl at the Nanyang house.
Now here in Guangping,
before resting for a few days,
we're busy moving again.
Now look—
your body's weak, and the hallucinations are back.
Alright,
my clothes are almost dry.
Let's go.
Take a look! Take a look!
Big and sweet pears!
Their pears
are sweet and crisp.
When Ji Li was still here,
[Xu Zhizhi, Yunmen Dance Troupe Dancer]
she often came with me
to buy pears from them.
Sir,
a catty of this.
It's full.
Can you hold this for me?
I'd like a catty of this.
Alright!
Tingzhou, pay her.
Here.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Take this pear.
It's very sweet.
Take it.
I'll give you one too.
Thank you.
Miss,
your herbs.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Let me take it.
Dad,
here's the cinnamon.
[Jiu Cangming
Jiu Xi]
Good, crush it all up.
Alright.
Just a moment.
Manniang's Cousin-in-Law?
What's in your basket?
Something delicious?
C-Can I have some?
Could you help me
take this to Uncle Jiu?
And also,
stop calling me
Manniang's Cousin-in-Law.
This house
is quite old.
And with all the shops nearby,
it is a bit noisy.
A good house is easy to find,
but good neighbors are rare.
Back in Nanyang City,
we ran into that dangerous
[Mrs. Duan, Tang Ruyun]
Human-faced Owl.
Just thinking about it now
still gives me chills.
Only by living next to you
can I feel a bit safer.
[Mrs. Jiu, Hong Ning]
Actually,
I was scared too when I first married him.
But gradually,
I got used to it.
You know,
we can't let those things
scare us from living our lives, right?
I'm back!
Banxia, come here.
Greetings, Mrs. Jiu.
Where have you been?
Why are you all sweaty?
Nowhere.
I just went to see a friend.
She's so reckless.
I actually think
Banxia has a lovely temperament.
Is she engaged?
We're looking for a match for her.
If I recall, your son
is also at the age of marriage,
right?
He's already engaged.
They'll be married by the end of this year.
That's great.
He's engaged?
My Lady,
you must've skipped your medicine again.
Or you wouldn't have had hallucinations again.
Why were you so surprised
that
Mr. Jiu is engaged?
The way you looked and talked today,
anyone would think
you're in love with him.
In love.
Stop mimicking nonsense.
Fortunately, there were no outsiders there.
If those words
were twisted and spread around,
people
would gossip about you again.
I'm not sick at all.
I know.
You're not sick.
It's just that
you occasionally
talk nonsense,
lack energy,
and cry
in your sleep.
Still,
your condition
is a bit mysterious.
For instance,
back then, no one believed
the bride was a demon.
Only you believed
Uncle Jiu instantly.
My Lady,
how did you figure out
the bride was a demon?
I don't know either.
When I saw Manniang,
she just felt strangely familiar.
I also felt fear
and some…
pity, maybe?
My Lady,
it was your first time meeting the bride.
Where did all those feelings come from?
Banxia.
-Mom.
-Madam.
This is from Mrs. Jiu.
She said when you
wake up from bad dreams at night,
reading this
can help calm your mind.
Chi Xue!
Come help me with something.
Coming.
May the heart remain in timeless serenity.
Like clouds drifting, like rivers flowing.
Face all
without turning away.
In peace,
release desires that cloud the mind.
For all things rise and fall, unite and part like the ebbing tide.
Who are you?
What's wrong with me?
[Liushui Pavilion]
[Chilian]
Miss Duan.
Ms. Xingxian.
It's really you.
If you hadn't sent me that invitation,
I wouldn't have believed it.
I've already divorced Zhang Pu.
These days, I play the Qin
at Liushui Pavilion
as a way
to make a living for myself.
Congratulations!
I have to thank you, Miss Duan.
If you hadn't shaken me awake
and helped me out,
I wouldn't even be alive
to play the Qin here.
You're the one who made it happen.
I've heard
that the owner of Liushui Pavilion
is a master of the Qin.
Most musicians don't
get the chance to perform here.
The fact that you do
means your skills are top-notch.
Top-notch? Hardly.
I hadn't touched a Qin in years.
It's all thanks to Mr. Bai.
He recommended me
and even wrote a new piece just for me.
That's how I found a place to stay.
Mr. Bai?
He's a renowned master of the Qin.
Kind-hearted like you,
he took pity on me for being all alone
and helped me find this job.
Great!
Great! Great! Great!
Miss Duan, it's my turn.
We'll talk more later.
Go ahead then.
Hoto noodles!
Hot Hoto noodles!
Freshly made and sold!
Waiter.
Any seats left?
Miss,
why don't you order first?
There's an empty seat there.
Alright.
One bowl of Hoto noodles, one stuffed lotus root,
and a honey cake.
Certainly!
This way.
Sir, are you finished?
I'd like to settle the bill.
Take care.
Can I help you?
Sorry.
Have we met before?
You must be mistaken.
This is my first time in Guangping.
I don't know you.
Farewell.
Think carefully.
I don't know why,
but you feel familiar to me.
I'm Duan Banxia.
Are you sure we haven't met before?
Yes.
Thank you, sir.
You're very kind.
Are you here for work,
for business,
or maybe to visit someone?
Where are you staying?
At an inn?
Or at a friend's place?
Sir,
how long have you been in Guangping?
Have you had a chance to look around?
Is your foot not hurting anymore?
It hurts.
It really hurts.
However,
I have some great herbal oil at home.
My neighbor, Physician Jiu
from Ganshan Clinic, gave it to me.
He is the best
bonesetter in Guangping.
My house is just up ahead.
Thank you for today.
You were
heading back to your inn just now, right?
The closest one nearby
should be Jude Hotel.
Are you staying there?
It seems so.
Here we are.
[Qingche Hall]
I still don't know your name.
My name is Man Ying.
Man Ying…
Jingchu is home to many Miao descendants.
The surname Man is a prominent one there.
Are you
from Jingchu?
So, Mr. Man,
how long will you be staying in Guangping?
I'm leaving.
When will you come again?
I won't.
For years,
I've been having the same dream
over and over.
In my dream,
there's a man.
He's about your height
and your build.
But the fog's too thick.
I can never see his face clearly.
Every time I walk towards him,
I wake up.
Someone told me
you can only dream about
people or things
you've seen before.
So I've always wondered
if he's someone
I met long ago
but forgot.
When I saw you
at the noodle shop just now,
you felt strangely familiar.
That's why I stopped you.
I know
this is a bit rude,
but I have to ask again.
Have you really never been to Guangping before?
Have we really never met?
No.
I see.
Thank you for carrying me home today.
You're done talking?
I'll be going.
My Lady, who's that guy?
My Lady,
what happened to your foot?
I remember you.
What brought you here?
Hoto noodles are ready!
Chi Xue,
you sure you can eat all this?
Have you come into money?
Physician Jiu gave you a salary?
It's not like I'm not paying you.
Why so many questions?
Enjoy your meal.
Last time at the Reunion Inn,
the person who helped us fight the puppets
was you, wasn't it?
Face covered,
wielding a curved blade,
with one move, you shattered Feng Tian's sword
into pieces.
How did you recognize me?
I smelled you
from three streets away.
Since when
did your nose become so keen?
Surprised?
I've practiced the Five-Sense Technique.
I learned it from a dog demon.
My five senses are sharp,
especially my sense of smell.
Sir,
don't add garlic, please.
I don't eat garlic.
Your nose is so sharp.
It's more tasty with garlic.
You're smiling.
You're admitting it, aren't you?
Here,
eat some more.
My master said you meant no harm
and told me not to go looking for you.
He took you as a disciple?
Yes.
Jiu Xi
is good at numbers
and a decent physician,
but he's not cut out for fighting.
That old man wants his skills
to be passed down.
So he took me in.
But he said
I'm just learning some basics.
Not really the one to inherit his legacy.
He needs to find someone else.
But I don't think he ever can.
Why?
He has an image
of an ideal successor in his mind.
He wants someone
exactly like that.
He's too picky to find them.
Take your time.
Here,
have this bowl too.
I haven't eaten this much in ages.
I've been so busy lately.
Busy with what?
Jiu Xi is getting married.
The old man is planning to
renovate the house.
That's good news.
Who is Jiu Xi marrying?
The daughter of a herbal merchant on Gujing Street.
The old man goes there a lot
to buy herbs.
Over time, they got close.
His wife picked the match.
Does Jiu Xi really like her?
I don't know.
But let me tell you,
he's been acting a little silly lately.
Sometimes when he's writing,
he just starts smiling
out of the blue.
Looks kinda weird.
I wonder if the bride
will like him.
Oh, right.
Thank you for that day.
Master said
if you hadn't shown up,
he and I alone
might not have been able to stop all the puppets.
If they had gotten loose,
we'd have been in big trouble.
From now on, you're my friend.
Friend?
Friend.
Alright, friend.
I'm heading home then.
Wait.
Sir, you're in good shape.
Do I look good?
Boss.
No problem.
[Clothes and Brocade]
Thank you.
You look so happy.
Feeling hungry again?
No,
I just smelled grilled venison.
It smells amazing.
It's Master's favorite.
Wait for me.
You're such a kind person.
From now on,
you're my brother.
Aren't we friends?
Friends aren't this generous.
You're family, a brother.
I'm home.
Go in.
Chi Xue?
Why are you back so late?
Master, what are you looking for?
I'm hungry.
I swear there was a plate of fried beans left.
Where is it?
What's that smell?
What are you holding?
Grilled venison.
Fresh off the grill.
Your favorite, Master.
Quick, quick, set it out!
It's grilled venison!
Wonderful!
Dad, Chi Xue,
what are you eating?
Your nose is quite sharp, isn't it?
Sit down.
Join us.
Alright.
Eat up.
This is so delicious.
We have to eat it with wine.
You're right.
Go, go,
bring out the good wine I've hidden.
Okay, I'll go get it.
Wait for me.
Dad, the wine's here!
Let's all keep our voices down.
Don't wake your mom.
Or we'll all get scolded.
Okay.
Let me fill your cup.
Dad,
you're playing favorites.
You snuck Chi Xue pocket money,
but none for me.
Yesterday I wanted to buy a poetry book,
but when I checked my pocket,
I didn't have enough money.
Nonsense!
I didn't give Chi Xue any pocket money.
Master didn't give me money.
This was bought by my brother.
Your brother?
The one from last time at the Reunion Inn
who used a curved blade.
Didn't I tell you
not to go to him?
I didn't.
He just happened to pass by
from Manniang's Cousin-in-Law's place today.
We ran into each other,
so I said hi.
Then he insisted on treating me to a meal.
He even bought me a lot of new clothes.
On the way back,
he bought the grilled venison for you.
Tell me,
how come other demon hunters
are all so rich,
and we end up losing money
every time we take a job?
Dad,
our clinic is barely breaking even.
You brat,
I'm saving up
to get you a wife!
I also gotta fix the backyard
and patch up the roof.
It's all for you.
All for you.
Go away.
Let's have a toast.
Here.
I'll drink tea instead.
Cheers, cheers.
Banxia,
I used to wonder,
if we'd never met,
what kind of life you'd have lived.
Hurry up, Dad, Mom.
Come.
Dad, Mom,
look.
Is my bunny pretty?
Yes.
Be careful.
Banxia,
at school,
you need to listen to your teacher, okay?
Yes, Mom.
When I come back, I'll recite
what I've learned for you.
Okay.
Here, have a duck leg.
More.
Thank you, Mom and Dad.
Mom, this one is for you.
Banxia,
I don't like to eat this.
Your mom likes this.
Here.
I like it too.
Eat more, okay?
Dad, let me help you.
Okay.
♫Melody echoes along the river; wild geese soar in sudden fright♫
♫The music ends, and I stand in solitude♫
♫I see you turn into a handful of starlight♫
♫Drifting past me♫
♫In tears, the past memories still glow♫
♫Crystallized into cold amber♫
♫I know it also brought you great pain to let go♫
♫But why did you♫
♫Still endure the pain and shatter?♫
♫Remember me, don't miss me♫
I don't raise rabbits.
♫Don't put the blame on yourself for my solitude♫
My name is Jiu Xuanye.
I'm Duan Banxia.
♫I hate that I failed♫
♫To catch the glistening starlight♫
♫We were meant to miss each other in this life♫
♫Only after missing did we learn how much love could hurt♫
♫To have loved you is to have truly lived♫
I really do like you,
but I don't know
when it started.
Maybe
a long time ago.
♫In tears, the past memories still glow♫
But I can
swear on my life,
if you're willing to marry me,
♫Crystallized into cold amber♫
I'll treat you with all my heart
for the rest of my days.
♫I know it also brought you great pain to let go♫
No matter what dangers may come in the future,
I will fight with my life
♫But why did you♫
to protect you.
♫Still endure the pain and shatter?♫
♫Remember me, don't miss me♫
Banxia.
Forget me.
♫Don't put the blame on yourself for my solitude♫
♫I hate that I failed♫
♫To catch the glistening starlight♫
♫We were meant to miss each other in this life♫
♫Only after missing did we learn how much love could hurt♫
My Lady,
wash up and go to sleep.
♫To have loved you is to have truly lived♫
How did it go?
Here.
These are all the Moon Bugs?
Still not enough.
There should be more at the Ganshan Clinic.
But that old man Jiu
isn't easy to deal with.
Can you handle him?
Oh, right.
I need to make a trip to Yangxi County.
There's a bear demon there.
It's time.
Be careful.
I know.
No matter what,
we still have more than ten days
before the Realm Gate closes.
We have to
be back before that happens.
Got it.
You went to see that woman again?
If you like her so much,
just bring her back to the Carefree Land.
Once the Realm Gate is shut,
she can't leave anyway.
What else can she do but stay
by your side every day?
So indecisive.
My Lady.
-Banxia.
-Wake up, My Lady.
Banxia.
Manniang's Cousin-in-Law.
-My Lady.
-Miss Duan.
-Manniang's Cousin-in-Law.
Miss Duan.
Why aren't you waking up, My Lady?
Manniang's Cousin-in-Law.
-Miss Duan.
-My Lady!
-Manniang's Cousin-in-Law.
-Miss Duan?
-Banxia.
-Miss Duan.
-Manniang's Cousin-in-Law.
Manniang's Cousin-in-Law.
-Miss Duan.
-Banxia.
Manniang's Cousin-in-Law.
Miss Duan.
Banxia.
Manniang's Cousin-in-Law!
Miss Duan.
Banxia.
Wake up.
You can't escape it.
Banxia.
Forget me.
No!
My Lady.
What's wrong, My Lady?
Did you have a nightmare?
Impressive!
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
There are Moon Bugs in this bag.
You're a demon,
aren't you?
I've heard the rumors.
Two demons
posing as demon hunters
are capturing evil demons across the land
and collecting primordial spirits.
They're also buying
Moon Bugs at high prices from other
demon hunters.
At first, I didn't understand,
but the moment I saw you,
it all made sense.
You're from the Carefree Land.
Is the Carefree Herb there
withering?
How do you know that?
If demons can enter the human world,
we humans
can also go to the Carefree Land.
12 years ago,
when the Realm Gate opened wide,
I went to the Underground City to look for my junior brother.
By sheer luck, I got a chance to go there.
I never thought
that outside the human world,
there would be
such a place.
No wonder
every 12 years,
more demons
show up in the world.
That's when I discovered—
the primordial spirits of demons
come from the Carefree Herb.
In the Carefree Land,
they devour primordial spirits to become demons.
And once the Carefree Herb loses its primordial spirit,
it starts to wither.
So,
after a demon dies,
its primordial spirit returns
to the Carefree Herb,
making it take root and sprout again.
It's a cycle
that never ends.
But the primordial spirits that come to the human world
can no longer return
to the Carefree Land after the demons die.
As a result,
the Carefree Land
will eventually run into problems.
All these years,
you've been traveling between the two realms collecting Moon Bugs.
You're actually collecting
the primordial spirits they swallowed,
aren't you?
You're
risking your life.
Mr. Jiu,
you're quite sharp.
Take it then.
Why are you helping me?
Then why did you help me?
Everything happens
for a reason.
Let's just say I'm repaying
your kindness.
Thank you.
I almost forgot.
My son is about to get married.
I need to hurry back to fix the roof.
These dishes are untouched.
Eat them for me.
Don't waste them.
Who?
A man.
He's about this tall,
with thick eyebrows, big eyes,
and a well-shaped nose.
He's very handsome.
I remember now.
There was someone like that.
But he's already left.
When did he leave?
He left last night.
He seemed to be in Guangping on business.
Once it was done,
he left.
Thank you, sir.
It's nothing.
[Jude Hotel]
My Lady,
that man has already left.
Let it go.
Let's go back.
I want to walk around a bit.
You can go back first.
But...
It's fine. Go back.
Alright then.
Take this umbrella.
The sky is overcast. I'll head back first.
Don't stay out too long.
Don't worry.
[Wu's Hoto Noodles]
I'm off now.
My books!
I'll pick them up.
Okay.
Let's go take shelter from the rain.
Last night,
I had that dream again.
Uncle Jiu once told me
that people and things in dreams
are reflections
of what we've seen and experienced in reality.
They don't appear out of nowhere.
But I don't know why
I dream so much.
I always have strange dreams.
They feel so familiar,
yet so unfamiliar.
Like déjà vu,
but with no clear reason.
Like something from a past life.
Mr. Man Ying.
Do you think there's really
Tea of Oblivion in this world?
Because I didn't drink enough of it,
I didn't forget
what happened in my previous life.
Have you really never seen me before?
Do we really not know each other?
Have you ever had
strange dreams
where someone
kept calling your name,
telling you to forget them?
Do you really have no impression
of me at all?
No, I don't.
Alright then.
Maybe I'm having hallucinations again.
Have I ever told you
that my family thinks
I'm mentally ill
and often hallucinate?
Since I was young,
I've been taking medicine
and seeing physicians, but nothing ever worked.
Maybe it's time for me
to take more pills.
I know a little about medicine.
It's not a big issue.
As long as you eat well,
sleep well,
and rest well,
you'll get better with time.
Don't take medicine recklessly.
Okay.
Sorry for the trouble.
I'll be going now.
It's still raining.
Take the umbrella.
♫Just sobered up after a dream, sighing for my life♫
♫In this desolate mortal world♫
♫The other side sees fantasies fading into obscurity♫
♫Is it a blessing or a calamity?♫
♫I'm all alone♫
♫Braving the snowstorm♫
♫Struck by sudden amnesia♫
♫Wait until the last peach blossom falls♫
♫Glance back with love for 10,000 years♫
Are you really not
coming back to Guangping?
It's a long journey.
Hard to travel back and forth.
♫If there were no regrets♫
I won't come back.
♫Why would the starlight still remain♫
♫To illuminate the world?♫
All right.
♫Coated in starlight, holding gleaming swords♫
♫Before daybreak♫
I wish you
a safe journey,
♫May you have no regrets♫
a smooth life,
♫Together, through seas and mountains♫
♫If all must fade away and be forgotten♫
freedom from fear and sorrow,
and joy that lasts.
♫I'd keep it all to myself♫
♫If we luck out♫
♫Let's reunite once again beyond the time♫
Thank you.
♫If there were no regrets♫
♫Why would the starlight still remain♫
♫To illuminate the world?♫
♫Coated in starlight, holding gleaming swords♫
♫Before daybreak♫
♫May you have no regrets♫
♫Together, through seas and mountains♫
♫If all must fade away and be forgotten♫
♫I'd keep it all to myself♫
♫If we luck out♫
♫Let's reunite once again beyond the time♫