[The Demon Hunter's Romance]
[Episode 19]
Big Brother.
Are you hurt?
Big Brother?
Here's some advice:
when you speak to someone,
think twice
before acting like you're top dog.
What are you waiting for?
Help Big Brother up.
Alright, alright.
What happened?
Why are you here?
Hey.
Big Brother.
Are you a-alright?
What's wrong with you?
This is the home of the four of us brothers.
Where else could we be
if not here?
Four brothers?
What are you doing?
Third Brother.
Do you think Big Brother
hit his head when he fell?
Even if it is brain damage,
it doesn't have much to do with the falling, actually.
Naughty.
Big Brother.
We should get to work.
It's almost time.
We have a lot of work to do today.
Let's go, Big Brother.
Where a-are you going?
Damao.
Are you going to the street to buy steamed buns?
Warm pancakes.
Hoto noodles!
Fresh Hoto noodles!
One bowl is as filling as two!
Guangping?
Damao!
Damao.
You came at the right time.
Look.
Freshly steamed meat buns.
I haven't even got a chance
to take them out yet.
Damao.
20 buns as usual?
Come here and have some pancakes.
They have both vegetables and meat inside.
Have some with a bowl of
warm meat broth.
I guarantee
you won't have to eat another meal today.
[A Spring Day in Guangping]
I've had enough!
Great!
Throw them!
This is Bu'er Bracelet.
How did it become a physical object?
Who cares?
Look.
They're fighting again.
This couple fights every day.
A man should marry a virtuous wife.
If you don't want to be here, get lost!
Fine!
The destroyed objects
have all become ink stains.
Everything here is originated from ink.
Could it be
I'm in that demon's painting?
Big Brother! Big Brother!
Big Brother!
Big Brother.
It's almost time.
It's time for us to go to the Huang Residence
and carry the sedan chair.
After getting this done,
you'll have enough money saved
to get married.
Third Brother, you're right.
After we help Big Brother get married
with that money,
I will be next.
Then Third Brother.
I'll be the last.
Big Brother.
You have to give me a hand.
Don't bother me.
Big Brother.
Where are you going?
You can't be like this.
We've received the deposit.
Where do you expect them to find people
to replace us if we quit now?
Besides,
a wedding is a big deal.
If we ruin it for them,
they'll become our enemies.
The four of us won't be able
to make a living around here anymore.
People will talk behind our backs in the future.
Third... Third Brother
is right.
Let go.
No.
I won't.
Why can't I apply force?
Big Brother.
Stop fooling around.
Big Brother is too naughty.
What should we do, Second Brother?
Do it.
Alright.
Stop it, Big Brother.
We should at least
get today's work done.
Right.
Put me down!
Big Brother.
Lord Huang is the one
who's getting married in a minute.
He is the county commandant.
If you run away now,
we're all done for.
Big Brother.
Behave yourself.
Don't act out of impulse.
You can, but there's really no need for that.
-Butler.
-Groomsman.
Well,
it's almost auspicious hour.
Cheer up, everyone.
His Lordship
will be out in no time.
Get the horse ready.
Thank you, thank you.
Wishing you happiness as well.
Congratulations, My Lord.
Congratulations.
My Lord.
It's okay.
Today is my wedding day.
I'm happy.
Thank you.
Youhuang...
Big Brother.
Why are you getting even more excited?
Wait for me here!
Wait for me here.
We've prepared a banquet at our residence today.
Make sure to come, everyone.
Okay.
Youhuang.
Why are you in here?
Have you seen Banxia?
Banxia?
How long have you been in here?
Did you find anything?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know you, either.
You don't know me?
How dare you!
I know you now.
You are the bearer.
Go and
carry the sedan chair properly for me right now.
If you delay my wedding,
see what happens.
Sorry, Lord Huang.
Congratulations, Lord Huang.
Hurry up.
Come on. Don't miss the time.
Be careful.
Let's go.
To the bride's!
Congratulations.
[He's Martial Arts School]
The bride
is too shy to come out.
Guys.
Let's rush her!
Bride! Bride!
It's said that the bride is grounding the rouge under the candle.
She's getting ready in front of the mirror.
She doesn't have to put on the entire makeup.
Keep her eyebrows undone for me to get them drawn.
Bravo!
Get on the sedan chair at the auspicious hour to celebrate your wedding.
May the couple live happily ever after.
The perfect marriage is a match made in heaven.
The couple will live happily in harmony.
Let go.
Big Brother! Big Brother!
How inappropriate!
So out of line.
My Lady, slowly.
Be careful.
Sit tight.
Quelian is in good hands with me.
Please rest assured.
I'll take my leave.
Dear son-in-law.
Take care.
So now, Youhuang, I,
and those three brothers
are all in the painting.
Then
Banxia should be here too.
Congratulations.
It's supposed to be a happy wedding day.
How unlucky.
Exactly.
What's going on?
My Lord.
A few days ago,
I heard that the Old Master of the Sun family
was dying.
Looks like
we've run into them.
What bad luck.
Crossing paths with a funeral procession
on his wedding day.
It's quite a weird incident.
Perhaps it can become something
as famous as the Six Wonders of Guangping in the future.
You went to Blind Liu for fortune-telling,
and you got me this date?
Well...
Bride.
We ran into a funeral procession.
We won't be able to advance
for the time being anyway.
Do you want to come out for some fresh air?
Are you insane?
Which sedan bearers' place are you from?
What’s your name?
My name is Xuanye.
Big Brother. Big Brother.
Your name is Damao. Damao.
You brat.
I'll remember you.
Don't even think about
working in this business again.
Please don't say that.
Calm down.
Calm down, please.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Please drink to your heart's content tonight.
Sure.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, My Lord.
Thank you.
Stop the sedan!
[Huang Residence]
Lower the sedan!
Look at the bride.
Welcome the bride!
What are you doing? Get out of the way.
My Lady.
It's time to get off the sedan.
My Lady, please be careful.
The bride crosses the saddle,
and the household will be in peace forever.
What happened just now?
It was nothing.
We ran into a scoundrel.
Big Brother.
We have to take the back door to get the reward money.
The front door is not for us.
Stop it.
Everyone.
Today is a day of great joy for the Huang Residence.
Master said there will be rewards for everyone.
Come with me to the backyard to collect the rewards
and have some wedding candies.
We are lucky to be here today.
Not only can we get the rewards,
but we can also join the wedding banquet.
Let's go.
Can you stop carrying me like this?
Okay, Brother.
What's the point of this?
May you and your wife live happily ever after, My Lord.
Good.
Reward him.
May you have a baby soon, My Lord.
Not bad. Give him a reward too.
Okay, thank you.
Next.
May you grow old together.
Good. Bravo.
Next.
Eternal love.
Reward.
Get a wedding candy, too.
Take it.
Thank you.
Next.
Wish you and your wife...
A happy birthday, My Lord!
I'll let you off this time.
Come on.
Next.
May you and your wife live happily ever after
and have a baby soon, My Lord.
Good.
Well said.
The bride is here.
Look into the mirror and bow.
The couple becomes one.
Evil spirits shall be exorcised forever.
The first kowtow is for
growing old together,
and living in harmony like lovebirds.
The second kowtow is for
expressing gratitude to your parents for raising you,
and wishing them good health.
The third kowtow is for
a harmonious marital life
and being united as one.
Banxia.
It's really you.
It's you again!
You're really out of your mind, you brat.
How dare you harass Her Ladyship?
You'll be in for it
after His Lordship finishes his business today.
Let's go.
This bearer is really bold.
He even dared to harass Her Ladyship.
Exactly.
He deserves to be detained here for days.
Brother.
They were saying
a bearer was arrested.
A-Aren't we
the b-bearers?
Right.
Third Brother.
Fourth Brother.
Second Brother.
Where is Big Brother?
Oh no.
So Big Brother was arrested.
Big...
Something happened to Big Brother.
Go look for him!
Are you stupid?
Second Brother.
Big Brother is here.
Damao!
Big Brother!
We're here to save you.
Find a way to open the door.
Okay.
Why don't we kick it open with our feet, Second Brother?
Big Brother! Stay clear.
Big Brother.
Did they hit you?
Big Brother, does it hurt?
Are you alright?
I'm alright. I'm alright.
Let's go!
Let's go.
But...
Brother.
You guys go first.
I still have something to do.
Where are you going?
This has nothing to do with you.
Go home first.
Big Brother is going to make a scene in the bridal chamber.
Big Brother asked us
to wait here
or go home.
But
what if Big Brother gets arrested again
later?
What should we do then?
We might as well
save him again.
My Lady.
Don't overthink it.
His Lordship has arrested
that madman.
He won't let him off easily.
My Lady, have some water.
Are you hungry, My Lady?
Do you want something to eat?
I haven't eaten all day. Of course I'm hungry.
I'll go get some nuts
for you, My Lady.
Wait for a moment, My Lady.
I'll be right back.
You again?
You don't remember me?
Right.
You must have forgotten too.
Otherwise,
you wouldn't have married Youhuang.
I don't have the time
to explain everything to you now.
Come with me.
Don't come any closer!
Stay away from me.
Are you leaving or not?
If you don't leave now,
this won't just be thrown on the ground, got it?
Calm down.
I have no ill intentions towards you.
I won't hurt you.
Are you leaving or not?
I haven't finished yet.
I'm not leaving.
Let me explain.
What you see
with your eyes right now
is all fake,
except me.
We are now
trapped in a painting.
I'm here to help you get out of here.
You'd better think about
how you can get out yourself first.
Hey, you...
It's you again.
Youhuang.
Listen to me.
Don't be afraid, Honey. I'm here.
How dare you.
You failed to ruin my wedding,
so you broke into my bridal chamber
and even tried to molest my wife.
I should have killed you just now!
You misunderstood.
The relationship between you two is not
what you think it is.
You're blinded.
I misunderstood?
Our relationship is not what it seems to be?
What do you scoundrel
intend to do!
It's not like that.
Wake up!
I wake up?
I'll help you wake up first!
Big Brother.
Are you hurt?
What are you waiting for?
Help Big Brother up.
Why were you so careless?
What happened?
Why are you here?
We... We were just talking about
getting to work.
Big Brother.
What's wrong with you?
This is the home of the four of us brothers.
Where else could we be
if not here?
Four brothers?
Sanmao.
Do you think
Big Brother hit his head?
Even if it is brain damage,
I don't think it has much to do with the falling.
He's just naughty like that.
Brother, we need to get to work.
It's almost time.
We still have a full day's work ahead of us.
Let's go, Big Brother.
W-Where are you going, Big Brother?
Where are you going?
Damao.
Are you going to the street to buy steamed buns?
Enjoy your meal.
Damao!
Freshly steamed meat buns.
I haven't even got a chance
to take them out yet.
20 buns as usual...
Damao.
20 buns as usual?
Come here and have some pancakes.
They have both vegetables and meat inside.
Eat it with a bowl of
warm meat broth.
I guarantee
you won't have to eat another meal today.
Look up.
Open your eyes.
The Six Wonders of Guangping are magnificent.
The grand mountains,
the gorgeous blossoms.
The century-old pride and grace peak at the present.
Recite it again.
Look up.
Open your eyes.
The Six Wonders of Guangping are magnificent.
The grand mountains,
the gorgeous blossoms.
Big Brother!
What's the urgent matter?
Why did you run so fast?
That's right.
We have to finish this job
no matter what the urgent matter is.
After we get this work done,
you'll have enough money to get married.
Third Brother, you're right.
After we have enough money saved
and help Big Brother get married,
I will be next.
Then Third Brother.
I'll be the last.
I have something important to do.
You guys get to work.
I have to go.
Big Brother.
Let's finish our work first.
When we come back,
we'll help you with your matter.
Big Brother.
We've already taken the deposit for this job.
Where do you expect them to find people to replace us
if we quit now?
It'll be a big deal
if we delay their wedding.
People will talk behind our backs
in the future.
Third... Third Brother is right.
Third Brother.
Wait! Wait!
Hold on. Hold on.
Look!
What are we supposed to see?
I don't know.
-Big Brother.
-Where's Big Brother?
-Big Brother!
Everyone.
Here.
Pass the wedding candies
around.
Please share in the joy.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Where are the bearers?
I didn't see them
when I came this morning.
What are you waiting for?
Go look for them immediately.
Go!
Hurry up.
Help us look for them. Hurry.
My Lord, here.
The hat
must be worn straight.
When you mount and dismount the horse,
keep your back
upright.
Let others see
how handsome you are.
The wedding etiquette
is very complicated,
so I've repeated it a few times.
Please don't mind my nagging, My Lord.
I know.
Who are you?
Who let you in?
I just want to have a word with you,
and then I'll leave.
Trust me.
You may leave.
Yes.
Today is my wedding day.
I'm in a good mood.
Just tell me what you want.
Why make such a fuss?
I don't need this.
I just hope
you can listen carefully
to what I'm about to say.
Okay.
Go ahead.
My real name is Jiu Xuanye.
Jiu Xuanye.
I'm a demon hunter from Ganshan Clinic.
Your real surname is not Huang.
You're just a constable.
Your surname is Chu,
and your first name is Youhuang.
Chu Youhuang.
This is not Guangping City.
This is just a bookstore
in the Underground City.
The owner of this bookstore
is a demon who is good at drawing.
This Guangping City is only
a city in his painting.
Demon?
Right.
You didn't believe any of these before, either.
Only after you saw
the Mirror Demon
escaped from your sword with your own eyes
did you start to believe that
there really are demons in this world.
Is that so?
Now,
we are not the only two
trapped in this painting,
Banxia is, too.
She's that
young lady from the martial arts school
who you're about to marry.
The three brothers who are going to carry the sedan chair
together with me are trapped here as well.
How is it?
Do you recall anything?
No.
So, you're doubting
what I said just now?
Isn't it obvious enough?
Although...
Although I haven't figured out
the rules
in this painting yet,
I can
prove one thing to you.
This was left to me by my grandfather!
It's all fake.
Do you even know
what you are doing?
I'm trying to prove to you
that in this painting,
everything that's destroyed
will return to its original form,
which is this ink mark!
Do you understand now?
Yes.
I understand now.
You understand?
So,
what do you plan to do next?
Guards!
Arrest him!
What are you doing?
Mr. Li. Mr. Li.
Madam, come in, please.
Okay.
Mr. Zhang. Mr. Zhang.
Please.
Have some tea.
It's him!
Let's see where you can escape this time.
Why is it so noisy outside?
What happened?
A sedan bearer from the Huang Residence
climbed over the wall and sneaked in just now.
My Lady.
He seemed to be here for you.
A bearer?
You know him, My Lady?
How could I?
My Lady.
It's almost auspicious hour.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Here.
Stay here and behave yourself!
Let's go.
Look into the mirror and bow.
The couple becomes one.
Evil spirits shall be exorcised forever.
The first kowtow is for
growing old together,
and living in harmony like lovebirds.
The second kowtow is for
expressing your gratitude to your parents for raising you,
and wishing them good health.
The third kowtow is for
a harmonious marital life
and being united as one.
Tie a knot and finish the make-up.
Join hands and enter the bridal chamber.
One.
Two.
Three.
Big Brother.
Are you hurt?
What are you waiting for?
Help Big Brother up.
Move your feet.
Hurry.
What's wrong with you, Big Brother?
You look unwell, Big Brother.
Did you h-hurt yourself somewhere, Big Brother?
Big Brother.
How about I get you a doctor?
Big Brother, say something.
Don't scare us.
Am I your Big Brother?
Yes.
Will you listen to me or not?
When mother died,
she told us all to listen to Big Brother.
We listen to Big Brother since Mother has passed away.
We'll listen to Second Brother if Big Brother dies.
Big Brother is not dead yet.
So we still listen to Big Brother now.
Alright. Alright.
I have a favor
to ask you now.
Will you help me?
Sure.
Big Brother.
What kind of talk is this?
We are brothers.
What do you mean do you a favor?
If you need anything,
just let us know.
Exactly.
If we brothers are of the same mind,
our strength will be sharp enough to cut through...
Cut through metal.
Good!
Here's the thing.
There's something
I've been keeping to myself
and haven't told you.
And I've been hesitating
whether I should tell you or not.
Big Brother.
Just say it.
Okay.
Here's the thing.
I went out
a few days ago.
When I was out...
Big Brother.
When did you go out?
I don't remember.
Right.
We were sleeping at home that day.
Listen to me.
I went out
a few days ago.
I first went south,
and then I went north.
Anyway,
I met a girl.
After I met that girl...
So it turns out
Big Brother met a girl he likes.
Big Brother has fallen in love.
He's got a story to tell.
-Naughty.
-Story.
Looks like you are not that stupid after all.
Big Brother, after all,
where is that girl from?
Which city?
She's a local, from Guangping City.
What a coincidence.
Exactly.
We are familiar with Guangping City.
Which family is she from?
What's her surname?
Let's go find her.
She's the girl from the martial arts school.
Martial...
Stop imitating me.
Shut up.
Which martial arts school?
Which martial arts school can it be?
He...
He's Martial Arts School?
Yes.
Isn't that
the bride
we're going to pick up later?
Yes.
Are you out of your mind, Big Brother?
Do you know
who her husband is?
He's famous for his fierceness.
Back when he went to suppress bandits on the mountain,
he killed a dozen bandits
all by himself.
He's murderous.
Big Brother.
He's really brutal.
Are you scared?
So you aren't going to
help your Big Brother, right?
You've forgotten
what your mother told you, right?
I... I...
I-I'm not scared.
Brother, you are scared.
You are more or less...
Shut up!
We are not bandits.
Even if we are caught,
we won't die.
In short,
will you
kidnap the bride
with your Big Brother or not?
I...
Good brothers.
Are In the heart.
We are brothers. We are the closest people in this world.
What about you two?
Brother.
The atmosphere has reached this point.
Well,
we'll go too.
Good!
I knew I wasn't wrong about you.
If we brothers are of the same mind,
our strength will be sharp enough to cut through...
Metal!
Congratulations.
Thank you, thank you.
Congratulations, Lord Huang.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Congratulations, Lord Huang.
Congratulations.
Wait a bit longer.
Stop!
Get ready.
Hold tight.
Run!
What happened?
What are they doing?
They're running away.
Where are they taking the sedan chair?
What's going on?
Have those four guys
never seen a funeral procession?
Quelian?
Quelian!
Make way!
What kind of people are they?
Watch out!
Stop, stop!
Stop!
Who are you guys?
You kidnapped me during my wedding in broad daylight.
Do you wish to die?
Sit tight.
I'll explain to you later.
Okay?
Let's go!
Brother.
She smells so good.
She's asleep.
Big Brother is asleep too.
Do you think Big Brother is tired?
Who's asleep?
Big Brother, you're awake.
Shut up.
You woke Big Brother up.
Let's go out.
Let's go.
Go.
You're awake.
Where am I?
This is just a shack.
Why did you bring me here?
Those from the Huang Residence
won't be able to find us for now.
You are alone?
Where are your accomplices?
They are outside.
So,
are you trying to rob me
or kill me?
Neither.
So you want to molest me?
Do you have any other questions
you want to ask?
If not,
just listen to me.
What I'm about to say
might sound unbelievable
and nonsensical to you.
But I swear,
everything I say is true.
I hope you can listen patiently to
what I say,
and then decide
whether to believe me or not.
Okay?
Did you two h-hear...
That's about it.
So you mean,
my real surname is not He.
My surname is Duan, and my full name is Duan Banxia?
Yes.
My current parents
are not my real parents.
My husband
is not my real husband either.
That's right.
I...
We are trapped in a painting.
This painting
was drawn by a demon.
Yes. Right.
Do you think I believe you?
Are you willing to believe me?
Although what you said
sounds ridiculous,
for some reason,
I just feel like
I should believe you.
According to what you said,
when I think about it carefully...
Indeed.
When I woke up this morning,
I had a headache.
I felt dizzy and groggy,
like I was dreaming.
Yes. That's right.
I was like that on the first day as well.
And
many things I did
felt familiar.
They just felt somewhat familiar to me.
I think
you should be able to restore your memory
very soon.
But even if
I recall everything,
we still don't know
how to get out.
Actually,
I've thought about it carefully.
This painting
should be the longest painting
in Enlightenment Bookstore.
It's one of that demon's
best works.
You,
I,
Youhuang,
and the three brothers outside
are all trapped in this painting.
Besides,
your parents
may be trapped here too.
This demon
is so obsessed with your parents that
even after over 10 years,
it still sent Chi Wangchuan
to kidnap your father.
I guess
your parents
are probably
the finishing touch of this painting.
They are the important characters.
If we can find your parents,
we may be able to find a way
to get out.
I think you have a point.
You know what?
I tried to
awaken Youhuang before,
but he didn't believe me at all.
Fortunately.
Fortunately, you believe me.
Of course I believe you.
It's just that
I haven't eaten anything
since this morning.
Wait for me.
I'll get you something to eat.
Okay.
Full of nonsense.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
Big Brother.
Are you hurt?
What are you waiting for?
Help Big Brother up.
Big Brother.
What's wrong with you, Big Brother?
You look unwell, Big Brother.
Did you h-hurt yourself somewhere?
Stop talking.
Leave me alone.
Big Brother.
How about I get you a doctor?
I'm your Big Brother.
Will you listen to me?
Sure.
Congratulations.
Hold tight.
Run!
What's going on?
Have these four guys
never seen a funeral procession?
Quelian?
Quelian!
Make way!
Why are you all kneeling here?
Waiting to pay your last respects to me?
Stand up now!
Get out there and
find her!
Hurry!
Yes.
My Lord.
Please calm down.
I'm not angry!
I'm just worried.
As an official,
I must have
offended many people in my life.
I'm worried that
they'll take the chance to take revenge on my wife.
Don't worry, My Lord.
All the officials in the city
are trying their best to apprehend the kidnappers.
I believe
we'll find Her Ladyship very soon.
No.
This is not enough.