[English subtitles are available]
[Oh My Lord]
[Episode 6]
[Huilan Hall]
Madam De.
A lone green stem,
two shadows of red.
Hurry!
Open it and let me see.
Are the twin lotus flowers as spiritual
as you said?
Bai,
why are you being so mysterious?
Madam De can't wait any longer,
open it now.
Koi fish?
Madam De wants to see the lotus.
No!
My lord,
I think...
Madam De cares more about
the meaning of the twin lotus flowers.
What do you mean?
My lord, think about it.
No matter how beautiful a flower blooms,
it will wither someday.
What if that day comes, and
Madam De holds you accountable for?
What will you do?
Here.
Do you think we're blind?
-Are these twin lotus flowers? -What twin lotus flowers?
Isn't this a water tank?
Bai Li,
how dare you!
Madam De, please calm down.
Please look carefully.
Flowers bloom and wither.
I'm worried
when the flowers wither,
they may make you upset.
So, I present you with
the twin lotus flowers that will never wither.
Madam, look.
The lotus tank is visually intermingled yet picturesque.
Put it in the imperial palace, and
you can see it every day.
These green leaves and koi fishes represent fun,
symbolize auspice.
If it is placed in the imperial palace,
it will bring spiritual energy.
What a joke!
Bai,
you can really defend yourself.
I think you broke the twin lotus flowers, so
you use this fake flower as an alternative.
Madam De...
won't be fooled by your little trick.
My lord, think about it.
Twin lotus flowers are so rare.
Once you do this,
you give Madam De hope.
Even in a place where there is no life.
Once the master has hope,
the spiritual energy comes along with it!
Madam De,
twin lotus flowers are hard to find.
It's even harder to find like-minded people.
I believe that being pure-hearted is efficacious.
If Madam De still wishes to admire twin lotus flowers,
you can try planting this seed yourself.
If the twin lotus flowers bloom in the imperial palace one day,
the late castellan must have
felt your longing.
Bai is indeed the most trusted person in this city.
This never withering twin lotus flowers,
I like it very much.
Tomorrow is the beam raising ceremony.
I want to see this yard filled with twin lotus flowers.
Don't miss the auspicious time.
Yes.
[Lord Xian's Palace]
How absurd!
He fooled her
with just a few tanks.
Your Highness,
eyebrows.
You go to Bai's Mansion again and
find Chen Youyou.
Tell her...
if Bai Li
appears at Madam De's imperial palace tomorrow,
I'll kill Chen Pingzhi immediately.
I've picked the flowers.
Why is this still all I have left?
What should I do?
My lord,
the lotus tanks are ready.
All we need is to send them to the palace tomorrow.
Miss Chen is quite smart.
She accidentally broke the flower,
but prepared and
thought of a better way for you.
Of course!
She is my girl.
I mean
she has been in Bai's Mansion for more than three months.
She knows more or less about
the affairs in the palace.
She learned to be smart.
Be careful.
Are you alright?
Miss.
Youyou,
what a coincidence.
I made some flower tea.
Do you want some?
Don't mention flowers to me.
I can't hear this word now.
You don't like tea?
I made other dishes as well.
Would you like to go back with me
and try them out?
Green tea?
I'm afraid I need to let you down.
My stomach is weak.
I can't drink such high-quality tea.
Early this morning,
I sent soup noodle to my lord,
but he didn't eat it.
Now, you too refuse to drink my tea.
Did I do something wrong?
So this is what you want to ask.
My lord just doesn't want you to overwork yourself.
I knew it he cares about me.
Miss Jiang,
a noble lady like you
should rest more.
He cares about you a lot,
so don't make him worry.
Miss Jiang,
you told me last time...
if I have any questions, I can ask you.
Does it still count?
What's your question?
Miss Jiang has been with my lord for a long time.
You must know him well!
What are some of his
daily likes?
Normally...
other than eating soup noodles and drinking flower tea,
he also likes to drink liquor.
Very much.
Thank you, Miss Jiang.
Miss.
Miss Jiang is so nice.
She told you everything
once you asked her.
But,
does my lord really like drinking?
I've never seen him drinking
even once since I came here.
Are you stupid?
Judging from Miss Jiang's personality,
she must be telling us the opposite.
I guess
my lord can't really drink.
Let's go!
Go!
[Calming Hall]
I've been making you angry a lot lately.
To apologize,
I sincerely invite you to the courtyard to chat a little.
My lord!
I wish you
to take the lead,
to have a successful life,
to swim in water like three fishes,
and to be blessed like four pigs.
Today is not my birthday, right?
Besides,
to swim in water like three fishes and to be blessed like four pigs...
I don't think there are such phrases.
It doesn't matter.
What matters is that
do you remember
what day is today?
What day?
Today is the 100th day of our wedding.
So,
this thing...
is from you?
Sure!
I handmade this for you.
Look at how soft this fur is.
It's comfortable when you hold on to it daily too.
This area can also be used
to clean.
Two functions in one item.
Isn't it practical?
But, why does this texture
feels so familiar.
General Gu! General Gu!
Bad news!
Lord Bai's favorite Ferghana horses
become bald!
Fast, take me to have a look.
Hurry up.
My lord, come and have a look.
Look at what I have prepared for you.
Look at these.
Once
when I was wandering outside,
I sometimes couldn't find a pot.
Then I put the raw meat on stones
and roast them with fire.
It's delicious!
This is my secret recipe!
You have so many secret recipes.
Of course!
I have many secret recipes.
I'll show you more in the future.
Sit down.
Well...
On this special day,
we should have a drink to celebrate,
right?
This first cup is
to celebrate our 100th day anniversary.
This second cup,
I wish you in advance on
the smooth completion of your work as scheduled.
My lord, you are not going to make me lose face,
right?
Then, this third cup,
I wish...
I wish
all of your dreams come true.
Here.
I too wish
all your dreams come true.
My lord,
you can't eat the meat like this.
It's very greasy.
Look at me.
Like this.
Look.
Is it good?
Why are you looking at me like this?
Because...
you are handsome.
It seems like
I can see you clearer like this.
Here!
Drink up and sleep well!
My lord, you are drunk!
You are drunk.
Nonsense!
You're the one who is drunk.
If you are not drunk,
why are you shaking?
Chen Youyou, you're drunk.
You're drunk!
When I, Chen Youyou, was wandering around,
I can drink more than a bunch of strong men do.
This is just a piece of cake.
Besides...
Besides,
I'm happy today.
I want to drink as much as I want!
My lord,
I'm sorry.
Although I didn't mean to,
I did cause you trouble.
But,
you are a lord.
Please forgive an average man.
You will understand me,
right?
Who are you?
I don't blame you
for the twin lotus flowers incident.
Of course you can't blame me!
Do you think this is easy for me?
I stay here every day, and
need to do everything depending on your mood!
That time, you...
You were so far away.
You closed your eyes and shot me with your arrows.
You even poisoned me,
and I almost died!
From now on,
I won't be like that again.
In front of me,
you can be yourself.
Of course I can!
Tell me.
You are mine.
You like me.
What's with that expression?
You're the one who mistreated me for the previous two times,
even though I was the one who kissed you.
But,
I was forced.
♫ Moonlight falls on your red lips ♫
♫ The autumn wind brings fragrance ♫
♫ Your beautiful hair is reflected in the pond. Memories fade ♫
♫ If the night breeze makes a difference ♫
♫ In the way you look back ♫
♫ Our fates are intertwined ♫
♫ We can't turn back ♫
♫ The handsome boy puts on a decent suit ♫
♫ Running at full speed on horseback ♫
[Wind Booth]
♫ Sadness and happiness can't be seen ♫
Apple.
What does this mean?
My lord.
What?
I found a box
at the back yard's door.
There's an apple seed inside.
Who sent it?
It looks like the butler from Lord Xian's Palace.
Lord Xian's Palace?
Lord Xian?
Why is there only the seed left?
I really did my best.
My lord, hurry up.
Drink it.
Then, I can save the apple.
[Gorgeous Vernal Scenery]
Miss!
Miss, drink this.
You should have drank
this hangover soup yesterday.
Last night,
when my lord brought you back,
I was so scared!
My lord looked pale
and even a bit angry.
Miss, what happened?
Tiao,
what time is it now?
It's already 9:00 AM.
Oh no.
Miss.
[Secret Letter]
A secret letter?
It looks very important.
If I give it to Lord Xian,
will it calm him down?
Can this save my dad's life for the time being?
But if it's important,
would Lord Qiansui be angry?
Forget it!
It's a life or death situation.
He will understand.
[Lord Xian's Palace]
I didn't expect Miss Chen
to be a spy of Lord Xian.
It seems that on the day of the body examination,
they already colluded
to set you up.
You've been plotting from the beginning to the end?
Do you have any sincerity at all?
[Lord Xian's Palace]
A woman's heart is like a needle in the sea.
From what I see...
those cold watermelons and barbecue
all are hypocritical.
[Lord Xian's Palace]
Since things have come to this,
don't hesitate, my lord.
Just...
Just do it.
[Lord Xian's Palace]
My lord!
Oh!
[Lord Xian's Palace]
No, no!
My lord,
what on earth
is Miss Chen up to?
Why did she go back?
For my conscience,
I had better think of another way.
[Secret Letter to Lord Qiansui]
My... my... my...
My lord, I...
I know
you drank too much last night, so
I came to visit you.
Do you need
hangover soup?
Is it only hangover soup?
I'm drunk.
I've been drunk for a long time.
I'll go prepare it for you now!
Weird!
He looks sober.
Why does he still want to drink the hangover soup?
Go home.
Bai's Mansion is your home.
Don't always run out when you're free.
Should I be honest
to my lord about my dad?
Chen Pingzhi?
Are you sure?
This father and daughter both
are troublesome.
My lord, I think
Why don't you...
I'll stop you there.
My lord!
Didn't you say she is a meticulous person
when she sewed a wrist strap for me?
She...
She's just faking it.
Didn't you say
she protected me in front of Lord Xian?
She's just afraid
to get in trouble.
Didn't you say she took care of my daily necessities
and even made supper?
My lord!
She has evil intentions!
Didn't you say she covet my beauty?
My lord, I think this is true.
I don't think so anymore.
My lord,
what should we do with Chen Pingzhi?
I have my own plan.
[Qingming House]
Chen Youyou,
just wait to collect your father's body.
No, Your Highness!
Please show mercy.
Your Highness,
here's the apple sauce.
It's chopped to such small chunks!
No, don't chop it.
Your Highness, I've broken the flowers and drank the liquor.
But, I didn't expect him to be so good at drinking.
Please give me another chance.
But, you seem to enjoy drinking very much.
No, no.
I'm not happy!
How can I be happy
if I didn't do what you asked?
Your Highness, please give me more time.
I promise you will be satisfied.
How?
Three days.
Just three days.
I promise he won't get to finish the imperial palace as he wishes.
Okay.