[English subtitles are available]
[Oh My Lord]
[Episode 9]
Seek over there.
Over there.
Hurry! Over there!
Lord, we still can't find her.
Keep seeking.
Don't miss any corner.
Yes.
Report!
Lord Bai,
we found a missing lady.
Where did you find her?
In the suburb of the city.
Two guys were burying her.
They ran away after they were found.
Did you find any clues?
No.
She has been in a coma.
Report immediately when she wakes up.
Yes.
Let's go to check the suburbs.
Kneel there.
Why does he want to kill us together?
Cry!
You either can't cry,
or just cried blind.
So useless.
Brother,
how about I get some more?
The heat is on recently.
And our goods
will be sold out shortly.
If they can't cry today,
we'll be finished.
Cry!
You can't cry either?
-Cry. -Cry.
They want our tears of fear.
Tears of...
Cry now.
The tears are used to make the rouge.
Rouge?
Cry.
Stop.
What's the point of crying like that?
Number Two.
Come out!
Let go!
Come here.
Chop her up!
I'll show you
the consequences of not crying.
Wait a moment.
Mr. Huang,
do you know
the legend of dirty peach rouge?
Your dirty peach rouge is not bad,
but it's still
a little worse than mine.
Your love tear rouge
is really smart.
But if it's only sold in Fuxian City,
it's not only risky,
but also easy to get you into troubles.
And if...
Get me into troubles?
Don't be angry.
I have a way to help you expand market.
Go ahead.
Precise localization, as well as small profits but quick turnover
are essential to business.
OK.
I'll give you three days
to make a makeup more popular
than the dirty peach rouge.
In three days?
I can't make it.
Mr. Huang,
calm down.
I'm really not a master of cosmetics.
You...
But I'm a genius in business.
I have a whole set of marketing plans.
I wonder
if Mr. Huang will give me this chance.
Second Chief.
Number Two,
tell everyone to cooperate with her
in order to carry out her plans.
If she can't make it,
bury them all.
Dad, don't worry.
I will be safe and live a good life.
[Fuxian City]
Lord,
we've been to the suburbs.
We have also searched everywhere downtown.
You haven't slept for three days.
-No sleep, rest, food and drink. -Look at these fans.
Let's take a break.
Miss Chen
might not have been taken away by human traffickers.
The rouge
is really good.
I like this.
Where did you buy it?
[Fortune Shop]
Come and have a seat here.
You're welcome, sir.
How are the dishes I cooked for you?
It's a feast.
Your ideas are really smart.
You carved fruit on the rouge
and the slogan of embracing...
Embrace the four seasons with beauty.
Yes, that's it.
The slogan is widely heard.
Everyone in Fuxian City
knows it.
They even buy four boxes at a time.
Yes!
How did you come up with this idea?
I admire you very much.
Thank you.
I need talents like you
to make our shop bigger and stronger.
I think
we'll be sworn brother and sister here today.
From now on, you'll be my Second Chief.
OK.
Brother.
Am I the Second Chief?
What are you talking about?
From now on, you'll be the Third Chief.
The Second Chief is she.
Mr. Huang.
Forget it.
I don't think he's happy about this.
Don't worry about him!
I say you are the Second Chief.
You're the Second Chief.
Third Chief, tell me
which day is lucky.
There's no lucky day within the next ten years.
Third Chief, why are you jealous?
You are so petty.
Well,
let's do it
tomorrow.
Mr. Huang,
since you said so,
I will be immature
if I still refuse, right?
Well,
tomorrow,
I'll ask those girls
to dance for us
and get some fine liquor.
Let's have a reunion dinner and have fun.
Come on, Mr.Huang.
Third Chief.
[Escorts]
[Fortune Teller]
If you find Miss Chen,
His Royal Highness will reward you.
[Fortune Teller]
Let's go.
Friendship cake?
It tastes much better than the one you gave last time.
Youyou,
where are you?
[Fortune Shop]
Please go back, Second Chief.
The backyard is the private residence.
Outsiders are not allowed to enter.
Although this is a place for businessmen to rest,
it definitely isn't that simple.
There must be something fishy.
We must save Miss Chen.
Lord,
I'll
turn the place upside down.
Sit down.
She is hidden in such a secret way.
We can't alert them.
OK.
Now let's review
the movements we just learned.
Jiuyue, show us first.
There is a wall in the east, and there's no door.
Not bad.
Quite good.
Shiyue, show us too.
Someone is watching in the west. We can't get out there.
You need more practice.
OK.
Let's learn the new movements.
Follow me.
Like this.
Siyue, you did it wrong.
It supposed to be like this.
There's a cliff in the north. We can't run away.
How is it going?
Five seconds.
Like this.
Good job.
Then, you guys practice hard here.
I'll take a break outside.
Keep practicing.
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Stop!
Where are you going?
Third Chief,
I'm considering
the safety of our Fortune Shop.
Look.
No one is watching at such an important place.
I'm here to help guard for Mr. Huang.
Do you think
you can cozy up to my brother by this?
Third Chief,
you were being a little narrow-minded.
We should be broad-minded
and open-minded.
I treat you as my brother.
Don't say things like that.
What I did is
for the business of Fortune Shop.
You know...
You two!
Where did you go?
I told you to eat light food,
but you only ate fish and meat.
Guard carefully!
I'm going to practice the dance.
Relax.
Guard carefully!
Yes.
Please.
General, we count on you.
There is a bug in your dish.
Where?
A bug.
-There is a bug. -Look.
There is a bug in their dish.
Look here!
Waiter, come here.
There is a bug in the dish.
There is a bug!
Bug!
Come on.
There is a bug in the dish.
There is a bug in their dish.
There are bugs.
There are bugs inside.
There is a bug inside.
There is a bug in the dish.
Give me an explanation.
Refund the money.
Lord.
Will this
really work?
Normally,
I should
take the lead and go for it bravely.
But I...
I'm too ugly.
So you have to
do this in person.
Lord, you...
Look at you.
Your gestures are
not very...
Not very feminine.
Look at me.
Get away!
OK.
Let's do as planned.
We caught one.
Help!
Why is she so heavy?
Yes.
Another teenage girl
is in danger.
[Fortune Shop]
Brother.
The woman tried to
sneak out today.
There must be something fishy.
She's so hypocritical.
Third Chief,
is the money real?
Better safe than sorry.
Brother,
you have to trust me.
Xiang,
you used to be the Second Chief,
Now you are the Third Chief.
You may be the fourth and fifth later.
If you can't make much money like this,
you won't be at home at last.
Brother.
Even if I don't have a home,
we're still two lucky brothers.
Get lost!
Go back to your work.
Leave me alone.
What are you doing?
I knew it!
I caught you!
What are you talking about?
I don't understand. Let go.
Stop pretending.
Come with me to see my brother.
What?
It hurts. Let go.
I made so much money for you.
Who will your brother trust?
I advise you to think it twice.
Let go! Let go!
How dare you threaten me?
Today is your time of death.
Youyou.
You are a murderer! Let me go!
Let me go!
Youyou.
You are a murderer!
Chen Pingzhi didn't die.
What did you say?
Your father didn't die.
Youyou.
It was my fault at the imperial palace.
I left you and put you in danger.
I was inconsiderate.
I'm sorry.
I have sent your father out of the city safely.
I know that
you wanted to ask Madam De for rewards and let your father go.
But Lord Xian wouldn't let it go.
To protect you,
I hid it from you.
[Don't let Lord Xian find you. I'll pick you up later.]
Youyou.
I've left Fuxian City.
Lord Qiansui saved me.
Be careful.
Don't let Lord Xian find you.
I'll pick you up later.
This...
This is my father's handwriting.
Is he really alive?
Where is he now?
When the trouble dies down,
I will take you to him.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You didn't give me the chance to explain.
Why didn't you tell me until now?
It hurts?
It doesn't hurt anymore since I've found you.
Youyou.
In the future,
I will tell you everything clearly.
Do you know
because of you,
I was caught by human traffickers?
If I hadn't been caught by them,
I wouldn't have ended up in this shabby place.
There are so many
rats, cockroaches and bugs.
They are big and fat.
Every day, they are wriggling here and there.
I am scared.
All right.
It's all over.
It's my fault.
My lord,
how about we deal with him first?
Let's go over there.
Lord.
-Castellan? -Bai Li, Chen Youyou?
I could get in thanks to my pet bug, General.
I didn't expect it to be so great.
To die for the people of Fuxian City
is also considered to die without regret.
What about you?
Why are you here?
I'm one of the missing women.
So am I.
That's not important.
The point now
is to save other women.
Do you have a good idea?
Castellan,
I have a plan.
They didn't look
so beautiful before.
You are really good at teaching.
Just so so.
Come on, guys.
Our Second Chief
made a lot of money for us.
Let's toast her.
Come on.
I'm flattered.
It's all thanks to your strategy.
Let me toast you.
You're quite humble.
Cheers.
Where is Third Chief?
Isn't he here?
Brother,
don't you think
he has prejudice against me?
Although he has
a full beard,
he is
very narrow-minded.
Exactly.
Forget about him. Come on guys.
-Cheers! -Cheers.
Cheers.
Brother,
I think you are in a good mood today.
Well,
I have another good news to announce.
Let them leave for a while.
You can leave now.
Leave. Leave.
Go.
You may leave.
Brother.
Have more.
Let's eat.
This is the customized rouge.
It will be available at our Fortune Shop.
Limited edition. There are only ten sets.
Ten sets?
How much can we earn then?
Brother, let me explain to you.
We won't sell it at the original price.
The one who offers higher price can get it.
Selling to the highest bidder?
Once it's available in our shop,
the rich people will try their best to get it.
Isn't that...
A hundred thousand.
A million.
Ten million!
A billion!
We're going to make a fortune, guys!
Cheers.
Come on.
Drink.
Cheers.
Brother, calm down.
This is just the first step.
Wait. I still have...
Look at this.
What is this?
This is the future of our Fortune Shop.
Future?
I think our buddies
are not very enthusiastic.
I...
Come on.
Guys, look at our future.
Come on. Look.
Look, this
is our Feng Shui land.
Well,
look here guys.
This is the residence for Mr. Huang.
Why is Chen Youyou so talkative?
Let's build a small yard here for all of you.
Bai Li,
get me
a set of rouge later.
Let's set up a rouge workshop first.
A rouge workshop.
Here?
Good. Good.
Look here.
And here.
Let's build a big house for Mr. Huang.
A big house?
A big house.
Brother!
Look over there.
Run!
Chase!
Stop!
There's one here.
-Chase them! -Stop!
Don't come over!
Go after her.
Let me go first.
Let me go first. I...
Are you alright?
Stop! Stop!
Leave me alone.
Don't chase me.
Go away!
Over there!
How dare you chase me?
One more there.
This way.
Brother, untie me.
Number Two,
I told you she was not a good bird.
You did't believe me.
How can she be the Second Chief?
Untie me!
Cut the crap!
Catch her!
This way!
Chase him.
And these two.
[Making a lot of money every day]
Over there!
Go after them!
Go.
Why are you all chasing them?
Come and catch me.
I'm here! I'm here!
Is she really here?
My son found that token.
I dare not lie to you.
I could't care so much.
Search inside!
[Fortune Shop]
Hurry.
Castellan？
You're just in time. Protect me!
-Castellan, why are you here? -Lord.
That reminds me.
Bai Li and Chen Youyou are still inside.
You...
Don't mind me.
Don't worry about me.
You just need to save them.
-Stop! -Stop!
Go!
Stop!
My lord!
What's wrong?
Wake up, my Lord.
My lord, don't scare me.
My lord, wake up!
My lord!