♪The wind gusts towards me♪
♪Crushing the clouds above the sea♪
♪The skateboard speeds by♪
♪Marking the moment we meet♪
♪Descartes's cardioid♪
♪Calculates the love function♪
♪Sigma's summation♪
♪Gets stuck on the moment
we're reunited♪
♪Nervous and expectant♪
♪You and I carefully embrace
the excitement♪
♪We recall the first time we met♪
♪Sour-sweet lemony candy♪
♪We still yearn♪
♪Though we haven't shown our feelings♪
♪What are you scared of Let me read♪
♪The love letter kept in the old days♪
=Binary Love=
=Episode 12=
=A Male Caregiver Who Returns the Favor=
Linlin, Linlin!
Are you okay?
Are you all right?
You rushed out suddenly.
Jesus.
Are you all right?
Linlin, are you all right?
Are you leaving now?
Sorry.
You can come at me.
But...
Just go.
Who are you?
It's okay. I'll take care of this.
(Outpatient Department)
Nurse! Nurse!
Someone is injured!
Be careful.
- Doctor, we need help.
- What happened?
The school doctor has examined her.
She feels pain in this place.
It is suspected of appendicitis.
Please take a look at her.
Here.
Take away your hand.
It hurts.
Come on, turn her over.
Be careful.
It hurts!
It could also be kidney stones.
Hurry. Get her to the emergency room
to run some tests.
Linlin, you're almost there.
Hang in there.
Don't be afraid.
(Emergency Room)
How is Linlin doing?
Hello. How's the patient
who just went inside?
She is undergoing treatment.
Your injury looks pretty bad, too.
You should treat it now.
Thank you.
Go ahead. I'll stay here.
No. I'll wait for her here.
Linlin needs someone
to take care of her now.
You have such a bad injury.
You can come back when she wakes up.
I'll let you know
the first time she wakes up.
(Outpatient Department)
(Emergency Room)
Doctor.
How's the patient in there?
According to the CT,
it should be a kidney stone.
But it's not big.
The patient can pass it on her own.
She'll recover after being given fluids
and anti-inflammatory drugs.
Is there anything
we should pay attention to?
Make sure she will drink more water
and do more jumps.
It can help her pass the stone.
Jumping rope will also work.
Okay. Thank you, Doctor.
Linlin, you're awake.
How are you feeling now?
Are you still in pain?
Would you like something to eat?
Where is Fang Yuke?
Lie here and don't move.
I'll see how he is doing now.
Don't move your hand after you go back.
You need to avoid certain food
and keep your hand from water.
Wen Tao!
- You can leave after having some rest.
- How is your hand?
Thank you.
How is Linlin?
The doctor said it's a kidney stone.
But it's not serious.
She's been put on a drip.
Where is she now?
In the emergency room.
The doctor said
Linlin should drink more water.
Thanks.
(Emergency Room)
Linlin.
- Are you all right?
I'm fine.
How is your hand?
It's okay.
See?
Don't move your hand around.
Are you still in pain?
The doctor said
I should just get some rest.
I'm hungry.
Let's go get something to eat later.
The doctor said
you're not fully recovered yet.
You have limited food choices.
You need to...
You need to drink more water.
Yeah.
Fang Yuke!
Doctor! Nurse!
What's wrong with him?
Go find someone first.
Okay.
Hello, can you hear me?
The patient has a mild concussion
from the car accident.
He needs to stay overnight
for observation.
Doctor, is there anything
I should pay attention to
when I take care of him?
He will have dizziness
and a headache in the next few days,
but don't worry too much.
The symptoms
will disappear in three to five days.
Right now his injured arm
is more serious.
It needs more attention.
It was just an ordinary fracture,
but it became severe
due to excessive stretching.
Don't worry too much about it.
Take care of yourself first.
Have the drip first
and go through
the admission formalities later.
Thank you, Doctor.
You're welcome.
Have some good rest.
(Inpatient Department)
Where are they?
We've been going in circles.
Keep your voice down.
We're in hospital.
I told you to come earlier.
But we had classes all the afternoon.
Call Fang Yuke.
I called him, but he didn't answer.
Come on, they're here.
Let me see.
What's going on?
Why is Fang Yuke lying in bed?
Isn't Zhou Linlin sick?
Do you think the four of us
look like mistresses?
Mis...
What do you mean?
- All right, all right.
- I don't know.
Let's leave it to the nurse.
Let's go.
But since we're here,
we should go in and take a look.
- Just go.
- Go.
Go.
But...
Fang Yuke.
Thank you.
(Inpatient Department)
I don't believe it.
There's no environment I can't adapt to.
You can't help it, right?
I've been waiting for you
for half an hour.
Are you here so late
because you miss me?
Don't you feel itchy?
No.
Why are you wearing the mosquito net?
The mosquito net was ill-designed.
I can't hang it up at all.
Let me do it for you.
You...
Is that how you're gonna hang it up?
I thought I can untie it directly.
Do you need my help?
I need you to sit here.
All right, I'll take care of the rest.
Tuck it in like this,
then the mosquitoes won't get in.
I'm gonna go.
Let me see you out.
Stop.
You'd better stay in there.
Thank you, little mosquito.
What's this?
Solanum rootstock seedlings.
These are for grafting.
Common cherry tomatoes
are susceptible
to verticillium wilt
and bacterial wilt during growth.
Only by grafting seedlings
onto solanum rootstocks
can they be protected
and grow the best fruit.
So, do you want to try it?
Who wants to try it?
What are you doing?
Making a wish.
When it blooms,
you'll fall in love with me.
Do you think
you will fall in love with me?
Don't put too much pressure
on the seedlings,
or they won't dare to bloom.
(Outpatient Department)
- Let's go.
(Nanshan, TAXI, Empty)
Sir, go to Xinyuan Residence.
(Outpatient Department)
Thank you
for last night.
You're welcome.
You wouldn't have been hurt
if it wasn't for me.
Get some sleep.
It will take a while before we get home.
I'll wake you up when we arrive.
Mm.
I'll go back then. Have some rest.
Don't go back.
What's wrong?
You haven't eaten anything all day.
You must be hungry.
I'll order some takeouts
and we can eat together.
Ms. Chen Pingping once said,
you'd better buy a pot
and cook yourself.
Takeouts will never be as healthy
as the food we make ourselves.
Can you cook?
It shouldn't be hard.
Let's cook together then?
Okay.
- Welcome back!
(What doesn't kill you makes you better)
Welcome back!
How did you get in here?
Boss asked us to clean the house up.
I asked you to clean up here,
but I didn't ask you to decorate it.
A famous person once said
good friends grow old together.
Fang Yuke had surgery,
and we'll take care of him together!
But Fang Yuke didn't have surgery.
It's about rhyming.
You know nothing.
- Just shut your mouth.
- Jesus.
Boss, this is the schedule
we worked out.
We will take turns each day
to look after you.
Ding, say something!
Well said. Take this!
Sorry.
Be careful!
Come on.
Why can't we talk outside?
Take them out of here right now.
Why?
The doctor said
Fang Yuke needs to rest
after leaving the hospital.
Really?
We can also take care of you.
We promise not to make any noise.
I need to talk to Fang Yuke,
just the two of us. Do you get it now?
Our Linlin has finally grown up!
Just go.
What secrets do you have
that I'm not supposed to know?
Linlin needs some space, okay?
Just go.
Go. Go.
Play this.
Who's that?
Pack your things and leave with me!
Leave? I just sat down.
My butt is still cold.
I just got a call.
There's an important meeting at school
that we need to attend.
What meeting is it?
Why should I, a different major,
also attend it?
I'm not going.
I said there is a meeting,
and there is a meeting!
Do what I say and leave with me!
But...
Well, isn't the schedule
I worked out wasted?
Schedule?
Does it hurt?
Yeah.
It's so annoying. My head hurts.
Do you want to hang out
with your schedule?
No, I don't.
Leave with me then!
Zhu Li, show me some respect.
Hurry up.
Oh.
Is your hand all right?
It's okay.
Sorry, I forgot my bag.
You two go on. Go on.
Let me take these off for you.
Okay.
Be careful.
All right.
One more round.
What was I going to do?
You...
We... we're cleaning up.
Oh, clean up.
It's good to be clean. You two go on.
We're really cleaning up.
All right, come on! I'll see you again!
Or never!
You...
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Well, I won't
take these off for you then.
You can do it yourself later.
Slippers.
I'll go make some porridge
and come back later.
Who allowed you to look so alike?
They're just cherry tomatoes.
I can't talk to animals.
Can't I even talk to plants?
This one.
How can you recognize it at a glance?
Of course I can.
You must bloom.
Do you hear me?
Linlin!
Wait a minute!
Coming!
Who's it?
Congratulations on leaving the hospital.
Why are you here?
It smells so good.
Is that for me?
Did you know I was coming?
No, no, it's not for you.
Don't touch it.
If it's not for me, who is it for then?
Fang Yuke?
Yeah.
You're still sick.
Why do you take care of him?
The doctor said he has a mild concussion
and needs rest.
Don't you have training today?
We have a day off today.
So I'm here to see you.
And Fang Yuke.
Are you here to see Fang Yuke?
He needs rest now.
Don't disturb him.
Why can't I see Fang Yuke?
Mr. Fang helped me a lot
with my English.
I'm always grateful.
Isn't it natural
that I'm here to see him?
What is this?
It's for you.
The doctor said jumping ropes
can help you pass the stone.
There are both ropes in these two bags.
You may use whichever you like.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Let's go to see Mr. Fang.
The porridge will get cold later.
It's hot.
Hurry up.
Mr. Fang, I'm here to see you.
I'll get the porridge first.
There are many guests today.
He said he's here to pay you a favor
for teaching him English.
What happened to your hand?
I just burnt it.
I've run water over it. I'm fine.
It's red now. You're not fine.
Come on.
The porridge will get cold
if we don't eat it now.
Linlin, it's super delicious.
Thank you.
Let me do it.
Put it here, put it here.
Come on, Mr. Fang.
I can eat myself...
It takes a hundred days for the bone
to knit and tendons to heal.
Linlin said you have
a mild concussion.
You must be more careful these days.
Here, one more gulp.
I'll take care of Mr. Fang
in the next few days.
- You?
Yeah.
What's the problem?
You're too busy training.
You don't need to do it.
You were busy studying, too.
You still helped me with my English.
It's called tit-for-tat.
- I...
- I can't forget your help.
Is it a little hot?
Well, I live closer to him.
It's convenient for me
to take care of him.
It's the end of the term.
You should focus on
working on your design homework.
I'm an athlete. I got hurt a lot.
I have more experience
in this area than you.
There is no porridge left.
Mr. Fang, I'll get you more.
I might as well have Big Mouth
and Ding stay.
I'm thirsty.
Can you get me a glass of water?
Would you like it cold or warm?
Here comes the water!
One cold and one warm.
Why are you staring at me?
Don't you want water?
Drink it.
Linlin, we should go now.
Let Mr. Fang have a good rest.
Oh.
I want to talk to you.
Linlin is also a patient.
She needs to rest now, too.
See you tonight.
(I'll jump rope with you at 11:00 PM.)
You have a lot of strength to use.
Don't you have training tomorrow?
It's still early.
Let's not worry about tomorrow.
I'll have fun with my teacher tonight.
Do you want popcorn?
No.
Have some water.
Are you worried that you'll
go to the bathroom at night?
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of you.
I can take care of myself.
Just go back to sleep.
I'm gonna stay here tonight.
I only have one bed,
and my couch is narrow.
You won't be comfortable living here.
It's okay.
I have a sleeping bag.
When did you prepare it?
I just sent Lin Ze a message on WeChat
and asked him to bring it to me.
I didn't want him
to interrupt our movie,
so I asked him to put it in the hallway.
You are well-prepared.
Still not good enough
compared with your 10,000 questions.
Fang Yuke.
What are you two doing?
(Little Theater of Unrequited love)
Mr. Fang.
You...
Why are you still up?
Where are you going alone late at night?
I'm going out for some air.
No, it's not safe to be alone at night,
and it's not convenient for you.
Don't hurt the other hand.
I'm okay.
Just go to sleep.
No.
I have to be with you tonight.
Mr. Fang.
What are you doing?
I heard some noise.
Do you need any help?
No.
It must be uncomfortable for you
to sleep with your clothes on.
Let me take your clothes off.
No, no.
Don't touch me!
I'll hurt you if you come closer.
I told you to feel free
to ask me for help.
Don't move, don't move. Your wound.
Come on. Right.
It's stuck.
I'll pull it out for you.
Fang Yuke.
♪When will a meteorite
streak across the sky♪
♪When I say the three words
Listen quietly♪
♪I speak as softly as if I whisper♪
♪But they're heard clearly♪
♪I've spent my life on them anyway♪
♪If moonlight can really
cause the tides♪
♪Can I respond to your love♪
♪How shall I tell you♪
♪That I miss you♪
♪Maybe I should stay right where I am♪
♪I'm waiting until the wind kisses you♪
♪Until you say yes♪
♪Until the next four reasons♪
♪Either the South Pole
or the North Pole♪
♪I will travel
all the way there for you♪
♪I'm waiting until the wind kisses you♪
♪Until you say yes♪
♪Until we meet again♪
♪The story never ends♪
♪And my story is all about you♪
♪If moonlight can really
cause the tides♪
♪Can I respond to your love♪
♪How shall I tell you♪
♪That I miss you♪
♪Maybe I should stay right where I am♪
♪I'm waiting until the wind kisses you♪
♪Until you say yes♪
♪Until the next four reasons♪
♪Either the South Pole
or the North Pole♪
♪I will travel
all the way there for you♪
♪I'm waiting until the wind kisses you♪
♪Until you say yes♪
♪Until we meet again♪
♪The story never ends♪
♪And my story is all about you♪