♪The blade dance
causing ripples to spread across the lake♪
♪Waving the banner amidst the storm and rain♪
♪The snow is not bothered
by the sadness and the happiness♪
♪Blazing through the desert
with the rein in hands♪
♪Young and inexperienced, it is apparent♪
♪Bold ambition
interspersed with recklessness♪
♪Mind not the predestination♪
♪Solving all the problems
that fate presents me♪
♪From all the trials and hardship♪
♪Spawn the vast courage♪
♪The journey to seek glory and justice♪
♪Is not in vain♪
♪One smile is all it takes
to get what you're thinking♪
♪A ballad to our journey♪
♪Pursuing the dream of our youth♪
♪We take everything as it comes♪
♪The distant land might be dangerous♪
♪But what's life without an adventure?♪
♪Youths are supposed to dream big and be sharp♪
♪Every struggle in life has taught us♪
♪That we shall do what we can wherever we go♪
♪Together, another journey awaits♪
[The Blood of Youth]
[Episode 22]
Xiao Chuhe?
Lord Yong'an?
Do you need to get so worked up about this?
Why can't I?
It's too late
to throw us off the ship now.
You're the Lord Yong'an
who'd rather get punished
for protecting Lord Langya
than change the decision
despite losing his title and status
and ending up wandering the martial arts world?
Good!
Great!
I've heard many things about you!
I admire you!
The world thinks
I am guilty.
Well,
that's only what they think.
Who is Lord Langya?
He would never commit treason!
There is no such reasoning in books.
And there shouldn't be
such nonsense
in this world.
I'm only upset
that I can't stand by your side
and fight for justice
with you.
You really are
the silly son of a wealthy family.
Mr. Mu,
if you encounter trouble on the island,
find the Golden Marquis Lanyue.
He will help you.
Golden Marquis Lanyue.
He is an admirable character too.
All right.
I'll remember that.
Come on.
Let's drink.
This liquor is called Qiulubai.
It's produced by the Diaolou Parlor
in the imperial capital, Tianqi.
They only bring out three jugs of this
to serve their guests
on the 15th
of every month.
Even for us, the Mu family of Qingzhou,
it took quite a bit of effort
to acquire this one jug.
You're a member of the imperial family, Xiao.
You must miss this liquor.
Mu Chunfeng,
let me give you a piece of advice.
You know Xiao Se's identity now.
It's not a big deal
if you want to get close to him
and form connections.
But you should ask him
whether he wants to be the Emperor first.
Be careful so that you don't misjudge
another person again.
Does it matter whether he wants
to be the Emperor or not?
I'm a merchant.
You can suspect my intentions,
but you can't doubt
my judge of character.
This is Hantanxiang.
It's a famous liquor of Luoxiang City in Nanjue.
Once the liquor is made,
it is stored underneath a deep cold pond
and taken out after one year.
It is chilly when you drink it,
and it has a faint peach blossom fragrance.
It's even better than Qiulubai.
Hantanxiang.
It is a rare liquor indeed.
You guys don't drink much, do you?
I do.
I love drinking!
What do you guys
usually drink?
Beauty of Four Seasons is on the milder side,
but it's the one I drink the most.
Different festivities
call for different liquors.
Sangluo, Xinfeng, and Tusu
are all fine liquor.
But the best
is the Seven Starry Nights.
I don't get many chances to drink it, however.
But sometimes, I get to savor it,
thanks to Third Master.
You get to drink Seven Starry Nights?
I often drink that liquor too.
What's the big deal?
I think
it's not as good as Beauty of Four Seasons.
It's too strong
and not sweet enough.
Did you forget
who my master is?
Come.
Let's drink Han…
Let's drink.
Xiao.
A toast to everyone.
The smell of the peach blossoms is so fragrant!
Good liquor.
It is great liquor indeed.
Tang,
I'm a liquor enthusiast as well.
Will you let me try
some of the Seven Starry Nights
when we go back to Beili?
It's a little embarrassing to say this,
but we snuck out and finished
the last pot
of that liquor last time.
My master is away on a trip.
We don't know
when he will return.
Never mind then.
Scholarly Sword Deity gave you
the Book of Liquor, didn't he?
Shouldn't that book include the method to make it?
The Book of Liquor?
May I have a look at it, Tang?
Are you interested in making liquor?
[The Book of Liquor]
So this is the book…
It really is this book…
Is it valuable?
It's priceless!
No.
I mustn't keep reading.
If I do,
I would be no better than a thief.
You're too harsh on yourself.
It's just a book about making liquor.
I'm not interested in it anyway.
But it was a gift from an elder,
so I can't let you have it.
If you like it,
you can keep it with you for a few days.
Fool…
Foolish!
Drink 30 cups of liquor in a row,
and your inner force and aura
will be greatly improved.
I've only heard
them say this,
so I don't know much about it,
but what I cherish
will not be as simple
as you think it is.
I…
I just remembered.
After drinking Principal City Lord's liquor,
my power and skill improved by leaps and bounds
the next morning.
Could that method of making the liquor
be written in this book too?
It's true that the liquor Master made
can boost one's cultivation.
Did he really learn how to make liquor
from this book?
Even if it isn't true,
you can make liquor for us
after studying
that book.
Don't drink too much.
It's good liquor,
but it's one of the strongest there is.
Great liquor!
Lei Wujie!
Where are you going?
I wish to travel north with the wind,
watching the snow sweeping across the land.
I wish to travel east with the ship,
seeing the elegant fairy brave the wind.
I wish to travel far with the clouds,
even the emperor ruling the court cannot stop me.
I will bathe in sunlight
on the top of Mount Kunlun.
I will witness lush mountains rise
at the edge of the ocean.
We shall reunite after a long journey.
But I won't go home unless I've seen the world.
"But I won't go home unless I've seen the world."
Great poem.
It is poetic and bold.
But I've never heard it before.
Who wrote this poem?
A peculiar man in this world
who also happens to be my friend.
One.
Two.
Three.
Lift that sword higher.
Position your fingers correctly.
Lunge.
-Go lower in your horse stance.
-Look.
With all of them gone,
Luo Mingxuan
has become
the eldest disciple here now.
Four.
He isn't the best cultivator himself.
He had better not misguide the others.
Keep going.
-We have a guest.
-Hold it.
Baixiao Sect?
One.
City Lord Sikong.
Elder Yin.
It is an honor to meet you.
What brings a disciple of the Baixiao Sect
to Xueyue City?
The storm has calmed.
Martial artists are ranked
on the Golden Ranking.
The Golden Ranking?
The Baixiao Sect hasn't released
the Golden Ranking in many years.
It seems that Baixiao Sect believes
the battle at the Lei Fortress
marks a new beginning for the martial arts world.
Spear Deity, please read the ranking.
Let me see it.
You read it.
Thank you, Third City Lord.
The first ranking of the Golden Ranking.
Weapon Mastery Ranking.
Spear Deity, Sikong Changfeng.
Weapon, Wuyue Spear.
Sword Deities. Lone Sword Deity, Luo Qingyang.
Weapon, Nine-Song Sword.
Scholarly Sword Deity, Xie Xuan.
Weapon, Ten Thousand Scrolls.
Wrathful Sword Deity, Yan Zhantian.
Weapon, Armies Breaking Sword.
Xueyue Sword Deity, Li Hanyi.
Weapons, Iron Glacier and Peach Blossom.
The Tao Sword Deity has fallen.
Only four Sword Deities remain.
What a pity.
Indeed.
Blade Deities.
Tyrant Blade, Tan Taipo.
Weapon, Kirin Moon.
Ghost Blade, Moon Snatcher.
Weapon, Yinyang.
Tender Blade, Su Yuluo.
Weapon, Chiluo.
Liquor Deity,
Baili Dongjun.
Weapon…
Fists and everything else.
Master,
I see my name!
Look!
I'm in eighth place on the second ranking,
the Jade Ranking.
Luo Mingxuan, a disciple of Xueyue City.
Master, I made it into the ranking!
You only barely made it.
What's there to be happy about?
Next year,
I'll get a higher ranking for sure!
Let's see who is in seventh place.
It's Qianluo!
Sikong Qianluo,
a disciple of Xueyue City.
In sixth place, Li Fansong,
a disciple of Mount Wangcheng.
In fifth place,
Lei Wujie, a disciple of the Sword Heart Tomb
of Xueyue City's Lei Fortress.
That's a long title.
In fourth place,
Tang Ze, a disciple of the Tang Clan.
In third place, Tang Lian,
a disciple of Xueyue City.
There is no second place.
No second place?
Second place?
There are two people in first place!
Two people in first place?
Jade Ranking.
First place.
Wushuang, a disciple of Wushuang City.
Ye Anshi, a disciple of Tianwaitian.
This…
Four of Xueyue City's disciples
made it on the list.
But none of them
was able to take first place.
The martial arts world is filled
with capable talents.
It's not a big deal even if we don't get first place.
There is one more ranking
that I will relay verbally.
What?
The Top-Rank List.
The Top-Rank List?
I've never heard of that.
Hasn't that been stopped
a long time ago?
It was stopped a long time ago.
Why are they bringing it up again?
Master, what does this mean?
The top.
As the name implies,
it means the top of the world.
Once the names are listed on that ranking,
the first place and second place will emerge.
The second place
will always go after the first place.
And the one in first place
will have to face challenges
from the entire world.
From what I know,
Ji Ruofeng sealed that list
over ten years ago.
And now, it has been brought back.
Is the competition for the most powerful
in the world
about to end here?
I'm just the messenger.
If Xueyue City does not wish to hear it,
I will take my leave.
No.
Tell us.
In fourth place on the Top-Rank List,
Yan Zhantian.
Tan Taipo.
Xie Xuan.
Li Tian.
In third place on the Top-Rank List,
Sikong Changfeng.
Moon Snatcher.
Tang Lianyue.
In second place on the Top-Rank List,
Luo Qingyang.
It looks like
Principal City Lord is in first place, after all.
And Baili Dongjun.
I still haven't heard my name
even until now.
Could it be that I am in first place?
The Head of Baixiao Sect says
that you have fallen
from your initial phase for some time now.
Now, you've returned to the Insouciant Phase.
On Mount Wangcheng,
your battle with Zhao Yuzhen
ended in a tie as well.
Although Zhao Yuzhen held back,
you will surely return
to the peak soon.
No need to fret.
This is all within expectations.
What surprised me
is the fact that there is someone else
that can rank above
Baili Dongjun
and Luo Qingyang.
That's right.
The first place should either be Luo Qingyang
or Baili Dongjun.
And you put them both in second place.
Then…
First place on the Top-Rank List.
There is someone in first place?
Really?
Is there someone even more powerful
than Principal City Lord?
Who?
In first place on the Top-Rank List,
Mo Yi.
Who is that?
-I don't know him.
-I've never heard of him.
Where did he come from?
Tell me.
Who is Mo Yi?
I've been the superintendent of the Lei Fortress
for 20 years.
I know the martial arts world
like the back of my hand.
Yet, I've never heard
of this name.
Mo Yi…
It has been so long since I last heard that name.
We've been traveling for so long.
We're finally close to our destination.
The Sanshe Island is up ahead.
Rest assured, Mr. Mu.
We will get you
what you need.
That won't be necessary.
His body can't hold on much longer.
You guys should get a move on.
We, the Mu family,
will handle the matter
on Sanshe Island ourselves.
All right.
Thank you.
Oh, right.
I have some poison with me.
It might be useful
when catching snakes.
Take this.
Thank you.
Mr. Mu,
you've already come this far.
Are you sure you won't follow us to the island
to see the immortal?
I'll pass.
Compared to immortals and divine beings,
my brother's happiness
is more important.
Xiao,
no one has ever seen the world
beyond Sanshe Island.
Will you be able to find what you seek?
Besides, how will you
navigate your way
in the vast sea?
What's your suggestion, Mr. Mu?
To prevent any accidents,
we've recruited
an astrologer
before embarking on this trip.
I studied astrology too.
I can find my own way.
What good
will your limited skills be?
-Miss Ye!
-Ye!
Miss Ye,
didn't you return to Tianqi
with the general?
I didn't really want to go back,
so I slipped out when I found a chance.
Then, you're here…
To help him, of course.
I don't know what my father thinks.
All I want is to help him return to Tianqi.
Because I helped you when we were younger?
No.
Because we're friends.
That's right!
We're friends!
Friends will travel thousands of miles
to help one another.
Well, I bet you're happy.
I haven't seen you in a while.
It has been a while.
Um…
You look even more beautiful now.
Miss Ye, you may be young,
but you're far more capable
than the masters
who've studied astrology for decades.
I was wondering
why you would answer
my recruitment.
So you came
for Xiao.
Perfect.
We have a map
of Sanshe Island.
Miss Ye,
you should go to the island
with Xiao.
Thank you.
Xiao,
when should I come and retrieve you?
How much time do I have left?
Five days.
Make it seven days then.
Come and get me in seven days.
All right.
I will come and pick all of you up
in seven days.
Please stay safe,
everyone.
Thank you, Mr. Mu.
Thank you.
I will.
Is this the undercurrent
Principal City Lord mentioned on the map?
Yes, the undercurrent is up ahead.
Be careful, Lei Wujie!
Hold on to the oars!
Hold on tight, everyone!
Hold on to me!
♪The silent temple, we still have
a long way to go in the martial arts world♪
♪The falling snow,
only clouds know the warmth of the cold moon♪
♪The wind is rustling, no man is born
without ambitious worldly desires♪
♪Let's talk about fate,
act with our heart and speak from our heart♪
♪Travel far,
and overcome challenges life throws at me♪
♪I do not waste my youth away♪
♪Like blade and sword, relying on each other,
we are devoted friends♪
♪How strong our bond is, no dream is small♪
♪Despite the conflicts and the feuds,
we sing proudly♪
♪Youths ought to be fearless♪
As expected of the celestial mountain.
♪Visiting all corners of the world,
with our youthful spirits♪
♪Traveling freely with friends,
it won't be lonely if I have my confidants♪
I'm exhausted!
I'm in no mood
to appreciate the scenery.
I just want
to find a place
to sleep.
It's a pity
there isn't an immortal
in this beautiful scenery.
There's a deity on the island.
He can ride clouds,
harness wind,
co-exist with Heaven and Earth,
and live as long as the sun and the moon.
He must be what they were talking about.
Guests have arrived.
[Mo Yi]
A pleasure to meet you.
Immortal,
we apologize
for intruding.
Few have been able
to reach this place
over the years.
Since you're here,
it must be fate.
There is no intrusion to speak of.
He seems like
an approachable guy.
Let's go!
I sense a familiar aura
on that immortal.
Have you met him before?
Yes and no.
I can't be sure.
Where did you guys come from?
From Beili.
Beili?
I haven't heard that name
for a while.
Do you know Beili, Immortal?
Not only do I know the name,
but it's also my birthplace.
I spent a long time there
in the past.
It seems
that you have traveled far.
You must be tired.
Since you're here,
there is no need to hold back.
Thank you, Immortal.
Immortal,
instead of pointing at me with your finger,
can you please touch my head?
Why?
It is written in the books
that if an immortal touches your head,
you will be granted longevity.
I wish to have a long life.
Someone once asked me
to do that.
And?
I shattered the cliff he was cultivating on
in one hit.
Um…
You can just point at me then.
Just pointing between my eyes will do.
So you two are the ones who seek my aid.
Why do you think it is us?
The three of them
may be physically and mentally exhausted,
but their auras remain strong.
They'll recover after a night's sleep.
But the two of you are different.
The aura of one of you is in a state of disarray.
You're on the verge of death.
The other was born with a defect.
You should already be dead.
As expected of an immortal.
He doesn't even need to check their pulse.
One look,
and he already knows what's wrong with them.
You are correct, sir.
You carry
a familiar presence.
Have we met before,
Immortal?
No need to call me that.
My name is Mo Yi.
Mo Yi…
Sir,
are you an immortal or…
I am already 64 years old.
You look like
you're only Lian's age!
You really are an immortal!
My master once told me
that the celestialhood
is something entirely different.
In my current state,
I can only be considered an Earth Deity.
Earth Deity?
An earth deity
can only change matters of the earth
but not of heaven.
Sir,
is our case
a matter of the earth?
Of course.
I can heal both of them
and they can be cured.
That's great!
However,
I have a condition.
Deities have conditions too?
Of course.
I will help you with your problem on earth,
and you must help me change heaven's will.
What do you wish to change?
I want to bring someone who's gone
back to this realm.
How can we help you?
You only have three days at most.
Tomorrow,
I will ask one thing from you.
If you can give me that item,
I will cure you.
What is it?
You'll know when the time comes.
Mr. Mo Yi,
have you ever met my master,
Baili Dongjun?
He left the city a year ago
for the immortal realm across the seas
in search of a brew.
Did you ever
come across him?
I met him once many years ago.
He is an interesting man.
He makes fine liquor.
I haven't seen him
since we parted ways.
Perhaps
he deceived you.
(Three days from now,)
(I will give you a new body.)
(You will give me what I seek.)
He is no deity.
What kind of deity makes demands and deals?
You burn incense
when you pray at the temples.
Moreover,
we're the ones who seek his help.
It's only natural that we have to pay the price.
But I am curious.
What do we have
that he would need?
I have an inkling.
Instead of the immortal realm,
it's closer to another legendary phase
we speak of in the martial arts world.
The Unbeatable Phase.
Yes.
You sit and concentrate in silence,
but your mind and soul wander
a thousand lis away.
It is the highest phase
that reigns above the Insouciant Phase.
Even my master was never able
to reach this phase.
Mr. Mo Yi's footwork that allows him
to move as swiftly and fleetingly as the wind
resembles more of one that has reached
the Unbeatable Phase.
It doesn't matter if he is a deity
or if he has reached the Unbeatable Phase.
I think something's strange
about him.
I have cultivated for a long time
under Supervisor Qi.
He has an aura that is similar
to that of the State Preceptor.
They might have cultivated
under the same master.
What's more,
the aura he carried
was stronger than the State Preceptor.
But when he spoke of his wish,
the look in his eyes changed.
How did it change?
From that of a deity to a demon.
It sends a shiver down one's spine.
Mr. Mo Yi
is different from what we imagined.
What should we do then?
Xiao Se only has three days left
to live.
Let's wait and see what happens first.
See if we can find
any clues
within these three days.
Maybe we're overthinking it.
You guys stay here.
I'll look for my master.
Lian,
you…
Don't worry.
I know my master.
He will do it
as long as he promised.
I have faith
that he is in this celestial mountain.
I think Baili Dongjun
was here too.
[Young Mo Yi,
selling oneself for the burial of family]
Master.
[Young Qi Tianchen]
Can we help him?
[Taoist Qingfeng]
Are you a deity?
No.
I'm just an ordinary person.
Will you buy me, sir?
I can help you bury your sister,
but I won't buy you.
You only need to become my disciple
and cultivate with me.
Cultivate?
As in, become a deity?
If I become one,
can I bring my sister back to life?
I can't do that.
Neither have I ever met anyone capable of it.
But you'll be much more powerful than me
in the future.
I'm not as powerful as you are.
It's not for me to say if you can do it or not.
All right. I'll do as you say.
What's your name?
My name's Mo Yi.
Mo Yi.
Ruoyi,
yesterday, you said Mo Yi and Qi Tianchen
carried a similar aura.
Could he be
from the Directorate of Astronomy too?
Before joining the Directorate of Astronomy,
the State Preceptor once studied
under Taoist Qingfeng
of Mount Huanglong.
He once told me
that in his later years,
Taoist Qingfeng took in a young disciple.
That disciple had incredible talent.
Within three years,
his cultivation and attainments
have reached the top two in the ranking,
second only to the State Preceptor.
But at that time, the State Preceptor
had already been cultivating for 16 years.
Yet, it only took
that disciple three years to catch up.
Three years.
If he had stayed in Beili,
he would've been sure
to take the highest rank someday.
Yet, he insisted on going out to sea
to seek the path of immortality.
He wants to get away from the mortal world
and become a true immortal.
Taoist Qingfeng couldn't change his mind
and set out with him.
But he has never returned since.
So you suspect
that disciple is Mo Yi.
If it is him…
Then what he said
about changing the mandate of heaven
would mean reviving his little sister.
She has already been deceased for so many years.
Even her remains
would be long gone now.
How can she be revived?
Mortality is heaven's will.
Going against that would mean
going against heaven's will.
But we must cure you.
There is no turning back.
Listen closely to what I'm about to tell you next.
This is our only chance.
Is anyone in?
Can you spare me a steamed bun?
I'll repay you when I grow up.
Is anyone inside?
Is anyone there?
Can you give me some congee?
My little sister is starving!
I can work for you! I don't need any money!
Is anyone in?
Anyone?
Is anyone inside?
If my father
hadn't saved you back then,
all of you would be dead!
I can't believe you guys would leave us to die!
Yi,
you're back.
Lyu'er,
I'm useless.
I didn't manage to find any food.
Look what this is, Yi!
Flatbread?
Where did you get this from?
A kind abbot
passed by earlier.
He gave me two pieces of flatbread.
I've already eaten one.
I saved this one for you.
You've already eaten?
Lyu'er?
Lyu'er!
Wake up!
(Lyu'er, Lyu'er!)
My dear Lyu'er,
I have faith
that we will be reunited soon.
Mr. Mo Yi.
Even though
you're just an insignificant character,
you are a nuisance.
Why did you do that, Mr. Mo Yi?
An immortal is unaffected by emotions.
So these are your true colors.
You're clever
and capable.
Unfortunately,
this time,
you must die.
Master…
Is it you, Master?
Master, are you here?
Has he awoken?
Impossible.
Are you here?
So he isn't awake.
He is familiar
with your aura,
and he protected you instinctively.
So be it.
He will never wake up
after drinking the Oblivion Broth.
I'll seal him and his disciple
in this cave forever.
Could my master be in here?
Master!
Master?
Master, wake up.
It's me, Tang Lian.
Master.
Master!
What did he drink
that put him in such a deep sleep?
Oblivion Broth.
(Third place on the Top-Rank List.)
(Baili Dongjun of Xueyue City.)
Master!
I've made a name for myself in the world!
I don't understand.
Why are you so determined
to make yourself renowned in this world?
When I was young,
I met a girl.
It was love at first sight.
She told me…
When you become
someone famous,
I'll know where you are
and come to find you.
The time I become famous
is the time we will be reunited.
I think she's here.
(Who are you?)
(Are you asking for my name?)
(I am Baili Dongjun.)
(Dongjun.)
(That's a nice name.)
♪All the hustle and bustle,
gone with the flowing water♪
♪We knew no sorrow when we were young♪
I forgot to ask you the most important thing
back then.
What is your name?
[Yueyao]
I'm Yueyao.
♪In the desolate setting sun♪
Yueyao…
Master.
Master!
♪All is gone, autumn is here♪
How could it be you?
Why are you dressed
like Yueqing?
Why did you endure
my attack?
Let her go.
Take it as I died for her.
I will bear
all of her sins.
No.
Come with me.
I'll take you to Changfeng.
He can heal you.
It's too late.
I'm dead.
Dead?
Our meeting.
Our reunion.
Don't you think
all of this feels familiar?
It's because we're in a dream.
♪Yearnings turn into poems and liquor♪
♪We can no longer return to the past♪
You knew all along.
When you drink the Oblivion Broth,
you remember those that you've forgotten,
and the ones you've lost will return.
Everything will change.
Will you wake up,
or will you stay
in this dream?
I want to live in a world
where you exist forever.
I've waited so long
for this day.
You silly man.
I'm dead.
♪The silent temple♪
♪We still have a long way to go
in the martial arts world♪
♪The falling snow♪
♪Only clouds know the warmth of the cold moon♪
♪The roaring fate♪
♪At last, we see the light at the end of the tunnel♪
♪Everything is just a flash in the pan♪
♪Waiting for the ride to the highest heaven♪
♪The ethereal fog♪
♪Fame and fortune do not matter
to an enlightened person♪
♪I face the sun♪
♪To have a pristine soul in this polluted world♪
♪Travel far♪
♪And overcome challenges life throws at me♪
♪I do not waste my youth away♪
♪Like blade and sword, relying on each other♪
♪We are devoted friends♪
♪How strong our bond is♪
♪No dream is small♪
♪Despite the conflicts and the feuds♪
♪We sing proudly♪
♪Youths ought to be fearless♪
♪Visiting all corners of the world♪
♪With our youthful spirits♪
♪Traveling freely with friends♪
♪It won't be lonely if I have my confidants♪
♪Travel far♪
♪And overcome challenges life throws at me♪
♪I do not waste my youth away♪
♪Like blade and sword, relying on each other♪
♪We are devoted friends♪
♪How strong our bond is♪
♪No dream is small♪
♪Despite the conflicts and the feuds♪
♪We sing proudly♪
♪Youths ought to be fearless♪
♪Visiting all corners of the world♪
♪With our youthful spirits♪
♪Traveling freely with friends♪
♪It won't be lonely if I have my confidants♪