♪The blade dance
causing ripples to spread across the lake♪
♪Waving the banner amidst the storm and rain♪
♪The snow is not bothered
by the sadness and the happiness♪
♪Blazing through the desert
with the rein in hands♪
♪Young and inexperienced, it is apparent♪
♪Bold ambition
interspersed with recklessness♪
♪Mind not the predestination♪
♪Solving all the problems
that fate presents me♪
♪From all the trials and hardship♪
♪Spawn the vast courage♪
♪The journey to seek glory and justice♪
♪Is not in vain♪
♪One smile is all it takes
to get what you're thinking♪
♪A ballad to our journey♪
♪Pursuing the dream of our youth♪
♪We take everything as it comes♪
♪The distant land might be dangerous♪
♪But what's life without an adventure?♪
♪Youths are supposed to dream big and be sharp♪
♪Every struggle in life has taught us♪
♪That we shall do what we can wherever we go♪
♪Together, another journey awaits♪
[The Blood of Youth]
[Episode 7]
Everyone, let's attack
and bring that lad back with us!
Lu Yuzhai.
I can't defy my master's order.
Tang Lian,
I suggest you get out of the way.
Together, at once!
Who are you?
Father?
Third Master.
Who's that man?
Lei Wujie,
you'd better remember this man.
(Shen Jingzhou of Blizzard Sword)
(and Wang Rensun of Shattering Blade)
(whom you've met)
may be first-rate experts.
But they are just some of the first-rate experts.
And this man
is the current top spear user of this age.
[Sikong Changfeng, Xueyue City]
The Spear Deity, Sikong Changfeng.
The Spear Deity, Sikong Changfeng?
The Third City Lord of Xueyue City?
You'd better don't start drooling.
Stop looking at him like that.
You'll embarrass us all.
Just now you asked who I am.
If you don't recognize me,
do you recognize my spear?
Greetings, Spear Deity.
Wushuang City
has sent so many elites this time.
Is this hostage
that important?
Go back to Wushuang City
and tell those old fogeys.
If they really think
they can overturn the martial arts world
by capturing a kid,
then
not only should they forget
about being at the top of the world,
I think the name of Wushuang City
can be removed as well.
One more thing,
Wushuang City
finally has great talent.
They'd better don't waste it.
Please convey my message
to Song Yanhui.
I'll definitely
convey your message to him
if I don't forget
at the time.
You held back just now.
Or else,
they'd be seriously injured
if they weren't killed.
Thank you for holding back.
It's nothing.
I hope we have a chance to fight again
after you recover.
Sure.
My swordsmanship
may be inferior to my second martial brother.
But I've practiced it for several years.
This is...
How is this possible?
The Spear Deity
is worthy of his name.
Indeed, only those who've become a sword deity
can completely control
the 13 swords of Wushuang Sword Box.
Xiao Se,
this sword is...
The second of the world's top ten famous swords,
the Vermilion.
The Vermilion.
Sikong Changfeng.
Hey, come back.
Using swords
and using spears
share the same principles.
I only used my inner force
to control Wushuang Sword Box by force.
If you want to understand
the rest of the principles,
you still have to rely on yourself.
Thank you for your guidance, Spear Deity.
You can leave now.
Yuzhai, come on.
Third Master.
Tang Lian,
you've done well.
Father.
Qianluo,
you've gone too...
Father,
can you come down first before you talk?
It's tiring to talk with our heads up.
Father!
Father,
don't be mad.
I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
Again?
Do you know
I turned Xueyue City
upside down
just to look for you?
Father,
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
Third Master,
Qianluo was indeed a troublemaker this time.
She must be severely punished.
Lian,
I helped you so many times
throughout the journey.
How could you say that?
She's right.
Qianluo did it out of kindness.
You call that helping me?
You've been holding me back all the way.
Did you even help?
Hold you back?
Qianluo,
it's your fault, then.
Why do you keep causing trouble
for Lian?
If it weren't for me,
he would have been in trouble
in Belle's Manor.
I heard
you helped him
break a formation
called...
Guxu Formation.
Ah, it's Guxu Formation.
Am I right?
Even if you don't intervene,
a mere Guxu Formation
can't stop me.
Lian is also right about that.
Lian's martial arts skills
are the best
among the younger generation
in Xueyue City.
I think
you're upset
because I interrupted
your alone time with Fairy Rui.
You...
All right, that's enough.
Everyone, calm down.
Fairy Rui?
Who's Fairy Rui?
She's a girl
with a beautiful face.
That's what happened.
-Father.
-Luo'er.
I never thought
the world's famous Spear Deity
would be like this in private.
It is unexpected indeed.
He's so charming.
I don't think
it'll be hard for them
to talk all night.
Next time,
you must not behave this mischievously anymore.
Do you hear me?
-Well...
-Yes, I heard you.
Mister Spear Deity,
I'm Lei Wujie from Lei Fortress
of Jiangnan Thunderbolt Sect.
I'm on my way to Xueyue City
to train under a master.
Young man,
you're a fine-looking man with talents.
Stop embarrassing yourself.
He said I'm full of vigor.
I'm Wuchan,
and this is my martial brother, Wuxin.
You had a rough day.
I was supposed to reach here earlier.
But I ran into an old friend
on my way here.
So we had a talk,
which delayed me.
No ordinary person could disintegrate
their own martial arts skills.
It was no wonder Wangyou thought highly of you.
Are you also here to take me away?
No.
I am here especially
to send Ye Anshi back to the sect.
I want to go back to Hanshui Temple.
I am here especially
to send Ye Anshi back to the sect.
White-Haired Deity?
White-Haired Deity.
The old friend I mentioned
is him.
Mr. Mo.
Not only did you run away without a word
after seeing me,
but you also struck me pretty hard.
Are you going to deny me?
Mr. Mo, you're an expert in martial arts skills.
How could I even injure you?
I'll take him with me, then.
Will Xueyue City not regret it?
I'll say it again.
Xueyue City doesn't fear the Demon Sect
or Tianwaitian,
let alone
a young man.
Let's go.
Wait.
Kid,
what do you want?
Why didn't you ask
if he's willing to go with you?
He's the Young Head
of the Tianwaitian Sect.
If he doesn't return to Tianwaitian,
don't tell me he should return to Hanshui Temple.
What if he wants
to return to Hanshui Temple?
Kid,
are you tired of living?
Do you think I will not kill you
because I fear Lei Hong
who's hiding in the Lei Fortress?
Wuxin,
do you really want to go?
I...
The twelve-year term has expired.
You should leave.
Why are you hesitating?
The armistice
is for a twelve-year term.
During that time, he was a hostage.
Now, the twelve-year term has expired.
The world is vast.
He can go anywhere he wants.
That's right.
Wuxin,
just say it.
At worst we can fight again.
You're seeking a master in Xueyue City.
How can you fight Spear Deity?
A sect is a sect.
Justice is justice.
Brotherhood is brotherhood.
Xiao Se, am I right?
He's right.
Young Head.
Mr. Mo.
Mr. Mo,
what are you doing?
Young Head,
it has been 12 years
since Tianwaitian waited for your return.
Today, the other 16 sects outside the region
have fallen apart.
Tianwaitian is the only one
with its members staying.
All of us are waiting for you
to return
and take charge of the situation.
♪The silent temple♪
♪We still have a long way to go
in the martial arts world♪
♪The falling snow♪
♪Only clouds know the warmth of the cold moon♪
♪The wind is rustling♪
♪No man is born
without ambitious worldly desires♪
♪Let's talk about fate♪
♪Act with our heart and speak from our heart♪
♪Travel far♪
♪And overcome challenges life throws at me♪
♪I do not waste my youth away♪
♪Like blade and sword, relying on each other♪
♪We are devoted friends♪
♪How strong our bond is♪
♪No dream is small♪
♪Despite the conflicts and the feuds♪
Mr. Mo.
I understand.
Let's go.
♪Visiting all corners of the world♪
♪With our youthful spirits♪
♪Traveling freely with friends♪
♪It won't be lonely if I have my confidants♪
Congratulations, Ye Anshi,
the Head of the Tianwaitian Sect
for his return.
Spear Deity, you don't have to force me.
I know.
Actually,
Old Wangyou is gone.
It doesn't matter
if I return to Hanshui Temple or not.
But Old Wangyou was right.
My home
is a place beyond the border,
beyond the sky.
You can return to Hanshui Temple,
but not now.
♪Traveling freely with friends♪
♪It won't be lonely if I have my confidants♪
Wuchan,
I'm leaving now.
Wuxin,
it doesn't matter
if you're the Head of Tianwaitian,
Hanshui Temple
will always be your home.
Do you still remember
the fist technique I taught you?
It may look ordinary.
But after countless practices,
even dripping water can wear away a stone
and sand can build a pagoda.
I hope you'll
never
get to use what I've taught you.
I had already forgotten about it.
It's best if you do.
Wuxin,
I can find a solution
if you don't want to go.
I know you're full of ideas.
People say
life is ruthless.
But who
can be really ruthless?
I can't avoid the inevitable.
I'll go
to settle an old score.
What happens after that?
After that...
I'll return to the martial arts world
and continue the journey
with you.
What do we do with the coffin
at the foot of the mountain?
Just bury it.
(I wish to travel north with the wind,)
(watching the snow sweeping across the land.)
(I wish to travel east with the ship,)
(seeing the elegant fairy brave the wind.)
(I wish to travel far with the clouds,)
(even the emperor ruling the court cannot stop me.)
(I will bathe in sunlight
on the top of Mount Kunlun.)
(I will witness lush mountains rise
at the edge of the ocean.)
(We shall reunite after a long journey.)
(But I won't go home unless I've seen the world.)
After struggling for half a night,
[Qi Tianchen, State Preceptor]
I finally got a good move.
You've been making advances
without leaving me a leeway.
I
have to put a lot of energy into it,
so I don't lose
so miserably.
The one struggling half a night
[Xiao Ruojin, Emperor Mingde]
should be me, right?
I dare not.
I haven't played weiqi with you for a long time.
But your move
is completely different
from before.
Your Majesty is wise.
Lately,
I did come to a realization.
What is it?
This world
is ever-changing.
Only the balance of Yin and Yang is not broken.
The Yin and Yang
are both in the vast world
and also
in this weiqi.
Be it attack or defense,
pursue or let it off,
there are countless moves
with losing and winning as the two outcomes.
For weiqi players,
it's nothing more
than a feeling of gaining and losing.
Since when did you learn
to insinuate?
I dare not.
Since you brought it up,
you can finish it.
About the hostage,
what do you think
I've gained
and lost?
If I may be bold to answer,
Your Majesty lost a hostage
in exchange for national stability.
It's the morality and justice of the human heart.
It seems you also think
that this outcome
is the best result.
I do think so.
There's one more thing.
One thing?
No,
I mean one person.
I heard
he also got involved
in this matter.
Where are we going now?
Of course to Xueyue City.
Are you sure this is the correct way?
Don't worry.
Tang
has gone to carry out his task.
Before he left,
I asked him to draw me a map.
See? This is the one.
We won't get lost this time.
I hope so.
[Xueyue City]
(Ladies and gentlemen,)
(the breeze from Southern Pass,)
(the flowers in Northern Pass,)
(the snow on Mount Cang,)
(and the moon's reflection on Erhai Lake)
(describe)
(the four wonders of the romantic Xueyue City.)
(The so-called Beauty of Four Seasons.)
Martial Uncle!
[Feixuan, Mount Wangcheng]
(I'm sure you don't know this.)
Martial Uncle!
He disappeared
only after a while.
When martial artists from the martial world
want to join Xueyue City,
they must first challenge the Dengtian Tower!
Dengtian Tower?
Excuse me, please make way.
Back then,
Xu Wei, an old beggar with a stick
from the martial arts world
managed to climb up
to the tenth floor of the tower in one go.
[Li Fansong, Mount Wangcheng]
Ten floors?
After that, he came down
to ask for a bowl of liquor.
After drinking,
he continued climbing Dengtian Tower
with his dilapidated stick
and climbed up another five floors in one go!
Incredible!
That's more like it.
Martial Uncle,
what are you doing here?
Feixuan.
Let's go.
Feixuan, stop pushing me.
Let me stay a little longer.
-Just a little longer.
-Just go!
Just a little while.
A little longer.
Nice!
Why are you dilly-dallying?
Do you still want to challenge the tower?
I was starting to get excited about the story.
He was just talking
about an old beggar challenging the tower
who climbed 15 floors in one go.
Finally, Spear Deity
created a storm
that changed into a spear
to defeat him.
We've already heard that story.
You're right.
But what we heard
in Mount Wangcheng
was hearsay.
Now,
what we heard at Dengtian Tower
in Xueyue City
is what we call a story.
Do you even know?
How pretentious.
I'll tell the Great Master
that you came to Xueyue City
to challenge the trials of Dengtian Tower.
Xiao Se,
I'm going to challenge Dengtian Tower now.
Instead of encouraging me,
you chose to pull such a long face.
What is on your mind?
Look who's talking.
We got lost three times
on the way to Xueyue City.
We've wasted a month
just for that 500 silver taels.
How about you pay back a total of 800 silver taels
including interest?
I'll go to challenge Dengtian Tower now.
Wish me luck.
Dengtian Tower!
Here I come!
Martial Uncle,
it looks like that person in red
is going to challenge the Dengtian Tower too.
It's your fault for sleeping in.
See? He gets to go first now.
Calm down.
Maybe he'll be defeated
very soon.
Martial Uncle,
didn't you learn
Great Master's Qi-Observing Arts?
Can you see how many floors
this young man can climb?
This young man
[Dengtian Tower]
can reach the level...
Feixuan,
it looks like I indeed
was late today.
(Mount Wangcheng's disciple?)
Someone is challenging the Dengtian Tower!
Let's go and take a look!
[First Among Equals]
He's on the first floor now.
♪The blade dance
causing ripples to spread across the lake♪
[Second to None]
♪Waving the banner amidst the storm and rain♪
♪The snow is not bothered
by the sadness and the happiness♪
♪Blazing through the desert
with the rein in hands♪
[Third Time Is a Charm]
♪Young and inexperienced, it is apparent♪
♪Bold ambition
interspersed with recklessness♪
[Peace in Four Seasons]
It's the fourth floor now!
He's amazing.
♪Mind not the predestination♪
♪Solving all the problems
that fate presents me♪
♪From all the trials and hardship♪
[Five Blessings]
♪Spawn the vast courage♪
♪The journey to seek glory and justice♪
[Hit On All Sixes]
♪Is not in vain♪
♪One smile is all it takes
to get what you're thinking♪
[In Seventh Heaven]
♪A ballad to our journey♪
♪Pursuing the dream of our youth♪
[Eight Ways to Sunday]
♪We take everything as it comes♪
[Be on Cloud Nine]
Not bad.
The eighth floor.
♪The distant land might be dangerous♪
♪But what's life without an adventure?♪
♪Youths are supposed to dream big and be sharp♪
[Perfect Ten]
He's on the tenth floor now!
♪Every struggle in life has taught us♪
♪That we shall do what we can wherever we go♪
♪Together, another journey awaits♪
♪Youths are supposed to dream big and be sharp♪
♪Every struggle in life has taught us♪
♪That we shall do what we can wherever we go♪
♪Together, another journey awaits♪
[Give a Hundred Percent]
It's the 13th floor!
Who is that man?
Lei Wujie of the Lei family
of Jiangnan Thunderbolt Sect
has come!
What are you doing?
Are you all right?
[Luo Mingxuan, Xueyue City]
You think?
How do you plan on compensating me?
Compensate you?
Do you know what that is?
No.
Two deities were playing weiqi leisurely
in Mount Tai.
It's said to be an endgame.
In the endgame,
it's hiding an exceptional martial arts skill.
If one person can comprehend the moves,
it's better than 20 years of hard training.
I was about to figure it out
when you entered.
So how are you going to compensate me?
Don't tell me
it's another 500 silver taels.
A good man!
I'll mark it down.
Three hundred silver taels would be enough.
Three...
Then, can I pay you
after I pass the trials?
Of course.
Great!
Pardon me for doing this, then.
What do you want to bet?
Liubo, Pai Gow,
Xuanhe, or Madiao.
I'm asking which you want to play.
Pick one.
I don't know any of these.
Not a single one?
Why did you come up here if you don't know?
I...
I only know one.
The big and small game.
Fine. Big and small, it is.
How boring.
Come here.
Can't we compete in martial arts?
No.
One round to determine the winner.
Take a guess.
Big.
Three, three, one.
It's small.
You lost.
It's my first time playing.
So this round doesn't count.
I dare you to have another round with me.
Sure.
I'll play another round with you.
If you win one round,
I'll consider it a win.
Let's begin.
Wait!
I'll go down the tower to have a bowl of soy milk.
I'll play the last round with you
when I come back.
Sure. Go ahead.
Don't forget to bring
-the silver taels you owe me!
-All right!
What an interesting lad.
(You're the least advantaged one.)
We need to fight
for certain things.
If I don't try it,
how will I know the outcome?
If you fail,
(you'll die.)
Xiao Se.
You lost on the 13th floor.
You're weaker than I thought.
I haven't lost yet.
That chap on the 13th floor
doesn't compete in martial arts with me.
He's playing dice with me.
You're a better gambler than me.
Can you teach me?
I can teach you.
But you need to pay more.
How much?
Another 300 silver taels.
So it's a total of 800 silver taels.
What...
Fine.
The person you met should be
Yin Luoxia's disciple.
Yin Luoxia?
It's Fairy Luoxia
who split the Canglan River with one palm strike.
She has been on the list of beautiful women
in the martial arts world for ten years!
Do you still want to learn from me?
Yes, of course.
Yin Luoxia loves gambling.
She once lost three consecutive bets
with Sikong Changfeng, the Spear Deity.
So she was forced to join Xueyue City
as its elder.
It's said
after she joined Xueyue City,
she only accepted one disciple
who loves gambling like her.
So tell me.
What method did he use to gamble with you?
I can only take a guess at first.
He just took a glimpse through the opening
and said I lost.
There's a hidden box under the treasure chest.
He looked at the dice in advance.
If your guess was right,
he'd only need to flick gently
to move the dice.
You'll lose no matter what.
So that's what happened.
I'm heading back now.
Come back here!
Gambling
is nothing but a small trick.
Challenging the Dengtian Tower
isn't a trifling matter.
If you want to win,
you still need to do what you're good at.
What am I good at?
Beat him.
I get it now.
He's out.
Excuse me! Make way!
He only took a short break.
Not necessarily.
There are 15 floors.
Martial Uncle,
that man in red keeps running around.
It looks like he's only taking a break
not because he was defeated.
If this goes on,
he'll steal away
today's limelight!
Calm down.
When he reaches the 16th floor,
I'll kick him down from the floor.
It also saves us the energy
of going up the floor one by one.
Since we're all waiting
for him to come down,
how about I invite you two
to have some tea?
Observe qi with the Purple Star,
seek dragons with all-seeing eyes.
What did you see?
Who are you?
How did you know my martial uncle?
Feixuan, calm down.
This mister doesn't know martial arts.
There are three phases of Qi-Observing Arts.
You only practiced the first phase.
Are you saying I misread your skills
and that you're actually an expert?
No.
You didn't misread me.
It's true I don't know martial arts.
I only want to invite you
to have some tea.
Just
for tea?
Since I run into
the disciples of Mount Wangcheng,
I'd naturally want to ask you to do a reading.
You can stop hiding your identities.
There's an organization in Xueyue City
called Cobweb
that specializes in collecting intelligence.
From the moment we entered
the southern part of this city,
we were already being watched.
You seem to know a lot of things.
I just don't know my fate.
So I want to have it read.
Please come this way.
Feixuan,
didn't you always say
you may have mastered the Divination Arts,
but you don't have someone talented
to practice on?
He can be your practice subject.
Go and perform a divination for him.
Talented subject?
Just go. You don't have anything to lose.
Come on.
You're back.
How was the soy milk?
After I reach the top of the tower,
I'll buy you a bowl.
Are you that confident?
My friend told me
gambling
is actually relying on little tricks.
So...
So I'm going to bet on big.
We'll open if you're sure.
If I want to win,
I still need to use real skills.
Move your hand away!
Six!
One!
Let go!
No, you let go!
-I said, let go.
-No, you let go.
If you don't let go, I'm going to bite you.
One, one, six. So it's eight points.
No, it's 13 points!
It's big!
Not bad.
Your martial arts skills
are a lot better than your gambling skills.
I don't feel flattered
at all.
What's your name?
Lei Wujie of Jiangnan Thunderbolt Sect.
Didn't I tell you that
when I came up earlier?
I'm Luo Mingxuan.
I know.
You're Fairy Luoxia's disciple.
I've long admired
Fairy Luoxia.
What...? You've long
admired her?
What's wrong?
She's already over 30.
They said she split a river in half.
But the one she split
isn't the Yangtze River or Yellow River.
Why would you admire her?
Listen.
She's actually an old woman.
Mingxuan,
come to Xizhao Chamber.
I'd better get going to the upper floor.
I'll see you around.
What an interesting chap.
I was only away from the city for half a day.
Someone has already reached the 13th floor.
What a bunch of trash!
Mister, we can begin now.
Wait.
What now?
The person who's challenging the tower
owes me 800 silver taels.
So I must do something
for him as a support.
Xiao Se?
Miss Sikong,
it's been a while.
What took you so long to arrive here?
You were supposed
to arrive at Xueyue City one month ago.
I don't want to answer this question.
Martial Uncle,
he passed the 13th floor.
[Thirteen Ingots]
He's heading to the 14th floor now.
Where's Lei Wujie?
Don't tell me
he's the one challenging the tower.
Miss Sikong, you're right.
We didn't have the time to spar
because we bade farewell in a hurry.
This is just nice.
What are you doing?
I can't let you go.
Are you trying
to stop me for Lei Wujie?
Martial Uncle,
didn't you say
he doesn't know martial arts skills?
That's not a martial arts skill.
It's one of the qinggong skills.
One can use it without using inner force.
Which qinggong?
The world's best qinggong,
Walking on Clouds.
Why is there no one here?
Eldest Martial Brother!
It's been a long time, Eldest Martial Brother.
Didn't I tell you not to address me that way
before you are officially accepted?
I can ignore the rest.
But I must address you that way.
After all,
we've gone through thick and thin together.
You're the Lei Clan's disciple.
If you want to join us,
you only need to bring a visiting card to see me.
Why do you insist on challenging
the Dengtian Tower?
I came to Xueyue City
to meet a person.
If I want to see her,
I must challenge the Dengtian Tower.
If I have to fight you,
I hope you don't blame me.
Not bad.
Your martial arts skills
have improved a lot.
I practice every day
and never slack off even for a moment.
Eldest Martial Brother,
again!
I didn't expect your Fire Infusion
to be this powerful.
It broke
my Bladelike Thread Formation in a flash.
Bladelike thread?
It looks like
an ordinary silk thread no matter how I see it.
See?
It breaks as soon as I pull it.
Nonsense.
My Bladelike Thread
is the best weapon in the world.
Unexpectedly, it can't beat
your Fire Infusion.
I'm not your match.
Just go.
Lian,
your acting skills are terrible.
You see.
There are
only two of us here.
You can tell me if you want to throw this fight.
I won't tell anyone about this.
I throw the fight?
Fine.
Then take a blow
from my Pear Blossom Needle Cloudburst.
Are you going to say I threw the fight again?
No, I won't say anything.
I'll keep my mouth shut.
♪The silent temple♪
♪We still have a long way to go
in the martial arts world♪
♪The falling snow♪
♪Only clouds know the warmth of the cold moon♪
♪The roaring fate♪
♪At last, we see the light at the end of the tunnel♪
♪Everything is just a flash in the pan♪
♪Waiting for the ride to the highest heaven♪
♪The ethereal fog♪
♪Fame and fortune do not matter
to an enlightened person♪
♪I face the sun♪
♪To have a pristine soul in this polluted world♪
♪Travel far♪
♪And overcome challenges life throws at me♪
♪I do not waste my youth away♪
♪Like blade and sword, relying on each other♪
♪We are devoted friends♪
♪How strong our bond is♪
♪No dream is small♪
♪Despite the conflicts and the feuds♪
♪We sing proudly♪
♪Youths ought to be fearless♪
♪Visiting all corners of the world♪
♪With our youthful spirits♪
♪Traveling freely with friends♪
♪It won't be lonely if I have my confidants♪
♪Travel far♪
♪And overcome challenges life throws at me♪
♪I do not waste my youth away♪
♪Like blade and sword, relying on each other♪
♪We are devoted friends♪
♪How strong our bond is♪
♪No dream is small♪
♪Despite the conflicts and the feuds♪
♪We sing proudly♪
♪Youths ought to be fearless♪
♪Visiting all corners of the world♪
♪With our youthful spirits♪
♪Traveling freely with friends♪
♪It won't be lonely if I have my confidants♪