♪The blade dance
causing ripples to spread across the lake♪
♪Waving the banner amidst the storm and rain♪
♪The snow is not bothered
by the sadness and the happiness♪
♪Blazing through the desert
with the rein in hands♪
♪Young and inexperienced, it is apparent♪
♪Bold ambition
interspersed with recklessness♪
♪Mind not the predestination♪
♪Solving all the problems
that fate presents me♪
♪From all the trials and hardship♪
♪Spawn the vast courage♪
♪The journey to seek glory and justice♪
♪Is not in vain♪
♪One smile is all it takes
to get what you're thinking♪
♪A ballad to our journey♪
♪Pursuing the dream of our youth♪
♪We take everything as it comes♪
♪The distant land might be dangerous♪
♪But what's life without an adventure?♪
♪Youths are supposed to dream big and be sharp♪
♪Every struggle in life has taught us♪
♪That we shall do what we can wherever we go♪
♪Together, another journey awaits♪
[The Blood of Youth]
[Episode 32]
Are you saying
that it was one of us
who killed Jinyu?
You can't say that.
I'm not Director Zhuoqing's disciple.
I don't know anything about the Art of Detachment.
If you don't believe me,
you can test me out.
But your master is not dead.
He is Zhuoqing's martial brother.
Over years,
you should've learned something from him.
Directorate of Incense,
this is a groundless presumption.
As you said,
everyone in the world is suspicious.
It's you, you,
you, you, or you?
Shut up!
My best friend is dead.
I'll do everything to avenge him!
Jade Deity.
I understand that you're upset.
But you shouldn't have said that.
It was remiss of me.
But I won't take the statement back.
What did you say?
His Highness Lord Bai is here.
Your Highness.
[In memory of the deceased]
Second Master,
I always imagined
what you looked like
all these years.
I imagined
that you were
a hermit who stayed on a mountain,
a brilliant scholar who wrote a lot of books.
Unexpectedly,
you are
just like what I saw back then.
Second Master,
actually, you were boring.
But it'd be a dull world
without a person
like you.
I'm sorry,
Your Highness.
I once asked you
why you chose me.
Why would you choose
a blind prince like me?
And you told me
you didn't choose me
because you hoped that I would ascend the throne
so that you could live a luxurious life.
But because
you thought it was worthwhile.
I know why Second Master died.
I can give up
on the throne.
But I must
avenge him.
Did Chong really say that?
It's hilarious.
I've already told you
that Lord Bai has always been cautious.
He won't take action
if the situation is undetermined.
We can only forgo this pawn.
Do not act rashly.
Are you blaming me,
Director?
Your Highness,
don't you regret it?
I want to ascend the throne,
but it's not an easy path.
Since I've made the choice,
I won't
regret any step I take.
Director, you should
figure out what to do next.
I've had everything planned out.
Your Highness,
you should stay behind the scenes
to map out a strategy.
So I found you a person to spearhead
the operation.
Who is it?
The real successor to the throne.
It's him?
He's still alive?
General,
you have guests.
I won't see them.
Well...
Hello,
General.
Leave us.
Yes.
General,
I'm sorry to offend you.
Among the Five Eunuchs,
you're the only one who looks right to me.
The rest
either look like scholars
or some sort of young masters.
Well,
what about me?
You look obedient
and have a saccharine smile.
I can tell that you're a treacherous official.
But
you're fit to be a eunuch.
General,
you must be joking.
Well.
Say it.
What do you have to see me about?
If it wasn't something important,
it'd be a serious crime
to barge into the General's Residence.
Of course, I'm here
because of an important matter.
Now that
Emperor Mingde is severely ill,
so a new Dragon Seal Scroll
will be written sooner or later.
A talented person chooses a patron of integrity.
Since every sector in Tianqi City
is picking a good master for itself,
I'm here to ask
about your choice.
You've got some nerve.
You're publicly starting a partisan dispute.
It's a capital crime.
However,
only the losing side will die.
Didn't His Majesty ascend the throne
with the help of the partisan dispute back then?
My daughter has made
the choice for me.
Xiao Chuhe, Lord Yong'an.
The entire Tianqi City
is aware of my choice.
Even His Majesty
won't doubt this.
You'll choose
between Lord Bai, Lord Chi,
and Lord Yong'an.
You indeed have no choice
if they're the only candidates.
But
what if I offer you
another choice?
A
better choice.
What are you trying to say?
I did speak
from my heart.
What have you got?
As you expected,
a scroll.
The name on the scroll
is also as you expected.
Where is the scroll?
General,
you've underestimated me.
How could I bring
such an important thing with me?
Even if you have the scroll,
it can't change everything.
You've joined
the military since sixteen.
You've become the general
of Beili
from a patrol captain.
However,
the two old friends of yours
have already left you.
One of them died on the battlefield.
Even his body
can't return to his homeland.
Another one died at the execution ground.
He was even persecuted for a serious crime.
General,
don't you want to do something
for them two?
I'm not
a very patient man.
Just finish what you want
to say.
I've found you
the best choice.
Just one word,
we'll march to Tianqi,
and it's all within our grasp.
[Snowfall Villa]
I suspect that it's Director Jinxuan
from the Five Eunuchs,
the top master in the imperial city.
How sure are you about it?
Ninety percent.
You can tell Lord Bai about this.
Killing Jinyu
is tantamount
to making Lord Bai take our side.
No rush.
It's not time yet.
When the time comes,
I'll make them pay for this.
I've given the drop of blood
that Consort Xuan gave
to Hua Jin.
Hua Jin said
she only needs two-week time
to derive a pill.
But,
Lord Chi never gives others
a chance to get a break.
Next,
he'll use a drastic measure
to turn the tide.
Well,
we'll stop talking about it.
Let's talk about something casual.
Qianluo seems to like you.
Lei Wujie
really likes you.
I didn't expect you
to change the subject.
I just think you're wrong.
What's wrong?
Not "seems".
She does like me.
Xiao Se,
you're shameless as always
even after having your name changed.
But Lei Wujie seems to think
that you like me.
You're more shameless than before.
Ruoyi,
actually, I know
you like Lei Wujie too.
I knew it
when you danced with him
on the Flora Spectacle.
I found the most primitive
and the purest quality
of a man on Lei Wujie.
We once had the quality before.
But due to various reasons,
we forwent it.
Only he still has it.
Wuxin once said
he was born with a pure heart.
What about you?
Do you like Qianluo?
I don't see a connection
between these two matters.
Tianqi City
is currently in tumult,
but we still have the mood
to chit-chat with each other.
If this gets out,
it'll be a joke.
You change the subject again.
If I was a playboy,
I would've gotten married four years ago.
She's got a pretty face and a beautiful body.
Besides, she's a bit wayward.
She's kind of a fair lady.
You sound like
a playboy who's watching
courtesans at Drunken Dream House.
Well, do you like Qianluo?
I do.
I have work to do, so if you'll excuse me.
You're here.
Your Majesty.
Thank you.
Take a seat.
Divine Healer,
I heard that you caught a cold
a while ago.
How are you now?
Feeling better?
Of course.
It was just a cold,
how could it get me baffled?
You're the Divine Healer.
How did you catch a cold?
Your Majesty,
I'll give you
acupuncture therapy later.
Divine Healer,
you've been sticking
so many needles in my body
these days.
Is it that hard
to cure my disease?
Your Majesty,
do you know
what a healer always says?
What is it?
Mental illness is the cause of all diseases.
Something is bothering you.
I can't cure this.
Mental illness is the cause
of all diseases.
I understand
what you're saying.
It doesn't help.
It needs to be cured.
Whoever started the trouble should end it.
Your Majesty,
who is your problem solver?
He's dead.
He's dead?
Yes.
We were so close.
Our mother died
when we were young.
We were princes.
But we never got
pampered.
Even
the eunuchs with some power
would dare to pick on us.
Physician,
go back and save him, will you?
Your Highness.
Don't go!
I can't.
(When my younger brother was six,)
he caught a severe cold.
It was still not cured
after being treated for so long.
When he nearly died...
Save my brother, will you?
Your Highness,
it's not that I don't want to treat him.
There's nothing I can do.
[Young Xiao Ruojin]
My hands are tied.
Save him, please!
Your Highness,
please go back.
Did he die that day?
This was what they said in the rumor.
On that snowy night,
I had knelt
at the door and begged that imperial physician
for four hours.
I
was a less coddled prince.
But an imperial physician
was ineligible
to afford this kind of kneeling.
In the end, I saved
my brother from death.
Your Majesty,
you're a righteous man.
But that was fake.
It was a story
I told the imperial physician
to spread to the world.
What really happened was
that night,
I had knelt for four hours.
But he insisted on leaving.
So I drew
the long sword my mother left for me.
I stabbed him with it.
From that moment on, I swore
that I'd never be a prince
who's a nobody.
I'd never be trodden
underfoot by others again.
I wanted to reach the top of Tianqi
with my younger brother.
So that everyone
wouldn't dare to look down on us.
Then,
I became the Emperor.
My brother
became Beili's Governor-in-Chief.
Not to mention Tianqi,
even Beili
and the entire world
would be afraid of us.
But in the end,
my brother died.
I killed him.
It was because
I couldn't gather my courage,
and I was afraid of losing
the vanity in my hands.
Your Majesty,
why didn't you call yourself the lonely Emperor?
The lonely Emperor?
Maybe every time
when I think of my brother, Ruofeng,
I see myself
as an elder brother
instead of an emperor.
Only when the younger brother was around,
the elder brother
would never feel lonely.
Uncle Pichuan,
are you tired of living
such a dull life?
What do you think?
This blade of mine is getting rusty.
I kind of miss Tianqi.
I'd like to gamble at Qianjin Gambling House,
have a drink at Diaolou Parlor,
and take a nap at Rainbow and Moon Pavilion.
You have no ambition.
How could His Highness
have a son like you?
I'm just
kidding.
It seems like
we can be summoned back
only when Xiao Se
becomes the Emperor.
It's not necessarily the case.
We can go back on our own.
Based on the latest news,
Emperor Mingde
has been severely ill lately.
Severely ill?
Do you have any plans, Your Highness?
[It's time to return to Tianqi now.]
The fire
that brings us back to Tianqi is here.
It's not Xiao Se who lights it,
but sometimes,
fate is strange.
Everything comes to me
when I want to go back.
Well, then.
Let's get ready
and march to Tianqi.
You're up late.
Are you waiting for some kind of good news?
I'm sure it's not good news
as you're here.
Fine.
Since you put it this way,
I'll leave now.
I won't cause trouble for you.
I was joking.
Your best buddy has laid dormant for years.
He seems a little restless recently.
Are they coming back?
Yes.
But you don't look surprised.
Based on our enemy's ways
of doing things,
once the time comes,
they'll take this step.
But what is it
that attracts them?
It's not known.
Baixiao Sect only found out
that before this,
Jinyan went to the General's Residence.
Then, the General
secretly sent 16 secret agents
out of the city.
It should be the Dragon Seal Scroll.
What is a Dragon Seal Scroll?
Back then,
during the Eight Lords Rebellion,
each prince barged into the palace
and went all the way to Pingqing Hall.
They were waiting
for the dying late Emperor
to send out
the Dragon Seal Scroll,
hoping their names were written on it.
But
only Lord Langya and Emperor Mingde
won in the end.
But when they
were about to step into Pingqing Hall,
the Five Eunuchs came out with the scroll.
Was Emperor Mingde's name written on the scroll?
The Five Eunuchs refused to announce it
despite holding the scroll.
At last, Lord Langya stepped forward
and took the scroll.
He tore it
after taking a glance at it.
Then, he announced
that the throne was passed
to the Third Prince, Xiao Ruojin,
which is the present Emperor Mingde.
It means it wasn't Xiao Se's father's name
that was written on the scroll.
Otherwise, why would he tear it?
Right.
But the Five Eunuchs
who were in charge of this
chose to remain silent.
So,
no one continued
to pursue this matter.
But there are two
Dragon Seal Scrolls.
One of them is guarded by the Five Eunuchs.
It means to declare the decree.
Another one is guarded
by the Directorate of Astronomy.
It means to accept Heaven's will.
After one of the scrolls was torn,
another one
should be sent to the Directorate of Astronomy.
But it just disappeared.
Why did the Five Eunuchs allow him to do it?
There's only one possibility.
It was Uncle Langya's name
that was written on the scroll.
He tore the edict
that had his name on it.
The Five Eunuchs couldn't stop him.
But several years later,
Lord Langya established
brilliant achievements in war.
The people respected him.
The missing scroll
suddenly appeared.
Lord Langya didn't want to take the throne,
but there were growing voices
in the Imperial Court,
the army, and civil society,
wanting him to be the Emperor.
The person who hid that scroll
was going
to make the brothers
turn against each other
so he could achieve his goal.
The new emperor took the throne.
The Five Eunuchs of the late Emperor
were going to guard the mausoleum.
But Director Zhuoqing was extremely powerful
at that time.
So he
wouldn't be pleased with that.
From the very beginning,
he hid the Dragon Seal Scroll
and waited for that day to stage a coup.
I guess
he was the one
who caused Lord Langya's case.
He just didn't expect Uncle Langya
to die
at the execution ground
before
he revealed the scroll.
And he died at the mausoleum
a month later.
Baixiao Sect
didn't find out about this.
Because it was Jinxuan
who hurt me back then.
And Jinxuan was the closest disciple
of Zhuoqing.
After Zhuoqing died,
the Dragon Seal Scroll went missing again.
I think it's most likely
in his hands.
And Jinyan
is Jinxuan's most valued helper
among the Five Eunuchs.
As he could persuade the General,
besides knowing the whereabouts
of Uncle Langya's old army,
he should have
enough leverage to do that.
The only thing I can think of
is the Dragon Seal Scroll.
I don't get it.
Isn't General Ye
Ruoyi's father?
Isn't he
always on our side?
Ye Xiaoying was the most loyal subordinate
of Uncle Langya.
He has waited for this moment for so long.
Unfortunately,
we're aiming for the same target.
But we've got
different choices.
[Endurance]
Ruoyi,
I was 17 when I first met
him.
I was the son of a butcher in Tianqi.
That time,
I took a butcher knife
and looked at him.
He told me
he saw an aura of a protector in me
when I was slaughtering the hogs and goats.
He asked
if I'd protect the nation with him.
Yet, I told him
to get lost
if he didn't want to buy meat.
Then,
I became a patrol captain.
I became the vice general
of the Pioneer Battalion.
There was one time,
we were surrounded by the enemy.
The entire Pioneer Battalion was wiped out.
I was taking my last breath.
And he
got me out
of the pile of bodies.
That was
when I swore
to die for him.
I didn't hear you
talk about this before.
It
was a long time ago.
And then,
I became General of Agile Cavalry,
Generalissimo, and then Defender-General.
The late Emperor bestowed a golden armor on me
and gave me the title of Golden Armor General.
But I was still willing
to be
the subordinate who followed his lead.
But he died
that day.
He didn't die on the battlefield
but at the execution ground.
A month before that happened,
Lord Langya suddenly condemned me.
He took away my tally as a result
of my lax control of the army force.
I know.
Emperor Mingde didn't kill me
just to prevent mutiny.
He saved this position for me
just to comfort me.
Over years,
I've indeed pretended to be comforted.
So the entire world
knows that I, Ye Xiaoying,
hold a grudge against the Emperor
due to Lord Langya's death.
But I dare not revolt
as I'm afraid of the Emperor.
This is the outcome
that everyone wants.
Well,
I'll just show it to them.
[Endurance]
Why are you being
so emotional tonight?
Ruoyi,
today,
I'll send a team of elite soldiers
to escort you out of the city.
Stay away from Tianqi for a while.
Why?
His condition is getting worse.
He'll die anytime.
Moreover,
the princes in Tianqi City are engaged
in a fierce fight.
I'm afraid there will be upheaval.
Upheaval?
When have you ever been afraid of upheaval?
Isn't that
what you always wanted?
You acquiesced to my decision
on helping Xiao Se.
Why would you suddenly send me out of the city?
Fine.
Let me ask you.
Did Xiao Chuhe enter Tianqi
to take the throne
or to investigate
the case?
From what I know of him,
he is here for the case.
That's it.
Xiao Chuhe
never understands this.
Only the Emperor
can find out the truth of this case.
It's impossible for an official
to turn against the Emperor.
Therefore,
in the battle between him
and Lord Chi,
I don't think he'll win.
But you used
to value him.
I valued him because I wanted to watch over him.
Just like how I watched
over Lord Langya back then.
He's got the capability and the guts,
but he's not ruthless enough.
What happened to Lord Langya in the end?
He died.
He was killed by his own brother.
I don't want
to see the same thing happen again.
Just because Xiao Se
never accepted
your support?
Ruoyi,
there's one thing you must understand.
He's Xiao Ruojin's son, after all.
No matter what,
Lord Langya was just his uncle.
He's done well enough.
Lord Langya was right about him too.
But I
don't want to wait any longer.
I don't agree with you.
Since you believe
that it's right,
just stay the course.
I know what you're thinking.
You've endured for years.
You only held back
what you didn't write down.
But that thing
is wrong, to begin with.
Ruoyi.
They're still young.
[Endurance]
[Revolt]
[Jingxue Pavilion]
I heard that you moved
to Snowfall Villa last night.
Not just yesterday.
From now on,
I'll stay here.
Did you have a fight with your father?
This is new.
Since childhood,
I've never seen General Ye
say
anything harsh to you.
He said something strange to me yesterday.
What did he say?
He doesn't think
you will win
in the Battle of Tianqi.
He even said
if you stay as an official,
no matter how determined you are,
you still can't exonerate Lord Langya.
It looks like what worries me the most
has already happened.
You mean the Dragon Seal Scroll?
You didn't say this
to your father's face, did you?
Of course not.
If he had known we were looking into this,
he wouldn't have let me leave.
I suppose he has accepted
that scroll.
Next, I guess
he'll gather Langya Army
and contact Xiao Lingchen
to start the rebellion.
That's what I thought too.
But hearing you say this,
it means this will happen for sure.
This will be the biggest rebellion
since the establishment of Beili.
Hundreds of thousands of cavalries
will set foot on the entire land
and march to Tianqi.
Countless citizens
will suffer because of this.
The nations
that lay dormant around Beili
will take this chance to make a move.
But I don't understand.
What good is it
to Lord Chi
if Langya Army rebels?
Why would the Dragon Seal Scroll
appear at this very moment?
Why would they go to your father
right when it appeared?
If Xiao Lingchen eventually ascends the throne,
Lord Langya has his place back
at the ancestral shrine.
What good does that do them?
I still can't figure this out yet.
But there's one thing for sure.
This is definitely a trap.
I believe your father could figure this out.
But he
will still fall for it.
Because he's a man with a strong ego.
He has no doubt about himself.
Even if he was trapped in a cage,
he could still kill the sick tiger
and leave without injury.
In the end, he'd kill the hunter.
Indeed, he has always been conceited.
But this ego
will eventually get him killed.
He'll drag the entire Langya Army
and Xiao Lingchen down.
Even if he wins in the end,
it'll also cause Beili to suffer a heavy loss.
[Lord Chi's Residence]
The General has made a move?
Yes.
Today, he
has secretly left the city.
I thought it'd take him a long time to make
this decision.
Perhaps,
he already made
this decision four years ago.
He was just waiting for a chance.
Now that the chance has come.
There's no need to hesitate anymore.
What were the terms?
I said
I want a new emperor,
the old rules to be abolished,
the Five Eunuchs not to guard
the mausoleum anymore,
and him
to give me the title of Marquis.
Did he agree?
He accused me of being a cunning subordinate
who tried to be
the powerful official of the previous dynasty.
But at last,
he agreed with me.
Your Highness,
did Ye Xiaoying
sense something?
Don't be silly.
Ye Xiaoying
is not an ordinary soldier.
Of course he did sense something.
He just didn't expect me
to be
the mastermind
behind all this.
Longxie,
go tell the two generals
that the day when they replace
Ye Xiaoying and become the leaders
of Beili Army is coming soon.
His Majesty
evicted all the siblings from here
except for me.
Do you know why?
Because
you were raised by Father.
The other uncles were no match
for you.
To be more specific,
it's because His Majesty knew
I wouldn't steal the throne from him.
The other princes
were ambitious
and ill-intentioned.
It'd be troublesome if they stayed in Tianqi.
As for me,
he trusted me.
Langya wouldn't do that either,
so he trusted him as well.
It took years
to build this kind of trust.
It wasn't a one-off project.
If so, what about
the case that happened four years ago?
One
would change
when he took the throne.
Besides, Langya
was a lot like an excellent emperor.
Historically speaking,
those who rise too high
won't end up well.
Basically,
even though you're full of talent,
you pretend to be
a good-for-nothing
just to cover yourself?
No.
I've always been a playboy who likes poems,
liquor, and beautiful ladies.
I'm not faking it.
This is me.
Chuhe,
I worked hard
when I supervised the nation.
I didn't make a mistake.
The officials
complimented me as well.
What you said to me
was harsh.
Since you care about the nation and the people,
let me tell you something.
What is it?
Fifteen days later,
an army will charge into the city.
Tianqi will be in danger.
Is it so serious?
Langya Army.
Langya Army?
Langya Army doesn't exist in the world anymore.
The main force of Beili's army Ye Xiaoying leads
joins forces with Lord Langya
to form Langya Army back in the day.
Xiao Se,
do you know what you're talking about?
Of course I do.
If the army that I mentioned
gathers up,
this dynasty will collapse.
You don't look like you're joking.
20,000 people in Wangli Army,
3,000 imperial guards,
8,000 Tianqi City Soldiers,
and 1,300
Tiger Soldiers,
there are about 30,000 soldiers.
But there are 200,000 people in Langya Army.
Based on the rule in war, we'll be surrounded
as they have more people.
It's 30,000 to 200,000.
We can only defend the city.
By then, divide them into two teams
to rescue His Majesty.
When I was on my way back to Tianqi,
there were army forces trying to stop me.
So I'm sure
the imperial family is behind this.
There are several princes in Tianqi City
and several old lords out there.
As long as they're from the Xiao family,
they'll have the chance to be the Emperor.
You think they're up to something else?
There are many guesses about that.
But I can't make a decision
until the moment
when the Langya Army arrives at the city.
But now, I just hope
you could trust me for once.
♪The silent temple♪
♪We still have a long way to go
in the martial arts world♪
♪The falling snow♪
♪Only clouds know the warmth of the cold moon♪
♪The roaring fate♪
♪At last, we see the light
at the end of the tunnel♪
♪Everything is just a flash in the pan♪
♪Waiting for the ride to the highest heaven♪
♪The ethereal fog♪
♪Fame and fortune do not matter
to an enlightened person♪
♪I face the sun♪
♪To have a pristine soul in this polluted world♪
♪Travel far♪
♪And overcome challenges life throws at me♪
♪I do not waste my youth away♪
♪Like blade and sword, relying on each other♪
♪We are devoted friends♪
♪How strong our bond is♪
♪No dream is small♪
♪Despite the conflicts and the feuds♪
♪We sing proudly♪
♪Youths ought to be fearless♪
♪Visiting all corners of the world♪
♪With our youthful spirits♪
♪Traveling freely with friends♪
♪It won't be lonely if I have my confidants♪
♪Travel far♪
♪And overcome challenges life throws at me♪
♪I do not waste my youth away♪
♪Like blade and sword, relying on each other♪
♪We are devoted friends♪
♪How strong our bond is♪
♪No dream is small♪
♪Despite the conflicts and the feuds♪
♪We sing proudly♪
♪Youths ought to be fearless♪
♪Visiting all corners of the world♪
♪With our youthful spirits♪
♪Traveling freely with friends♪
♪It won't be lonely if I have my confidants♪