♪The blade dance
causing ripples to spread across the lake♪
♪Waving the banner amidst the storm and rain♪
♪The snow is not bothered
by the sadness and the happiness♪
♪Blazing through the desert
with the rein in hands♪
♪Young and inexperienced, it is apparent♪
♪Bold ambition
interspersed with recklessness♪
♪Mind not the predestination♪
♪Solving all the problems
that fate presents me♪
♪From all the trials and hardship♪
♪Spawn the vast courage♪
♪The journey to seek glory and justice♪
♪Is not in vain♪
♪One smile is all it takes
to get what you're thinking♪
♪A ballad to our journey♪
♪Pursuing the dream of our youth♪
♪We take everything as it comes♪
♪The distant land might be dangerous♪
♪But what's life without an adventure?♪
♪Youths are supposed to dream big and be sharp♪
♪Every struggle in life has taught us♪
♪That we shall do what we can wherever we go♪
♪Together, another journey awaits♪
[The Blood of Youth]
[Episode 25]
Twenty-three years ago,
your ancestors escorted His Majesty
and fought their way to Tai'an Hall.
Many people died
in that bloodbath.
But their glory remains
in the world.
This glory
runs in your veins.
Let me ask you.
Will you make a way
for Lord Yong'an who returns
to the city alone?
We will!
Good!
Tiger Soldiers!
Get ready, soldiers!
An hour later, we shall depart!
Yes!
[Tianqi]
It's you.
I remember you.
The first disciple of Wushuang City,
Lu Yuzhai.
I remember you too.
Lei Wujie of Xueyue City.
You got it wrong.
What did I get wrong?
I'm not
my dumb martial brother.
I have a good memory.
I never forget
people I've met just once.
You got my name right
but my title wrong.
You left Xueyue City?
No.
I didn't come here
on behalf of Xueyue City this time.
I'm here as one of Tianqi's Four Guardians,
guardian of the East,
Azure Dragon.
When I was a child,
I had heard
legendary stories
of Tianqi's Four Guardians.
Azure Dragon
was Li Xinyue, the Sword Heart with dreams.
The sword in your hand
must be the Heart Sword,
the fourth most famous sword in the world.
Then you should be glad
you are going to fight with the legend.
However, before we start,
I got two things
to say to you.
First,
as a spear user,
you're no match for Qianluo,
and you're far worse
than my third martial uncle.
What's the second thing?
Second,
as an eldest martial brother,
you are so much worse
than my eldest martial brother, Tang Lian.
And
you Wushuang City
think you can be the best in the world?
What a joke.
Get in formation!
I hate things
like formations.
Kunlun Sword Deity once said
swords
are a lone weapon.
The sword is lonely,
and so is the swordsman.
A group action like this
is simply deplorable.
But I heard that Sword Heart Tomb
also has a generational sword formation.
Sword Heart Tomb's Thousand Men Formation
guards the sacred site of the tomb.
It's impregnable.
A little stunt like yours can never
be compared with that.
Based on what I heard,
you are not a talkative
and aggressive person.
Maybe it's because
I've been hanging out with someone
who likes to be sarcastic,
and I've picked up
some bad habits.
I used to be a humble
and polite hot-blooded young man.
You're stalling for time.
You saw through me.
I mean,
I'm going to fight
against a dozen of you alone.
What's wrong with me stalling for time a little?
It's useless.
Other than Wushuang City,
there are too many people who want to kill him.
Stalling us
only gives others
the opportunity to kill him.
At least we just want
to capture him.
The people who want to kill him
are as many as the people who want to save him.
As for what you said
about capturing him,
do you know
what he would say to you
if he heard you say that?
What would he say?
Bah.
Attack!
[Luo City Army]
Report!
What's going on?
General,
there is someone blocking our way ahead.
Someone is blocking our way?
[Chen Hu, Luo City Army]
Who dares to get in our way?
This road is closed.
Who are you?
How dare you stand in the way of the Luo City Army.
I'm Vermilion Bird of Tianqi's Four Guardians,
the guardian of the South.
You must be the descendant of that predecessor.
For the sake
of his friendship with His Majesty,
please get out of the way.
Do you know
what this line means?
Whoever crosses this line
will die!
General!
Kill her!
Yes!
Kill!
I shall clear the path for you with my spear
and help you ascend
to the throne of Tianqi.
[Luo City Army]
[Muliang]
[Ji Xue, Baixiao Sect]
Culminating the qi of a sword with a city.
Lone Sword Deity's melancholy sword thought
truly lives up to its reputation.
Last year at this time, in this place,
as the peach blossoms, her face blushed.
Her beautiful face is no longer here,
leaving the peach blossoms
booming in the gentle breeze.
What brings you here, sir?
I was wondering why Ji Ruofeng would reopen
the martial arts rank.
It turns out that Baixiao Sect
has a new successor.
Where is your father?
He has not yet recovered from his serious injury,
so I have to do it for him.
Why did you reopen the rank?
I want to put an end
to the past martial era
and mark a start
for the new martial era.
Interesting.
Mister Spear Deity, you have made it
to third place on the Top-Rank List this time,
but you're still a little behind Luo Qingyang.
Mister Spear Deity,
are you confident that you can stop him?
My eldest martial brother
has made it to second place too,
but when we were in Xueyue City,
I beat him up every day.
He's the Principal City Lord,
yet all he does is drink and make liquor every day.
Whenever I see someone like him,
I'll always beat them up.
This
is my tribute
to the City Lord of Melancholy City.
Melancholy City?
When Beili was founded,
this city
was once prosperous,
but due to climate change,
the inhabitants moved south.
It ended up becoming ruins.
People call it Melancholy City.
Later, the Sword Deity lived here alone,
and so people call it Muliang City
to show their respect.
He guards this city all on his own.
This kind of spirit
is truly admirable.
He's here.
Let's go.
He has no intention of leaving the city.
How do you know that?
The sword thoughts on his scabbard
told me that.
This is really a duel
between masters of the Top-Rank List.
I can never
get it.
But I haven't
delivered my gift yet.
You can follow his example.
Throw the liquor over to him.
I'll give it a try.
Now that the gift has been delivered,
I should get going.
So this is Ji Ruofeng's daughter,
the new successor of Baixiao Sect.
And the new White Tiger.
Sir, here's your tea.
Does it rain a lot here?
Yes.
It often rains here,
especially in this season.
Sometimes,
it rains for two weeks.
Do you come
from far away, sir?
Yes.
I have two homes,
both in faraway places.
What brings
you here then?
To kill someone.
Sir,
that's very funny.
Waiter,
do you have liquor here?
Yes,
but it's not the shop's.
It's the liquor
I kept for myself.
Can I buy it from you?
I'll pay you three times the original price.
It's just common liquor.
That's very generous.
Please wait a moment.
Sir, here's your liquor.
What is the name of this liquor?
This jug of liquor is worth only ten copper coins.
There is no name.
It's just homemade plain liquor.
Plain liquor?
I've always heard them talk about it.
I wonder if the liquor here
is the same as those
in Snowfall Villa.
Snowfall Villa?
What place is that?
I don't know either.
One of them said
it was an elegant manor
with snow falling in front of it
and flowers flying at the back,
and the other said
it was a wrecked inn,
which is just a little bigger
than your tea shop.
There was leakage everywhere
and holes in the roof.
Waiter,
I've reserved
this tea shop for now.
Come back
four hours later.
Sir,
what do you mean?
Did you forget
what I just said?
I'm here
to kill someone.
Leave now
before it's too late.
Tang Lian.
Do you know
what the real power of the real Heart Sword is?
The real power of it
is it can command all swords.
All your swords are afraid of me.
So, of course you are no match for me.
All right.
I've shown all my cards.
Isn't it time
for you to show your cards too?
I've been looking forward
to your Wushuang Sword Box.
Master.
Half-step Insouciant Phase.
Half-step Sword Deity?
What are you doing here?
Have you no shame?
You brat, mind your mouth.
Maybe you shouldn't be
called Wushuang City.
You should change it to
Shameless City.
At first, you were ganging up on me.
I was outnumbered.
I can let that slide.
But even your former city lord
is here to fight me now.
You're bullying a kid. Do you have no shame?
City Lord Song,
you are a few years older
than my master.
And you
want to draw your sword on me?
All I can practice
is theories inside the sword hut,
and I can only put them into use outside.
I've stayed in my hut for too long.
I haven't made any improvement.
That's why I left my city and came here today.
Are you saying
that you want to forge your path
with my blood?
My surname is Lei, Lei of the Lei Fortress.
You know
we are powerful.
We don't get intimidated easily.
I heard
that when you were young,
you struck your sword toward the sky.
It was so beautiful
that even the migrating swallows
turned back
and flew around
the residual sword qi,
hovering above it.
That's why your name is Song Yanhui,
which means the return of the swallows.
But after what I just saw,
I'm really disappointed.
You!
When a swordsman
forgets the reason for drawing his sword,
he loses the heart of the sword.
How can a person who has lost the heart of a sword
become a sword deity?
City Lord Song,
do you remember
the reason for drawing your sword?
The reason for drawing my sword?
Back then,
you swung your sword at me.
You made me realize
that the reason I drew my sword is to protect.
Today,
I shall return what you gave me.
If you want to become a sword deity,
perhaps you will
have to start learning from drawing the sword.
Just one swing
to determine victory.
You're too arrogant.
I'm still young.
I can afford to be arrogant.
Master!
When one practices
sword techniques for the sake of practicing,
he loses the soul of the sword.
I'm leaving the city today.
Why must you leave the city?
To practice sword techniques.
Can't you practice it in Wushuang City?
Why do you have to go outside of the city?
Because there is injustice outside the city.
I will draw my sword for injustice,
for all the people of the world,
and for all the people
who are suffering.
You are right.
All these years,
I only draw my sword
because I want to win Xueyue City.
I have forgotten all those things.
Master,
should we go after him?
No.
We can't catch up with him anymore.
[Tianqi]
[Luo City Army]
How many more men can you kill?
300? 500?
Or 1,000?
I don't want to kill anyone,
but if you don't withdraw your troops,
then I'll kill as many as I can.
You are very strong,
but you've underestimated
the strength of the Luo City Army.
Today,
we shall
fight you till the end.
It's Ye Battalion!
Charge!
Kill!
Oh, no. They're going to charge
and break our formation.
Line up for defense!
Attack!
Will many more die in the future?
Yes.
This is war.
The faster and quicker you win,
the fewer people will die.
It's not about killing the enemy,
it's about
winning the war.
All right.
Let's win it fast then.
You really like Chuhe, don't you?
His name is Xiao Se.
You again.
I thought there would be
a large troop here to stop me,
but you are the only one.
I heard that in the past few years,
although you couldn't use
your inner force anymore,
you never stopped
the practice of staff skills.
I've been waiting for this day.
This day?
A day for a rematch.
Don't bluff.
Your meridians have just been reshaped.
Your power is just
at the Carefree Phase, at most.
How are you going to fight me?
There will be no one to save you today.
I don't need others to save me.
You're at Sturdy Phase,
you think you can take me down?
Very well.
After these years of honing your skills,
you are indeed much stronger than back then.
You are good enough to fight with me.
Perhaps you would wonder
why you had not encountered any obstacles
on your way back to Tianqi.
That's because
someone stopped them for you,
and they
couldn't stop me.
It's a pity
that I don't want to kill you yet
because my disciple
wants to have
a fairer duel with you.
I look forward to the day
when you become a true master.
When that day comes,
I will come back to kill you.
The eldest martial disciple of Xueyue City,
you're just as I heard.
Black Tortoise of Tianqi's Four Guardians,
the guardian of the North,
that's who I came here as.
I heard that despite your young age,
you have already mastered
the best hidden weapon technique
of the Tang Clan,
Fatal Blossom Shower.
It would be an honor
to see it today.
I'm from the Tang family,
but I'm here for the Xiao family today.
I didn't bring any hidden weapons.
All I have
are my fists
and these seven cups of liquor.
Dubhe, Merak, Phecda,
Megrez, Alioth, Mizar, and Alkaid.
The Seven Starry Nights.
Insouciant Phase.
This is good liquor.
These are the real Hanging Heaven
and Distant Seas.
Those were
just children's plays.
I traveled around the world when I was younger.
I have seen the spectacles of the world.
I have sung all the songs of the world
and met a man who had no regrets.
I also had a dream of ten years.
I saw blood and bones everywhere.
Heroes drew their swords and shouted!
Yes.
[Tianqi]
Chuhe.
Uncle.
You're back.
I haven't seen the city yet.
Make way for him!
He is still the same as back then,
like an untamed wild horse.
Only now the pony has grown up.
I think no one
can control him anymore.
Your Highness,
a group is approaching.
How many of them?
Sounds like
a few hundred people.
Why are there so many people here?
How much further?
Less than a li.
Get all troops on alert.
Get prepared to face the enemy.
Stay alert!
Your Highness.
Like father,
like daughter indeed, Miss Ye.
I have always heard that you are weak,
that you couldn't even stand for a long time.
I didn't expect to see you
to be as imposing as your father
when you rode the horse.
You flatter me, Your Highness.
I left Tianqi without permission this time,
please forgive me.
Never mind.
You and Chuhe
are best friends who grew up together.
I trust you.
Are you implying
that you don't trust my father?
Your Ye Battalion is called
the Tiger and Wolf Battalion,
and your father is the head of the Tiger and Wolf.
It's a pity that we can work together
to conquer the world,
but we can't trust each other completely.
I assume we're here
for the same man.
Your father and I made a deal
to see who could get him
after a year.
You are still
thinking about that?
Looks like this girl from Xueyue City
has been through
a great battle.
What's the matter? You ran into an enemy?
Luo City Army isn't strong enough
to be considered an enemy.
You are quite arrogant.
I guess you've fended off
a group of enemies for him.
On our way here from Tianqi,
we haven't really done anything.
We are in no position
to compete over him with you.
I suppose you understand,
right, Miss Ye?
Yes, I understand.
None of us can get him
because he won't listen to us.
But we can support him.
Just like what we are doing now.
We are chasing after him.
Come on.
Let's go back to Tianqi.
Young Lady,
should we go after them?
We will follow them until the gate of Tianqi City,
then, you all can turn back.
Yes, Young Lady.
Ye,
you don't trust Marquis Lanyue?
Qianluo,
don't simply trust people from Tianqi City.
Especially those
from the imperial family.
Miss Ruoyi,
are you going to Tianqi?
Of course.
What are the odds?
I'm going to Tianqi too.
How about we travel together?
Well, well, Lei Wujie,
didn't you see me here?
You only greeted Ye
but not me.
Qianluo,
I've just escaped
from Wushuang City's men.
Please cut me some slack.
Wushuang City?
Lord Bai made a move too?
Yes,
but they probably
only wanted to stop him.
They don't intend to kill him.
Everyone is here.
Tang Lian should've departed too.
I wonder where he is.
There is no need to worry about him.
With him here,
every problem can be solved.
We just need
to wait for him in Tianqi.
Qianluo has got
a very good point.
Everyone knows how reliable
the eldest martial disciple of Xueyue City is.
We will see him in Tianqi City.
You have two cups of liquor left.
But there's only
one of you left.
I can see
that you have no strength left.
You have one last cup left,
but I don't think
you will drink it anymore.
Won't I?
This is the first time
I've seen such incredible liquor,
but I know
if you drink another cup,
you will die.
But if I don't drink,
how can I live?
You can go your own way, and I will go mine.
Some of you are dead,
and some are maimed.
They are incompetent.
As assassins,
they failed to kill and were killed by others.
They have nothing to complain about.
You people from Dark River
can be really coldhearted.
But what makes you think
you can negotiate terms with Xueyue City?
♪Don't be afraid of the roars and the thunders♪
♪Don't be afraid of the waves and the wind♪
♪You can't see the end of the world
without traveling♪
Even if I don't use hidden weapons,
I can still make this move.
The
Fatal
Blossom
Shower!
♪Riding a nimbus cloud while singing♪
♪I'm free to do whatever I want♪
♪I would rather travel light
than wear that lavish fur♪
♪Riding on a spear while singing♪
♪I know the universe is endless♪
♪Facing the rising tides and mountains,
my heart is as calm as a millpond♪
♪Fame does not matter to a carefree person♪
♪Riding a nimbus cloud♪
♪Through the seas and the clouds♪
♪A fantasy in the martial arts world♪
♪Disrupts the time in the world♪
♪Taking a long journey and singing♪
♪With stories that will never end♪
♪It's better to stay passionate in this life♪
(Lian,)
your mother and I are going away today.
Take good care
of yourself in Tang Clan.
Father,
where are you going?
A place far away,
but we will
come back a year later.
All right.
Father, Mother,
why aren't you back yet?
I can't hang in there anymore.
Is your name Tang Lian?
Yes, my name is Tang Lian.
Every year on this day,
you are here waiting for someone.
It's been three years.
My parents
said they would be back a year later.
Your parents
aren't coming back.
You
will live with me from now on.
I'm Tang Lianyue,
and I am now your master.
Father,
Mother,
were you also
lying in a place
where no one knew
and dying
like me?
Would you like
a cup of liquor to warm you up?
Lying here in the rain,
you must be freezing.
Want to drink it?
Why don't you want it?
If you came to humiliate me,
I'd advise you to give up.
You're just like Tang Lianyue described,
you're a rock.
You will have one more master from now on.
I'm Baili Dongjun.
You are Baili Dongjun?
Yes.
I'm Baili Dongjun,
who is even stronger
than Tang Lianyue.
Lian,
once you leave,
how long will it be
before we see each other again?
I...
We only see each other
when there is an assignment.
When there isn't,
it's as if I don't exist.
Is it that in your heart
I don't matter at all?
No.
It's just that I...
In front of others,
you are the eldest martial brother
who carries a lot of responsibilities.
Why is it
that you stutter whenever you speak to me?
Are you afraid that I will swallow you?
Master Lianyue told me
to wait for someone in Xueyue City.
And I will protect this someone
when he tries to finish a very important mission.
It's just that this mission can be very dangerous.
I'm afraid...
I'm afraid that I would implicate you.
But I'm not afraid of being implicated.
Rui,
I will come back to you.
By then,
I won't be here as Xueyue City's
eldest martial disciple
or the Tang Clan's disciple.
I will come to you as Tang Lian.
When?
When I complete
the mission given by my master.
I wish I could drink
Master's liquor again.
♪The silent temple♪
♪We still have a long way to go
in the martial arts world♪
♪The falling snow♪
♪Only clouds know the warmth of the cold moon♪
♪The roaring fate♪
♪At last, we see the light
at the end of the tunnel♪
♪Everything is just a flash in the pan♪
♪Waiting for the ride to the highest heaven♪
♪The ethereal fog♪
♪Fame and fortune do not matter
to an enlightened person♪
♪I face the sun♪
♪To have a pristine soul in this polluted world♪
♪Travel far♪
♪And overcome challenges life throws at me♪
♪I do not waste my youth away♪
♪Like blade and sword, relying on each other♪
♪We are devoted friends♪
♪How strong our bond is♪
♪No dream is small♪
♪Despite the conflicts and the feuds♪
♪We sing proudly♪
♪Youths ought to be fearless♪
♪Visiting all corners of the world♪
♪With our youthful spirits♪
♪Traveling freely with friends♪
♪It won't be lonely if I have my confidants♪
♪Travel far♪
♪And overcome challenges life throws at me♪
♪I do not waste my youth away♪
♪Like blade and sword, relying on each other♪
♪We are devoted friends♪
♪How strong our bond is♪
♪No dream is small♪
♪Despite the conflicts and the feuds♪
♪We sing proudly♪
♪Youths ought to be fearless♪
♪Visiting all corners of the world♪
♪With our youthful spirits♪
♪Traveling freely with friends♪
♪It won't be lonely if I have my confidants♪