ðŸŒ¿ [Episode 8] ðŸƒ
[Incoming call- Young Ran]
Yes?
Go to So Bin and Joon. It seems like there was a fight.
What?
♫ We call this the end ♫
♫ The more we try to find where our heart lies ♫
♫ The more we try to hide from each other ♫
♫ It gets harder  ♫
♫ Holding you in my arms for the last time ♫
♫ Your embrace was ♫
♫ warmer and much smaller than I thought ♫
♫ With you my dear (With you my dear) ♫
♫ So I hated the fact that my feelings were late ♫
Let's go out.
What's wrong? You said we should enjoy the festival.
The genre here is teen romance. It doesn't suit us.
Geez, you realized that now only?
The cart bar by my place, they have good food. Udon and soju, what do you say?
What soju? Maybe I'd settle for some wine.
Why are you doing this? Since when did you drink wine?
You said your head hurts when you drink wine.
Let's have some grilled eel with soju!
- Sure, marinated grill it is.
- Salted grill it is!
Marina-te...
We really don't suit each other.
Will you be okay with not going to the hospital?
Go in. We're close enough.
I'll walk you home. You're hurt.
How will you go home alone if you walk me home?
Let's go.
What about you? I don't like you going alone like that.
Geez!
- Where is Joon?
- How would we know?
Let go of me!
That psycho jerk would have collapsed somewhere, why?!
[Youth Villa]
Sanitize, apply ointment, and after it dries, put a band-aid on the wound.
I don't have it.
- What?
- Band-aid.
- Is the pharmacy open now?
- You don't have to go to the pharmacy.
- What is this?
- I should put a band-aid on it, apply ointment, and sanitize it. Right?
No, sanitize, then apply ointment—
I'm going.
I know how to do it all but...
can't you do it for me?
I can put the band-aid on.
I think I hurt my finger also.
Not that it hurts a lot.
Then it's okay.
[Youth Villa]
Close your eyes.
Does it hurt a lot?
It hurts like hell.
Don't be in pain.
Also, don't get hurt.
Why? Do you hate me getting hurt?
Yes. I hate it a lot.
Shall I get revenge for you? I'll pull out all of Oh Chun Gook's hair.
Why would you touch Oh Chun Guk's hair?
You scared me.
Only touch my hair.
Are you happy?
♫ Another day  ♫
♫ passes like this ♫
♫ In the corner of my dull heart ♫
♫ A small flower blooming with hope. ♫
♫ A word  ♫
♫ that makes my weary heart flutter ♫
♫ Now, let it shine on me  ♫
♫  All of my pain...  ♫
This is me.
♫ ...fades away like a morning shower ♫
♫ All the past days I regretted ♫
♫ I'm no longer that person ♫
[Missed calls- Nam Soo Hyun]
Senior, is something wrong?
Are you okay?
Did you perhaps call me because you were worried?
Those three calls?
I'm glad you're okay.
What is this?
He worried for me.
Wow, it's you.
Why? Can't it be me?
Did you wait for Unni?
Unni isn't coming back.
She isn't staying out again, right?
I'm worried that we'll get punished.
I'll call her.
Yes, Unni. Where are you?
Ah, okay.
- Soo Hyun?
See you tomorrow.
What is she doing with Soo Hyun all night that she is staying out all night?
The manager of the bar she works at has some work so she will be staying there overnight.
Oh, okay.
Such good times. I want to have a boyfriend to text, too.
Oh my god!
I only spent 5 minutes in there.
- Yesterday...
- What about yesterday?
Who were you with? Why did you stay out all night?
Wow, I almost thought you were my mom.
Did you perhaps...
were you with the person who is tall, has bangs straight like this,
and handsome, the one you're friends with?
Handsome?
I'm not sure because everyone around me is handsome.
The most handsome one of them is Nam Soo Hyun.
Mi Joo, go and sleep.
- It's morning though.
- Just sleep some more.
How sick are you?
He seems to have a severe fever and seems to be in pain.
- He was also hurt here.
- Hurt?
We treated his wound yesterday. Now I need medicine for his cold.
- What are the symptoms?
- Seems like a cold.
Give me something with a quick effect.
He has to take it 3 times a day after each meal.
Are you okay?
♫ Just talk to me if you need anything ♫
♫ And I'll do it for you ♫
What do you want to eat? If I had known you were coming, I would have ordered something.
You ran over here just because I said I'm sick?
You look okay.
I got better after seeing you.
I was in a lot of pain earlier.
I should stop calling you "senior" now.
What should I call you?
Whatever you're comfortable with. Senior is fine.
I did save your number. Have a look.
[My Bin]
What did you save me as?
I'm really curious.
What?
Did you just hide your cellphone?
Did I?
What is this anxious gaze?
No! No, no, no! It's nothing!
- I caught you!
- No, no, no, no.
♫ My eyes are full with you ♫
Huh? BA Major '21, Yeo Joon?
Are you TA Noona Seol or something?
That... There are a lot of Joons in the world.
There's also a Choi Joon, from your year.
Choi Joo— Wow... I'm really hurt.
I contemplated all night on what to save you as.
I'll think about it, too.
Sorry.
For now, why don't you take the medicine?
If Kim So Bin, my senior from BA Major '19 tells me to drink it, I should.
[Incoming call- 010-9905-542]
That's an unknown number. One moment.
Hello?
Ah, yes, Professor.
Yes, yes, I've heard.
Next week?
Yes, I understand.
Excuse me... The phone call just now...
He's my brother.
Professor Yeo Joon Wan.
Oh... I see.
He's the person I hate the most.
So I hated that you would be working with him.
I'm sorry. I was being selfish.
Why you hate him,
can I ask?
Never mind. Next time...
I have a memory of getting severely beaten by him when I was little.
Enough to pass out.
Professor, did that to you?
That event was traumatic for me.
Don't come near. You'll catch my cold.
I have a strong immune system.
No. Step away.
- I don't want to.
- Don't. I've warned you.
Hey, BA Major '21! Listen to the words of your '19 senior.
I don't have much patience. Don't provoke me.
How-How is the medicine?
It supposedly has fast effects.
Now I feel warm. Did I catch your cold?
What do you mean? We didn't do anything.
Come here.
- Sit down.
- No. No. I feel like I have a fever now.
I didn't even do anything.
- One moment!
- Soo Hyun, here! Hurry!
Enjoy.
Thank you. Enjoy your meal.
Wheel of fortune?
What does this mean?
A fate that you can't avoid.
A fate that can't be avoided?
- How about you?
- I...
If not then fine.
I'll look.
Ask what you're curious about.
That man and I... how will it turn out?
Choose one.
[STRENGTH]
In the end, it'll end well.
It ends well? I wasn't even getting my hopes up!
It won't be easy.
The results are what matter!
Don't you think so?
Yeah, right.
The results will be good in the end. A happy ending.
Give me the fees for reading your tarot fortune, 1,000 won each.
[THE MOON]
This is suffocating.
[NSH]
I still haven't returned this.
Yeah?
What? You picked up on the first ring.
I was going to pay you back with three missed calls.
- I'm hanging up.
- I'm sick.
Your voice sounds lively though? If you don't have anything to say...
I do have something to say! You have no patience.
What is it?
Do you have time tomorrow? I have something to give you.
I'm busy.
Ah, I was going to cut the call first.
I might just not return this to you!
But... he should have bought a more vivid color.
I heard you punched someone.
- Because of Yeo Joon?
- Yeah.
Yeah? I asked you to stop the fight, not to participate in it.
It turned out that way.
This is the first time I'm seeing you worry about others' problems.
Did I not care about any of your matters?
You nagged a lot.
But you've never used your fists for my sake.
You're the one who uses her fists.
Is that my problem?
I take care of myself too much.
But he's magician Yeo Joon these days, making you change and all.
Because he's so different from me,
I thought that there was no reason to become friendly.
That is what you thought, but?
I don't know either. He's also like my younger brother.
Maybe you grew fond of him.
Fond?
Sit over there. I'll go buy some coffee.
No, I'll go.
No, the one you buy tastes bad.
Wait.
Gosh.
Soo Hyun!
Yes.
Please lend me your phone.
My phone?
You're holding yours in your hand though.
It turned off. I have an urgent call to make.
Is that true?
It's not true.
My number is 010-366-7883.
That's my phone number. You've memorized it right? Since you're smart.
I should learn your number, too. Life is about give and take.
I didn't memorize it. I'm not that smart.
That's all right. You're good-looking.
I'm also not someone who is that good-looking.
Why is everything wrong?
Am I that wrong for you?
Don't answer. There's an order for everything.
I won't bother you.
Can't you just give me your number?
I will just look at your messaging app profile.
Do you not want to do that either?
Did something happen?
Why does Mi Joo look so devastated?
I think I did something wrong.
What?
Mi Joo asked for my phone number.
She asked and?
I didn't give it to her.
Why?
I don't have that kind of luxury.
Who needs luxury to share a phone number.
To have interest in someone and start something,
I don't have time for that.
And... there's nothing I can do for the other party.
Do you have to do something?
The other party could do something for you instead.
And if you like someone, you can make the time for them.
Even if you like someone, you might not be able to afford it.
It was like that for me.
Towards who?
You.
Don't be too startled. It's something of the past.
I was only sick for a couple of days, but my skin is all dry.
It's really glowing.
- Hey, Joon.
- I told you I would see you at school.
We went to school together before, too.
If I were there, I would have thrown a punch at Oh Chun Gook!
I didn't know you would come, so I left.
I saw you there.
You probably saw wrong.
I have somewhere to go. So you can head off first.
My mother's sick so I rented out my room.
Can I stay at your place for just one month? That's fine, right?
- I don't think it'll work out.
- Why not?
Do I have to explain that to you?
So you're really dating Kim So Bin.
Introduce her to me sometime. I have a lot to share.
Shouldn't you not be like this to me? Why can't I stay at your place?
I have a roommate.
Roommate? Who? Kim So Bin?
Senior Nam Soo Hyun.
- That psycho?
- Shall we all live together?
You're lying!
You lied about your father being ill that time.
Did you repay the money you borrowed from that time?
How many times do you plan to fool me until you stop?
Who is lying to who?
Gosh.
Will Yeo Joon really press charges?
There's too much definitive evidence.
Ah, Yeo Joon. Isn't there any other way?
Don't touch him. He's a scary kid.
You shouldn't get fooled by his looks.
What is scary?
How should I put it? His money, popularity, smarts.
He uses everything he has to get what he wants, but it doesn't show.
Because he's always going around smiling.
Even during the festival, he deliberately got beaten up at a place with a lot of people.
He provoked you so that you would punch him.
He'd be the victim and you the perpetrator.
Do you think Joon can't use his fists?
Hey, do you have proof? You're making him look too bad.
Even now, I wanted to stay at his home for some time, but he said that he lives together with Nam Soo Hyun.
Nam Soo Hyun?
He must have lied because he didn't want you around.
Habitual liar.
- Habitual?
- Everything about Joon is a lie.
- You don't know who his older brother is, do you?
- He doesn't have a brother.
What do you mean? Professor Yeo Joon Wan.
- The new Professor, Yeo Joon Wan?
- Yeah!
All the professors have totally got his back.
Even if he bombs his exams this time, I bet he will get good grades.
There were stories that he stole some tests in high school.
He comes from such a rich household. That's what makes him so arrogant.
Wow!
Come see me for a moment.
"See" you?
Go talk it out.
You'll be contacted by the police soon.
Hey, you bastard, you provoked me first.
There was just so much evidence, I had no choice.
I figured I'd inform you in advance so you wouldn't be shocked.
So this is how it turns out... I guess Nam Soo Hyun will be my cellmate.
- What are you saying?
- You didn't know?
The day you got beat up by me, I got punched by Nam Soo Hyun.
Soo Hyun punched you?
See this?
I have evidence, too. I won't settle, I'm suing him.
Stay quiet. That'll be best for you.
Don't mess with him.
That psychotic jerk.
I don't like pineapple pizza.
You're the one who likes pineapple pizza. I just eat the crust.
I didn't even know that So Bin didn't like it.
You're serious?
I've ended my one-sided love.
How about as friends?
I'm going to care for myself first from now on.
So what did Joon say?
To not mess with Nam Soo Hyun.
Joon did?
These two are best friends for life now.
Gosh, Joon that two-faced bastard.
The real psycho wasn't Nam Soo Hyun but Yeo Joon.
Hey. Quiet down.
Why? Or else, you'll punch me again?
What?
I messed with your roommate. What are you going to do about it?
I heard you're living with Nam Soo Hyun. That's a lie, isn't it?
This jerk... I heard you were quite famous in high school.
Saying you didn't have a brother when you had one.
Isn't this also bullying?
Lying and treating others like fools, stabbing them in the back.
Things like that are considered psychological bullying.
It turns out that your brother is a professor here—
I'm living with Joon.
- Why is that any of your business?
- Really?
Bullying is what you guys are doing.
Should I make it a bigger case? There are a lot of witnesses.
What? You're going to punch me again?
Geez, these people really have a knack for angering others.
Remember what I said earlier.
I told you to stay quiet.
Did you really punch him to avenge me?
I did not know you could punch people.
For me? Unbelievable.
Is your fist okay?
Was I that important to you?
To the point that you would want to avenge me?
How can you smile right now? Why are you leaving Oh Chun Gook alone? Report him to the police.
I'll take care of it.
This was always my dream. To have a brother who would punch someone who beat me up.
What a dream to have...
- It makes me want to call you brother.
- Stop it and go.
Then I should cling on more. You know how I am.
Why did you say we were living together?
No one would come if I said you were living with me.
You're really taking advantage of my image well.
I was even thinking of selling emojis of you.
"No. Go away. Get lost. Forget about it."
All of your lines are golden.
Yeah, Goo Hyun?
- Brother...
- What's wrong with your voice?
Mom said not to tell you but...
her back problem must be bothering her again.
Uncle said if she doesn't get surgery she may never walk again.
But Mom said that even if she dies, she won't have the surgery.
- What do I do?
- What do you mean?
Don't worry about it. Just study.
Okay.
Enjoy.
So Bin! You're here?
- What's the urgent matter?
- I don't have an appetite.
Even pineapple pizza doesn't taste good.
You called me out to say that? I'm going.
Whenever I think of you, there seems to be a huge hole in my heart.
At first, it was small so I didn't notice,
but now it's just gotten bigger.
Now it's this big.
It's just emptiness. You feel it when something you are used to is gone.
There's something I have to confess to you.
The day your mom left, she said this to me,
"Stay by my So Bin's side."
"Take care of all of the bad people who make So Bin miserable."
Why would she pressure a young child? When she couldn't even do it herself.
No.
I liked it. It felt like I became Superman.
I never once felt pressured.
I think I liked you.
And I still do.
It's too late Chan Ki.
I like someone else.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
I was too late.
[Beer]
Why did you suddenly ask me to drink first?
Because I thought I wouldn't be able to talk about this in my right mind.
Why? Do you need money?
No.
I, actually,
asked Soo Hyun for his number and got rejected.
I know.
You don't keep secrets from each other.
The thorn deep in your heart is Soo Hyun, right?
- I know.
- Even I know that you like Nam Soo Hyun.
- Was it obvious?
- A lot.
Even this beer would know just by looking at your eyes.
I'm going to tell him my feelings.
- Nam Soo Hyun?
- Yes.
I know I'll get rejected considering he didn't even give me his number,
but I can't give up.
Have you ever told him that you liked him?
Even if you like someone,
you might not be able to afford it.
It was like that for me.
Who?
You.
No.
I missed the right timing.
I...
don't know when the right timing is, and I'm just going to do it.
- I'm envious of that courage.
- Let's do this together. The confession.
What? You want us to do it together, holding hands or something?
- So that Nam Soo Hyun can choose?
- No, let's each do it separately.
I will feel sorry if I alone do it.
[Myungil University]
[Drop out form]
Nam Soo Hyun, is something wrong?
No.
What about somehow going through this semester and taking the next one off?
Will it get processed right away?
You need to fill that in, discuss it with Professor Park and get his approval.
All right.
Professor Park...
It's Brother's rich junior.
- We meet again.
- Yes.
Have you seen my brother?
He said his class ends around this time. He wouldn't allow me to come so I came here secretly.
He must be at his part-time job.
That school canteen job?
Yes. Let's go together then.
[Water]
It's Brother.
Will they eat together?
[Lounge for cooks]
You lived in this kind of place?
Why did you come here?
It's true.
- Let's go.
- I'm going to stop studying.
I came here to say that.
- What are you saying again?
- I have to earn money.
I can't look at you working hard alone.
Goo Hyun!
Do you think this will help me?
You live like this,
how can I sit and study properly?
Nam Goo Hyun, get it together!
I don't care about school.
Survival comes first. Both mom and you...
are my responsibility.
Don't act up and go.
♫ When the rain stops falling down my heart  ♫
- Excuse me.
- Sorry.
Can you talk to me for a moment?
I got the surgery money from Goo Hyun.
I'll convince your mom.
I'm sorry for not being a capable uncle.
You are doing a good job.
♫ All I need is you to be there for me ♫
Nam Goo Hyun.
Where did you get the surgery money?
I borrowed it from my friend.
Do you think you're the only one with a rich friend? Even I have a rich friend.
Who is your rich friend?
There is someone.
Did you perhaps...
meet Joon?
Tell me you didn't.
♫ Like the sun ♫
♫ You would always smile ♫
♫ for me ♫
♫ When the rain stops falling down my heart  ♫
[Yeo Joon]
♫ I just want to leave it all behind ♫
♫ Even when the world turns its back at me ♫
[Drop out form]
♫ All I need is you to be there for me ♫
Let's eat together.
I have some other engagement.
Ah, is that so?
How about tomorrow?
We have class tomorrow.
It's better not to go through hard times when we are young.
But in retrospect,
all those hard times become a part of your memories.
Let's get something to eat together sometime. I will buy you something nice.
Okay.
I said we could eat something you like.
I like this the most.
Is that so?
Can I talk about me?
Yes, tell me.
I took time off school thrice, during my undergraduate studies.
Because I didn't have money.
I didn't want to tell anyone.
I also didn't want to
trouble others more than that. I would have rather died.
Yes.
But this one person
called me out uselessly and
bought me food every day.
I managed to live those days
because of those meals.
Receiving help that I can't repay...
is painful.
Soo Hyun,
the situations change.
Now, it may seem impossible but
it was me who thought I was alone.
If you open your heart and accept help,
get help, and endure.
If you handle those times like that at least,
you will get the chance to
repay and succeed.
Contact me anytime.
I'll buy you food.
Thank you, Professor.
[Yeo Joon]
Come see me for a moment.
My mother's surgery fees,
did you give it to Goo Hyun?
Are you angry?
I'm really thankful, but don't do that next time.
I'll get the money that I need, whatever it takes.
I keep showing my worst to you.
You've seen me at my worst, too.
Why is it that things we don't want to show others,
are the only things we show each other?
I know, right?
Do you know what makes me the most miserable?
When you have no money...
and can't protect what's precious to you.
There are people who have money but have nothing precious to protect.
Aren't I pitiful?
Are we comparing misfortunes?
Well then,
let's talk about some happy things.
This place is nice.
Does misery have an end?
I am not too sure,
but it seems misery
does end one day.
Is your mother's state serious?
It was when she worked back when she was young.
She injured her back.
All of her life, it has been bothering her.
I hope the surgery goes well.
You, your mother, and your brother,
all seem to have a good relationship.
My mother says she hates me.
She says I am sly and two-faced.
And you?
Do you also think that way?
Didn't you also dislike me because of that?
You are not sly nor two-faced.
What?
The you your mom speaks of...
isn't you.
That's how she pictures you in her heart.
If someone is saying infernal things to you,
it's because their heart is in hell.
There's no reason for you to believe exactly what they say.
That's...
even if those are your parent's words.
I'm going.
Hyung...
You turned around.
Go safely.
Joon,
I never disliked you.
No one in that house wants to see you or misses you.
You have no family.
I have no family.
But...
I'm no longer sad.
♫ When everything was falling apart ♫
♫ The reason I was able to hold on ♫
♫ Was because you were standing at the end of this road ♫
Did you eat?
Yeah, I ate.
When are you going to sleep?
[D-1]
[Gong Mi Joo]
Good night.
How is it?
It's a good drawing.
Does it not remind you of anyone?
It's a real person?
It may not look like a person, but it is an actual person.
It's too perfect, right?
Is this drawing...
of Soo Hyun?
See! You can tell.
Yeah. You drew it well.
It has the same aura.
Right.
I consider this as a notice that I am going to confess.
You're going to confess?
Yeah. Tomorrow.
So Bin, help me a bit.
Soo Hyun,
do you have time tomorrow?
Next time?
No, let's meet tomorrow.
Why?
I have something to say to you.
There are three kinds of concentrated growth.
They are market penetration, market development, and product development.
Integrated growth is further divided into three things.
Backward, forward integration, and horizontal growth.
Senior, why are you so sleepy lately?
I picked up another job, so I'm a bit tired.
Senior, here are my notes.
I'll use them well.
I will give you the list of possible questions that can come on the final exam to you later.
You're okay, right?
- What?
- This is weird.
He isn't acting like Nam Soo Hyun. Why is he smiling?
What? It's nice to see.
Well, his character has changed too much.
Senior! To celebrate your change, I'll buy us a meal.
No.
Oh, he didn't change.
Is there no other method...
I'll...
treat you to a meal.
Yeah, a meal...
You should've chosen something nicer.
I don't know if I'll get the chance to treat you again.
What are you talking about? This is just the start.
I am going to slowly mooch off you.
Mi Joo, what brings you here?
I just felt like eating with you
and you were just here.
What's going on? You two are speaking in a similar way.
Is it because you're roommates?
Hello.
Yes.
You know Mi Joo is a drawing genius.
Show them the profile photo.
She's a genius, isn't she?
Yes. It's drawn well.
It's a portrait.
Is that me?
What? Why are you laughing?
What part was funny?
It looks just like me.
It doesn't look like you.
What? What's with this atmosphere?
Soo Hyun,
please spare me some time later.
The weather's nice today.
Do you have something to tell me?
I like you.
I'm sorry.
Are you rejecting me? In just three seconds?
I want to know the reason at least.
Someone, if not me, will like you.
Why not you?
I only need you. You are enough.
I am...
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who's sorry for liking you as I wished.
He should at least not look so handsome going around if he is not going to be mine.
I shouldn't have confessed.
I should have just had a one-sided love.
That stupid tarot card!
♫ When I open my eyes ♫
♫ The same day repeats every day ♫
♫ I stood alone in front of the mirror ♫
♫ and awkwardly smiled ♫
♫ Sometimes, I feel burdened when things get hard ♫
♫ When everything was falling apart ♫
You can't live here anymore. People find it uncomfortable.
♫ ...at the end of this road ♫
♫ When the rain stops falling on my heart  ♫
♫ I just want to leave it all behind ♫
♫ Even when the world turns its back at me ♫
♫ All I need is you to be there for me ♫
BA Major '21, try giving me a call.
Oh. I got it. Shall I call you now?
I was going to show you something nice.
Wait a moment.
Ah, I still didn't return this to him.
Found it.
[Calling- My Bin]
[Incoming call- My Joon]
Have I graduated from "BA Major '21"?
Cute.
But what was that diary? It didn't look like it was your type.
This?
This is Soo Hyun's death note.
(T/N: Death note: anime reference, a book where you write down the name of the people you want to kill)
Your name was also written here.
- Let me see.
- No. It's his secret information.
[It's all over now]
12th May is...
[1,000,000 won sent by Nam Soo Hyun.]
What is it?
Nothing.
Did I tell you I wanted to die?
You say that regularly? You don't even know what it feels like wanting to die.
My reality is shit.
You won't understand even if I die and come back to life.
I think I have to go somewhere now.
Where?
Can I tell you later?
Do you know when we actually feel pathetic?
When we can't protect
what is precious to us because we don't have money.
Senior.
I'm sorry.
People should live as they are because that is comfortable.
We return to our old self even if we try to change because our mind or body remembers who we were.
It's the same for me. Even if I am determined, I can't change.
Dad?
Dad.
I'm sorry.
For not being able to keep up the promise
that I will take care of
Mom and Goo Hyun.
Dad!
Senior!
Why did you switch your phone off? I looked around for you a lot.
Oh, I have to go.
Senior?
Shall we make the lie that I told
into the truth?
Let's live together.
You don't want to?
I'm sorry that I can't refuse your offer.
- Later, I will—
- Don't think about later and
live in the present.
Don't die.
♫ Ever since I met you, my eyes are full with you ♫
♫ One, two, three ♫
♫ Then show up here, please ♫
♫ Count to three and will you come to me? ♫
♫ Talk to me ♫
♫ On a beautiful sunny day ♫
♫ I'll come pick you up ♫
♫ Talk to me ♫
♫ Ever since I met you ♫
♫ My eyes are full with you ♫
ðŸŒ¿ [At a Distance, Spring is Green] ðŸƒ
- I think we will live well together.
- Are you sincere?
Is it about doing our own laundry?
Why did you do nothing about it all this while?
I'm traumatized by it, and I don't want to show you that side of me.
It's only natural for us to go unplanned as it is a youth trip.
Fold your finger if there's a girl you like.
I'm by your side. Don't forget.
Hey, Kim So Bin, why are so surprised? Am I a molester or something?
The thought that my memory could be wrong makes me feel scared.
Are you afraid of knowing the truth?
I want to know.