Sure.
[The number you have dialled is not available.]
[Please try again later.]
With all due respect,
it didn't work
your design
is not your usual level.
Patrick.
I remember it was in this area.
Where did it go?
Let me help you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
What a coincidence. We meet again.
I've been
for the past few months.
It's a probability that you bumped into me.
Really? You're a designer?
No, just purchasing.
Why? You seem upset.
No.
I'm looking for
a bronze glutinous silk.
I used to have it here.
I heard it was paid by a client today.
It won't be displayed anymore.
Do you mean
Is it the pure colour
It's very unique.
You know.
Let me ask
the demo of our company.
I think I've seen this before.
Wait.
I'll ask him for you, right?
Thank you.
We're in the same field. We should help each other.
Hey.
Press her down now.
I'll find you a picture
on the Internet.
I'll fix the code
and send it to you.
Is this okay?
Why not?
She's a rookie. She doesn't understand at all.
I can't tell.
I see. Okay.
How is it?
Take a look. Is it this one?
Oh.
Yes, this is it.
Do you have one in your company?
We have a demo.
I can give you the phone number of the vendor.
Just contact him.
Sure.
Let me write it down.
Write down his number.
Okay.
I remember their company
in an industrial park nearby.
You can go to him directly.
What a coincidence.
Okay, I'll call him right away.
Hello?
Hello.
Are you Mr. Yu?
Yes.
Hello.
I'm looking for a fabric.
Are you looking for the number?
Wait. I need to check the inventory.
Hold on.
Why is it gone?
Here.
It's here.
But it's not a coincidence now.
I'm at
Sunshine Plaza.
I'm here to visit my client.
You're here too.
What a coincidence.
Let me see.
I'll visit the client for half an hour.
In half an hour,
we'll meet at the cafe
at Sunshine Plaza.
Okay?
Okay.
Okay, bye.
My name card.
Ms Ding, this is mine.
Ms Ding.
Ms Ding has unique eyes.
Our material
just applied for an international patent.
and the real silk
more than 95 percent
more than 95 percent.
It's hard to detect
their differences.
Don't worry about the quality.
It's definitely top-class.
Of course quality is important.
But I care more about the price.
As for the price,
depends on the amount you want.
We have
5,000 meters, single price is 30.
Talk about 10,000 meters later.
Thirty.
It's almost like silk power spinning.
Mr. Yu, if I had the budget,
why would I buy
non-natural fabric?
Ms Ding.
Feel the texture of this material first.
Our material
is
the 23mm silk.
can be
more than 95%.
But the price is only half of it.
I think this cost-effective ratio...
I'll be blunt, Ms Ding.
You can't find
in Asia.
This is indeed a good thing.
But the price
at most,
at most.
23?
I'm afraid
this price.
Mr. Yu, as you know,
we are very strict
the purchase rights.
If the price doesn't work,
Unfortunately,
we can only work together next time.
Sorry.
Waiter, the bill please.
Ms Ding.
Wait.
I'll buy it.
Ms Ding, here's the thing.
We
know very well
in the industry.
I
sincerely hope
cooperate with May.
As for the price,
about the price.
Let me tell you the truth.
25.
25. It can't be lower.
Please have a seat.
But the price of 25
can't be exported from us.
We have a Hong Kong Brothers Company.
If they offer it,
the agent price will be higher
than ours.
But can the official smuggling work?
No problem. There's a refund.
The price there is cheaper than here.
It's normal.
As long as you agree,
I'll deal with my boss.
Okay.
As long as the price is good, the goods are the same.
we don't care which supplier.
I should hire someone
in May.
Ms Ding,
I guess you need
you need some typed rice samples.
I'll ask our Hong Kong Brothers Company
to send you some.
Are you sure? After that,
I'll ask my superior for a price.
Okay.
I want rice, silver gray, three meters each.
How long will it take?
Soonfeng mail,
Maybe the day after tomorrow.
I'll send it to your company's address.
What do you think?
Sure.
Happy cooperation, Ms Ding.
Happy cooperation.
Is this okay?
Remove the flowers and catch the wood.
Don't worry.
Have you forgotten what I used to do?
The company, position, and name are the same.
It was just a year ago.
Is it handsome?
I found a fabric dealer.
I think it can solve this problem.
What I just sent you is A4.
Tina, can you do it?
Hello, who is it?
Hello, it's me.
Oh.
What is it?
Seeing the dress you designed,
I like it.
Really? Thank you.
But we think
the cost of silk fabric you use is too high.
It may not be suitable for making clothes.
I've talked to Leo about that.
Eric is looking for
to replace the fabric.
Here's the thing.
I found a bronze droplets.
It's highly authentic and the price is good.
You can see
as a replacement.
Sure.
Where are you? I'll go find you now.
No need.
Tell me where you are.
I'll just give it to you.
You don't want to see me that much?
We'll still be friends.
That's what you said that day.
Don't get me wrong.
I've been tired lately.
I finally got some rest.
You don't have to come here.
I just left the studio.
It's on the motorcycle. It's not troublesome at all.
Forget it.
I don't know when
when I can go back.
I'll contact you later.
Ding Yike.
Why are you always so awkward?
Is it fun?
What's wrong with meeting?
I'm going to eat you.
Who's uncomfortable? Don't button your hat.
I'm at the Fabrics Library.
It'll take more than an hour.
I'll give you two choices.
You either stay where you are
Wait for me to pick you up.
or I'll wait for you at a distance.
Zhao Moyuan.
Can you stop being so bossy?
You're the bossy one.
When we were together,
together.
When we broke up,
you said it alone?
You pretended to be rational.
You're the one who broke up.
Do you have evidence?
I sent that message.
But I sent it by mistake.
I sent it and withdrew it.
Zhao Moyuan, you are a rascal.
You're the rogue.
Hello?
Zhao Moyuan.
Who else?
Calm down.
Hello, Qian. Where are you?
Moyuan, Moyuan may have had a car accident.
I don't know.
He said
It's near the studio.
Okay.
Excuse me.
there is a patient called Zhao Moyuan today.
Which room is he in?
Let me check.
Please hurry.
732.
732. Okay.
You're here.
How did it go?
It flew a dozen meters away. What do you think?
I hope it's nothing serious now.
We don't know when he'll wake up.
When he wakes up,
ask him and the doctor yourself.
By the way, I'm going to pay the bill.
Watch out for me.
Okay, go ahead.
Zhao Moyuan.
Get up!
Aren't you that great?
Aren't you so overbearing?
Get up and fight with me.
We haven't finished talking.
Why are you lying down like this?
What about your Partric series?
What about Leo?
What should I do?
Zhao Moyuan.
Mo Yuan.
Zhao Moyuan!
Wake up!
Wake up, Zhao Moyuan.
You have to wake up.
I'll promise you anything, okay?
You said that.
You're so pretty.
No.
You're awake.
I'm awake.
Of course I am.
You're crying and making a scene.
rubbing and rubbing. How can I not wake up?
You can move.
Of course I can.
What? You want me to stay still?
Do you think I'm disabled
or a vegetative?
I told you to watch less dramas.
Come on, help me.
Well,
Didn't Qian say you don't know
when will you wake up?
Yes, I flew over ten meters away.
Where did you get hurt?
I'm seriously injured.
Look.
My left leg is fractured.
Isn't it amazing?
It hurts when you put the clapper on.
I asked
a nurse
that painkiller.
Then I fell asleep.
Qian definitely didn't know
when I woke up, right?
I'm thirsty now. I want some water.
I'm not going.
I want water.
You colluded with Qian to lie to me. I'm seriously injured.
You want me to get you some water? Can you pour me a glass?
I'm not going.
Then go.
I don't need you anymore.
Fine.
Don't you dare say that again.
The door is still open. Be careful.
Well...
He's fine.
I'm leaving.
You...
Keep your promise.
Can you still write?
No. What?
Okay.
Hey.
What now?
You...you...
Didn't you say
you wanted to show me some fabric?
Where is it?
Fee.
What are you doing here?
You're so dead.
Can you come in later?
Do you want to explode you right here?
Hey.
Hello, aunt.
Excuse me.
have you seen
such a big cow paper?
I didn't see it.
Hello, nurse.
Have you seen
such a big cow paper?
No.
Please think again.
I just arrived here.
I didn't see it.
Yes, a black car.
The last number is 0806.
According to his accent,
He doesn't look like a local.
We can only try our best to find him.
We're expecting to inform you
in 48 hours.
It takes 48 hours.
That long?
I have no choice.
Can you hurry up?
We'll do it as soon as possible, okay?
Okay.
Let me know if you have any news.
Thank you.
Ding Yike.
Why did you come down?
Go upstairs.
How can I ignore you?
What if it gets serious?
Why don't we sit down and talk?
No need.
There are no demos in the fabric library.
Fabrics send me rice samples.
I think they will arrive next Monday.
It's okay. We can make it next Monday.
Please send her home.
Okay?
And tell Xu Fei
I'm fine. Don't worry.
Don't bother Qian.
I can go back myself.
Just listen to me.
Losing bags and fabrics.
When did you lose yourself?
Didn't you say
if you don't want to pour me water here,
then leave here.
Don't get in my way.
Excuse me.
Let me help you.
No, I can go back myself.
Send it back right away. Thank you.
Let's go.
Boss, calm down.
He
just broke his toe.
Yes.
He has found someone for the sample.
Yes. Fortunately, the samples are ready.
It should be fine.
Okay.
Okay, no problem.
Bye.
What happened?
Nothing.
He can still be alive.
and yell at me.
That's great.
Don't blame me for lying to you.
It’s Moyuan’s idea.
I know. He's a bad guy.
Yes, he's a bad guy.
Anyway,
if he didn't really like you,
why did he do that?
Normally,
it's not up to me
to persuade
to persuade me.
However,
I've seen you two
walking all the way.
So,
I'm just trying to look old and nag.
When these two
When they're angry,
you can say 10,000 times you break up.
When you calm down,
I can really leave and leave.
That's the end.
Otherwise, just recognize one word.
Coward.
Listen to your heart.
Follow your heart.
and walk around.
After all,
no one is perfect.
As long as they are safe,
what are they doing?
Am I right?
Coco.
What happened to my prince charming?
Qian left before he finished.
You didn't answer my call.
I dare not leave the shop and go to the hospital.
What do you want?
My phone is dead.
Don't worry.
He's fine.
He just broke his toe.
He'll be discharged in two or three days.
Are you lying to me?
Why would I lie to you?
Where are you going?
I'm going to buy some trotters for him.
Chicken feet.
It's good for your health.
You two made up?
Kids, mind your own business.
Let's go.
Why are you making a fuss?
I'm still a patient. Don't scare me.
How did you get in?
The spare key you left with me.
But you can't
come to my house without permission.
Come on.
Xu Fei said
you went to buy groceries for me.
I have to hurry back.
I have to eat.
You don't welcome me, do you?
Fine.
I'll leave if you don't welcome me.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Let's stop it.
Let's make up.
Okay.
Go cook.
Zhao Moyuan.
I haven't eaten anything
I haven't eaten anything.
I'm so hungry.
I have snacks here. I'll get some for you.
I don't want sweet food.
I'll make noodles for you.
Soon.
The pain reliever is over. It hurts.
Does it still hurt?
Let me get you some medicine.
I think I have painkillers.
If it hurts so much,
Why are you discharged so early?
Because of you.
Because I want to see you all the time.
You're amazing.
We break up every time we fight.
I have to get discharged.
I'm telling you this.
You like
a boyfriend like me.
How can you fall in love with someone else?
Right?
If I hadn't apologized to you in advance,
and give in.
If you really break up with me,
you might not be able to find your boyfriend.
What's wrong?
Are you unhappy again?
I'd rather never get married
than let you scare me again.
I just broke my toes.
I can walk.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I won't scare you anymore.
I made you worry.
I'm the one who should apologize.
Let me say it again.
Leo is important to me,
but she's just my senior.
You are my girlfriend.
I don't love you
I don't love you enough.
I just didn't realize
you have taken over my life.
everywhere.
So you can't leave me.
You can't leave me.
You have to be responsible for me.
Okay?
Leo's old name was Lam.
Olin.
When she took her master's degree in literature,
I didn't go to school.
But at that time,
I already knew
she was a rising star.
When everyone is by her side,
will become a supporting role.
She's very good at
and cutting.
It's only been four years in London,
in London for four years.
of the United Fashion Designer Association.
At that time, no one suspected
she would be the next.
Alexander McKun.
or Kawakubo Reinence.
But at her most glorious moment,
her boyfriend
jumped out and said she imitated herself.
Many people are jealous of her.
took the chance to kick her when she was down.
So in an instant,
all praise became doubts.
Even the school
her annual design suspected of plagiarism
to drop out of school.
I don't believe
she would imitate others.
Because I've seen her
from freshman to senior year.
Her design concept
matured little by little.
Later I found out
It turns out
he wanted to make Leo's design
as his own.
Leo firmly disagreed.
He even wanted to break up.
So he got angry.
The villain complained first.
A few years later,
I got
the American Fashion Designer Association.
Since then,
I've been looking for Leo.
I wanted to help her clear her name.
I want her to stand on the TV again.
But she disappeared completely.
She disappeared in the design industry.
I don't want to give up.
This kind of search becomes obsession.
It even affected my emotional choice.
For a long time,
I liked the girls
Leo's personality.
But don't worry.
They were the ones who pursued me.
A proud man like me
never pursued anyone.
It's you.
Let me ask you.
Before me,
how many ex-girlfriends do you have?
Enough, stop ordering.
I'm asking for trouble.
Mr. Patrick Cho.
He's famous at a young age and he's a shooter.
There's no one around him without a girlfriend.
Even the president's daughter
fell under your jeans.
Don't be jealous of me.
I've received
the punishment of God.
I wanted to avenge Leo.
And then?
my ex-girlfriend
was stolen by my ex-girlfriend.
And she published my work
to publish my work.
That’s not enough?
She joined hands with Shen Jin
and kicked me out of the shop.
What is this?
Shen Jin has no conscience
He may have some conscience
but he has no taste.
He really believes that I want to steal it.
He won't believe me no matter how I explain it.
But I can understand that
he had a crush on my ex-girlfriend.
What does Leo mean to me?
In his heart,
in his heart.
Alright.
I already told you
I told you everything.
Now I know.
why I didn't tell you
about Leo?
First, it involves my privacy.
Second,
My ex-girlfriend cheated on me.
It's really embarrassing.
Thank you for your trust.
I'll keep it a secret for you.
So you still care about
between me and Leo?
No.
Being jealous of his idol with a stupid fan
to be jealous of his idol.
What do you mean?
What?
Am I wrong?
What you did to Leo
are different from
from those fanatic fans?
Dumb fan. Dumb fan.
This...
A crazy fan.
All right.
I'll understand and support you.
I'll make your collaboration a success.
Because I like Leo too.
I want to see her too.
shining brightly.
Hello?
I have another request.
Can you stop
come here again?
We...
I just want you and me.
If he comes again,
I'll be very sad.
Do you know
Last time at the door,
I saw you hugging him from behind.
My heart was about to stop beating.
Okay.
I told him not to come last time.
He and I...
between me and him.
And that day,
I was really giving him an emergency.
Emergency.
You can do it.
I told you to hold him from behind.
If you need an emergency,
I want to go in shock right now.
Since last time...
my heart still hurts.
I also need
artificial respiration.
Morning.
Have you eaten?
Yes.
Morning.
Good morning.
You're wearing peach blossoms.
Looks like you've turned calamities into blessings.
I'm in a good mood.
You should treat us to dinner.
Internet celebrity bread or milk tea
Both are good.
So this afternoon,
can you
with me again?
No.
We've discussed with the boss.
I'll do my best to
to receive Linda.
When she approves the budget,
after she approves the budget.
We...
How is your husband now?
Linda will come tomorrow.
Can he sit in a wheelchair?
Don't curse him.
He's recovering well.
He just walks slowly. He doesn't need a wheelchair.
By the way,
keep an eye on
from Hong Kong these days.
It's the rice sam from the fabric dealer.
Now you know how to order people.
If the replacement fabric is approved,
the cost will be saved.
You'll get a bonus.
We're at the studio. Don't worry.
I found the latest new series manuscript.
Look who he looks like.
Leo inspired me before.
And now my muse
has changed to a fat girl with short hair.
That's all.
There's no Fei Fei at all.
Go back. Don't be tired.
I'll take care of the rest.
I'm not tired.
I'll help you finish this.
Didn't you say
you must give a satisfactory design
a satisfactory design?
Seeing you two working so hard,
I feel a little uneasy.
I think after this job,
if I don't send you
to Dubai for half a month,
Do I feel guilty?
I think Partrick's foot is broken,
but he's in a good mood.
Didn't you see
who sent him this morning.
Who?
It's okay. It's okay if you miss it today.
When you reach May tomorrow,
you'll see it.
Look at you. I feel embarrassed.
Look at this.
Where should I change it?
A little bit here.
How is it?
Pretty enough. Be confident.
He's just the vice president of a group.
He's not the president of any country.
Dating the first family.
Of course I don't have a famous designer.
as a famous designer.
What a nice day today.
Actually, I'm worried about you.
I heard Linda is quite picky.
Their lord
is the one
in the same group.
They told me last night
because their lights
the color temperature was wrong,
Linda criticized them.
Half an hour.
What are you afraid of?
As long as she's not blind,
she will be conquered by my design.
Arrogant.
Okay, I'll pick her up at the hotel.
See you in the office.
Watch your feet when you walk.
Slow down.
Bye.
Okay, bye.
This is it, right?
Yes.
Let's wait here.
Okay.
I heard she has a bad temper.
She's just strict.