(Back From The Brink)
Watch on kisskh.co
(Episode 27)
The long river falls as trouble arises.
(Calm your heart and stop worrying. Understand the underlying meaning.)
(Ponder upon its logic.)
(Move your brain, and you feel dizzy.)
(Only then, you shall see two.)
The long river falls as trouble arises.
Five hearts facing the sky, lying underneath the lake.
Calm your heart and stop worrying. Understand the underlying meaning.
Do you think Chenyi can save you?
Entering one's mind with one's eye.
Do you think you can replace me
just by practicing my techniques?
Only then, you shall see two.
Ponder upon its logic.
Move your brain, and you feel dizzy.
Do you think you can master my techniques
after acquiring the Ghostly Eulogy?
Stop dreaming.
You will only obtain immortality if you submit to me.
Yanhui, my pawn, heed my command!
Tianyao, just go!
Yanhui!
Just go!
You...
Go!
(Rip out his Heart Protecting Scale.)
Tianyao, go!
Just go!
Yanhui?
(Rip out his Heart Protecting Scale.)
(Rip out his Heart Protecting Scale!)
(Heart Protecting Scale!)
Just go!
Destroy the dark flower!
(You'll die if he destroys the dark flower.)
(I won't let you die.)
Destroy it!
Yanhui?
Tianyao,
you did great just now.
You should've been that decisive from the start.
Now that the dark flower is gone,
I won't be able to survive for long.
However,
I don't fear death.
Compared to the days when I had to wait for my demise,
I don't feel sad at all.
Tianyao,
why do you look sadder
than me?
Yanhui,
you will live on.
Tianyao!
What's wrong?
Yanhui,
don't be afraid.
You'll be fine.
You'll live on.
You saved me many times
ever since our first encounter.
If I can exchange my life
for yours,
it'll be a dream come true for me.
Is this the Life-Swapping Spell?
The nine stars.
Yinghuo said
someone was willing to sacrifice their lives
to preserve mine.
So, she was referring to you!
(Yanhui, )
(I'll return the Nine Stars of mind's eye to you.)
(They'll preserve your life for me.)
Yanhui,
I hope that you can lead
a peaceful life
after I retrieve my body.
So, back then,
you knew I wouldn't die!
You risked your own life
to fight Suying!
Why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I was afraid that you might not be willing to accept it.
Tianyao?
Tianyao!
Yanhui.
There's nothing to fear about death.
There's truly nothing to fear about death.
I'm not upset at all.
How could you not be upset about it?
I don't want this!
In the future,
you can lead
the life you want to lead.
You can have all the buns you like.
You can go wherever you like.
Tianyao!
Why did you do it so quickly?
Tianyao, why did you do it
without any hesitations?
Only by destroying the flower
was I able
to receive
your current embrace.
You...
Stop blaming me.
Stop blaming me, okay?
Tianyao, I won't blame you at all.
I won't blame you.
Don't leave me!
I still wish to have delicious buns
together with you!
I still wish to go...
Tianyao! I know my fault now! Don't leave me behind!
Tianyao!
(Ghostly Eulogy)
(Tianyao, you mustn't destroy the dark flower!)
(You mustn't destroy the dark flower!)
(Yanhui.)
(I'm waiting for you.)
Tianyao!
The flower...
The flower is gone.
Tianyao!
Tianyao is gone too.
Yanhui.
Tianyao?
Tianyao!
I...
I truly fancy you!
I fancy you a lot!
I fell for you before you ripped out
the Heart Protecting Scale from my heart.
After you ripped it out,
although I was afraid of you,
I still fancied you a lot!
Ever since you brought me
out of the Royal Palace of Qingqiu, I knew
that I'd helplessly
fallen in love with you!
However,
I can never tell you that in person anymore.
What should I do?
This is just a dream.
You can never hear
my confession again.
Will you disappear
once I wake up?
I don't want to wake up!
This isn't a dream.
We're in a dream.
Why are you still lying to me?
I'm truly fine.
Are you done crying?
If so, it's time to apply the ointment to your wound.
Why are you in my dream as well?
You don't recognize me?
It's only been a few days since we last met each other.
My goodness.
What are you doing?
Isn't it cold?
Wait, this isn't a dream?
It really isn't.
Yanhui!
That hurts.
This is great.
This is great!
This is great! You're still alive!
I'm sorry.
I've made you worry.
He is alive,
but if you don't apply
the ointment right now,
your hair
might not be able to live.
My hair?
Where did my hair go?
Maybe my Dragon Flame
burnt a part of your hair
when I destroyed the dark aura.
Will love disappear?
It won't.
It definitely will.
Is this ointment even useful?
Chenyi made this himself.
Let's give it a try first.
Apply a bit more on my head.
Of course.
After all, I think
none of us
has any experience going bald, right?
When did you get here?
Oh, come on.
If I wasn't here to save the day,
the Heart Protecting Scale couldn't even return to your body.
The Heart Protecting Scale?
Did it return to my body again?
The dark flower on your head was already destroyed.
That's how the Heart Protecting Scale could return to you.
You made it as if it was a life-and-death struggle.
Indeed.
I'm still better
at doing such things.
Oh yeah, that works too.
Who else in this world
do you think can possess
both beauty
and brain?
The Heart Protecting Scale is inside your body.
If other people find out,
I'm afraid
it'll spell trouble for you.
Before this, I didn't know about
your feelings for me.
That's so mushy.
It's best
if I could exchange my life
for your life in peace.
You...
Shouldn't I be the person
you two should be thankful for?
I flew across the vast sea
and rushed back
in order to save you guys.
All right then. Thank you.
Thank you.
In the end, I still have
to become your matchmaker.
What did you discover when you gave him
the Ghostly Eulogy?
I discovered
the truth.
(He locked me in a water prison.)
(I discovered remnants of his memories)
(when I was trapped underwater in the Dark Phantom Palace.)
(I could see my past)
(from his memories.)
-You crossbreed! -You crossbreed!
What are you doing?
-Get up, crossbreed. -You crossbreed.
You're a crossbreed!
Get up!
You crossbreed!
That hurts!
Let me go!
You crossbreed!
This child is gifted.
He can control his shadow at such a young age.
In time,
he can defeat you without any problem, Elder.
Only the strongest person in our clan can be the clan leader.
It's the survival of the fittest.
Now that the Shadow Clan has given birth to a gifted child like him,
Elder Yingcheng, I don't know
if I should be happy
or sad for you.
Bai Xiaosheng
is the evil child stated in the prophecy.
If he can bully his playmates today,
he can definitely slaughter our village in the future.
If so...
If so, I'll send him somewhere far away.
That won't do.
The Shadow Clan can only avoid calamity
if we offer him to our lord as a sacrifice.
Mother.
Mother?
Sheng.
Mother.
Mother, what's the matter?
Let me go!
A shadow spirit can isolate their body
from all things in the world.
In order to prevent himself from getting injured by foreign objects,
(he used my true effigy)
(to create a shadow robe.)
He was jealous of my talent.
With this shadow robe,
I can restore my body.
And I won't need to worry about
any external injuries again.
(It seems that Dark Phantom was hurt)
(by a master before.)
(He was afraid of his reappearance.)
(That's why he needed)
(the shadow robe)
(to protect himself.)
(It's a shame that I couldn't see that part of his memory.)
(I didn't know)
(who injured him in the past.)
I did disperse a cloud of dark aura
in the Dragon Valley 20 years ago.
But I didn't know who it was.
I don't know if he was the one I'd injured.
Right now, Dark Phantom
still has your true effigy.
If you come here to see us,
that means he can harm you easily.
He has other plans for me.
If my true effigy perishes,
he will be in trouble too.
However, I can actually
do something to him.
Do what?
I'll seek revenge.
What else do you think I'm going to do?
(It's all thanks to the shadow robe.)
(If not, what happened 20 years ago)
(will happen again.)
(A Millennium Spirit Dragon?)
(If I can extract its inner core and use it to boost my strength, )
(in the future, )
(no Taoist spirit can harm me again.)
(That dark aura seemed strange.)
(What exactly was it?)
The flame of the Spirit Dragon.
Changlan.
My Lord.
When can you initiate a war between the Taoists and spirits
for Sanchong Mountain?
The beings of Qingqiu
are all under my spell.
As for Chenxing Mountain's Lingfei,
initially, I wanted to kill her in Qingqiu
to initiate a conflict between the two realms.
But now that I think about it,
I think it's more useful
to keep her alive.
When she returns to her clan,
it'll be the beginning
of the war.
Very good.
You're far superior to Bai Xiaosheng.
My Lord,
regarding Bai Xiaosheng,
I'm afraid he has turned on you.
It doesn't matter.
Just leave him be.
You do look
exactly like Changlan.
You look different
from what Changlan
had described to me.
Let me do it.
He imprisoned you for many years,
yet he mentioned me in front of you?
Sometimes, when he holds a discussion with Zhao Yu,
he'll bring up your name.
When my mind's eye was still clear,
I heard of you.
I guess he said nothing good about me.
Your Majesty,
I came here
because I want to ask you something.
What is it?
I saw you
inside Dark Phantom's mind's eye.
Your Majesty, I wish to know
how exactly
you sealed him away.
Actually,
I didn't seal him away
with my powers alone.
And
he wasn't sealed away
in his mind's eye.
He was sealed within the body
of Master Qingguang of Chenxing Mountain.
Master Qingguang?
He's the founder of my sect.
I thought he was on retreat
in Starhaven?
Back then, in order to stop Dark Phantom
who was causing chaos everywhere,
Xuelin practiced Ghostly Eulogy by herself.
She intended to make herself
the Lord of Dark Aura
and swallow Dark Phantom.
(She intended to end her life)
(at the Obsidian Riverhead after swallowing Dark Phantom.)
(However, Xuelin wasn't able)
(to master the Ghostly Eulogy.)
(Her body was ruined instead.)
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Take a sip of this.
(But Dark Phantom kept committing atrocious deeds.)
(We couldn't just allow him to get his way.)
(To Qingguang) (She wrote a letter to Qingguang)
(requesting his help.)
(She intended to seal Dark Phantom away)
(with our combined powers.)
(I prepared a trap in the vast desert.)
(Xuelin built the geomantic compass to absorb the dark aura)
(while Qingguang reinforced my trap.)
Xuelin.
It's been a century since we last met.
You've summoned me again.
Is it because you're willing to return to my side?
Dark Phantom, your dark aura is running rampant.
Innocent people have been hurt.
I can't just let you
keep this up.
I haven't found a way
to disperse the dark aura.
Now,
I can only seal you away temporarily.
Xuelin,
you lied to me!
Xuelin.
I didn't expect you to call me here
just to seal me away!
You lied to me!
Xuelin!
Polars of Qiankun!
So, the vision I saw
when I was inside the geomantic compass was...
Qingguang
used his body as a vessel
to seal Dark Phantom away.
And the injuries
Xuelin had sustained back then
exhausted her life force entirely.
After she passed away,
I followed her wish
and sealed the Ghostly Eulogy
within the screen.
However, even when she was on her last breath,
she still couldn't figure out
how to get rid of the dark aura.
She only knew
that one could manipulate the dark aura and cause it to implode
if one mastered the Ghostly Eulogy.
As for Qingguang,
once he returned to Chenxing Mountain,
he focused all of his efforts
to suppress Dark Phantom, which was in his body.
Twenty years later,
I found out
that he had sealed himself away completely.
He sealed himself within Starhaven.
I assume this has something to do
with Dark Phantom.
So Lingxiao
visited Starhaven every year
in order to help Master Qingguang reinforce his seal.
All these years,
I've been trying to find a way
to get rid of the dark aura.
After fifteen years,
I finally invented
a spell
that could curb the dark aura.
However, I never expected Changlan
to become Dark Phantom's follower.
He even mastered visual spells.
Fifteen years ago?
Wasn't that the year
Changlan offered the Phantom Clan to Dark Phantom as a sacrifice
and opened a portal
to Dark Phantom's mind's eye?
Fifteen years ago.
When Dark Phantom was trapped
within Starhaven,
I regained freedom
temporarily.
Back then,
I tried to search for him in his mind's eye.
However, I never found him.
Until fifteen years ago,
he suddenly returned
and told me to meet our new ally.
His name was Changlan.
This useless twin son
was actually his hope
of turning the tides.
Your Majesty,
didn't the brush sprite say
that the second twin son of the royalty of Qingqiu
should be
imprisoned?
So, how did he manage to escape?
Also, how did he
end up being
Dark Phantom's trusted aide?
Regarding that, we need to talk about
what happened long ago.
Although we were twins,
I never knew about
his existence
for many years.
After that, when the late king passed away,
Zhao Yu told me
that he couldn't bear to see Changlan suffer any longer.
Only then did I find out
that I had a younger brother.
Back then,
Xuelin and I just got married.
After our discussion,
we decided
to release Changlan
from the dungeon forever.
But he told me
that he didn't want to stay in Qingqiu.
I could understand why.
Thus, I allowed him to leave.
After that, I found out
that he had gone to Luochuan Dragon Valley
and had been living there.
I heard that he had a good life when he was living in the valley.
If so, how did he
end up like this?
Speaking of which, he could be considered an old friend of yours.
Why did he attack you too?
Changlan,
when he first came to Luochuan Dragon Valley,
he wasn't someone who would do something terrible like this.
My Flaming Dragon Fang
contained his blessings too.
Could it be
that you met Suying at the time?
Back then,
he did tell me
not to trust Suying easily.
But I didn't listen to him.
He might have left the valley
out of disappointment.
After that,
we never met each other again.
No matter
what he became after that,
right now, he's trying
to collect
violent and evil aura in the world
to make him stronger.
Violent and evil aura?
What is that? How does one collect it?
By leading people to commit evil deeds and initiate wars.
If we wish to stop Dark Phantom
from returning to this world,
our first step
is to stop Changlan.
If so, we need to return to
the Royal Palace of Qingqiu immediately.
Now that I think about it,
everything Changlan did
was aimed at initiating the war
between the Taoists and spirits
so that he could set the Lord of Dark Aura free.
We have to bring His Majesty
back to Qingqiu
to expose his evil plots.
Lingfei said Changlan wanted to assassinate her.
Once she returns to her base,
she'll definitely gather her troops and prepare for battle.
A disaster is coming.
And the Heart Protecting Scale
just returned to your body.
You still need to rest and recuperate.
You need to rest and recuperate too.
Elder Lingfei!
What are you laughing at?
You look pretty funny
in that getup.
Actually, it hasn't been too long
since I left.
However, I was thinking about you
all the time.
I've truly
fallen for you.
What about you?
Did you miss me?
I wouldn't have fallen for you
had I known you were this heartless back then.
Bai Xiaosheng...
Are you sure you don't want to consider me at all?
No.
Fine. I admit.
Tianyao
is pretty good.
You can come to me anytime
once you guys have broken up.
I'll definitely reserve a spot
for you.
It's getting late.
You should head back and rest.
No thanks.
I'm here to bid farewell.
Bid farewell? Won't you come with us
to the Royal Palace of Qingqiu?
I'm going
to seal away the entrance
to Dark Phantom's mind's eye
and stop him from contacting Changlan.
By then, it'll be easier
for you guys to deal with Changlan
in Qingqiu.
Are you heading there alone?
Nope, there are two of us.
Two?
It's me
and you, which I keep in my heart.
It's getting late.
I won't waste your time.
See you.
That was quick.
Yanhui.
Tianyao!
I made you a tiara.
I wonder if you like it.
It's so nice.
This tiara
can cover the bald spot on my head.
I like it!
Let me help you put it on then.
These eyes of mine,
which have seen through countless relationships,
have never failed me indeed.
Tianyao,
within the Taoist clan...
Only husbands
can comb the hair of their wives, right?
If so, you...
We are married, aren't we?
We notified our kin
when we were in Tongluo Village.
We announced our marriage to the world
in the main hall of Qingqiu.
Yanhui,
do you know something?
You were already my wife
when I gave you the nuptial agreement.
If so, you better keep your word.
I will.
I put my seal on it.
It's decided for life then.
See you.