♪At dawn♪
♪I open my eyes♪
♪At long last, the night is past♪
♪The story has ended♪
♪If someone ever asks the question♪
♪I'll say I never regret it♪
♪Where I touch you♪
♪Is marked with the trace of our entanglement♪
♪Goodbye is not farewell♪
♪Why always focus on results?♪
♪In an instant, my longing for you♪
♪Spilled to the horizon♪
♪The barren land is singing♪
♪The ground is remaining silent♪
♪Light penetrates the sea♪
♪Flowers bloom among the dust♪
♪The mayfly gazes upon the sky♪
♪Swearing to pursue the light♪
♪My soul is searching♪
♪For the time rift♪
♪And you♪
[Back From The Brink]
[Adapted from the novel of the same name
in jjwxc.net by Jiu Lu Fei Xiang]
[Episode 38]
(Are you okay?)
Are you okay?
Why are you hurt?
Xuelin,
who am I?
Why do I have no parents?
Why does everyone fear me?
You were born
out of chaos.
They fear you because they don't know you.
You don't need to fear.
Do you fear me then?
Why should I fear you
when you work hard on your cultivation
and not hurt people or commit evil deeds?
Look.
I found this puppy
when I went out today.
Just like you,
it's still a child.
You guys should look after each other
in the future,
okay?
I'll get you something to eat.
Wait here for me.
Okay.
Only I can
receive her attention.
Where's the puppy?
I took a nap just now.
The puppy disappeared when I woke up.
I'll look for it then.
Xuelin,
forget about it.
I'm sure it left of its own accord.
Just let me follow you in the future.
Xuelin,
when will I
be cured?
Soon.
Member of Chenxing Mountain,
why did you invade Qingqiu?
I'm here to save people.
I don't desire to go against Qingqiu.
I'll leave this place
once I find a cure for him.
You wish to save someone?
I'll help you.
If you wish the two realms to bury the hatchet,
I'll help you do that.
We still have a long way to go in life.
Are you willing to join me?
Xuelin,
don't blame me for this.
You...
How could you hurt him?
You abandoned me first!
You're studying my techniques.
I know.
You're just like the others.
All of you want to harm me!
Are you all right?
You like him?
You like Qingqiu?
You cannot do so.
You can only stay by my side!
(His dark aura has infected many people.)
(It's all my fault.)
(The dark aura is the source of extreme evil.)
(The world can only be at peace)
(after it's eradicated.)
(There's no way to eradicate it at the moment.)
(I hope our descendants can find a way
to resolve this issue.)
(People will deceive me,)
(hurt me, and betray me.)
(Only I can)
(protect myself.)
(I want this world to submit to me)
(and obey my order!)
(I am the king!)
Tianyao.
(The Millennium Spirit Dragon?)
(If I can boost my power with its inner core,)
(no Taoist or spirit)
(can hurt me again.)
This shadow spirit is gifted.
It can form objects by manipulating shadows.
Maybe,
I can use him to repair my body,
which was hurt by the dragon scent.
The leader of the Shadow Clan
was always the strongest of the bunch.
Now, the Shadow Clan has a gifted child like him.
Elder Yingcheng,
I don't know if I should be happy
or worried for you.
Bai Xiaosheng
is the evil child stated in the prophecy.
If he can bully his peers today,
he can
slaughter the entire Shadow Clan tomorrow.
We can only avoid this calamity
by offering him to our lord.
Mother.
Mother, what's the matter?
(Stop.)
(Dark Phantom, stop!)
Xuelin?
You've summoned me again
after a century.
Are you willing to stay by my side?
Xuelin!
You lied to me!
(You think you can keep me in check?)
If I can control this body,
I might be able to achieve
what I couldn't achieve before.
My current priority
is to kill
the dragon that can hurt me.
This battle is very vital.
We must take down
all monsters.
Yes, sir.
And
from now on,
all of you
must stay alert.
Do not...
General!
General Lu!
Go get Master Suying!
Hurry!
Go now!
[Wangshu Manor]
Master Qingguang, this is a sudden visit.
Is there anything important?
Master Suying, I heard that you traveled
all around the world
just
to find a certain herb
for Mr. Lu.
However, no matter
how effective the herb is,
it cannot
save the life of a normal civilian.
Master, do you have a way to save him?
The dragon-scale armor is impregnable.
It can even
delay time itself.
Are you referring
to the Millennium Evil Dragon
in Luochuan Dragon Valley?
(The evil dragon is extremely powerful,)
(but he's as naive as a child.)
(You can trick him into falling in love with you)
(and gain his trust.)
(After that, you can strike him down)
(when he lets down his guard)
(during the wedding.)
I will use your dragon scales
to create a suit of armor
and protect my true lover.
I will assist you in secret.
Forget about me.
Qingguang.
The evil dragon is seriously wounded.
Hurry! Harvest his scales
and extract his inner core!
(You old geezer,)
(don't spoil my plan!)
(You brought chaos upon the world with my body.)
(Luckily, the dragon fire woke me up
from my slumber.)
(I will seal you away again!)
Master?
Lingxiao,
pay attention to the seal
in Starhaven constantly.
Remember to come here
on the same day every year
and assist me
in strengthening the seal.
Yes, Master.
You were
the cause of everything.
You were the source
of everyone's tragedy.
You should feel lucky
that your tragedy
will end here.
You practiced my techniques
and filled your body with the dark aura.
People in the world
will only fear you.
Why don't you submit to me?
In your dreams!
Dragon King, since you know
where Yanhui is,
why are you still pulling a long face?
Naturally, he's fretting about how to save her.
The entrance to Dark Phantom's mind's eye
is always well hidden.
The entrance at Misty Forest
vanished long ago.
Now,
getting into Dark Phantom's mind's eye
is an ordeal.
What should we do then?
We can't just sit idly by.
Starhaven
is directly connected
to Dark Phantom's mind's eye.
But...
Will Master Lingxiao
let you break the seal in Starhaven?
If Dark Phantom escapes during the chaos,
we'll be in deep trouble.
Lingxiao will aid us
if I promise to deal a huge blow to Dark Phantom.
Your presence counters the dark aura.
It's easy if you're just
dealing with Dark Phantom here.
However,
Yanhui and Dark Phantom are in the same place now.
What if you hurt her by accident?
Shadow spirits can isolate their bodies
from all things in the world.
To prevent himself from getting injured
by foreign objects,
he used my true effigy
to create a shadow robe.
Then when you're here with us,
he can harm you easily.
He has other plans for me.
If my true effigy perishes,
he will be in trouble too.
Do you know where Bai Xiaosheng is?
Yanhui tried
to locate him too.
He's in the Misty Forest.
Dragon King!
Repair the shrine
and collect the dark aura.
[Dark Phantom Shrine]
Repair the shrine
and collect the dark aura.
The dark aura is controllable.
You were led astray by your selfish desires.
But now, you're blaming it
on the dark aura?
How ridiculous.
The dark aura only exists
because of the greed of humans.
It's the malicious intent
that people wish to get rid of, yet couldn't.
You took this path,
yet you're going against me?
You even intend to suppress this evil?
You're the joke here.
Once I strip you
of all your dark aura,
you will know
that there are no wrong paths in the world.
The winner takes all is the only truth here.
(He's actually)
(absorbing all of my dark aura?)
(He's under Dark Phantom's spell.)
[From Zitai to the desert,
a lonely grave faces the sunset.]
[Taoist Zihuan, Tiandao Sect]
My primordial spirit!
Bai Xiaosheng!
You useless fool!
(Dark Phantom has merged himself)
(with Bai Xiaosheng's true effigy.)
(If I want to damage him,)
(I have to remove)
(his shadow robe.)
Tianyao?
Get up.
Yanhui is trapped
within Dark Phantom's mind's eye.
I need your assistance.
How can I assist you?
My presence counters the dark aura.
If I head to Dark Phantom's mind's eye hastily,
I'm afraid Yanhui, another master
of the dark aura,
will be hurt.
You once said
that Dark Phantom used your true effigy
to create a shadow robe
that could isolate himself
from all other objects in the world.
Are you telling me
to strip the shadow robe
from Dark Phantom
and put it on Yanhui?
That's right.
Once Yanhui is wearing the shadow robe,
I will enter his mind's eye
and eradicate him.
Although this is risky,
it's worth a try.
We have no time to waste.
We need to rush toward
Starhaven.
But why?
The entrance in Misty Forest
was destroyed long ago.
Right now, Starhaven
is our only way of getting there.
I'm around.
There's no need to complicate things.
This is?
It's an upgraded version of the shadow cave.
I didn't just sit idly by
when I was imprisoned.
Wait for my signal.
You and I were born from the same source.
You cannot hurt me.
I will take back
Bai Xiaosheng's
true effigy today!
It's just a shadow robe.
You cannot do anything about me.
This is my mind's eye.
You're but a part of me.
Time to die!
Great timing!
Here you go.
I thought I would need to endure
a tough battle to get back my true effigy.
I didn't expect you two
to be thinking of the same thing.
Although I only got a small part
of the shadow robe,
it's enough to protect you.
Bai Xiaosheng,
how dare you betray me and join her?
I would've destroyed
my true effigy and perished with you long ago
if it weren't for her.
By the way,
I even brought
your old friend here today.
Tianyao?
Tianyao.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to reunite with you.
I'm afraid this isn't the time
for you two to be lovey-dovey.
Leave with Bai Xiaosheng.
I will take care of it.
Tianyao.
Yanhui!
There's a shadow cave here.
I'll bring you outside.
You can actually travel with people now?
Not just that,
but I can also take you anywhere you like.
I have a plan.
Let's leave for now.
Both you and I
were toyed by fate.
Why don't you join me
in oversetting this world?
I have the shadow robe!
You cannot hurt me with your dragon fire!
Tianyao, now!
Tianyao.
Yanhui.
His mind's eye is collapsing.
Let's go!
I sense a dragon scent.
Could it be that the dragon
had retrieved his body
and defeated Dark Phantom?
Tianyao,
we actually succeeded.
What's the matter?
♪Feelings start swirling secretly
with every tiny leap♪
Yanhui,
I can finally touch you again.
This is great.
♪Time slows down when you love someone♪
♪Every little thing is a love letter♪
Tianyao,
I think
I hear your heartbeat.
Why is it
beating faster and faster?
Do you feel uncomfortable
after retrieving your heart?
No.
Suying returned the dragon heart to you
when we were at Guanghan Sect.
I'm sure she wanted us
to end up like her and Lu Musheng.
She wanted us to suffer like her.
Yanhui,
trust me.
Although we counter each other,
we won't
end up like them.
As long as we believe in each other,
I don't fear the future.
♪Quietly loving you for me♪
♪The dream that filled the starry sky♪
♪Let there be a contour on the moon♪
♪Full of chapters, you're the beginning of
my romantic poem♪
♪Waiting for a new secret language to emerge♪
Mind you, I'm still here.
I wonder
who was the one
who made your plan to steal his shadow robe
work?
Thank you for your help.
I'm only helping you
because of Yanhui.
We could only defeat Dark Phantom
because of your help.
Yanhui,
I need to thank you too.
Thank you for retrieving my true effigy for me.
It's a shame that it's in tatters.
It's fine.
These are the scars of my battle
with Dark Phantom.
I'll take this half.
As for the other half,
you have to keep it on all the time.
Especially when this guy
is by your side.
You mustn't remove it at all costs.
I'm just kidding.
You guys only became a couple
all thanks to my contribution
as your matchmaker,
right?
Now,
I sincerely
give you two my blessing.
All right.
Your matchmaker is done for the day.
I'll slip into your shadows.
Why is there still no news of them?
Could it be that something had happened
to the Dragon King and Yanhui?
I knew we should go there together.
Your Highness,
you're the only
royal descendant of Qingqiu.
You mustn't try anything risky.
Dragon King is the only dragon in the world.
Why can he do it then?
You!
Mr. Yan,
don't be angry.
His Highness is just worried
about the Dragon King.
I'm worried about the Dragon King too.
However, Dark Phantom
excels at manipulating people's hearts
with his dark aura.
If we act recklessly,
it might backfire on us instead.
With Tianyao's and Yanhui's
current strength,
they will stand a chance
of defeating Dark Phantom.
Therefore,
Your Highness,
please calm down.
I don't wish
to lose anyone again.
You won't lose anyone.
Yanhui?
It's the Dragon King and Yanhui!
Yanhui!
Yanhui, you're back!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Luckily, Tianyao made it in time.
Enough already.
Come back.
Come here.
Our baby is more important.
The Dragon King was so flustered
when you were gone.
He even called your name in his dreams.
Is that so?
We were worried about you too.
It's fine now.
Dark Phantom's mind's eye has been destroyed.
You guys don't need to worry now.
Where's Xiaosheng?
He has retrieved his true effigy.
He's merging it with his body.
We've sent him back
to his room.
Dragon King, congratulations
on completing your body.
I'm sorry
about Chenyi.
I couldn't make it in time.
Luckily,
the Dark Phantom is out of the picture now.
His Majesty's
and Her Majesty's wish
has finally been fulfilled.
Mr. Yan, please allow us
to proceed with their mourning.
Lanterns!
Pray.
They're floating to the sky.
Have these grudges
finally ended?
What's with that question?
Maybe it was because of
the numerous things we'd been through.
I was always tensed up.
Now that I can finally relax,
I feel strange.
There are no feuds or grudges now.
In the future,
no matter where you want to go
or what kind of life you want to lead,
I will always stay by your side.
I'm free.
Master,
the nebula on Starhaven
had dispersed.
Master, you must've
sealed Dark Phantom away successfully.
It was the dragon.
He had retrieved all of his body parts.
He already vanquished the dark aura
inside Dark Phantom's mind's eye.
This is great,
Master.
You two, head to Qiyun Monastery
and tell Master Qiyun
about this news
so that she can have some peace of mind.
-Yes, Master.
(Yanhui,)
(I knew you could do it.)
Are you okay?
Why did you bring me here?
I prepared something nice for you.
This is
the fruit wine I had chilled
with the cold spring water.
Try it.
What do you think?
It's delicious.
You finally smiled.
You stopped smiling
ever since His Majesty passed away.
My mother passed away when I was young.
My sister died in a foreign land.
And now, my father is gone too.
I'm the only person left
in the family.
You're not alone.
You still have me.
Yes,
I still have you.
However,
my family will never be complete again.
I can understand
your feelings.
Although the Dragon King
had defeated Dark Phantom,
our kin
who had left this world,
they will never return again.
Here.
Drink up.
It's moving.
It's moving!
The baby is so strong!
Be gentle.
Don't scare the baby.
Okay.
I'll keep it down.
I'll lower my volume.
Well,
do you think this is a boy or a girl?
I hope it's a girl.
She'll take after you.
But I heard from other people
that daughters take after their fathers.
But you don't resemble
Leader Chenyi at all.
Actually, Leader Chenyi
isn't my biological father.
I'm just a foster daughter
he picked up from the battlefield.
Sorry about that.
I made you upset again.
It's fine.
I was just wondering
if I resemble my father
or my mother.
If my in-laws can give birth to a beauty like you,
I'm sure they're someone extraordinary.
Actually,
I've never seen them before.
All these years,
I've been traveling between the two realms.
I tried
to locate them too.
However, there was never any news of them.
It seems like
they're no longer
in this world.
Gone away from us is the day of yesterday.
My dear,
you shouldn't be too upset about it.
You should smile more often
for our child's sake.
Tianyao?
You...
Tianyao!
Yanhui,
rest well.
I'll make a move first.
Wait!
Don't you remember
what happened here?
I don't.
You don't?
That's fine.
I'll tell you what happened.
Look.
This is no ordinary bed.
Back then,
you hatched out from your egg
on this very bed.
It's very meaningful
to me.
And this blanket
is very special too.
(When you hatched out from your egg,)
you used this blanket
to cover your...
I remember now.
Really?
I...
I never forgot about it.
If so, why did you say
you don't remember it?
When I hatched out from my egg,
I was completely naked.
It was disgraceful of me.
I don't want to remember it.
We've been through so much together.
We even got married twice.
There's no need to hide anything.
I still think there's a need
to hide it.
You...
Where did you come from?
You have my true effigy with you.
I know all about
the conversations you had
and the things you did.
If so,
what did you hear?
I heard everything.
-Is that so?
-You wish to fight?
You want to fight me?
I'll leave then.
You guys can deal with it yourselves then.
Listen up.
The three of us
have to live together now.
I know you guys are madly in love with each other,
but you should think about my feelings too.
Tell me.
What's our next mission?
The death anniversary of the valley's elves
is in a few days.
Tianyao and I
plan to return to the Dragon Valley.
That won't do.
You two mustn't go there together.
-Why?
You guys are only able to see each other
all thanks to my effort.
The dragon scent in the Dragon Valley
is stronger.
What if you go there
and the dragon power overwhelms you
and kills you?
Forget it.
I wanted to return
to Chenxing Mountain anyway.
I need to tell my master
about Dark Phantom's defeat.
All right.
Look at you two.
Although you two
have been through much together,
you two still have many regrets.
The formed
is born out of the formless.
All things are born out of nothing.
All things belong to nothing.
The formed is born out of the formless.
Sect Leader!
Greetings, Sect Leader.
Use your dantian to breathe
and maintain a steady rhythm.
Do not slack off.
-Yes, sir.
Sir, have you come out of your retreat?
I intend to leave the sect for a few days.
Since Zichen and Ziyue aren't around,
you shall be in charge of the sect
for the next few days.
Yes, sir.
Proceed with your lesson.
-Yes, sir.
(Is that Dark Phantom's mind's eye?)
(Something's wrong!)
I thought our sect leader
was leaving the mountain?
-Yeah.
-That's right.
Yeah.
♪You are in the opposite direction,
I can't see you clearly♪
♪My grey hair represents my longing for you♪
♪Each frame slipping through my fingers♪
♪Marks our history♪
♪The breeze blows, the pear blossom falls♪
♪The swan goose honks♪
♪I trace your silhouette♪
♪One portrait after another♪
♪I caress your cheek♪
♪One memory after another♪
♪I drown my nights with this forlornness♪
♪The wind blows as I sigh♪
♪Everything I've been through in my life♪
♪Is so that I can find you♪
♪Who has had the taste of a true departure?♪
♪Just like the moon,
our reunion is few and far between♪
♪Among the green hills and the clear rivers♪
♪My love for you will never change♪
♪How easy it is to meet and part♪
♪Retelling our encounters to the endless rain♪
♪May the drifting petals scatter
throughout the world♪
♪And the spring breeze remains the same♪
♪I carry the memory of you with me♪
♪And move forward♪
♪I look back a few times♪
♪Trying to look for the you I knew♪
♪We hold hands,
reminiscing on our good memories♪
♪The mortal world is as bustling as always♪
♪Sometimes, it's just hard♪
♪To convey my feelings♪