(Back From The Brink)
(Episode 6)
Come and have a look.
(Wangyu Tower)
Come.
Slowly.
Exclusive prescription! Mouth ulcers!
There's no rush.
Never-ending coughs? Feeling irritable?
Night sweats?
As long as you have this,
you can be cured.
Gather around.
Don't push.
All right. Next.
Please come inside.
My neighbor
couldn't be cured at many clinics.
In the end, he was cured
by Physician Fu.
Is that so?
I can finally cure myself of the illness
that has been troubling me for years.
Next.
(Men are charming)
(when they work.)
What's wrong?
What's wrong with me?
(Is it the Heart Protecting Scale again?)
(This doesn't feel right.)
Done.
Next.
What are you?
You have no aura on your body.
Neither do you.
Are you
a human?
I've had an inflammation recently.
Here.
Remove the pimple on my face.
Otherwise, you are finished.
Stupid familiar.
I dare you to touch him.
He's just a familiar.
Is this necessary?
I'm the only person
who can hit my familiar.
Do you
like him?
(Is that what it is?)
Do you love him deeply?
Are you willing to die
for him?
I suggest you have your brain examined.
I can't cure your illness.
You feel shy, don't you?
It's all right. I understand.
Do your best.
I have high hopes for both of you.
Don't let me down.
I will forget
about the pimple.
Physician Fu is great.
Yongzhou City is full of weird people.
You must be cautious in the future.
What's wrong?
I...
I don't know.
I'm fine.
Well...
Turn around.
Why?
Turn around!
Which side?
Whatever! Just turn around!
(She has been acting weird recently.)
Isn't it delicious?
It's so delicious.
(Couple Trial)
(The trial for this Taoist spirit couple)
(should be very interesting.)
What's wrong with me?
You are love-struck.
Love-struck?
To Tianyao?
How is that possible?
Impossible.
Why isn't it possible?
Love always
comes suddenly.
Well, why?
There's no reason.
Love is something you can't figure out.
Impossible.
Absolutely impossible.
It's not possible.
How?
No way.
Not at all.
No.
Lady.
The young master of the Feng family,
Feng Qianshuo,
has gotten a new concubine.
He has invited you to the ceremony.
Look.
He already had a few concubines,
but he didn't say why he got a new one.
Since you fell for him,
you need to look after your familiar.
Many monsters have gone missing
for no reason
in Yongzhou City recently.
Missing?
Why?
I am still investigating.
Anyway, just be careful.
Let's go, Yuli.
Come with me to meet
the young master of the Feng family
tomorrow.
(Oh no. It's happening again.)
What's wrong with you
recently?
I'm fine.
What is this?
I plan to retrieve
the dragon horns from the tower.
I want you
to give me some Heart Blood.
Are you going to get the dragon horns tonight?
Aren't you afraid Suying
has set up a trap
to catch you?
I scouted the place.
There's indeed a Gold-eating Beast
hidden in the Dragon Horn Formation.
But I have
made enough gold
to distract the Gold-eating Beast
and buy time to break the formation.
(It turns out he was borrowing money...)
Yanhui, lend me 3,000 gold.
It's for an emergency.
(To reclaim the dragon horns.)
You were spending my luck.
(He worked hard to make money)
(to retrieve the dragon horns.)
(I didn't expect him)
(to prepare and plan)
(in secret.)
(Meanwhile, I have been immersing myself)
(in the weird feelings)
(and got obsessed.)
Suying is so brazen.
She must have something up her sleeves.
It's too dangerous for you to go alone.
I'll go with you.
No need.
As you said,
Suying will have something up her sleeves.
The dragon horns are the second most important.
What she wants the most
has always been the Heart Protecting Scale.
I will not be in danger
as long as you are not around.
Right now,
snatching the Heart Protecting Scale
away from you
is easy for her.
You are right.
Go without me.
(Wangyu Tower)
Here you go.
Be careful.
You need to be careful, too.
Thank you.
It's so great.
Love comes all of a sudden.
But thankfully,
I am rational.
I didn't get overwhelmed
by love.
(Sneaking out for fun)
(without his master's consent?)
(This familiar)
(is not loyal.)
(Let me see)
(where you are going.)
(There were no guards a few days ago.)
(Why are there so many)
(disciples of the Guanghan Sect here today?)
Sect Leader.
Do you have a death wish?
Tianyao.
She has transported the dragon horns.
I have taken away the dragon horns.
Thank you
for your help during this period.
Leave with me.
Yes.
You are no match for her.
Why did you follow me?
For some reason,
I fell in love with you.
I will never
fall in love again.
Yanhui.
What?
Thank you.
What for?
Thank you
for stopping me today.
Should I see you
sacrifice yourself
and get me in trouble?
However,
I didn't expect Suying
not to recognize you.
If I were to
do something like what she did,
I would not live
with a clear conscience,
let alone sleep well.
If the other person
were planning something,
I would be worried
and frightened.
How can she be so calm?
Do you still remember
the appearance of the bug
you just chased away?
Wasn't it just a bug?
They all look the same.
Why should I remember it?
To Suying,
I am that bug.
Someone dispensable.
She can get rid of me easily
if she thinks I'm an eyesore.
Tianyao.
There's a water bug
in legends.
Its name is Hui.
It turns into a serpent after 500 years.
A serpent turns into a dragon
after a thousand years.
The dragon becomes a Horned Dragon
after 500 years.
After 1,000 years, it becomes the Ying Dragon.
Mortals believe
dragons aren't born as dragons.
They become dragons
after enduring the passage of time,
adversity, pain, and change.
I believe
you will one day
change back into a real dragon.
You might become
so strong that the people who humiliated
and overlooked you
can only acknowledge your existence.
You are so stupid.
Why did you scold me when I was comforting you?
Hui is a water snake.
You...
Shut up!
He is the Millennium Spirit Dragon?
In that case,
the dragon horns
belong to him.
Interesting.
Since the Guanghan Sect
transported the dragon horns at night,
where would
they hide them?
(Tianxiang Workshop)
I'm sure this one will do.
It'll be done
after refining a day with the dragon horns.
The person who sealed the dragon horns
is quite impressive.
(Let me see)
(if your love)
(can overcome this trial.)
Is he from Tianxiang Workshop?
(Tianxiang Workshop's young owner, Feng Qianshuo)
Young Master Feng from Tianxiang Workshop
is marrying another concubine.
Seriously.
He is the only successor
of the Tianxiang Workshop, after all.
Halt.
That's Miss Xiange from Wangyu Tower.
Young Master Feng, can we speak in private?
A lady is snatching a man.
Sure.
I invited you every time
whenever I married a concubine.
You were never here.
What?
You finally came this time,
but you're trying to snatch me away?
I have something
that requires your assistance.
You didn't come here
because you cared about me?
I do have something I care about,
but it's not you.
Seems like
I fell in love with the wrong person.
Whatever.
It's rare for you to be here.
What is it?
I want to know something.
Ask away.
What is inside.
Tianxiang Workshop?
Tianxiang Workshop
is a business of the Feng family.
Don't tell me
that you know nothing.
Why are you
asking me that suddenly?
That's because
there's an increase in missing familiars
in Yongzhou City.
I want to know
where these missing familiars
have gone.
That is none of your business.
Also, knowing
about that
does your harm.
You won't tell me?
Fine.
I'll ask you one question.
Are those missing familiars
related
to Tianxiang Workshop?
Yes.
Thank you.
You...
I never owe people any favors.
Since you gave me the information,
I will pay you the reward.
Is that so?
I don't want any gold or treasure.
Why don't you
give me a kiss?
You are always happy
after meeting Young Master Feng.
Nonsense.
I see that Young Master Feng
is loyal to you.
He sent you invitation letters
whenever he married a concubine.
It seems to me
that he just wants to make you angry.
Since you
like Young Master Feng as well,
why don't you tell him honestly?
He is different
from us.
(Tianxiang Workshop)
(Wangyu Tower)
Who is it?
No.
No!
I can't take it early in the morning.
Stay away from me.
Turn around.
Don't let me see your face.
I am someone who just confessed to you
and got rejected by you.
Can you know your place
and stop making me excited?
Oh no.
I can't take it anymore early in the morning!
I can't take it.
No. I can't take it.
Control yourself.
Wait.
What is this?
The golden beans I've earned recently.
You asked me to control myself,
and you're still giving me money?
Are you seducing me
or rejecting me?
I'm taking it away, then.
Wait.
Go away. Leave the money here.
Hello, deary.
Regarding the heart issue
you asked about previously,
Qijue Agency's answer
is to study more
if you are heartless.
Replenish iron if you lack blood in your heart.
- Also...
- Stop!
Is that reliable?
You're asking me to eat iron?
You should just ask me to eat dirt instead.
Do you need me to answer this question?
No need.
Just tell me.
What should I do if my heart lacks flesh?
That
is a difficult problem.
If you only
lack a little,
it will recover by itself.
If you lack a lot,
you might need external help.
External help?
For example, a huge power
to fill in the gap in your heart.
A huge power.
How huge?
For example,
the power of the Millennium Spirit Dragon.
(Nonsense.)
What else?
According to Qijue Agency's knowledge,
nothing else.
That's it?
And you want me to pay you 100,000 gold?
After receiving your 100,000 gold,
we also have a gift for you.
Until now,
your spending
at Qijue Agency
totals up to 120,088 gold.
Congratulations on surpassing
Young Master Wang
and topping the Richest Clients Leaderboard
of Qijue Agency.
Do you also operate the gambling den?
Yes.
Seems like you spent your money for nothing.
Not really.
At least I know
my life
can only remain
with huge power.
Huge power?
In that case,
when I complete my body,
I will be able to help you recover
the missing piece of your heart.
Then,
you can still live
without the Heart Protecting Scale.
So, tell me.
How do you plan to get the dragon horns?
Are you willing to help me?
What else can I do?
(This fragrance pill)
(has the aura of my dragon horns.)
Can you guess what this is?
The pimple guy.
Why are you here?
(When did he come inside?)
(I didn't notice him at all.)
Who are you?
Where did you find this?
What is this?
Do you want to know?
Sure.
But you have
to agree to a condition of mine.
What condition?
I want
her.
Impossible.
Why do you want me?
I want you to leave him.
Although I don't know
what you two are talking about,
I can't leave him.
I tried.
I couldn't do it.
Do you love
this disabled dragon
so deeply?
He knows your identity?
Where's my dagger?
We can't let him leave!
Calm down.
Don't worry.
I will never tell anyone
your true identity.
Actually, I'm here to help you.
If she is willing to leave with me,
I will immediately
tell you the dragon horns' location.
What
do you want?
Give me this lady, and you will get a secret.
Will you do it?
No.
(This familiar can really endure the trial.)
Stop talking nonsense with him.
We can't let him leave.
What a coincidence.
I'm not leaving.
You tied me up professionally.
Tell me. What's your name?
I am Bai Xiaosheng.
After leaving you,
I couldn't forget your pretty face.
It was
love at first sight.
Nonsense!
The gaze of liking someone
should be like how I look at him.
(There she goes again.)
Judging from
your empty gaze
and scheming look,
you must have an ulterior motive.
I'll give you another chance.
Fine.
Actually,
you look like my previous love.
You are both charming, pretty,
and bold.
When I saw you,
it felt like looking at the sun.
Is that so? Where's the sun?
She's dead.
You'll be dead if you lie again.
Why won't you believe
that it was love at first sight?
You...
Enough.
Don't talk nonsense with him.
Hold it.
Miss Yan.
I'm willing to tell you
the location of the dragon horns,
but I'm only going to tell you.
Come here.
Tell me.
Come closer.
Suying took the dragon horns.
I saw the whole process.
(Nonsense.)
(I was there, too.)
(Why didn't I see you?)
I have a special ability.
I can hide my trace.
(I hid in a spot)
(where I would not be discovered.)
(Anyway, )
(the disciples of the Guanghan Sect)
(didn't notice that I was following them.)
(I followed them)
(to a place.)
(And I saw the dragon horns there.)
The dragon horns are at Tianxiang Workshop.
He said they were at Tianxiang Workshop.
Let's go.
(She doesn't plan)
(to make the dragon horns hers.)
(This pair of master and familiar)
(can forget about their self-interests.)
(They do have a really close relationship.)
We don't know where he comes from.
How does he know you are a dragon?
The Seven Star Disciples
of the Guanghan Sect are capable.
Even if they didn't notice him,
the dragon horns
should be heavily guarded.
How could he investigate the place
without being seen?
Do you think
he is sent here by Suying?
He is here to confirm our location
and capture us all.
When Suying wants to do something,
she will do it herself
without doing it in a roundabout way.
Does she know
that I possess the Heart Protecting Scale?
If another person
knew about the Heart Protecting Scale,
you would have been dead.
We have ruled out
every possibility.
There has to be a reason.
Seems like
it was really
love at first sight for him.
Someone used to tell me
that when every impossible result
has been eliminated,
the only reason remaining
will be the truth.
Sudden love is bound to have an ulterior motive
behind it.
Aren't you afraid?
Didn't my love for you
come suddenly as well?
Tell me. What is my ulterior motive?
I want you to lie to me
and stab me?
(This person's origin is unknown, )
(and his trail is mysterious.)
(I'm no match for him)
(with my current ability.)
Why did you take out
the Heart Blood?
Fusing blood with the formation
to trap this person.
This is for you to retrieve the dragon horns.
That's such a waste.
He knows too much.
We can't let him run around.
I already tied him down.
You won't be able to tie him down.
He said the dragon horns
were in Tianxiang Workshop.
Do you think it's believable?
I was planning
to scout the place tonight, anyway.
What if it's a trap?
We'll know after scouting.
All right.
I'll go with you.
You?
Don't try to stop me.
I can't see you
getting hurt right now.
I just don't want myself
to feel bad.
(Tianxiang Workshop)
What's that noise?
Be careful.
You are the one who should be careful.
I like you right now.
You must keep a distance from me.
Otherwise, I'll be infatuated.
Don't touch me.
This is serious.
Let's go.
Move!
Hurry!
Walk faster!
Hurry up! Move!
Familiars.
What are they doing?
I can sense the dragon horns' aura inside.
Let's have a look inside.
Let's go.
I knew you wouldn't give up.
This place is dangerous. Come with me.
I'm not leaving.
I want to know the whereabouts
of the missing familiars.
Is it worth it
just to help a bunch of monsters?
Yes.
Where are they?
Where are those people?
It's heavily guarded outside,
but there's no one guarding inside.
It's a Starpoint Formation on the door!
Someone triggered the Starpoint Formation.
Come with me.
Come on.
Are we leaving already?
Young Master Feng!
Which thief
dares to trespass on Tianfang Workshop?
They are hurt. They can't go far.
After them!
- Yes!
(The body)
(of the man in black)
(whom I hit looked like...)
The injury
on your left shoulder looks serious.
I've stopped the bleeding for you.
How is it? Are you feeling better?
This isn't worth it.
It is.
Xiange.
Yanhui?
Who is this?
We shouldn't stay here for long.
Help me bring him back.
Sure.
Carry him.