(Back From The Brink)
(Episode 5)
(Suying?)
(You are my sworn enemy.)
(Familiar Depositary)
(Qijue Agency Stable)
Buddy, do you want one?
Are you guys willing
to let them treat you as such?
Of course.
Why not?
Judging from your unhappy expression,
I assume this is your first time being a familiar.
That's fine.
Look at you, all clean and white.
You're not hurt at all.
Look at this buddy over here.
When you bring that up,
I can't help but feel sad.
My master
was jealous of my good looks.
That's why he left
a scar that would never disappear
on my
handsome face.
By the way,
you can give it to me
if he doesn't want it.
My master always thought I was a herbivore.
Actually,
I can have meat, too.
Have you two never thought of escaping?
Where can we escape?
In Yongzhou,
monsters die in abrupt ways
once they tear their pact of servitude.
Sometimes, their bodies are not even found.
The pact of servitude was created
by monsters for humans as a sign
of gratitude before.
However, no one expected it
to end up like this.
Tianyao?
Why did you guys chain him up here?
Ma'am,
familiars are supposed to be treated like this.
Release him immediately!
Okay, ma'am.
Please pay up, then.
(Vegetables for sale!)
(Fresh vegetables for sale!)
Sorry about that.
I didn't know
they would treat you like that.
They weren't that unkind to monsters
when I came to Yongzhou
three years ago.
Have you asked for information?
I don't have enough money.
I think I have to borrow money
from my friends.
You have friends in Yongzhou?
Of course.
You can even borrow money from them?
What do you mean by that?
I'm just curious.
You were cultivating in Chenxing Mountain before.
Why would you have friends in Yongzhou?
Three years ago,
I made a new friend
when I joined Master in subduing monsters.
Yongzhou City is a huge place.
I may not be familiar with other places,
but I know every single path
that leads to her place.
Keep it.
What is he doing here?
Was he the friend
you mentioned just now?
(The Richest Man in Yongzhou, Wang Pengyuan)
How is that possible?
It won't be this sum by next month.
Have you offended him before?
Don't be like that.
It's nothing worth mentioning.
Let's go.
(Wangyu Tower, Yongzhou)
Wangyu Tower.
Is your friend
here?
She's the owner of Wangyu Tower.
She's a famous businesswoman in Yongzhou.
Do you know her? She's a good friend of mine.
Let's go.
Sorry, ma'am.
According to our rules,
no familiars can enter this building
except those who are owned by our owner.
Is she really
your good friend?
It's me.
Look at me.
Can I enter the building with my familiar?
No.
Only familiars that belong to our owner or important guests
can enter the building.
Good friend, huh?
Where did you come from?
You must be new.
Get someone else here. Let me in.
I can't let you in even if I get someone else here.
Let me in!
No.
What do you mean? Get out of my way.
Let me in.
No.
Get out of my way!
I can't.
I truly can't.
Get out of my way!
Ma'am!
What's going on?
First Young Master.
Yuli?
(Yuli, Xiange's familiar)
Miss Yan?
Great timing.
Tell him who I am
and if I can go inside with my familiar.
Take a look.
Miss Yan, please calm down.
He's new here. He has never seen you before.
This is our VIP.
If you mistreat her again, I won't let you off.
Yes, sir.
Miss Yan,
please.
I told you I had a good friend here.
Miss, it's been a long time since you came.
Our lady misses you.
It's because I had plenty of things
to do before this.
But speaking of which,
judging from Xiange's personality,
I find it hard to believe
that she would set so many rules here.
I thought Wangyu Tower
was a place for people to forget their differences
and enjoy themselves.
Now, they're classifying beings?
Miss, you came at the wrong time.
The Guanghan Sect keeps a close eye on everything now.
If Wangyu Tower
stays different from the rest,
people might get something on us.
Miss Yan, you just left the mountain not long ago.
You can stay here for a few more days
and take a breather.
-Miss Yan. -Miss Yan.
Miss Yan.
I missed you guys!
We missed you too!
It's been so long
since I last witnessed a scene like this.
Yan, you got yourself a familiar, too?
What kind of spirit is he?
I cannot detect any spiritual energy from him.
He...
Our lady is here.
My Lady.
(Xiange, the owner of Wangyu Tower)
You never came back
after we parted ways three years ago.
I'm afraid you already forgot about me long ago.
My lady, please do not blame me.
I missed you.
You're as mischievous as always.
I missed you so much.
They're having a ladies' talk.
You should come with us.
Did you miss me?
Let's go.
Treat him well.
Do not bully him.
They won't chain you up.
I'll pick you up when I'm done.
Let's go.
Please.
How did you end up getting yourself a familiar?
It's a long story.
Xiange,
actually, I came here
to ask you for a favor.
Go ahead.
How much do you need this time?
You're my good friend indeed. You do know me well.
Seems like you need a huge sum.
That's right.
It's...
1,000 gold?
10,000 gold?
100,000 gold?
Yanhui,
why don't you sell Wangyu Tower
while you're at it?
I know it's a huge sum.
What trouble did you get yourself into? Why did you need so much money?
Did you leave the mountain
for another reason?
I need to buy a life-saving piece of information
from the Qijue Agency.
Qijue Agency?
What kind of info is it? Why does it require so much money?
I'm sick.
Sick?
You...
What's the matter with you?
My heart is pretty weak.
You should go to a physician, then.
-Come. -No.
I'll bring you there.
It's a long story.
My illness is peculiar.
Anyway, I lack money.
Wait here.
Let us introduce ourselves first.
All of us
are Miss Xiange's familiars.
I'm fifth in rank.
I'm ninth in rank.
You can call me Fifth.
You can call me Ninth.
(Fifth Young Master, Xiange's familiar) Look at his nose
and eyes.
You do look handsome.
No wonder Miss Yan took a liking to you.
Don't just pull a long face all day.
You need to learn how to smile.
You need to smile warmly.
Curve your brows and lift your lips. Do you know how to do it?
I can teach you.
Take note of the smiling angle.
The standard smile requires eight teeth to be shown.
Like this.
(Ninth Young Master, Xiange's familiar) Don't listen to him.
You won't be able to stay for long
if you only depend on your looks.
(Familiars' way of conduct) You need to study and learn more.
An outstanding familiar
isn't made in a day.
Any outstanding familiars
must be able to predict their owners' intentions,
observe their needs,
protect their owners' reputations when they're outside,
and make sure they don't need to worry.
When our owners take a glance at us,
you have to think of everything in advance
and act before them.
Act if they tell you to, and stop when they tell you not to.
If they tell you to go East,
never go West.
If they tell you to stand, never sit.
So, we must follow everything our owners...
What are you two doing?
Is our lady too lenient on you guys usually?
Is that why you guys are behaving rudely?
Fine.
I'll leave, then.
Sir, sorry about that.
Please wait here.
I'll make you a pot of tea.
It's fine.
Thank you, First Young Master.
I have something to ask you.
When I entered the city today,
I saw a pair of dragon horns on top of the city tower.
When was it placed there?
It's already been there for a few days.
I can't remember clearly.
It just appeared there
one morning.
Rumors
regarding the dragon horns
have been circulating
within the city, too.
What kind of rumors?
Some say
dragon horns are treasures
that absorb the essence of Heaven and Earth.
Even though they're placed at the city gate,
no one is guarding them.
That means the dragon horns
must be fake.
(Some say)
it's the sacred treasure of dragons,
and it'll protect itself.
It'll protect itself?
I heard that the pair of dragon horns
devours people.
It devours people?
To me,
those are just mere rumors.
The dragon horns
have attracted the attention
of many greedy people.
Many bodies would be dragged out
of the city gate tower every morning.
I speculate
that a strong master
is protecting the dragon horns secretly.
Those who have shallow cultivation
cannot tell that.
They thought no one was protecting them.
That's why they came up with rumors
of the dragon horns devouring people.
Dear guest,
please take care.
(Wangyu Tower)
Look.
I got 20,000 gold from her.
She's my good friend indeed.
I'll definitely repay everything
once I start to make money.
You still lack 80,000 gold.
You have to find four other good friends.
How about I
sell you, then?
It's just for the time being.
Forget it.
You pull a long face every day.
I can't sell you for a good price, anyway.
You don't need to waste your money.
You can return the money
to your friend.
As long as I retrieve my body...
Stop.
I will never believe your words.
What should we do?
We need to make money somehow.
This is great!
They're gambling today.
We'll get rich in one go!
That's right. It all falls on you now.
Here's our chance.
You can enjoy yourself.
I have something to do. I need to go.
Wait.
This is for you.
This
is for your living expenses in Yongzhou.
Keep it well.
Take care of yourself.
Now we
are in the same boat.
I'll make a move first.
(The dragon horns are harmless.)
(Suying did set up a trap around them.)
(Let me)
(see what's going on with it tonight.)
It's the Gold-eating Beast, indeed.
I should be able to lure it away
if I have enough gold pieces.
The dragon horns are right in front of me.
I'll take a gamble.
Come! The more you bet, the more you earn!
Big or small? Place your bet!
Come! Big or small?
Big!
Small!
Again!
Big!
Here!
Here. Big!
Small!
Big!
(I thought I could win enough money)
(to purchase the info from Qijue Agency by gambling.)
(What should I do now?)
We have a challenge today.
On the left is Qiang.
On the right is Fu.
Which one will you guys bet on?
My Fu will surely win.
Am I right? You guys should bet on it.
Wrong! My Qiang is the strongest!
Bet on Qiang!
Everyone, place your bet!
Do place your bet!
Fu is going to win!
I'll bet on Fu!
Fight!
Qiang, beat it up!
Shut up!
Fu?
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
It won.
I won.
Miss,
I think Fu
died suddenly!
Qiang won.
Even crickets
can die suddenly?
That's right.
Poor Fu.
It's been killed
on the battlefield.
Fu!
Yanhui,
lend me 3,000 gold.
It's for an emergency.
I ran out of gold!
It took
all my luck
to get your Heart Protecting Scale.
Even Fu
died because of me!
You're wrong.
You were spending my luck.
(Wangyu Tower)
20,000 gold
was all gone
in one night?
Miss Yan,
pardon me for being straight,
but your familiar is too much of a spendthrift.
You should get a new one as soon as possible.
You're right.
I will.
I'll consider it.
You two can resume your work.
Okay.
Mr. Fu,
you should rest early, too.
Yuli,
I have a question.
Is there a way for us to make money
in Yongzhou City?
Mr. Fu,
do you want to alleviate Miss Yan's trouble?
I guess so.
Actually,
there are many ways
you can do that.
First, you can take care of her
so that she can be healthy
and happy.
Second, you can...
You just need to tell me
how I can make money.
We don't have any ways to make money.
We all depend
on our lady to make money.
Sir, who are you looking for?
The person in charge.
I'm looking for the person in charge here.
I'm looking for someone.
She's not here today.
Hurry up.
Is she around or not?
She's around.
Wang Pengyuan!
Hui!
Wasn't he the one
you were avoiding yesterday?
I'm no longer avoiding him.
I won't avoid him
today.
Hui,
I've finally seen you again.
Do you still remember...
You were captured by monsters
when you were going to pray in Huguo Temple.
I saved you.
I remember that.
Since then,
you'll remind me of it whenever you see me.
You still remember that?
If so, do you still remember
the moves you used to subdue the monsters?
Every frown and smile too.
Even the wind in the mountain valleys?
Even the incense in the temple.
You said you would come back and look for me.
I didn't say that.
I never expected our next encounter to be a few years later.
Hui,
I heard from people that you were looking for me today.
I was delighted to hear that.
Actually,
I need your help
to do something.
Just tell me.
What are you looking at?
Have you never seen a handsome guy before?
Hui,
he's...
He's
the new familiar I've subdued.
Serve our guest tea.
Hui, what kind of familiar
is he, then?
He's an auspicious koi.
So, he just brings good luck.
Although he's not very useful,
he can at least ward off bad luck for you.
That's great, too.
Drink it first.
Come here.
Come with me.
Let's go.
I'm negotiating a deal here.
Don't mess it up.
You should head back first.
Go.
Just go!
Just go already!
Remember to clean the room.
I'll inspect it later.
Go now.
Hui,
you actually care about me?
I'm so happy.
I guess so.
He's a little dumb.
That's right.
Just now,
you said you needed my help.
What do you need my help for?
Well...
It's not a big deal.
One day,
I saw your name
on the Richest Clients Leaderboard in Yongzhou,
published by the Qijue Agency.
I just spent a little money on that.
I never expect them
to jot down my name on the list.
A little money, huh?
A little money.
Hui,
do you lack money?
Yes.
I want
to borrow money from you.
I'll get upset if you say that.
Borrow?
You don't need to borrow money from me when we're this close.
You can spend my money all you like.
But I require quite a lot.
Money isn't an issue to me.
I can never finish spending them.
Hui, how about this?
Come with me.
See if
I'm rich enough to meet your standards.
Is that okay with you?
Sure.
(Free of rent for one month)
It looks like
they revere you.
This street belongs to my family.
They're just my tenants.
I even established a new business incubator.
Do you want to check it out?
I do.
However, it will be a bit far
if we walk there.
Hui, why don't you
pick a horse together
with me?
Sure.
This is my horse.
This is your horse?
But the horseshoes...
They are made of jade.
Jade?
What if
the horse crushed them by accident?
I can just get a new one.
At first, the shopkeeper
wanted to make one with gold and jade.
But that's so vulgar.
I demanded one entirely out of jade.
If so, how much does this horse of yours
cost?
It's only 100,000 gold.
100,000 gold?
(I can't afford to pay you back)
(if anything happens to it.)
Hui,
if you're unsatisfied with it,
I still have many precious horses for you to choose from.
They're much more expensive than this steed.
It's okay.
I'll take this horse.
Okay.
We'll take you.
It's getting late.
Mr. Fu,
what are you doing here alone?
Yuli, you're alone, too.
Our lady wanted some snacks.
She told me to buy some supper from the night market.
Mr. Fu,
do you want to try it?
It's fine.
Your hand is...
I burned my hands by accident
while I was cooking two days ago.
Let me take a look.
How did you do that?
My element is Water.
So I could treat your burn.
Mr. Fu, you can actually utilize such magic arts?
It's not difficult for you to make money, then.
I'll try to promote you.
Thank you so much.
Mr. Fu,
are you waiting for Miss Yan?
I'm afraid you have to wait for some time.
When I came back,
I saw her visiting the night market
with the wealthy.
Mr. Wang.
She was smiling while chatting with him.
It looked like she was enjoying herself.
I heard from one of the stall vendors
that Mr. Wang might try
to propose to Yanhui tonight.
Hello, Mr. Wang.
Mr. Wang is here.
I never thought riding on an expensive horse
like this would be so cool.
I'm glad that you like it.
However,
it's much cheaper
compared to my turtle.
Mister, it's been so long since you came here.
This is the newest seasoning
we imported from the Western Regions.
Please take it.
That pepper of yours
is worth nothing.
Mister,
look at our Golden Ruyi.
This is a precious item.
It's just a mere Ruyi.
It cannot showcase.
Mister's domineering aura.
Mister, look.
These golden boots of mine
are the only pair in the world.
If you wear it,
you'll be the dashing man
in the entire city.
Take a look.
Mister.
Wait.
Does your family
own the entire street?
It's a business incubator.
I'm giving youngsters a chance to start their businesses.
I just collect rent from them
every month.
Hui,
do you think I'm wealthy enough?
Of course.
You're more than that.
Do you need more staff here?
Silence!
I cannot hear Hui.
Hui,
what were you saying just now?
Mr. Wang,
do you need more staff here?
No.
But I need a landlady.
What?
I need a landlady.
I...
You...
Can I?
You can!
I'm delighted today.
I'll distribute red packets to everyone!
(Look at all that money!)
(I wouldn't need to go to the gambling den)
(if I had known about this sooner.)
Hui,
you truly can.
I...
You!
Tianyao?
Time for you to head back.
Wait for me!
I'll consider it first. I'll give you an answer later.
-Wait for me! -Hui!
I'll wait for you!
What are you doing?
Why did you awaken
my conscience and dignity?
Do you know
there are many important decisions in life
that we have to make immediately
when the situation
is still blurry?
Why did you do so?
Why did I do so?
I was just trying
to help that mister
to sober up.
Do you think I'm not good enough for him?
He's wealthy enough that he can fill the sky with gold.
Do you think you're good enough for him?
And, when he was
walking alongside you,
his eyes were glued to you
all night long.
I assume he truly fancies you.
But you?
You only had eyes
for his wealth.
You have no feelings for him at all.
You're just using him.
You're speaking as if you know me inside out.
Who said I was after his wealth?
I'll explain things to him tomorrow.
Tomorrow? You should do it today...
Stop it!
Tell me, then.
They assigned us
to this place.
Those are members of the Guanghan Sect.
We have nothing to do here.
Why should we stay here?
Tianxiang Workshop?
It's my first time
hearing about this place in Yongzhou.
(Tianxiang Workshop)
Mister,
what does Tianxiang Workshop sell for a living?
Tianxiang Workshop
sells incense.
It's just an incense workshop.
Why are the immortals
of the Guanghan Sect guarding this place?
I can tell you guys
are new to this place.
Tianxiang Workshop
is the property
of the famous.
Feng Family in Yongzhou.
Its owner, Feng Ming,
is the best incense maker
in the world.
The incense he makes has mystical effects.
I speculate
that his reputation as an incense maker
has attracted the attention
of an important organization like Guanghan Sect.
If Feng Ming is that amazing,
why have I not seen his name
appear in Qijue Agency before?
You see,
revealing your income to others is never a sensible idea.
Ordinary people like us
have no chance to see
truly wealthy people.
What kind of incense are they producing?
It smells
pretty strange.
Sorry, it's the smell of this excrement.
Sorry about that.
You possess the Heart Protecting Scale.
Don't run around.
I know that.
(Tianxiang Workshop)
Keep an eye on the entrance.
Do not allow anyone to enter
without my permission.
Yes, sir.
Nine-Tailed Fox,
(Dungeon Arena) how dare you seduce Mr. Lu?
I will make you suffer so much.
(Yunxi, Princess of Qingqiu) that death seems like the easy way out.
Master,
(Feng Ming, the owner of Tianxiang Workshop) this is the incense
made from the extract
of this nine-tailed fox.
Open it.
Fox Incense?
Mr. Feng, you're known as
the number one incense maker in the world.
How dare you attempt
to trick me with this?
Pardon me, Master!
Master, I thought you wanted
an incense
that could make Mr. Lu fall for you again.
Fall for me again?
I just need him
to recover his memories.
Master, please pardon me.
I misunderstood
your intention.
I will see to it immediately.
However,
it's extremely difficult to produce
incense that could help one recover their memories.
I'm afraid I can't do it alone.
May I
borrow the power of the dragon horns?
You are planning to steal the dragon horns, too?
Master, you're overthinking it.
If you didn't kill that monster for me
back then,
I would have no way
to avenge my wife and child.
Now, it's my time
to repay the favor.
I will offer everything I have.
Please believe me!
Master,
I do not intend
to steal the dragon horns.
Once the incense is completed,
I'll definitely
return them to you.
All right.
You have three days.
You will get what you desire
tomorrow.
Mr. Wang, please come inside.
Mr. Wang,
why did you come here personally?
Do you guys
have any incense
that can boost one's charm?
Mister, you mean...
I've admired a lady for a long time.
Today, I finally mustered enough courage
to propose to her.
She was going to say yes,
but in the end,
she said she would consider it.
I guess
I must be too fat.
Or I'm not tall enough.
Or maybe
I'm not humorous enough.
That's why she hesitated.
Mr. Wang,
in my opinion,
I'm afraid
you're not the issue here.
I think that lady doesn't fancy you enough.
She doesn't fancy me enough?
If so, I...
Mister, calm down.
Calm down.
Since you're here,
I will surely solve your trouble for you.
Mister, please wait a moment.
Mister, look.
This is Fox Incense.
Fox Incense?
This incense
was made by the workshop owner himself.
The person who consumes this
will fall deeply in love
with the first person they touch
and cannot stop themselves from loving them.
No.
I need to clarify things with Wang Pengyuan.
Clarify what?
What are you doing here?
They said you were in the backyard.
That's why I came.
Great timing.
I have something to tell you, too.
Please go ahead.
I've thought about it the entire night.
I think I still need to tell you the truth.
I...
Wait.
I'm sure you haven't eaten anything
after you woke up, right?
I brought you some breakfast.
It's made
with nutritious ingredients.
Wang Pengyuan,
I have to reject you, anyway.
I cannot accept your feelings
like this.
I...
You should try this first.
It won't be as nice
when it gets cold.
Here.
Okay.
(The Fox Incense)
(has a plain taste.)
If you mix it in food,
no one will find out.
Once she consumes it,
she will fall helplessly in love
with the first person
she touches.
(Remember, )
(you must)
(be the first person she touches.)
I've finished it.
What are you doing?
I...
There was a bug.
A bug flew by just now.
A bug?
Where?
Over there!
I don't see any bugs.
I don't see anything.
Fatty, what are you doing?
I just want to touch you.
No.
I'm rejecting you.
What are you doing?
You...
Just let me touch you!
I won't do anything else!
Hui, just one touch. I promise.
Hui, stop running.
Are you out of your mind?
What are you doing?
You touched her!
He...
He touched you.
Where did he touch you?
My hand.
Whose hand did he touch?
Mine.
Did you beat him up?
No, I didn't.
Well...
What's wrong with you?
You look especially
pleasing to the eyes today.
Don't be ridiculous.
Where did you go this morning?
I...
Yuli found a way
for me to make money.
All right.
(Although we've been sticking together for some time, )
(it's my first time realizing that he's so handsome.)
Why are you together with him?
I've already fallen for him.
I will leave with him.
(Bai Xiaosheng, Shadow Spirit)
You!
Terminate
our pact of servitude.
Just treat it as if I'm buying her from you.
Are you willing?
She's just a lowly familiar.
Of course, I'm willing.
Xiaosheng, let's go.
I'll send you there first.
Send me there?
I was initially looking for a couple
in which a Taoist and a spirit were in love.
I thought you guys were it.
But I never expected you
to break up that easily.
Such a waste of my time.
You're also a jerk.
(Couple Trial)
Such couples
are infuriating indeed.
It seems like I need to find
a new couple again.