♬～
[Cross the sea, explore the land, and fly in the sky]
[Humanity has always chased dreams]
♬～
[In 1961, that dream took humanity into space for the first time➡
In 1969, we reached the moon]
[While paying a heavy price in 2003]
[Still, people still dream]
[They believe]
[That there is hope if you keep trying]
(Asano) What are you doing?
I'm looking at the sky.
Far beyond the sky.
Ah, space.
(Ruka) Ah, I'm back.
see you later .
hang on .
I'll give you this.
Is it okay?
thank you .
Open it. (Terao) Yeah.
(Miyuki) Thank you for your hard work.
(Miyuki) Yes, thank you. Thank you for your hard work.
Nami!
[but only]
[Some people stop because they can't see where they're going]
(Miyuki) Nami!
(Miyuki) Please do this.
(Nami) Yeah.
♬～
is that so . Understood . ➡
Excuse me.
[Some people stand still as their dreams are shattered]
[A light of hope found after continuing to challenge]
[That will happen eventually➡
It will become a light that illuminates the future of someone who has not yet seen it.]
thank you .
How was it?
The best time is before dawn.
Have you been embraced by the ocean of Obama?
Huh?
Ah! Ah, ah….
Ha ha ha ha...
[The path to a grand dream is ➡
It starts quietly from here now]
♬～
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous...
Wow! (Tadokoro) Danger!
What are you doing, brother? Sorry.
Huh? Hmm...? (sniffing sound)
The city stinks. Where is it from?
Um... it's from Kanagawa. For what?
Starting today, I will be a teacher at Wakasa Fisheries High School.
In Wakamizu? yes .
this . Huh?
this . Hmmmm... Morning takoyaki.
Morning... Ah, the money is fine.
Yeah . No... that...
Oh, that's dangerous.
♬～
Ah...
Ah, good morning...
Ah, good morning.
Thank you .
I guess I'm a teacher. From today here.
(Nami) Takoyaki in the morning?
Huh? Ah, ah, yes. Um... Morning Takoyaki.
(Kurose) Look! You guys hurry! ➡
Hurry!
(Kusakabe) Well, I'm Professor Asano, who started today. ➡
Well then, sir, please give me a brief self-introduction. yes .
Well, I'm Junichi Asano, and I'll be taking care of you from today.
Your first step as a teacher➡
I hope to be welcomed at this traditional Wakasa Fisheries High School ➡
I'm very honored... Why did you come to this school?
I studied oceanography at university.
I love the sea...
Why? That being said... (Kurose) This place has already collapsed. ➡
Let's all eat takoyaki.
(Kusakabe) Well, excuse me for a moment...
Huh! New teacher! ?
Yes, I was just at the school gate.
Huh, I didn't notice. Handsome?
⚟ (Sound of door opening and closing) (Nami) Ah, I'm here.
Eh, good morning.
Young.
My name is Junichi Asano and I will be taking care of you from today. nice to meet you… .
(Nami) Stand up.
Thank you.
Huh? Terao Terao… Terao-kun? (Nami) Take a seat.
(Ryūku) Wake up. It's always like that.
It's better not to touch it.
(Boss) I heard the results of the selection exam. That was a shame.
yes . But I don't think it's over yet.
(Boss) I see.
If you're Kijima-kun, there will definitely come a day when you can go to space.
thank you . We will continue to do so➡
I hope it will be useful in the development of the ISS replenishment aircraft.
(Boss) Ah, that's about it.
The price of mackerel that I usually buy depends on the amount of catch, transportation costs, and processing costs.
It's almost decided by these three...
(Sounds of students talking)
To review, the formula is... (chime)
(Yuzuki) Hey, that's really good. It's the best. Can I borrow it?
(Nagisa) Okay. (Yuzuki) Thank you.
(chime)
Space food? Please wait a moment.
My specialty is technology development.
Chief: Hey. (Boss) Yes, I'm going now.
Well then, that's it. (Kijima) Ah, that...
Why me? (Boss) As I said earlier. ➡
We need your rigor and analytical skills. ➡
That's it.
Mr. Kurose.
Huh...
♬～
(Kurose) My canned mackerel is steamed raw. ➡
The water released during steaming contains water-soluble proteins. ➡
Throw it away. ➡
With this one step, the fishy smell will disappear and the soup will remain clear and not cloudy.
(Kurose) What are the characteristics of our canned mackerel that are not found in commercially available products?
Everyone is amazing. (Kurose) My student Hana➡
His eye for fish and knife skills are on par with professionals. ➡
For students in the food department➡
Let everyone acquire this skill and graduate. ➡
In order for people from my hometown to survive in this town➡
This is a technology that everyone needs.
♬～
Are you disappointed?
Huh? no… .
This is Higashiguchi, the chief. (Kijima) Ah...
This is Kijima.
I've been waiting.
I heard that you were in charge of developing the ISS replenishment aircraft.
Yeah . (East exit) A little difficult➡
I heard that he was hated for smoking.
To prevent accidents in space➡
I was just saying what I needed to say as an engineer.
Isn't that a great thing?
You are very welcome at our house.
(Kurose) The class was very difficult.
The students look at the teacher.
If you make a mistake on your first move, grab it back.
It's like a thump.
He's not that kind of character either. (Kurose) It's a character problem.
If you get licked, it's over. Sorry.
Thank you for waiting. Grilled mackerel set meal.
Accidents happen even when eating in space.
Chewing movements Swallowing movements Gastrointestinal reactions. ➡
All of them are space environment technologies. (Kijima) Technology?
Well, from Kijima-kun's point of view➡
You might think that such a thing is a technology.
No, that's not true.
Safety is the first priority in space.
The same goes for food.
(Kijima) Um...how many other people are in charge of space food?
It's just you and me.
Ah...
What? Isn't it amazing? Obama's mackerel is .
Did you come without asking me anything? Huh?
I heard that this school is going to go bankrupt.
No, uh... is that true?
It's not that easy... Thank you for waiting.
Funamori set meal. (Kurose) It's easy.
Maintenance costs for the boat we own➡
It costs billions of dollars.
Even on a small boat.
I'll enjoy having this .
It costs twice as much as a regular course.
From the prefecture's finances➡
It's inevitable that people will talk about losing it.
But Wakasa Suisan➡
It's a prestigious school that has been around since the Meiji era, right?
Executives of general trading companies, major food manufacturers, etc.
(Kurose) Mr. Asano.
This school is now a school where I can pursue my dreams.
A school that fights against reality.
⚟ (Terao) Ruka. (Ruka) Welcome back.
Are you outside again? I'm catching a cold.
I can always see the sky.
It's not empty. Beyond the sky. universe .
"If you get licked, it's over"...
What are you doing?
You won't understand if you keep quiet.
Are you too kind?
You won't understand if you keep quiet!
Ah, yes, that's right. It's like this, it's like this.
Try saying something!
Hey! Get up there!
Terao! It's you, you.
Hey, what are those eyes? Oh? Where are you looking?
People are talking, so look into their eyes!
Hey!
Why are you fiddling with your cell phone during class?
Get your cell phone out! It's confiscated! It's confiscated! Oraora!
Huh...what are you doing?
What are you doing?
I'm home . (Miyuki) Welcome back.
Hey mom. (Miyuki) Huh?
That's what happens after I graduate.
Ah, everyone at the market was so happy.
I feel like I'll feel more energetic if Nami stays with me.
Open page 24.
As you can see from the graph➡
If the catch of mackerel decreases, the unit price will...
Terao-kun, wake up.
Class is starting. Wake up!
(Yuzuki) Teacher.
Wake up!
what?
"What?" isn't it? If you want to sleep, sleep at home.
Well, I'll do that.
Ah, ah….
Hmm...maybe it's not suitable for me.
(Kazuko) Yes.
Huh... a little bit .
It would be rude to sigh after eating my meal.
Sorry. (Kazuko) Did you come on a business trip or something?
Teacher at Wakasa Fisheries High School.
(Kazuko) Micchan! (Michio) What's up, Kazu-chan?
Wakamizu's teacher is coming. (Michio) Wakasui! ?
I've only just moved in.
Young teachers are rare these days. (Michio) Hey, yeah...
I guess so. I'm talking about it going bankrupt.
Shigeru! (Kazuko) Mr. Shigeru! a little bit .
That's bad, that's a bad thing to hear.
No, it's okay. Um... I heard that too.
Oh yeah? Hona, huh? (Michio) Sayana.
(Michio and Kazuko) Hahaha...
(Shigenobu) Was my son sleeping? Huh?
Sosuke Terao.
Eh! ? Oh... um... is that your father?
Hahaha... Sorry.
I scolded my son in a strange way today...
Yeah.
If you get carried away, please slam me.
(Michio) Shigeru: That's the problem. It's different from our time.
These people's times are so rough ➡
Of course, among students➡
It seems that the teacher and students also wrestled with each other.
At Wakasa Suisan? (Kazuko) Yes.
Mr. Shigeru is from there. This person too.
Shigeru is my junior.
Kazu-chan Ui. (Kazuko) Yes, yes.
(Shigenobu) Teacher Teacher Well, one drink. (Michio) Please, please.
Oh, sorry. Please, please.
I understand now.
(Shigenobu) Delicious. Delicious. (Kazuko) Yes.
Graduation album.
This and this. This is me at this time.
(Shigenobu) Young! Nice face.
Looks like everyone is having fun. That's it! Hahaha!
Hey Shigeru! What are you doing? Follow the teacher.
The store is already closed today.
(Tadokoro) Yes, sorry for keeping you waiting for the takoyaki sauce.
Oh, teacher, how did you do it? School.
What do you think...
You did a lot of work.
But I'm still young so it's okay.
Well, I'm about to tell you the most important thing.
yes .
(Tadokoro) Find your next job as soon as possible.
I don't know anything about this town.
is that so . Well then.
(Tadokoro) Looks like you've been hit hard.
Why did I come to such a failing school in the first place?
What are you doing...
What do you want to do?
It's serious.
♬ (music)
“What do you want to do?”
♬～
what? Oh no, I'm sorry.
Don't say it at school. It makes people think I'm getting carried away.
No one would think that.
It's better if you don't bother us. Why?
There's no point in saying anything.
There is no need to ask the teacher for anything.
I mean, why did you come here?
Something I was asked about earlier...
Ah... .
I love the sea and diving is my hobby.
Because it looked like something fun.
only?
Ah, Sugawara-san, what do you enjoy doing?
Is it really dancing? I don't know.
I don't know, so I just dance. I see.
He looked really nice, though.
The teacher doesn't understand.
I was born here, so I want to work here.
Somehow, it seems like everyone works here.
I'm not saying I'm giving up though.
That's what everyone does.
There is nothing that only we can do➡
It's not like I have any big dreams.
I don't expect anything from anyone.
No matter what I said, people thought it was just that and it was over.
Hmm...
You won't know until you try it.
I understand. No matter what I say, you won't be treated.
You won't know if you'll be accepted until you try.
You won't know until you try.
No, I understand. No, I don't know.
There are some things I understand. No.
You won't know until you try.
Even if I tried, I couldn't stand the statue.
Huh? Oh... were you watching?
What an idiot teacher.
♬～
``You won't know until you try.''
[The universe is infinitely far away]
[But the first step is at your feet]
gentlemen…?
Off-campus training? yes .
You used to do it, right?
It's better to move your body instead of just sitting at your desk ➡
I think the students will have fun too.
(Kusakabe) Well. ➡
But we must bow to those involved in the fishing industry. ➡
It's not an easy story.
No, I buy that desire.
Leave it to me. please .
Practical training! ? yes .
I was wondering if I could learn about fishing with the students.
That's impossible. (Sonoda) Lately➡
Fuel prices are going up and fish is cheap. (Susaki) The fishing is poor and I can't see the future.
I don't have the luxury of doing that right now.
(Susaki/Sonoda) No, no….
Should I go home? Oh wait...
You just told me to leave it to me.
If Mr. Momose says no, no.
Eh... (Shigenobu) Teacher, what's wrong?
The off-campus training that was shown to me at the graduation event➡
Now I'm wondering if I can do it again.
That's a good idea. Wakamizu's students would be a force to be reckoned with.
Good for you, Momo-san!
Well then.
I guess so. (Susaki/Sonoda) Let's do it.
gentlemen!
(Sounds of excitement from students)
(Nami) I'll get it. (Ryūku) Yes.
(Nami) Ryuku: You're fishing for red mackerel and mackerel.
Ah, that's bad.
As expected of Nami. I can work here anytime.
I hate this manly place.
Uncle, leave it here. (Momose) Oh.
(Nami) You'll get used to it, Terao.
I come here every day before school and help out. ➡
That's the reason I'm sleepy.
♬～
(Sounds of excitement from students)
Kanagashira and . (Yuzuki/Nami) So cute!
show me . Teacher teacher teacher! ➡
Cold, cold! What are you doing now? ➡
Here it is. Acchisee, over there.
There are also two types. 2 types. yes .
this… . Oh... that's it.
Wait a minute... Teacher! Is that a slut?
This is a squid.
Teacher, that's enough. Carry it.
(Students) Good luck, teacher. Teacher, teacher, do your best.
(Student) Ah! Sorry, sorry.
Wow...! (Momose) Ah! Hey!
Sorry.
What next...? Don't do anything.
♬～
An interesting teacher has arrived.
⚟ (Momose) Shigeru-san! (Shigenobu) Oh? ➡
Ahhh again. (Nami) What happened?
(Shigenobu) Oh? (Nami) What happened?
Lately, large numbers of large jellyfish have been appearing. ➡
The net is torn, and the boat where the fish are escaping stops.
About the problems faced by fishermen in the field➡
Let's all think about it.
(Nagisa) Isn't tearing the net dangerous?
The one that swells when you get stung, right?
(Ryūku) It's almost swollen. The poison is weak, but the amount is dangerous. ➡
When I touched it, it was confirmed to be a welt. Hey Terao.
Huh?
How can I sleep when I'm talking to this guy?
That's it!
What if I make a bag or something with this and sell it?
That's good! (Yuzuki) What?
Genius! (Sounds of students talking)
(sound of clapping hands)
(Ryūku) This one is 98% water, so when you process it, there's almost nothing left.
Well, that's the end of the story.
There was nothing we could do.
Well, I have to try it...
You don't understand.
Are you skipping lunch today too? (Nagisa) I'm on a diet.
Persimmon peas are good.
Are you there? (Yuzuki) I don't need it.
I mean, look at this. Today's main.
Corner boil?
(Nagisa) It's hilarious.
what? (Nami) About that jellyfish➡
What can't be done? (Nagisa) Why are you having Kakuni for lunch?
Leftovers from last night. I'll get angry if you leave it behind, so please.
(Nami) It would be a waste if there were so many jellyfish.
What is mottainai? It's just a nuisance.
Eat one of these. (Nami) This problem is with me.
Don't force yourself on me. I'm on a diet.
(Terao) Nothing can be done.
About one is fine.
It's full of collagen. My skin is so smooth.
Yuzuki: That's fine.
which one?
(Nami) When salt is removed from sea ingredients➡
You can make bittern. ➡
That means if you take water from this jellyfish➡
This means that you can extract the plump collagen and bittern.
in? (Nami) Extract those two➡
Make different food. (Yuzuki/Nagisa) Another one?
Tofu . (Yuzuki/Nagisa) Tofu! ?
When you think of bittern, you think of tofu. It's jiggly with tofu.
that… . (Nagisa) Okay!
(East Exit) Today is sensory evaluation day.
He says that the way we perceive taste changes in space➡
Apparently there are also astronauts.
In other words, it is meaningless to give the same evaluation as on the ground.
A special environment of numbers and space➡
Both must be considered.
please .
(East exit) What do you think?
No, to be honest, I don't think it's appropriate to call this a meal.
That's right! This is definitely more delicious than baby food!
Even if we think so, we must not slack off. ➡
Safety is our top priority. (Kijima) Yes.
(Yuki) Peperoncino again?
Are you currently in charge of space food?
(Kijima) Yes.
You seem dissatisfied. (Kijima) No, I'd say I'm dissatisfied...
A person who has been analyzing ship hulls in the technical department➡
If you suddenly get transferred to the department that creates menus...
There's a menu table.
I want to explore space.
We also performed structural calculations and track design. ➡
Now it's the viscosity and salt concentration of the sauce.
(Yuki) You underestimate the sauce too much. ➡
If this drop flies off in zero gravity, it will enter the equipment and cause a short circuit. ➡
A single drop can stop a mission.
I understand. ➡
But… someone who has never cooked before➡
It felt like I was suddenly asked to stand in the kitchen.
I understand, but it's not a place for anyone to stand.
Well, that's... yes.
(Yuki) If so, no one has eaten it yet➡
Isn't it a bad idea to create a new menu?
♬～
It stinks! Damn it!
(Nagisa) That's tough. (Yuzuki) The sound is amazing.
(Yuzuki) Do you have a memo? (Nami) Let’s record it➡
I don't understand. (Nagisa) If you do that, why don't you give it a title?
How about “Save the town with jellyfish”? (Nagisa) Isn't it a bit big?
(Nami) How about jellyfish cooking?
(Ryūku) Honma. (Haruka) What's fun?
Mr. Kikuchi was in Tokyo, right?
(Haruka) Yeah. (Ryūku) Have you ever been to Harajuku?
(Haruka) Yes, though. (Ryūku) Yeah. ➡
I want to open a cafe on Takeshita Street. (Haruka) Hmm.
⚟ (Nami and her friends talking)
(Nami and her friends talking)
♬～
thank you . It was heavy, wasn't it?
(Terao) You just get used to it.
Ah, thank you for the other day. Umm, practical training.
Ah, that kid.
I met you the other day too. Even then, I was looking at the sky like that.
I said it was the universe.
universe?
Ruka!
Welcome back brother.
(Terao) Did you go outside again? I'm catching a cold.
⚟I was looking forward to something and had a hard time sleeping.
⚟Jellyfish? ⚟Yeah.
(Nagisa) Wow, what is this! ? (Yuzuki) Something from yesterday➡
There are so many. (Nami) Definitely Terao.
(Yuzuki) How much should I do?
(Nami) Okay. (Yuzuki) Yeah.
(Yuzuki) Okay, Nami, I'll pass behind you. It's hot, it's hot. ➡
Oh... Okay, let's go. ➡
Oh! (Nagisa) Purupuru.
Add powder. (Yuzuki/Nami) OK!
(Microwave notification sound)
♬～
(Nagisa/Yuzuki) Huh! (Nami) Yes!
(3 people) Delicious!
A recital? The results of this time➡
Let's put this all together.
Is it okay for us to release something like this?
That's all I've accomplished.
If you put it out there, it's a win.
Victory ! ? (Nami) It's impossible, it's impossible.
You won't know until you try. (Yuzuki) Are you going to tell me the truth?
(Kurose) Oh? (Kurose/Yuzuki) Hello.
So please hurry up and bring all the materials for your presentation.
Eh! ? (Nagisa) I'm so tired.
The judges don't want to be impressed.
Look at data and numbers.
That's why you guys did such amazing things➡
We have to show our track record.
For example, the amount of damage caused by jellyfish on the coast of Wakasa Bay➡
such as protein content. (Yuzuki) Muzu.
Well, I'll try making it anyway. Yeah .
(Yuzuki) Yes. (Nami) Yes.
(Yuzuki) Please. (Nami) Nice to meet you.
(typing sound)
♬～
We extract collagen from large jellyfish➡
We developed tofu as a new value-added food.
(Nagisa) This research aims to effectively utilize local resources and ➡
The purpose is to reduce the burden on fishermen.
(Yuzuki) We can also expect economic effects from branding.
(applause)
Well done, Mr. Asano. Well done.
The students did a great job.
(Kurose) Don't be so humble➡
The teacher must have rewritten all the materials. ➡
That was perfect. ➡
The students invented it, but the teacher took credit for winning. ➡
I'm sure the students understand that too.
(Nami) “In our sea➡
There is a jellyfish that is called a nuisance.'' ➡
`` No one has expectations and no one hits the market ➡
It has been labeled as useless.” ➡
``There is no destination, just being carried away by the ocean current➡
Just swimming around the place➡
Troublesome jellyfish” ➡
``I feel like that➡
I thought it was just like us.”
(Nami) “There’s no way I can be the main character in the ocean➡
I don't have anything special.'' ➡
"One of many others"
(Nami) “But the truth is, there are things that only we can do.” ➡
``Even if you're a nuisance that no one expects from you➡
It must be worth it.” ➡
"We wanted to prove it."
(Nami) “That’s why I invented this jellyfish tofu.”
♬～
What should I do if I destroy the students' thoughts?
(Kijima) Certification standards? (East Exit) Major food manufacturers are now ➡
We're starting to get into space food.
We have to set the standards.
Do you know HACCP? (Kijima) Hassap?
Don't you even know that? (Yuzuki) What? What is Hamap?
(Ryūku) Hassap na. (Yuzuki) I don't understand English.
(Ryūku) It's in the textbook.
The food hygiene management system that NASA devised to produce space food.
NASA is that NASA? Are you going to explore space?
There's nothing else like it.
ＮＡＳＡ ？
(East Exit) Yes, it is a food hygiene management system created by NASA. ➡
It is essential for future food hygiene management. ➡
The space environment is harsh. ➡
We need to aim for HACCP or higher.
(Nagisa) Then we need to get that HACCP➡
Does that mean the jellyfish tofu we made can't be commercialized?
(Ryūku) Yes, from now on, we won't be able to do anything without that HACCP.
If you do it, you should take it now.
(Ryūku) Huh? It's an impossible game right now. ➡
Don't take HACCP lightly. (Yuzuki) Certainly. ➡
It was made by NASA, the space agency. ➡
Isn't it impossible for us? (Nagisa) It's just impossible.
There's no point in just doing it.
Try it, you won't understand.
(Ryūku) No, no, I understand. (Nami) I don't understand.
Let's try it. You can even make jellyfish tofu!
That's right. (Yuzuki) Should I try it?
That's amazing. Oh, teacher.
He's way ahead of me.
(Yuzuki) What is that?
Um... can I join in too?
It's obvious. What should I do if my teacher is missing?
(Ryūku) No, that's why it's impossible to get HACCP easily.
Does that mean we can make space food at home if we take that?
Well, if you get HACCP, yes.
If we did that, wouldn't we be able to send our mackerel cans into space?
No compromises are necessary. Shauninuni.
It's Kijima-kun's turn.
(Kijima) It is true that the space environment is harsh.
One microorganism or one piece of debris can lead to an accident.
Failure is not an option. (East exit) Yes.
(Kijima) I will create a new standard for space food.
Sending our canned mackerel to space.
[At that time, no one knew about it]
[With high school students from this small port town➡
A new teacher who came from outside...]
Thank you for waiting.
Oh, I don't have chopsticks. You can use your hands, right? You can use your hands...
Thank you for your hard work.
[With the adults who live here➡
With the support of adults watching over the universe➡
Eventually it will be true➡
Canned mackerel made by high school students will be sent into space]
[It all started with a dream of just one word]
[“Canned Mackerel Goes to Space”]