=Penthouse=
"All characters, locations,"
"incidents, and backgrounds"
"of this drama are fictitious."
That wasn't a dream.
Seol A
fell at Hera Palace.
I... I killed her.
Yoon Hee.
Soo Ryeon.
You're early.
=Episode 17=
Well, why did you
want to meet here?
I have something to tell you.
To tell you the truth,
I used you all this time.
What... What do you mean?
The person who sent you
to Seol A's place in Bosong Village.
That was me.
And I arranged everything
so you'd move to Hera Palace.
I used you.
I really needed you...
for my revenge.
I am...
Seol A's mother.
It must be shocking.
I'm sorry that I'm only telling you now.
I was busy looking for Seol A's killer.
And now,
I'm ready to catch the culprit.
The culprit?
Ro Na, what are you up to?
It's the weekend. Let's go out...
What are you doing?
Stop that.
You'll get hurt.
You were right.
Talent?
That's completely useless.
Money and connections are
the talents I need.
Someone like me
shouldn't have got into singing.
So it doesn't matter if I lost my voice.
Let me go, darn it!
Let me go!
How did you get in here?
Seo Jin is
the beginning of my misfortune.
If anyone tries to ruin my girl's future,
I'll kill them all.
Yoon Hee.
You're hurt. You need to get treated.
Let me go!
I'm not leaving like this.
I'm going to let Ro Na
get into Cheonga Arts High.
I can't let her live like I did!
- Yoon Hee, come here.
- Let me go!
Let go!
Yoon Hee!
Give it to me.
Give me your phone!
What are you doing here?
Ms. Oh?
What happened to your face?
Did something happen?
People at Hera Palace
are trying to kill me.
I'm so scared.
Please help me.
Help me. I don't want to die, Ms. Oh.
Why would anyone try to kill you?
You're fine. No one is around.
Let's get out of here.
You're fine.
One second.
I need to find something.
I hid my phone somewhere.
You should go first.
How dare you try to run from me?
No, please...
Please don't kill me.
Die.
- No, please.
- Where's the phone?
Where's your phone?
"Beware, Risk of Falling"
Ms. Oh?
It was you?
Are you the one who saved me?
Thank you.
If you're gone,
Ro Na can get in.
If you're gone for good...
Hello?
What? Where are you calling from?
Cheonga Arts High School? Okay.
What...
What did you just say?
We have an extra slot for Bae Ro Na
in the vocal music department.
An extra slot?
But why...
I mean, how?
One of the kids
who got accepted died yesterday.
Yoon Hee, are you okay?
I'll tell you everything.
When you witnessed Cho Sang Heon's death,
I was actually...
there in that house.
Cho Sang Heon?
Then...
the one who killed Cho Sang Heon was...
you?
Basically, yes.
But I don't feel guilty
over that man's death.
He only got what he deserved.
Soo Ryeon, I have...
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I let you buy the house in Bosong Village
for keeping your mouth shut
on Cho Sang Heon's death.
You need to purchase
Unit 501 of Building 3 by tomorrow.
I made you move to Min Seol A's house.
All these didn't happen by chance.
I planned everything.
Don't you get what I'm saying?
Why?
Why did you do that?
Ever since Seol A died,
my life has been simply painful.
It was like a living hell everyday.
I needed to do everything I could
to catch her killer.
That's why...
That's why I used your feelings.
I needed you,
who despises Cheon Seo Jin.
She's involved in my daughter's death.
Seo Jin?
It's not just her.
Dan Tae, Kyu Jin,
Yoon Chul, Ma Ri, Sang A,
and all of their children.
They're all accomplices in Seol A's death.
They locked her up in the mechanical room,
abandoned her body,
then burned down her house
to humiliate and insult her.
They all must be punished.
I'll make sure they pay
for everything they did to my girl.
The police will
begin the reinvestigation very soon.
What about the evidence?
If the culprit hasn't been caught,
doesn't that mean there's no evidence?
I saw it.
You saw what?
I saw the person
who pushed Seol A off
from right here, on the 47th floor.
And who...
is that?
She has a ruby ring on her hand.
A red ruby ring.
It has to be the same ruby ring
Seo Jin wore at the party.
"Logan Lee"
One second.
Is something going on?
I'm fine.
I'll call you later.
She has a ruby ring on her hand.
A red ruby ring.
It wasn't a ruby ring.
It was this apple necklace.
I killed Seol A?
I killed someone?
No, no.
I never did that.
No, I couldn't have.
I didn't do it!
I killed Soo Ryeon's daughter?
No.
No. It...
It wasn't me.
No!
No, it wasn't me.
It wasn't me.
I didn't do it.
I didn't!
Everything is about to come to an end,
my daughter.
Hello?
Did you have a good talk with Ms. Oh?
She got too shocked,
so I couldn't elaborate.
I should've told her a bit earlier.
How much
do you trust her?
What do you mean?
"Oh Yoon Hee"
To be honest, Ms. Oh is
one of the suspects.
There's no way.
She's like my little sister.
You need to be more coolheaded.
Ms. Oh was...
also at Hera Palace
on the night Seol A died.
That's true, but--
Don't trust anyone but yourself,
not even me.
"Cheonga Arts High 1st Semester Midterm"
"April 21, 1st test, Maths"
Dad.
Memorise the answers.
You can do that much, can't you?
This is something only I can do.
Don't ever let Eun Byeol win.
I'll check if you've memorised it all.
Be at the study in the morning.
Five, three, one, three.
Five, three, one, three, five.
Four, two, one, two, four.
Secretary Cho.
Report Hye In's death
the first thing in the morning.
Okay.
Sim Soo Ryeon.
I don't know what you're up to,
but I can't let you go yet.
"2020 Jakomo Headquarters Site"
Ro Na.
You're playing the piano again?
Why did you push me?
I liked you, Ms. Oh.
Yoon Hee.
It was you?
Was it you
who killed Seol A?
Soo Ryeon.
I... I wasn't going to kill her.
I must've been out of my mind, Soo Ryeon.
Why did you do that to the poor girl?
You thought it'd be fine
since she's an orphan?
If someone doesn't have parents,
they can just die a wrongful death?
How can you kill someone
just to get your girl into the school?
Soo Ryeon, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I must've been out of my mind.
All I thought about was Ro Na.
I did that before I knew it.
Soo Ryeon, please. I was out of my mind.
Please forgive me.
Soo Ryeon, please.
Please, I beg you.
Please forgive me.
Forgive you?
How dare you ask me to forgive you?
Your daughter deserves to die
just as my daughter did.
Just like how Seol A is dead!
No!
Not Ro Na! Please!
Kill me instead, please!
No!
Soo Ryeon, no, please.
I'm so sorry!
Die!
Hello?
Is this Ms. Oh Yoon Hee?
This is the police.
What?
The police?
The police will
begin the reinvestigation very soon.
So where's your school?
I don't go to school.
I got kicked out.
You can't go around stealing stuff, kid.
You're a huge troublemaker.
Ro Na.
What's going on?
Are you okay?
Are you Bae Ro Na's mother?
Yes.
What's going on?
Why is my daughter here?
She stole beer from a convenience store.
It's on the CCTV footage,
and she admitted to what she did.
Ro Na.
Did you really steal that?
I did.
I stole it.
They won't sell it to me,
so I had no choice but to steal it.
Are you crazy, Ro Na?
Why?
It doesn't even cost that much.
Why did you hit me?
Who do you think you are?
You don't have any right to hit me.
Like mum, like daughter, no?
I didn't want to go home. This is great.
Get me locked up
in the jail, the prison, or wherever else!
What in the world is wrong with you?
Everything is already driving me insane.
So what has got into you?
Why do you make me so worried?
And now you're stealing things?
You're stealing now?
Are you really crazy?
Stop hitting me!
- Are you crazy?
- Ma'am.
Are you crazy?
- Ma'am, calm down.
- Stop hitting me!
- Calm down, ma'am.
- What's with you?
- What will you do now?
- Ma'am!
Let me go.
That hurts.
Why are we here?
It's cold.
I'm leaving.
You
don't want to make up with me, do you?
And you don't want to go back to school.
You have no plan...
to pull yourself together
and live a good life, right?
Do you know what I had to do
to get you into Cheonga High?
Stop using me as an excuse.
I've done everything I could.
Okay.
Just quit everything.
Quit your school.
Quit singing.
Quit everything,
and go do whatever you want.
I don't want to live anymore.
The moment you gave up on your life,
my life ended as well.
I no longer have a reason to live.
There's no reason.
I don't want to live anymore.
So you're going to kill yourself here?
How can you say that to your daughter?
You'll kill yourself over my theft?
Is that the only reason?
What do you expect me to do?
I hate you.
I hate you so much.
Can't I even do this much?
Am I not allowed to throw a fit
and whine on you?
You're my mum.
You're the only one I can rant at.
Can't you let me do that?
How am I going to live
without you, Mum?
You're the only one I've got.
I'm sorry, Ro Na.
I'm so sorry, Ro Na.
I try not to,
but I get so angry when I see you.
Why did you meet Eun Byeol's dad
and let her say that to me?
I'm so angry that I'm going crazy.
Ro Na.
That... That was my mistake.
But nothing like you imagine
happened on that day.
Trust me, will you?
You are...
You really are the only one for me, Ro Na.
You're the only one in my life.
I mean it.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry I'm not a good mum for you.
I made you suffer so much.
I'm so sorry, Ro Na.
What's so bad about you?
I wouldn't trade you
for a thousand of Ms. Cheon.
I really love how you're my mum.
You're a nice person.
No. No, I'm not.
I'm sorry.
Mum.
I'll go back to school.
I won't give up on singing either.
I won't let Eun Byeol win. Never.
I'll win that trophy at Cheonga Festival,
and I'll get into Seoul University.
I'll become a success
and protect you, Mum.
What am I going to do?
I made you
a daughter of a murderer.
What am I going to do, Ro Na?
Don't get mad even if I don't do well
on this test.
I might be the last place.
Should I go with you?
No.
I can manage.
From now on, I'm in this fight alone.
One second.
I'm glad
I didn't throw away your uniform.
You look the prettiest
when you're in your uniform.
See you later.
Pull yourself together, Yoon Hee.
Nobody knows.
No one.
I must brace myself
for Ro Na's sake.
Because...
I'm a mother.
I'm Ro Na's mother.
Hey.
You're coming back to school?
Can you
do me a favour?
The necklace.
"Soo Ryeon"
Why are you so surprised?
You're leaving early for work.
Yes, I have
a meeting in the morning.
Ro Na called me today saying
she's going back to school.
I heard things were okay with the police.
I'm so relieved.
Yes.
I'm a little busy.
I'll see you later.
Do you have some time tonight?
I want to ask something
about the night Seol A died.
Tonight?
I have to do overtime, so I'll be busy.
And I don't know anything,
so there's nothing I can tell you.
I didn't live here at that time.
I understand how confusing this is.
I'm so sorry, Yoon Hee.
But I
must find the culprit who killed Seol A.
I need your help desperately.
I'll help you
with anything you need
to get your revenge on Seo Jin.
My revenge?
Just be honest.
You're trying to get what you want
without getting any blood on your hands.
You knew I'd jump in and help you
if Seo Jin was involved.
Everything was a lie.
You pretended to help me
and worry about me.
You were a hypocrite!
Is that wrong?
That's how it all began,
but my heart really went out for you.
I don't want to hear this.
Why me?
Why did you get me involved?
Why did you shake my life around,
send me to Bosong Village,
and get me involved with Min Seol A?
Do you have any idea how hard it was
for Ro Na and me?
Why did you do that?
You're also a mum who has a daughter.
Then you could try to understand me.
The culprit is in Hera Palace.
So what do you expect me to do?
I need you to testify.
Please go to the police
and tell them as much as you know.
The police?
Me?
Why should I?
Do you know what this is?
Seol A's ashes are in this necklace.
My poor girl who died a miserable death
is in here.
Stop talking about Seol A.
Yoon Hee.
I'm late. I have to go.
"Cheonga Medical Centre"
"30 Years with Our Patients"
Goodness.
Look at how pathetic you are.
You got divorced
and kicked out of your house.
I can't believe you can still sleep.
What brings you here so early?
Have you heard?
Chairman Joo signed an MOU
with Logan Lee,
and they are
building a casino hotel in Myeong-dong.
Isn't it good that he's doing something
with the money that's tied up?
Don't make it sound that easy!
Because you took care
of your emergency with the alimony?
We put in
60 billion won into that land.
How can he sign the MOU
before he tells us anything?
It means he thinks we're both pushovers!
What if
that land turns into a jackpot?
We might not be able to take our share!
So? What's your plan?
We need
to assert our ownership.
How did you become a doctor
with such a slow brain of yours?
Shouldn't you be the most furious
at Chairman Joo?
It looks like you already packed up
and resigned from the hospital.
You need to figure out
a way to make a living from now on.
Did you find a new hospital?
Where is it? Your hometown?
Why should I go back to my hometown?
I've got a lot of patients here.
What if you don't?
Did you forget
the contract you signed with Seo Jin?
You said you would take seven billion
and leave Cheonga Medical Centre
forever, didn't you?
No.
I've just been appointed
as a director of Cheonga Medical Centre.
What are you talking about?
The day before my father-in-law passed,
he told me to take this hospital.
So I'm moving my stuff
in the director's office today.
I wanted to turn it down,
but it is his last wish,
so I should do it, shouldn't I?
Does Seo Jin know?
Not yet.
She'll find out soon enough.
"Question, Answer"
Hey, Seok Hoon. Why are you so late?
I thought you weren't coming.
Come in.
Who?
My gosh.
What are you doing here?
Didn't you drop out? You're back?
Gosh, no way.
She didn't even take the exam yesterday.
Where's my seat?
- What?
- My gosh.
Move.
Oh, okay.
Thanks.
What is going on now?
He's being openly nice to her?
Am I the only one who finds this odd?
I'm going out with Ro Na.
So you'd better watch what you say.
What?
Be my boyfriend.
Didn't you hear me?
You can't be serious.
What are you thinking?
You said you liked me.
So let's date.
I think it'll be fun.
Since I'm returning after I dropped out,
I want to plan a little surprise event.
Seok Hoon.
Have you completely lost your mind?
What? You're going out with Ro Na?
Anyone can tell that she's just using you.
As a shield to return to school.
Don't you see that?
I don't care.
Whatever her reason is.
- What?
- Everyone, be seated.
The exam will begin in 10 minutes.
- The call cannot be connected.
- Gosh.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Joo Dan Tae.
What the heck are you thinking?
You haven't even apologised yet.
Yes.
Why are you calling so early?
Did you hear the news?
About Cheonga Foundation's
newest appointment decision.
If there was such news, I'd know about it.
Ma'am, we have a problem.
I have to go, Attorney Lee.
Hello?
Chief Director Cheon Myung Soo
sure had sharp foresight.
My gosh.
Bae Ro Na is back.
What did you say?
I thought she wanted to drop out.
She decided against it.
She even brought a consent form
signed by her mother.
Where is she now?
"Music Class 1"
Ma'am.
I'm so glad
that Ro Na is back.
Let's be honest.
She's way too talented to drop out.
She's smart, talented,
and kind.
She's perfect in every way,
unlike one of the students that I know.
She'll become
a world-famous classical singer.
Since when did you care so much
about Ro Na?
Ever since she was bullied
by the kids at Hera Palace.
Is that so?
And that's why
I plan to take
extra good care of her from now on
to protect such a talented student.
Anyway, have a good day, ma'am.
Wait, no.
Our soon-to-be chief director.
How about I just call you "Soon-to-be"?
Soon-to-be.
Soon-to-be!
"JKING Holdings"
Seowon Bank won't let us take out a loan?
Do they know how much our net worth is?
I don't get it either.
What else can we do
if we fail to get a loan?
Logan will only let you become a co-CEO
if you can invest the same amount.
Many companies, including Oseong Group,
are trying to reach out to him.
If he wants to cancel the deal
because of the investment...
That won't happen.
Did you take care of it?
Yes, sir.
I guess it's time
to show him the new collateral.
Ms. Oh.
Call Logan.
I have something to show him.
"Jakomo"
Despite the bad economy,
our sales went up in the last quarter,
and we also scored high
in customer satisfaction.
My gosh.
Thank you all.
Since our products are doing very well,
how about we use this type of leather
to increase our profit margins?
Our main goal isn't to sell products.
We're a mindful company that sells value.
To keep our customers,
we must stick to high-quality materials.
"Hye In's caregiver"
Is everything okay with Hye In?
Well, apparently,
someone registered her as dead,
so they've put the treatment on hold.
What's going on?
What do you mean?
Someone registered her as dead?
You saw this coming.
Registering her death
will secure his ownership
over half of her land.
We cannot let him take that land.
My late father left it to Hye In.
He tried to kill her.
How dare he covet that land.
I just got a call from Joo Dan Tae.
He wants to show me a land lot.
It's probably the same one.
He has no shame.
We can't put it off any longer.
Schedule a meeting with him right away.
Oh, Princess Je Ni!
How did you do on your exam?
Was the tutor spot on about the questions?
Don't ask. I bombed it.
Get me a new tutor.
But...
I did better than she did.
What? You beat Eun Byeol?
So you got the highest mark?
Eun Byeol, you got a perfect score
on everything else.
She marked her answers wrong by mistake
and totally bombed her exam.
She got 58.
The lowest math exam score in our class.
What? 58?
Eun Byeol? You got 58?
Hey, Eun Byeol.
My gosh.
Ro Na came back today.
She came back?
You mean, Ro Na came to school?
Are you serious?
That's why Eun Byeol had a breakdown.
She changed her answer sheet 10 times,
saying she made mistakes.
Then she was rushed for time,
so she marked the wrong ones.
Here's something even more shocking.
Ro Na and Seok Hoon announced
that they're dating.
What? Ro Na and Seok Hoon?
Why would he date her?
Gosh, what is going on?
What took you so long?
I told you to run over here
whenever I called.
What the heck are you thinking?
Why are you back?
Have you forgotten everything?
Shall I tell the whole world that your mum
is an adulteress?
Did you just scoff?
Yes.
Go tell everyone.
What?
If you want everyone to know
that your dad cheated on your mum,
go tell people.
What did you say?
Hey.
You're scared, aren't you?
I bet you're really bothered
by the fact that I'm back.
That's why you marked the wrong answers.
You got a perfect score on everything
until yesterday.
You need to be stronger mentally.
What if...
you make the same mistake on your CSAT?
Bae Ro Na! Do you have a death wish?
I haven't even started yet.
Brace yourself
for what's to come.
Ro Na.
Hey, Seok Hoon.
Want to come over and study with me?
My mum isn't home now.
We can also have dinner together.
Sure, sounds good.
I told him I missed him,
and he came right away.
Let's go. I'm hungry.
How dare you hit on Seok Hoon!
Are you a gold-digger just like your mum?
Hey! Are you done?
Eun Byeol, enough!
Why do you always take her side?
You don't know anything!
Why do you even like her?
Do you not know what kind of girl she is?
Her mum is an adulteress.
Her mum is a disgusting homewrecker
who destroyed my family!
My mum is not an adulteress.
Watch what you say!
She seduced a married man.
She's a gold-digger and an adulteress.
Defending her won't change that fact!
Seok Hoon, she's far below your league.
How could you date a lowlife like her?
Aren't you embarrassed?
How are we different?
We're nothing special.
Do you realise that?
We might even be worse.
We act all classy
and superior than others,
but we're rotting inside.
What?
How could you compare us
to that good-for-nothing?
Why not?
Because your mum will be
the chief director of the foundation
and my dad owns a big company?
Do you want to know the real truth?
My dad and your mum are seeing each other.
What did you
just say?
They're having an affair.
They're guilty of disgusting adultery.
Now you know, so stop causing a scene
before we end up humiliating ourselves.
No. No!
No way!
Follow her.
She's shopping at the department store.
Nothing out of the ordinary, sir.
Have someone tail her.
I want you back in the office.
Hello, Mr. Gu.
I think I've managed to fool them.
Okay.
She knew everything but hid it all along?
How long has she known about it?
I've booked a meeting with Logan, sir.
We should leave now.
Okay, thanks. Let's go.
Are you not feeling well?
Pardon?
You don't look so well.
I heard Ro Na dropped out of school.
If you ever need my help, let me know.
I don't think
Seo Jin will be happy to hear
what you just said.
I make my own decisions.
I decide who it is that I need
and when to help my people.
It's my call.
Thank you for saying that.
But my daughter went back to school today.
Really? I'm happy to hear that.
Oh, right.
I thought about what to give you
as a promotion gift and got you
something that befits your new position.
A new car.
I must ensure your safety
for the company's continued success.
You're giving me a car?
It's too big of a gift.
It's too much. I can't accept it.
Thank you for not telling anyone...
about what happened that day.
So you want to invest
with this site as collateral?
As you can see,
this prime location
will guarantee us a big loan.
Yes, yes.
The location is spot on.
I almost want it for myself.
Then as soon as we secure the loan,
I'll set up everything and proceed
with the co-ownership agreement.
All right.
I like the way you handle business,
- Mr. Joo.
- Thank you.
It's been a while, Logan.
What brings you here?
This is the furniture company I run.
Oh, really?
I was just talking some business
with Mr. Joo.
He's planning to invest
with this site as collateral.
I'll give you a tour and tell you more.
This way, please.
There seems to be some misunderstanding.
This land belongs to my daughter.
Unfortunately, she died a while ago.
So she no longer owns the land.
I am the rightful owner of this lot.
What are you talking about, honey?
What do you mean Hye In is dead?
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
Have you lost your mind?
You're losing your mind.
I clearly told you
to wait.
How could you go ahead
and register her death?
She died six months ago.
I'd say we've waited long enough.
It's not like she'll come back.
Why postpone it and pay a fine?
The value won't go up if it's left unused.
I own half of this land anyway,
so I can do whatever I want with it.
Did you refuse to get a divorce
because you wanted Hye In's land?
Or...
is it because I'm next?
Are you planning to kill me
so you can take full ownership over it?
What on earth are you talking about?
Did you think I wouldn't know
that you killed Hye In?
How much do you know?
What did you and Yoon Tae Ju
scheme together before he died?
Are you curious?
Do you want to know?
You can come in now.
"Hamin Hospital"
Joo Hye In...
Hye In, say hi to your dad.
Dad?
She's saying hi.
Aren't you happy to see her again?
Hye In?
Thanks to the treatment,
she's a lot better now.
Although it took her a while to recover
from all the sedatives they gave her
to make her stay asleep.
All her organs are almost
back to normal now.
She's learned to speak again,
and she can even walk a little.
Aren't you happy, honey?
You were always so good to Hye In.
What...
What in the world...
I brought her here because
she said she had something to say to you.
Hye In, why don't you tell him yourself?
Grandpa left this land to me as a gift.
I won't let anyone take it away from me.
Soo Ryeon.
How dare you lie to me
and hide Hye In.
Joo Dan Tae.
I'll make you pay
for everything you've done, one by one.
What in the world is going on, Mr. Joo?
Were you trying to put up
a fake collateral?
By claiming a living daughter was dead?
And this isn't even your property?
I'm very disappointed in you.
No, let me explain.
Logan.
I want you to know that
you can't do anything with this land
without Hye In's permission.
I've got to go.
She's not feeling well.
You idiot. How could you miss that?
You darn punk.
You didn't keep an eye on her properly.
What the heck have you been doing?
How could you not know
that Hye In was alive?
I'm sorry, sir.
I thought I was keeping
a watchful eye on her.
Shut it.
You said she was at the department store.
So how did she suddenly show up there?
You idiot, who were you tailing today?
Sim Soo Ryeon.
Enough is enough.
Soo Ryeon has another daughter?
Who's her father then?
My gosh.
She knew where Chairman Joo was.
That's why she brought her daughter there.
Are Soo Ryeon and Logan
helping each other?
That sounded too tense.
When singing high notes,
you should breathe from your stomach.
Let's try again.
Ro Na's singing
that day
was the best I had ever heard.
"Soo Ryeon"
The call cannot be connected.
Please leave a message--
Logan.
Wait by the penthouse exit.
I'll be right there.
Let's talk.
I'm busy right now.
I don't care how busy you are.
Why didn't you answer any of my calls?
You haven't given me
a proper explanation as to why
you were with Yoon Hee at the villa.
I told you...
I told you.
I went there to get some rest.
Then she happened to join me
after the team dinner.
She was wearing my clothes.
The clothes that you bought for me.
Her clothes were ruined,
so she had to get changed.
Do I have to explain everything to you?
Logan has finally signed the deal, right?
So fire her immediately.
Logan wants her around,
and so do I.
What?
Be careful.
There are many eyes watching.
Don't change the subject.
I don't know what you're thinking,
but don't forget the promise
we made when we got back together.
I decide whether we keep seeing each other
or break up.
I make the call.
Eun Byeol.
Open the door.
Please? Eun Byeol.
What are you doing here?
Who let him in?
I told you not to let him in.
Well, ma'am...
Don't yell at her.
She called me
because she was worried about Eun Byeol.
She won't come out of her room.
I heard she was throwing
and breaking things earlier.
She's angry because she bombed her exam.
If you're trying to use her as an excuse
to come back, give up already.
I have sole legal custody of Eun Byeol.
Even if it weren't for Eun Byeol,
we were bound to meet again anyway.
Goodness.
Is there unfinished business between us?
Oh, you need to leave the hospital soon.
Goodness.
I guess you haven't heard.
I have a new job.
A new job?
Where?
I'm surprised someone's still willing
to hire you.
Yes, Cheonga Medical Centre.
Are you kidding me?
I've been appointed
as the director of Cheonga Medical Centre.
I thought I should tell you myself.
What are you talking about?
I never approved such a decision.
How could you be appointed
as the new director of the hospital?
It's in your father's will.
Your approval won't be necessary.
"Will and Testament"
The day before he passed away,
he left Cheonga Medical Centre to me.
Well...
I had no idea back then,
but this was Father's last wish.
I look forward to working with you,
Chief Director Cheon Seo Jin.
You disgusting leech.
What's going on, Attorney Park?
Why didn't you tell me
about the appointment of a new director?
Come to my office now.
Right now!
"No Caller ID"
Who on earth...
Two, three...
Two, one, three, two, one, three, two...
"April 22, Science, English"
What are you doing?
Is this how you aced the exam?
Pretend you never saw this.
Dad got it for me.
Until when will you keep this up?
Dad said I could do this.
So just mind your own business.
Besides, you helped me fudge my grades
all this time.
Did you suddenly grow a conscience?
What happened to your arm?
Let go.
Did Dad do this to you?
Tell me. Did Dad do this?
I had to pay a price
for what I got.
Two, one, three...
This isn't called a price.
It's violence and abuse.
What's with you?
It's not like you didn't know.
Mind your own business!
I'll figure out what to do with my life.
You already ditched me anyway.
If this continues,
Dad will end up killing us.
I don't care.
I just have to beat Eun Byeol.
Two, one, five, three...
Sim Soo Ryeon!
Sim Soo Ryeon, where are you?
Where are you?
Jeez.
Where's Joo Hye In?
Where are you hiding her?
Somewhere you'll never find.
You can't dare to kill her again.
Tell me. Where's that brat?
How dare you treat me like a fool.
You don't deserve to be called human.
You worthless scumbag.
You're a murderer.
That doesn't matter at all.
Since we know more about each other now,
we can become a happier couple.
You're a psycho.
You're...
too classy,
elegant, and beautiful.
A woman like you
should be punished.
For deceiving your husband
and planning to backstab him.
I must punish you!
After you're punished,
everything will go back
to where it should be.
=Penthouse=
Let's go to the US together.
I'll make you happy.
You have no reason to feel guilty.
I've finally found a decent partner.
Why don't you use me?
Don't trust men too much.
I'm not in the mood
to put up with your temper.
It's beautiful.
Expect a bloodbath.
Someone might die.
They have to suffer the exact same way
to realise their sins.