=Penthouse=
"All characters, locations,"
"incidents, and backgrounds"
"of this drama are fictitious."
=Episode 16=
Dad!
Wait, Dad!
I'd rather die.
I can't let you leave like this!
You pathetic fool!
Just look at yourself!
You want to be my successor
when you're such a weakling?
Not a chance!
Cheonga belongs to Seo Young now.
I've had enough of this!
If I've lived my life wrong,
it's all your fault!
You always
compared me with Seo Young
and made us compete against each other.
You were always so hard on me!
You never truly loved me.
You used your children
for your own reputation!
I...
always craved to be loved.
That's why I had an affair.
How dare you talk back to me?
You're no longer my daughter!
No!
Cheonga is mine!
You can't take it from me!
Let go!
Let go. I said, let go.
No!
Let go!
- I said, let go.
- No!
Let go! Let go...
Seo Jin.
Dad.
Gosh, Dad!
Dad. No, Dad! Dad!
Dad!
Seo Jin.
No.
Seo Jin...
"CCTV, Cam 05"
"Delete CCTV footage"
"The video can't be restored once erased"
"Letter of Appointment"
"Name: Cheon Seo Young"
"Cheonga Arts Foundation: Cheon Myung Soo"
"Letter of Appointment"
"Cheonga Arts High School"
You can't do this to me.
You were the first
to abandon me.
Are you all right?
Mr. Kang, his driver, just called.
He said the chief director collapsed.
Ms. Cheon, you were with me today.
After that, you were in the lesson room.
What?
You must pull yourself together.
Will you fall down like this?
No.
I can't let that happen.
You should go.
I'll take care of the rest.
I never came here.
I never met my dad either.
Seo Jin!
Are you okay?
It's Dad! Seo Jin!
Open the door!
Get the master key.
Give me the key.
Can you come and open the door?
Open this!
- Seo Jin!
- Seo Jin.
What happened?
- Seo Jin!
Seo Jin!
- Get her quick.
Get her help.
Take her out quickly.
- Over there.
- Hurry up!
- Hurry.
- Go.
Hurry up!
The CT scan doesn't show
any external injury, Chief Director.
What?
Her body was covered in blood.
The other girl's blood
must have got on her as they fought.
She has been thoroughly examined.
You can be rest assured.
But still,
make up something for her diagnosis.
Yes, sir.
Stop putting on an act and get up.
Did you do that?
Oh Yoon Hee bled a lot from the neck.
I'm sorry, Dad.
But I couldn't take her anymore.
She went on and even insulted you, so--
Dad.
Do you know why you were slapped?
It's not because you hurt some girl.
What you did wrong is
losing to some girl like her.
Why did you lose?
You're the daughter of the chief director.
But
you let some poor girl without a dad win.
Do you have to make me
fawn over the judges to let you win?
Is that all my daughter can do?
I'm sorry, Dad.
I've done wrong.
Don't let this happen again.
You must be the best of the best.
If you aren't,
you don't deserve to take the foundation.
Yes.
I'll make sure I become the best.
You turned me into this monster, Dad.
So don't think that you died in vain.
Since you're at least...
leaving me this one thing.
Hello?
Hey, Seo Young.
It's me.
Don't just stand there.
This can't be happening.
Will you please do something?
Do something.
- Do something to save him.
- Honey.
No.
No, Dad.
No, you can't go like this.
No, Doctor.
He's too young to die like this.
No, honey!
Honey.
- Honey!
- Dad.
No, Dad.
Honey.
No, Doctor.
Please save him.
Honey. No, honey.
Honey.
Seo Jin.
Honey...
Seo Jin!
Seo Jin. Seo Jin...
- Seo Jin!
- What...
No, Dad.
- happened to him?
- Honey.
He had acute myocardial infarction
and fell down the stairs.
Mr. Kang found him
and brought him to the hospital,
but he already passed away
before he got here.
Honey, open your eyes.
How dare you humiliate me like that?
You got a divorce and even had an affair?
You're a disgrace to our family.
How dare you want Cheonga all to yourself?
As of this moment,
you're removed from the board.
And leave Cheonga Arts High School.
You'll also have to return the inheritance
I've passed on to you.
No.
- No!
- Cheonga belongs to Seo Young now.
You're no longer my daughter!
No.
No!
Seo Jin, calm down.
This is a lie!
This can't be real!
Why would my dad die?
Seo Jin...
No!
- Seo Jin!
Bring a bed.
Now!
- Seo Jin...
- Seo Jin, wake up.
- Seo Jin.
Wake up, Seo Jin.
- Seo Jin, please.
- Seo Jin.
Seo Jin!
I'm fine.
Mum.
You look really awful.
It looks like you'll collapse again.
I'm fine.
Are you sure you're okay?
You've been through a lot.
You barely got any sleep for three days.
I'll go get some rest.
Could you prepare some abalone porridge?
She hasn't eaten for days.
Yes, Dr. Ha.
I felt so bad for her.
Ms. Cheon is a heartless woman, you know.
And seeing her break down like that
at her father's death
even broke my heart.
How many times did she faint
at the funeral?
Tell me about it.
I was surprised to see she was on an IV
and still stayed at the funeral hall.
She was practically half-dead.
Why did he fall down
when his secretary wasn't with him?
I heard he could've lived
if he'd been found a bit earlier.
He already had a weak heart.
He was so concerned about his health,
enjoying his success and wealth.
I can't believe he died
out on the street in the rain.
Who would believe that?
Anyway,
the chief director's position is vacant.
Who'll become the next chief director?
Come on, it has to be Seo Jin.
He made an announcement before.
Then Ms. Cheon will rise up
as the Sun King of Cheonga Arts High,
the one who wields absolute power.
Dr. Ha has the worst of luck in his life.
How can his wife be a bigger success
as soon as they got a divorce?
They really signed the divorce papers?
They split up for good?
You can't tell anyone.
They're keeping it low for Eun Byeol.
They don't want her to get hurt.
Nonsense.
She wouldn't get hurt at all.
Didn't you see her doing her workbook
lying on her stomach
at her grandfather's funeral?
That girl is even more tenacious
than her mum.
Why does she study so hard?
Once her mum becomes the chief director,
she'll become the first place in school
even if she sat there doing nothing.
What a good girl.
What do you mean?
Why is it because of you?
I exposed
Seo Jin's affair to the chief director,
then he fell down that night.
Maybe he was too shocked
and had a cardiac arrest.
How did he react when you told him?
He rebuked me instead.
He called me crass and rude.
That's odd.
People say
he values his reputation and honour
above anything.
If he found out
about his daughter's divorce and affair,
he wouldn't have let her go in peace.
Soo Ryeon, are you suspicious
of Seo Jin right now?
She benefitted the most
through the chief director's death.
She covered up her shame
and became the chief director.
And the CCTV at Cheonga High
broke down two days before his death.
It's a bit odd to be a coincidence.
I'll look into this.
Find out who was on duty as the guard
on the day Cheonga's chief director died.
Cheon Seo Jin is involved in this.
"Mr. Gu Ho Dong"
I'll do it as soon as I get to school.
"Security Office"
Goodness, good work, sir.
Have this energy drink
and take it easy, here.
Goodness, thank you, Mr. Gu.
Don't mention it. Take this.
Anyway,
I haven't seen Mr. Choi for a few days.
Wasn't he on night duty
on the night the chief director died?
Was he too shocked?
He quit.
What? Why?
He became a chief manager somewhere,
and I heard he'll be paid a hefty amount.
Really?
Where did he go?
I have no idea.
Maybe he won the lottery.
He even changed his number too.
I see. Is that so?
Anyway, good for him, then.
I'm so out of it.
Please excuse me.
- Thank you for the drink.
- Sure.
- Take care.
- Bye.
He changed his phone number too?
Did you take care of everything?
I made Attorney Park keep his mouth shut.
Did you meet the school guard
who was on night duty that night?
Keep his mouth shut
so that he won't say anything weird.
I already got him another job.
I'll make sure he doesn't cause a problem.
Thanks for your help.
I'll repay you, Secretary Do.
What are you doing?
Why are you here?
I was worried about you.
Are you feeling better?
I'm fine. You can go.
And if you have no business,
do not come into my room.
I'll stay away.
You finished
your porridge.
You must've been hungry.
I needed to get the energy.
I had no other choice.
Wait.
What happened to your hand?
How did you get hurt?
I fell down by mistake.
It's nothing.
Where were you
on that night?
The night your father passed away.
I was practising in the lesson room,
with Secretary Do.
What do you want to find out from me?
No, it's nothing.
Get some rest.
Did you meet the school guard
who was on night duty that night?
Keep his mouth shut
so that he won't say anything weird.
No, she couldn't have.
That just can't happen.
I have to talk to you.
The funeral is over,
so pack up and leave as promised.
What are you talking about?
I told you about Eun Byeol's state.
She needs more therapy.
Will you use her
as an excuse to stay here?
We were going to keep our divorce secret
only until the moment
I become the chief director.
There's no reason to hide this anymore.
She's ill.
Your impossible expectations are
eating her alive from the inside!
Eun Byeol isn't
a weakling like you.
I can take care of her mental health.
If you got seven billion won as alimony,
shouldn't you show some courtesy
and leave quietly?
Mum, Dad, you two got divorced?
Eun Byeol.
No, it's not like that, Eun Byeol.
I was going to tell you after your test,
but you already heard me,
so you leave me no choice.
We got divorced.
Dad isn't going to live here anymore.
It's settled.
No, he can't go.
Are you telling me to live
as a girl without a dad like Ro Na?
Other kids are going to talk.
Just put up a show and live together.
Please don't split up.
Mum.
Can you give him one more chance?
He has been good to us lately.
Everything is settled already.
We just won't live together.
You're still free to meet him
whenever you want.
I still don't want this to happen!
Dad, don't go.
You have to live with me.
Don't go anywhere.
Don't worry, Eun Byeol.
I won't go anywhere.
I'll stay by your side.
You're now the daughter
of Cheonga Foundation's chief director!
You're Cheon Seo Jin's daughter!
Someone like Ro Na isn't a match for you.
Your dad was nothing but an accessory
that you can live without.
I'm all you need.
You've got your mum here
who can do everything for you!
I need Dad in my life too!
I don't want that brat
to take my dad away from me!
What?
I know everything already.
You're leaving me to live with Ro Na.
You're disgusting.
It's not like that, Eun Byeol.
Don't be so immature, Eun Byeol.
You can't turn back anything
by throwing a fit.
Get back in there and study!
You already lost minutes of time
over this unnecessary argument.
You can't do this to me.
I'm not going to let him go.
Once he leaves, I'm leaving too!
Eun Byeol. Eun Byeol!
Eun Byeol!
Ha Eun Byeol.
You.
Do you have to take things this far?
We already agreed upon this.
Shut up and pack up your things.
You and your smoking habit.
You still haven't quit?
Things keep happening
whenever I try to quit.
Did the tough days go by all right?
How's Seo Jin?
She's fine. Completely.
By any chance,
did she tell you?
On the day the chief director died,
she met him with me.
With Father?
Why did he see you?
He found out everything
before he passed away.
He found out his daughter is divorced
and...
she is having an affair
with Joo Dan Tae too.
Thanks for coming to the funeral.
I'm sorry for what happened to him.
He's still too young to die.
Did you get some rest?
I don't have any time to rest.
There's a lot of work with the foundation,
so I've been busy.
The inauguration ceremony
will be held after the board meeting,
but the transition began,
so I have to get to work right away.
Of course the board will say yes.
They will.
There's no reason for Mum
or Seo Young to oppose my appointment.
I finally got everything
I ever wanted,
except for you.
I miss your touch...
to death right now.
I'll wait at the villa tomorrow night.
Don't work too hard.
Bye.
"Wiretapping in progress"
You look as if you're going to a party.
You're going to work dressed like that
as soon as his funeral is over?
It looks as if
you've been waiting
for your father's death.
Watch what you say.
I'm just hoping you won't commit
an even bigger crime as a mother
who has a daughter.
I wasn't going to say this to you,
but the one who killed my father is...
you.
I'm holding myself back
to avoid making a noise.
Lie low unless you want me to sue you.
Are you blaming me right now?
Then who had an affair?
Who's the one that caused his fall?
Complete your daughter's withdrawal
before you mind our family business.
You look pathetic
to lurk around hoping for a change.
Your daughter is
hopeless anyway.
Now that she dropped out,
it might help her to learn her place
if you two leave Hera Palace for good.
Don't be so sure.
We'll have to wait and see
who'll end up leaving this building.
Sure.
Good luck.
"New Chief Director Cheon Seo Jin,"
"you've done well through many hardships"
"New Chief Director Cheon Seo Jin"
It must've been very tough
to go through so much trouble, Ms. Cheon.
Ms. Cheon, we're here too.
My goodness.
Look at how worn out you are.
It must've been so shocking and hard.
This is a nameplate made of pure gold.
This is Kyu Jin's heart, Ms. Cheon.
Don't call her Ms. Cheon now.
She's Chief Director Cheon now.
I give you my congratulations
for becoming the new chief director.
I'm not the chief director yet.
The board will have to take a vote.
It's only a matter of time anyway.
Goodness.
She's awfully charismatic.
I'm sorry,
but the midterm begins today.
We are limiting parental access
to the school grounds at the moment.
Our teachers must have made a mistake.
For fair and just operation of our school,
please leave
immediately.
I see.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay.
- Sorry.
- Let's go.
- I'm so sorry.
- Goodbye.
Keep it up, Chief Director.
"New Chief Director Cheon Seo Jin,"
"you've done well through many hardships"
"New Chief Director Cheon Seo Jin"
Thank you.
I've been heartbroken
after suddenly losing a family member.
It's reassuring to receive
such warm comfort from you.
Education is the key
that drives Cheonga Foundation.
I'll make Cheonga grow into a foundation
that nurtures and brings up great talents.
I'll put in all of my soul.
I can't believe how brazen
and confident that cheating woman is.
How can she be like that as a human?
Didn't she look as if she saved a country?
Tell me about it.
She's a so-called educator
who had an affair with a parent.
How dare she kick us out?
If we report her
to the district school board,
she'll be fired
as the chief director in a flash.
Honey!
Don't you think a golden nameplate
is too much?
Do you know how much the gold price is?
It was paid by the Operation Committee.
Joo Dan Tae is the one who decided on it.
This feels awful.
How can she kick us out like that?
What did she say? "Fair and just"?
No way.
People say you're an idiot
if you work at Cheonga High
and don't get enough money
to buy a house within three years.
Even so,
we should watch our mouth before Ms. Cheon.
Try to read the politics.
I've been killing myself
using all my energy to keep my mouth shut.
I'm driven mad with the impulse
to insult her to her face.
There's nothing we can do.
We're the underdogs here
as long as she holds our kids hostage.
Then
what will happen to Soo Ryeon?
Now that Ms. Cheon is divorced,
she might have to leave the penthouse.
Seo Jin is taking over the penthouse?
Gosh, just the idea gives me chills.
Cheon Seo Jin and Joo Dan Tae.
They're invincible. Ugh, so annoying.
- My gosh!
"2020 1st Semester Midterm, Korean"
If I catch you cheating,
I'll take away your sheet, no excuses.
You'll get zero points.
I have 20-20 vision with my glasses.
Don't even dream of doing anything.
"Chief Director Cheon Seo Jin"
What...
did you just say?
Why are you so shocked?
Don't you think you are the best candidate
as the next head of arts?
Thank you.
I will stay loyal to you
until the day I die.
I'll do my best.
In that case,
show me what you'll do, not just in words.
Pardon?
I'm sure you know that Seoul University
looks into extracurricular activities
as they consider a student's admission.
That's exactly why
I'd like to put you in charge
of Eun Byeol's student record.
I completely understood what you said.
Do not worry about anything, Ms. Cheon.
I mean, Chief Director.
"Chief Director Cheon Seo Jin"
I will put all of my soul into this
to live up to your expectations and trust.
I don't care what kind of award it is.
Reading, discussion, essay,
whatever it may be,
everything that goes into the record
will be given to Ha Eun Byeol.
And give your full support for the clubs
that she's a part of.
So we're giving all of the awards
we have at school to Eun Byeol?
Quiet.
What's going on?
Hey.
Am I an outcast?
You didn't know?
You should've been nice to people.
Wow, you're really harsh, aren't you?
Hello?
Yes, who is calling, please?
This is Joo Dan Tae, Head of Operation.
Are you Seok Kyung's teacher?
I am.
Hello, this is Ma Doo Ki.
It's Chairman Joo Dan Tae.
Yes, please speak.
Yes, of course.
I'll be there.
It's an honour
to meet you in person, Chairman Joo.
I haven't been considerate enough
after leaving both my kids in your care.
We should've played golf together.
Let's find a date to play together.
But I'm still a beginner.
I'll practise harder starting today.
You seem busy, so let me cut to the chase.
It seems like
Seok Kyung is stressed out about midterms.
There's nothing I can do to help as a dad.
It's so heartbreaking.
Yes, of course it is.
It must have been so painful.
So what can I do to help?
The test.
Pardon?
"CEO Joo Dan Tae"
What's up?
I need your help.
I can't do this on my own.
I don't care if you kick me out abroad.
But...
I don't want to lose against Eun Byeol.
You know,
I can't bear to see my children
lose to someone,
even if
she's up against Eun Byeol.
So...
are you asking me
to leak out the test papers?
But this is too dangerous, so...
What is this?
Open up.
I never abandon anyone
once I take them in on my side.
If you promise to help
with Seok Kyung's tests for three years,
I'll be your retirement plan.
Until the day I die?
I hope Seok Kyung won't have a problem
on her test tomorrow.
Goodbye, Chairman Joo.
I love you!
That dirty jerk.
"JKING Holdings"
Joint investment?
Yes.
Mr. Lee suggests
we join him in this investment.
It seems like
he concluded the Myeong-dong lot is
more suitable as a hotel
and a casino business for tourists
than a shopping district.
A casino business?
In Singapore,
the hotel and casino in the city centre
brought in a huge number of tourists--
It's not like I'm not aware of that.
But do you think it'll be easy
to get the casino business approved?
And in the middle of Seoul?
Logan, maybe you aren't well-versed
in how business is done in Korea.
This is my business.
If I didn't have the confidence
to do it in the first place,
I wouldn't have done it.
Now.
This is a business outline
for hotels and casinos
that I'm pushing in New York
and in Seoul.
The estimated budget,
one billion.
Dollars.
And since I'm staying in America
most of the time,
and
for better business operations in Korea,
I'm offering you
to be my co-investor.
That's over one trillion won.
Listen, you have to understand.
This is a massive business idea,
and I'm on the verge of contracting
with some of the biggest, and I mean big,
big corporations, okay?
I only came here today
because Ms. Oh asked me to come.
It was a favour.
If you don't want to do it,
you don't have to.
Let's go.
Give me some time to look into this.
No.
Business is about information.
Which is something that you don't have.
"JKING Holdings"
Logan, one second.
Will you give this up?
Oseong Group is dying to get this project.
It wasn't easy to get this meeting.
Oseong Group?
"Oseong Group Jumps into Hotel-Casino"
"Oseong and Logan Lee is about to sign..."
Is something moving forward already?
There are a number of articles
that were published this afternoon,
and Oseong's stock price skyrocketed.
Call Logan immediately
and get me a dinner meeting.
Do whatever it takes
to have him seated before me.
Do you understand?
I'll trust what you can do.
He probably hasn't left yet.
I have 150 billion won
tied up in Myeong-dong right now.
If I can free that up
and join his casino business,
I'll rake in
at least 50 million dollars a year.
"Jakomo"
"Compose new message"
"Please check the email I sent"
I knew it. This is it!
It's so nice.
I wonder what it's made of.
It's incredibly soft.
You're here.
Yes! My gosh.
Well, Sang A
wants to buy a new couch.
This is made of the finest material
and also has the highest repurchase rate.
Let me see.
My gosh.
- This is the one.
- Where will you put it?
Well...
In my husband's study.
Yes, the study.
"Mr. Gu Ho Dong"
Excuse me for a second.
Gosh, no worries.
Don't mind us and just answer it.
Go on.
I'm sure he'll take the bait
because of the money
he's invested in the lot in Myeong-dong.
For a joint investment,
you'll have to start a new company.
Right, I've already thought of something.
He doesn't trust people easily.
You must make sure the executives
of Oseong Group are all in on this.
Chairman Park and I go back a long way,
so I'm sure he'll help me out.
More importantly,
do you have a full list of Joo Dan Tae's
real estate properties and total assets?
No.
He keeps it strictly hidden from me.
Oh, right.
In his study, there's a secret room
only he can enter.
That's probably where he's keeping
all the related documents.
But you can't go in
without his fingerprint.
Fingerprint?
Don't worry. I have an idea.
Hey, wait.
Looks like he's taken the bait.
Can we have a quick talk?
Cheon Seo Jin.
Dad.
You're a murderer.
You do not deserve this trophy!
No, it's mine!
Stop tormenting me!
You're dead. You're already dead!
Cheonga Foundation is mine!
Ms. Cheon.
My gosh.
You're still here?
What's the matter?
Eun Byeol
is such a strong person mentally.
After Mr. Cheon passed away,
I was worried it'd affect her exam scores,
but she aced all three exams
she took today.
As for Seok Kyung,
she bombed her exams.
Really?
She studied hard.
I'm glad.
But...
I understand.
You must be devastated.
I'll clean this up for you.
I'd appreciate that.
I have plans.
Don't worry about a thing. Just get going.
"Cheonga Arts High School"
"10th grade"
"Exam Papers and Answer Sheet"
"April 22, Science, English"
Darn it. I can't see a thing.
"Midterm Exam Answer Sheet"
You're looking for
a jacket for men, right?
How about this one?
The colour is exquisite.
It's nice.
I'll take this one too.
I'll take all of them.
Can we reschedule our dinner this evening?
Something came up.
Where are you now?
You promised we'd meet up tonight.
Next time.
I can't get out of this.
Forget about next time. Meet me now!
I need you now.
You know what I'm going through.
Come to the villa.
I'll be waiting.
Sorry.
Your wife?
You guys seem to adore each other.
Well, yes.
Then you two have agreed
to this joint investment.
You can't change your mind now.
No turning back.
Again, I'm convinced by Ms. Oh.
I'm glad I could be of help.
It's such an honour.
To celebrate this, how about
we drink this bottom up?
Why don't we give it a try?
Salute.
That's nice.
With this MOU and everything else,
I'm curious as to how Ms. Oh managed
to move your heart and convince you.
Well, I would say...
her bravery?
There are many smart people out there,
but brave? Not so much.
Bravery?
Excuse me.
Unfortunately, something urgent came up.
Is it okay to leave you two alone?
Yes, of course.
We have plenty of time.
Yes, please excuse me.
Oh, wait a second.
It's a present.
Oh, thank you.
I appreciate it.
Talk to you soon.
Okay.
"Success, fingerprint scanned"
Yes, it's ready now.
I'll be on my way.
Here you go, sir.
I'm performance-oriented,
so I always reward
those who produce good results.
So I'd like to promote you
to manager of the investment team.
Seriously?
Please keep up the great work.
Our past doesn't matter to me.
What matters is that
I need you right now.
I'll do my best.
I hope you're not getting tipsy yet.
I'm just getting started.
You may never guess this about me,
but I can hold my liquor very well.
Tipsy? Not at all.
- Excuse me for a moment.
- Sure.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay. Gosh, this is bad.
I'm sorry.
There's a first-aid kit in my car.
Secretary Cho, where are you?
Are you all right?
- Yes, I'm... My gosh!
- Oh, no!
I'm sorry, sir.
Are you all right?
I'm so sorry.
My gosh.
Sir, are you okay?
No.
Please don't die, Mum.
Stop.
Sir!
- Sir, are you okay?
- Go away.
Get away from me!
Sir, what's the matter?
Sir, please...
I told you to stop.
I told you... I told you to stop.
The kids went to the study room,
and I sent Ms. Yang home early.
This way.
This is...
My furniture company owns this land.
Looks like he wants to build
his own village on that land.
Is that why he tried to kill Hye In?
What do you mean?
Right before my father passed away,
he left the land to Hye In.
There's a safe here.
But this is...
How are we going to open it?
I think I know how.
"Searching"
"Error"
"Fail"
Where are we going?
He has a villa nearby.
We've been doing this for over two hours.
It's a six-digit number.
Considering all the possible sequences,
we may not be able to open this tonight.
But we may never get another chance.
Shouldn't we take him to a doctor?
There's nothing here.
He'll wake up soon.
I'll go pick up some medical supplies.
Please wait here.
There are fresh clothes in the closet.
You can get changed.
Secretary Cho, is that you?
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
Look who's talking!
Why are you here?
And why are you wearing my clothes?
There was a bit of a situation.
Don't get any funny ideas.
What kind of situation?
I suppose you think you're important
now that you work for him,
but Joo Dan Tae is mine.
How dare you set eyes on him!
Take off my clothes at once.
You have no shame.
You can't stand him cheating on you?
Don't act like you're his wife.
Don't you dare judge me
by your lowly standards.
Oh Yoon Hee.
Are you that insecure?
That ruthless Cheon Seo Jin I know
is totally head over heels for this man.
I'm suddenly getting very curious about
what kind of man
Joo Dan Tae is.
Shut your mouth.
Know your place.
How about you know your place first?
You're a mere mistress.
Don't you dare mess with me.
Chairman Joo needs to get some rest now,
so stop causing a scene here
and just get lost.
I'm telling you this as the manager
of JKING Holdings' investment team.
Have you lost your mind?
You don't deserve such a position!
What are you waiting for? Drag her out.
I'm afraid she'd wake Chairman Joo.
Please come with me, ma'am.
Let go. Let go of me! I said, let go!
Oh Yoon Hee.
Tell Chairman Joo to come outside!
That crazy witch.
You woke up.
Are you all right?
I know you have no interest
in my private life,
but I've shown you too much.
My wife doesn't know about my condition.
You've regained your consciousness,
so I'll be off now.
Why didn't you tell her?
I mean, Seo Jin.
About what happened today.
It seemed like you had a painful past.
I could tell from your face.
I'd never tell others
about your personal scars.
I'm not that crude.
I saw nothing today.
So don't worry
and just take care of that lady outside.
Good night.
Let me talk to Chairman Joo!
Let go! I said, let go!
Oh Yoon Hee.
Where do you think you're going?
Get back here and explain what happened!
Hey! Oh Yoon Hee!
Let go. I told you to let go!
Calm down. It's no big deal.
It's no big deal?
This villa is a private place
for just the two of us.
What the heck was she doing here?
Yoon Hee, that witch...
She left wearing my clothes.
What were you doing in your bed?
It's not what you think.
We met up for work.
I told you to fire her.
You said you'd kick her out right away.
Why let her drag you around?
It's my company, so I decide what to do!
Some stuff happened,
so I had no choice.
Don't get so worked up.
Let's talk inside.
Oh Yoon Hee!
She gets on my nerves.
How many times do I have to tell you?
I came here
because I wanted to be comforted by you.
Did you have to ruin my mood like this?
You'll have to give me
a proper explanation
as to what happened today.
Drive Ms. Oh home.
I'll go separately.
"Joo Dan Tae Village"
"Detailed Information"
"To be completed on May 19, 2023"
Hold on.
Safe unlocked.
How did you figure it out?
May 19, 2023.
It's right here under aerial view.
There are tons of real estate documents
and billions of won in cash.
What's this?
It's a photo of Seok Hoon and Seok Kyung
when they were babies.
Who's this woman?
There's an unusual tattoo on her shoulder.
Is she the twins' mother?
He told me their mother
died right after giving birth
due to sepsis.
Honey, what are you doing here?
Well...
I told you not to enter my study
without permission.
What is this?
This ring.
Hye In's dad and I got this
as our wedding ring.
Why is this here?
You finally found it.
I was excited and thrilled every day,
wondering when you'd find it.
Don't tell me...
Did you...
kill him?
How could you?
How could you kill an innocent man
and keep his finger as a souvenir?
You don't deserve to be called human!
The moment I saw that wedding ring
on that jerk's finger...
I totally lost it.
How dare he steal you from me.
The fact that you were pregnant
with his child
made me want to tear his heart
to shreds.
You...
You're insane.
How could I stay sane
when my woman betrayed me?
How dare you leave me
for that lowlife.
You and I never loved each other.
Our parents forced us
to get engaged.
And I never once opened up to you.
You killed someone.
How could you be so shameless?
You're evil.
Evil?
Evil...
You betrayed me,
but I took care of your daughter
for 16 years.
I did that for you.
You're the one who said
even her biological father
wouldn't have been that good to her.
So you have no right
to ask me for a divorce.
So what if I had an affair with Seo Jin?
I'm sorry,
but you betrayed me first!
I think that's enough
to make up for this finger.
Let's forget everything and start over.
I know we can be happy again.
Love?
We can start now.
We've betrayed each other once,
so that makes us even.
Well, I'll take that as a yes.
I'm going to wash up.
Can I see your ID?
I'm a college student.
Please just cash me out.
We have to check everyone's ID
before selling alcohol.
- Do you mind...
- Hey, is that you?
Waiting List?
- My gosh!
It really is Bae Ro Na.
Gosh, look at her makeup and hair.
Did you run away from home?
Gosh, we're so stressed out
studying for the exams.
My gosh.
You even drink alcohol now?
Mind your own business.
What's with her?
She must've lost it after dropping out.
Hold on.
Why are you getting in so late?
Do you know what time it is now?
What on earth did you do to your hair?
Ro Na!
Why did I bother working so hard?
What's the use of being promoted
to manager
and living in a fancy house?
I've totally ruined my daughter's life.
Can we meet for a moment?
Come to the 47th floor at Hera Palace.
"Hera Palace"
Min Seol A, 47th floor.
Min Seol A, 47th floor...
"Beware, Risk of Falling"
Joo Dan Tae.
It was Joo Dan Tae.
Die!
"Hera Palace, 47th floor"
"Beware, Risk of Falling"
Ms. Oh?
It was you?
Are you the one who saved me?
Thank you.
If you're gone,
Ro Na can get in.
If you're gone for good...
That wasn't a dream.
Seol A
fell at Hera Palace.
I... I killed her.
Yoon Hee.
Soo Ryeon.
You're early.
Well, why did you
want to meet here?
I have something to tell you.
To tell you the truth,
I used you all this time.
What... What do you mean?
The person who sent you
to Seol A's place in Bosong Village.
That was me.
And I arranged everything
so you'd move to Hera Palace.
I used you.
I really needed you
for my revenge.
I am
Seol A's mother.
=Penthouse=
I saw it with my own two eyes.
Off the railing on the 47th floor.
I decide whether we keep seeing each other
or break up.
Bae Ro Na is back.
I'm going out with Ro Na.
I haven't even started yet.
I look forward to working with you,
Chief Director Cheon Seo Jin.
It's time to put an end to this.
Don't trust anyone but yourself.
I must become stronger and tougher
since I'm a mother.