=Penthouse=
"All characters, locations,"
"incidents, and backgrounds"
"of this drama are fictitious."
=Episode 4=
Hello?
What? Where are you calling from?
Cheonga Arts High School?
Yes, okay.
What...
What did you just say?
We have an extra slot for Bae Ro Na
in the vocal music department.
An extra slot?
But why...
I mean, how?
One of the kids
who got accepted died yesterday.
No... No way.
Did I do it?
"14 hours ago"
Please pick up your jacket.
There aren't that many left.
Great work today. - Sure.
It's pretty.
Where's my wife?
She won't pick up her phone.
She's taking a shower right now.
"Somang Children's Home, 2004"
Find the child that was left there
wrapped in a navy jacket
in December of 2004.
"Santa's Surprise Donation of Love"
"Somang Children's Home"
"Adoption Record"
"Name: Min Seol A, English Name: Anna Lee"
"Somang Children's Home"
Cheers! - Cheers!
Cheers! - All right!
There has been a minor issue,
but let's forget everything and celebrate
our kids' admission to Cheonga High.
I wouldn't say it's minor.
Once she goes out and speaks up,
it'll be turned into a social issue
that children from rich families
bullied another kid as a group.
You're right. These days,
it's a weakness to be rich.
But you know,
I can't really have any fun at this party
knowing that she's here in Hera Palace.
Just enjoy yourself.
I'll go to the mechanical room and show--
Sit down.
Darn it.
A wise man once said, "Your mouth may
bring about disaster."
Watch your mouth.
Honey.
It's... It's this watch.
I put this on for the first time today.
Hey, look. - Wait.
I decided to put this on today
since this is a special occasion.
It's an antique skeleton pocket watch.
Wow.
I got this off an auction on Only Watch.
And the final price
came to 1.5 billion won!
All right!
That cost you 1.5 billion?
Goodness, what if you lose it?
You're showing off a bit too much.
All right, then.
Let us begin the party now.
All right! - Yes!
Forget all the depressing thoughts.
Let's dance and have fun tonight.
Cheers!
Cheers! - Cheers!
"Adoption Record, Name: Min Seol A"
She was adopted in 2015.
"Dissolution of adoption in 2017"?
If you're done,
get out of here already, will you?
Min Seol A.
Why was she sent back after her adoption?
She was adopted to the US,
so why did she come back?
What's the reason?
Why is this paper still here?
I have no idea!
I'm sure she did something wrong
if she got kicked out.
This man.
This is Assemblyman Cho Sang Heon, right?
Why did he take a photo with Min Seol A?
Dang, what's weird about an assemblyman
taking a photo with an orphan?
Darn it.
I took care of her
after her parents abandoned her.
How dare you make a scene here?
There must be a reason she was sent back.
Who adopted her?
Will you let me go?
Who were those people?
Please tell me anything.
Darn it. You're unbelievably annoying!
You abandoned your own kid.
Stop spewing out nonsense at this point!
You people.
What have you done to Min Seol A?
What have you done to her?
If you need anything,
please don't hesitate to tell me.
Sure.
I'll do that.
What are you doing?
You are even rootless at that?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
You were very kind to me.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
Mummy is sorry.
I couldn't recognise you.
"8 missed calls"
"8 missed calls from Husband"
"Tutor Min Seol A"
Please pick up your phone, Seol A.
Your call cannot be connected.
You'll be redirected to voicemail.
I can't believe this.
No one would go
looking for Min Seol A
in the mechanical room, right?
What if...
she exposes our relationship?
Who would believe her?
Everyone would think
a crazy girl is throwing a fit.
We just need to find that darned phone.
Things won't come to an end
just by getting our hands on her phone.
She's not an ordinary girl.
If you think she's easy to deal with,
we might end up taking a blow.
Where is she?
Put her on the phone now. Now!
What are you doing in here?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
You didn't answer when I called out,
so I was afraid you might have collapsed.
The chairman is looking for you.
Goodness, I'm quite late, aren't I?
I'm sorry.
I'll be down soon.
Okay.
Get my dress ready.
Yes, ma'am.
Seol A.
It's me, Seok Kyung's mum.
I have to tell you something, so call me.
"Min Seol A, maths tutor"
Dance, dance! Keep it going!
This is great!
Wait just a little longer, Seol A.
Mum will come for you very soon.
This is fantastic.
How much does it cost to shoot one up?
It looks so pretty!
It's so pretty!
Honey, come here. Honey.
What's wrong?
Look at that.
My goodness. One second.
I can't believe this.
Dr Ha, hurry. - Awesome.
What is it? What's going on?
It looks like she died on the spot.
That's...
It's her.
You know, that girl.
Who is it? Who?
Min Seol A.
The fake tutor who taught our kids.
This is insane.
Why did she die?
Does she know how much that statue cost?
Why did she die there of all places?
She's nothing but trouble to the end.
Today was a very important day.
She fell and died there
on purpose to get us in trouble
by putting herself on display.
You said we had nothing to worry about.
I thought she was locked up.
Did you let her go?
Are you insane? Why would I do that?
Then who is it? Who let her go?
That's not what's important right now.
It won't help the situation
if we get suspicious of each other.
First off,
we need to remove her body.
In two hours,
Hera Palace's first anniversary ceremony
will be held around this fountain.
We invited all kinds of famous people.
Are you going to let them see that?
Exactly.
So let's report this to the police first.
Once the police get here,
they'll put us down as suspects
as well as our kids.
What about our kids?
Wait.
Are you saying our kids killed her?
We know that they didn't.
But the police won't share the same idea.
If we get unlucky
and the police end up finding her phone,
that moment will be
the end of our children's future.
You all need to listen up.
Min Seol A has
never been to Hera Palace at this hour.
What do you mean?
I'm saying Min Seol A
didn't fall down and die right here.
Did she say she lives in Bosong Village?
Are you suggesting
that we dispose of her dead body?
Article 161 of the Criminal Code says
anyone who abandons, hides, or takes away
someone's dead body, bones, remains,
and other articles in the burial place
will face up to seven years in prison.
We don't have any other choice
to protect our children.
That girl can't come back alive anyway.
And all of us
can't suffer just because of her.
I'm for that idea.
We must protect
our kids and Hera Palace.
Let's follow the majority rule.
However,
whatever the result may be,
we must all go with the result.
Let's vote by a show of hands.
Who's for it?
All right.
We have
an hour and 50 minutes until the ceremony.
We can't lose a minute or even a second.
Gentlemen, we'll move the body.
Ladies, take charge of the fountain.
Leave it to me.
I can definitely do that.
Ma Ri, please take charge of the scene.
Remember.
Everything must look perfect
before the anniversary ceremony begins.
Wait.
Why should we listen to what you say?
Because none of us is
free from the responsibility
for Min Seol A's death.
Is this big enough?
This is perfect.
Let's clean that up first.
Don't you think we should call 119?
I already told you. We can't do that!
If the news reports
on the death of a kid at Hera Palace,
our house price will drop in an instant.
On top of that, she recorded
our kids' mischief on her phone.
Do you want Min Hyuk to get expelled
and live his entire life
as an assailant of a group assault?
I didn't say that!
Darn it.
Let's dry her up.
It's not supposed to rain until tomorrow.
The police will get suspicious
if she's found wet.
What are you doing? Dry her up with me.
Goodness. - Oh dear.
My gosh.
You expect me to do it too?
Let's take off.
"1 hour 25 minutes left"
"until the anniversary ceremony"
What?
What's going on?
Why did it stop?
Excuse me.
The police.
"Police"
Wow.
You're all dressed wonderfully.
"Sugar and me"
I heard an assemblyman will be
attending the anniversary ceremony.
Attorney Lee asked for extra security
at our patrol division,
so I came to visit you first.
Right, we received a report that
they heard someone
screaming in the building.
The residents were cheering loudly
during the fireworks.
Someone must have misunderstood
and made a report.
And I asked our security team
to guard the assemblyman,
so you can return to your post.
I see. In that case, I'll leave.
Wow.
Are you taking a golf trip?
Goodness.
Yes, you're right.
What can I do?
Yes.
I'm going out this weekend,
so I wanted to put it in my car now.
I see.
A golf trip.
Are you all right?
Goodness, I guess you had a lot to drink.
You're all dressed very nicely.
So why are you wearing latex gloves?
We helped the staff carry
the champagne bottles for the party.
In this day and age,
we have to be very kind to our employees.
You have great manners.
I see. - Yes.
You should go first.
You must be busy on duty.
Shall I, then?
Let's go.
That's Min Seol A's bag.
I wrote down her suicide note.
You can put it there with her.
"A suicide note"?
I knew it, Seo Jin.
Not only are you pretty,
you're also astute.
"I shouldn't have been born.
I want you all dead."
That's a nice phrase.
How's the fountain coming along?
Why did she die here of all places
and make us do so much work?
I never liked her from the get-go.
Don't you think
you're too harsh on the dead girl?
She's still a little kid.
That's odd.
Why do you keep taking her side?
Do you somehow feel guilty?
What are you talking about?
Do you really want to bring it on?
Wait, don't do that. - Hey.
Bring it on. - No, wait.
Bring it on. - Goodness!
We have no time to get into a fight.
When will you wipe all the bloodstain?
We're in a total hurry.
Why is there so much traffic at this hour?
There's no traffic.
It's a drink drive checkpoint.
"Sobriety Checkpoint"
What? Why?
Why did we forget about this?
We all had a drink today.
Should we have called for a chauffeur?
This will be the end of our lives.
Calm down, will you?
If there's any problem,
I'll do anything to cover it up.
"Sobriety Checkpoint"
"Police"
Hello, sir.
This is a sobriety checkpoint.
Blow into it.
Wait.
Officer.
I can't believe this.
You look exactly like
my late brother who recently died.
My goodness, Mother. My goodness.
Take this.
You should have a team dinner with this.
Are you bribing me?
The world isn't like that now.
You can't pull this anymore.
Come on, blow.
Let him go.
What happened?
I didn't drink.
Darn it. Why are you saying that now?
You scared me.
You never asked.
Anyway,
Lady Luck is on our side too.
"Bosong Village"
Cut off the security camera.
"Bosong Village, On patrol duty"
Okay.
Darn it.
Dang. Go.
Get in there.
"Video Damaged"
"46 minutes left"
"until the anniversary ceremony"
What a relief.
We wiped away all the bloodstain.
Let's hope the men get their job done.
It's too early to jump to conclusions.
Look at that wimpy stream.
When will this huge fountain
be filled up again?
Fill it up in the toilet, then drop it in.
What? - You want me to do this too?
Hurry. We're running out of time.
"Hera Palace"
Be careful. Careful.
It's over there.
Put her down carefully.
Careful, your hands.
My gosh.
That's Min Seol A's house.
Let's say she jumped from there.
It won't do us any good
if her body is found too soon.
Let's put her up there.
What? Up there?
Yes.
Let's just put her here.
Push me up. Almost there.
You need to use your power.
Kyu Jin, you need to do this right.
Darn it, come on.
All done.
The other shoe.
What?
Where's her other shoe?
Darn it.
One of her shoe is gone.
Is her other shoe down there?
"Hera Palace"
It's not here.
It's not here either.
No, it's nowhere to be found.
It's not in the fountain either.
We can't lose more time.
Let's do our best to wrap this up.
Put her bag on the rooftop.
So they will find her suicide note.
Then
are we all done?
We have to do one more thing
to complete her suicide note.
Man, what's this mess?
Gosh, look at this.
What if there are bugs here?
Gosh.
Be quiet!
This house is way too tiny.
Try to be careful.
I mean,
the government should redevelop
houses like these.
Gosh, that darned dog.
There's...
something right here.
What is it?
It's dog poop.
Darn it!
Stop being so loud.
What's that?
Is... Is that an eye?
"Assemblyman Cho Sang Heon"
We have...
exactly 25 minutes left.
Since we haven't found her phone,
this is probably for the best.
And now, all the evidence
will burn away.
Mum. - No.
Mum!
Are you all right, Ms Sim?
What happened?
You collapsed in the elevator.
Do you not remember that?
Did anything happen?
No.
The ceremony is still going smoothly.
Ms Sim.
Ms Sim is heading downstairs.
"Chairman Joo Dan Tae"
Are you feeling better?
I heard you were ill.
Did anything happen here?
Like what?
What is it?
Should we expect to see something?
You should tell me about it.
I heard you collapsed in the elevator.
Ms Yang told me.
You still don't look too well.
You should get some rest after this.
But I'm relieved you're fine.
The lighting ceremony will begin soon.
"Hera Palace"
I'd like to thank you
for coming out to celebrate
the first-year anniversary
of Hera Palace at such a late hour
on behalf of all of our residents
as a representative.
I'd especially like to thank
Mr Cho Sang Heon,
the assemblyman of our district.
Thank you.
And now,
let us begin the lighting ceremony
that will make this fountain perfect
as Hera Palace's symbol.
Keep your eyes on the statue of Hera,
sculpted by a famous Italian artist.
Mr Cho?
One second. - Sure.
I saw her
fall down onto the fountain.
Had I been dreaming?
Now, please hold up your glasses.
For Hera, the goddess
of marriage and fidelity,
and the glory and honour of Hera Palace.
Cheers! - Cheers!
Great job. - My gosh.
Cheers.
This is a wonderful ceremony, Mr Joo.
It's unusually grandiose.
I heard you shot up fireworks
from Han River as well.
I did.
It's all thanks to your help, Mr Cho.
Thank you.
She must be your wife.
You're as beautiful as people say.
Honey?
You should say hello to him.
This man.
This is Assemblyman Cho Sang Heon, right?
Why did he take a photo with Min Seol A?
She's not feeling well today.
Please understand.
I see.
Honey.
Is this blood?
Oh, this is...
I spilled some wine on him today.
I stepped on my dress by accident.
I'm sorry
I ruined your shirt.
It's all right. Don't mind me.
You were worried about your ruby ring.
Look at how big that thing is.
How much did that cost?
You're way too dressed up today, Ms Cheon.
Two, three.
We look great.
Gosh, we look awesome.
"Are you okay?"
"Please call me"
"I have to tell you something"
Where are you, Seol A?
Please send me a reply.
What's going on? - Please step back.
What's going on?
Isn't that where the orphan girl lives?
The girl who walks around at night. - Yes.
I heard she lives alone with her dog.
Why did she set her house on fire?
The fire won't die down.
My goodness. - Look at that.
My gosh.
What happened?
Goodness, what's that? - What?
There's a person! - Where?
My goodness! - What?
Please step back.
Is that training shoe behind Lady Hera
also from Italy?
What do you mean?
What? - What's that?
What's he saying?
I guess the kids pulled a prank.
I wasn't seeing things.
That was definitely Seol A.
Hey! Who did this?
My gosh, you rascals.
Kids do that out of curiosity.
They're so adorable.
All of you.
What have you done to Seol A?
What are you doing? Get that thing out.
My gosh, these kids.
A fire in Bosong Village?
Okay, an orphan lives there alone.
What do you expect me to do?
I'm not a fireman.
My goodness!
We have breaking news.
A fire broke out on the fifth floor
in a building in Bosong Village.
It took about 30 minutes
for the firefighters to put it out.
No one seemed to be inside the house
when the fire broke out,
but about 100 residents had to evacuate
because of the fire.
The police and fire authorities
are investigating what caused the fire...
Thick, grey smoke
seeps through the windows.
While working on putting out
the fire on the fifth floor,
the firefighters found
a dead body on top of a gazebo,
which has shocked the residents.
The victim is a teenage girl who was
a resident of the apartment building.
The police are combing through
CCTV footage from the building
to determine if it was a homicide.
Gosh, that poor thing.
I feel so bad.
My goodness, I can't believe this.
Gosh, that poor thing.
She's so young.
Her parents are horrible
for abandoning their young daughter.
Terrible. - They're awful people.
She died? - My gosh.
Seol A died?
We found a suicide note on the roof.
It looks like she died by suicide.
"I shouldn't have been born"?
Gosh, she must've been a spiteful kid.
So she started a fire at her place
and jumped from the roof?
What about the missing shoe?
We haven't found it yet.
No, that is nonsense.
She'd never kill herself. - Ma'am, don't.
"I shouldn't have been born."
Gosh, what on earth are you doing?
You can't just go ahead
and touch evidence!
This is obstruction of justice.
I saw it with my own two eyes.
That hand...
There is no way
Seol A took her own life.
No, wait! Please!
Wait, please!
Excuse me. Can you help me?
Help me untie this.
I have to go.
Excuse me.
Can't you hear me?
Mr Yoon?
What are you doing here?
Don't get so worked up.
It won't do you any good.
You were told that you'd all die
if you did anything reckless.
If you want to find your daughter,
you must do as I say.
If you do anything reckless,
Joo Hye In and your daughter
will both die.
That was you?
Are you the one who called me?
Answer my question!
Are you the one who told me that Hye In
isn't my real daughter?
Why?
Why did you tell me?
If Chairman Joo finds out,
you'll be put in danger.
I don't care.
My daughter is dead.
What's the use of staying alive?
My daughter...
My daughter is dead.
You've helped Dan Tae
do all sorts of evil things, so why?
Do you suddenly feel guilty?
This won't undo your sins!
You're right.
I work for Chairman Joo,
so I must do as he says.
Since my life is in his hands,
I will continue to obey his orders
until the day I die.
Then why are you doing this to me?
What do you want from me?
I may be his hound
and a piece of rubbish,
but I figured you deserve to know
what really happened 17 years ago.
She was born at 32 weeks,
but all her organs including her heart
are perfectly normal.
She's truly blessed.
Everything's normal?
Living things can be
very persistent, can't they?
That baby was also born at 32 weeks,
but her condition is getting worse.
The mother is a single mum,
so she doesn't know what to do.
She can't afford the hefty hospital bill.
This is a good thing for your baby.
So don't cry, okay?
You made the right choice.
Trust me. You did the right thing.
"Mother: Sim Soo Ryeon"
"Mother: Kim Jung Bin"
He switched the newborn babies
in the neonatal unit.
"Mother: Sim Soo Ryeon"
But I couldn't kill that baby
because I felt like it was
desperately struggling to live.
So I left the baby
in front of the children's home.
I, too, had no idea
that Min Seol A was that baby.
No! Stop!
I'll give you a tranquillizer.
Get some sleep.
No, don't leave. Get this off me.
How could you call yourself human?
Mr Yoon!
"Always be healthy, Sugar!"
"Let's be happy together for many years."
Joo Dan Tae.
I will kill you.
I will kill you with my own two hands.
I will kill you!
Just like the suicide note says,
I made the necessary arrangements
to make sure the media will conclude it
as a depressed girl setting her place
on fire and taking her own life.
"Hera Club Chat Room"
Gosh, that darn dog.
No! Don't come near me!
Woof, woof! Go away!
Gosh! - It's okay.
Even if her last location
shows up as Hera Palace,
they won't find any evidence
that directly connects us to her.
So we have nothing to worry about.
That girl is just a loser
who acted up and ended up killing herself.
Do you think that girl
really took her own life?
Do you think someone killed her?
I don't trust Joo Dan Tae.
Do you trust him?
That jerk?
Gosh.
Look how he even forged her suicide note.
I have to say, you creeped me out earlier.
Did you really have to do that?
As if you're that psycho's loyal dog?
I don't care whether or not
she took her own life.
I did it for Eun Byeol, and you know that.
I don't even want to hear that name again.
Hey, did you see this? Look.
This is Min Seol A, right?
"The arsonist was a middle school girl
suffering from depression."
They found a suicide note
blaming the world.
"I want you all dead"?
Gosh, I can't believe this girl.
Talk about being resentful.
How creepy.
Well, then our incident
will be buried naturally.
Right?
Of course.
Who would mourn the death
of a sociopath like her?
Shut it!
Stop talking about that dead girl.
She has nothing to do with us now,
so let's just plan our trip.
You've been so on edge since yesterday.
Did you kill her?
Min Seol A.
What?
No, why would I?
Gosh. Then why are you overreacting?
Of course you didn't kill her. That girl
took her own life.
Darn, this is ruining my day.
Let's stop talking about that swindler.
We'll soon have to deal with a bomb
that's worse than her.
What do you mean?
The girl who's taking Seol A's spot.
She's dumb and obnoxious. I hate her.
Why do you hate her so much?
Are you jealous?
Gosh, are you crazy?
Why would I be jealous of her?
You'll know what I mean.
She has nothing, but she's so arrogant.
I hate her more than Seol A.
The wishy-washy ones are more annoying.
Really? I look forward to meeting her.
Right, Seok Hoon?
Gosh.
Hello?
What? Where are you calling from?
Cheonga Arts High School? Okay.
What...
What did you just say?
We have an extra slot for Bae Ro Na
in the vocal music department.
An extra slot?
But why...
I mean, how?
One of the kids
who got accepted died yesterday.
No-- No way.
Did I do it?
"Hera Palace"
Hey! Kids!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
What are you doing, lady?
Gosh, why are you back here?
You're really annoying.
It's pretty impressive.
How could a girl die
as if it was all planned out?
Ro Na is unbelievably lucky.
Thank goodness
you girls are okay.
What the heck are you talking about?
You heard, right?
Min Seol A is dead.
Min Seol A?
The one who got in with the highest score?
How did she die?
Maybe you killed her,
and you're just playing dumb now.
They're saying it was a suicide,
but I find it very hard to believe.
You really didn't do it?
If it wasn't you...
My gosh! Did Ro Na do it?
You'd better not say
anything like that about Ro Na!
I will teach you a lesson.
Have you lost your mind?
Gosh!
What is this?
Ms Oh, there's blood on your hand.
Did you really do something last night?
Enough, Je Ni.
Let's go. Everyone's waiting.
This is an expensive dress.
I'm so upset!
What-- What is this?
No way. Did I really...
No, no way. That can't be.
Why don't I remember anything?
Hi, Ro Na.
Mum, I've been accepted
to Cheonga Arts High School!
Yes!
Hey, I got in!
I've been thinking hard,
but that girl...
She had no reason to kill herself.
She got in as the top student,
so she would've gotten a scholarship.
She had a bright future ahead of her.
Why would she take her own life?
Then are you saying
one of us killed her?
Who would do something like that?
That is insane.
Who knows?
I know you stepped out last night.
You seemed to be in a rush.
Dr Ha!
Are you suspecting me?
I went to the loo!
For that long?
What?
That reminds me.
Didn't you also step out, Ma Ri?
Goodness.
I went outside
to throw up because I was too drunk.
I can't believe this.
Right, Attorney Lee.
Who did you talk on the phone with
for so long?
It seemed like an intimate call. - Yes.
What are you talking about?
That was my mum.
What? Do you want to see my call history?
I talk with my mum every hour.
Right? - That's right.
What are you all doing?
Show us! - Are you provoking us?
Let me see. - What are you doing?
Show me! - How dare you suspect me!
Hey! - Let me see your phone.
What's your problem? - Stop it!
Show me now! - What's with that attitude?
Gosh! - My goodness.
The cops
will arrive at Hera Palace shortly.
Min Seol A
took her own life.
What we say is the truth.
Min Seol A's phone records
show that you two spoke quite often.
She was my kids' math tutor.
She died in Bosong Village,
but her phone was last pinged
at Hera Palace.
Why do you think that is?
How would I know?
Isn't it your job to find that out?
Turns out,
everything was a lie.
She told us she went to UCLA
and that her name was Anna.
So you must've been angry with her.
Because she totally deceived you.
Why would people like us
let that bother us?
We have a ton of other things
to worry about.
She was just like a fruit fly.
Sure, she was annoying.
But that was it.
So we just let her be.
Was she accepted to Cheonga Arts High
with the highest score?
Is it true?
Yes.
I was very surprised,
but I still congratulated her.
Are you sure?
Rumour has it that you tried
to get her admission cancelled.
That is a groundless rumour.
Had I wanted to do that,
it would've been done a long time ago.
I sincerely congratulated her
on being accepted.
I just feel bad
that I couldn't protect her
as an adult.
Mr Joo.
You talked to Min Seol A on the phone
the day before she died.
Did you meet her that day?
I called and asked her to stop by,
but she didn't show up.
I'm upset that
she deliberately lied to us,
but it's very unfortunate
that she took her own life.
Your wife, Ms Sim,
kept calling her too.
My wife?
There was
a misunderstanding
between her and our kids,
so my wife was probably
trying to get that sorted out.
She's a very tender-hearted person.
Are you ready to talk now?
Where is your phone?
If you want to go home,
you'd better tell me now.
Are you doing this because of the video
of you cheating?
It's awfully lame
that you're being this pathetic
just because of that.
Hey, who do you think you are?
I already know enough about you.
Your adoptive parents abandoned you,
and you got deported from the US.
The reason for deportation
was also theft, I heard.
No, I never stole anything.
I was framed by people like you.
Who would believe an orphan like you?
Just tell me already.
Where is your phone?
What can you possibly do
by keeping your mouth shut?
Who knows?
I may know much more
than you think.
What could you possibly know?
The admission process was rigged.
I know all about it.
You'd better stop
before I lose my patience.
You obviously feel guilty.
Your daughter, Ha Eun Byeol.
Was she accepted fairly?
Are you sure she didn't
steal someone else's spot?
Did you think no one would know?
Shut your mouth before I kill you.
Die! Die! Just die!
Meet me at the penthouse
at 9.
"Nakwon Musical Instruments"
"Righteous Korea"
"Chief's Office"
I just finished interviewing
all the residents at Hera Palace.
Should we do an autopsy, sir?
Hey, are you out of your mind?
You know how many cases we already have.
Why waste time on an orphan
who killed herself?
Conclude it as suicide
and process it as an unclaimed body
with no family.
Yes, sir.
"Min Seol A, suicide"
"Yoo So Yeon, suicide"
"Cremation in Progress"
Yes, sir.
She's being cremated now.
Okay.
The immediate cause of death
was the damage to her brain
as well as to her cervical spine
due to the fall.
There's something unusual though.
I found this
inside her body.
What is this?
Looks like she swallowed it
minutes before her death.
Seol A.
Mum is so sorry.
For coming for you too late
and for not recognising you.
I'm so sorry for leaving you all alone.
This is all my fault.
It's all my fault.
I was too foolish.
I'm a fool.
Seol A.
Who did this to you?
Tell me.
I'll find out who did this to you
and tear that person to shreds.
Seol A...
Hey!
Hey. - What?
It's gone.
What's gone?
I can't find it. It's gone.
What are you talking about?
My antique pocket watch.
What? You idiot!
Gosh.
You're unbelievable.
Hey! Lee Kyu Jin!
What is wrong with you?
What will you do now?
That hurts! - Lee Kyu Jin!
You're unbelievable! - That hurts!
Why did you want to meet at your place?
Don't worry.
The kids are away on a trip,
and I gave the housekeepers a day off.
My wife won't be coming home tonight.
So it's just you and me.
Just the two of us.
Still, this is your place,
and I don't feel comfortable here.
We finally got rid of that headache,
so we should enjoy some wine.
We'll have a small party.
But we haven't found Seol A's phone yet.
There's a video of us on that phone.
I keep getting a bad feeling.
Why? There's nothing to worry about.
The police closed the case as suicide,
and she's already been cremated.
Are you serious?
She's already been cremated?
Yes, of course.
I have influence over everything.
But I do feel a little bad for her.
Had she stayed clueless,
she wouldn't have died.
But then again,
she's probably better off dead anyway.
How dare she record a video of us
and use it to blackmail us.
She basically
brought it upon herself.
Let's forget about it and celebrate.
Here's to our good luck.
Cheers.
=Penthouse=
I will not forgive anyone
who tries to shake up Hera Palace.
That means there's a witness.
I saw Dr Ha.
Did Dr Ha do something to her?
Are you hiding something from me?
It'll be our secret.
You got that?
We'll be punished for what we did to her.
I will not forgive
those who did this to you.
Maybe your mum pushed Seol A.
Why are you all doing this?
There's no way I killed her.
The day Seol A died at Hera Palace...
Where were you?
Do you not remember?