=Penthouse=
"All characters, locations,"
"incidents, and backgrounds"
"of this drama are fictitious."
"Hera Palace"
=Episode 3=
Wipe everything she touched thoroughly
no matter how long it takes.
It's filthy and disgusting.
Yes, sir.
Have you always been like this?
What do you mean?
I know what she did was wrong.
But she's still a kid.
Don't you think you were a bit too harsh?
Are you saying what I did was wrong?
If anything,
we should set an example for our kids.
Isn't that what parents do?
What you did today
wasn't something a grown-up should do.
You got a GED and
you live in Boseong Village?
You con people to make money.
Do you think Cheonga will accept you?
That's my warning to you
to live straight.
You stole Seok Kyung's key ring too?
You're a thief and a fraud.
A kid like you can't go to school with us.
Your first-place admission
will be cancelled, of course.
I just
did my best to live my life.
I just worked hard to death.
Sugar.
You're the only one for me.
I'm sorry to text you so late.
Did you get home safe?
Congratulations
on your first-place admission to Cheonga.
"Seok Hoon and Seok Kyung's mother"
I have a feeling
you'd have a very beautiful singing voice.
"Congratulations, my princess"
"from Dubai, Dad"
Thank you. - Thank you.
The right-hand side.
It's tilted to the right side.
Bring up the left side. Yes.
Keep it level.
Okay.
"Yoo Je Ni Accepted to Cheonga Arts High!"
Wait, I'm the one who got accepted.
Why did you put Dad's and your name there?
You're embarrassing me.
I shouldn't miss the chance to put
my name on a placard as your mum.
It looks wonderful.
Shouldn't Dad be back on a day like this?
He didn't even call. He texted me.
I'm totally disappointed.
Dubai is on the other side of the world.
Try to understand him.
But he sent you an awful lot of flowers.
Hey, we should take a photo.
I'm going to send it to Dad.
Okay.
Say cheese.
Je Ni!
My goodness.
Congratulations.
Congrats. Here. Take this.
And this is...
Thank you.
You can hold it, Ms Kang.
Instead of the regular school lunch,
I got the buffet table arranged
for everyone.
Goodness.
And for the teachers,
I booked a place
that serves premium beef.
Goodness gracious!
You're so generous, Ms Kang. - Oh, well.
Wait, you should have a bite of this.
This one.
Goodness.
Thank you!
This is great.
Please excuse me.
"Yoo Je Ni Accepted to Cheonga Arts High!"
"Congratulations"
Bae Ro Na, I heard you are
the number one on the waiting list.
That little-- - She's on the waiting list?
My goodness, that poor thing.
You were so confident before,
but you completely lost your face now.
That's why you should only do things
that are in your league.
How could you even think
of sending a girl with no talent
to Cheonga Arts High?
The one with no talent
isn't Ro Na, but your daughter.
I'm sure something went wrong.
How can Je Ni get in
when Ro Na couldn't?
Can't you see that?
You've seen that already.
Do you still live in that delusion?
That's the truth,
and that's what's right.
Get it?
That woman.
Right.
There's an orphan who got accepted.
You should go find that student.
Who knows?
If you give her a pile of cash,
she might give up.
Congrats! - Congrats!
Je Ni, congrats. - Great job!
I'm so jealous. - I knew you could do it.
Good for you! - Congratulations.
Well done. - That's awesome.
That's really great.
Thanks a lot, Je Ni.
Doesn't it look good?
It's good.
Are you going to have more? - Of course.
You should eat some.
My mum is celebrating I got accepted.
I'm not in the mood to talk to you,
so get lost.
What's with this?
What's wrong?
What's going on?
You wish someone who got accepted
would just die right now, don't you?
Then you'd get in
as the top of the waiting list.
Gosh, you look like
you might kill someone.
Bad news.
The list had been decided already,
kiddo.
What are you talking about?
You didn't know?
There are 23 spots for vocal music majors.
They let kids from rich families in,
then throw in a few geniuses
to make the school seem genuine.
So someone like you has
zero chance to get in the school.
A girl who has to worry about
the cost of her dress
doesn't seem to belong at Cheonga.
Hey, Yoo Je Ni!
Also,
let me tell you this as I feel for you.
Ever since the school was founded,
no one on the waiting list ever got in.
So...
wake up from your dream
and give up as quickly as you can.
There will be an orientation session
for new students tomorrow
and we'll have a celebration
at Hera Palace in a few days.
Are you jealous?
Boo-ya.
Hey, Eun Byeol.
Oh, the text for Cheonga's orientation?
Of course I got it.
What time are you going to go?
Eight in the morning?
I'll get there around then.
"Eun Byeol"? - Should we go together?
Darn it. No.
That's Ha Eun Byeol.
Eun Byeol must've messed up.
So what if she did?
Her grandpa
is the chief director of the school board.
She definitely made a mistake then.
Please let me see Ms Cheon Seo Jin.
"Celebrating Eun Byeol's admission"
I have something to tell her. Please?
I already said you can't do that.
You can't go in without an appointment.
Stop making a scene and go home.
"Cheonga Middle School PTA"
"Soprano Ha Eun Byeol"
Hey.
What are you doing?
"Celebrating Eun Byeol's admission"
Hey!
Bae Ro Na.
What do you think you're doing?
Do you know her?
It's her. The top of the waiting list.
I see.
Why are you making a scene here?
"Ha Eun Byeol"
You. You're Ha Eun Byeol.
What's with you?
I saw you
coming out crying from the audition hall.
You made a mistake, didn't you?
What are you talking about?
I didn't make any mistake.
You made a mistake
and messed up your audition,
but you still got in
thanks to your mum, didn't you?
I heard your grandpa is
the chief director of the school board.
Something's going on.
Right? Something is going on.
Let me go. Nothing is going on.
Let go. You're wrong.
Let her go!
What on earth have you done?
This is the only way you'd see me.
What?
Tell me
why I didn't pass the audition.
I didn't make a mistake like she did,
and all my lyrics and notes were correct.
So why didn't I make it?
Show me the scores.
I will not accept the results
until I see the scores myself.
You're just like your mother
in playing the victim.
What did you say? - Face it.
You weren't good enough, that's all.
What about her? She made a mistake.
It wasn't a huge mistake anyway.
And we hold the audition
to choose students who have potential.
You have zero talent for music.
So stop causing trouble
and get out of here now.
No.
I know for a fact
that the admission was corrupted.
I cannot accept this.
Corrupt admissions?
Can you be responsible for what you said?
The students who got accepted
had been decided already, right?
That's how Ha Eun Byeol got in
despite her mistake!
If you do not leave now,
you'll get dragged out.
The one who bought out my teacher
was you, lady.
"Lady"?
You never taught me.
Why should I call you Ms Cheon?
Goodness.
I'm not going to move an inch
until you show me the scores.
Hey. - Eun Byeol.
What are you doing?
Get up.
Get up!
Eun Byeol!
Eun Byeol! Are you okay?
My arm hurts. - Are you all right?
"Seoul Gangnam Police Station"
Ro Na.
Ro Na, are you okay?
Mum. - Are you hurt?
What happened to your hands?
Eun Byeol got hurt, not her.
I can't believe
how barbarically strong she is.
What did you say?
What have you done to my daughter?
My goodness, please.
Goodness.
Starting now, you can talk to me.
Please take care of this, Mr Lee.
I won't show her mercy,
so punish her according to the law.
Why are you letting her go?
You can't just trust her
and let her go! What are you going to do?
What do you think?
You and your daughter
can take the punishment.
Now, here's the security footage,
and I prepared this
for you to see with your own eyes
just in case.
I may look like this,
but I'm pretty kind for an attorney.
Here.
Come on.
"Cam 209"
She kept trying to pull me up.
It's okay. It's all right, Ro Na.
Look, that's assault,
property damage,
spreading rumour and defamation.
She's guilty of numbers of things.
Right.
She has a history of school violence too.
What a shame.
How did you educate your kid?
Hey!
And look.
Slide to the next video.
"Cam 212"
The mum and the daughter are
both extreme in nature.
This is...
Gosh.
Right.
She filed a suit against you too.
Both you and your daughter
have been continuously harassing
Ms Cheon and her daughter,
and we'll make sure
you two get punished for what you did.
For your information,
we won't settle the case.
But if you insist,
we'll drop both cases
for 100 million won.
What?
How does that make any sense?
That was the end of my role.
If you can't find the money to settle,
we'll take legal actions right away,
so it's your choice.
Goodness.
Why did you mess with Ms Cheon?
You don't have any power or connections.
Is she stupid or naive?
Have a great time.
Will you please do something?
Are you okay?
Oh Yoon Hee.
Darn it.
You're late.
Seo Jin left a while ago.
Did she?
I have to go back to the hospital.
The assailant went to high school
with Seo Jin. Did you know?
Isn't that interesting?
Yes, this is interesting.
Kyu Jin is very quick with these things.
Aren't you scared?
I'm an expert on affairs.
Gosh, this is so exciting.
You made a mistake
and messed up your audition,
but you still got in
thanks to your mum, didn't you?
I heard your grandpa
is the chief director of the school board.
Something is going on.
Right? Something is going on.
"Judge"
Get a grip!
Practise. Practice is the only way.
"Judge"
"Score Sheet"
That was a mistake.
That wasn't what I am really capable of.
It'll be fine if I keep my mouth shut.
As long as I keep quiet.
We won't settle the case.
But if you insist,
we'll drop both cases
for 100 million won.
Oh, really?
I don't care if it takes a while.
Tell her that I won't settle for anything.
Okay.
Great work today, Mr Lee.
You must be in a great mood.
Why would I be in a great mood?
Eun Byeol didn't get the first place.
That's a pretty necklace.
I haven't seen that before.
My dad gave it to me.
Did you get sick of the one I got for you?
You wanted it badly.
I don't have to wear it
every single day because it's from you.
"Cheonga Arts High School"
"Min Seol A's Ongoing Scandal"
She's a total goner. - Really?
Nothing can save her.
How did she get in as the first place?
She must have had
connections that led to her admission.
That's disgusting.
Isn't she just a criminal?
She should be sent to a reformatory.
"Cheonga Arts High School"
"Cheonga is completely finished"
"I'm worried about my child as a parent!"
I'll surely get rid of a girl like this.
Don't worry.
I can't let her dishonour
the school that I will succeed.
Min Seol A.
How dare you deceive me
and defile something that's mine?
If you cancel her admission,
Bae Ro Na will automatically get accepted
as the top of the waiting list.
I can't let that happen.
I'll make her sign
a disclaimer of her admission,
then process it at the entrance ceremony.
Then I'll be able to get rid of
both Min Seol A and Bae Ro Na.
Both of them
will never get into Cheonga Arts High.
"Cheonga Arts High School"
"The 2020 New Student Orientation"
"Chief Director's Office"
"Headmaster's Office"
To be honest,
the waiting list is meaningless.
No one would give up
after they worked hard to get admitted.
Seo Jin.
I'm sorry for everything.
And it's only natural for you to hate me.
But please help my daughter.
Could you do that?
What?
Seo Jin.
She hasn't done anything wrong.
Please, I beg you.
Don't you think
it's too harsh for her to suffer
because of the adults?
Please let Ro Na get accepted.
You...
You have the power to do that.
Are you
asking me to use my connections
to let her get admitted unfairly?
Even the mighty Oh Yoon Hee
can't hold onto her standards
when it comes to her kid.
You despised people who used
their money and connections.
I didn't expect to hear that from you.
What can I do?
I'll do everything as you say.
If you don't want to see me,
I won't even come anywhere near you.
I won't come anywhere near the school
until she graduates.
Seo Jin.
If you tell me to clean your house,
I'll do that, Seo Jin.
You said you'll do whatever it takes
to make your girl get in Cheonga.
Where's your confidence now?
Stop asking me for help.
You should go out and kill one
of the students who got accepted
to let your daughter get in.
You're that heartless.
Go find the money to settle the case
unless you want to ruin her future.
This is an announcement for the students
of Cheonga Arts High, class of 2020.
New student orientation
will each be held by the major.
Have you heard?
She works at a bar.
I heard her sponsor got her in here.
She's so brazen.
I would've been too ashamed,
and would've given up on coming.
If she knew when to be ashamed,
she wouldn't work at a bar.
Have you seen it?
Have you seen me working at a bar?
Have you seen me with a sponsor?
Look at her eyes.
She looks so obnoxious.
Let's go.
What if she gets her filth on us?
There she is. - That's her?
My gosh.
She is on another level.
I thought you wouldn't come.
You're pretty determined.
Don't mess with me.
I'm not looking to get along
with your immature play.
Let's ignore each other from now on.
Why are you so arrogant?
Your pride won't help you
last long in this place.
You're a disgrace to Cheonga Arts High.
So get lost from our school.
Stop messing with me.
Why? Are you scared?
Let her go.
Take your seat.
Who's Min Seol A?
"Chief Director's Office"
"Headmaster's Office"
Come in.
We have a lot to talk about, don't we?
I'm sure you already know my father is
the chief director here.
If you sign the disclaimer that says
you give up on your admission,
I won't hold you responsible for anything.
You were accepted as the first place,
so you should save your face.
Sign that paper and leave.
I'm going to attend this school.
What?
I don't understand why I should give up.
You really are something.
What's that naive look
as if you did nothing wrong
after you deceived people?
It's a crime to forge your identity
and documents
to trick people for the tuition money.
I got accepted thanks to my talent.
It's a different matter from that.
Is it?
You're young, naive, and ignorant.
Do you want to ruin your life
for forging documents?
At the very least,
I did my best for the money I got paid.
You were also grateful
because Eun Byeol's grades went up.
If you still say the tuition is a problem,
I'll do part-time jobs to pay it back.
So I can't give up on my admission.
You shrewd and impudent thing.
People have a bad idea of orphans
because of kids like you.
Stop talking,
sign that now, and leave.
"Chief Director Cheon Myung Soo"
Please let me sing.
I want to sing.
Do you really think I'll let you in?
It's horrifying and chilling to think
you could've affected my daughter.
The fact that you two were
breathing in the same room
feels disgusting on its own.
I can't believe she got involved with
a girl who got never educated at home.
Unbelievable.
My gosh.
I'm also a human, just like Eun Byeol.
Did I make her ill or what?
Your daughter isn't the only precious one.
How dare you compare yourself to her?
Are you saying an orphan like you
is as good as my precious girl?
Do you think Eun Byeol knows
what her mum is like?
What are you trying to say?
The 35th floor. The garden.
The man from the penthouse.
What?
Eun Byeol is very conscious of Seok Kyung.
If she finds out about your relationship
with the man in the penthouse,
how would she feel?
What did you just say?
Do you finally understand
what I'm trying to say?
I'm going to attend this school.
If you let me do that,
I won't tell anyone.
You can't pull this nonsense on me.
What did you see?
Do I have to say it in my own words?
It was a misunderstanding.
I don't know.
I'm not sure
if others will also think the same
after seeing the video.
I'll see you when school begins.
"The video"?
I'll make sure I call her out later.
Nice. - Just wait.
Her admission might get cancelled.
She went to the chief director's office.
I heard she was the first place.
She must be an excellent singer.
Will they kick out the first place?
Boys, I'm sorry to barge in,
but may I see that?
Sure. - Thanks.
"The truth about Min Seol A"
"She got caught walking into a bar"
She was the first place?
Yes.
But she might get kicked out.
She's an orphan
who got caught working at a bar.
Hey, isn't that Min Seol A?
Hey.
She's charismatic.
Thanks.
Why did you suddenly visit Hye In?
Our kids got into high school,
so I'm going to give her more attention.
She hasn't been doing well lately.
"Cam 01"
Okay, you should do that.
I'll stop by right after work.
Okay. See you later.
The colour of the diamond
is gorgeous and elegant,
just like her.
I like it.
I'll wrap it up for you.
Sure.
Soo Ryeon?
I can't believe you called me first.
It feels great.
Are you coming back during this break?
My parents say we should get married--
Let us
break off our engagement.
What did you just say?
I can't deceive my feelings anymore.
I already told my father.
I am
going to get married soon in the US.
I'm sorry, Dan Tae.
You won't be able to reach me from now on.
Hello? Hello...
Who says you can do that?
You can't break off our engagement.
Who says you can?
You can't break off our engagement!
Is his kid still that dear to you?
You still can't give up?
Yes?
This is bad.
That girl knows?
Are you sure?
She knows about this place.
She definitely saw us.
Once she opens her mouth,
that'll be the end of our lives.
There's no security camera
on the 35th floor, so don't worry.
She has the evidence.
I think she got something on her phone.
We have to find it and destroy it.
What an interesting girl.
I'll manage.
Are you crazy? We can't do this now.
I'm driven mad with anxiety.
Are you getting shaken
by a little girl like her?
Cheon Seo Jin, it's you.
Min Seol A is
not an ordinary girl.
We don't have any time to spare.
It's me, Joo Dan Tae.
Do you think
I'll let a little girl destroy my life?
What are you going to do?
Do you have a plan?
Girls like that are easy to deal with.
She'll pretend like she's smart,
trying to make use
of the weapon that she has.
But she has no idea
it'll turn into a knife that'll come back
at her.
If you die...
If you give up...
I must be going crazy.
I can't do this to that poor girl.
There has to be another way.
Hey, move it.
You have a lot to do.
I'm sorry. I'll do it quickly.
Gosh, this is why it's never good
to hire youngsters.
I only hired you because you begged me.
Gosh.
Ms Oh.
I heard you're moving.
Did the landlord tell you to move out?
No, it's not that.
We're just downsizing.
Where will you be moving?
We haven't decided yet.
It's just me and my kid,
so I'm sure we'll find something.
Gosh, it's not easy to raise a kid.
Hey, slow down.
Stop the treatment.
It's unlikely that she'll wake up,
so why keep her on life support?
It's time to stop.
She managed to live pretty long
while being well looked after
by her fake parents.
Don't you agree?
Your wife will be shocked.
It's about time
she tasted true misery.
Get ready for it quietly.
I don't know if this is okay.
If the accuser finds out-- Gosh.
You know who the accuser is.
She's no ordinary woman.
I'll deal with her.
I sent the settlement money,
so make sure she gets it.
Well, I guess
I have nothing to lose.
Cheers.
By the way,
is she your first love?
I can tell that she is.
I thought you were the ambitious type.
You actually have
a naive side to you.
Even if she is your first love,
how could you spend
100 million won so easily?
Or... My gosh.
Are you two still seeing each other?
Since when?
You seem very busy,
but you still have time for fun.
No, we are not seeing each other.
Goodness.
Darn it.
If Seo Jin finds out,
we're both dead meat.
Right?
I wouldn't be surprised if it were to lead
to a murder case at Hera Palace.
Gosh, there will be blood everywhere.
I finally get why she asked
for 100 million won.
She obviously did it for a reason.
I could tell it had something to do
with adultery.
You know, because I'm a divorce lawyer,
I'm incredibly quick--
Will you stop it already?
Darn it!
What...
You scared me!
Hey! Brace yourself!
I'll tell my mum on you!
Why did you gather everyone?
The parents of the kids who got in
all signed this petition.
It's for cancelling Seol A's admission.
You can sign it and give it to me.
I couldn't sit back and watch,
so I decided to carry the ball.
Of course we can't let that girl
go to school with our kids.
All of us here signed it already.
Soo Ryeon, you're going to sign it, right?
Is this really necessary?
Adults ganging up against that kid?
I can't agree with this.
Look at her talking like she's better
than everyone else.
She has to make a fuss over it.
You did this
without my permission?
As you pleased?
Pardon?
Well...
We didn't want to get you involved,
so we did you a favour.
What is with this reaction?
Don't tell me
Min Seol A also knows about the petition.
I'm sure she knows.
The rumour has already spread
throughout the school.
Why do something I never even asked for?
Why mess with her?
I said I'll take care of everything.
Am I really the only one
who's not qualified?
Hey. Save me. Please, save me.
All right. Look over here.
I'll make you look pretty.
My gosh!
What is this?
Save me! - What on earth is this?
Please, don't do this.
What is this? - Stop this!
Don't do this--
Don't be scared. We're here
to celebrate.
Ms Anna Lee, congratulations
on entering Cheonga Arts High
as first place.
What are you to feel bad for us?
You should be punished.
You're like this, and that's why
your parents left you. - Awesome.
Who do you think you are?
What are you?
Tell us the truth.
Don't keep anything from us.
Why bother asking?
It's obvious that Seok Hoon led it.
Seok Kyung planned it,
and Seok Hoon led the other kids.
Right?
Je Ni, you had no choice
but to go with them, right?
Same goes for Min Hyuk. We could barely
hear his voice, right?
Yes, that's right.
Min Hyuk recorded it.
And Je Ni cursed more than anybody else.
They all took turns
and drenched her in alcohol.
This is a group assault.
All of our kids were involved in this.
It's terrible and shameful.
We're also responsible as their parents.
Our kids did something wrong,
yet we're trying to kick Seol A out.
Don't you think this is just wrong?
What's your point?
We should apologise
and ask for forgiveness.
And we have no right to ask the school
to cancel her admission.
Are you saying we should let
that sly brat walk all over us?
Do you think your kids will be okay
if people find out about this?
Their admission might be jeopardised,
and the stigma will follow them
to Seoul University of Music.
I don't think you realise
the seriousness of this.
What then? Are you saying
we should sweep it under the rug
without apologising?
Enough.
We should talk to Seol A in person.
The first anniversary party is tomorrow.
If there's a problem,
the party will be ruined.
All of you should be
extra careful until the party is over.
Who turned this off?
You are being fooled by Joo Dan Tae.
Joo Hye In is not your daughter.
"You are being fooled by Joo Dan Tae"
"Joo Hye In is not your daughter"
"Korea's Best DNA Testing Centre"
"Bio Geno"
"DNA Test Results"
Our analysis shows
that she's not your biological child.
Hye In is...
Hye In is not my daughter?
How is this possible?
"Bio Geno"
I can't believe this.
Then...
where is my real daughter?
"Seok Hoon and Seok Kyung's father"
Come to the 50th floor.
"Come to the 50th floor."
"50th Floor"
You people are really scary.
Are you that afraid
that I'd expose everything?
Then you never should've done it.
Let's keep this simple.
The video you have
and the original voice recording.
Just hand them over.
Where is your phone?
Did you think I'd trust you enough
to bring my phone here?
I'm not an idiot.
I will make sure I reveal
your true faces to everyone.
You're pretty smart.
But I wonder how long you can hold out.
I hope it won't be too painful.
"Joo Hye In is not your daughter"
"Ms Sim Soo Ryeon's baby"
There must be a problem with her brain
due to her premature birth.
That poor thing just keeps sleeping.
It's my fault.
It's all my fault.
Don't beat yourself up.
I'll take care of your baby now.
I even thought of a name for her, Hye In.
Pretty name, right?
No.
It's already over between us.
I have never forgotten about you.
After you left me,
I got married impulsively and had twins.
But their mother died
from septicaemia after giving birth.
Would you be a mother
to my poor twins?
That is absurd.
Please leave.
I will protect both you
and Hye In
from now on.
Just like my twins.
How...
How could he do such a thing?
Hello?
Are you ready to listen
to what I have to say?
Who are you?
I asked you if you believe
that Joo Dan Tae has been fooling you.
How can I believe you
when I don't even know who you are?
Who are you?
Your real daughter.
Don't you want to find her?
My daughter?
Is she alive?
Where is my daughter now?
You're going to have to find her yourself.
If you want to find your daughter,
you must do as I say.
If you do anything reckless,
Joo Hye In and your daughter
will both die.
Just like that man in the US.
Did my husband...
really kill him?
Believe what you want to believe.
What's important is that
Joo Hye In's heart
will also stop beating soon.
If that happens,
Joo Dan Tae's truth
will be buried forever.
How dare you try to kill my daughter.
Hye In is my daughter.
If you even lay a finger on her,
I will teach you a lesson.
Hello?
Go to Somang Children's Home
in Yeongdeungpo.
Find the child that was left there
wrapped in a navy jacket
in December of 2004.
Gosh.
Hello?
Sorry?
Cheon Seo Jin has dropped the charges?
Why, out of the blue--
She has been generous enough
to let it go,
and that's all you need to know.
She said you don't need to thank her,
so don't hover around her.
Goodbye.
Gosh.
This is very unlike her.
Ro Na, what are you doing?
It's the weekend. Let's go out...
What are you doing? Stop!
Ro Na. - Let go!
What's the matter?
Ro Na, you'll hurt your neck. Stop it!
I said, stop!
Ro Na, enough. Stop it!
Gosh.
I don't want to sing any more.
What?
Ro Na, don't do this. Stop, please.
You'll hurt your neck!
You were right, Mum.
Talent? It's completely useless.
Money and connections trump it all.
A girl like me doesn't deserve to sing.
So I don't need my voice any more.
Ro Na, don't do this.
I don't care if I lose my voice.
Please stop!
Gosh, please. Ro Na.
Just hit me instead. Just hit me.
Hit me instead. Just hit me, Ro Na!
Don't do this. Please stop!
Please... Please don't do this.
Ro Na, I'm sorry. It's all Mum's fault.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
What?
Min Seol A is in the mechanical room?
What? Then...
you should've taken her phone from her
and destroyed it.
Did you find her phone?
She'll talk soon.
I'll take care of it,
so you don't need to check in on her.
Provoking that brat
will only make her more arrogant.
Still, I don't know how I feel about
locking up that young girl.
We have to protect our children.
Their future is on the line.
How come Soo Ryeon isn't here?
She's not feeling well, so I came alone.
I have to say, she seems
rather uninterested in her own kids.
Some might think she's their stepmother.
Let's wrap it up here.
I have a lot to do because of the event.
It's been a long time
since we last organised
such a big party for Hera Palace.
But our kids ruined everything.
Darn it.
This is upsetting.
Don't be upset.
It's just a small setback.
Let's throw a spectacular party
to congratulate our kids
on getting accepted.
Bingo!
Let me plan this party. Please?
"Somang Children's Home"
Over here. - Got it.
Coming through. - Hey, watch out.
Excuse me. May I help you?
Isn't this Somang Children's Home?
They moved.
We began the construction a few days ago.
Do you know where they moved to?
No, I don't.
Do you have the director's number?
The number changed
as soon as they received the money.
I heard the director was
closing down the whole children's home.
They closed it down?
Honestly, I don't know
how they lived here with all those kids.
It's so mouldy,
and there's no heating.
Goodness.
It's practically a dump.
"Aram Detective Agency"
I'll pay you handsomely.
The sooner, the better.
You said the place already shut down.
How will I find the director?
My gosh.
If you find the director today,
I'll pay you twofold.
Get it done before the evening
and I'll pay you threefold.
Are you feeling very ill?
Do you want me to stay with you?
No, it's okay.
You're in charge of the event.
You should go.
Then I'll head over there now.
You can take your time.
Okay.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
Don't say that.
You're all I care about.
I'll see you in a bit.
Hello?
You found the director?
Where?
No! Darn it.
Let's see. If it was 2004...
You won't be able to find any records.
I discarded all the records
when I closed the children's home.
Did you leave your kid
at our children's home?
Why did you decide to close it?
And what happened to those kids?
Do I owe you an explanation?
All my life,
I looked after orphans
and contributed to social welfare,
so I think I deserve to take it easy now.
Why even look for a child
whom you abandoned years ago?
You sold a children's home in the suburbs.
Where did you get the money to open
a driving range of this size in Gangnam?
Can you tell me
where you got all the money?
I can do some digging and find out.
Shall I look into it?
I'm going to come here every single day.
I won't give up
until you show me the kids' records.
So fight me if you're willing
to risk everything you have.
Darn it.
That crazy woman.
Fine.
I'll hand over everything.
"Children's Records"
Go ahead and look through it yourself.
Darn it. You totally ruined my day.
However,
you cannot leak any information,
and no photos whatsoever. You got that?
Okay.
Good.
"Somang Children's Home, 2004"
Where are you, my baby?
Mum's here.
They put in a lot of work.
I know, right? - Yes.
Come on up.
Great job. - Thanks.
Look at this.
Go on in. - Thanks.
"Hera Palace"
It's all your fault.
All of this...
Cheon Seo Jin!
It's all your fault.
You're the reason why I'm living like this
and why my daughter
ended up in such a mess.
It's all your fault.
I'll make you pay for it.
Hello?
What? Where are you calling from?
Cheonga Arts High School? Okay.
What...
What did you just say?
We have an extra slot for Bae Ro Na
in the vocal music department.
An extra slot?
But why...
I mean, how?
One of the kids
who got accepted died yesterday.
No-- No way.
Did I do it?
=Penthouse=
What if she exposes our relationship?
People will think she's crazy.
Are you saying someone killed her?
Did you kill her?
Our kids killed her?
We have to do it to protect our kids.
Honey, there's blood on your shirt.
Ms Oh, there's blood on your hand.
This will get rid of all the evidence.
What did you do to Seol A?
What did you do?
I will tear you to shreds.