=Penthouse=
"All characters, locations,"
"incidents, and backgrounds"
"of this drama are fictitious."
That night,
=Episode 6=
she was with me
at Hera Palace.
You can check the CCTV footage.
Stop the witch hunt, please.
Framing an innocent person
won't do the school any good.
Min Seol A's death
has been concluded as suicide.
Must we create another victim?
Why did Dr Ha pull the plug
on something we almost had finished?
I don't understand.
I can
totally understand.
Do you think our kids will be disciplined?
We'll minimise the damage by any means.
Are you all right?
Yes.
I believe you.
That you didn't mean any harm.
You should hold out for your daughter.
Make sure
you protect Ro Na.
I will.
Thank you.
Our people's helping hand, Cho Sang Heon,
will keep you safe.
Let me leave my bank account details
for your contribution.
From Assemblyman Cho Sang Heon
of Happy Future Party.
You jerk.
"Message from Assemblyman Cho Sang Heon"
"of Happy Future Party"
"JKING Holdings"
I can only eat lunch after the meeting.
Is that all right?
Of course.
I'm excited to go out on a date with you
after so long.
Don't worry about me
and take your time to work.
"CEO Joo Dan Tae"
All right.
Then give me a little time.
"JKING Holdings"
What are you doing?
You need to leave.
If you don't, I'll bring the chairman.
Please help me.
Please help me out just this once.
He knows Seol A is my daughter.
Cho Sang Heon knows.
He's blackmailing me right now.
I need the evidence of his corruption.
I'm sure my husband knows something.
I need to know what Cho Sang Heon did
to Seol A.
Please help me out just this once.
The chairman told me
to keep investigating Mr Cho's back.
He's as sly as a fox.
"Adoption, dissolution"
You wicked jerk.
You should
expose this first.
"SBC"
"Editor-in-chief"
Gather round!
Gather round now.
This is Cho Sang Heon.
The assemblyman? - It's Cho Sang Heon.
It's Cho Sang Heon. - That assemblyman?
Cho Sang Heon.
This is just the beginning.
Last night, a news outlet
exposed an affair between Cho Sang Heon,
an assemblyman in his second term,
and a certain actress.
Assemblyman Cho's associates
flatly denied the charges as fake news
and announced their decision
to hold everyone liable
if they take part in spreading the rumour.
Reporter Song, please report in detail.
This scandal will likely
have an effect on the upcoming election.
Oh Yoon Hee. It was you, wasn't it?
If you took my money,
you should've stayed quiet for life.
What are you talking about, Mr Cho?
You put this out there.
How dare you deny it?
You need to get here now
and hand me all the money I gave you.
If you don't, that'll be
the end of your daughter's life!
Hello?
Hello? Mr Cho!
Darn it, that impudent brat.
How dare she stab me in the back?
I'm not going down alone.
It wasn't easy to get to this place.
"Oh Yoon Hee's family"
"Oh Yoon Hee's Movements"
"Politics Monthly M"
Why are you so late?
You're dead.
How did you know I was here?
You must've been in a hurry, Ms Sim.
May I go inside?
Are you here to negotiate?
But I'm sorry,
I'm a little busy.
I'll contact you again very soon,
without Chairman Joo finding out.
We need to talk now.
I said I'll contact you later.
Do you like it?
It's my gift.
What?
All the news outlets were reporting
the breaking news about you.
How does it feel to have
the entire nation's attention?
So it was you
who slipped the information?
Then shall we begin
our negotiation?
"Somang Children's Home"
"List of Children Adopted Abroad"
What is this?
You remember, don't you?
The kids you helped get adopted
from the children's home
and the horrifying crimes
you've committed to this day.
Why is this considered a crime?
They got adopted to rich families
and enjoyed living a luxurious life
they couldn't even fathom.
How dare you use those poor kids
to run a business?
You're less than a human.
What is this nonsense?
All these kids
were abandoned again,
just like Seol A.
Where are we going, Dad?
We're leaving to see your brother.
My brother?
Yes.
He's a bit ill.
So you need to help him a little, Anna.
Can you do that?
That was the day I found out
I had a sick brother.
Come on.
It wasn't me!
I didn't steal it! - Shut up!
Come on. - You get in there.
He's my brother! Tell them!
Say something to them, please!
All these kids were given up
as soon as the bone marrow transplant
was finished.
They were all deported!
Did you let these poor kids get adopted
to use them as donors?
Then they framed them and kicked them out
once they served their purpose?
Hey, lady.
I have no idea what this is about.
How would I know what the adoptive parents
did to them?
Everything had been planned already
before you sent them.
That's how you built your building
that cost you 10 billion won.
Do you have evidence?
Are you guilty of your crime
only when there's evidence?
This is evidence of a connection
between you and Director Min.
I already knew he had been
laundering your slush fund.
You've done your share of work, Ms Sim.
Are you this desperate
not to get kicked out of your house?
Hey, you know what?
You're the one who did that to her.
You killed her.
You abandoned her first.
You don't even know anything.
You need to ask for forgiveness
and get punished for your dirty crimes.
I'll expose everything
you've done to Seol A.
I've been in politics long enough.
There are many out there who can save me.
And one of those people
is your husband, Joo Dan Tae.
If you want to know,
I'll call him myself and ask.
Let go.
I said let go!
Get up.
I will
kill you.
Mr Cho, I'm here.
Mr Cho!
This is Oh Yoon Hee.
Are you in there?
Mr Cho, I'm coming in.
Mr Cho. Are you here?
Mr Cho.
"Oh Yoon Hee's family"
Why is Ro Na's photo here?
"Bae Ro Na, vocal music lesson room"
You need to get here now
and hand me all the money I gave you.
If you don't, that'll be
the end of your daughter's life!
"Bae Ro Na, vocal music lesson room"
"Husband"
I know that woman.
You should get out of here.
I'll manage the rest.
A man just died.
Trust me
and leave this place.
You need to leave.
Hurry.
"Soo Ryeon"
Your call cannot be connected.
Where are you?
I... I didn't see anything.
I don't know anything.
I haven't seen anything.
Are you sure everything is resolved?
Our school's reputation
could've fallen into the gutter.
Group assault?
And why is my granddaughter
involved in this ruckus?
Don't you know what our school is like?
We have 50 years of history
as the most prestigious private school.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Something like this won't happen again.
Why did Eun Byeol do that?
As if she was raised without proper care.
Stop it, Mum.
Dad, my husband arranged
this special occasion
to help you two feel better.
You're right.
I heard your resort is doing very well.
Yes.
We recorded our highest sale last month.
You must've taken after your father
in your knack for running a business.
This is why one's family is important.
Please excuse me.
I need to go back to the hospital.
Sit down.
Enjoy your dinner.
I said sit down.
We aren't done eating.
What did I tell you?
I told you he wouldn't like
eating a course meal.
Seo Jin, is something going on?
Did you two get into a fight?
I heard your parents' grape farm
isn't doing so well.
Do you need money?
Is that why you're protesting?
Father.
Goodness, a narrow-minded man like him
isn't good for anything.
I'm sorry.
That's as big as my mind gets.
Please excuse me.
If you continue to disappoint me,
I'll hand over Cheonga Foundation
to Seo Young.
What do you mean?
Why would Seo Young take over?
No.
I'll succeed the foundation anyway.
I'll wrap up my business and work there.
In order to build up the foundation,
it might be better for her to take over
since her in-laws have enough power.
If you leave it to me,
I can do a great job too, Dad.
Don't be greedy.
That place is mine.
Why did you marry such a useless man?
He never lets a day pass by in peace.
Your father.
"Your father"?
Yes!
Your majestic father and mother.
How can they never forget to show
that they do not approve
of their eldest son-in-law?
What exactly is your problem?
If I got rid of your countrified nature,
the least you can do is try harder!
What more do I have to do to try harder?
I've done everything I could.
What do they hate so much about me?
Because my parents
are uneducated and poor?
Or because they have a grape farm?
If they hated that so much,
they shouldn't have let me marry you.
If I'd known they'd torment me like this,
I wouldn't have married you!
I guess you regret it to death.
Do you have nothing to hide
now that everyone knows
you gave 100 million won to Yoon Hee?
You betrayed the woman you loved
and came to be with me!
You made this choice yourself!
Do you know that
you're becoming lousier by the day?
I hate everything about you,
but what I hate the most
is this inferiority complex
engraved in your mind.
That's the worst.
Hey.
Hey!
Stop right there!
Darn it.
You!
You're home.
When did you get home?
Just now.
You called, right?
I fell asleep while getting a massage.
I'm sorry.
You must be very tired
if you went to get a massage at this hour.
On top of that,
you fell asleep too.
I haven't slept well lately.
I guess I was a bit tired.
Kyu Jin is in your study.
I prepared wine and a light snack.
Okay.
Thanks.
Goodness.
I'll take it.
Thanks.
Thank you.
I wasn't expecting your call
all of a sudden.
What now?
Did something happen to our kids again?
No.
I wanted to discuss our business today.
In three months,
the redevelopment of Bosong Village
will be announced.
I plan on building the second Hera Palace.
Wasn't the redevelopment plan
for Bosong revoked many times already?
And there's trouble over compensation.
I heard
Changryong Village is the most likely.
Bosong Village currently has
a total of seven units on sale.
If we do our best,
we can purchase up to 10 units.
This is a beautiful chance to make
eight billion won in a short period
by putting in just two billion won.
That much?
But what about the titles?
Of course we'll use different names.
I already got the people.
Goodness, Chairman Joo.
You're a man with a great initiative.
You remind me of my mum.
But wait, Bosong Village.
Min Seol A.
It's where that kid used to live.
You're right.
That's why Dr Ha isn't in this plan.
Our kids got punished
with 20 hours of volunteer work
after the Min Seol A incident,
so he must pay for disappointing us.
I'm glad you did.
"Stop the witch hunt, please.
Framing an innocent person
won't do the school any good."
I'll meet you at the garden.
What was that guy saying?
I get that she's his first love,
but his wife was right there
with her eyes wide open.
He must have gone insane from
his in-laws repeatedly killing his spirit.
Goodness. That loser.
I'm not done talking yet.
Our plan includes
Min Seol A's old house too.
What?
There's no need to buy a house
where someone has died.
She set it on fire and killed herself,
so the owner put it up like a giveaway.
He's looking for a quick sale,
so I plan on purchasing it this week.
All right.
This is a great opportunity for us.
We can do the work ourselves
to wipe out Min Seol A's traces.
Okay.
Let's take that house.
She ended up doing us some good.
Joo Dan Tae.
Things won't go the way you want.
I won't let that happen.
What's going on?
Why are you so passionate today?
Don't say another word
and play along with me.
Why did a charming woman like you
marry a guy like Ha Yoon Chul?
I wanted him because I couldn't have him.
And I thought that was love.
I was foolish and immature.
Come here.
There won't be a thing you can't have
from now on.
Assemblyman Cho Sang Heon
of Happy Future Party,
who was suspected to be in an affair,
was found dead in the bathroom
of his vacation home.
The police began the investigation
with the possibility of slipping
and suffering from cerebral haemorrhage,
which could've led to his death.
At this point, there is no evidence
pointing to the possibility of homicide.
The NFS plans on conducting an autopsy
to find the details of the incident.
The actress who was suspected...
He was found in the bathroom?
of having an affair with Mr Cho
has not made a statement at this point.
He wasn't there.
The police will make another report
as soon as they have further information.
Hello?
This is Songpa Police Station.
We'd like to question you as a witness
regarding Mr Cho Sang Heon's death.
Could you come to the station?
You were the last person
he talked to before his death.
We need you here immediately.
Ms Oh.
Ms Oh?
I'll kill you if you scream.
Do not look back.
Who are you?
You'll only answer my questions.
Why did you run away
from Cho Sang Heon's house?
That's...
I didn't kill him.
When I got there,
he was already dead.
I mean it. Please trust me.
Why were you there?
He had been blackmailing me.
He had a wrong idea
that I leaked out his love affair.
That's why
I went there to explain myself.
"Bae Ro Na, vocal music lesson room"
Someone was there.
I heard someone's phone vibrate,
and there was a bag on the sofa.
What you saw
is of no importance.
Head over to the police station
and tell them Cho Sang Heon
was already dead in the bathroom.
Other than that,
you have seen or heard
absolutely nothing.
Why... Why do I have to lie?
If you want
you and your daughter to live,
you'd better do as I say.
Instead,
I'll give you important information.
You look so pretty,
my daughter.
"The late Min Seol A"
You aren't alone anymore.
Mummy will always be with you.
My son, you're the best.
Eat just one serving. - I love you!
You need to lose weight. - Have fun!
I love you too!
Good luck. - Okay.
Soo Ryeon, I'm so jealous.
I heard Seok Hoon will play
the solo for the admission recital,
and Seok Kyung will sing the solo too.
The guests for this admission ceremony
all look amazing too.
Ms Cheon. - Hello.
Ms Cheon.
Why did Dr Ha do that?
I can't believe he took her side.
He made everything go haywire.
I talked to the chief director
and made the punishment
as light as possible.
So let's wrap it up at that.
It's 20 hours of volunteer work!
How can Je Ni do such rough work?
This isn't the first time
we got in trouble for trusting you.
Then you can draw a line between us,
and don't get involved with me.
Fine, do that.
Let's draw a line!
Do you think I'm scared?
I can always find another teacher.
Head of Arts, time to begin your class.
Are the kids all there?
Wait.
"Head of Arts"?
Who?
Ms Cheon became the new Head of Arts
for Cheonga starting this semester.
What? - What?
I'm the Head of Arts,
in charge of your admission recital.
As you all know,
we do not have the first place this year.
So the second place, Joo Seok Kyung,
will sing the solo.
Give her a hand.
Cheonga's admission recital is
an important event with a long tradition.
Many important figures of the industry
will be there as honoured guests.
I hope everyone, not just Seok Kyung,
will practise very hard.
"Spring's Voices, Op. 410"
The shocking truth has been exposed
behind years of support for an orphanage
made by Assemblyman Cho Sang Heon.
Cho was involved in the overseas adoption
for a bone marrow transplant.
The children were sent back afterwards
and he made tens of billions of won
through the process.
The police have arrested Min,
the director of Somang Children's Home
who worked hand in hand with Cho
in the children's adoption process,
and will investigate him in custody.
I'll give you important information.
In two days,
Bosong Village's redevelopment
will be announced.
You need to purchase
Unit 501 of Building 3 by tomorrow.
"Bosong Village Redevelopment Plan"
"Confidential"
"Bosong Village"
"Samseong-dong, Hera Palace"
Bosong Village
will be redeveloped?
"Assemblyman Cho Sang Heon Found Dead"
"Illegal Organ Trafficking Exposed"
Make sure you check and see
no one makes a connection to me.
You don't have to worry, sir.
Mr Yoon.
Last night,
why didn't you pick up my call?
Hye In wasn't doing so well,
so I must have missed it.
I'm sorry.
You were at the hospital?
Mr Yoon, you never let me down.
You barked when you were told
and bit as you were told,
like a loyal dog.
Isn't that so?
Has it been 20 years
since you started working for me?
You work very hard day and night.
You may leave.
"JKING Holdings"
Yoon Tae Ju.
Did I keep
that old dog by my side for too long?
Your work here is done now.
Great work,
Joo Hye In.
Honey.
It's Hye In.
Hye In is in...
Ms Joo Hye In.
On December 17, 2019,
at 11:35 p.m.,
she passed away.
Honey, I'm sorry
I couldn't protect her.
Hye In...
"The late Joo Hye In"
You should let her go now.
You've done a lot too.
I want to be alone for a moment.
Okay.
You should do that.
I'll be in the car with the kids.
Let's go.
"Hamin Hospital"
One, two, shock.
Charge to 250 joules.
Charged to 250 joules.
One, two, shock.
Her pulse came back.
Hye In is in danger.
It seems like the chairman
will take care of her himself.
Kill her
just as he wants.
That's the only way
you and Hye In could survive.
There's this drug that can stop
your heartbeat momentarily.
Once she gets into her casket,
please take her somewhere safe.
If you're even a little late,
she may not wake up forever.
Hello?
She regained
consciousness.
She had been taking
too much sleep aids,
so she'll be
under intensive care for a while.
Thank you so much.
I'll never forget what you did.
Thank you.
"Dalhyun Real Estate Office"
What?
Unit 501 in Building 3
is really listed for sale?
Yes, the price is very low.
I've received many calls about it, but...
It hasn't been sold yet?
You know what happened there, right?
I'm assuming you know about the accident.
What accident?
Come on.
A young girl lived there alone,
but she set the place on fire
and took her own life.
It was all over the news.
Then,
that's where...
The owner has agreed to pay
for the renovation.
It'll look new once it's renovated.
It gets a lot of sun as it's facing south.
No, it's okay.
Thank you.
I just let her off the hook.
I could've totally punched her back.
Why let her off the hook?
I'm so upset.
What was I supposed to do?
What if she demands
compensation like last time?
We can't afford to move again.
If you can't trust the information
that can transform your life,
so be it.
The choice is yours.
"Bosong Village Redevelopment Plan"
Fine.
I'll just take a big leap of faith.
Who cares if someone died there?
She did her best.
What's wrong with moving there?
You couldn't prove your income
for the past three months,
and your payments were overdue
in the past,
so we can't grant you a loan.
I see.
No one will lend you 20 million won
when the collateral is a small flat.
You can't take out a credit loan
if you don't have a permanent job.
We have to have experts
appraise the building first,
so we can't grant you a loan right away.
"OK Cash, Fast Loans"
You must sign the contract by midnight.
"Easy Loans"
"Low Interest, No Collateral Needed"
You must be in urgent need of cash.
How much? - 20 million won.
What about the collateral?
Can I use my long-term lease deposit?
Do you have the papers?
"Yongho Loans"
Our interest rate is quite high.
Can you handle it?
Yes.
Please grant me a loan.
Here. Sign this.
Right here?
"Agreement to Give Up Organs"
"Oh Yoon Hee"
Sir!
Sir, I'm in a hurry.
Sir, are you inside?
Sir!
Gosh, what's with all the fuss?
Goodness.
What brings you here so late?
"Oh Yoon Hee"
Oh Yoon Hee
signed the contract last night.
Good work.
I'll call you later.
You're already up?
You should get more sleep.
Are you feeling better?
Yes, I feel much better now.
Thanks.
Oh, did you go
to Assemblyman Cho's funeral?
Barely anyone showed up
because of the extramarital affair
and the adoption scandal.
This is why you must lead an honest life.
I'm going to the gym.
What about you though?
What?
Nothing.
You must've changed your cologne.
You smell nice.
What do you mean?
Someone bought that place?
I came as soon as they opened,
but someone bought that place yesterday.
But do you know who bought it?
Oh Yoon Hee?
She's...
Gosh. Who is she, really?
She couldn't have known
about the redevelopment.
I know it was listed at a low price,
but how could she morally be okay
with moving into that place?
Her daughter got admitted
in Min Seol A's place,
and she's even taking her home now?
That is just wrong.
I'll call you later.
She's one mysterious woman.
Oh Yoon Hee.
She keeps getting on my nerves.
Oh, boy.
Darn it!
Why don't I see any articles about it?
This is driving me crazy.
Hold on.
Maybe they're not announcing it today.
No, it is today.
Let me see.
If this goes wrong,
both Ro Na and I are done for.
Kyu Jin is here!
You punk. Why are you
eating chips so early in the morning?
What was your name again?
Sir, you have mail.
Ms Kim, I like your outfit today.
Nice and bright.
Is it summer now?
Who told you to jack up the heat?
You guys think you can be wasteful
because you're not paying for it.
What's all this?
Why isn't there a name on this one?
What is this?
My gosh! Goodness.
What is that?
"I know what you did at this time!"
"JKING Holdings"
"I know what you did at this time."
"No Caller ID"
Lunatic.
"Cheonga Medical Centre VIP Ward"
Good morning. - Good morning.
"No Caller ID"
"I know what you did at this time."
"I know what you did at this time"?
What are you going to do now?
Hold on. This punk
even knows where I work.
This is insane!
But you know,
that creepy eye right there.
I swear, I've seen it somewhere.
Darn it.
Wait. - Why didn't you tell me
you lost that watch?
That's not important right now!
I'll be suspected now!
Chairman Joo. - Darn it.
Goodness gracious!
Dr Ha!
Why couldn't you find it
in the flower bed?
Are you blind or what?
You couldn't find it either. Why blame me?
Hey!
You should've looked
more thoroughly! - You little...
Gosh, I want to punch you right now.
Goodness. - Hey.
Geez, you piece of...
From the sign that was hanging
above the fountain
to the recording
uploaded on the school website.
Something's not right.
Maybe Min Seol A
didn't actually kill herself.
What if one of us killed her?
Isn't that why
we're being threatened like this?
Let's be honest.
Wasn't Chairman Joo the one
who started and led the whole thing?
You suggested that we should
move the body to Min Seol A's place.
Did you want to take care of it quickly
because you felt guilty?
So you dragged us into it
and set Min Seol A's place on fire.
You started that fire?
My gosh.
Chairman Joo, you really scare me.
Come to think of it, didn't Seok Kyung
benefit the most from this?
She became the top student
because Min Seol A died.
And she even has a solo performance now.
This is exactly what this person wants.
Doubting each other and becoming divisive.
So what's important now? The fountain,
the recording, and the pocket watch!
Someone knows what we did.
Somebody knows.
That means there's a witness.
We must find out who it is.
Our number one priority is finding out
who's threatening us.
There's someone I'm suspicious of.
Who?
Someone with the recording
who isn't here right now
and wasn't involved in the incident at all
on the night of the party.
Are you talking about Soo Ryeon?
Why would she do that?
Her kids are involved in this too.
You're right!
She's the only person who wasn't there.
And she got all worked up
whenever Min Seol A's name came up.
Am I wrong?
She didn't come to the party that evening
and even left during the ceremony.
What if
Soo Ryeon really saw us?
That day, she wasn't
feeling well, so she stayed in...
Your wife, Ms Sim Soo Ryeon,
kept calling Min Seol A as well.
I'm excited thinking about
our date in a while.
Don't mind me.
Take your time and finish your work.
Chairman Joo! Where are you going?
What's going on?
"Camtech Viewer"
"CEO Joo Dan Tae"
When did you start
doing things behind my back?
I guess you didn't know
I had CCTV cameras in my office.
I'm sorry, sir.
You're sorry?
Tell me what you are scheming
with my wife!
I saved you from the streets
and gave you a proper job.
How dare you betray me.
You'd better tell me.
What did you tell my wife?
You can never get away from me. Got it?
Thank you for everything
over the years.
"End Call"
Darn it!
Secretary Cho.
Get in here!
Bring Yoon Tae Ju to me at once.
Dead or alive, I don't care.
Just bring him to me!
Yes, sir.
Did you look into that thing?
Here's your wife's call log.
Anything unusual?
I looked up the number she called often,
and it's a detective agency.
A detective agency?
Well...
Do we really have to do this?
This is so pathetic.
Come on. I'm sure she's up to something.
You need to help us out
since you're an attorney.
Oh, there she is.
Gosh.
Let's hurry. We might lose her.
Go! - Gosh.
Let's go. Put on your seat belt.
"Aram Detective Agency"
Who are you? - Move!
Who are you guys?
You know this woman, right?
What did she ask you to find out?
I will ask again.
Why did she come to see you?
That's confidential information,
so I can't tell you.
You'd better tell us
before I break all your limbs.
Okay, I'll tell you.
I'll tell you everything,
so please don't kill me.
How have you been?
I'm sorry for not visiting you often.
I knew it!
What on earth are you doing here?
What brings you here?
What is this?
You even got
a columbarium niche for Min Seol A?
Why are you
so obsessed with that girl?
What is your relationship to her?
What are you talking about?
Are you the one who's been threatening us?
And did you upload that recording?
Was it all you?
I trusted you!
How could you do this to us?
I... - Calm down.
Gosh. - My goodness.
You even got a columbarium niche for her.
Are you her mother or what?
Let me see.
This isn't Min Seol A.
Who is this girl?
She's my daughter.
What?
My daughter died recently.
Gosh. - Say something.
Well...
You see, we were just...
Gosh. - Are you okay?
Ma Ri, what's the matter with you?
Goodness.
Just be quiet.
What did you just say?
"An affair"?
Yes, the lady in that photo asked me
to find out about her husband's affair.
She thought her husband
was cheating on her.
Look, I really cannot disclose
personal information like this.
That was really it. Please believe me.
"JKING Holdings"
If this man comes here,
tell him I suspected that my husband
was cheating on me.
"JKING Holdings"
And?
Did you find anything?
No.
I tried but gave up.
He's not the type
to leave behind evidence.
I kept digging but found nothing.
I can't believe Chairman Joo.
How could he hide
his ill daughter in the hospital
all this time?
That's what I'm saying. My gosh.
You must've been heartbroken, Soo Ryeon.
Even I'm so upset.
You always said you were busy.
Was that all because of your daughter?
I'm sorry
for not telling you.
Gosh, why are you sorry?
The jerk who told you to hide it
is the one to blame.
I did hear about Seol A's suicide.
But I was preoccupied with my daughter
because she was so ill.
It must've been so hard for you.
Think of me as your big sister.
You can rely on me from now on.
We've known each other for years.
Was she born out of wedlock?
I mean, why else would Chairman Joo
try so hard to hide her?
Am I wrong? - Ms Cheon.
What on earth are you talking about?
How could you say such a thing
knowing she lost her child?
There you are.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
They followed me to the columbarium,
so I had no choice.
We already lost her,
so I wanted to keep it a secret forever.
They should apologise for following you.
Anyway, take this as an opportunity
to befriend the ladies at Hera Club.
I don't care about what happened,
so don't worry.
Where are you now?
I think my husband is on to something.
You should leave immediately.
Take the first flight-- - I already
packed up. I'm actually
headed to the airport now.
I'm relieved.
Make sure you call me when you arrive.
No, our deal ends here.
You will never hear from me again.
Take good care of yourself.
Thank you for everything,
Mr Yoon.
Chairman Joo.
This is my final act of loyalty.
"2 months later"
What is this?
This phone
was inside the air handling unit.
I see.
Who is this?
She doesn't live here.
I'm sure she'll come back for it.
Seok Kyung, your cold got worse.
The admission ceremony is tomorrow,
but you can't perform solo like this.
You should go see a doctor.
I don't think Seok Kyung
can perform tomorrow.
I know you practised really hard,
but what can you do?
We can't ruin this important performance
because of you.
We need someone to sing
Seok Kyung's solo part instead of her,
but we don't have much time.
Any volunteers?
I'll give it a try.
Really?
Are you confident?
Yes, I'll give it a shot.
Then Eun Byeol will do the solo part--
I'd also like
to give it a try.
Ro Na, have you lost your mind?
Know your place. How dare you.
All right.
Then why don't we listen to both of you
and go with the one who's better?
Who wants to go first?
I enjoyed both of your performances.
Now, here's my decision.
This song...
was better performed by Ro Na
in all aspects.
Ro Na.
You will perform solo tomorrow.
Thank you, Ms Cheon.
I'll do my very best.
The performance has to be perfect.
You can do a good job, right?
Yes.
Don't let me down.
I borrowed it at the last minute,
but it fits you perfectly.
My princess, you look stunning.
I can't believe
I'm performing at the admission ceremony.
Mum, this isn't a dream, right?
I heard many famous vocalists
will be there.
I'll do a fantastic job.
Just like you, Mum.
Watch, I'll teach those kids a lesson
for making fun of me
that I was on the waiting list.
Okay. I'm so proud of you, my princess.
Thanks to you, I get to smile like this.
Thank you.
Mum, you look so downcast these days.
Is something bothering you?
No.
Not at all.
Let's hurry. - Okay.
Are you ready?
We're almost there.
Okay.
"Simultaneous Signal"
"Cheonga Arts High School"
"Admission Ceremony"
"2020 Admission Ceremony"
Hey, how did it go?
Okay.
All right, thanks.
Get ready, Eun Byeol.
This was supposed to be your stage.
Your grandpa is here.
Show him that you are the future owner
of Cheonga Foundation.
Ro Na, are you all right?
Hey, Ro Na. Let me see.
Let me take you to the hospital.
No, Mum. I'm okay.
I have to perform.
Ro Na, you're badly injured.
You need to see a doctor first.
I said I'm fine!
Hurry. I need to go to school.
I can't be late. Hurry, Mum.
What do I do?
Ro Na, hold on tight.
We will now begin
the 2020 admission ceremony.
You can't enter now.
Get out of my way. I must perform.
The performance hasn't begun yet.
You cannot go in.
I'm singing the solo part.
I must go in!
I said, you can't go in!
Gosh, please!
I must go in. Let me in!
Hey! Why can't you let her in?
Gosh, back off!
You! - Ouch!
Are you all right? - Let's go.
Get them!
Gosh! - Stop!
Get off me!
Hey, let her go!
Ro Na, go!
Mum. - Ro Na, just go!
Go away!
Hey, are you okay?
=Penthouse=
Sim Soo Ryeon.
What on earth are you thinking?
That was my first time hearing
"I love you".
Oh Yoon Hee moved
to Min Seol A's place?
She has something to do with Min Seol A.
Did she die because you guys bullied her?
Do you want me to die like she did?
Protect your child at all costs.
Did you kill Min Seol A?
I want to live here too.
A place like Hera Palace.
I will do whatever it takes to make sure
you get to live here one day.