=Penthouse=
"All characters, locations,"
"incidents, and backgrounds"
"of this drama are fictitious."
=Episode 13=
"Personal Information: Logan Lee"
"Father: James Lee, CEO, Lee Corporation"
My husband has recently been
most concerned about this man.
A rumour says he'll open a shopping centre
in the Myeong-dong land Dan Tae bought.
His name is Logan Lee.
All I know is that
he's a Korean-American
who's filthy rich.
You don't even know what he looks like?
No.
Even my husband hasn't met him.
He keeps scheduling a meeting with him,
but it always gets cancelled.
If you manage to contact him,
he'll have to hire you for that position.
This is the information you have on him?
I secretly took pictures
of those documents at Dan Tae's study.
Pretend as if you approached Attorney Lee
to obtain the information.
That way, he won't be as suspicious.
Can you do this?
I'm a guy who passed the bar exam
while I was still a student.
Who does he think he is?
He keeps telling me to come and go...
Goodness.
Are you all right?
Yoon Hee.
Gosh, come on.
Did you come out to fetch me?
You had too many drinks, Attorney Lee.
No!
Don't call me Attorney Lee.
I'm a guy who identifies with my name.
Call me Mr Kyu Jin from now on.
Mr Kyu Jin... No.
Call me Kyu Jin. Just Kyu Jin.
Try it out. Do it.
Kyu Jin.
"Resident Car Park"
Anyway,
is something troubling you today?
I saw you walking over
swearing under your breath.
Something is...
troubling me.
Yes, something is making me furious.
I had to put on a show for my mum,
singing "Woman of Samba,"
and doing all kinds of things
to borrow 30 billion won.
Then I took it
and gave it all to Chairman Joo's project.
And all of a sudden,
that Logan Lee or whatever showed up
and kept fooling around with...
No.
Kyu Jin, shut up.
Anyway, Yoon Hee...
my heart is racing.
Pardon?
Good night.
Right.
"Resident Car Park"
Idiot. He has got to be the biggest moron.
What did he just say?
30 billion won?
A real... - A real estate agent.
Then say, "I've been a real estate agent
for over 10 years."
I am a real estate agent
for... for over 10 years.
Myeong-dong is...
Korea's number one shopping district.
Myeong-dong is
Hello, Mr Logan Lee.
I'm Oh Yoon Hee.
The only one Logan Lee is in contact with
is his secretary.
You need to meet his secretary
and persuade him first.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Excuse me.
You're Mr Logan Lee's secretary, right?
Hello.
My name is Oh Yoon Hee.
May I meet him for just a moment?
You cannot see him
unless you made an appointment ahead.
Excuse me, sir.
This is a very pressing matter.
It's really important to me,
so just for 10 minutes, no, 5 minutes.
No, even just one minute, please.
Get her out of here.
Wait, it'll take only a moment.
Do you think I'll give up?
I am
putting everything I have in this too!
I got scared for nothing.
Hey, Soo Ryeon, it's me.
I haven't met him yet.
It must be hard for you.
It's not a big deal.
I'm totally determined right now.
Logan Lee?
I'm going to make sure I see him.
All right.
Call me when you have any good news.
Good news?
When did you get here?
Who were you talking so friendly with?
Ro Na's mother?
I had to talk to her
about something in the kids' school.
I already told you
that I don't like that woman.
I told you to stay away from her.
She might have approached you on purpose.
There's nothing I can do for her.
Why would she do that?
I don't even know much
about what's going on at the school.
I thought you had an important meeting.
Darn it!
He cancelled on me again!
That jerk is acting very high and mighty.
He's rich, but he can't be that rich.
It's nothing.
It'll be resolved soon.
I'm sorry, Ro Na.
I really have to meet someone. Yes.
Don't wait for me and go to sleep.
Hello.
It's me again.
Please let me see Mr Logan Lee.
I beg of you.
I really have to see him. Please.
Follow me, Ms Oh.
Pardon?
Hello.
Thank you so much for your time.
I'm Oh Yoon Hee.
What's your state of business?
I'm here to set up a meeting between you
and Mr Joo,
the president of JKING Holdings.
Did he send you here?
If that's the case, I really don't have
anything to say to you.
Please escort her out.
Let us leave.
No, wait. No.
No. No, I can't go like this.
Wait.
I must bring you to Mr Joo.
Please help me.
My life depends on this.
You are the only one person
who can help me.
Wait.
Do you know about Myeong-dong?
Myeong-dong is
the number one shopping town in Korea.
Here is the estimated
investment profit...
Darn it. Why can't I remember?
Okay.
"Myeong-dong is
Korea's leading commercial district
with high symbolism."
You may just speak in Korean.
He can understand.
Really?
Thank you.
Now that we're in this situation,
let me just be frank with you.
Joo Dan Tae deceived me,
and I lost a huge amount of money.
In order to get that money back,
I must get a job at JKING Holdings.
I'll make sure
this doesn't hurt you in any way.
I just need you to meet him once.
If you help me out,
I'll make sure I'll pay you back.
Please, I beg of you.
Please, sir.
Then why don't we set up a meeting
for tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
"JKING Holdings 2020 Employment Interview"
"JKING Holdings"
At last,
we finally meet, Mr Joo.
I may be the Logan Lee
that you were looking for.
Logan Lee?
Wow.
What a view you got here, Mr Joo.
What do you think?
Do you now feel like doing an interview
with me?
Oh Yoon Hee, I almost let you
fool me completely.
How am I supposed to believe
he's the real Logan Lee?
I've never met him to this day.
And you're saying you brought him here?
You're going to regret
what you just said right now.
He wants to know that
you are really Logan Lee.
Prove yourself.
Prove myself?
Please.
As you wish.
"Logan Lee"
Please.
You have a very respectable employee,
Mr Joo.
Now, can we get down to some business?
Oh, for your information,
he can understand Korean pretty well.
You may speak to him at ease.
You look beautiful.
Like a woman who's loved.
Is that how I looked?
It's always great to get some flowers.
Take a seat.
I wonder what you have to say to me.
You should open that up first.
I think you got a present too.
Should I do that?
I knew it was you.
You killed my daughter.
What's wrong, Seo Jin?
It's nothing.
Isn't this the ring you wore on that day?
What did you say?
At the first-year anniversary ceremony
for Hera Palace.
It looked really great on you,
so I still remember this.
You were worried about your ruby ring.
Look how big that thing is.
You're way too dressed up today, Ms Cheon.
And you got the same ring
as a present?
Give it to me.
Goodness.
Are you all right, Seo Jin?
You're bleeding a lot.
That ring is awfully sharp.
What if you scratched your face?
You can't let your pretty face get hurt.
Seo Jin, why are you trembling?
If you found your lost ring,
wouldn't you be happy?
What are you talking about?
I never had a ring like this.
I think you're mistaken.
Why are you so sensitive today?
Is there a story behind this ring?
Just say what you came to say.
Why did you want to see me?
This weekend,
I wanted to throw a party for Hera Club.
Seok Kyung and Seok Hoon
were chosen as school ambassadors,
and I never had a chance to thank you.
You came to see me over some party
you wanted to throw to celebrate?
You're an expert at throwing parties.
If you're the lady of the penthouse,
shouldn't you be able to manage it alone?
Something urgent came up,
so I must go.
Yes.
Run along
to Joo Dan Tae.
I knew we'd be on the same page.
"JKING Holdings"
Okay, so,
I would have to talk further details
with Ms Oh here, right?
"Yangjae Flower Market"
You can do as you'd like.
Are you free this weekend?
We're having a party at Hera Palace,
and I'd like to invite you.
Oh.
It would be an honour.
I'd love to see the Hera Palace myself.
I hear from Ms Oh here that
there's a marvellous fountain there.
I'll prepare the best party of your life.
I'll be looking forward to it.
Talk to you again soon.
Now, let's talk.
Ms Oh,
why do you want to get a job
at my company of all places?
I'm in need of money.
I saw your job advertisement
for an experienced employee
while I searched for a job.
Then I did a bit of research to find out
what the chairman of JKING Holdings
wants the most right now.
Luckily, Attorney Lee Kyu Jin
quickly told me about
a man named Logan Lee.
So Attorney Lee told you?
Is your speciality in
getting clingy with everyone and anyone?
I used that speciality of mine
to persuade Logan Lee.
Logan Lee came here today
solely thanks to what I did.
It wasn't you.
If you wish to sell
that land in Myeong-dong,
you'll need me from now on.
Don't forget.
Unlike how you look,
you must have a knack for this.
Fine.
In that case,
make sure you finish this job
and get him to sign the contract.
But that's all you can do.
As soon as I seal this contract,
I don't think there's any reason
for me to keep you around.
At that point,
you might end up begging me to stay.
Do you really think so?
That crazy woman.
Soo Ryeon.
Cheon Seo Jin is here.
Really?
What about what I asked you?
Don't worry.
I hid it very well.
What brings you here?
I told you not to come to my office.
So why didn't you pick up your phone?
I was in an important meeting.
Did you send this to me?
What were you thinking when you sent this?
What are you talking about?
Why would I send this to you?
It wasn't you?
Some flowers and this ring...
were sent in your name.
What?
I threw that ring away
in the rubbish bin at home
on the day Min Seol A died.
That happened months ago.
And someone sent me that ring
under your name.
This person knows what we did.
They're trying to blackmail us!
Lower your voice.
There are a lot of ears around here.
Don't be scared.
Min Seol A
killed herself.
You already know...
she didn't kill herself.
The threatening letter with the eye.
The one who wrote that is after us.
Director Min already died in prison.
I said I took care of him already.
It wasn't him.
The letter, the flowers,
and this ring.
Sim Soo Ryeon.
Your wife sent these to me.
What?
Why are you so suspicious of her?
Why would she do that?
To expose what we did to Min Seol A!
Don't you get it?
She's trying to torture us to death!
She wants to get her revenge!
Your wife is
somehow related to Min Seol A.
Min Seol A might be...
a daughter you didn't know she had.
What kind of nonsense is this?
It's not nonsense!
Her daughter is already dead!
What?
The girl in the columbarium.
She gave birth to her before our marriage.
The columbarium?
How could he hide his ill daughter
in the hospital all this time?
I'm sorry
for not telling you.
Was she born
out of wedlock?
That girl
wasn't your daughter?
No.
Before we got married,
we both had
someone else in our lives.
And we each had kids.
Seok Hoon and Seok Kyung
aren't her biological children.
I got remarried to her
when they were still infants.
And they grew up thinking she's their mum.
I could've never imagined.
Seok Hoon and Seok Kyung aren't
Soo Ryeon's biological children?
Then where's her ex-husband?
He died
before the girl was born.
I am...
more suspicious of your husband.
What do you mean?
You threw out
this ring in the rubbish bin at home.
Then who could've got his hands on it?
If your husband knows about us,
wouldn't he want to threaten us
by using Min Seol A?
Could it be him?
I doubt it.
He can be a bit of an idiot,
but he's not that low.
Do you still trust him?
Then let's check and see
who sent you
the flowers and the ring.
"Fairmont Ambassador Hotel"
"Joo Dan Tae funded Cho Sang Heon"
"Why was Seol A killed?"
"Possible Suspects"
"Lee Kyu Jin, Ko Sang A"
"Joo Seok Hoon, Joo Seok Kyung"
"Oh Yoon Hee, Cheon Seo Jin"
"Anna Lee"
Ms Oh was also at Hera Palace on the night
of the fountain lighting ceremony.
She was at Hera Palace?
Are you sure?
Yes, sir.
She went to Cheon Seo Jin's lesson room
and made a big scene.
She was caught on security cameras,
and Cheon Seo Jin's husband,
Ha Yoon Chul, is the witness.
Oh Yoon Hee.
Her daughter got into
Cheonga Arts High in Seol A's place,
then the two women moved
to the flat in Bosong Village
where Seol A used to live?
"Possible Suspects"
"Oh Yoon Hee"
Everything has been completed.
Everyone who was
at Hera Palace on that day and hour.
The suspects for Seol A's murder.
Eun Byeol, what are you doing?
You might fall down.
Dad.
I have to memorise everything
for my midterm until tomorrow.
Goodness, my girl.
Hello.
Hey, Ro Na.
Isn't it great to live in Hera Palace?
It is. - Your friends are here too.
Yes.
All right.
Are you feeling better?
Who asked you to worry about me?
And don't lay a finger on my stuff
with your disgusting hands!
Do you want to get on my dad's good side?
Eun Byeol.
Why are you so mean to your friend?
"Friend"?
She's not my friend.
I don't keep a girl like her as a friend.
And can't the elevators
for the upper and lower levels
be completely separated?
How long do I have to live my life
running into her like this?
This is so annoying!
Eun Byeol!
Are you all right? Are you hurt?
Eun Byeol. Eun Byeol!
Did you look into it?
Some man ordered those flowers
to be delivered to you.
And
the number he left was Dr Ha's number.
I covered up your medical malpractice,
and you repay me with this prank?
So you want to be a loser to the end?
Eun Byeol, what's wrong?
Stop right there. We need to talk.
I don't want to talk to you!
What's going on?
Don't you know
why she became that sensitive?
You should've given her a break.
Why did you stress her out over midterm?
I think you're stressing her out.
You're blaming me again?
Eun Byeol is my daughter,
and I know her best.
So stop meddling with her while she's busy
studying for her test.
I don't expect you to be my husband.
But do the least you can
and try to copy what other dads do.
My reference books.
My workbooks.
Eun Byeol.
Where are my reference books?
Did you throw them out?
Do you want me to do worse than Ro Na?
What?
Why were you so nice to her?
Don't you know how much I hate her?
I don't even want to breathe
the same air as that girl.
Why did you talk to her
and treat her nicely?
Because she's your classmate.
Why?
Do you feel bad for her?
Are you worried about her
because she's your first love's daughter?
Do you feel that bad for her
for growing up without a dad?
What...
What kind of nonsense is this?
Mum told me everything.
I heard you're seeing her mum.
Eun Byeol.
Did you want to leave us
to be with your first love?
Is that why you're nice to Ro Na?
Why are you saying that?
Don't listen to anything Mum says.
I love you the most in this world.
You liar!
You looked at her with a smile.
You aren't on my side.
That's a misunderstanding.
Will you please hear me out?
Mum is the only one who thinks of me.
Do you know what she did for me?
Min Seol A was...
Bring my reference books back now!
If you don't,
I will
kill myself like Min Seol A did.
What...
What happened to you?
Since when did you become such a wreck?
I'm sick of this.
You're a coward,
and you're the worst dad in this world.
Get out!
I don't even want to see you,
so get out of my room!
You!
Why did you tell her about Yoon Hee?
Do you have to break her heart too?
Why?
It's not like I made it up.
Don't you think she should know the truth
if she wants to fight against Ro Na?
Wait, did you do that
to make her more competitive?
You really make me shudder.
You're not the one to talk.
You acted as if you'll leave quietly,
then went out and did dirty things
behind my back.
I guess you got excited
for finding my weakness.
If you want Eun Byeol
to keep treating you as her dad,
shut your mouth, lie low,
then sign the divorce paper.
What makes you so confident?
Should I let the world find out
about everything you did?
If you got the nerves, go ahead.
You'll end up looking like an idiot.
Are you sure you'll be fine?
Let's play fair
until the day we get divorced.
You aren't showing good manners
to someone you lived with for 17 years
by stabbing me in the back like this.
Goodness.
Do not
provoke me anymore.
I won't condone this any longer.
Unbelievable.
The letter, the flowers,
and this ring.
Sim Soo Ryeon.
Your wife sent these to me.
She's trying to torture us to death!
She wants to get her revenge!
Is that all?
Is there anyone else we should invite?
There is.
His name is Logan Lee.
He's an important guest,
so pay extra attention to him.
Isn't he the guy you had to meet?
I guess you finally reached him.
I'm so relieved.
I also want to see what he's like.
And one more.
You can invite Unit 4502.
You mean, Yoon Hee?
May I do that?
I don't really want to,
but she's involved with Logan Lee.
I have to invite her against my will.
I guess she's meant to be
someone that's helpful for you.
Don't be so mean to her.
Try to treat her nicely.
Something about her feels very eerie.
I have no idea what she's thinking.
Then I'll give her the invitation myself.
It's very exciting to think
everyone in Hera Club
will get together for once.
Let's go get some dresses tomorrow.
Logan Lee has a very picky taste.
Really?
I was worried about what I should wear.
"Yang Mi Ok"
Yes, Ms Yang?
The chairman is
throwing a party this weekend.
They also talked about
going dress shopping tomorrow.
Really?
All right. Thanks for your help.
Why is Ms Sim taking so much time?
What's her plan?
What do you think?
You look great.
I knew you'd look great in everything.
You look stunning, Ms Sim.
You look great in everything,
so I don't know what I should recommend.
You should choose one for me.
If you like it, I like it too.
Try that on too.
Everything needs to be the best.
You must stand out at tomorrow's party.
I'll take everything she tried on.
Go on.
I'll take that scarf too.
Yes, Ms Sim.
What's wrong?
No, nothing.
You look very beautiful,
Seol A's mother.
What are you doing here?
How did you know I was here?
I know everything about you.
You seemed very relaxed before.
Why are you so scared?
Why?
You ignored my warning
and came here to get ready for the party
with your husband.
Stop minding my business
and get out of here.
Ms Sim, may I go in?
Let me help you.
No, I can do this alone.
I changed
my mind.
At tomorrow's party, let's tell everyone
you're Min Seol A's mum.
What?
It'd be more fun with more audience.
It's a perfect day
for a surprise.
I'll tell them when the right time comes.
So you need to stay out of this.
I already told you
that I won't let you go on
if you meddle with my business again.
Tomorrow is the D-Day.
And I am not going to negotiate.
On top of that, everyone who knows Seol A
will be at the party tomorrow.
Don't you think it's a perfect occasion?
Give me just a little more time.
There's something I must do.
Hey, lady.
Why should I care about your situation?
I'm not that nice.
I've already been punished.
I'm not happy.
Are you done getting changed?
What are you doing?
You have to go, please.
Honey?
What's wrong?
Goodness, are you okay?
I'm fine.
I just got dizzy.
I guess I worked too hard
getting ready for the party.
I'm sorry.
I'll get changed and come out.
All right.
Don't forget.
Tomorrow is the day.
"Cheonga Arts High School"
Why did you gather us this time?
I was so worried,
thinking something happened.
I think
the person who's impersonating Min Seol A
is Ro Na.
Bae Ro Na?
That shoe suddenly disappeared at school,
and she's the only one
connected to Min Seol A.
Oh, you're right.
She lived in Min Seol A's flat.
And Ro Na was accepted
in Min Seol A's place after she died.
Then she moved to Bosong Village.
Everything seems so fishy.
And she even came to live at Hera Palace.
Isn't it so odd?
Did she plan all of this?
What if
she's possessed by Min Seol A's ghost?
Enough!
That's just your speculation.
There's no proof that Ro Na did it.
Proof? We'll look for it.
How?
Do you have an idea?
Just leave it to me.
Hey, Ro Na.
What are you doing? Studying English?
Look at this. You got everything wrong.
Give it back. - You wish.
Give it back! - No. No way.
I got it.
What?
There's no group chat.
She probably deleted it already.
Enough already.
Why snoop through her phone? - Wait!
This dog...
No way. Is it the same dog?
"Sugar"
"Sugar"?
So it was really Ro Na?
She pretended to be Min Seol A
and threatened us?
Can you still deny it?
See for yourself.
They're holding the same dog.
Is this a coincidence?
See? What did I say?
I told you that it was Ro Na.
Gosh, I can't believe this.
This is serious.
Gosh, that brat toyed with us.
Bae Ro Na.
Why did I try to be nice to her?
She's really something.
Earlier, I sent some materials
on the lot in Myeong-dong
to your secretary.
Did you see it?
Oh, no. Not yet.
That's not my priority at the moment.
Listen.
I met with Mr Joo because
you desperately asked me for a favour.
That didn't mean that I was going
to sign the contract right away.
A contract
is made between two people, so...
wouldn't it be nice to know
what kind of people I'm dealing with?
Of course I understand.
That being said,
what kind of person are you,
Ms Oh?
Me?
What exactly do you mean?
I heard you were admitted into Hera Palace
in a very dramatic way.
You bought some old, beat-down apartment
and made some big money out of it?
Oh, that.
Chairman Joo must've told you.
There was a bit of a situation.
"Situation"?
I wonder what that situation was.
That apartment was listed
way under the market price.
A young girl
died there.
A suicide, apparently.
Suicide?
And you still decided to go
with the purchase because...
Of course I had no idea at first.
But for some odd reason,
living there didn't spook me out.
I actually met that girl once,
and she was very kind.
Did you guys know each other well?
No, just a little.
Had she had parents,
she wouldn't have died like that.
"Hera Club"
"Oh Yoon Hee, Anna Lee"
"Little Hera Club"
You...
Did you really mean
what you said about Seol A?
"Moved to Hera Palace from Bosong Village"
"after Seol A's death"
"Daughter got into Cheonga Arts High"
"Hera Palace"
"Mr Logan Lee, you've been invited"
"to Hera Club's private party."
"From Joo Dan Tae and Sim Soo Ryeon"
Wait and see.
It'll be a party you'll never forget.
Gosh.
What are you doing here?
Ms Oh?
What happened to your face?
Did something happen?
People at Hera Palace
are trying to kill me.
I'm so scared.
Please help me.
Help me. I don't want to die, Ms Oh.
That's right.
She said "people at Hera Palace".
I clearly remember it.
I'm sure of it.
When you see me with this scarf on,
consider it a sign
that I'll make you mine.
I see.
Why was Seol A
at Hera Palace that day?
No way.
What if it wasn't a suicide?
Did someone kill her?
No, that is absurd.
Mum. - Hey, Ro Na.
These must be from Ms Sim.
All of those?
My gosh.
Did she send this for you?
This dress is so beautiful.
It's something you'd see in a movie.
Be confident.
Don't be intimidated.
You're the star of the night, Yoon Hee.
She has such amazing taste.
Try it on, Mum.
It's stunning.
Come on. Put it on.
It's so exquisite that
I don't know if I can actually wear it.
The colour and design are amazing.
Why did she send so many things?
Mum, try this on.
Does it look nice? - You look radiant.
You look like Hera,
the deity of prosperity and honour.
Gosh, stop it.
This is really nice.
I need to talk to you.
Meet me in the community room at 6?
Ro Na.
Ta-da.
"Bae Ro Na: Okay, see you later"
Mission cleared!
On a night like this,
one drink isn't enough. - That's right.
My gosh.
I have to say, Chairman Joo and his wife
put a lot of work into organising this.
They hired hotel chefs,
and all the dishes are very special.
Is Logan Lee that important?
He can't be more important than you.
Sang A, please.
Are you serious?
Don't you know who Logan Lee is?
His father is James Lee,
the most successful Korean American ever.
I must say, you really don't know much
for someone who's highly educated.
This is why I tell you
to read the newspapers.
Honey, wouldn't it be so nice
if you could help me build connections
on an occasion like this?
You know? - That is why
I'm all dressed up like this.
Not everyone can do that.
You need to be on Chairman Joo's level
to connect with a hotshot like him.
There's obviously a reason
why they live in the penthouse.
There she is, the penthouse lady.
Gosh, look who's here! - Soo Ryeon.
That dress looks new.
You look stunning.
And that scarf goes very well
with the dress.
My husband got them for me.
It's a special day, you know.
Of course.
Chairman Joo has such exquisite taste.
Gosh, I wish my husband were here today.
Where's Chairman Joo?
He went to greet Logan Lee.
He'll be here shortly.
I should wait outside.
First impressions are important.
Yes, of course.
Oh, my.
My gosh, Ms Cheon. - Ms Cheon.
Gosh.
That scarf...
You two are wearing the same scarf.
What? Soo Ryeon said she got hers
from Chairman Joo.
I doubt Dr Ha bought that for Ms Cheon.
Ms Cheon, did you pick it yourself?
Why did you have to buy that one?
Stop it.
We somehow showed up with the same scarf.
I don't like to wear what others have.
Is that so?
I thought it was the opposite.
I thought you were cool with it,
using and wearing what others have.
It doesn't bother me, so keep it on.
I'm sure you took the time
to pick out the scarf.
I need to use the ladies' room.
Did you see how flustered she was?
She suddenly fled to the ladies' room.
Did she pick the same one on purpose?
She always acts all proud and confident,
but she's actually a copycat.
Seo Jin.
You always got what you wanted.
The same goes for Joo Dan Tae.
Sim Soo Ryeon.
Do you think the penthouse
will be yours forever?
Welcome!
It's very nice to meet you.
Welcome.
This is my wife.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Logan Lee.
It's an honour to meet you.
I'm Sim Soo Ryeon.
Thanks for coming tonight.
You guys look like a lovely couple.
I'm jealous, Mr Joo.
If I knew this was going to be
the kind of scene,
I would've brought a partner myself.
My goodness. Sang A, he's so funny.
We can't have our important guest
feeling lonely,
which is why I invited someone for you.
Come on in.
What? How...
Chairman Joo.
Did you invite Ms Oh?
Yes.
I invited her.
I can't believe you invited her
without our permission.
This is very unlike you, Chairman Joo.
She's not here as a member of Hera Club.
She's here because she's now
an employee of JKING Holdings.
I'm now a member of his investment team.
Thank you for inviting me
to such a wonderful party.
I've never been to a party like this.
This is so amazing.
Hi, Logan.
You're looking great today.
The suit looks nice on you.
Thank you. You look splendid yourself.
Thanks.
What are they talking about?
What is going on?
Am I the only one who doesn't understand?
Ms Oh, when did you start working
for Chairman Joo's company?
Congratulations, Yoon Hee.
My husband told me you're very competent.
I heard you arranged
the meeting with Logan for him?
What?
She did?
But why? How?
Are you and Logan close?
Well, the night is still young.
I'll tell you all about it later.
I'm starving because I'm surrounded by
all the scrumptious foods.
Can we eat and talk?
Sure, sounds good.
This way, please.
After we eat,
there will be a lighting ceremony
at the fountain.
Mr Lee wanted to see it.
Yes, I hear it's the signature
of Hera Palace.
My, look at you all dressed up for a date.
What are you guys doing here?
Where's Seok Hoon?
Did you come running
because Seok Hoon wanted to meet up?
Unbelievable.
I have nothing to say to you guys.
You seem to have a habit of running away.
Shall I call Seok Hoon for you?
You'll regret it.
He can be very scary.
Seok Kyung, why are you doing this to me?
Did you really think I was your friend
just because I was nice
to a lowlife like you?
Seok Hoon and I had a bet
over who'd do a better job of fooling you.
Don't tell me you actually thought
he had feelings for you.
My gosh.
What did you say?
Stop playing innocent.
You impersonated Min Seol A
and threatened us. We know everything!
What are you talking about?
I never impersonated anyone.
Have some shame. You give me the creeps.
Of course she'll play dumb.
Why bother asking?
Look at her putting on an act.
Let me get straight to the point.
We refuse to go to the same school as you,
so apologise for what you did
and drop out.
Then we'll just let it go.
Why should I do that?
I didn't do anything wrong!
What a crazy psychopath.
I bet you also stole Min Seol A's shoe.
I can't believe you're a Cheonga student.
You're a disgrace to our school.
Do you have nothing better to do?
Are you scared I go to the same school
because I might outdo you?
Is that why you're doing this?
Why would we be scared? You're a nobody!
Who do you think you are?
Don't get so worked up.
She'll spill the truth soon.
Where's Seok Kyung?
I saw her going out earlier.
The tutor will be here shortly.
You have a knack for surprising others.
How did you win Chairman Joo over?
He's very picky about who he hires.
Yoon Hee, you're really
full of surprises.
I heard you brought Logan Lee.
That's very impressive.
How did you do that? - Let's just say
my sincerity won him over.
Where did you learn English?
Your pronunciation is pretty good.
I studied a little.
If you'd like, I can put you in touch
with a good English tutor.
I understand everything.
I just can't speak it well.
You're hosting this party,
so don't drink too much.
All right.
Is Dr Ha not coming?
I invited him.
Obviously, he won't come.
Their marriage is falling apart...
Oh, boy.
I thought you two made up.
Didn't he send you
those flowers and the ring as well?
Go easy on him.
All married couples fight
and lie to each other sometimes.
It's normal.
Right, honey?
Well, I've never
lied to you about anything.
You know that I'm a lousy liar.
Excuse me.
Bravo!
What's going on?
You're really amazing, Soo Ryeon.
You know
how much I admire you, right?
You're always so elegant and kind.
You're the most amazing wife
who takes such great care of your husband
and a great mother.
Both of your kids get good grades,
and you're throwing this party because
they were picked as student ambassadors.
You have no idea how jealous I am.
They're not even your biological children.
How did you manage to raise them so well?
What? What do you mean?
They're not her biological kids?
Ms Cheon, are you drunk?
You didn't know?
My gosh.
I thought you all knew.
Gosh.
I'm sorry, Soo Ryeon.
But times have changed.
There's no need to keep it a secret.
I've always thought of them
as my own children.
I raised them like my own.
I'd appreciate it
if you could watch what you say.
Whatever it is,
it's not nice to be secretive
and hide things.
There's no need to hide it
if you're unashamed about it.
I'm not going to lie.
I could tell that
they weren't your real kids.
You were too bold in certain situations,
and a biological mother never would have
behaved that way.
Is that right?
As they say,
no parent is perfect.
I suppose I should try harder.
It's not something that comes with effort.
A mother's love for her children
is an instinct.
Are you enjoying the party?
The lighting ceremony will begin soon.
You should do it then.
Tell everyone that you are
Min Seol A's mother.
Say it loud and clear
so I can hear it.
If you don't do it,
I'll have no choice but to get involved.
What was that about?
Why bring that up on an evening like this?
You're one to talk.
You bought the same scarf for your wife
and kept smiling next to her
with those loving eyes.
Are you that happy? Having a blast?
If you love her that much,
why are you seeing me?
I didn't get her that scarf...
You know this party is important to me.
You didn't have to make
everyone uncomfortable like that.
Have you lost your mind?
I don't know.
You're suddenly acting like a stranger.
Tell me.
How much do you love me?
This is so unlike you.
You know how I feel. - No, I don't!
So prove it to me right now.
Do it now!
Don't drink any more.
You're already drunk.
I'll wait at the villa after the party.
There are a lot of eyes watching,
so you go in first.
Okay.
You jerk.
How could you do that here?
Do you have nothing but animal instincts?
You know, I never liked you.
Joo Dan Tae, you scumbag!
So you knew?
But I won't let you hit me after this.
This is enough, right?
What did you say? You jerk!
You insecure loser.
You don't deserve a woman like her.
If you have any conscience,
you should let her go.
You don't know how to love a woman.
What? You scumbag!
You darn jerk. I will kill you!
You piece of...
What are you doing? Break it up.
You jerk! - Gosh!
Get back here. - Hey.
You fools! Enough!
You little... - Hey!
Come here. - You punk.
Logan Lee!
Logan Lee is here!
What about the lighting ceremony?
Will you take responsibility
if the contract falls through?
Move. I'll kill that scumbag!
You piece of... - Stop it! Enough!
Goodness. - You jerk.
Break it up already!
That's why Seok Hoon and Seok Kyung
were always cold to her.
I always found it odd.
No wonder she never seemed interested
in their studies.
Now I understand why
those two kids always looked sad.
Right?
She was always busy
pointing out their faults.
Now it all makes sense.
Right?
Ms Cheon.
Oh, cheers.
Soo Ryeon.
Is that really true?
What Seo Jin said earlier.
I'm sorry
for not telling you.
Gosh, why are you sorry?
That crazy witch.
Who is she to expose
such personal matters? How dare she.
Joo Dan Tae must've told her.
They're both evil.
Must you give birth to be called a mother?
You raised them as your own all this time.
Soo Ryeon, don't take it to heart.
The whole world
knows that you've done your best.
I'm okay.
I really mean it.
It must've been so hard for you.
"Fake Min Seol A"
"Bae Ro Na"
"Drop out of school"
Where did Chairman Joo go?
His guest is waiting.
My husband isn't picking up either.
Did something happen?
I'm already being punished.
I'm not happy.
Honey!
What happened to your face? - Gosh.
It's nothing. - What happened?
What are you doing here?
You should've dressed up at least.
You're a mess.
Gosh. - My goodness.
I've changed my mind.
I don't want a divorce.
What?
I said, I don't want a divorce.
Until the day I die.
I don't care if you cheat on me.
Just be my miserable wife
for the rest of your life
and die miserably.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
I had to deal with something urgent.
Enjoy the party.
Dr Ha. - Dr Ha.
What was that about? - My gosh.
What on earth? - Gosh.
Goodness. - Oh, boy.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
No, it's fine.
I've set it up so that
you can begin the ceremony.
This way, please.
Okay.
Let's go.
Wow, it's an honour.
Shall I? - Please.
I also prepared
a special welcoming gift for you.
All right.
Shall we all count down together?
Okay!
Ten!
Nine, eight... - Nine, eight...
seven... - seven...
six, five... - six, five...
four... - four...
three... - three...
two... - two...
one. - one.
Zero!
"Min Seol A"
"The one who killed Min Seol A is here"
=Penthouse=
This is solid evidence that Sim Soo Ryeon
has been threatening us.
Because she's Sim Soo Ryeon's daughter.
I'll get a divorce.
Let's sign our divorce papers.
You didn't know that your mum
hit on my dad?
I want to drop out.
The one who killed Min Seol A...
This is Min Seol A's phone.
Let's avenge Seol A's death together.
What are you doing here?