[Jirisan]
[The places, people, organizations, accidents, and the background stories depicted in this drama are fictional]
For a very long time,
as many years as the mountain existed,
countless people have visited Jirisan.
(T/N: Jirisan means Mount Jiri)
[The first Pia Valley Autumn Leaves Festival]
[Protect Nature | Love the Country]
For some people, this mountain has been a land of hope that holds the spirits of their loved ones.
But to others, it's been a spiteful land of death and deepest sorrow.
Still, many people, bring their own stories to climb this mountain,
but not everyone goes back with hope in their hearts.
This place is still the border.
The border between exploding hope and severe devastation.
Between life and death, where a beginning and the smell of blood coexist.
Jirisan... is the land between this world and the next.
[2018]
[Jirisan National Park Interpretation Office]
[Jirisan National Park Haedong Ranger Station]
Search Team 1, moving to the falling rock zone.
Volunteer Team 1, arriving at the trail entrance.
Are you new?
Yes, Sir. Hello.
- I just got dispatched to the Haedo—
- Jung Goo Yeong!
Yes?
Follow him.
To where…?
The mountain. It's a missing case.
Yes, Sir!
Why? Are you going to wear those?
Let's go, hurry up!
Hurry, get on. Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry.
Ranger station to all rangers.
Name of the lost hiker, Yeom Seung Hoon. Age 14.
Time of climb, 11:45 a.m. yesterday.
[Time of accident: 8.23.2018 5:25 p.m.]
[Time of climb 8.23.2018 11:45 a.m.]
He used the Haedong Ranger Station trail.
[Lives without parents, left behind a note "I'm sorry, Grandma," Signs of possible suicide]
Top, white shirt. Bottom, grey pants.
Bokseon Middle School uniform with white sneakers. And a sky blue backpack.
The last place he used his cellphone was the Samheungbong Peak communication tower.
It matches the statement of the witness who saw him last.
The first search area was 3 km within that communication tower.
Haedong Ranger Station,
Bidam Shelter,
and Jangteomok Shelter rangers makes up Search Team 1.
[Jangteomok Shelter]
Seseok Shelter,
Wusong Shelter,
Moojin Ranger Station rangers searched as Search Team 2,
but failed to track the hiker.
We'll expand to 10 km and begin the second search.
Civilian Volunteer fire department takes section A, the unrestricted trail.
[Access allowed as per environment protection and parks regulations - System in place to monitor safety]
911's Mountain Rescue Team takes area B.
Restricted Trail sections C and D for park ranger teams 1 and 2,
[Restricted trail to protect the environment and wild animals - Potential danger - limited cell phone coverage]
and the support team.
Considering the fact that the hiker had no gear on,
the golden time is only 30 hours.
It's been 23 hours and we have 7 hours left. We have to find him within that time.
- How's the climate?
- The typhoon's moving north faster than expected.
Falling rocks! Watch out!
Step back, it's dangerous.
Hey!
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Bring a stretcher, get an ambulance ready.
Min Seok. Min Seok!
- Is he all right?
- I think so.
- Are you okay?
- Take all his clothes off.
Yeah, okay.
Search Team 1, a ranger has been injured due to falling rocks...
We need to take him to the hospital first. Possible bleeding...
Excuse...
Are you all right?
Search Team 1, heading to Yangseok Peak now...
And you are…?
Kang Hyun Jo. I just got posted here.
We sent Min Seok to the hospital.
Take the newbie instead.
Oh, by the way…
Demon Seo is her nickname.
Be careful so she doesn't bite you.
Pardon?
Search is done in pairs. You know that, right?
Fix your shoelaces and stay close.
If you lag behind, I'll abandon you.
Yes!
Volunteer Team 1.
Searching the 7 km area on the trail.
No missing hiker found.
[Soomgol Rock]
[Knife Rock]
Rescue Team 1, at Knife Rock, we haven't found the hiker.
Typhoon Bitak is heading north at a much faster speed than anticipated.
It was formed in the sea southeast of Okinawa,
and is heading north at 15 km per hour.
It will pass Jeju and Namhae around 10:00 p.m. tonight.
We're expecting up to 300 ml of rain in the Jeju and Jirisan areas.
Please protect your facilities from the strong wind.
Seung Hoon!
He's not here.
Ghost Rock. Yangseokbong Peak. The hiker can't be seen.
We'll move to Seonghwang Tree.
Seung Hoon!
Where's Seonghwang Tree?
It's a place where many people die.
So all the places we've searched so far are suicide points?
Yes. Once it happens, it happens again and again at the same places.
Does that mean… we've been looking for a dead kid?
Don't say such an unlucky thing.
Who said we are looking for a dead kid?
We're trying to find him to stop him from dying.
Wait for me!
Search Team 1. Weather's getting worse.
We'll join at Doongji Tree and search together.
Search Team 2. At Dosang Falls now.
We'll join the search, too.
Typhoon Bitak is accompanying strong wind of over 50 meters per second in speed.
It will reach the peninsula at around 10:00 p.m. tonight.
There is a storm warning on Jeju and in Jeonnam Province.
Have you not found him yet?
- I'm afraid not.
- We pulled out the dogs and rescuers.
The dogs' sense of scent doesn't work well in the rain.
Yes, I understand.
The missing hiker's family is here.
Search Team 4. Search Team 4.
He's the commander in charge of the search.
I'm sorry… because of my grandson.
- I'm really sorry.
- Not at all, Ma'am.
You must have traveled far. Please take a rest.
We'll let you know right away if we hear anything.
Gyung Seon, please escort her to the night duty room for rest.
- This way, please.
- Please get some rest.
Search Team 4. The weather's turned very bad.
What should we do?
Search Team 2, taking a detour. The water level's too high.
Volunteer Team 1, pausing the search and evacuating to a shelter.
The current is too strong!
Grab him! Get in!
One, two! One, two!
Search Team 3, man down!
Yours, too.
- Excuse me?
- We can pick them up later, so throw yours out too.
Why are you doing this?
This is a lightning-prone area.
There must be a good reason we're passing here in this weather.
This is the shortcut.
We can save an hour.
We must join them for the search before things get worse.
Never go near a big tree, it'll work as a lightning rod.
Grab something else even if you slip.
If there's nothing to grab, just roll down.
That'll be faster.
All of this...
Senior! Wait!
Are you okay?
Senior, over there.
Look. Look over there.
Search Team 5, Under Bidam Cliff.
We found a backpack that looks like that of the hiker's.
Are you sure?
It's a sky blue backpack.
[Yeom Seung Hoon | Bokseon Middle School, Grade 1, Home Room 5 | 7ª Grade in the USA]
It's his backpack for sure.
What about the hiker?
Did he fall with his backpack?
No, we don't see the hiker.
No signs of a crash either.
It looks like only his backpack fell.
Senior,
isn't this Jirisan?
Sir, there's a photo of a wildflower habitat above Bidam Cliff.
I think that was the hiker's destination.
We must search there.
It takes at least three hours to get there, even on sunny days.
It'll take twice as long... on a day like this.
We'll go. Please give us permission to search.
Retreat.
Who is it?
Chief.
The 30-hour golden time is almost up.
The missing hiker's not even wearing proper gear.
If he's alive, we must go now.
He might already be dead.
He came to the mountain to kill himself.
[Possible suicide attempt, Bullied at school]
Are you giving up your life for a dead body?
If something happens to you, other rangers must come to help.
Will you take responsibility for their lives?
The wind speed's over 20 m/s.
There's no time.
Retreat this second!
This is an order.
Withdraw all teams.
Are we really going back?
You said we must look now if he's alive.
Let's go back.
Senior.
Hey, newbie! Are you okay?
Demon Seo is indeed ruthless.
Our Demon Seo.
How could she drag you to a lightning zone in the storm?
Where's Seung Hoon?
Look after yourself first. Your body comes first.
Dude, how can a ranger say something like that?
To a newbie at that.
A ranger must protect the mountain even if his body is torn to pieces, understand?
I'll say this as a team leader.
You must be vigilant.
I'm so sick of this. Sick of it.
I'm sick of you.
Yes, Sir, Team Leader. I get it.
- If you're not alert, you'll get hurt.
- Ouch.
My head hurts and it hurts to sit.
[Missing time: 23 hours]
What the chief said is right.
We'll resume in the morning after the storm's passed.
Get some rest until then.
What do we tell his family?
We have to tell the truth.
Yes, this is Jirisan National Park.
So, we made a bet among friends.
How high is Cheonwangbong Peak?
It's 1,915 m.
Including the stone monument?
Then it's 1,916.35 m.
I'm hanging up now.
Get some rest.
Shouldn't you get some herbal medicine even if it tastes terrible?
How can a ranger collapse so easily?
He's not dead.
How do you know?
He's alive for sure.
We can't keep searching based on your guess.
[Family Communication Report]
[Impressive Education Filled with Happiness]
[Classroom and Education Information for Parents]
[Lives with grandma without parents]
[Left a final note, "I'm sorry, Grandma."]
[Signs of suicide, a missing report filed]
[Bullied at school...]
[Elementary School Level X]
[Not even Elementary School Level]
Please help me.
Senior.
I didn't know what to tell her.
We had to stop the search.
But we'll resume when the storm dies down, so…
I'm sorry… I'm sorry.
[Wind Speed: 32.6]
[[Wind direction: SouthWest]
[Precipitation level: 35.0 mm]
Senior! Are you okay?
Are you insane? Did you follow me?
Where do you think this is?
If I'm insane, so are you.
At least I won't be lonely, being in a crazy pair.
I thought… I'd regret it if I didn't come.
Isn't that why you're here, too?
Let's say he really is alive.
He'll die if we don't rescue him now.
Seeing as I am here already, please take me with you.
You said a search is done in pairs.
If you whine along the way, I'll kill you.
It's not like you'll notice if I whine.
It's much more dangerous than you can imagine.
Isn't our job always dangerous?
Our job is to come back safely from a dangerous place.
We must be a pillar to each other.
If you get blown away, so do I.
If I fall, so do you.
So let's both be careful.
Copy!
♫ Destiny, it’s all meant to be ♫
♫ I will never let you go, never let you fall ♫
♫ Spend your life? ♫
Hey!
What the hell are you doing, bastards?
Didn't you hear what the chief said?
I'm sorry, Sir. I tried my best to stop them…
But the wind's slowing down.
Soon the sun will rise, too.
Please let us go up.
The search will start after the storm passes entirely.
Unpack your gear.
Seo Yi Kang is missing.
So is the newbie.
Their gear's gone, too.
Damn fools, honestly.
Excuse me...
She has something to tell you.
Seo Yi Kang.
Yi Kang, where are you?
Answer me, Seo Yi Kang!
Search Team 5, Seo Yi Kang.
Where are you?
I'm sorry, but…
Have you arrived there?
The wildflower habitat above Bidam Cliff.
Yes, Sir.
Seung Hoon...
[Message (1/10)]
[I'm sorry for making you worry, Grandma.]
[8/25 4:01 a.m., your grandson.]
...sent a message.
That message we saw wasn't the last one he sent.
Do you remember this place?
We've been here with Mom and Dad.
It's so nice being here.
Let's come back together.
[There are flowers you like here.]
[It's time for you to take your medication. Please do not skip taking them.]
[I love you, Grandma.]
[I'm sorry, Grandma.]
I'm sorry for making you worry.
He's... still alive.
He went from a cellular dead zone to a signal zone on his own.
We're calling him repeatedly, but he's not answering.
I think his battery ran out.
The support team's on their way,
but it'll take them three and a half hours minimum.
You're our only hope now.
You guys have to find him.
Let's split up.
Look for the signal zones on GPS.
We'll only search those areas.
We'll look for survival points, not suicide points.
Yes!
Reception area on the way from the habitat to Bidam Cliff.
He'll be there. Hurry!
Golden time's up.
Even if he's alive,
he'll be critically ill.
Those that want to live instinctively look for these places.
Between big rocks.
Inside a big stump.
A tunnel of tightly-woven bushes.
Under a big rock carved like a cave.
Where you can hide from the rainstorm and keep your body warm.
That kid, came to the mountain to live.
He would surely have found a place like that.
Any progress?
I haven't found him yet.
He's nowhere to be seen.
I've looked in all the places you mentioned.
But he wasn't there.
He's still alive.
He must be here somewhere.
But where?
Those that want to live instinctively look for these places.
Where you can keep warm.
Between big rocks.
Senior, where are you?
What is it?
Have you seen a weird mark made with twigs and rocks?
No.
Something shaped square. Have you seen it?
I've never seen anything like that.
Why do you ask? Just look for the hiker.
What about a black rock then?
What the heck?
There must be an oak tree nearby.
There were oak tree leaves scattered around.
What on earth…?
Do you mean Sangsuri Rock?
Is there such a place? Is it near here?
But that's outside the reception area.
He's there.
He's probably there.
Don't you get it?
If he's there, he couldn't have sent the text.
But we've looked everywhere else.
So, please,
let's make it our final place to look.
Senior, over here!
Senior!
We found him!
The hiker found under Sangsuri Rock at Bidam Cliff!
His state of health?
Seo Yi Kang!
He's unconscious.
His body feels very cold.
His pulse and breathing?
Seung Hoon! Yeom Seung Hoon!
Seung Hoon, open your eyes! Wake-up.
Hey! Stop right there!
You all right?
I'll just carry him on my back.
Put him on my back.
Be careful.
Come down carefully.
Take your time!
Are you okay?
- Over here!
- There they are.
Check his vitals.
Pulse and breathing, normal.
Great!
Take the lady with you to the hospital.
Yes, Sir.
Take care of her.
See you in a bit.
We're at the bottom.
His pulse is normal, on the way to the hospital.
Come down safely.
Great work.
Thank you.
Where is Yi Kang?
She's probably passed out.
Well done, Yi Kang.
Why aren't you responding?
Hey, Yi Kang! Can you hear me?
Hey, Yi Kang!
Did she just turn it off?
♫ Our memories hold on to times of the past ♫
♫ Something's gonna bring it to the air tonight.
Can't imagine my life without you ♫
♫ And when the world needs something, about to feel this way ♫
♫ When we were young, everything we did ♫
♫ When we were young, and wild and free ♫
♫ Tell me the truth, walk across to life ♫
♫ There's going to be everything I need ♫
Will you not spring yourself up here?
Aren't you going to train?
In… just a sec… Let's rest a bit.
Are you here to play?
How can you save anyone at that pace?
If there is one thing that Jirisan is, is that it's big.
Stranded hikers will be dead while you rest like that.
I think… I'm really dying.
You got your patrol area assigned, right?
Have you been there?
No, not yet…
Our main task is to guard this mountain.
You must have all the place names, tree species, and distribution of vegetation memorized by heart.
Demon Seo…
Do you have a death wish?
No, Senior.
Even if I die…
Can I have a sip of water?
Yes. At Sohn Rock.
Okay. Coming.
Is this Sohn Rock?
Sohn, as in hand?
They're making it harder to go down.
Why would they have a date at such a tough place, not a pub?
That's so annoying.
Should I… hold your hand?
Shut up and follow me.
Wait… Slow down…
How did you find this place?
It wasn't me.
He did.
Newbie.
Yes?
How did you know about this place?
Well, umm…
Let's say… the mountain told me.
The mountain?
That's believable.
People have been serving Jirisan from before the Three Kingdoms.
(Refers to the three kingdoms of Goguryeo, Baekje, and Silla)
Being an object of faith for such a long time,
can't just be a superstition.
There's energy in this mountain that's difficult to explain.
That's what I mean.
This time, for instance,
there's no reception here, but a text message was sent.
- The mountain saved the kid.
- Ah.
Stop the nonsense.
So what? What is it, anyway?
Oh, that.
This is...
how the red commies communicated with each other.
When they fell behind from their team or was out of contact,
they made a secret code like this to communicate.
That's still there?
They pick a spot that no one else will discover.
A place that won't be…
destroyed in the wind and rain.
Like this place.
What do those twigs signify?
It was to notify their location,
or so we assume.
I must go somewhere now.
Thank you for calling me.
See you later.
Wait a moment.
Here.
I'm Kim Sol, a cultural resources foundation researcher.
If you happen to find another historical place like this, please call me!
All right.
This must be quite valuable.
This here,
could be useful when we can't use radio or cellphones on the restricted trails.
It's perfect for signaling a lost hiker's location.
Look here, Senior.
Pretend these rocks are Bidam Cliff.
Here…
Stick a twig in it.
See? It's right where Sangsuri Rock is.
Now tell me the truth.
How did you find this place?
I saw this place.
It's not my first time.
I keep seeing…
where missing hikers are on this mountain.
You really are crazy.
Are we really going on patrol?
Wait for me!
I'm coming!
[2020]
[Report on the Search and Rescue of Missing Persons]
The official search report of the Yiseokjae incident is over as of today.
Return to your ranger station or shelter,
and focus on your tasks.
Then…
If we end like this, what about the lost hiker?
If that many people searched for over a month and couldn't find him,
it's hopeless.
The autumn leaves season starts next week.
There will be a lot more tourists.
Check the safety facilities and do a good base duty.
Yes, Sir.
But when are we getting a new member?
We've had a vacancy for a while.
Someone's coming.
Really? Who?
I hope it's someone experienced, not a newbie like her.
It's someone you know.
Who is it?
Seo Yi Kang?
Yes.
The Seo Yi Kang that I know?
No way.
She hasn't quit yet?
She asked to be reinstated.
Even so, not her.
Who is she? Why is this a big deal?
Long time no see.
Yes, it's been a long while.
How have you been?
You…
Why are you back?
What do you mean by "why"?
She's Ranger Seo Yi Kang, who knows this mountain best.
- You know what I mean.
- Shouldn't you be on patrol?
Grab your gear and follow me.
Okay…
[Report on the Search of Missing Persons at the Jirisan National Park]
Coffee.
Is it a missing case?
Yes.
Yiseokjae, that's near Yiseok Falls, right?
Where did this person go missing?
There's no witness.
Why are you back?
Have you looked near Gaeam Falls?
That's in the opposite direction to Yiseok valley.
You know that well.
I think we should search there.
Did you get a tip-off?
Please.
Pass me the card.
Just a sec.
Senior.
Well…
What happened to that senior?
What do you think happened on a mountain?
They were stranded.
Stranded?
Why did they have to go up there in heavy snow?
We almost died rescuing them.
But.
Did you say "them"?
You mean…
Someone else went missing, too?
Why?
Control room speaking.
Yes, Sir.
I don't understand.
I really don't.
Why did he want us to come here?
Be careful, it's slippery.
Okay.
What is this place?
Gaeam Falls.
It's famous for its scenery even though it's in a restricted area.
There's not even a single ant here, what does he want to find here?
Senior.
What's that?
Illegal hikers.
We tell them not to come, but they still do.
They keep trashing the place, that's why we won't let them in here.
Why?
[Yang Geun Tak]
[Hiker: Yang Geun Tak]
It's him.
The missing hiker… we've been looking for.
How did you know?
Hundreds of people looked for over a month in vain.
But you…
You just got here. So how did you know?
I want to know, too.
How did you know…
the missing hiker was there?
[Always being with the mountain]
This is the Jirisan volunteer fire department website.
Did you figure it out from this?
This is a picture of a joint search with the rangers
during this Yiseokjae accident.
And?
Isn't that the mark you discovered
at Sangsuri Rock?
This one's different.
Only Hyun Jo and I knew this signal.
We decided to use this
to signal where a lost hiker is when there's no reception.
So this signal...
pointed to Gaeam Falls?
[Moojin area missing person search in progress]
This was three months ago during the Moojin area accident.
I also found the mark there in the photo.
It was pointing to Seonghwang Tree.
You found the missing person's body there, right?
Yes.
This was six months ago during the Jeonmukgol accident.
And this one was the Oerae Valley accident.
Here too…
It pointed exactly to a missing hiker.
That's impossible.
Maybe it was a prank?
It was exactly at the place Hyun Jo and I decided on.
Someone is sending me a signal.
If it's between you and that Hyun Jo guy…
It must be him.
No.
Hyun Jo…
can't come to this mountain anymore.
[Kang Hyun Jo]
[Saegum Central Hospital]
Someone…
is sending me a signal…
from up there in the mountain.
I wanted to know who that person is.
That's why I returned.
♫ Bleed it out ’til someone’s sacrifice ♫
♫ Like faith without a fear ♫
♫ Feel like I’m grounded ♫
♫ Last thing I wanted ♫
♫ Hold me like you used to do ♫
♫ Be brave, time to face ♫
♫ Last thing I want is to stop and stare ♫
♫ Destiny, it’s all meant to be ♫
[Jirisan]
~ Preview ~
So why did you go there that day?
I'm here because there's something I need to find.
- What is it?
- A dead body.
- Go to the headquarters.
- I'll let you know first if I find anything.
I saw the mark...
But this was the only way.
Who is this person?
Why are you asking about the ribbons?
Moojin Valley, pine tree habitat!
Park ranger down! It's Kang Hyun Jo.