[Jirisan]
[The places, people, organizations, accidents, and the background stories depicted in this drama are fictional]
Lee Da Won!
- Lee Da Won.
- Da Won!
Lee Da Won's cell phone signal was last detected
from the repeater in Seongnae Stream, Jeonmuk Valley.
She's new but still a ranger.
She would have left some kind of a sign.
There's a dead tree southeast of Hurricane Lily Habitat in Jeonmuk Valley.
We must check under that tree.
That signal only you and Hyun Jo know?
What's that?
It's near the pebbly road at Haebawi Rock.
How did it go? Did you find her?
We found a pink-colored cell phone.
It's covered in blood.
But... what about Captain Jo Dae Jin?
So this was recorded on Da Won's phone?
Then, let's go down together.
No. I'll go by myself.
Haedong Two! Found the missing at the Amleung Ridge!
How's Da Won? Is she all right?
The missing... has no pulse and is not breathing.
Presumed dead.
We have a couple of things to ask you.
The deceased... was holding this in her hand.
Did you do that to Da Won?
Why did you do it?
And Hyun Jo, too?
Did you do that to Hyun Jo?
Why did you do that? Why?
Tell Seo Yi Kang at Haedong Ranger Station
that I didn't leave the mark this time.
He said he didn't leave the mark this time?
When you and Hyun Jo had that accident,
why did you go to Black Bridge Valley?
What happened to you and Hyun Jo?
What were you doing with Da Won?
Why do you suspect the captain?
Why did you return to the mountain?
I can't understand any of it.
Maybe you shouldn't have come back.
When do you think... we can quit this work?
It's not something you can quit when you want to.
It involves saving people's lives.
Saving people's lives is our job.
But I'm seeing more dead people than live ones.
Do you remember him?
[Chairperson Yang Geun Tak]
He's come back to the mountain.
The mountain spirit will be infuriated once again.
The mountain spirit is not the only one up there.
Grandma told me a long time ago,
that the evil spirit comes before the mountain spirit.
Black Bridge Valley Village.
Have you forgotten all that's happened there?
Never forget, especially the Black Bridge Valley area.
Don't ever go there.
Black Bridge Valley.
[1991]
Over there is Black Bridge Valley Village.
Oh, I see.
This place is a perfect location for cable cars.
We'd appreciate some help from the national park to get consent from the villagers.
It'll be good for the mountain and the residents.
The national park regulations require that we stay neutral.
Our job is to show the roads.
Yeah, okay...
How have you been?
We brought you a guest.
Please say hello. This is the mayor of Black Bridge Valley Village.
Hello.
I'm Yang Geun Tak, the president of the Jirisan Development Committee.
My name is Kim Jae Gyeong.
Ah, yes.
- Leave!
- Jae Gyeong, stop!
- Get out of here!
- Please stop!
We have no intention of moving out. Leave.
Mr. Kim.
I told you we'll give you
as much relocation compensation as possible.
This uppity— Seriously.
Do you think this is about greed for money?
This place is our home and where we stem from.
We have no further business. Please leave.
You'll all...
absolutely regret this.
Oh, dear.
What happened?
Oh, my.
Anyway,
- Can't even take a shower.
- Excuse me, passing through.
What happened?
Look in there.
Who could have done such a thing?
It's him! The cable car man.
He messed with the well to kick us out from here!
That's right. That's right.
- It was him.
- Yes, it must be him.
Has anyone seen him putting that in there?
We've not seen him do it.
We can't report him to the police when we're not even sure.
Are you saying we should do nothing?
This might not be the end. He could do something else to us.
Don't worry too much.
We'll do more patrols.
And think of ways to enhance village security.
We'll protect you with all our might!
Please do not worry.
[Jo Dae Jin]
People started dying.
Three people died from this small village.
Can this be just a coincidence?
Did you guys hear that just now?
Is this the Black Bridge Valley Village?
Yes, sir. It's supposed to be in the Deokseoryeong area.
But it doesn't show on the map.
Shouldn't we go look?
Has there been any missing report?
No.
Then don't worry about it.
We've had a lot of people asking for time off lately.
Even if we are short-staffed, please plan thoroughly
and resolve the mountain spirit ritual without an issue.
But, Sir.
That's enough.
He could've staged this for more views.
But it could be real.
Looks like his cell phone was working well enough to post the video.
If he were in real danger, he would've called for help.
He dropped his phone and the video ended.
Maybe the phone broke, so he couldn't call.
You spent two hours carrying that jerk down.
It will be exactly like that.
You go up there for this, there's a 98% chance it's nothing.
Something about it bothers you too, to take the 2% off.
[On patrol to Black Bridge Valley, Deokseoryeong, with Hyun Jo.]
[You guys take care of the promotion booth for the ritual]
[On patrol to Black Bridge Valley, Deokseoryeong, with Hyun Jo. You guys take care of the promotion booth for the ritual.]
I don't care.
Some slack off all day long and then others work too much.
Something's off with the satellite phone battery.
Ah, that Jung Goo Yeong, I told him to check the devices carefully.
I'll do it when we get back.
Never mind that. Just take this.
What's this?
Ghosts are supposed to come from the north today.
I was warned not to go near Black Bridge Valley today.
I guess you don't actually hate me.
Since you care about me like this.
Are you trying to climb over me?
I'm a ranger. Must be good at climbing in general.
Let's go.
Hey!
Wrong way.
There's not a single soul here.
Should we go back?
- Wrestling will start soon.
- Wrestling, my butt.
Keep searching carefully. You never know when accidents happen.
- Oh? Hey, what's that?
- Woah!
- Stop the car.
Mister! Mister!
Mister, are you okay?
Call for 119, hurry.
Mister!
- Whoa!
- Go away!
Get off me!
Calm down. We're the police.
Ghost... Ghost lights.
I saw ghost lights.
Ghost lights!
Ghost...
Up there.
Ghost lights.
Oh... Okay, sir.
Granny...
Hey, what are you doing?
Didn't you go to work today?
- Neither did you?
- I only do it once in a while.
How could you be off all the time?
What do you mean all the time?
Oh, hey.
- Mr. Park.
- Hello.
- Did you eat?
- Not yet.
One second. I'll make it quick.
Take your time.
Breaking up is...
What are you doing?
Don't.
What are you guys up to?
A day off?
- Yes, it is!
- What's wrong with that?
- Don't you get days off?
- I take every day off.
He takes days off all the time but me, only rarely.
Why are you all coming for me? Take as much as you want. Okay, okay.
You guys.
Anyway, have you watched that video yesterday?
The guy who posted that Black Bridge Valley video?
We found him by the road and took him to the hospital earlier, but he was totally out of his mind.
Didn't Yi Kang and Hyun Jo go there earlier?
Yes... Black Bridge Village in Deokseoryeong.
What are you saying?
Yi Kang went to where?
To Black Bridge Valley Village?
Yes.
What?
Black Bridge Valley Village in the north.
She can't go north today.
It's the day ghosts come from the north.
Whoa. Now, this is something.
When did the village get demolished?
I heard in 1991.
- Is this your first time here, too?
- I never had a reason to come.
There's nothing to see here, plus it's dangerous, so people rarely come here.
Hello?
Anyone there?
We're from the national park.
Anyone?
See?
I said there's a 98% chance it's nothing.
If he got stranded, it must be around here.
Check the bushes, he probably went into it.
Let's check that side.
[Kim Jae Gyeong]
Hello?
Anyone there?
We're from the national park.
Nobody?
What's wrong?
Huh?
What is this?
We're back to where we started.
I think we're lost.
Turn your GPS on.
[Error]
It's not working.
What's that?
Senior,
do you see that?
What can that be?
The smell...
It's dangerous. Run!
[Goo Yeong]
Hello?
Yi Kang and Hyun Jo? They're not back yet.
Yeah.
All right. I'll try to radio them.
What was that?
Yi Kang and Hyun Jo went to Black Bridge Valley,
but they're not back yet.
These punks!
I told them not to go there, how many times?
But, Captain.
The one who posted the video from Black Bridge Valley was found by the roadway.
And he's been saying something strange.
That he saw ghost lights there.
Haedong Ranger Station, Control Room.
No, we need to go.
Seo Yi Kang, where are you?
Maybe their radio broke.
Or maybe they're on their way down.
This way.
[Seo Yi Kang]
Call me if they don't return by 6.00. And keep trying to reach them.
They'll be all right.
It's Senior Yi Kang.
Black Bridge Valley is different.
You've heard a saying, "mountains make people hallucinate." Right?
Black Bridge Valley is that kind of place.
[1991]
So, when can we start using the well?
Not for a while.
We can't drink rotten water.
I'm sick of traveling like this to get water.
It won't kill you.
- See you later.
- Okay, see you.
- Be careful. It's slippery.
- Okay.
Someone's been missing?
For how long?
Since yesterday, when she went up to get water from the stream.
There were buckets and bloodstains near the stream,
so I thoroughly looked around.
But she's nowhere to be seen.
It's all because of him.
If he hadn't ruined the well,
my wife wouldn't have gone to get water.
We'll find her.
I promise.
So give us some time. And please don't worry.
Mrs. Kim Seong Sook.
- Mrs. Kim Seong Sook!
Mrs. Kim Seong Sook!
Even park rangers often get lost near Black Bridge Village.
Sometimes seemingly safe paths lead to cliffs,
and trails disappear suddenly.
The mountain is making us hallucinate.
We must stay alert.
Check around those trees, too.
Mrs. Kim Seong Sook!
Her pulse is very weak!
Was she found here?
She had fallen next to that tree.
It's all because of me.
I heard she could have survived if we had been a little quicker.
I passed by that tree several times.
Had I found her a little earlier...
Let's go in.
We should see her off.
[2019]
So what are those?
People say they see ghost lights
on dark and foggy nights like this on the mountain.
Is that really a ghost light?
Of course not.
Don't you remember this smell?
What's this smell?
Dog odor combined with ammonia.
It's a bear.
Bear? That's...?
I heard wild animals' eyes look like that, reflected in the light.
That's impossible. I heard Asian black bears hate people.
Also, they aren't aggressive, as long as we don't attack them first.
I've never seen anything like this before.
Even if they aren't aggressive, bears are the wildest of wild beasts.
They're over two meters tall and weigh over 100kg.
I don't know why they're so provoked, but I'm sure it's more dangerous than a ghost light.
- Pass me your walkie.
- Yes.
The battery's dead.
This is a "no signal" area.
We're trapped.
[1991]
Mayor!
Cable cars or whatever...
I can't leave this place now.
We're not here because of the cable cars.
Most of the villagers have left.
The park decided to demolish the village, too.
- Why don't you move to...
- I'm not leaving!
How have you been? Did you eat?
Dad keeps saying he sees things.
What do you mean?
He says he sees ghost lights.
There's no such thing. He saw wrong.
No! There is. I saw them, too.
Let's call it a day.
Yes, sir.
- This way.
[2019]
Why are you trying to meet him at this point?
Are you charging him a fine?
- How's his condition?
- They say he's much better.
That's the one.
Hello?
So, on my way from Deokseoryeong to Black Bridge Valley,
- there was some woman.
- Excuse me?
Anyway, I've made the call.
What did you say?
About what?
Someone was at Deokseoryeong?
No, well... It was her fault.
Why did she go up there when she clearly was not in good shape?
Don't tell me you left a lost person there and came down on your own.
Could you let the rangers know that I'm here?
Jeez, lady.
Do you want me to take myself in for illegal hiking?
I'll make a report on my way down, once I'm done with my business.
Where was it?
Well, I... I was busy, too.
Where the hell was it?
When will they leave?
How would I know?
I'm sorry.
But... I didn't expect a place like this in the mountains.
It must have been a secret hideout for the red commies.
What? There's a pole.
It must be one left behind by the illegal hikers.
More like crampons. Pretty serious.
- Whoa!
- What was that?
- Senior...
- What's up with you?
There's someone here.
Her breathing is too weak. She has serious hypothermia.
We must hurry up and get her to a hospital.
Will you be okay?
Do I have a choice? We must go.
There's been a missing report.
Please gather at the restricted trail entrance in Deokseoryeong.
I called each shelter and the rangers on their day off.
Any news from Yi Kang and Hyun Jo?
No.
But... those two aren't the only ones at Black Bridge Valley.
Senior, we're back again.
You all right?
What's that?
Ah, honestly.
What happened? We couldn't reach you.
Who's that?
- And what's that?
- Get her on your back.
Quickly!
What is that?
- Get on.
- Hurry up!
What the heck? What is that?
Hurry up! Hurry!
In here.
Watch your step.
On two.
What happened?
- She's in a bad state.
- I know.
That's why we were trying so hard to get down, but couldn't find the way out.
Same for us, too.
We kept going around in one direction in the foggy area.
We could only come because of your flashlights.
- What's that thing?
- Bears.
- What?
Nonsense.
What are you saying? Are we trapped?
Hang on. There must be a way.
A way? What way?
You can't get out because you can't find your way.
- Calm yourself down.
- Don't tell me to calm down.
Why did you come up here in the first place and get us into this?
Did I tell you to come? Go back down then.
- Stop it, both of you.
- Stop what?
The promotion test is only a few days away.
I don't have a second to waste, and what the heck am I doing here?
Did you take a day off only for that? When everyone's busy as hell?
Only? It's something very important for me.
I'm meeting Yang Sun's mother soon for a pre-wedding introduction.
I should at least have a team leader title since I've got nothing else!
Hey, seriously.
Is that something you should say here and now?
Team leader? What's the big deal about the title?
Stop bragging. You're already a team leader.
Do you think it's all fun and games for me?
I've not rested a day since I got promoted.
And now...
I can't use my legs.
I might not be able to walk
if I keep climbing the mountain.
Her condition's gotten worse.
I don't think she can last long.
Park Il Hae. Can you hear me?
- Did you get to Black Bridge Valley?
- Yes, sir.
We met Yi Kang and Hyun Jo.
We got a call about a missing person
between Deokseoryeong and Black Bridge Valley.
Do you mean the woman in a red jacket?
Did you find her? How is she?
She's not good. We must take her to the hospital immediately.
Our situation's not that great either. We can't find our way out.
It's hard to secure a clear view because of the fog, and the GPS is not working.
We don't know why, but the Asian black bears aren't leaving our side.
Yi Kang and Hyun Jo tried to carry the victim down, but they failed.
Let me talk to Yi Kang.
Seo Yi Kang speaking.
You will take the lead and find the way.
You're the fastest, and you know the mountain best.
I'm not confident.
I cannot find the way.
I almost got lost there once, too.
And a missing person ended up dying because of me.
I analyzed the surroundings and found out why.
It was because I was tracing the animal path, not the human one.
I'll take her. You just hurt your knees.
I'll do it. My knees are newer than yours.
The man-made path leads to the village,
but the one the animals have made is in the opposite direction.
If you feel like you're going in circles, go the opposite way, no matter what.
Abandon everything except your headlamps and walkies. Make yourselves as light as possible.
Hyun Jo, you take the front since you can steadily carry her.
Goo Yeong, assist him, and Il Hae, the rear.
You failed when you were in pairs, but now it's four of you.
Trust one another.
Don't worry about anything, just run forward.
Your fellow rangers will watch your back.
Let's go. Run!
What's the matter? What happened?
Please get rid of the trees, too.
[Kim Jae Gyeong]
Had I saved her...
could I have saved this village?
Do you... want to quit this job?
Quitting won't end it.
You'll keep seeing dead people on the mountain,
and only feel guiltier with time.
You can't escape the mountain even if you want to.
With that sympathy in your mind,
[Kim Jae Gyeong]
try harder to save people with all your heart.
That's our job.
[Kim Jae Gyeong]
How's the missing person doing?
They'll save her.
They're different from me.
You come here every year.
[Kim Jae Gyeong]
It's a pleasure to meet you. I'm Jung Goo Yeong.
He's my senior that I've told you about.
Isn't he handsome?
I appreciate everything you do for my daughter.
By the way, how tall are you?
Mom, why would you ask something like that?
Around 170 cm...
171...
This is a gift to the Best Ranger of the Month, Mr. Jung Goo Yeong,
from the chief of the Jirisan National Park.
He will also be paying for your meals today.
Please enjoy.
- The Best Ranger of the Month?
- Yeah.
You must be really good at what you're doing.
Of course, he's an excellent ranger.
Oh, yes.
The flowers are so beautiful.
They're as beautiful as you.
The chief must have meant them for you.
Do you like flowers?
Of course.
They're beautiful.
So pretty.
See? What did I tell you?
I knew he'd come empty-handed for the first meeting.
Things are looking good.
What's the time? We have to patrol the mountain spirit ritual.
What's going on?
Are you still carrying that thing?
Throw it away.
That's up to me. It's mine now since you gave it to me.
Let's go. The ritual must have begun.
He keeps trying to climb up.
- Hello.
- I'm glad you're here.
Have you looked for Asian black bears near Black Bridge Valley?
Of course.
We have No. 35 and her two cubs born this winter.
Are you sure they chased you? They're such sweet babies.
Do you think I made that up? Say something.
It's true.
Maybe you provoked her first.
Are you nuts?
Well, anyhow.
I guess you should thank the bears.
You got to save someone, thanks to them.
Didn't you say you found her while being chased by the bears?
Without a missing report.
It would have been impossible to find her hidden in the rocks on that huge mountain, otherwise.
We saved her, not the bears.
- It was the bears.
- You have no idea how we survived.
- What?
- We nearly died.
- Is that so?
- You're driving me insane.
That doesn't make any sense.
What do you mean, thanks to the bears?
They guided you all the way there.
To find that person.
Guide us? You're insane.
Well, that's a surprise.
Why don't you answer your phone?
I was going to call back after work.
Didn't you say you were coming home this week?
Let's go to a bigger hospital.
I told you.
That won't make a difference.
Then, do you want to continue on like this?
Are you planning to die on the mountain?
That's not a bad idea.
What about the position at the headquarters in Wonju?
Honey,
why don't you go rest up at the residence?
Let's have a delicious meal together.
A serious fall accident at the Jeonmuk Valley in the Amleung area.
[From Jirisan National Park Office]
I'm sorry, Honey.
But wait for me at the residence.
I'll call you.
I'm really sorry...
but I must return to the mountains.
I'm really sorry.
Did something happen?
The real mountain spirits are going there
...to take care of the mountain.
Ranger Station, Control Room.
A major rock-falling accident occurred at the rocky ridge of Jeonmuk Valley.
A number of illegal hikers are injured.
Rangers from all stations and shelters, mobilize to Jeonmuk Valley.
[Deoksan Temple]
What are these?
What?
Why did they throw all these away in this deep forest?
That's what I'm saying.
Get some help and clean these out.
Yes, Sir.
[Caution]
[Asian black bear protection area]
What are you doing here?
I'm looking for something.
Did you lose something?
The rangers already took all the lost articles near here.
What brings you here?
Here?
This was my hideout when I was little.
We called it the Black Bridge Valley Shelter.
- Then...
- That's right.
This is my hometown.
This is your hometown?
Yup.
You've seen the video, right?
Yes.
What that man said is all wrong.
This village didn't disappear because of cable cars or demolition.
The villagers left because of the ghost lights.
What do you mean?
Whenever something bad happened to the village,
the ghost lights always apeared first.
I heard wild beasts' eyes glow like that
reflected in the light when it's dark.
I saw them with my own eyes this time.
The ones I saw were Asian black bears' eyes.
Back then, there were no bears on the mountain.
Whatever you're looking for, I hope you find it.
- Yes.
- Then.
♫ The same day, it makes me feel smaller ♫
♫ There are people that come to mind when that happens ♫
♫ Clear eyes, and the sincerity in them ♫
♫ Make me smile so I can stand up again ♫
♫ Without you, I wouldn't be here ♫
♫ Now I won't let go the hand I grabbed ♫
[Jirisan]
You know what though?
Today's our one-year anniversary since we met.
If I get the murderer, maybe you'll wake up.
We should let people know what happened in here.
You knew this.
Since when have you known about this?
We weren't the only ones on the mountain that day.
Jung Goo Yeong?
Why did you go to the mountain that day?
It could get too risky for you.
There is a way.
Why are these people together?
How can we? We don't know who it was.
Hyun Jo knew about the murderer.
♫ I'm always by your side, with you ♫