[Nanno] Adults say that a school
is a safe space,
an innocent place.
DIARY OF GOOD DEEDS
A community free from violence.
However, the violence outside…
-will always find its way to places…
-[girl screams]
[Nanno] …it doesn't belong.
-[vicious stabbing]
-[students screaming]
Don't you agree?
[theme music]
[clock ticking]
Why are you always slacking off, huh?
Finish your work right now.
I have other things to do, got it?
That sounds like a "you" problem,
not mine.
Wait.
If you hit me with that,
I will report you to the PTA.
I'll tell them what you did.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
What is this here? Come on.
Are you scared of the PTA?
If that's how you feel,
we'll just stay here, yeah?
You won't be the only one
that doesn't get to go home.
No one goes home.
No fair.
It's his problem, not mine.
I can't stay here.
I have a student council meeting.
Me too. I have to go home
to edit my YouTube videos
which I upload every Tuesday.
If you want to leave,
tell Koh to finish his work.
I wanna go home, too.
My daughter's waiting.
Koh.
Koh, just do your work.
If I don't, what are you gonna do?
Then just give it to me. Come on.
No way.
He has to do it.
Koh, do it now.
Come on. Do it for us.
Fine. I'll do some work for you.
I'll do this one for you, Kaew.
I will do this one for you, Duang.
And I'll answer…
this third question for his daughter.
-Daddy!
-Tang!
Well, I don't need to do it for her now.
His daughter is here.
That freakin' kid came in
at the worst time.
-Daddy, can I play a game on your phone?
-Here.
Look at that.
If she gets to play games here,
I'm not doing shit.
Hey, Koh.
[panting]
[Boong] Close the door.
-Close the door!
-What on earth are you doing?
-[Boong] Just close the door.
-[Koh] What the hell?
Get out of the way.
-[both panting]
-What's going on?
What the hell is going on?
-Close the door.
[Sa] Close the door!
[door closes]
[panting]
[Tor] What's going on?
-What happened?
-I don't know.
We heard someone was attacking the school.
[Suer] They're wearing our uniform
and stabbing people.
-We ran here to get away.
-[Koh] What?
That's not true, Suer.
Yes, I swear. I saw it with my own eyes.
A kid was stabbed in the throat
over and over, and over.
I also heard that someone
got their face slashed.
How many of them are there?
[Boong] I don't know.
Hang on. Just calm down.
Move the desks over here, hurry!
We'll block the door.
[Tor] Stop.
Do it quietly.
Do you want them to hear us, huh?
Turn off the lights and close the shades.
[clattering]
Keep it quiet. Keep it quiet.
Koh! What are you doing?
Grab a desk and help.
Everyone, sit over here.
Keep as quiet as you can
so they don't know where we are, okay?
Do I still need to finish my homework?
Hey, Koh.
I'm just curious.
He was so serious.
Stop it, Koh. Can you shut the fuck up?
The prisoner will hear you
and come and kill us all.
Have you all lost your fucking minds?
You really believe what these two liars
are saying to you?
If you don't believe us,
go and see the carnage for yourself.
This is bullshit.
-[clanks]
-[principal] Attention everyone.
All students and faculty.
There is an emergency
on the school premises.
A serial killer convicted of eight murders
has escaped from prison
and is attacking students.
The prisoner is wearing our school uniform
and has already injured
three of our students.
I want everyone to remain calm.
And stay in groups
until the next announce--
-[clattering]
-[speaker screeching]
[exhales deeply]
[foreboding music]
Are the prisoners gone?
How am I supposed to know that?
'Cause I saw you using your phone.
I'm trying to call for help,
but it's not working.
There's no fucking reception
at the school today.
Can you get through to anyone?
-I can't at all.
-Does it work?
[Duang] I can't either.
I found something…
about the murderer.
What does it say?
The news says,
"A typical Friday morning
has turned into a day of tragedy
at one of our city's
most prestigious private schools.
Law enforcement officials have yet
to release a statement
but sources within the building report
that a young woman,
a recent graduate of the school,
returned with a murderous vendetta.
The unidentified female
is said to be walking around
smiling and carrying a black bag.
She has been using a knife
to stab multiple victims
-over and over and over again."
-Tang, don't be scared.
-It's gonna be okay. Stop it!
-[Nanno] "The story--"
Did they post a picture of her?
It's still loading on mine.
Hey, hey. Wi sent me a message.
She said the murderer is in building one.
What else did she say?
She said the murderer
is coming to building four.
-But that's our building, Dad.
-Quiet. Quiet.
Are you making this up, Boong?
No. Look at it yourself.
[Sa] Hey.
My friend said she's on her way
to our floor right now.
Damn it.
Anyone whose phone works,
try to text the police to come help us.
-It won't send at all.
-What?
Can you send a text?
-I can't send a text, either.
-No. It won't let me.
What should we do, Daddy? I'm scared.
[Tor] It's okay.
[shushes]
Tang, It's okay, baby.
Listen, everything's gonna be okay.
[clattering in distance]
[Tor] Shh. Just keep it down.
Keep it down.
[muffled cries]
-[sobbing]
-Keep quiet.
[Tang whimpers]
-[Tor] Keep quiet, Tang.
-Shut up, you little brat.
They're going to hear us.
Shut up. Don't order my kid around.
[Boong] Both of you, shut up.
[tense music]
-[shushing]
-[Tang whimpering]
[Tor] She's gone.
She's gone. We're safe now.
[Sa] Are we safe now or not?
I don't know. What are people saying?
The reception is gone.
Be quiet.
I think I can hear something out there.
Did she come back?
Shut up, shithead.
-[banging]
-[all screaming]
[female student]
Open this door for us, please!
-Help! Please!
-[doorknob clanking]
Hey! Hey! Wait! Don't open it!
-What are you doing?
-[Suer] What the hell?
How can we know if she's a student
or the murderer trying to get us
to open the door for them? We don't know.
For our safety, I forbid you
to open the door to anyone.
What if she's not the murderer,
but a student?
Are you just gonna let her die out there?
How can we know that?
She might come in and kill us all!
What if she's not?
Will you let her die?
What kind of teacher are you, anyway?
[scoffs]
I don't know.
I'm not risking my daughter's life.
You only care about your daughter.
What about the people out there?
Then I'll let her in!
-[grunts]
-[Tor] I said no!
-I said no.
-Kaew! Open the door now!
-[both grunt]
-I won't let you!
[Koh] What? What is wrong with you?
You could have hurt her
pushing her like that!
I don't care.
If I had to choose
between a student or my daughter,
then I will protect my child.
Doesn't the girl out there
need protecting, too?
Shut the fuck up!
-[Suer] Hey, stop.
-[Boong] Stop it!
[panting]
[Nanno] You guys can stop fighting.
She's dead now.
[students gasping]
[all screaming]
You're the real murderer!
How am I a murderer?
-Because of you she's dead.
-I helped you guys.
How did you help us?
Think about it.
If we let the girl inside,
the murderer would've come in, too.
She would've already murdered all of you.
What I did was sacrifice her
to save all of us.
Don't fucking say that!
Admit it,
you are only thinking about Tang.
You didn't think about us at all.
-I did.
-Fucking liar.
It's obvious that you only care
about your daughter.
Just you wait.
Once I get out of here,
I will tell everyone how you abandoned
your students out there!
No school will ever hire you.
Not ever again!
Your career will be done.
-Koh!
-What?
Can you shut up?
If the murderer is still outside,
she could still come back to kill us.
I think it's too late.
She's probably waiting for us
right by the door.
This is all your fault.
Why didn't we run away from the school?
Why did you bring us here, anyway?
If you're so smart,
why don't you tell me where to go, huh?
I'm grateful that we found the others.
At least we won't die alone.
I don't wanna die at all, okay?
[Kaew] Can you please calm down?
Did you not hear the principal saying
that everything will be fine?
We don't even know if he's still alive.
He's probably dead already.
Come on, Koh.
You heard the same thing I heard, right?
He was talking,
then all of a sudden something happened.
[Tor and Tang whispering prayers]
[mumbling]
[Koh] This teacher is fucking useless.
He is the adult here,
but he only cares about himself.
How will a prayer help you now?
Do you think God will come
and lead you both out of here?
[Tor mumbling]
Let me tell you, the only thing
God can do at this point
is escort you and your daughter to heaven.
[breathing heavily]
You little son of a bitch.
-[Sa] Koh, stop!
-[Koh] Fuck you!
-[Suer] Hey!
-[Kaew] Calm down! Calm down!
-How could you do that?
-[Kaew] Do you want to die? Fuck you!
You guys can fight all you want!
Go ahead and kill each other,
you stupid idiots!
[clicking]
Don't you think…
we should find weapons
to protect ourselves?
In case the murderer gets here.
[sighs]
Yeah.
Right. What do we have?
This shit is so useless.
Shit.
Hey, Tang, you want this?
[Tor] Koh, I'm warning you.
Sir.
Do you want this?
I saw on the news that a teacher
stabbed some students with a pen.
I found a pair of scissors. You want them?
[clattering]
I found a box cutter.
Who wants it?
I'll take that.
[cutter clicking]
Of course, you'll take it…
for yourself.
I'm the oldest one in the room right now.
I need the sharpest weapon
to protect all of you.
Protect us like you did
that girl out there?
You piece of shit.
Suer, I found another box cutter.
Here.
You can have this. Okay?
Find anything else?
I found another metal pipe, Koh.
Take it.
Okay.
[ominous music]
Dad, I'm hungry.
Does anyone have something to eat?
[Tor] Anyone?
I'm thirsty, too.
Does anyone have water?
Just give her some water.
We don't have any.
Don't lie to me.
I know you've got some.
Give her some water now!
[Suer] I said we don't have any.
I saw the look you two gave each other.
Give the kid some water.
I said we don't have any.
Then I'll search your bag.
-Give me this.
-[Suer] No. Hey!
[clatters]
[Suer] I told you we don't have any.
[Tor] Just wait a little longer.
We'll get some water
when we get out. Okay?
[thuds]
[Tor] Everything's gonna be okay.
Koh! You drink our water?
How's that? You said you didn't have any.
You know, I was saving that
for my girlfriend.
[Koh] What do you mean?
But you said you didn't have any.
Are you saying
that you lied to the kid? Really?
To save water for your girlfriend?
What kind of man are you?
[burps]
Do you think they're gone?
[Duang] I don't know.
I don't hear anything.
I don't either.
If she was still here,
no one would be alive right now.
Actually, I think that
this might be our only chance
to get out of here
before she comes back.
You go ahead.
Go and find someone to help get us out.
[Kaew] I agree.
If you think
this is our only chance to get out,
then you can go.
Do you expect me to go out there alone?
I meant all of us could go out there
together so we could protect each other.
We're gonna die if we all leave.
Do you want me to go out there
to die alone?
Oh, fuck off.
You deserve to be the first
to go out and check, Koh.
If it weren't for you,
every single one of us would have left
before all of this went down.
But because of you, we are stuck here.
What? You're gonna blame me, yeah?
Why don't you blame this on our fucking
teacher for giving us all detention?
I did my job.
You didn't do yours.
Oh, great. Blame everything on me.
I guess they should blame me as well then.
I'm not blaming you, Koh.
Then how about this?
Let's take a vote
on who should go first.
If you think Koh should go,
raise your hand.
Sa.
What are you doing?
He shouldn't go out there alone.
[Sa] I feel bad for him.
This isn't the first time
you stuck up for him.
What's going on?
Nothing. I don't want him to get hurt.
[Suer] Are you sure?
If it makes you feel better,
then I'll vote for Koh.
Fuck off.
How could you do that?
Everyone voted for you to go.
-Go on, get out.
-Do you really think
that I'll go get help?
If I get out of here, you'll see.
If I get away,
I won't give a shit about any of you.
Prepare to die in here.
That's true.
If all of you did that to me,
I definitely wouldn't call
for help either.
[Kaew] Let me ask you.
Who are you?
Why haven't we seen your face
at school before?
Oh, I forgot.
So, let's see.
My name is Nanno.
Today is my very first day here.
I'm a new student in grade 11, class four.
I also seem to have incredibly bad luck.
On my first day of school,
a psychopath escapes from prison.
How about this, then?
If you feel so bad for him,
then you can go with him.
Both go find people to help us.
Of course, I could go with him.
But I still haven't figured out
why I should get people
to help any of you.
And the kid? You don't feel bad for her?
How ironic that the one who lied
and refused to give the kid any water
is asking me to show sympathy.
If we had to choose the one
most likely to come back and save us,
wouldn't it be the adult here?
Because he would have to come back
for his daughter.
If I go out there,
-I'm taking Tang with me--
-Also…
you're a teacher.
You're responsible for your students.
Koh.
I won't go anyways.
Why not? You have a box cutter.
You have one, too.
Why don't we make Suer go?
[Koh] That's a good idea.
Suer would have to come back for Sa.
I'm not going. I'm staying with Sa.
Come to think of it,
isn't Kaew in the student council?
Haven't you pledged to help
your fellow students?
But I don't have anything to fight with.
I'm happy to give you my cutter.
-[sighs]
-That's enough.
Stop changing the subject.
Everyone voted for you to go,
so you have to go. Go!
-Yeah.
-That's right.
-[Tor] Go.
My ass. Listen to yourselves.
[scoffs]
[Kaew] Whatever. We voted.
You have to go
and find someone to rescue us now.
If you're able to get us help,
I'll make sure you pass this year.
Oh.
Is that how you wanna play?
Yes.
Fine. I'll go get help.
-[door creaks]
-[Koh gasps]
[foreboding music]
Shit.
[Suer] What is it?
What?
The body is gone.
She came back to get the body.
Fuck! We were too loud.
She has to know that we're in here.
We were arguing
because you wouldn't go for help.
[Kaew] Koh.
Listen to me.
Maybe the body wasn't taken
by the murderer but by somebody else.
The police might have come to investigate
without knowing that we were here.
How could they not know? We were too loud.
[exhales deeply]
I won't go.
[Kaew] If you won't go,
then what's your plan?
You're just gonna sit there?
[Koh] That's exactly what I'm doing.
If we keep quiet for 15 minutes,
then I'll go, okay?
[clock ticking]
[tense music]
Someone open the door for me.
The door.
You want me to get help, right?
[Kaew whimpers]
-[Tor] Koh!
-[screaming]
-[Boong] Hey!
-[Duang] Kaew!
-[Suer] What are you doing?
-[Kaew] Koh! What the fuck are you doing?
Let me in right now.
Weren't you the one who said that
the body is gone
because the police were here?
[doorknob clanking]
If that's what you believe, then go.
I won't fall for your shit.
After all, you pledge to serve us
at the student council.
We voted for you way before
you all voted for me. So go serve us!
-[Kaew] Fuck you! Let me in!
-[doorknob clanking]
[Koh] You should go now
before the murderer comes back.
What's wrong?
Do you want to join her?
What a gentleman, pushing a girl outside.
[Kaew] Koh, fuck you!
I'm more of a gentleman than you.
You sad excuse for an adult.
[phone rings]
[Suer] Is someone calling you?
[ringing continues]
It's Kaew. She's video-calling me.
The reception is really bad.
[breathing heavily]
Kaew!
-Hello.
-[Boong] Kaew.
What should we do? She can't hear us.
[Kaew] Boong.
-Boong.
-[Boong] Kaew. Can you hear me now?
It's…
It's really dark out here
and very, very quiet.
I don't think
anyone's in the school anymore.
Kaew, leave through the front gate
and then call the police for help.
That's what I'm doing right now.
[Boong] What's wrong, Kaew?
What's happening?
-Kaew, get out of there.
-[Suer] What is it?
You should leave. Go.
It could be the murderer.
Get away from there!
What if it's someone who can rescue me?
Kaew, listen to me.
Leave now. Don't go in there!
[Boong] Kaew!
-It's so dangerous. Just leave.
-[Kaew] Fuck.
What the fuck is this?
[panting]
It's dangerous. Just go.
Okay, you just leave.
Run!
-[Suer] Shit.
-[Koh] Kaew, why are you running away?
-Shit.
-Why aren't you going for help?
[Kaew] Fuck you, Koh. Shut the fuck up!
I'm out here because of you.
This should be you, you fucking asshole!
This is all your fault!
-Kaew.
-[Suer] Hey!
-Kaew! Kaew!
-Get out of there!
-[clattering]
-[Suer] No.
[breathing heavily]
It hanged up.
[sobbing]
It hanged up on me.
What should we do now?
What?
This is your fault.
You pushed Kaew out there.
You all were forcing me to go,
but I didn't want to.
[Tor] But I agree.
If someone should go and find Kaew,
it should be Koh.
[Suer] I agree.
But I think that…
Fine. You win. I'll go.
Being here is worse
than anything out there.
[desk clatters]
[door clanks]
Tang. Tang.
All right.
I'm not so sure that
Koh is gonna be of any help here.
What if he just takes off?
Oh.
Koh is not like that at all.
He will definitely go and help Kaew.
You've stuck up for Koh
so many times now.
Why are you so worried about him? Tell me.
It's not like that.
I just don't want people to misjudge him.
If you don't believe
that Koh went to help Kaew,
then why don't you try calling him?
[phone ringing]
[busy tone]
[sighs]
No answer.
[phone ringing]
-[Koh] Hello?
-Koh, you answered.
[Koh] I came out here to look for Kaew
but I can't find her.
[Sa] You see?
I told you that Koh isn't like that.
Since you're out there, why don't you go
and see if you can find somebody
to help us?
[Koh] To be honest,
I don't wanna help anyone.
Can you do it for me, then?
Can you help me out?
[Koh] Fine.
I'll figure something out. I gotta go now.
Help is on the way, okay?
Excuse me.
You can't go out there right now.
Do you want me to pee in here?
Koh has gone to get help.
Just be patient.
I think you should wait here
in case the killer is nearby.
If she forces her way in here,
you and I can protect the others.
You're a strong man.
You can protect everyone.
Bye.
-Uh…
-Suer.
[Suer grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[Sa] Can anyone else
get through to anyone?
[Tor coughs]
Come and sit down, Sa.
[breathing heavily]
What do you want?
Nothing.
Just say what's on your mind.
If we do get out of here, then…
there'll probably be an investigation
in to the girl who died in the hallway.
I did it to protect all of you.
Everyone knows.
[Nanno] Everyone in here does.
But Koh…
If Koh manages to finds help for us,
everyone will consider him a hero.
People will be more likely
to listen to him
than to you,
Suer, Kaew, Sa,
Duang, or Boong.
What kind of father
do you think Tang wants to have?
A father who kept everyone safe
but is known to be a murderer,
or a father who was a hero
because he saved us all?
[Tor] Tang.
Daddy's gonna go find help.
I need you to stay here with them.
[Tang] No.
But, sir, what if the killer comes in?
You girls will find a way.
You will.
But, Dad…
I have to leave you here, Tang.
Come on.
Sa…
lock the door.
[door lock clicks]
How come you had to say that to him?
Don't you know how scary it is
for us to be left alone?
How scary is it?
We have no weapons to defend ourselves.
If something happens…
You're smiling?
[laughs]
Come over here.
Do you remember when she showed us
the picture of the murderer?
She had the exact same haircut as Nanno.
[Duang] Oh, no.
And she lured all of the guys out--
[laughing]
It's you, right? You're the killer!
Is that what you girls think?
Why were you laughing?
You admit that you're her by laughing.
How could I not laugh at you?
You girls think
that I'm some psycho killer
even though I was with you
when the killing first started.
And, Boong,
didn't you say that
you saw the so-called murderer?
It's true, I did see her,
but I didn't see her clearly.
It could have been you. Isn't that right?
Didn't someone get stabbed out
in the hallway
when this lady
was inside the room here with us?
[claps]
Great, Tang.
You're smarter than all of them together.
Why are you playing
with the box cutter, then?
[Nanno] No reason.
I just wanna make sure
that it works just fine
in case I need to use it on someone.
[footsteps in distance]
-Shit. Is that the killer?
-Shh. Shut up.
[male student screams]
Is that Koh?
We should go and help him.
Come on.
Suer left a long time ago
but all you care about is Koh.
My boyfriend isn't screaming.
If it was Suer,
I would go and help him, too.
-Come on. Let's go.
-[Duang] Wait.
Are you crazy? I'm staying.
You can go by yourself if you want to.
I wanna go with you. I wanna find my dad.
-Come on.
-I'll go with you then.
Hey, Boong.
Please don't go.
Someone will come for us soon.
You still think that someone
will come for us?
As long as this kid is with us,
Mr. Tor will come back for her for sure.
The kid just said
she wants to find her dad.
[Tang] Let's go. I'm worried about my dad.
If you wanna stay, then stay.
I'm out of here.
Can you not put pressure on me like that?
I don't wanna stay here
with this new girl.
Who said I was staying with you?
I'm going with them.
It's better for us to stick together.
At least one of you
will be the bait for the murderer
so I can run to safety.
Hey, Tang.
What do you say, are you a big girl
who can be the bait?
What are you saying?
Nobody was thinking that.
Is that so? Forgive me.
[Duang] Wait.
I'll go with you.
[whispering]
Keep quiet. Keep quiet.
Keep a lookout.
If you see something, say something.
Okay.
[Sa] What are you doing?
I wanna take everyone to my dad.
[Boong] Are you calling Koh?
If he's with the murderer…
We'll go and save him, right?
[Boong] We'll know where to stay away.
Why are you so awful?
[Boong] Sacrifices have to be made.
I'm thinking of ways to…
to keep the rest of us alive.
Boong is right.
Koh might be our last hope.
Hurry up and call him. Now.
[Tang] My phone isn't working right.
Mine's working.
Where's Koh? We'll go the other way.
He's over there.
We'll go this way.
Shit!
Fuck.
[panting]
What's wrong?
Ah, fuck.
[Duang] Of course Sa
didn't take us to safety.
She fucking brought us to Koh.
-You bitch!
-That's not true.
What is not true?
I saw it. Let us look at it then.
-[Sa] Let go!
-My phone!
Let me see.
No.
You won't show us because
you're taking us to Koh, aren't you?
You guys are so selfish.
You only care about yourselves.
[Duang] You will get us all killed,
you know?
You can go alone.
[ominous music]
-Hey, Sa, watch out!
-[screams]
[sobbing]
[Sa, Duang, Boong] Kaew!
[gasps]
[Kaew] Sa.
-What happened?
-You need to help.
[Sa] Why?
It's Koh.
-What's wrong with Koh?
-It's Koh!
[foreboding music]
[all screaming]
[Tor] Tang! Tang! Tang!
What… Sa! Are you all right? Sa!
[gasps]
[sobbing]
What happened?
[Suer] Police. Call the police now!
-[Tor] What happened?
-[Suer] Sa.
The prisoner killed Koh.
[sobs]
-[girls whimpering]
-Oh, my god.
[Tor] Whoever did this is a monster.
What should we do?
[Tor] Are you all right?
[girls crying]
[reporter] This evening, a serial killer
who was previously convicted
of killing eight students
broke out of prison and returned
to the scene of the crime carrying out
yet another vicious attack.
The killer injured three students
before attempting to escape
when they saw her fall to her death
from the roof of the school building.
The campus has been under
police lockdown since late this evening.
Are you telling us that the three students
who are found to be
severely injured are okay now?
They are fine.
[reporter] That is all we know so far.
-[Tor] What?
-[reporter] We will continue to update…
How is that possible?
Didn't a student die outside
of our classroom?
What?
We thought you were dead.
I… I had an asthma attack.
I tend to faint
when I'm in an intense situations.
Well…
if that's the case,
then I wonder who…
ended up killing Koh?
Hmm…
Suer was totally overcome with jealousy.
-[Koh screams]
-[grunts]
Perhaps Tor didn't want Koh to tell people
what happened in the classroom.
[Tor grunts]
Or it could have been Kaew who was angry
with Koh for pushing her out of the room.
[Kaew screams]
In all honesty,
if it weren't for Tang here,
the three of you would have ganged up
and killed me by now, wouldn't you?
What?
Forget about it.
The real mystery remains.
What are we gonna do with Koh?
I'll let you geniuses decide.
Let's go, Tang.
How about we go and find Duang's phone?
I saw it fall into the drain.
We could really use
your small hands to get it out.
Can you get it for me, please?
This phone is very important.
Why is it so important to you?
The phone isn't even yours.
Hmm…
That phone recorded everything
that happened in the classroom.
It will be a key piece of evidence
that will be used to find who killed Koh
and the people who willingly let him die,
like your father for example.
So, can you please get it for me?
I can't reach it. It's too deep.
Sweet Tang.
[Nanno] You're such a good daughter.
You'll have a bright future
at this school.
You're just like anyone of us.
[Nanno laughs maniacally]
[maniacal laugh continues]
[closing theme music]