[foreboding music playing]
[fire crackling]
[footsteps approaching]
WHAT CAN MONEY BUY?
That room is our lab
for botany experiments.
That's for the students who love nature.
And this is our room
for sewing and textiles.
That's for the students
who are interested in fashion.
Although the school has many
extracurricular activities,
we still prioritize academics
or the students.
Most importantly, we have received
many academic awards.
[foreboding music continues playing]
SPACECRAFT SIMULATION ROOM
MANIT PATNACHAI
[teacher] What's the matter?
Whose names are in the wall here?
Oh, these are the names of the parents
who have donated money the rooms.
Let me show you the other rooms, okay?
[Nanno, in thought]
Money. What can it buy?
A room?
Fame?
Objects.
Social standing.
Maybe…
money can buy even more than that.
[teacher]
And that's all the rooms we have.
The rest are empty until we get
more donations from the parents.
Let me show you
the classrooms downstairs, yeah?
What's the matter?
If I wanted to buy this room,
that wouldn't be a problem, right?
[whirring]
Thank you so much.
[theme music]
[student 1] What are we eating tonight?
[student 2]
I'm not hungry. Let's go bowling.
[student 3] Hey, I want to have sushi.
-[student 4] Yeah.
-[student 2] But when I see your hair,
I want to have egg noodles.
[all laughing]
-Ramen.
-Hey, it's in fashion right now.
-Here's your souvenirs.
-Oh!
-[screaming, ululating]
-Hey!
-[both cheer]
-Yeah!
-Hey, why are you guys screaming about?
-That's a lot.
You're acting like you've never been
to England before.
[Tap] Hey, we screamed
because we're excited…
Guys, you each owe me 2,000 baht
like you said.
-That's just your allowance. Hurry.
-Come on. Hurry.
We all made a quick bet if you would buy
more souvenirs than To.
Damn. You way outdid him this time. Look.
I thought I bought too much stuff.
Man! You got way more shit than I did!
[Whan laughs]
To, why didn't you follow him around
to see what he bought
and then buy one thing more than him?
You traveled together, didn't you?
Yeah, I made plans with him,
but he was never free to hang out.
Hey, I had to spend time with
my parents too. I never get to see them.
And you invited me to a football match,
but your seats were behind the goal.
I never sit there.
DINO AND FRIENDS
Dino, well, he…
Dino is the kind of person who…
How do we say it?
Actually, if I didn't know him for years,
I would think
he's a typical stuck-up rich person
because he's someone
who seems to have everything.
I mean, he's rich, and he comes
from a family with a lot of influence
and people just can't get to know him.
He's the kind of person who likes to bring
a lot of expensive things, man.
Everything he buys is the best that money
can get you, you know what I mean?
For example, the car he drives
is very expensive.
Everything he has
is what adults can afford
but not at all a kid would buy, you know?
I invited you for a dinner at my hotel,
but you didn't come.
Did you have the duck
at the Four Seasons instead
for the rest of the Thai first group?
[laughing]
Didn't you say there was
a government minister with you
at the Tower Bridge that day,
enjoying the scenery?
Who would wanna go to that?
-To.
-What?
You really suck.
You need to learn
how to do some networking.
-[To] Why?
-Just in case
you decide to become a government minister
in the future, you know?
I don't think I can become
a government minister.
[Pop] Fuck. You aim low.
Dino?
I think he likes to show off a bit.
I don't know.
Hey, this is just my opinion.
I asked a few of my friends
what they thought.
I think he's a bit jealous of me.
I'm not really sure.
But he's so rich.
A new car…
I think he might end of owning Thailand.
-[Pop] Hey, guys.
-Stop. You're giving me a hard time.
I saw someone's name in that room. Nanno?
Who the hell is that?
[Whan] Oh, that's the new student.
She bought a room here on her first day.
She's filthy rich.
Why did she do that?
[Nanno] To start a company.
Hello, I'm Nanno,
and I'm the new owner of the room
and the company.
Here.
What do you do?
[teacher] Good morning, everyone.
Fuck.
-[Pop] Here we go again.
-Welcome back to school.
It's nice to see everyone back again.
Today, we will start the new term by…
giving you last term's grade.
[all boo]
[Pop] I don't want it.
Remember, what goes around
comes around, huh?
Here.
I really don't wanna see
my grades, though.
[teacher] And for you.
Let's look at it at the same time.
-I got 2.48.
-One, two.
[groans]
You got 3.36?
Fuck. This is so unfair.
Look at my grades. It's so bad.
My parents promised
to give me a motorbike.
But they're totally going to downgrade
to a scooter when they see these grades.
[Nanno] I can help you get the motorcycle.
[Pop] How?
Make an appointment with me.
NANNO COMPANY LIMITED
-Yeah.
-That'd be cool.
Yeah.
You promised to get me a motorcycle, yeah?
Oh, I can get it for you,
but that will require a little bit of work
and that will require
a little processing fee.
It's this much.
I think that's pretty cheap,
compared to the price
of the motorcycle that you want.
-What do you think?
-Just try it. I would do it.
-Yeah.
-What about you, man?
It's cheap.
-Yeah.
-[Whan] Come on, just do it.
[Nanno] Great. Thank you very much.
Give me your report card.
I'll process this right away.
[Whan] Just give it to her.
Why does she want it?
[Whan] I don't know. Just do it.
-[Pop] Hey.
-[Whan] What?
[Pop] Hey.
-[Whan] What's she doing?
-[Dino] Is she really going to…
[groans]
[Whan laughing]
Shit.
-My report card.
-[Whan chuckling]
[Whan] Guys, look. She's recreating it.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Pop] How did she do that?
-[Pop] I could just give my parents this?
-Yeah, wait a second.
I'm sure you'll get your motorcycle now.
Yeah.
They're just the same.
Yeah, they're exactly the same.
[Nanno] I can do other things as well.
What else can you do?
[Nanno] Well, pretty much anything.
NANNO COMPANY UNLIMITED
Can Nanno Company really do
anything we want?
Look at that.
[engine revving]
Som cheated on me.
-Pat!
-You're begging?
-Please!
Hey, Pat!
[woman shrieks]
[man growls]
[chuckles]
[woman continues shrieking]
Pat!
Here. Get me a pretty one, yeah?
I'm so proud of you.
You got yourself a girlfriend.
Here's a check for you.
-Appreciate it, Dad.
-She's really adorable.
CAN YOU DO THAT
FOR THE SAKE OF YOUR FRIEND?
Okay, that's it for today.
See you all tomorrow.
[Pop] Goodbye, ma'am. See ya.
Guys, let's go.
-Dino, I have a question.
-[Pop] I'm hungry.
Isn't there something I can help you with?
-I'm already hungry.
-Nah.
Are you gonna play snooker alone?
Come on, Nanno.
He doesn't need any of your help.
His family is wealthy.
He gets good grades.
His parents live abroad.
He doesn't have a cheating girlfriend.
Let's just say if you have any problems,
Dino can help you.
Dude, are you crazy or something?
Her company is already so big.
Why would she need my help?
Well, she doesn't need
to worry about that,
because the next customer
is going to be me.
What do you need her help with?
I wanna go out, but not to a nightclub
or anything like that.
I want to go way over night,
so I want Nanno to write a letter
to my parents.
Let's say there's a camp
or something like that, okay?
Hmm. What about Dhamma Camp?
Oh, yeah, that's a great idea.
I always love going to Dhamma Camp.
What?
-Let me go, too.
-Yeah.
You can't come up with it yourself?
Are you copying me?
Yeah, I am, but I'm also thinking
of my friends, bringing all them with me.
-Tap, To, Nanno, and Dino, too.
-I'll come.
-Unlike you.
-Yeah, right.
Just let her go on a trip by herself.
[Whan] Hey, what the hell. Let me go, too.
-You're too late.
-[Whan] No way.
-Are we going to Osaka?
-Oh, come on.
-I'm going too.
-Oh, no fucking way.
I'm bored of Osaka.
-Let's go to Hong Kong. I want congee.
-No.
-I want to wear bikinis, you guys.
-I'm going, too.
I'm going, too. Hello.
-Okay, okay.
You can come as well, all right.
I feel bad for you.
-You're right.
-But you know what…
You can't choose where we go.
-Hey.
-Dino, where are we going?
I'm tired of going abroad.
Fuck, he's bored.
-Rich people are like this.
-Yeah, I guess that's true.
He has been traveling abroad
since he was ten.
Who wouldn't get bored with that?
Then let's go somewhere in Thailand, yeah?
Ugh, but I'm so bored of Thailand.
-That's so lame.
-What shall we do?
I don't care.
-Why don't we go to a tea plantation?
-I don't want to.
Can I suggest a place too?
I wanna go to Dino's house.
Damn. That'd be rad.
I've heard a lot of great things about it,
so I want to see your big mansion
with my own eyes.
There's really nothing special.
It's just a normal house.
From what I've heard,
this house has a big, beautiful garden.
There's a massive swimming pool, a golf
room, a snooker room, and much more.
It's completely clean…
…that you can go horseback riding there.
It's so big.
Tons of horses,
many expensive horses, I think.
I heard he has…
everything that…
we, normal people…
can't really afford.
Like servants who will take off
your shoes. They'll do anything.
And people to serve them breakfast in bed
whatever you want in the morning.
Uh, I'm afraid you're gonna be sloppy
and break things.
Oh, god.
But, but, but…
I promise that I'll be the one
who watches these guys,
if anyone breaks anything in your house.
I just wanna visit your house, even just
once in my lifetime, you know, Dino?
It's not about the responsibility. It's…
-Come on, Dino. We're your best friends.
-[Tap] Yeah.
I think you can trust your friends.
Why don't you trust us?
Yeah, or maybe you don't
consider us your friends, yeah?
-[Dino] No, come on.
-Exactly.
-Of course, you're my friends.
-[To] Yeah.
-Come on.
-What's up with you?
-Just do it.
-Please?
-Come on.
-Yeah.
-Hey, do it for your friends.
-Hey, stop. Hey, hey, hey. Come on.
Fine.
[all cheer]
-The golf room is mine. Don't come in.
-I'm reserving the light displaying room.
-Take the light room.
-Each take one.
I'll meet you up later.
-Bye now. See you.
-Bye.
-See you tomorrow.
I'll have that letter
for Dhamma Camp, if you want it.
Thank you.
GO HOME
[upbeat music playing]
[navigation voice] In 100 meters, turn
left. Your destination is on the right.
Turn left over there.
Oh, it's here. It's here.
That would be 540 baht.
[upbeat music continues playing]
-Hello, Dad. Hello, Mom.
-[Dino's dad] Hey.
You're back. Have you eaten?
Yeah, Dad. I have.
[Dino's mom] It's a bit messy.
We're getting a delivery out tomorrow.
Do you need my help, Mom?
No, it's okay.
You should do your homework first.
We can do it ourselves, you know?
Yeah, it's okay.
Come on. Let me help you, Mom.
No way.
If you really want to help us out,
why don't you concentrate
on your studies, okay?
Okay.
How's everything at school, hmm?
Everything's fine, Dad.
Actually, my friend sent a driver
to drop me off just now.
Mm. That's a nice friend.
Okay, I'm gonna go do my homework, Mom.
Okay.
Can you pass me that?
[exhales]
This is good.
Okay, that's done.
Yeah, that one.
WE CAN ALWAYS HIDE SECRETS
[cell phone beeps]
Tell me when we can come over,
so I can write that letter for you.
I don't think I can let you
come over to my house.
Let's go somewhere else.
[cell phone beeps]
I already bought a new dress
for the party at Dino's.
Here's the theme. The theme… "Celebrity."
[Whan chuckles]
[cell phone beeps]
No way.
Let's dress up as movie characters.
[cell phone beeps]
I have old glam outfits
for the red carpet.
[cell phone beeps]
Hey, can you guys stop chatting
and get in your fancy clothes already?
Get dressed. Come on.
[line ringing]
[Nanno] Hello?
Turns out I do need your help,
but can you keep a secret?
Of course, I can.
Client requests are always
strictly confidential.
I want you to…
change my friends' minds.
Oh, why is that?
Hey, I think it would be easier to solve
the problem by helping at your house,
because your friends,
they really wanna go.
[Nanno chuckles softly]
-My house…
-What about it?
[Dino clicks teeth]
-I have valuable things there.
-Hmm.
So, I don't want them to come.
Uh-huh.
Is there any way to do it?
Change their mind?
Maybe it would be better…
if you find another house.
Is that what you really want?
Mm-hmm.
A house that they would like.
Let me see…
what that'll cost you.
200,000.
That's cheap, right?
Yeah.
All right, then.
Please give me the cash tomorrow.
Is that okay with you?
Okay.
-Hey, Mom.
-Mm?
Is there anything to eat?
Oh, there's watermelon in the fridge.
[Dino's mom] Did you find it?
Yes, I did.
[Dino's mom] Dino.
I'm sorry I didn't remove the seeds.
It's okay, Mom.
[Dino's mom]
Have you gotten your bonus yet?
The loan sharks won't stop asking.
[Dino's dad] Why do they keep on asking?
It's like we don't have a child
to take care of.
-Have you received it?
-We need to pay for Dino's tuition.
Have you gotten it?
Yes, in our bank account.
-How much is it?
-It's 200,000 baht.
Good. We can pay them back right away,
because I've heard if anyone
doesn't pay them back,
they'll hire a gangster to kill them.
[Dino's dad] Yeah, I know.
Dino, you're a big liar.
Fuck you! How can we be friends
with someone like you for this long?
You lived in a crappy house, but you
always act like you were so freaking cool.
You fucking smell that?
You reek of a poor, Dino.
[suspenseful music playing]
THE ATM IS 1.5 KM AWAY
[beeping in a normal pace]
[beeping faster]
[beeping slows down]
Hey, Dino.
What are you doing?
I was just getting some water.
You can pour me a glass, too.
Here you go.
Very good, son.
-I'm going back to bed.
-Mm.
-Don't stay up late, okay?
-Okay.
[somber music playing]
AN ORDINARY MORNING
[Dino's dad]
Hey, I told you my money is gone.
Wait a minute.
How can you not take responsibility
when my debit card is still here,
but the money has disappeared?
Don't you understand?
Just go. It's nothing.
Excuse me, are you really accusing
someone in my family of stealing?
Hey, you're not taking any responsibility.
I don't know. I don't know.
You stop and listen.
My bank card was with me the entire night.
What? Who else would go
and take the money out?
This is your fault. Check the account,
find the money, and put it back.
That's it. Yeah.
They should pay us back no matter what.
What if we don't get it back?
[Dino's dad sighs]
I don't know.
DINO'S HOUSE
How is it? Do you like it?
[Dino] Actually, it's a bit small.
Really? Do you want me to look
for a new one for you?
It's fine.
Can you show me around the house?
I want to see how similar it is to mine.
Of course.
WHO WOULD BE AS FREE AS DINO?
[classical music playing]
[Whan and Pop laughing]
[Whan] Fuck.
-[Pop] Whoa.
-[Whan] Shit.
This is your house?
-[Pop] Wow.
-[To] It's so big.
[Tap] Hey, you prepared an afternoon tea
for us, too? It looks really delicious.
[To] Oh, my god.
-[Pop] Where are you going?
-[Dino] You don't come here every day.
[Whan]
Hey, is this from the era of Louis XIV?
-It's so soft.
-Yeah.
That's right. My dad has good taste.
Dino, can I play golf?
[Dino] Be careful not to destroy my house.
-Yeah, I'll be careful.
-[Tap] Let's take pictures.
-[Whan] Yeah.
-We're not gonna come back here.
Hey, can I smoke this, man?
[Dino] Go ahead. My dad won't notice.
[Pop] It smells nice.
What are you guys so excited for?
You act like you've never seen
this kind of stuff.
Our dads keep that kind of stuff
in our room.
We're not allowed to touch it.
That's totally true, actually.
None of us have this much freedom as you.
[blows]
I think you should hold off
on smoking that.
If you wanna smoke it,
you should have a whiskey, too.
Right, Dino?
-I'll get it, then.
-Which brand is the fur?
You don't need to.
I don't know. I took my mom's.
You can call the servants.
Yeah, right. Why get it yourself, man?
-Mm-mm.
-[Dino] Oh, yeah.
[To] What's the big deal?
[chuckles]
Oh, my god.
He calls the servants with a bell.
[all laughing]
-[Tap] He's a rich kid.
-[Pop] Oh, that's great.
Dino, whiskey.
-[Pop] What about you?
-[To] I want tea.
Whiskey.
[Pop] Excuse me.
I would like some whiskey.
Yes. As you wish.
[Tap] Yeah, I want whiskey, too.
[To] Tap, which kind of tea this is?
Are you all right, Dino?
-Yeah.
-[Tap] I think it's Earl Grey tea.
-All right, then.
-I had this in London before.
[To] Oh.
[Whan] Hey, Dino.
Why don't your parents have
any pictures in the house?
I want to see the ambassador
and his wife, you know.
-Yeah, me too.
-Right?
We must have left
all our pictures in England.
[Tap] I'm so jealous.
I've never been to Europe.
If you wanna see
what Dino's parents would look like,
we can look for them
on the newspaper or the Internet.
Isn't that right, Dino?
I'll go look for one.
[Pop] No, sit down.
Just stay here with us.
Let the servants get it.
Excuse me.
Can you get the pictures
of Dino's parents?
-Yeah. We wanna see them.
-[Pop] Now, please?
[To] Do you think his dad is handsome?
I mean, Dino's good-looking.
-His dad's probably handsome, too.
-[Pop] Good point.
[Whan] Yeah. He must be handsome.
-[To] Here it is.
-[Whan] Wow.
-[Whan] Hey. No way.
-Is that him, Dino?
-[Pop] They don't look the same?
-[Whan] His dad is younger.
and his mom is still young, too.
[Tap] Mm-hmm.
I also don't think Dino
looks like his parents.
He looks more like…
Everyone says that,
but he actually looks more like
his grandfather at that age.
[To] I see.
[Tap] Oh, he looks like his grandpa.
His grandpa must be handsome.
[Whan] I agree.
Let's eat, then.
[Tap] Sounds good. I'm starving.
[Pop] Yeah, let's eat.
Where's the kitchen? Take me there.
[bell dings]
THE ART OF EATING
[all] Whoa.
-[Pop] Looks so good.
-[Whan] It's delicious.
Fuck, this is like
a Michelin-starred restaurant.
Your cook is awesome.
He must have been a chef
at a hotel before this.
-[Tap] I agree.
-Well, this is Mr. Dino's house.
Why would you think of the ordinary?
[To] That's true.
[Tap] Wow, it's so good.
-[To] Which one?
-[Tap] Try this.
-[To] This one?
-[Whan] Yeah, it's amazing.
Hey, everyone.
-Let's make a toast too.
-Okay, let's do it.
-[all] Cheers!
-[Tap] Cheers! Yay!
[Tap] Ugh!
What the hell is this?
There's no way that's whiskey.
I think you're too young to drink.
You're all underage.
[all laugh]
-Young?
-[all laughing]
Wait, who do you think you are
that you can tell us
what we can or can't drink?
Yeah.
I think servants shouldn't talk so much.
[To and Tap laugh]
[Pop] Whiskey!
He's still not moving.
Yes.
Why is he being so annoying, man?
[To] He's so fucking dumb.
Dino is generous.
If it were me, I would tell my dad
to fire his ass.
[all laugh]
I'm gonna stab you.
You should listen to Dino,
you work friend.
To is so cool, right?
When he's at home,
he's not like this at all.
-[Whan] Yeah.
-[Tap laughs]
[Pop] Is he a pussycat when he's at home?
[To] My dad is strict.
[Whan chuckles]
[Pop] Pour it for everyone.
For Dino as well?
[Tap, To, Whan, and Pop laugh]
[Pop] What the fuck you think? Of course.
[To] You don't serve the owner?
Yes.
-[Tap] The aroma's good.
-Yeah, it is.
-[Pop] Raise a toast?
-Yeah.
-Come on.
-Cheers!
-Mm.
-Mm. It's good.
-It's good.
-[exhales]
-Straight to the heart.
-This is the life.
We do have whiskey and cigars.
But I still think we can have more fun.
That's why I brought some weed as well.
-[Pop] Woo-hoo!
-[To] Ooh, all right!
But this is my house.
[Pop] So what?
It's because this is your house
that we can do stuff like this.
Fuck yeah.
What if my parents come back and smell it?
They'll get fucking high.
Dino, what are you scared of?
If the weed smells, let them deal with it.
-Exactly.
-That's right.
…them.
-But I--
-Hey, Whan is totally right.
What are servants here for anyway?
It's also not very often
that we can hang out like this
and have fun with no adults around.
[Pop] Yeah.
But I'm worried that my parents
might smell it.
[Pop] Hey. Your parents
won't believe them anyway.
You are the one who's in charge
what happens inside your house,
not your servants.
Anyway, if you tell them
not to say anything,
they'll act like
we were never here, right?
-[Whan] That's right.
-[Pop] That's true, yeah?
-What's up with you?
-Come on.
You all know that's what
we came here for, right?
-Yeah.
-We can go somewhere else.
-[Pop] Let's have some fun.
-Mm.
Just have some.
[To coughs]
-[Pop] It's good stuff.
-[Whan] It's a little strong,
but this smell is good.
[Tap] I'm gonna smoke it all.
It smells fucking good.
[Dino coughs]
[Pop] Look at him.
-[Pop] Come on.
-[Tap] Are you all right?
I want to have you guys
come over to my house next time,
but I can't invite you anymore
now that I've experienced Dino's house.
-[Pop] Hey.
-[To] Huh?
You tried to compare your house
to Dino's house?
-Geez. I won't dare anymore.
-[Pop] Right?
Hey, it's okay.
[Pop] Come on, come on.
[cutlery clattering]
-[Tap] To, have some veggies.
-[Pop] I think the pork ribs…
-I got it on my plate.
-It's good to have it with red wine.
-[Tap] Hey, I want some.
-[Whan] Yeah, me too. I want some.
[Pop] Get the red wine.
Uh, you've all had too much already.
[Pop] Whatever. Shut up.
Dino. Your servants are ruining the party.
[Tap giggles]
[Dino] He's probably just worried.
We've all had so much already.
I mean, what if we throw up?
-Just wipe it.
-[Pop] Who cares if we throw up?
Having pork ribs…
-with red wine is a fucking work of art.
-[To] Yeah.
Come on, go get it.
[Dino] Just get it.
-[Pop] My glass is getting dusty now.
-[Dino's mom] It's all right.
[Tap] I want red wine.
-[Tap] I want to have red wine.
-[To] I want to have red wine.
-[Pop] Hey.
-I'll go get it.
[Pop] You should be as obedient as she is.
[Tap] Yeah.
[Pop] Look at this mug face.
Are you working at a casino?
Wine, miss.
[gasps]
-[Whan gasps] Shit.
-[To] Hey.
This is brand new.
[Pop] What the fuck.
Hey, calm down now.
[Pop] Your maid obviously did it
on purpose.
You, you were all too young to drink.
[Pop] Stop talking, man.
Okay, then.
-Let's get out of here
-But they were…
Okay, let them clean this room.
It's so annoying. Let's go, guys.
[scoffs]
Fuck me.
I'm being considerate of my host or else,
I would punch him in the face.
Son…
IS THIS FUN ENOUGH?
This sucks!
The wine's not coming off.
She needs to buy me a new one.
[door closes]
I'll buy you a new one.
They're getting on my nerves.
[Tap] Hey.
Look, we only get to hang out as a group
every once in a while, you guys, come on.
We're alone. Those losers are gone.
We can do whatever the fuck we want.
How about we do
something crazy and fun, yeah?
[To] Tap, you're scaring me.
[Tap and Whan laugh]
Hey, do you have anything else
besides golf, Dino?
Is this fun enough for you?
-Fuck!
-Hell, yeah.
-[To] Fuck!
-[Pop] What the hell.
Hey, that's something do to.
How about this?
Fuck, what?
[Pop] I'll only load one bullet
and whoever gets shot
will win the entire pot.
Everyone, 200,000 baht,
at you.
[gun cocks]
[Pop] Are you playing?
Fuck, no way.
What if I shoot myself and die?
-Yeah.
-[giggles]
Just shoot your arm.
[Pop] Whan, what do you want again?
Chanel? You can buy six handbags.
What do you say?
Fuck. Fine. 200,000. Let's go.
You?
Yeah, let's go.
And you?
[Tap] Yeah, I'll do it too.
-Nanno?
-Do you accept checks?
Yeah.
Dino, what about you?
I'll do it.
Cool. Then, I'll start first.
[Tap] Fuck. He's really doing it.
[suspenseful music playing]
[gun clicks]
-Fuck!
That was scary.
It's your turn.
[Tap] To, do it. It's 1.2 million baht.
-It's my turn already?
-[Tap] Yeah.
-Do it.
-[Tap] It's 1.2 million.
Do it.
[all] Do it. Do it. Do it.
-[grunts]
-[gun clicks]
-Fuck.
-[laughs]
[breathing heavily]
-You suck.
-Go get it.
Wait and see. With my luck, I'll get it.
-[all] New boobs. New boobs. New boobs.
-[Whan laughing]
-[gasps]
-[gun clicks]
[laughing]
-[Pop] The boobs burst.
-[laughing]
[Tap] Fuck!
[laughing]
All right, my turn.
-You're brave.
-Six Chanel bags for you.
Come on. Do it.
[To and Pop] Six bags. Six bags. Six bags.
[gun clicks]
[To and Pop laugh]
No Chanel bags for you, girlfriend.
[laughs]
Fuck, it's Nanno's turn.
-[Pop] Huh?
-[Tap] Come on!
[gun clicks]
[panting]
-Here.
-[To] Are you fucking crazy?
Dino's the last person.
I think our host has a chance
to win it all, you guys.
End the game.
[To] Yeah, do it.
[all] Dino! Dino! Dino!
Wait.
I think that's too easy.
-That's right, put it in your mouth.
-[Whan] Hey! Hey! Hey!
-What the fuck did you stop him?
-[shouting] Because I wanted to!
I can't take your behavior anymore!
What are you guys even doing?
Huh?
What are you doing?
What the hell!
Do you know how much money
your parents spend in order to raise you?
Do you know how hard it was?
Have you ever even thought about that?
Have that even occurred to you?
And what are you guys even gambling on?
You're betting your lives for money?
The fuck are you thinking, huh?
To throw your life for money,
what a waste.
I'm speaking to you as…
a father,
not because I'm older
or more mature than you.
I'm the father of the person you--
[metal clanging]
[Whan screams]
-[Pop grunts]
-Hey!
That's enough! That's enough!
Stop! Stop it!
[Dino's mom screams]
Why did you do this?
How can you do this?
-What are you doing?
-Don't shoot! Calm down!
-It's the last bullet! Don't shoot!
-Whan, don't be scared now.
She wouldn't dare to shoot
anyone of us here
because she can't afford to pay
our hospital bills.
[Dino's mom wailing]
[Pop] Stupid woman.
Do you really think the gun is loaded?
You fucking idiot!
[screaming]
[Dino screaming]
That's enough! Stop!
That's enough!
[Pop panting]
[Tap] She's not moving.
Is she dead?
Pop, this is all your fault.
Fuck. What should I do?
[Nanno] It's not that hard.
Just do what you've always done.
[Nanno guffawing]
"DO IT" CAMP
Dad, Mom.
How was Dhamma Camp, Dino?
So, did you meditate a long time?
No, Mom.
[Dino's mom] I forgot
to pack your mosquito repellant.
I'm sorry.
[Dino's dad] Eat, son.
Hey, Pop, you should give more
than everyone else.
I'm totally broke, man.
Dino, you don't have to. It wasn't you.
You're the boss. You can clear things
up for us. Don't worry.
350,000.
This should be enough to keep shut.
This includes compensation
to pay all of your hospital bills.
[Dino] Don't… Don't tell anyone.
[Whan] Take it.
[Dino's dad] Dino.
If you're going to another session
of Dhamma Camp,
don't forget to tell us.
What about you?
What do you think money can buy?
[giggles]
[somber music playing]
My opinion, money is the most
important thing in the whole world.
If you don't have money,
you can't really do anything at all.
I hope I have never have to live
without it. I mean… Fuck that.
I don't know why I should live
without money. I deserve it.
Who wants to do that?
Oh… I think I'd be so unhappy.
If I saw some new clothes that I like,
but I didn't have money to buy them,
even just thinking about it
doesn't feel good.
No, no, no. That's a no-no.
If I were to imagine myself as poor,
I can't think
of what that would be right now.
Even now, I get stressed.
When I only have 2,000 baht
in my wallet, I feel so poor.
It can pretty much buy everything.
We can even buy people with money.
I came up with a project.
When I grow up,
I want to contribute to society.
I will buy all of this land.
I'll build a temple.
I'm going to invite monks
and goddesses to pray all day.
I'll invite poor people and then,
I'll give the poor people
rice, rice, rice.
so they will never go hungry again
in their lifetime.
[somber music intensifies]
Subtitle translation by Tanida Itthiwat