No.
What about them?
Are they waiting for an answer?
When the breeze blows past my face, it blows through my hair
And tells me a few words
The spring breeze blows, the flowers bloom
It's you, it's you
The autumn leaves fall, the winter leaves bloom
Episode 16
Don't look at Chi Cheng as a playboy.
He is a top student who graduated from the University of Tsinghua.
You don't have his family background.
You should at least know some culture.
What are you doing?
I'm reading.
Why didn't you reply?
What are you doing?
Da Bao.
Are you busy?
Yes.
If you are busy, then say it.
I want to go to you.
Yeah.
Zhu, help me get rid of this rogue.
Does it hurt?
No.
Let's go out and chat.
I don't have time.
The car is at the door.
Whatever.
I found that reading the book of the dragon
is like seeing a surprise turn.
It's always a joke, a joke, an exaggeration.
The most exciting PG game on the line.
The mahjong is over.
The queen of the prize pool.
Find the golden city.
The super high rate of compensation.
The reward frequency is high.
There are many opportunities to take revenge.
Hurry up and join.
The Macau New Beijing Entertainment Center.
The end of history.
Where are you going?
Tea house.
You said that history is so dramatic.
Why would someone like to read novels?
Do you think religion can monopolize the truth?
I think that all the unkind behavior
is due to the fear of humanity.
Especially those who are highly respected.
They will not hesitate to confuse the public at all costs.
Just like what you said, the situation of the blind.
What do you think?
Don't talk to me about these shit.
Let's talk about the steel door.
Are you free tonight?
What?
You want to be hurt by me so quickly?
Except tonight, the time and place are up to you.
It seems that Yue Yue is going to see her parents tonight.
What a coincidence.
Except tonight,
there is no time for anything else.
Then it's a coincidence.
I can't let you run away.
Distinguished guests, ladies and gentlemen, good evening.
I'm the bilingual artist, Nancy.
Of course I can understand.
Thank you for taking the time to attend this summer concert.
First of all, let me invite the piano, John, to bring us his performance.
Let's welcome.
Guanxi.
Let's have a good talk.
Thank you.
Forget it.
For the sake of revenge, I can't help but sacrifice.
He can't do this all the time.
So I can keep him here.
I'm sorry.
Sorry that I hurt you.
It's a music concert that is famous for singing.
You're done?
Is it that good?
You have one too.
You'll know when you taste it.
I want yours.
Aren't they all the same?
You...
Endure it.
It's truly yours, Bi Jiu Tian.
Do not be angry.
It's a good thing.
Endure it.
This chance runs out part-time,
something else is going on.
Or maybe
Lu Di has sold shampoo
to a girl just like a friend.
A Yan.
Darn it.
What am I talking about?
Show some respect.
What do you mean?
You're just showing respect to others' pants.
I just want to see if you've worn the pants I bought for you.
You've bought so many pants and so many pieces.
How do you know if I'm wearing them or not?
You're talking nonsense.
I bought all your pants myself.
I chose the brands, style and fabric.
You're waiting for me to sell them to the market?
Blow it for me again.
What?
Tang Ren.
Why do you blow it again?
My girlfriend likes it.
She likes it more and more?
She used to think that these are all bad things.
It's true.
A young man like you
is doing all these for a woman.
You want this and that.
You've been baking for so long.
You're doing all this to make a friend.
What's wrong?
You're not happy to see my girlfriend off?
Be good.
Blow it for her.
I'll do it.
Wait, Why don't I do this for her.
You're doing this with my finger Consort ahead.
I knew that Bidu's response on your shoulders
was so experienced.
So,
I should blow it for her.
Why is everything so nice?
What do you think?
I don't know.
That sense of near orSTEAND still considered as meaningless.
How long
Before the powered-up moisturization
Please give Deposit
Worship for a while
Don't be a kid.
Who's a kid?
Don't touch the water.
What's wrong?
Take it to your girlfriend.
I won't eat it this time.
You're too annoying.
This cup is needed.
Give it to him.
If you don't give it to him,
he will definitely
play you fair in court.
I requests you
to keep it for me one more time.
If you can't,
let the bad guys
get the job done.
I'm nice to you,
to start the woman's dream forever.
What're you staring at?
Hey.
What's the difference between him and Wang Zheng Long?
He is just a young boy
who has no girlfriend.
Moreover,
he is even more beautiful than Wang Zheng Long.
He is just watching the pot in his bowl.
Go to sleep.
He left.
He left early.
What time?
Around...
I decided it at night.
He didn't sleep here last night?
Why should I let him sleep here?
Did you two do nothing?
We played a trick on him.
Again?
Can you do something else?
You think I want to play tricks on him?
He's the one who keeps asking for it.
If I didn't ask for it,
would I be satisfied?
Don't just sell clothes.
Your sister is a deep woman.
What did you say?
I mean,
that's not how men are.
After all, men are flesh and blood.
It's too monotonous to just go there.
If it goes on like this,
the city will be changed for a few days.
Yueyue also ran away with another man.
Who are you going to revenge?
I think
you should give her more
and she'll definitely respond.
Take her down while it's hot.
Did you two really
have no physical contact yesterday?
Yes.
Does she steal the smallest weapon?
Why not?
How do you respond?
I'll answer her.
You're going to respond to this?
It's from her mouth.
What a great opportunity.
Brother,
you don't mind being dirty,
but I do.
Brother,
I'm coming.
It's me.
It's your turn.
I'm back.
Hello?
I want to go up to you.
You should give her
more and she'll definitely respond.
Me too.
What did you say?
I...
I said
I want to go up to you.
OK.
What's wrong with you?
Do you want to
join me to have a drink?
My side!
Wow.
How could you do this to me?
You really are telling him the truth?
Stop laughing. It's all your fault for making this bad idea.
Now, it's so embarrassing.
People just hang up and disappear.
Is that what you're saying?
Then what should I say? I'll say it.
Come on.
I'm not a woman.
I'm not a
Why are you here?
Look.
I...
Damn.
Why is Chi Cheng here?
How would I know?
This is the clinic.
I'm here to change the medicine.
It's normal, right?
Why are you here?
Your house and the company are quite far from here, right?
There's no hospital nearby.
What should I do now?
How would I know?
What?
You're too fast.
I haven't done it yet.
You just killed me.
Are you crazy?
No.
You like him?
I like him.
I'm going out to chat.
Let's go.
How did they know him?
Then we can find a breakthrough from Guo Cheng Yu.
Maybe we'll get an accident.
So?
How did you get this wound?
In your shoulders.
Why would you go to our company?
The taste is good.
The chef is good.
I went to taste it.
I was thinking if I could dig a few chefs away.
So?
Did you dig it away?
The chefs there are
as good as the thieves.
The chefs didn't dig it away.
I'm in trouble.
Why?
Hello?
Hello, boss.
There's something wrong with the car.
Okay.
I'll be right there.
The snake is more important than the person.
Yes.
You can't go back.
I'm going to the hospital.
I'll be there.
Okay.
Don't forget.
You can investigate Wu Suowei
and all my detailed information.
Send me a message.
Okay.
This...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm fine.
Well...
Ask him.
I'm almost done.
Done.
Wait.
What's wrong?
Come on.
I...
Yes.
That's it.
I'll get you some medicine.
Okay.
Take this and eat it.
It'll be better.
How much?
32.
Just give me 30.
Well,
I've got the credit card.
How about we add a contact?
I'll transfer it to you tomorrow.
You're a cheat.
You're an excuse.
Forget it.
I have to help Wu Suowei find out the news.
I'll add it first.
Okay.
I'll go first.
I'll transfer it to you tomorrow.
You...
It's okay.
I'll find a way to contact you.
It's evil.
It's an
It's not as annoying as our entire group.
We've not buried it in a single piece.
It's our coaster.
It's so thin that no one can see it.
It seems that someone really wants to sell your snake.
After all, your snake is expensive.
So this snake
is hiding in the company.
Car?
The canteen?
The chef there
is just like a thief to me.
So he found it early.
Let's just get it back.
No.
Don't do it wrong.
The car is already locked.
Could it be that the chairman has already known the news
and transferred it to the ground?
Since they are selling it secretly,
they must be more afraid of that old man than me.
And it's not just one person.
Use it well.
That's right.
Such a big snake.
It's not easy to get it out of the company without any damage.
The chairman may have arranged a lot of people.
Even if we get it out, it's still a two-way trade.
It's hard to guarantee that the old man will get it again.
We have to find a way to get it back.
Now Guo Changyu has already known this news.
The old man and I have been in a two-way trade.
We've already made the old man and I get a discount.
Guo Changyu?
How did he know?
He has a few hundred eyes.
You know it too.
You want to find something?
Where's the gift?
Where is it?
You're living together, huh?
No.
I should be leaving.
I'm sorry.
Why are you taking things from him?
I just want to see
what kind of books
that guy who said he wanted to sleep with me reads.
Why do you still remember this?
I thought I would forget him as soon as I touched it.
Hey.
When did you start to have feelings for me?
I really don't have
that kind of feeling for you.
Since...
Since the day...
So, according to what you said,
you arranged all the meetings
on purpose.
It was you who arranged it.
And you pushed it on me.
Yes.
Then why didn't you just say you liked me?
Are you shy?
Don't you want to?
I...
Do I want to
or not?
Who are you asking?
I...
Why are you so afraid of me?
I won't eat you.
Don't be afraid.
I've never been here before.
We're all men. What do you want?
I don't want to
be like this with you.
What?
You've never kissed a man?
Nonsense.
Do I look like
I've kissed a man?
Then how do you know you like men?
I...
I don't know
if I like men.
But...
But I know
I like you.
I don't know
what's going on
between Wu Suowei and Chi Cheng.
And that Guo Chengyu.
He and Chi Cheng
look like they're not on good terms.
How did he find
my clinic?
Why is he so calm?
Or
I should talk to him.
I saw you
talking to Chi Cheng that day.
You two know each other.
I'm sorry.
Who told you so?
And now heН's
troublesome as well.
No.
That was a wrong idea.
If
we get anything wrong,
and investigation his hurt again,
he'll have
Tell them not to know about my sauce.
Understand?
So long now.
What's wrong?
Stop facing it.
Not at all.
The fire place is private.
How do you know it's private?
Don't tell me that
Mom.
It looks like a well-made picture.
I didn't expect it to be that boring.
You haven't got up yet?
I don't want to get up.
You don't want to get up?
Why don't you want to get up?
I want to die.
Did he do that to you?
Did you bleed?
You...
You bleed.
Bleed?
Yesterday,
he kissed me.
That's all?
I thought you were in trouble.
What a waste of feelings.
Master,
don't you want to comfort me?
Master.
Okay, take your medicine.
Thank you, Dr. Shuai.
Did something really happen?
Dawei.
You haven't got up yet.
Why are you having a fever?
Why don't we just stop here?
You're so kind.
You should just bite your tongue.
When you go public,
sell it at a good price
and open a store.
Maybe
many girls will come after you.
What are you doing?
In my dictionary,
there's no half-way.
Why are you getting up?
I'll go to rest for a few days.
No.
You're having a fever.
I'm a new patient.
I can't get rid of the needle and needle.
I can only fight against the needle by force.
I'll get you some medicine.
No need.
By the way,
I don't want to see Chi Cheng these days.
Shuai, come to me.
Help me apply it.
Okay.
Thank you.
Dawei, your slippers.
I don't know if I like Xiu Hainan.
But I know
I like you.
Shuai,
challenging me?
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
You must be a woman.
Yes, I am.
Are you summer?
Yeah.
Come on.
But you are worried about me
And I
You don't even care about me
As long as you are in love with me
It's your choice
You know
I just share it with you
We…
From now on
I think butter or paint
You must have mein
I won't play much
Once in theOwn Side
Ok
I won't give in
No
I'm going to find it.
One.
It doesn't matter.
Keep it.
One.
Two.
I really want to tell you
that
there is no such thing as a sunset or the sea of clouds.
If today is over,
I won't look for you again.
I'll wait for you.
Come, don't be afraid.
The week is open.
I still want to tell you
that there is no such thing as a sunset or the sea of clouds.
The sun rises and sets.
I'll wait for you in my eyes.
Don't be afraid.
Time stops.
The last night on earth.
I just want to confess to you.
I'll spend the last moment with a heart.
Maybe there is no regret.
The last night on earth.
When life turns into dust.
The moment when the sea is kissing the sky.
I will leave you with no hesitation.