destiny?
How dares he? To my sister?
She was his sister?
You got something to say?
The guy who sued your sister, that's him!
Let go of me
Let go!
Fire and the last number is seven!
This year, at their house with Chun-woo club members...
Chun-woo club?
It's a social club that's made up of powerful men.
He also knows how to use a sword, why doesn't he look for the thief himself?
A sword?
Episode 10
There will be at least 50 guards on the day of the meeting
You guys! Guard the outskirts!
30 government inspectors!
Don't you even dare let a rat in! Do you understand?
Yes, Sir!
It'll be impossible for him to even step foot into the house.
Go!
Visitors entering the house during the meeting will be strictly prohibited.
I am Park Jeong Hee, the lord of Young-dong
Lord Park! Welcome!
Please, do come inside!
Lord Shim personally comes out to verify the faces of the members of the Chun-woo club.
That bastard does not have any way in to the house.
Hey you servant! Why aren't you working?
But, who's this woman?
Sweet mother of god!
Sweet mother of god! Aigoo!
What's the matter?
That thing..
How do I look?
Geez! You don't even have a look!
You bunch of frauds! You guys are bored, aren't you?
You have nothing better to do, so this is what you do!
Do I look like I'm fooling around to you? Then you are a fool
I'm doing this as a side job, to pay up your foolish debt!
Servant, during meal time
Hair dresser, during spare time!
Oh! So you will have two jobs?
Very wise! Very wise my servant!
By the way, its a surprise that you had such a skill, Bong Soon
I've done every type of work that pays!
Oooh, these eyebrows are as pretty as crescent moon
A person's life can change just by changing the shape of their eyebrows!
His lips are red like a cherry!
What's this reddish stuff?
Oh, this rouge?
Do they sell this?
Bong Soon! Your first client is here!
Yes ma'am
Goodness, that girl sure is strong.
If you say that you want to take this girl as your wife, I'll rip your teeth off,
so don't even think about...
Where is he?
Hey Yong?!
Where did I lose it?
You didn't have to...
It's nothing compared to your gracious
release of my servants, which solved the work shortage problem.
It wasn't that much trouble.
If you need more please ask for more.
Yes ma'am, I'll be going now
Ma'am, servants?
Yes, I heard that the contract servants didn't work hard enough
So I've pulled out a list of government servants and sent her the reliable ones
Where did you get the lists?
Of course from the palace
You could do such a thing?
Hey kid, my husband is a high rank officer
Such a work is nothing to him
ma'am, ma'am
What a pity. Stop it and pack your stuff!
What?! Planning to flee?!
Careful of what you say! If we get caught, will be spanked for 50 times
I don't wanna lose my sleek ass
Dad, your butt is hanging on your thigh
Believe me and just pack your stuff!
DId you hook a guy?
Is he a wealthy widower?!
Why do we have to be so shabby? Its all because of that maidservant or something we tried to find, isn't it?
Yes, it is
Then! As soon as we get that maid, we won't have to live like this anymore.
Yes that is true, but how?
My lady has promised me to find her
Now we are free! Ummm the smell of freedom
Ewww... It smells like horse dung
Well done girl! Good girl
OH MY DAUGHTER BONG SOON!!!
I'm going out.  Don't drink too much
Hey! Where are you going?!
Where does she go to everyday?
Perhaps she might have actually hooked a wealthy guy
Suspicious, very suspicious
Stop pooping, you horse!
You fool!
Have you seen a person looking for this?
Sorry but I haven't
Excuse me, have you seen anyone looking for this thing?
No, sorry
It's made of a tiger's claw..
Excuse me, have you seen a norigae made of a tiger's claw?
Isn't it the one with goblin's face on it?
You've seen it?! seen it?
Ummmm..
Are you looking for this?
Why do you have it?
Is it yours?
Give it! I've been looking for it for ages!
Why is it yours?
Because its mine!
I thought I had lost it.
I'm scared
I''m here. I'll take care of you
I'll never let go of this hand
This can't be right
No way
Can't be true
Sit! Sit!
What is it?
Just sit here
Come closer, I've got something to give you
Surprise!
What's this?
This is what is called a rouge
This is something that you put on your lips
Hold on let me get an oil
How did you get such a precious good?
Of course I bought it.
You are suspecting me?
Then how did you get the  money?
What the..
You are truly suspecting me, aren't you?
Are you suggesting that I've stolen this stuff?
I only bought it because I thought you would look pretty.
Alright, thank you for the present.
Try it! Try it now!
Later
She will look so nice
This is embarrassing!
Why did you join here?
Huh?
Ummmmmmm, it's that..
You've come here to seek the legendary assassin, didn't you?
Same here.
A legendary assassin?
You don't know? The babies even stop crying when the story is told
Who is that?
Oh my god, you know nothing.
They're really popular here.
They originally come from here, you know.
I heard that..
Just by drawing their sword a little bit!
Enemies all around would fall dead.
You liar. Those stories are all made up, right?
Hey! Do not mock your senior!
Alright! Just kidding
Calm down bro.
I guess I should learn the way of the sword from them!
You can't
Why not?
One  was acknowledged for his great skill and has joined the palace guard
and the other one?
The other one has disappeared
Disappear? Why?
That I don't know. Perhaps he might have left the world
Training in a deep mountain
Training?
Stop eating!!! You eat more than a pig!
I am not a pig!
Stop!Stop eating! Stop!
I pity you for having such a father
I guess I wasn't mature enough back then
Stop!!!!!
Do you like it?
Are you truly offering these precious goods to us?
I wouldn't spare the cost for you two ladies
How do I look? Does it fit nicely?
It fits perfectly.
These things look better on young ladies
No ma'am, it looks much better on you.
In fact, such a young lady is fine looking even without a norigae
By the way, Eun Chae has to find a good husband now, doesn't she?
Have you found anyone?
I ask of you to look for a good marriage for her
Her dad is keeping her too busy these days.
I fear that she won't have time to meet a good husband
A girl should not go out so often! Where have you been?!
Are you going to the construction site again?!
Yes
Stay at home for a while. Jung Chi Hong has even visited you aunt's house
To seek you!
How did he know the place?
That's what I would like to know
Oh, and
Did he take your handkerchief?
I heard that he claimed you like a lunatic with your handkerchief in his hand
A handkerchief?
Hey Eun Chae! Eun Chae!
She won't even listen to me! God damn it!
This is all dad's fault!
Its all because he beats me like a dog in front of the kids!
Now tell me about it, you know the guy that you met the other day, don't you?
That day I could tell that you two were not strangers
How do you know him?
Back then
I thought that the kid had reincarnated
What? What kid?
Your first love that you said died?
I really hope I could meet him again
But will he visit this place again?
We are here
Come in please
I am Kim Mu Young
Oh! Lord Kim! Welcome. Please step inside
All the members are here! Close the gate!
Hold on!
I'm sorry that I'm late. I am a new member of the board, Kang Chul Jung
You are charming as I heard. Please come in.
Yes sir.
How did it go?
So?
I've sent it
We almost had a tornado coming towards the parliament
I guess that I've sorted things out to dodge it
If Lord Hopan had been caught, other lords would not have been safe
If so, the parliament would have been a chaos
Isn't it so?
By the way, I see many new faces today
Yes, I hear there are some new members of the board
So today's meeting is a farewell party and also a welcoming party
Here you are!
This is one of the new members, Kim Mu Young.
Pay respect to our lords
Holy father!
You scared the crap out of me!
I thought it was a chopped off head
You're better at least. Mr. fraud peed himself after seeing this
This is so detailed! How do you create such a thing?
First you glue pig's leather to a mask
And put some wet papers on to it. Then it appears just like a real human face
But does it glue properly?
Yes, it sticks well
Careful! If this gets on your skin it will melt your skin in an hour
Melts skin?! Geez! This is dangerous!
This is a very small present for lord Kim who made it possible for us to go to China as an ambassador
This is pig leather, isn't it?
Feels like human flesh
Oh! I almost forgot! Someone was looking for you
Really?
Who is it?
Quick go check it out
Thief! Thief! Thief!
Attention! Do not panic and close all the path! Do not allow even a rat to sneak out!
My golden toad! My gold! My toad!
Mr. Byun
No one has managed to sneak out
Whoever took that toad is still in here
So regardless of your rank, please cooperate
Begin!
Excuse me sir, would you please spread your arms
Thank you so much
Thank you sir! You can go now
Excuse me would you raise your arms
(Do not touch it! It will melt your skin in an hour)
Why do you sweat so much sir?
Thank you sir
Hold there lord
You must get on a boat to China! Must!
Iljimae!!!  its Iljimae!!!
Find it!
Yes, sir
Call the archers!
Archers to the front!
Aim!
That rat!
If you don't surrender now your body will be full of holes!
How dare you ignore my words!
You are a dead man!
Hey you do it
Shoot!
So you are the Iljimae huh?!
What the heck? What is this?!
Where is he?! Where is he?!
What the heck is that?!
We've conducted a thorough search, but haven't found it anywhere
Perhaps its flown to the sea
Chun-Woo Club?
Chun woo club..
Is it a special day today, mother?
Your father has a meeting with his friends
Friends? But I've never seen his guests
Yes, but it is a very special meeting with very close friends
So you must pay respect to them
Do you understand?
Yes, mother
Geom!
Would you draw me a flower?
But I don't have a paper to draw
Oh yes the paper...
Draw it here if you don't mind
Alright sister
How is it?
This is fantastic! How do you draw so fast?
Sky, Friend? A friendship that pledged to sky?
Your father was murdered
They say you can never trust anyone.
We were very close, and the club was special to us...
Now I see! He is among the Chun-Woo club
So, it wasn't Won Ho's son that Kwon Do Hyung tried to inform the truth, but Kim Ik Hee..
I've got the wrong guy
Your Majesty! I will arrest those guys for treason.
Leave them
Sir?
But your Majesty, those guys betrayed you
Even so, if we arrest them for treason, someone might see it suspiciously
I heard there are rumors about Shim Gi Won's conspiracy, among first lords
But..
They don't know anything yet, do they?
Yes Majesty, they are just waiting fro a letter from Chung
Now is not the time yet
Yes, your Majesty, that is also my will
What is it?
Doesn't look alike
What are you talking about?
Yong isn't your real son, is he?
What?
He and I look exactly the same. Look carefully next time
Look at these gentle eyes
You and him have no similarities, look at your height.Be honest with me. I've heard things.
I'm telling you the truth! He is my son! Did that hunter guy come to you also?
I should have killed that guy!
Yong and I even share this similarity of eternal hunger!
I got to eat something
Oh!Ma'am! What is a rouge? Is it a food?
A rouge?
Yeah! Bong Soon is obsessed of her rouge and thinks that I've stolen her stuff
Is a rouge that delicious? I don't even know the taste of it
Why? You don't like it?
Bring this back to the pub, on your way
This to the pub? Why?
Forget it, I'll bring it back then
Are you really suspecting me? I've really put my hands off since Ja Dol left like that.
Why are you doing this to me? You really think I have no sense at all?
You shouldn't suspect a person like that! You're so cruel
You are pathetic. It wouldn't be easy to find another pathetic guy like you
Just spend a night with her! For women, the body comes first, and then the mind will follow.
She won't come to me, ever
He still lives in her mind
That guy?
Yes
Today is his memorial day
You should return, your Majesty
You've emptied your seat for too long, your Majesty
Do you know what day it is today?
Today is the day that Kwon Oh died
How did it go?
Still looking for him, your Majesty
Where you going?
I've heard a rumor that you hang around with that nobleman's son all the time
Are you jealous bro? huh?
Yong you! Follow me
Where? Where are we going?
You're giving this to me?
You said you've lost it, didn't you?
Goodness! Look at this color! Fantastic
Where did you get it? This isn't cheap stuff
It isn't yours?
I've found mine
What the...
The color isn't pretty at all!
The weather seems cloudy...
Ummm, ma'am?
The government servants list that I asked of you last time...
Oh that! It's in the drawer
Really?
Who is that servant, by the way?
According to my husband that woman servant murdered an officer and was executed recently
My brother...
You're being pursued, aren't you?
Please have mercy
Whatever it is, boys like you gotta pay for what you did
Here! Take this
Wow...
My brother
I've found him
The man who didn't let go of my hand and protected me is alive
Can you see? Those powerless and miserable people
Here! Take this and beat up that boy
Bro!
You did not know this is what we do?
If you can't do it, get out of the circle!
Boss, even though we are the bad guys, how could you do such a thing to a child?
Trust me, I'm trying to make him leave
Take a break and have some of this please
Thank you! Bless you my lady
Thanks to you, we get to eat and even earn money at the same time. Thank you
Its my pleasure, I thank you for the hard work
In a short time the building will be done and I'll let you live in it
No, my lady, how could humble people like us do so?
Father! Father!
Whats wrong?!
They are destroying the village!
What?!
Those bad guys are beating up mom and grandma
Let's go!
You lots!
Stop it right now!
My lady!
You okay? Are you okay?
You...
My lady, this is the guy, isn't he?
You're pathetic
What? Pathetic?!
How dare you do such a thing to a child?! You lots are worse than an animal
Worse than an animal, my lady? I'm disappointed
We don't enjoy this either.
We were told by the lord to clean up the mess, we had no choice but to do it
You go and complain it to your father if you want
Father ordered this?
Get out of here!
Hey! Let's go!
Yes!
Leave it!
Let go of this!
Aren't you a girl?! You've got some strength
What are you doing?
Don't! It's dirty! Don't do it!
I told you to beat up the kid not your leg
I told you becoming a ruffian isn't your type
Put your legs up! I'll smash them!
What's wrong with you?
You pushed me?! Bring it on!
What's wrong with you?!
Go do your work
Alright, ok then
Your own wife wouldn't even cook for you, I pity you
Who..who says such a thing?
So cute!
Don't you dare touch me!
Go! Go!
Alright I'll be gone then
I'll bring a fresh eel tomorrow
I'll cook a fresh eel for you
You're not supposed to do that to a married man!
Don't ever come here.
If you're really up to it, just send the eel.
That butt! Eww!
Ah, she's so obnoxious!
Hey!You forgot your spoon!
What brings you here?
You didn't even have lunch, didn't you? I brought some food
Spare the food! Guys like me don't deserve food. I should just starve to death
I am sorry, I misunderstood you
How's the sale?
Its pretty good
That Iljimae guy is our life saver!
In this case, that thief is better than our son
Don't compare our son to a thief!
My wife has not only pretty face but also beautiful mind and great cooking skills.
Come!Come! This is the place
Wow! I've even been to the palace, but this place is even more better!
Oh, Eun Chae! Where are you going?
I'm on my way to father
You're going to complain about something, aren't you?
Say hello to this man Yong, he is my loyal servant
I devote my self to you sir!
This is my sister, Eun Chae
We've met each other today, didn't we? Perhaps we are destiny!
My lady! Don't be so shy!
Have you seen my sister?
Just met by chance on the road
My lord!
Whats wrong?
Gotta use the toilet! Sorry!
Its that way! Hurry
My father is also a member of the Chun-woo club
Lee Won Ho
Plotting treason
Suicide
What are you doing here?
Ummmm...its that..
Get out of here!
Oh! I've come here to give you this back
Get out now!
Yes, my lady
My lady! My lady!
Whats all the fuss about?
Its up!
What is up?
Iljimae! I heard Iljimae was in action!
For sure?
This time he disguised himself and fleed with the golden toad!
He even used a dummy that looked exactly like Iljimae to confuse the guards!
That is extrodinary! He is not a common thief
Yes indeed my lady! This is a secret, but he even gives back what he has stolen to its original owners!
Then we could call him a righteous outlaw?
Yes! Iljimae is the model of righteous outlaw, isn't he?
You're right
I wonder whether Iljimae uses magic and tricks like the Jun-Woo-Chi
He is great anyway
Magic!
Sir, we meet again
Off duty?
What business do you have here?
Master Byun invited me
What?
Oh, you are curious about how the master and I got close?
Its because my socializing skill is so great! Nothing more
Pathetic
What's pathetic? Oh is it because he is the one who pulled my father's teeth out?
Well, the past is in the past and..
My father wasn't very innocent, so..
By the way sir, I heard you've captured a fleeing government servant recently
Capturing a fleeing slave must be very rewarding, isn't it?
It seems like they haven't granted you a special promotion
I'm sorry sir! Sorry sir! I will shut my mouth
This! This is pure gold and..
and...
This one is a jade
This too! This one looks good, doesn't it?
You certainly are a fashion leader my master!
I thought the big black dot under your ear was actually a giant mole
I always thought that your fit line is beautiful and clean!
Here master! Try this one on!
Shall I?
By the way, your sister, she seems like a heroine
I've heard that she is constructing her own guest house by herself?
Oh, that?
That's nothing. Father gave that to Eun Chae.
Lady Eun Chae is extraordinary!
Your father must care for her a lot, huh?
He loves her
He even trusts her with all the classified documents.
Classified documents?
You know, the list of wealth for each noble family, the number of soldiers, bribes, and so on.
I've never seen the like of this in my life.
What's wrong with him?
I think it's because of that thing, right?
Geom, Yeon...
You're alive somewhere, aren't you?
Daddy, why have you gotten so old suddenly?
Still you eat all the healthy food
I wish you could stop doing all the hard works
Why does she have to work so late with those lowlife people?
All you get by working with them is itchy
I'm itchy just by imagining it!
Servants are useless.
You take care of the business. Go clean that dirty guys and bring the lady home,  OK?
But, she were so stubborn last time.
Since when did you start to question my order?
Bring her home! If its necessary bring her by force
Yes, my lord
Gee-bong
If you happen to touch my precious daughter, even by a flash, I'll kill you
Do not worry my lord!
Go shit yourself!
Bro!
What brings you  here?
I'm quite close to the Master Byun, you know.
What about  you?
I can't stand this job anymore because of the lady
How could you possibly bring her by force and not touch her?! Damn you shit lord!
You mean lady Eun Chae?
Let's go home my lady! You're only making us difficult
Let go of this! Do not lay your hands on me!
My lady, I'm also in an awkward situation here
What you doing?! Let's go!
Careful you girl!
Are you ok my lady? Its nothing, don't worry my lady
Let's move
Preview Episode 11