Can you help me look for someone?
Of course.
An acquaintance of mine is looking for a runaway servant.
I heard you're looking for someone
It must be hidden in the Forbidden Palace
Forbidden Palace?
I'll get it myself.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Aigoo Aigoo!
It's dangerous!
Get out quickly!
What to do now?
No. N..no.
Before I die...I have something to tell you.
That's why I wrote these words..
Someone was looking for you.
Who was it?
He said he'd wait for you on the Nam Mun bridge
Your Excellency, he is here to see you.
What are you guys doing?
I'm sorry
Aigoo.
Are you blind?
Are you going to pick up the Miss, young Master?
You're a bit late today, young Master.
Go quickly! Or else you'll miss her.
What happened?
There...there was a man
who was bleeding a lot.
Blood?
Who are you?
Young Master! Young Master! Young Master!
What should we do now?
Brother!
One guy is dead already, the other one is badly injured.
He may be already dead.
Who suddenly appeared?
Young Master of Lord Byun Shik.
What?
The second young master
Did he see your face?
No, he didn't, sir
Alright.
How did you find me?
Seung Seung accidentally bumped into a man.
She said that person was bleeding a lot
I heard that you went out to pick me up.
So I was worried...
You still went there even though you knew it was dangerous?
Are you crazy?
However...
This is the arm you injured last time...
What to do...
With this kind of injury
The exam...
I'll take it. No matter what.
Don't tell anyone else about this.
Yes...
You're always here
Do you live here?
That girl...
I heard you got stabbed intefering in someone else's fight?
Don't go waltzing about everywhere.
You need to take care of your body, at least.
After all, what else do you have?
This jerk, really...
You old fool!
I'm sorry!
What's going on?
That man ran away with another woman in the middle of the night
and Slick tracked him all the way to Han Byung Do and brought him back.
Really?
You should ask Slick to find that father and daughter cons...
So, how did he get scammed?
Do you remember that cart they had?
Sticky Rice Story?
He invested in that and lost all his money!
ALL the money?
Yeah!
Just one moment!
Ah, what? What?
The thing I asked you for last time... How is that going?
What?
Oh, that person you wanted me to find?
I heard you got scammed.
Huh?
Ah, what are you talking about?
That pocket change?
It was embarrassing to see father and daughter
Doing anything they could to make money
So I just thought of it as charity
And just gave them some spare money I had left.
What, you think the great Yong wouldn't have money? Hahaha...
Ahh, is that so?
Then bring me some of that money.
I only start AFTER I see the money.
Okay, I understand.
I'll bring some money in,
So please find that person for me.
I'll trust in you.
He's looking for someone?
Ah, just
Just try to remember a bit more.
I'm trying to remember
I'm trying...
So, Lee Won Ho?
Lee Won Ho, Lee Won Ho, Lee Won Ho...
Yes, I remember, yes yes.
Wow, it's been over 10 years now.
Back then,
Did all of the family die also?
Hmm...
The family...
Yes, his wife and daughter should still be alive.
Really?
Aigoo...
Hey,
This is all fake.
Real? Yeah right.
Really?
Is it really fake?
And it was so expensive too...
I'll go and catch them,
So tell me.
How do you order this?
It's not all that complicated.
You just put in an order at that inn in Inchun, and it comes really quickly.
Is that him?
Yes.
You've heard how salt traders are better off than anyone else?
He's monopolized all of the salt coming in from the Inchun harbour.
Really?
There's more than that.
He's also well-known for being humble and kind to everyone.
Look, look at that.
-Here, let me carry this.
-Young sir, it's okay, I can carry it.
Then, I will start the wedding arranagement as soon as possible.
By the way, what will do about the dowry?
Bong Soon doesn't have a mother, so I will take care of everything.
Dowry?
Bong Soon
Dad
My dear daugther
Dad, we're getting the contract tomorrow.
From now on, our life will no longer be unfortunate
This lass!
What's with this look on your face when you're going to be married to the rich family in In Choen?
What? Becoming a wife in a rich family?
HEY!
Where did they go?
Aishh!
Where is the son of this house?
I already said, our family only has three daughters. We don't have a son.
Have no son?I saw it with my eyes.
You were fooled by that lady and her kid. It's just...
You are the 7th person this month
My money
DAD!!
I'm here, Bong Soon
Aren't you gone yet?
I'm going nuts. All the money that I've spent my entire life to save has...
Aigoo... my money!
So cold
How come he's not home yet?
Lets see if he will fall for this
The brothel Wol Hyang needs 100 Mo Hyang toys
50 leather gloves. If there's no shipment within three days, we will buy them from a different store.
I was fooled by that rascal and I feel like my life is cut short 10 years.
But he's just like me, a tricky lad
He also has a special reasoning skill
What are your doing young master?
Let GO!!
Please calm down, young master
No more exams, it's over
Young master,
Are you able to withstand it any longer?
Why don't you try the other hand?
It's hard for the wounded arm to pull the bowstring
Take it!
It's not that easy
That's why you have to train the strength of your arm first.
The only way to do it is your willpower.
Young master has been there for three full days
I'm afraid that he will collapse
They should have caught the bait by now.
Could it be that they sense something already?
Yong, I'm starving. My feet are all numb, and my body is cold too.
I have to deliver stuff, too
Brothers, please wait for a little while, they're coming
They're coming..
You all have already waited for three full days
Please go home to change and come back here
It's smelly
I don't smell anything.
You placed a big order.  I will give you a discount.
You come to deliver this yourself?
What happened to your father?
That jerk, I have placed a restriction on him from entering the city.
Ahh!  Why?
He created a big problem, a grand one.
Please check if these are the items that you have ordered and are correct.
By the way,
these are all fakes, aren't they?
What is this nonsense you are talking about?
Is this your first time doing business with me?
I will not give you any discount!  Hurry up and pay.
You are the one who should pay up.
You are caught red-handed.  You con-artist!  Give back my 200 coins.
Ahh Bong Soon.  Bong Soon.
My daughter, Bong Soon.
My baby.
Hey, look here young man.  How many times have I told you?
I lost everything.  All I have are dog hairs.
Put me in there instead!
Yong!
What did my Yong do?
Why did you put him in jail? Yong! Are you alive in there?
Hey you!
Aigoo Aigoo
Bong Soon...
Bong Soon.  My daughter, Bong Soon.
Who are you?
Yong will confiscate the wages from Bong Soon &amp; her father.  If they get caught trying to escape,
each defendant’s punishment will be 50 beatings each on their behind.
Prepared and overseen by officer, Hwang Soo Rhung.
Ok, here.  Both of you stamp it.
Now, Bong Soon's turn.
You people...
if wasn't for my father, I would not have let you go like this.
By the way, don't you ever try to trick my Yong about doing rice cake business.
Rice cake!?
What rice cake?
Ok.
I understand.
I said I don't need it.
Keep the hostages here and Soe Dol will come here all the time!
I am short-handed.
How about me?
I have to work this old man as my assistant.
have to share my meals...
he is old...how can he be my assistant?  He is like my boss.
You said that you didn't want to clean up the horse droppings.  Instruct him to do it.
He looks like he can tolerate nasty stuff well.
Ahh, Dae Shik...
make sure you deligently watch over these two con-artists so that they won't escape.
But why?
To get rid of these stuff so that we can recoup what we have lost.  Idiot!
That little...
Stop drinking so much alcohol!
Here!
I can deposit 20 coins
Wow, you really brought me money.
If you found her for me. I'll give you more money.
Great! I'll found her quick.
Hey. Let's go!
Oh, boy!
Father!
You're eating at a time like this?
It tastes so good, huh?
I told you to fatten this little kid.
Hey. Bring him.
Father!
Did I say I was going to kill you?
I'll send you to a far away and good nation.
People are saying that there Joseon men are that popular!
Hey, bring him.
No!
Give me just a little bit of time.
Last time, I said exactly ten days.
I can't wait anymore. Do you think I live eating dirt? Let go of me!
I have something very important to tell you.
A traitor's child?
That's what I said.
If we find the traitor's child, the compensation is huge!
So let's join forces.
How about we split the compensation in half?
If that kid is the traitor's child, that means I'm...
... the king's child.
Wow, because you don't have money you're just making stories up!
Please believe in what I'm telling you.
You're getting noisy.
I'll give you exactly 15 days from now.
Prepare that money by then.
Do you understand?
Guys!
Let's just go.
That guy is a traitor's son?
That's why...
Am I crazy? Why would I share that with you?
Hurray!
You worked hard.
You can finish for today.
Yes.
I asked Father to fix the lantern...
Miss! Please come out!
Shining your path is the only thing I can do.
I'm always thankful.
Eun Chae.
The lanterns shining this way and that.
Ahh... so cool.
Young master Shi Hoo?
With an arrow?
What are you doing, hanging out like this.
He lightened the lanterns?
If others saw, they would think he is Eun Chae's lover.
Young master!
I polished your shoes.
Aigoo.
That little rude!
Oh my...
Ahjussi! Ahjussi! Get yourself together!
Yong!
Hey, Slick wants to see you right away.
He said to tell you he found her. Who are you looking for again?
What?
He said he found her?
What is that?
Who is that?
What's wrong with him?
Can you bring this person to a doctor?
Do it for me as a favor.
Geom!
Ahjussi! Ahjussi!
Get yourself together!
Who could he have possibly wanted to give this to?
Exactly.
It must be...
It seems he is related with Lee Won Ho.
It's not Kwon Doo Hyun.
Shim Gi Won and Kwon Doo-hyung made a blood pact with me
Do you really think I wouldn't be able to recognize Doo Hyun's handwriting?
Let's see.. Kwon Doo Hyun
Here it is.. He wrote so many petitions.
What...
It's different.
Just hold on! Just bear it for a little.
Geom!
It's alright. It's alright.
-There. There!
-It's alright.
Just hold on for a bit.
Hey! Hey!
Aigoo! Just hold on
Hold on!
Look here!
He was in a coma for the whole night and at dawn he...
He looks like he has been wounded for at least 3 days.
He didn't treat the wound well so it developed an infection, which I believe is what killed him.
He's from Shim Gi Won's house?
Yes.
We just confirmed it.
But, why
Sir... from the corpse's ankle...
Hong is busy now?
I've never seen you around.
Your little brother is looking for you.
You found the wrong person.
I don't have a younger brother.
Someone called Yong from Hanyang is looking for you.
He said you would know if I told you it's from Geom.
How did you.
Geom?
Come here!
-Why are you doing this?
-Come here!
Did you not hear?
Take your clothes off now!
We neither saw money in the Commander's pocket nor stole it.
This low class thing...
How dare you glare at me?
Someone...
saw one of you...
steal the money.
Right?
Of course. My own two eyes,
I witnessed it.
This one is being difficult.
Undress her first!
My prize is about to get away.
If this continues, my work will be wasted.
Leave me alone! Let me go!
Sorry to disturb you.
I think there's a problem with the pickled fish.
You!
I must leave, go inside and bring it to me.
Let's go.
Don't you see I'm looking for a thief?
We're going to check the pickled fish and come right back.
-You punk!
-This guy...
Why this jerk...
I can stand anything.
But if someone touches my head, I go crazy!
You jerk!
You haven't tasted what it really means to "pour oil on the flame", have you?
You can't handle my one fist, but bully everyone.
Are you all right?
Yes
Let's continue our conversation.
That's him.
What a brave guy!
You will die today!
Stop hitting! Stop!
Move aside!
I'm going to bury this jerk!
I'll undress.
Really? I guess Nobles are smart.
They grasp the situation quick.
But if you don't find the money, I'll petition the magistrate to punish you.
What did you say?
Us, why?
If you don't find any money on me,
It proves he is guilty of lying!
Ok Ok! One minute.
Let's not ruin our future
just trying to get her naked.
You guys, let's go! It's a misunderstanding.
Hey, what's this...
Wait and see,
I'll get you for this.
Are you all right?
Aigoo
I'm sorry.
You got involved because of me
What?
No, it's not!
It's in my nature to stop unfairness.
But you and our Geom are...
That is...
He's like a brother to me.
There are no secrets between us. That cute boy!
Really?
Thank you.
Listen, tonight
Come to the Deokchan Harbor at eleven. Nobody must know.
Yong, no, Geom and I will wait for you with a boat.
You don't need to worry.
You can live with your brother from now on.
Come here!
Let me go!
Your brother...
is looking for you.
I see.
Of course he is.
My mouth will stay shut if you behave well.
This wench!
Just kill me!
Fine. That's enough.
But how can I only kill you?
He's waiting at Deokchan harbor right?
I'm begging you
Follow me!
I'm...
Friend!
You've come.
Where is she?
Your sister?
How do you...
Don't worry. I'll help you both.
Let's go!
By the way,
Thank you.
I'll never forget this kindness.
I didn't do it for you.
I heard everything from Hunter Jang.
I planned to call you here, turn you in to the authorities and collect my reward.
But my heart changed.
Why?
That is...
You know, your sister is that kind of person...
You know, the kind of person you just want to help. She knows how to change people's hearts.
I'm going crazy.
Thank you.
Sure, be thankful.
All that reward money...
This guy! You...call me Brother from now on.
Got it?
Brother
Who are you?
Aigoo, you work hard.
We're merchants from Bong Hwa market.
What are you doing here?
We must catch the first boat out in the morning to arrive at the market.
We have no where to sleep, so we sit here drinking, killing time.
By chance, have you seen a suspicious woman here?
Suspicious woman?
A slave beat a guard down and ran away.
What? How could such a thing...
Geom!
Sister!
Let me go!
Do you want to die? To die horribly?
But my sister's over there!
She's being chased!
If you go after her right now, her life will really be doomed.
If she's not caught by now,
I'm sure she ran far away.
I'll search the area here
with some people.
You just go up first.
Thank you Brother,
Don't worry.
I'll contact you soon.
I'm going to leave.
Now that I think about it,
She may have gone to Hanyang.
I told her you were living in Hanyang!
Geez...
She's so pretty!
You two look alike.
You'll recognize each other as soon as you meet.
That's blood.
Yong
That man died.
He died?
Yes as soon as you left, the authorities came and took his body.
By any chance...
Did he say anything before he died?
No, he just called "Geom, Geom"
Then he died.
But who is this Geom?
Is it good news?
The civil exam is in two days.
Two days?
That fast?
You didn't know?
Yeah
Yong didn't say anything.
Does Dani know?
But this little brat...
That brat.
You brat, come here! Come here!
What? Why?
Come here!
Let me see some exam papers.
Ah, Yong is taking the civil exam?
Yes
Wait...
It's here, grass paper.
Do you have anything better?
Of course, I have Ja Moon paper.
But it's very expensive. Only noble families can afford it.
Yes..
The exam is in two days
But you're still out playing around without me knowing about it?
It's all about using your basic skills.
Do you think cramming it all in would do it?
Be quiet!
Read another page if you're talking! Hurry!
Hurry!
Dani, the exam is the day after tomorrow. You didn't know either, did you?
What's this?
I did some sewing, but they said they didn't have money
and gave me this useless piece of paper.
It's so soft.
Yong! You need to have paper for your exam, huh?
You can take this.
Hey.. this is expensive paper.
Only noblemen can afford to us this!
Mother!  I can really have it?
That's amazing! I'm going to go show it off.
Hey! Where are you going?!
That rotten brat!
That--
Wait, Ja Dol must be taking it too.
Brother hasn't come back yet.
There wasn't any other news?
Thanks.
Sister... where are you?
This is a special exam.  You have only one chance to pass.
You'd better not miss this chance. You're not going to have another like this one.
You are a prestigious person.
Maybe you could use your influence...
You bastard!
Play fair!
Win on your own merit.
This is the will of His Majesty, and I agree.
There shouldn't be any illegal activities.
This is the exact order from His Majesty.
Also, this is what I feel.
Yes, yes.
I understand His Majesty's will.
If somehow...
Should you fail and Shi Hoo should pass,
I will erase your name from our family records.
Just know that.
You bought it?
You bought that paper for Yong, didn't you?
Stop speaking nonsense.
Ja Dol is taking the exam tomorrow, you know.
A toothless idiot
bought candy for him.
Are you praying for Ja Dol or for Yong?
This is to wish you good luck on your exam.
It's fine.
I should use what I normally use. If I use something my hand is not used to...
It's nice.
Go home please. You are ruining my image.
Am I going into battle here?
I'm really losing face. Go!
Okay okay, do well on your test okay.
This will help you relax.
I'm not nervous.
You're not nervous?
My heart is racing inside.
You're really not nervous?
I'm not nervous. I'm not nervous so could you please just wait for me over there?
Yong...
Yong!
Ta-da!
Our Yong, Hooray!
Ja!
Yong is the winner!
Yong...
Yo...
Father! What is this?
Why are you so stupid?
Yong is the winner!
Yong, Hooray!
G-go!
Hooray!
Hooray! Hooray!
Aigoo... what a useless show.
Life is quite interesting...They even let a dog take the exam now.
Where is it? Where? Where is this dog?
This bastard.
Brother!
Yong, I found your sister.
Minister of Military, Lord Byun Sik
47, 50, complete
If your number is called, step this way. The rest, stand over there.
What's that? Why are they standing there?
They're sons of noblemen.
This side?
We're half-bloods and average people.
This is too much.
Noblemen get to shoot riding cows, and we have to do it on horseback?
That's not fair.
If you're unhappy then leave! Hurry!
Let's start.
Hit the bullseye!
She must have been starving. Looked like a beggar.
I found her stuffing her face in the kitchen.
Are you her brother?
You look like her.
She said she came to Hanyang looking for her mother and her brother.
Mother?
She said she was seperated from her mother too when she was young.
She was taken as a slave,
and her mother became a gisaeng. She cried her eyes out telling me the story.
Aigoo..
You should have come just a little earlier.
Where did she go?
I...
I gave her some stolen goods.
She must be going through gisaeng houses in Hanyang, looking for her mother.
Kibang?
Number 230!
Yes.
It's a hit!
They said you screwed up!
What happened?
Thought you'd pass for sure.
Don't feel too bad.
A bastard will never get a government position anyway.
Didn't you know?
Oh, you didn't know.
Don't feel too bad about that either.
Those who perform a glorious feat
on the battlefield.
Even if they're bastards, may enter the court.
But, what to do.
To get you to a high position.
You can't create war.
What should you do?
What should you do, huh?
I'll just be out for a while.
Ok. Play as much as you want today.
Wait a second. I bought something tasty.
What's wrong with him? Did he mess up his exam?
It's not been posted yet so don't worry too much about it.
Why are you going in and out of here.
Is it that wrong to go in and out of my brother's room?
A brother?
Go bring Shi Wan.
Let me ask you something.
Is there a girl selling goods around?
Young master!
Don't they do business here?
You're here, young master?
Young master Shi Wan took everyone out to the lantern festival.
You should go in and wait. The wind is pretty cold.
It's alright.
They are going to go crazy over this.
Excuse me, by any chance...
Is there a gisaeng who used to be a servant? She's about 40 years old.
Who used to be a servant?
Let's see, no I don't think so.
Could you get me a cup of water?
What brings you here?
A Gwanbi slave caused some trouble and ran away.
Where is the washroom again?
Young master, did you see a strange girl?
What's wrong?
Some slave girl caused some trouble and ran away, and it's an emergency country wide.
I didn't see her.
I understand.
Where did you go?
I went to the washroom.
Are you leaving? He will come soon.
I'll come back later.
Isn't he handsome?
He's the minister's bastard son.
If Geom grew up nice.
He would look noble too.
Anyways, a bastard
can't get a position at the government anyway even if he passes the exam.
Stop right there!
Preview Episode 7