♪I intentionally bump into you
and test you by teasing you♪
♪Your fingertips
are beating the drumbeat of my heart♪
♪Your teasing eyes on my lips♪
♪What a game of extreme flirting♪
♪I play along with you,
pulling and teasing♪
♪Your wrist brushing past my waist♪
♪A force that is too intense♪
♪A prelude that is too ambiguous♪
♪Your eyes are invading my lips♪
♪The breathing gradually
becomes mysterious♪
♪Crossing the red lines one by one♪
♪No more resisting love♪
[Indulgence]
[Based on fanqienovel.com's work
'Desire to Flirt' by Red Hat]
[Episode 25]
Why am I in the hospital?
Are you awake?
You were involved in a traffic accident.
Someone sent you here.
Then...
What about my child?
Is my child all right?
The child is lost.
What?
You...
Calm down.
What do you mean the child is lost?
Tell me what you mean.
You were involved in a traffic accident.
The situation was serious.
We had to do it to save you.
Who allowed you to do that?
Who agreed with it?
Return my child to me!
Return my child!
Calm down.
Here.
Sit down.
He is not picking up his calls
and his door is unlocked.
Did something happen to Qiu Yu?
Qiu Yu.
Qiu Yu!
What is this?
This is...
A listening device.
Listening device?
Listen to this.
Wei.
I know many hackers nowadays
can hear other people's phones remotely
to steal information
or listen to what they say.
Qiu Yu was listening to my calls.
I trusted him.
Why did he do this?
I know.
You've been treating Qiu Yu
as your younger brother
but this person is dangerous.
You must guard against him.
Tuan and Qiu Yu are both missing.
We looked everywhere.
Why don't we call the police?
They are not missing
for more than 24 hours.
We can't make a police report.
Let's wait a while longer.
What if something happens to Tuan?
Don't be too anxious.
Rest for a while.
Perhaps there will be news of Tuan
when you wake up.
[If you want to meet Tuan,
come to Warehouse No.2 alone.]
Tuan!
Qiu Yu.
Qiu Yu, where are you?
Yu.
I'm going out.
Wait for me at home.
Wei, I found Tuan.
Qiu Yu, where is Tuan?
Warehouse No. 2.
But they said
they wanted the SD card in your necklace
to exchange for her.
SD card?
Wei, come here quickly!
Tuan is in danger.
Ask them not to hurt Tuan,
I'm coming over immediately.
Yu, I found Tuan.
She's at Warehouse No. 2,
come over immediately.
Tuan!
Qiu Yu.
Didn't you say you've found Tuan?
Where's Tuan?
Wei, you are here.
Tell me.
Did your father kidnap Tuan?
Wei,
calm down.
Come here.
Come.
Stand here.
I prepared a gift for you.
Look.
Zhao Yibin?
Don't you want to know
the truth behind your parents' accident?
I've solved it.
I'll say it.
His father, Qiu Sheng,
asked me to mess with
the Bai family's car
and said it was
just to cause a small accident.
I was worried
and followed behind them.
In the end, Qiu Sheng used a truck
to force the Bai family and
Xu family to crash into each other.
That's murder!
I have nothing to do with this.
I beg you.
Can you let me go?
I see.
Wei,
you know the truth now.
I've also avenged you.
Let's go abroad
and live a life without worries,
all right?
I won't leave.
I want the real murderer
to be punished by law.
Wei,
you will never win against him.
He can use any means possible.
I don't want you to get hurt.
Wei.
It's your father, right?
Qiu Yu.
Qiu Sheng is your father.
Everything you did
was to cover up his crime.
No, Wei. Listen to me.
Listen to me.
I have nothing to do with him.
I just want to protect you.
Protect me?
You listened to my conversations
and kidnapped Tuan to threaten me.
Is that what you call protecting me?
Wei, I had no choice.
I had no choice.
Please believe me, Wei.
Qiu Yu,
why did you become someone like this?
Yes. Why did I become someone like this?
I was dumped at an orphanage
as soon as I was born.
I was bullied.
One day, I found my biological mother
and my biological father.
Did you know how happy I was?
I wanted to tell the whole world
that I had parents.
But when I first returned home
and saw my mother for the first time,
she was already crazy
from being tortured
by that devilish man.
Do you know that?
She didn't recognise me.
She no longer needed me.
♪Hidden clouds,
dim light falling on the back♪
♪The solitary bench at the street corner
shelters emotions♪
♪The moon's trajectory in the night sky♪
♪Is mending my sad heart♪
♪My courage to get close to you♪
♪Stops me from running away♪
♪The wheel of fate is turning,
and we meet again♪
♪Piecing our memories desperately♪
♪Love takes us by surprise♪
♪The you in the photo album♪
♪Are shining in the past like stars♪
♪You are in the light and shadow♪
♪Melting all my fear away♪
♪Those youthful memories
are healing enough♪
♪That I become obsessed with them♪
♪The world is suddenly full of meanings♪
♪Walking through the rain,
I have found you♪
♪In between the embrace♪
♪Are the stars
scattered across the horizon♪