Oh, this is annoying
She's impossible
Ugh
There she is
Darn it
Excuse me
Oh
What?
It was you?
Darn it
(Hello)
(Is the wallet still for sale?)
(Yes, it is)
(How much are you
willing to come down to?)
(How much are you willing to pay?)
Ugh, she's such a slow responder
Seriously?
(I think I see a scratch in the buckle)
(Can I get a closer look?)
(You'd need to take
50,000 won off for that)
(Can you do that???)
Come on
(It's the start of the semester
so I'm short on money)
(My friend gifted it to me)
(but I lost it...)
(and I feel so sorry to her)
(Can you please reconsider?)
(I need that same wallet)
(Sorry, I have a buyer who's
willing to buy it at the listed price)
Oh, darn it
(Actually, the thing about
my friend was a lie)
(I really wanted to buy that
so I saved money for a month)
(I really wanted to have it
so I worked part-time in telecom sales,)
(at the supermarket,
and I also distributed flyers)
(Please???)
Come on
Please, please
Please
(Eunvely sent you a message)
(Okay, I'll give you
a 50,000 won discount)
Yay
You should've said that earlier
Baby, I'll see you soon
How pretty
Was it you, Sae-na?
I would've given it for free
if I knew it was you
Oh
You can take it
Hey, I have money, too
This doesn't even cost that much
You don't have to
I haven't used it for over two years
I didn't even think
someone would buy this
It's from an old season
I was going to donate it to a flea market
I'm perfectly fine
It's not as pretty in real life
I'm not buying it
Bye
Oh, this is so embarrassing
(Episode 3)
Is he the guy you mentioned last time?
Yes
He looks better in real life, doesn't he?
Can he sing?
Or dance?
Well...
if he can't do both,
just send him to the other place
Throw that away on your way out
Soo-bin
Tomorrow's your pay day
but you still haven't sent me
a copy of your bank account and ID card
Can you...
please pay me in cash?
That would complicate the paperwork
I have my reasons
You can pay me less
Please do me a favor
You're not
a student at Hankuk Arts University,
are you?
Why are you here?
You don't have to come here anymore
Where are you going?
You don't have to know
Joo Sun-jae, pick up your phone
You're the only one
wearing noise-canceling headphones
You should put your phone
on silent mode or turn it off
I'm leaving
Hi
You're Moon Ye-ji
Since the door is open,
I'll let myself in
(This is crazy)
(Ye-ji is in Sun-jae's studio!)
Time for school
Hey!
You trash
What?
Trash
You're cute
Hey!
Did you smoke in the hallway again?
I can't believe this
Come out for a second
You should go to school
Have you ever gone to school
with a cat?
I'm Ok-sun, and I'm lonely!
Let's go to school!
Ugh, what's wrong with her?
- Hi
You're here again
Did you go to Sun-jae's again today?
Yeah
I go there every day
I might win the perfect attendance award
You're putting in so much effort
Joo Sun-jae
Oh!
"Please find Joo Sun-jae"?
Joo Sun-jae
Sae-na, let me see
Your lips look beautiful
That color is so you
Where did you get it?
- Isn't it pretty?
- It is
It's so pretty
It's no.3 Dragon Planet
Let's buy that on our way home
We have to
Ju-hyuk
Yes?
How do I look today?
Incredible
I'm so pretty
Sae-na
Is your ideal type
still a good-looking guy?
Of course!
(But you're looking right at him)
(Does Sae-na have poor vision?)
How many fingers am I showing?
Joo Sun-jae seemed
pretty handsome last time
Does he have a girlfriend?
I don't know
- Why isn't Sun-jae coming to school?
- Joo Sun-jae
Joo Sun-jae
No, I like Tae-jun
When is Tae-jun coming?
Choi Tae-jun
Choi Tae-jun, Joo Sun-jae
Hi
Were you waiting for me?
Of course, not
I know
Trash
I told you I'm not trash
Do you have no social skills?
Hey
You shouldn't say
things like that to anyone
especially me
You're already in trouble
Sungwon Villa Room 203
What do you think will happen
if I upload this?
Everyone is wondering who you are
What's wrong?
(I told you I had no choice)
What are you doing?
(I told you I was sorry)
Let's skip school today
There's this place I go to
every Wednesday
Let's skip school and go there today
Open the door
Just once, come on
Let's get some air
Your mind is full of this right now
He looks thrown off
Hello
Hi
This does look a bit stuffy, I know
Where's the guy you used to
come here every week with?
Who's the new face?
Did you get a new boyfriend?
I told you he's not my boyfriend
And
he's not my boyfriend, either
We should clean that up first, right?
Yes
Please do a good job like you always do
Sure
Thanks
Think of this place as your mind
and empty it
Let's go!
What?
You'll have to work all day at this pace
Do they have bowel problems?
Their poo is so stiff
What was it I had to feed them?
#I found Joo Sun-jae
Sun-jae changed his number
Stop calling
How about doing this in this part?
Play that again
Da-eun
We won't be able to win like this
What do you mean?
You can't focus at all
Are you in a bad mood today?
Everything
got complicated
I don't drink plain milk
Oh
But it's good
Go away
You can't eat this, anyway
Hey, don't stroke him
Why?
You're getting his hopes up
You can't even take responsibility
but you're pretending to be kind
and making him expect you
to always be there
You're giving him false hope
I don't like that
He might not want you
to take responsibility
He might just want
a warm touch at this moment
Looking away right now
may hurt him even more
Right?
If you can be so considerate to dogs,
can you be more considerate to me, too?
Please
How did you do that?
By being flexible
Why are you in Ye-ji's seat?
Because she's not here yet
Sae-na, I knew it
You're practicing really hard
I should practice harder, too
Why would you say that?
Because your shoes are worn out
They're vintage
You!
Soo-bin, you're here
I haven't seen you two
together in a while
I know, right?
You were always talking about Joo
- Sun
- Jae
these days
No, I wasn't
We met in the hallway
Oh, right
Joo Sun-jae
Is he performing with you?
Probably
Probably?
Why do you sound uncertain?
Isn't today the last day of applications?
Today
You have to submit
the application in person
He'll be here
Sun-jae will be here
Let's wait
Hi, guys
Hello
Good morning
Who's submitting their applications?
- Me
- Okay
- Are you performing, too?
- Yes
Sir!
Good morning
Yes, it's a wonderful morning
But you troublemakers
should go back to your class now
We're not troublemakers
We're artists
Fine, off you go now
- Hurry up
- They're hilarious
You know today's the last day
to apply for the arts festival, right?
Yes
Have you all submitted
your applications?
Anybody left?
No, right?
- No
Oh
Moon Ye-ji
Have you finally gotten back
to your senses?
But who are you performing with?
Probably Soo-bin
Yes, Cha Soo-bin
But Soo-bin is performing with Da-eun
Really?
- Oh
- Whoa
- Joo Sun-jae is here
- Isn't that Joo Sun-jae?
That's Joo Sun-jae
He's actually here
He's even performing
at the arts festival
No way
Oh, okay
Hey, I got something
You, too?
I got a picture
What's this?
(Snap and Spark)