(This program is intended for mature audiences.
It may feature explicit content, violence, and strong language.)
(Hello.)
(Welcome to our hotel.)
(Here, every couple will experience romance)
(and unforgettable memories.)
(May)
(recently broke up with her boyfriend two months ago.)
(Tong)
(is May's ex that she's trying to forget.)
(Both returned to the hotel by chance.)
(But tonight, there's a reservation error.)
(And there's some kind of energy)
(that makes them open up and end up in the same room.)
(And room number 207, unlike any other room,)
(holds some secret.)
(What is this box?)
And where did it come from?
Huh?
It's locked with a code?
Read it.
Unlocks it.
(Unlocks it. Password: The day we met)
The day we met is the password.
The day we met.
Does it mean us?
I don't know.
But
try it.
The day we met.
April 11th.
Then...
One.
Four.
(Thank you for coming here. To discover the truth,
open the next box. Password: The day of love confession)
Thank you for coming here.
To discover the truth,
open the next box.
Password is the day of love confession.
The day I was brave to confess love to you.
May 22nd.
No.
Tong.
What?
There is someone.
Did the lights go out?
- I don't see anything.
- I really saw someone earlier.
Nothing there at all.
There's nothing there.
It's okay.
I'm right here.
We broke up already.
Don't touch me.
May,
why are you being so cold to me?
Our relationship
ended a long time ago.
But I still love you.
I saw the lights flickering earlier.
So I came to see what was happening.
Ma'am, you got here just in time.
I saw a strange shadow earlier.
So, you found the box.
Do you know this box?
I know it well.
It's mine.
Would you like to come in first?
Many decades ago,
I stayed in this room with my husband.
It is mine.
(Honey.)
(Smile, please.)
You're the most beautiful in the world.
You always say such sweet things, honey.
Thank you for marrying me.
I'll take care of you forever.
(This will be the box for our memories.)
We'll keep all our good memories in this box.
What if one day we forget about it?
Then we'll come back and open it together again,
and we'll remember it all over again.
(My husband)
had an accident.
A car crash on the day he went out
to buy flowers for me.
(Where did you go, honey?)
Honey, what's wrong?
Honey.
Honey, stay with me. Please, honey.
I never even had the chance
to thank him,
or to apologize
for our fight before he had to go.
But...
Why does it need a passcode?
Some memories
shouldn't be opened until you're ready.
Ma'am, what day was it when your husband
first told you he loved you?
It was
July 2nd.
It's
the same day as ours.
Two.
Zero.
Seven.
Sorry for not having the courage to tell you the truth.
The truth is, I'm afraid of losing you.
Why does it
feel like our relationship?
May.
I'm really sorry.
I was scared
of tying you down.
I was afraid I wasn't enough.
But I thought
that you weren't serious about us.
There's a ghost!
Honey.
You're back, aren't you?
He won't hurt anyone.
Don't be afraid.
He just wants the last box opened.
What's the passcode?
Password.
The day we were ready to be together.
Forever.
May.
I'm ready now.
Ready to stay with you forever.
February 28th.
(Thank you for loving me. Thank you for forgiving me,
and for having the courage to start over)
Thank you for loving me.
Thank you for forgiving me,
and for having the courage to start over.
I prepared them for whoever finds this box.
The one who dares to love.
The one who dares to forgive.
And...
The one who dares to give thanks.
I might not be perfect.
And I promise
to love you with all my heart,
and never let you go again.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
Good morning.
Was last night
just a dream?
It was all real.
Believe it now?
Did you see him?
I did.
Their love lives on.
♪In this room where shadows fall♪
♪Where your soul still walks the hall♪
♪Though you're gone, you're here with me♪
♪Love lives on eternally♪