(Previously)
Is this the guy you owe money to, Nant?
How did you get this laptop?
The guy who had the laptop
said he found it at his dorm,
which is near Playboyy.
The person he was doing
a sex call with must be at that dorm.
He could be a host at Playboyy.
A no-name actor is exposed.
He has been having sex with strangers.
He has been having cybersex.
(Live video is starting soon)
I'm back.
First, I would like to thank
a generous fan who got me a new laptop.
The one I just bought broke after a day,
so I haven't been online.
Do you miss me?
If you do, send me a gift.
(Can you take off your pants?)
(I want you to stand)
(You're cute)
(Take it off)
Take it off.
Which one?
The top or the bottom?
(So horny)
(Can we meet?)
(Go lower)
Go lower.
Lower?
(Take it off)
(Take your pants off)
(I want to see more)
I need to see some cash
to be motivated to go lower.
(Is your new laptop good?)
Guys.
The donor just texted me.
He's so sweet.
(Let's do a private call
in case you want more)
I'm sorry.
I need to go.
If you miss me,
you can send me gifts.
Bye.
(Nuthyyim91 is Calling)
Hello.
What's your name?
Nuth.
Are you Phop?
Yes, are you Nuth?
You bought me a new laptop.
You won't come online without a laptop.
I'm glad we finally get to talk.
We've been chatting for a long time.
Wow.
Do you like me that much?
Yeah, I haven't even seen your dick.
Is it huge?
Do you want to see it?
If you do...
Done.
I transferred via the app.
Let me see how much you shaved.
Show me your face too.
That's so hot.
So sexy.
Call my name.
Nuth.
Yes, Nuth.
That's so hot.
Hey.
(Lollipop69 blocked you)
(Successful money transfer)
(Mom, I got my bonus)
(I'll give it to you,
give some money to my siblings)
I'm not proud of myself.
Anyone would say it's disgraceful.
But I wasn't born rich.
This is the only way
to make my life better.
At least my mother and siblings
will have a good life.
"Playboyy The Series"
(Episode 4: All about feelings)
Shit.
Captain.
This is so dope.
I respect you.
Your girlfriend is so hot.
Her boobs are bouncy.
Hey, that's his girlfriend.
From now on, we'll believe you entirely.
You are one of us.
I'll talk to Keen
and ask him to make you a starter
and join the next match.
Her moves are sick. Look at her waist.
- So horny.
- Shit.
So hot.
His girlfriend is so fair.
Look at her boobs.
(Thank you, guys
I've completed my mission)
(I'm now a rugby player
for the university)
(Awesome)
(Amazing)
(Good job bro!)
(Hey, you've been quiet
How are you? Why won't you come home?)
Captain.
I need to talk to you.
How could you do that?
- Do what?
- The clip.
Does your girlfriend know
that you were filming?
What a stupid idiot.
I thought he found out that I was acting.
Of course.
The camera was so close.
Does she know
you showed it to your friends?
I knew it. She doesn't know.
You can't do that.
You're violating her rights.
Puen.
Why are you such a good person?
I just showed the seniors.
I didn't sell the clip.
I have to act like them
when I'm with them
or they'll think I'm a pussy like you.
If you know the real me,
you won't think I'm a pussy.
Be gentle. It hurts.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean it.
Do you want me to suck your nipples
so you can come faster?
That's enough. Let's just stop.
Okay then.
Honestly.
Am I that unfuckable?
No, I just need a little help.
If I don't take enough orders,
I don't get enough money.
If I take many orders,
then I run out of juice.
Let me ask you something.
Have you been hard with a client
without any help?
Well...
Sometimes.
It depends on how I feel.
Some guys are so handsome,
but I don't get turned on by them.
That's enough.
I didn't make you come.
I have to go.
(#Massageformen)
(#Hotguy #Needajob
# Massageformen #Massageforwomen)
(Are you available?)
Zouey, are you asleep?
Look at me.
Yeah.
Do you think I can sleep?
Are you thinking about him?
Yeah, you?
Hey.
I think...
What if he's not doing it for the money?
He doesn't have to like me.
What if he doesn't like sex with me?
Do you understand
that it's hard to find
another person who likes BDSM?
Yeah.
You have a point.
Keep talking.
Well...
When I wasn't living with him
and we didn't meet often,
I was excited.
But...
When I moved in with him
and we were together all the time,
I felt like
I got bored.
Do you think it's possible?
Yeah.
Of course.
I told you.
He might not be dating you
for your money.
Maybe he was...
You weren't exclusive.
Free sex.
Yeah.
Then what I said to him was mean.
Hey, wait.
Where are you going?
I'm going to do the right thing.
I'm going to apologize.
I'm going to tell him how I feel.
Looking like that?
Thank you.
I have to go.
- Wear some pants.
- Okay.
I really don't understand you guys.
- What's the first rule of this job?
- I know.
Don't fall in love with the client.
I don't know
if I think of him as a client.
Don't say "true love" and "soulmate."
It's not true love.
But we just get along.
Get along?
Like him?
You can get along with other people.
Not just the doctor's son.
Why don't you find someone
in the BDSM group?
I have something to tell you, Soong.
The guy I'm seeing
is friends with the doctor's son.
I heard him say
that he wanted to die because of you.
I don't care if you love him or not.
You can't just
be ignorant about it, right?
You should be responsible
for his feelings.
(I'm here, how should I start?)
(Just be true to your feelings)
What?
What happened?
First is coming.
I'm sure he's trying to make it up to me.
I'm going back to him.
Hold on, what for?
Get over him.
It's impossible.
Even though we're just sex buddies,
we can't be in
a monogamous relationship.
I think it's possible.
Try being in love.
What stupid love?
You first got a smart watch.
You sold the ring you stole.
You almost got him to buy an apartment.
You're just being a leech.
Don't overthink it.
If he's acting out or he's heartbroken,
just let him be.
Ignore him.
Find a new baby
and share your income with me.
Why did you do this?
Huh? Why did you lie to me?
Why?
Why did you do this?
You lied to me.
You lied.
Why did you do this?
Why did you do this, Soong?
You lied to me.
You lied.
How could you do this?
Tell me, Soong.
Why did you do this?
How are you?
You've been here for days.
Yeah.
I still can't get over it.
It's such a big deal.
Why do you like wearing a mask?
So others don't see
my facial expressions.
It allows me to be who I truly am.
It's easier that way.
Really?
- You can be the sadist that you are.
- Yes.
You like that, don't you?
Choose which one you want.
Don't you have the dog mask?
I'm not that kinky.
Even though he doesn't have the dog mask,
it isn't guaranteed
that he isn't Nuthyim91.
I must find out the truth.
Today...
Do you want to switch roles, Master?
Nant.
This isn't what we agreed on.
Really?
- Then why did you do it to me?
- I never did.
Nant, what the hell is wrong with you?
You're scaring me.
We don't use weapons.
- The contract is clear about that.
- What contract?
You drafted and signed it yourself.
How can you forget something like this?
Who are you?
Tell me where the contract is.
Tell me or I'll slit your throat.
You know I'm not afraid to.
(Slave and Master Agreement)
Why do you not know about the contract?
Nant knows about it.
You're not him.
Tell me who you are
and what happened to Nant.
Are these the guys
Nant was involved with?
Yes, who should we start with?
They were hosts at the Playboyy.
These three guys
have resigned.
But they were hot for awhile.
That's why First got conned.
There's an old apartment building
behind the bar.
Aob, Teena, Soong, and Jump live there.
After your brother met Aob,
I saw him walking out of this building
with Teena, Soong, and Jump.
He knows all three of them.
So what?
Why do you think they're Nuthyim91?
I don't know if they are.
But your brother was a drug addict.
That's why he was in debt
and signed the contract with me.
So he would get cash for drugs.
I saw these three men doing drugs
in the bar's locker room.
- Maybe...
- One of them sold drugs to him.
(I want to clear the air with you)
What are you going to do?
I'll do anything to find out the truth.
Do you want add-on services?
If you rush it,
I'll only give you 500 baht.
Let me fuck you for 2,000 baht.
What?
Your dick is huge. I can't take it.
Let me fuck you.
Wait.
Do you have a condom?
I don't like wearing it.
Don't worry.
- I can come outside.
- Hey.
No, it's risky.
I don't care
if you like wearing it or not.
Sex workers
get diseases because of people like you.
I'm sorry. I'm not in the mood anymore.
I'm sorry. I can give you a handjob.
It's okay. Let's just stop.
Give me the QR code.
(I have to pay for your sibling's tuition)
Sex workers aren't the only ones
conning people.
Sometimes clients con us too.
We can't sue them.
We just have to accept it.
(This is Nuth,
I'm so upset that you blocked me)
(You don't realize
how long I've been watching you)
(I donated and sent gifts to you
and you make me so happy)
(Looking at you before bed
makes me sleep well)
(You must find it strange
that a stranger is so crazy about you)
(But it's how I feel)
(Let's talk, I have a job offer for you)
(I'm sorry, I didn't mean to block you)
(I accidentally blocked you,
what's the job offer?)
(Shoot a movie with me as the director)
(If you're interested,
come to this location)
(Here is the deposit,
you'll get the rest after we're done)
(10,000 baht deposited)
I didn't think I'll meet you again.
How have you been?
I'm good.
Excuse me.
How did we meet?
Hey.
At the dorm.
- At Soong's place.
- Really?
How do I know Soong?
It's loud here.
We can't talk.
Let's go back to my place.
It's easier to talk.
I have a bed and other stuff.
I'm not drunk yet.
He knows Nant, but he isn't surprised.
That means he doesn't know
that Nant is missing.
He is probably not involved.
But he might know something.
I'm sorry, Zouey.
I have to do this.
I don't have feelings for him.
Hello, Zouey.
Come here now.
If you don't do anything,
your dream will just be an imagination.
But a fulfilled dream
is something only the rich can achieve.
Hello.
It's Nuth.
I'm sorry. I need some money.
I didn't spend it on guys.
Please.
Let me borrow one more time.
Then...
I'll sell you the stuff.
But...
Please give me more percentages.
Of course. Thank you.
Send me the location.
Okay.
So?
Where is Nant?
Huh?
Are you going to tell me or not?
Where is Nant?
Do you know Nant?
You're here.
Figure it out.
Hey.
I know we didn't end on good terms.
Let's clear the air.
Let's not do this.
You started this mess.
You wouldn't have sex with me.
But you slept with someone else.
Huh?
Hold on.
Who did I sleep with?
I'm sad.
I think about you all day.
How could you do this to me?
You act like a virgin.
- But you are a whore.
- Hey.
You're not making any sense.
You're high, aren't you?
I don't know what you're high on.
But I never slept with anyone.
You can't get back at me
by making out with my friend.
I can make out with anyone.
We are not a couple.
You have no right to be jealous.
You know they're dangerous,
why did you get involved with them?
I tried to find out
- what they did to my brother.
- By making out with them?
Was it necessary?
Are you jealous?
No.
Do you care about my brother?
I...
I'm worried about you.
I don't want you to be in danger.
That's not true.
Were you dating my brother?
Did you like him?
You killed him
because he messed around with them?
This isn't a thriller.
It was nothing.
I didn't like your brother.
I guess I was just protective of him.
Because I made a contract with him
to be his master.
I'm not your slave.
Even though my face looks like his
and my voice sounds like his,
I am not him.
Feel free to help me find my brother.
But don't cross the line with me.
This is the last song.
Please leave after it's over.
Everything comes to an end.
This song.
This bar.
My relationship.
Your relationship
with the pizza delivery boy.
And everything
started because
Captain wanted us to have sex.
Why do you like having sex?
You were rough the first time.
You know.
I just wanted to be bad like in the movies
because my life sucked.
But after trying it,
I realized that
just watching isn't enough.
What about you?
Why are you afraid to have sex?
You know.
But after meeting him,
I feel like I want to have sex with him.
But sex isn't enough.
I want his love.
Yeah.
I also want love.
In the end, it all comes down to love.
I'm sorry about your relationship.
He shouldn't have done that to you.
But I'm not sorry about yours.
He wouldn't have done that
if he didn't have any feelings for you.
I know consent is something
you're worried about.
I just think
that you guys
just misunderstood each other.
Wait.
I never slept with anyone.
Why does he think differently?
Think about it.
Shit.
Captain's clip.
How did he see that?
You should ask him.
But I think that's the reason.
Zouey.
My relationship is over.
But yours is still hopeful.
Let me ask you something.
What's your feeling right now?
I'm hot.
I want him back.
Relax.
We'll just do some test shots today.
Tell me your name, age,
height, and weight.
I'm Phop.
I'm 20 years old.
I weigh 73 kilograms.
My height is 182 centimeters.
Okay.
Tell me about a sexual experience
and jerk off.
Are we shooting porn?
I've never had a boyfriend.
Let's just do it.
There are instructions
and prices on this board.
I'll show one at a time.
If you let me do it,
you'll get the money.
(Licking nipples)
(Sucking)
(Licking ass)
(Sucking until your eyes meet the camera)
(Kissing)
(Penetration)
Should we continue or not?
Who's wearing the condom?
Me.
Why? Are you scared?
Of what?
You were probably so drunk
you couldn't remember.
You were wasted that night.
You were hallucinating
and sleeping on the ground.
Soong found you.
You went back to his place.
So that's how we met.
I see.
What about Jump?
What kind of person is he?
What do you want?
Why are you asking about my friend?
Let's continue where we left off.
Tell me everything that happened.
Are you a friend of Zouey?
What do you really want?
I'm sorry.
I was wasted at the bar.
Now I can't do anything.
You should leave.
Hey.
You really want me to leave?
Be mad at me.
He already rejected me.
I'll wait for you at home.
It's not like that, Zouey.
He just wanted to have sex with me
because he wanted to know something.
- But I rejected.
- Shut up.
Sex is so important to you, huh?
- It's not like that.
- Fine.
What are you doing?
Come on.
- What are you doing?
- You want sex, don't you?
- Huh?
- You want sex so badly, don't you?
- What are you doing?
Come on.
- Let me go.
- You want it, don't you?
- Come on.
- Zouey.
Let's do it.
Zouey.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
- You want it, don't you?
- Stop.
- Stop it.
- I'm going to sleep with you.
Zouey.
It's so important, huh?
Sex.
- Come on.
- No, Zouey.
It's not like that.
- You want me, don't you?
- No, Zouey. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You are a terrible friend.
You.
I've never judged who you slept with.
But you can't sleep
with your friend's boyfriend.
I'm not your friend.
What the hell did you say?
- Hey.
- Calm down.
How could you say that?
It's true.
Zouey, listen to me.
Thank you for thinking of me as a friend
and for caring about me.
You said that I've changed
ever since I came back.
I seem more mature and I smoke.
I cook and I don't drink beer.
What?
What the hell are you talking about?
I'm actually not your friend.
I'm not Nant.
I'm his twin brother.
Nont.
What the hell?
Feelings.
Feelings make us humans.
The feeling of disappointment.
The feeling of hopefulness.
Phop.
Even though I don't have any money,
I have stuff.
The feeling of expectation.
The feeling of hopefulness.
But it doesn't matter
what feelings we have.
We should not feel hopeless.
Especially when it comes to
feeling hopeless to humanity.
(Next Episode) Nant was involved
with three sex workers at Playboyy.
One of them made him a drug addict
and had debts.
Are you sure you have no other secrets?
Those three guys
are your crush,
your pizza delivery boy,
and your employee at the car wash shop.
How did you get here?
Who the hell are you?
It's hot.
Let go of me!