(Previously)
You said my brother committed suicide.
I'm begging you.
Please tell me what happened.
I terminated the contract.
You are my slave.
You want me to love you?
I'm doing just that.
Do you have the clip
when Nant and Nuth had a call
before he committed suicide?
Who knows?
It could have been a setup.
Your brother might still be alive.
- You must continue searching.
- I won't.
If he's alive
and not telling me anything,
that means he doesn't want to be found.
It must be a big deal
for you to come see me now.
Do you still have
the stuff I asked you to keep?
Good. Keep it well.
Don't throw it away.
Don't lose it.
Don't let anyone see it, Keen.
Embassy warns tourists going to Korea
about copycat crime.
Investigation on the drug case's
scapegoat is ongoing.
The culprit behind
the death of a saleswoman
shows signs of serial murder.
The housekeeper has been found guilty.
The police have found a naked John Doe
in the forest in Baan Bor Pae,
Tha Chang Subdistrict,
Bang Kalm District,
Songkhla province.
The police suspect...
Tha Chang Subdistrict,
Bang Kalm District,
Songkhla province.
The police suspect...
I've been having dreams about sleeping
with Nont and Nant at the same time.
The disturbing thing
isn't that I see Nant as Nont.
But I'm starting to forget Nant's face.
Because they're so alike
I can't tell them apart.
Right now I feel like
I like Nont more than Nant.
(Playboyy)
(Episode 9: The real person)
You're not so horrible after all.
You didn't have to act all cool.
You're lonely, aren't you?
You want to have friends, don't you?
Who said so?
I've been on my own for this long.
I'll keep living like this.
After working for a while,
you'll get it.
How long have you been working?
I started at 18.
Now I'm 34.
Do the math.
Shit.
You've been working for 16 years.
You'll be as old as my dad
in a few years.
I'm sorry.
Why do you do this job?
I grew up poor
and had to provide for myself.
I've done everything.
But after I gave this a try,
I started liking it.
So I never stopped.
What about you, Puen?
Why are you working at Playboyy?
I'm just like you.
I'm working to provide for myself.
But I'm not in it
for the long run like you.
I'll probably become
a professional athlete after graduating
and follow my dreams.
It's getting late.
Do you want to go to my place?
Let's drink.
(Private clips of athletes)
(A professional swimmer)
(Join the group now!
New clips every day)
(Hot, sweaty, ripped athletes!)
(250 baht for a lifetime subscription)
(Don't overthink it,
have some milk and go to bed)
(How do I subscribe to the group?)
(When are you posting a new clip?)
(I want to see his face clearly)
Captain.
What are you doing?
Captain!
You made a mess. Zouey will nag you.
I know.
What is it?
Your private group
only has clips of athletes, right?
What if I have a clip of someone famous?
Can I sell it to you?
Is he an athlete?
If he isn't, I know some guys.
No.
But I want to create buzz for him.
Can you help me?
Huh?
Help me.
(Tutor denies gay rumors)
(He says he loves
his mom the most)
(Tutor receives the journalist award
for promoting Thai culture)
(Wears Thai costumes to Korea)
Puen.
Yeah?
I had a sugar daddy.
But he was so jealous.
I just looked at a person on the street.
He sent his guys to beat that man up.
So I couldn't have a crush on anyone.
That sucks.
So that's why you never
show your emotions.
I really loved him.
But he got sick of me one day.
He told me to work here
and he got himself a new sugar baby.
I was so heartbroken then.
Now I'm old.
It's too late to be in love.
Hey.
I'll just be blunt.
You couldn't have boyfriend sex with me
because you like me, right?
Then I'll be blunt too.
You're flirting with me
and making me jealous
because you like me, right?
Yes.
Because you took my virginity.
Who is the winged goddess
whose beheaded statue
is at the Louvre Museum in Paris?
A.
Nike.
B, Adidas.
C, Puma.
D, Reebok.
Why are you learning this for?
Nike.
The Goddess of Victory.
The substance in
arachidonic acid,
metabolite,
which one
acts as
a chemotactic
stimuli?
What is a stimuli?
Is this human language?
They're pronounced
metabolite and stimuli.
Fuck it.
I'm tired.
Zouey.
Why do you think we learn these things?
Like math,
we have calculators.
-Like Thai,
- we already speak it.
Hey, Zouey.
If I go to the psychologist
and she says I'm a psycho,
what should I do?
Do you think Soong will dump me?
If he really loves you,
he'll stay with you
and help you get through it.
I went crazy last time.
What if he dumps me this time?
I don't know how fucked up I'll be.
What should I do?
Iced grande oat milk vanilla latte.
As usual, Tutor?
You remember.
I'll have that with two pumps of syrup.
Okay.
Iced grande americano.
Extra shot.
Dark roast.
No syrup.
Make it as bitter as my life.
The heir of Jeeli Group.
You're not as scary as I thought.
Why would I be scary around
a good person like you, Mr. Journalist?
I just want what's mine back.
Why would I have it?
Don't make me say it bluntly.
It might make the news.
Are you threatening me?
Try interpreting it.
I think a journalist
who promotes Thai culture
shouldn't be involved
with someone who's taken.
Don't you think so?
I think I'm doing a good job
preserving Thai culture.
Ramayana,
Khun Chang Khun Phaen,
Lilit Pralor,
and other pieces of Thai literature
always have characters stealing lovers.
How do those stories end?
Oh.
They all end in a war, don't they?
Return what's mine
or I'll jump to the end.
Look at the back.
Do you see something?
Here.
Shit.
It says room service.
Hello.
What hotel is this?
Okay, thank you.
Hello, Dad.
Can you contact the police for footages
from the CCTV at Harvey Hotel?
Yes, it's about Nant.
Why the long face?
Why are you being short with me?
Are you nervous?
Yeah.
There's nothing to worry about.
I'll wait outside. Don't worry.
Come on. Let's make you more confident.
Spray it right here.
And here.
Go!
Wow.
- Smells good?
- Very good.
Hug me.
You smell so good.
I can live a normal life.
But when I have sex,
I lose self-control.
I don't know if this is because of
a past trauma
or the chemicals in my brain.
Come on, First.
I don't think
it's about a family trauma.
Professor Napadol is brilliant and kind.
I'll talk casually with you.
I think...
You might be putting yourself
too close to temptation.
So...
Do I need to take a test
- or get my blood tested to check?
- Of course not.
I've seen you since you were young.
I know who you really are.
You are just confused.
You might be stressed from school
and need to release that tension.
Avoid going out.
Avoid using the app.
Avoid meeting people you have sex with.
And...
Try playing sports and meditating.
(She's so fucked up, man!)
(She doesn't even work at a hospital)
(Her clinic is at her own house)
(She told me to meditate
when I'm turned on)
(Does she also work
at the Ministry of Education?)
(What if you are sexually turned on?)
(Play soccer!)
(I play rugby all day,
but I have the energy to fuck my man)
Smile for your daddy.
Good.
Come on.
No.
I won't accept your cash
no matter how much it is.
How upset would First be
if he found out?
I'm not your father.
Do you know
how degenerate First will be
if you still hang out with him?
If you're not doing this for the money,
then do it for First.
You've done things for First
your whole life.
Take a look at how he grew up.
Wait.
What about this?
What's wrong with you?
You don't know
how to eat cheap food anymore?
No.
I just feel like...
Have you ever felt like sex is boring?
Rough sex is boring.
Vanilla sex is boring.
I feel like masturbating from porn
is more satisfying.
Aob, aren't you going to say hi?
Aob.
You're wearing yesterday's clothes.
Where have you been?
Look at him.
Are you in love?
So, what's going on?
In love my ass.
How can Aob be in love?
He's always working.
If he's going to be in love,
it must be that boy Big Gun
who he's mentoring.
Big Gun?
Is that right, Aob?
- Really?
- So?
- Hey, is he good?
- Master.
- Is he good?
- Come on, I knew it.
- Aob, the Big Gun?
- Aob.
- So?
- Tell us.
- What the hell?
- He took my cigarette.
- Huh?
- He won't say a word.
Damn it.
- Really?
- I knew it.
That boy must be good.
Soong.
Did you have a fight with First?
What the hell?
It must be serious this time.
He looks stressed.
What the hell is wrong with you guys?
Damn it.
I'm all alone.
I'm talking to myself.
Damn it.
I'll just eat this.
Damn it, Porche. If I get arrested,
come bail me out.
Shit.
This is great.
We usually only see
each other in the room.
You look more relaxed.
I get to see the sunlight.
Dad will send me
the CCTV footage to me soon.
So we'll find out
who the masked man is.
What's up with you and your dad?
Why do you have connections
with the police?
Why do you know how to use a gun?
I'll be shocked if you tell me you are
a mafia leader like in a series.
You'll be shocked.
Do you know who my mother is?
A Member of Parliament.
Right?
When Nant was first missing,
it was on the news everywhere.
My father was also
a Member of Parliament.
My parents were in opposing parties.
Mom was the one
who got him disqualified
as a Member of Parliament.
So this isn't a mafia series,
but it's a political series.
Why do you care about this mask?
It might not mean anything at all.
The suspect is Nuth's boss.
Nant owes him money.
We can investigate both
at the same time.
The members of my dad's party
used to say,
"Structural issues and people issues
can be solved at the same time."
Thank you so much
for being there for me
and everything is ending soon.
Without you,
I would have given up a long time ago.
Let's go.
Do you think the guy in front
was looking at me strangely?
(I had to hide under the bed
for hours until he left!)
(Think about it carefully, he's famous)
(You might get sued)
Did you forget to zip your pants?
(I've thought about it)
I didn't.
What's the matter?
You're late
and you look upset.
If you don't want to
walk with me, just tell me.
So we can walk separately.
No.
I want to walk with you.
But I'm just tired from walking.
Let me get something to drink.
Give it to me.
Please.
(Judo - fucking hard
and loud in the gym)
First.
Come out.
You've been in there for an hour.
Yeah.
You don't even know
that he's really avoiding you.
Don't be so dramatic.
He won't reply to my texts.
He won't pick up.
He's not at home.
Damn it.
He probably dumped me.
Why do I love him that much?
Come on, First.
Why would he dump you?
You have done nothing wrong.
He finds a psycho like me disgusting.
First.
Hey.
You're not a psycho, okay?
Why is your first thought
always him hating you?
What if he got into a car crash?
What if he's at some hospital?
You must find him.
Don't jump to conclusions.
You're right.
I have to find him.
Again.
Okay.
Good.
Stop being so negative about yourself.
You are my friend.
You are a great friend.
I won't let anyone hurt you.
Especially you hurting yourself.
Promise me.
Look at that. It looks so good.
Which one?
What about the macaron?
Sure.
This looks good too.
Wait.
Hello, did we get a slot
for the interview?
Fired?
What did I do wrong?
What clip?
I'm meditating.
Did we get a slot for the interview?
Hello.
I'm free.
I'm meditating.
Did we get a slot for the interview?
Okay.
You're good at meditating.
Do you want to try me?
Turn it off!
Turn it off right now!
Haven't you seen people fucking before?
Turn it off!
I crave the taste of your lips,
your voice,
and your hair.
When I walk on the street, it's silent.
I'm craving.
Food does not give me energy.
I crave you even more in the morning.
I want to eat you up.
You're like a smooth almond.
Baby.
Hey.
Why is that shirt so important?
Why don't you wear something else?
Coach got it screened for me.
He's leaving the hospital today.
If I wear this shirt to pick him up,
he'll be happy.
It's okay, there's no need to find it.
Oh.
You still have your school uniform?
Yeah.
When I like something, I try to keep it.
(I'd love to know
what you're going to do)
(Hello, are you Big Gun?)
(Meet me at court today)
(Yesterday was hot)
(I want to eat you up)
(Especially...)
(your Big Gun)
(Are you coming tonight?)
(If I go)
(Will it be easier to join the team?)
You're flirting with me
and making me jealous
because you like me, right?
Yes.
(If you come, you can enter
anywhere you want to)
(I'll be entering every hole)
Because you took my virginity.
You're mean.
Why did you make me shower alone?
I love you.
You're the only one I love.
Nuth.
Have you seen this clip?
Wait.
Nuth.
Have you seen this clip?
What? Let me see.
What is so important about this clip?
No.
You've been typing the script
since this morning.
You haven't paid any attention to me.
I'm going to sulk.
Come on.
What clip?
Show me.
Here.
The famous journalist
that every girl is fangirling over.
He was caught in a drama
and he might be banned
and fired from the show.
They're going to ban him,
but still watch his clips?
What a phony.
By the way,
have we tried this position before?
Are you nuts?
I was just making a conversation.
I wasn't trying to sleep with you.
Here.
This account has so many leaked clips.
Actors, models, and influencers.
They're not careful at all.
It's not fair to say that, Phop.
They probably didn't know
that they would be betrayed.
Also,
a lot of people secretly take
and sell these clips.
Those people should be criticized
for making a profit
from other people's privacy.
Hey!
(Captain of the rugby team)
Hello, Keen.
I was about to call you.
Huh?
I told you to keep it well.
Okay.
Saying goodbye is not
the hardest part of a break up.
It's leaving without
even saying anything.
That hurts like a motherfucker.
And what truly kills you inside
is when you have to leave
while you're still so deep in love.
And when it's not a fiction,
but it's your real life...
No matter how badly you wish
for a plot twist,
you will never get one.
Just say it or we'll all get in trouble.
Okay.
I'm sorry about the mask, Nont.
You were sure
that the mask owner is the culprit.
I don't have any evidence.
No one would have believed me.
I know you're as worried
about Nant as I am.
Please do this for him.
He gave me this mask
to wear to a party.
That's it.
After that,
I left it with Keen
in case he wanted to use it.
I swear I never removed it
from the closet.
So who took it to film with Nant?
Is it possible
that there is more than one mask, Nont?
I went to every place
that sells these things.
No one had it. It's custom made.
It's true,
but what if they custom made
more than one?
We'll get the CCTV footage
from the hotel soon.
If you lie to me,
I'll kill you.
Keen.
Why, Soong?
You were fine this morning.
What did I do wrong this time?
It's not your fault, First.
I...
I have a new sugar daddy.
If you're gonna lie,
at least look at my fucking face, Soong.
Please tell me the truth.
It's for your own good, First.
It's about my behavior?
Isn't it?
It's gonna get real dangerous.
We can't go on like this.
Trust me, this is what's best for us.
You fucking asshole.
You promised me you'll be there for me.
You said we will solve this together.
We'll go through this together.
It's hurting me too, man.
I don't want you to be this.
This monster... God damn it!
Will you hold me?
You love me, right?
I still do.
Honestly, I won't be happier
with anyone but you.
Yeah, you won't.
For sure.
You'll miss me. Please.
Soong.
Don't go.
Please.
I hate hurting you, man.
So why are you then?
Why isn't love enough?
Huh?
Yeah.
You're right.
Let's stop hurting each other.
I won't let you leave me.
I'll be the one who leaves.
The truth is
everybody says,
"Be true."
(Captain of the rugby team)
Fuck you, Captain.
How could you do this to me?
I always knew you were horrible.
But I didn't think
you would be this horrible.
I can't help it.
I already warned up.
The truth that even you yourself
is not good enough.
So you lie...
So you conceal yourself.
So you try to change.
Why?
Why did you lie to me?
Why, Puen?
I don't...
You said you were going to be with me.
You lied, Puen.
I just have sex with him, but I like you.
Why did you lie to me?
Why, Puen?
Why?
Why did you lie to me?
I'm sorry.
But if changing
your true self doesn't help
and if my true self
is a monster,
it's time I unleash the monster.
(It's not Nuth and not Captain's coach)
(Who is the masked man?)
(I got what you asked for)
(10th June night at the Harvey Hotel)
(This is the clearest footage)
(Nant is in it)
Are you
the man who wore the dog mask?
The police found him dead and naked
in a forest near Rangsit.
Based on initial assumptions,
he has probably been dead for 48 hours.
(Man found dead)
(Next Episode)
Think about it.
Who would go do drugs in the forest?
Also,
he was missing for months.
Auntie.
Can I see the CCTV footage?
My only suspect is Nuth's boss.
Tell me who did this to you, Puen.
How does that involve you?
Are you going to continue your search?
If Nant really died from his stupidity
like we're hearing on the news,
then I'll hate him to the bone.
But if someone killed him,
I'll take revenge for his death.