(The Auditors)
Didn't you see someone
rushing to the rooftop?
I didn't see anyone.
I was chasing the blackmailer.
It doesn't seem like you've captured him.
I thought you were outstanding
enough to catch him.
I'll find him.
Please find him as soon as possible.
It's me.
I lost track of him.
Come to the control room.
Yes, sir.
He entered the Welfare Floor
which doesn't require an employee card.
That is where an outsider hardly knows.
He must've known the company structure
if you look where he moved around.
Then, he is really…
(The Auditors)
You're the best. You taught him a lesson.
He must've got a scar.
I guess he's dispirited now.
Is that enough?
No. He humiliated you.
I mean. He embarrassed you.
Do you think he really looks dispirited?
Did the blackmailer really appear?
You were amazing.
What are you saying?
He failed to capture him.
What if he didn't give up
and succeeded in putting drugs in the food?
Today's lunch might be…
Oh, no. I skipped breakfast.
He failed to put drugs
in the food. Don't worry.
I also announced that
they should strengthen
access control and
reexamine ingredients again.
How did you know he would appear?
Let's have a meeting related to this case.
Let's talk about the details then.
By the way, where is Goo Han Soo?
These are employees of our clients.
Wasn't there a man
with a black uniform, hat, and a mask?
His height was this much.
We sometimes wear masks
but no one else does today.
No one wears a hat, too.
Yes.
Visitors in the morning were
all female reporters
who came to interview
the ethics management department.
I see. Thank you.
Thank you.
Hello, sir.
I'm Goo Han Soo from the Audit Team.
- Hello.
I'll help you.
Thank you so much.
JU Construction's employees are all kind.
He said he felt his mother from me.
He always gives me
instant coffee sticks and snacks.
You're going to the supply room, right?
Right.
I'll push it.
Thank you.
Weren't you uncomfortable before?
What?
I felt sorry when I took the supplies
at the outsourcing head office.
I know that was your job.
Thank you for your understanding.
I'll push it now. Thank you.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Be careful.
I saw the apology.
Was it a simple incident?
I'm sorry, but I can't say it now.
But we work for the employees.
Feel free to report any difficulties to us.
If I report, does something bad change?
Of course,
the difficulties won't bother you anymore.
Please report to us.
(Justice and safety is my faith.)
(Cafeteria Fraud. Victims lost
their families and money, too…)
Me, too.
Where have you been? Did you have lunch?
I just ate bread.
Employees shouldn't skip a meal.
Today, many people skipped lunch.
I understand it
because Mr. Shin and Han Soo were busy.
And the deputy director
suddenly felt pain in his stomach.
Do you really think so?
He just skipped a meal because
he's worried there's a drug in the food.
I felt the same way.
Let's go in.
Go to the cafeteria and eat something.
We ate lunch there, but we're fine.
I'm serious.
I feel sick to my stomach.
I really feel chilly and nauseous.
Let's have a meeting.
- Yes, sir.
I tried to induce the blackmailer
but failed to run after him.
The cafeteria will
strictly manage access control
and install extra CCTVs
to prevent the recurrence of the accident.
I've checked the guest list to see
who visited the company that morning.
No one was suspicious.
We failed to induce him.
So, we should go back to square one.
Let's reveal his identity by searching
for data and apprehending a situation.
It's like finding a needle in a haystack.
We don't know where to begin.
Given that he threatened us to investigate
the corrupt cafeteria management,
he might be the victim
who failed to win a bid.
He knew who the team leader was,
although it's only been 20
days since I was assigned.
He also knew that the cafeteria
would resume its business.
It's a notice only posted
on the bulletin board.
He is the one who can enter
the company and cafeteria freely.
He also knew precisely
about the company structure.
Are you saying he's one of the employees?
If he failed to win a bid,
he would run a restaurant.
Could an office worker run a restaurant
while working at the company?
Do you think he did run a store himself?
In cases like this, the family
runs a business instead.
Internal regulation doesn't
limit employees' families from
running a construction site cafeteria.
I'm a drop in the ocean.
Many people gave more money than me.
What if the family member of the
blackmailer gave money to the agency?
Based on the agency's past behaviors,
the odds of that are pretty high.
Why did he recklessly put drugs in the food
although he lost money?
He also knew he'd be severely punished
if someone died.
He might've lost
something more significant than money.
If he lost his family member,
he would lose his reason.
My dad was dead from overwork.
To meet the deadline, he hadn't slept
for a few days, then he fell down.
But, it was really tough to get
recognized as an industrial accident.
Have you achieved recognition
of industrial accidents?
I barely achieved it after a legal
battle over a couple of years.
If I couldn't win the battle,
I would be mad and do whatever.
I felt wronged a lot.
I didn't care about going to jail
at that moment.
You've got the recognition of
industrial accidents and are living well.
Your dad must be resting in peace.
JU Construction entrusted
management authority to the agency
for three years under the former CEO.
The investigation range is four years
including the recent one year.
Find every bereaved employee
and the names of the deceased
on the Family Event bulletin board.
Divide the period and get it
done quickly by working together.
Yes, sir.
Assistant Manager Moon, you're a fast
worker. Gather and arrange materials.
Yes, sir.
Please check this out.
I'm done.
Between the people who failed to win a bid
and the employee's dead family members,
find a name that matches.
Yes, sir.
Han Soo and Seo Jin. Here it is.
In three cases the name of the
person who failed to win a bid
and the name of the employee's
dead family member are the same.
You two go to the first case's restaurant.
The names of the restaurant's owner
and the civil engineering department
leader's dead father are the same.
It's hard to investigate
one case out of the three.
This employee resigned seven months ago.
- Chief Ok.
- Yes.
I heard you have acquaintances
in every department. Is it true?
What brought you here?
Do you want to get some coffee?
Sounds good.
I have something to ask you.
Do you know Lee Sun Hyung
who worked in this department?
She resigned.
Did her sister-in-law
run a cafeteria at the construction site?
Welcome. Are you two?
Please take a seat where you want to sit.
Actually
we're from the JU Construction Audit Team.
May I ask you something
about Lee Dong Cheol?
I'm Lee Dong Cheol. What brings you here?
Mr. Vice President.
Something serious is happening
inside the Audit Team.
The low-level employees
of that team rushed out of the office.
And Mr. Shin also went out for something.
He's maybe on outside duty.
I don't think so.
Where have you been?
I guess you visited
the technology development office again.
Don't you think
you've partially focused on J-BIMS?
Of course, I should focus on it.
Our future depends on this project.
Our future? Yes, it's important.
But I think you should pay attention
to the fundamental task
of the construction companies.
Have you visited the
construction site recently?
If you visit the construction site
as much as you visit
the technology development office,
the speed of construction
work will increase.
I'm not sure
how fast the construction speed would be.
But I can see how much
you stew yourself over the J-BIMS.
This is Shin Cha Il.
Do you remember Lee Sun Hyung
who resigned seven months ago?
I found out that her sister-in-law
ran a cafeteria at the construction site.
But she was running many stores.
Even if she didn't win a bid,
I don't think it did damage her.
Did you find out the cause of his death?
He died in a car accident,
and his brother who quit the job
is studying in the UK.
Thank you for your efforts.
(Sir, he's a homonym. It's not him.)
Are you interested in that job?
Do you remember the restaurant
that was in this location two years ago?
It's called Hangunchan Restaurant,
and the owner name was Lee Kyung Sook.
Of course, I remember.
I used to have lunch here all the time.
It's such a shame.
Has anything happened?
The owner chipped some money in to open
a restaurant for the construction site.
But she ended up getting scammed.
Because of that, this restaurant
was eventually put up for auction.
Nobody seems to hold out
in this place for long since then.
Have you recently heard about the owner?
Don't get me started.
She passed away about three months ago.
I found out about it late,
so I wasn't able to make a condolence call.
I felt so sad when I heard the news.
I gotta go.
The blackmailer is one of the subcontract
purchase headquarters employees.
Yes, tomorrow.
Be prepared.
Hello, sir.
You must be tired, but
you came to work early.
I'm always tired.
You must've been tired
yesterday in particular.
Because you had to run away.
What are you talking about?
Chief Im!
Chief Im.
Are you okay, ma'am?
I'm okay.
Did you send it by yourself?
You told me to investigate corruption
in the construction site restaurant.
Following the audit, no
issues were identified.
It's not that nothing happened.
You just couldn't find anything.
Please tell me why.
Tell me now if you do not wish to be
regarded as a meaningless criminal.
My mother…
Wow, it's spacious!
My mother was so happy…
to finally receive the permit
to run a restaurant…
at the JU Construction site
after waiting for years.
But…
You're now a rich person.
- What's all this?
- What are these?
What are you doing in my restaurant?
Who are you…
- What do you mean by that?
- We are the owners.
In fact, someone else received the permit.
It turns out that my mother was informed…
that she could have the permit
by paying a bribe to an agency.
And she paid the agency 200 million won.
We went to the agency
and tried to figure out,
But they made an excuse,
saying that the permit was not
for this year, but for two years later.
It was a scam.
I don't have money, I've
pulled all the money I have,
so I'm at a loss to pay back
my loan interest right now…
We were supposed to sign a contract later…
Didn't you draw up a contract?
Can't we get our money back?
We can help but it's not easy.
Oh my.
There's no evidence that we paid the money…
(Audit Office)
(Reporting to the audit team)
What's this?
I also reported it to the Audit Team,
but there was no response.
I tried to find out how this fraud started…
by moving the department
to the subcontract purchase headquarters.
But all I found out was…
that the company was not responsible for it
due to the end of the
contract with the agency.
What do you think about that, sir?
Don't you have any documents from before?
We entrusted the operation rights
to an agency back then,
and the contract with the agency ended.
The agency committed
fraud regarding the permit
to run JU Construction's
on-site restaurant.
But JU Construction said
they're not responsible for anything,
and they didn't investigate anything.
Do you think it makes sense?
There are more than 100 subcontractors
that we manage.
That's a subcontractor as well…
How can the purchasing department manage…
whether the subcontractor
receives a bribe or not?
No matter what the situation is,
you chose the wrong way.
Im Jung Yoon, the chief of the
subcontract purchase headquarters…
sent a threatening letter to the company,
causing a major scare…
and you seriously damaged the safety of
the construction site by drugging the food.
I propose the dismissal
of Chief Im Jung Yoon.
I think this has gone wrong…
File this.
Yes, sir.
You're doing well.
I have a stomachache. I will be back soon.
I have a bad stomach.
Please handle the resignation
of Chief Im due to health reasons…
and wrap it up without
any criminal charges.
As I said before,
we're about to announce J-BIMS…
so let's leave it at that.
Is there anything else you want to report?
There is no legal liability
for JU construction…
about the agency
defrauding bidders of money…
under the pretext of operating rights.
However, as the company entrusted
the operation rights to the agency,
I would like to suggest
taking moral responsibility,
and supporting the victims' legal costs.
We can transform the company into one
that fulfills its ethical responsibilities.
I like that.
And it's true
that the subcontract purchase headquarters…
neglected to manage the agency,
and sat on the sidelines.
For him to take responsibility,
I suggest giving the head…
of the subcontract purchase, Pyeon,
a three-month pay cut...
Let's have him transferred
to Sanpo factory.
Vice President…
the audit team caught the guy
who sent the threatening letter.
It's an internal employee.
But they decided to fire him
and not make it a big deal.
Because we have a momentous occasion.
Shin posted an apology on the bulletin
board saying that he would not audit.
But apparently, that was a trap…
to open the cafeteria
to lure the blackmailer there.
I will post an apology.
I will announce it…
on every board in the office.
And to take responsibility
for not managing the agency properly,
President…
got the head of the subcontract purchase
transferred to a suburban office.
I wouldn't catch in the crossfire, would I?
This brat thinks of me as a big pushover.
Who's in charge of this?
Yes, President.
Sorry? Sanpo?…
President, what did I do wrong?
Please tell me…
That's why you hired a
new audit team leader.
How dare you transfer me?
Hey.
Yes, sir.
Are you happy now?
Are you?
Just you wait.
See what happens
when President Hwang Geon Woong comes back.
The company decided
not to press criminal charges.
I understand how you feel…
But please remember
that there were a lot of victims of this.
How are the workers?
Some people are still hospitalized,
but they will be okay.
Chief Im.
Can I ask…
How your mother passed away?
I wanted to let people know
that my mother was wronged somehow…
My mother had a hard time…
so she got a serious illness.
She said she lost all my marriage funds,
so she couldn't let me pay
for the hospital bill.
On a cold day at the river…
Goo Han Soo.
What was I supposed to do?
There are people who have been affected,
but no one is responsible for that.
Should I have just put up with it
and kept reporting it here and there?
Even if no one is giving me an answer…
including the Audit Team.
I've sent Chief Im home.
This happened due to
our complacency as well.
We could have prevented it
if we checked the report two years ago.
But everyone turned a blind eye.
Everyone was indifferent
because it was an external issue.
Eventually, even innocent
internal employees got damaged.
Please do your audit thoroughly
to prevent this from happening again.
Are you heading home?
Yes, sir.
- Bye.
- See you later.
See you tomorrow.
If the audit team doesn't audit properly,
such a tragedy could occur.
Everyone will see us as an audit team…
that takes action
when they get a threatening letter.
Enjoy the food.
Han Soo is here.
Why is he just going up?
Leave him alone.
What was I supposed to do?
Even if no one is giving me an answer
including the audit team.
Hello.
I think it's trust
that we need in the Audit Team.
We need to get close
to the employees first…
so they can report anytime.
To make them think we are on the same side…
How about posting this announcement?
That's a good opinion.
I agree.
It feels a bit awkward…
but one more vote for approval!
Gathering all your opinions…
I agree 50%.
Please, sir.
Wow, what is this?
The audit team is trying hard
to build strength.
Write a report.
About…
forecast for construction orders
in the second half of the year?
Everything about Shin Cha Il.
About that,
I came to the office early
in the morning the other day,
and looked into the resume of Shin.
So I know about him well…
He went to Sunghan university…
Everything that's not on the resume.
If the contents are poor,
a personnel appointment will be posted
next to this one.
It's nice to go for lunch with you.
I hope the menu is good today.
What's the menu for today?
Stir-fried squid and pork cutlet and…
It looks like we have a lot of work to do.
You know I only agreed 50%.
You gathered all our opinions.
You need to put up with…
Let's decide who will be in charge
of the Internet report bulletin board.
You can be in charge, Goo Han Soo.
Yes, sir. I'll do my best!
Good luck.
Thank you.
What brought you here?
I came here because I heard
that Gun Woong seems to be on the mend.
I told him.
That's good. How is he?
He got better.
He will become conscious soon.
It's not the time to talk about it, but
the performance of the business is poor.
The stock price is down at the bottom.
The economic sentiment index is the worst.
There is also a lot of uncertainty
in the real estate market.
I have no choice
but to reduce the amount of sales…
That's why it's hard to be the president.
Because the president needs
to get through the current situation.
Once J-BIMS is completed,
the competitiveness of orders
will dramatically increase.
Alright, I'm looking forward to it.
How's everything with Dae Woong?
Are you getting along?
The last thing I want to see is the
brothers arguing over management rights.
I wish your father had distributed well.
(JU Construction's
vision and innovation!)
(J-BIMS presentation demonstration)
Vision and innovation?
That's nice.
Hello.
Can I have a gukbap here, please?
Hello, sir.
I don't feel like eating
alone. Can I join you?
Do you often have dinner out?
No one at home today?
There's no one all the time.
Alright, you live alone…
- Thank you.
- Enjoy the food.
Sir…
The Audit Team has been changing
since you came.
Should I say it became a proper audit team?
I feel proud and responsible these days
as a member of an audit team.
And…
My new goal is to become someone like you.
I'm not still convinced by you saying
that we have to doubt everyone…
But even if you said it,
you trust the team members, don't you?
Enjoy the food.
It looks delicious.
I feel proud and responsible these days
as a member of an audit team.
My new goal is to become someone like you.
What's going on?
About the audit report of the
building material purchase you wrote…
You reviewed that had
been approved already.
You're the team's next ace.
I feel reassured.
What's wrong? Is there an issue?
I found something strange
while checking the purchase lists.
I should've explained you in advance.
Our youngest must have been shocked
as it's your first time.
You are right, the actual amount
of steel purchased is 300 tons.
Then, why is it shown
that the company paid for 420 tons?
Because the remaining
amount is reflected here.
There were advanced purchases.
Every time they purchase,
they get benefited.
Even so, shouldn't we report accurately?
You are right.
But as the construction goes on,
there are a lot of additional costs.
It's a hassle to always be accurate.
Do you think I'm getting bribed
to keep my mouth shut on this?
I didn't mean that…
Do you think I will destroy this place?
I didn't mean to say that…
Cha Il, don't bother these little things,
focus on the big.
Auditing is all about
looking at the big picture.
Let's go.
Good Morning.
Good Morning!
Don't come near me!
I'm whistle blowing on workplace bullying.
Yoon Woo!
Don't come!
Okay. Okay, put out
the fire and let's talk.
I said don't come near me!
This crazy bastard,
who do you think you are to start a fire?
Is it fun?
Get back to work!
Take care of it.
Yoon Woo, are you fine?
The informant's
psychological state is unstable,
it is better to give him some time.
I heard you were
Oh Yoon Woo's colleague as well.
Yes.
He was considered for the
most Popular Employee Award,
because of his good personality.
I don't know
how he even thought of starting a fire.
I wonder how hard time
he must have had with his boss.
I wonder how much he was harassed…
But is there anyone in the Technology
Development Team who would do that?
Never heard of it.
Isn't that team super busy right now
as they have the J-BIMS
Demonstration coming up?
This is Shin Cha Il.
Okay.
We will do the interview
after I meet with the President.
I heard there was an incident at the lobby.
And the Audit Team took him.
Yes, we plan to investigate as soon
as the informant is in stable condition.
I wanted to ask you about it.
I had my network scour
for it at full capacity,
I'm sure of it,
Shin Cha Il is a disgusting person.
I didn't know he would go this far.
Sir, why don't you go
to the Audit office and spill it out?
I'm sure he will be embarrassed
in front of his team and walk out.
It's no fun spilling it out all at once.
I'm going to stop him, slowly.
Yoon Woo, tell me what happened this time.
Why do you look so worn out?
So upsetting.
You were really happy when you
moved to the Tech Development Team.
I was…
I really wanted to be in that team.
The Audit team will
do our best to help you,
so don't worry and tell us
everything that happened.
You said you were constantly bullied by
Mr. Park Jae Hwan from
the Tech Development team.
Do you remember when
did the bullying start?
I'm not certain,
but it has been approximately 3-4 months.
Is there a specific reason that you
decided to report it after
bearing it for this long?
It was my motto to work for the
Tech Development team
ever since I joined the company.
More than anything,
I took pride in being a part of the
J-BIMS Demonstration,
that plays an important role
in shaping this company's future.
That's why I endured
through the difficulties.
Good Morning, Sir.
Sir, I think there is an error
in the server access system.
It's not an error.
Yes?
From now on,
you cannot access the J-BIMS server.
We deactivated your access, already
received confirmation from Section Chief.
Are you saying, I cannot participate
in J-BIMS development anymore?
Yes, you have been excluded.
There are other works, too.
The security team asked for something.
Here, do this.
The other employees
are busy with the Demonstration.
I could not accept getting excluded
from the J-BIMS Demonstration.
In other words, they are asking me
to leave the Development Team.
You must have worked so hard for it.
I have to analyze the situation. Ms. Seo
Jin, please lead the interview this time.
Me?
The more you do interviews,
the more you get the hang of it.
Lead the conversation
and get as much information as you can.
Be focused.
You can go inside.
I'm sorry, I'm not a very organized person.
Please have a seat.
You made it here quick. It hasn't been long
that you informed you were coming.
It's a simple interview
so it's better to get done with it quick.
Sure.
Please excuse me as I may not be able
to give you enough time for the interview.
Can I borrow this?
Just a moment.
Please use this, that looks crumbled.
I'll start with the interview.
Oh Yoon Woo reported that he was bullied
by Manager, Mr. Park Jae Hwan.
It's my fault, a self-immolation attempt…
I apologize that I didn't know Yoon Woo
was going through a difficult phase.
I heard both of them
are in charge of the same tasks.
Yes, cost optimization engine development.
Mr. Park is the main
and Yoon Woo is the support.
Oh Yoon Woo said that he was verbally
abused. What do you think about that?
Chief Park is a sensitive person.
He played an important role
in the team and had a lot of work.
Yoon Woo who supported the team,
made a lot of mistakes and had a weak base.
Chief Park scolded him
a lot and got angry, too.
But it's difficult to say
that he verbally abused him.
What was the reason to kick out Yoon Woo
from the J-BIMS Demonstration?
It was Mr. Park's idea.
He was worried he might be a hindrance.
I feel sorry for Yoon
Woo, but work comes first.
This is Shin Cha Il from the Audit Team.
I am requesting for an interview.
Hello, this is Yoon Seo Jin from the Audit
Team. I am requesting for an interview.
That is Chief Park right?
Why does the perpetrator look so down?
People might think he
was the one to get bullied.
Right?
Yoon Woo, it's been so long.
Why don't you come more often?
Exactly. Dad, where's the chicken?
Right now! Right now! Let's go, Let's go.
Yoon Woo, you said our chicken is
delicious, but why don't you come often?
Did you find some other place?
Right?
I was stuck with some work.
What work? Why didn't you tell me?
We could have solved it together.
Have a good meal.
Yoon Woo, first have this.
You know, it's chicken
when we are stressed.
At our place chicken
is really good, eat up.
It's delicious right! Stress relieved
right! Shall we have beer too?
Yoon Woo, Team leader has
given you time off so rest well.
So, don't think much, now let's eat up.
Okay, here, take another one.
See I gave you two, you know I care right?
You have to eat to strengthen up.
Good to see you smiling!
Dad, Beer please.
Oh Yoon Woo and Chief Park's arguments
are contradictory.
Why do you think Chief Park bullied you?
Is he like that with other employees too?
I know I lack a lot.
But, he speaks harshly to me.
We are still waiting on the solution right?
It delays other work, too.
I'm sorry, I'll complete
it within this week.
Yes, please. Meeting over.
Thank you.
Yoon Woo, please wait.
How many times
do I need to tell you?
Why do you have a brain
if you don't use it at all?
You pointed out his in competencies. But,
you didn't verbally abuse him, did you?
No, I didn't.
How many times do I need
to tell you correct this?
I'm sorry.
Others are getting affected by delays
on our side. Please think while working.
Do you have any evidence or anyone
to testify regarding the verbal abuse?
Of course, there is none! I have
never bullied or verbally abused him.
I'm sorry, the simulation seems
to be difficult at the moment.
I will get back to you with
this as soon as possible.
What kind of meeting preparation is this?
I'm sorry.
Oh Yoon Woo, how could you
do a mistake on the attachment?
I'm so embarrassed right now.
Are you trying to screw me up
because you have ill feelings towards me?
If that's the case, let's talk it out. It's
difficult for me to continue like this.
Always when it was two
of us or over the phone.
Since our team had strict security
program installed on our phones,
we cannot voice record.
Yes, Chief.
Are you in your right mind?
Why can't someone even
send an email properly?
You are purposely trying to screw me up
and make me look bad, right?
No...
You use your brain to screw me up
instead of using it for work.
Such an incompetent, unlucky brat.
I may not be good enough,
but excluding me from the J-BIMS is unfair.
It's almost at the last stage of the
Demonstration and running out of time.
Instead of being of help,
he is just a hindrance.
Honestly, I wish Yoon Woo leaves the team.
For everyone's sake.
I'm back.
What do the other team members say?
He gets in a lot of trouble.
I guess, he lacks competence.
But chief is a really good person,
so he doesn't say much.
If it was someone with a temper…
Chief Park often gets annoyed.
He was not like this before
but it's getting worse day by day.
Yoon Woo does make a lot of mistakes.
I heard he was good
when he worked under Chief Shin.
Chief Park oversees
Yoon Woo's work very discretely.
So whenever anything is late or goes wrong,
he blames Yoon Woo.
Have you ever heard Chief
Park verbally abuse Yoon Woo
or bring up his home environment?
Yes? Bring up the fact that he is adopted?
I think that's a bit too much.
Chief Park… may be sensitive,
but he is not trash to bring that up.
Even though we are busy and
may not look interested in others,
if we see things happening,
we won't turn a blind eye.
Oh Yoon Woo is making things up.
It's ambiguous and we lack evidence.
Yes, Sir.
It's been long since
you came to my place.
Wait.
It's okay.
I can go to my house.
What are you saying?
Just rest here till tomorrow.
I'll finish up work at office and be back.
Let's have a nice dinner together.
Does no one from your team know
that Chief Park bullied you?
Everybody just knows that he scolded me.
He used harsh words
when it was only two of us.
What about the Section Chief?
Does he get angry too?
Never, the Section Chief
is a really nice person.
Yes, Section Chief.
How do you feel now?
I am better now.
I am granting you special leave for 10
days. Please rest and let's meet up later.
The Demonstration will end in 10 days.
Am I completely excluded
from the J-BIMS Demonstration?
It's not possible to have you participate
in J-BIMS at this time.
We are too tight on schedule to work
out our emotions towards each other.
No, I'll be in the office right away.
Yes?
Okay.
I understand.
You can't report back to work on J-BIMS?
He says I'm on leave,
but he is actually asking me to drop off.
I'll get back to the office
and let the Audit Team know about this.
Section Chief Jihoon granted leave to
Yoon Woo and asked him to drop off J-BIMS.
It's been decided to work on Yoon
Woo's report after the J-BIMS is over.
Then, nothing changes for Yoon Woo.
We have to investigate further.
There is no evidence
to the verbal abuse argument.
That's because Development Team's special
case that makes recording impossible.
We received testimonies from
Development Team team-members
that they never witnessed Chief
Park verbally abused Yoon Woo.
As of now, Yoon Woo's report
is just a one-side claim.
Considering the situation,
we will separate Chief Park and Yoon
Woo until the demonstration is over.
We will decide whether Yoon Woo
is return back to the Development team
or transfer to other team
after the demonstration.
I'll go to the Audit
Office and let them know.
The President already
asked Audit Team Manager
to stop the investigation
and cause an issue.
Is it because of the President?
Did he ask you to cover up this issue?
Is this what you meant
when you said Audit Team
should always look at
things with suspicion?
How painful must it be
for Yoon Woo to think of self-immolation?
I understand how important
the Demonstration is,
but is it worth ignoring someone's life?
I don't think so.
I'm not ignoring him. We are just
postponing our decision for 10 days.
Why does the victim have to excluded?
Yoon Woo did his best for the
J-BIMS Development for the past year.
Do we have turn a blind eye on bad things
for the sake of company's profit?
You have lost your sense
of judgement and are biased
because of your personal feelings
towards the informant.
Is that so? How about this?
What if someone is trying to
leak company's important technology?
What do you mean?
You may cover up employees getting bullied.
But, I'm sure you are going to
investigate a big case like this.
This is where they place bets
on illegally leaked information.
- Is it…
- J-BIMS.
The only thing important to us is evidence.
It's disgusting to criticize bribery
while treating one's life as meaningless.
Think before you answer.
It might be decisive
factor to report the incident
to the police as soon
as this investigation ends.
The Demonstration cannot be messed up.
I have found evidence regarding the leaking
of important technology at the J-BIMS.