(The Auditors)
(All characters, organizations, and
events in this drama are fictitious.)
(Staff ensured child actors' safety in the filming of this drama.)
Shin Cha Il!
Hey! Wake up!
Hey!
Darn it.
(Caution: Flammables)
Wake up.
Hey, Director Chae. Director Chae!
Director Chae, wake up!
Are you all right?
(The Auditors)
(Final Episode)
Shin Cha Il,
are you okay?
What about you, Mr. Hwang? Are you okay?
I'm not okay, punk.
Hang in there.
They're almost here.
You're so spiteful.
(Paramedic)
This patient breathed in a lot of smoke.
Connect him to an oxygen mask and prepare some Arformoterol.
- Okay. - Okay.
Emergency patient coming through!
(Hanjoo University Hospital)
You should get treated too.
Excuse me, can someone take a look at him?
Please follow me.
(Emergency Medical Center)
Uncle.
What about Mr. Shin?
He's being treated.
What about you? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
But what happened?
- A slush fund? - Yes. Shin Cha Il is like a rat.
He's been going around poking his nose in everything.
He also came to me to ask me questions.
But it's not true, is it?
So that was the money...
Director Chae was talking about.
I realized why Director Chae had approached me before.
It was a trap set by Hwang Se Woong.
That was why I went straight to the funeral home.
Darn it.
That was what happened.
You can't leave.
You need rest.
How is the patient who came in with us?
It doesn't look very good. He's still unconscious.
You shouldn't be moving around either.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
No, he's not okay.
Please help me stop him.
He shouldn't be moving so much.
Doctor, no one in the world can stop this stubborn man.
Don't worry.
I won't hold the hospital responsible.
We must stop the cremation.
Otherwise, the evidence of the homicide will disappear.
Mr. Shin, over there.
Stop them.
Who are you people?
Hurry up and move your car!
Mr. Shin, what's the matter?
It must be stopped.
What?
We must leave for the cremation.
We're late.
The body must get an autopsy.
Mr. Hwang Gun Woong was killed.
Mr. Shin, what kind of behavior is this?
What...
What do you mean?
Who are you saying killed my husband?
Are you out of your mind?
Hold on. Answer me.
Who killed my husband?
Vice President Hwang Dae Woong.
After Vice President Hwang visited the hospital,
President Hwang Gun Woong passed away.
What's the plan?
An autopsy is needed...
to resolve the suspicion.
Do it.
- Yu Seon? - No.
Do it now.
But how do we stop the cremation?
We'll tell them Hwang Se Woong is suspicious.
They won't believe it.
There's no concrete evidence.
Then what do we do?
I will accuse you as a murder suspect.
A suspect? What do you mean by that?
It's simply a bait.
Even so, that's a bit...
No.
Let's do that.
Yu Seon will react to it right away with it.
In return,
you must catch Hwang Se Woong for sure.
Sir.
I'm the one being treated as a murderer.
But why do you look worse than me?
Are you all right, Mr. Shin?
- Head to the hospital at once. - Understood.
Thank you.
Don't get up.
You still need to be treated.
What about the autopsy?
It has started.
As it's a high-profile case, it'll be conducted with urgency.
And Mr. Chae?
He's still unconscious.
But President Hwang...
moved him to Naseon General Hospital's VIP room.
Get some more rest.
We're out of time.
I must see him.
Only family members can visit him.
You can't meet him right now.
I must meet his family at the least.
Mr. Shin.
What is wrong with you?
Why are you risking your life in audits?
One's life...
depends on the audit.
Mr. Gu, come with me.
Ms. Yoon.
Investigate the fire site.
Everything burned down.
Nothing can be used as evidence.
I don't see any CCTVs around, either.
Mr. Shin.
I want to know, too.
Why do you go that far and risk your life in audits?
Excuse me.
Hi.
I'm Gu Han Soo from the JU Construction Audit Team.
Oh, I see. Hi.
What brought you here?
How's Mr. Chae doing?
He breathed in a lot of smoke. We need to wait and see.
But he's getting better.
That's a relief.
May we see him for a moment?
You can't go in.
We're from the JU Construction Audit Team.
We'll leave as soon as we see Mr. Chae's condition.
Only family members can visit him.
Murder?
What on earth is going on?
Vice President Hwang.
Aren't you innocent?
Mr. Yang.
Do you trust me?
What? Me?
Of course, I trust you.
Mr. Yang. Can you give us some privacy?
Sure.
Seo Jin.
Get off the case.
"Get off the case?"
Why all of a sudden?
I can't help but get worried.
Look at Shin Cha Il and Director Chae.
If even you get hurt...
I can't let that happen.
Get off the case for your mom's sake.
Should I transfer you to a different department?
I'll resign.
All right.
But only after I see the end of this case.
Seo Jin...
- What is it? - Mr. Hwang Dae Woong.
You're arrested without a warrant...
on suspicion of murdering Hwang Gun Woong.
You have the right not to make unfavorable statements...
and appoint an attorney. Understood?
- Take him. - Yes, sir.
Fine.
Put that away.
Don't worry.
I'll be back soon.
Vice President Hwang has been arrested.
The autopsy revealed the circumstances of the murder.
Some drug was injected.
And definitive evidence was found.
What definitive evidence?
That... I'll look into it.
Mr. Shin.
Tell me what to do next.
Transfer to the Business Support Team this instant...
under President Hwang's order.
What are you saying?
We'll move your belongings for you.
Mr. Gu.
Go to the Subcontract Purchase Team with Ms. Yoon...
and secure the data.
Mr. Shin?
Let's go.
We should hurry, too.
The President's office took everything already.
(Business Support Team)
Mr. Shin.
There wasn't any data we could secure.
What do we do now?
Mr. Gu.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Hwang Dae Woong. It's your lighter, isn't it?
Yes.
You said you didn't see Mr. Hwang Gun Woong,
but this lighter was found in his hospital room.
What happened?
I wonder too.
The only fingerprint we could find on it was yours.
You'd better tell the truth.
Continuing to plead the Fifth could work to your disadvantage.
Do you still refuse to tell us?
(JU Construction)
(Notice of Extraordinary General Meeting)
I heard he killed Mr. Hwang Gun Woong.
- Is it true? - It's crazy, isn't it?
What will happen to the company now?
I hear Vice President Hwang has been arrested.
They'll discuss his dismissal?
I heard on my way here...
that he killed Mr. Hwang Gun Woong.
My gosh. I'm too scared to work here.
(Extraordinary General Meeting, Detailed Meeting Agenda)
"The fact that..."
"the vice president of the company is a murder suspect..."
"is wreaking havoc on the company's reputation and..."
How about we add that he also contributed...
to creating the slush fund?
Pardon me?
Everyone knows that he and Director Chae...
were close.
Oh, right.
- Mr. Yeom? - Yes, sir.
Go and tell everyone on the Audit Team...
that anyone who helps Mr. Shin...
will definitely pay for it.
(President Hwang Se Woong)
You all understood what I just said, right?
I relayed the message, okay?
Yes, don't put your life on the line for work.
Having a long, uneventful career is a good thing. Okay?
But...
doesn't that mean it's okay to help him...
if we're willing to deal with the consequences?
Why would you interpret it like that?
I think this is my last chance anyway.
Hey, don't think like that. It's simple.
A long, uneventful career is not what I want.
I'll help you guys in every way I can.
Ms. Ok.
You need to dissuade them.
What will you do, Mr. Yeom?
- Are you going to back out? - What?
My goodness. What do you want me to do?
Fine, go for it. I don't care what happens.
It's out of my hands now. Gosh.
I have to go and update Mr. Shin on something.
- See you in a bit. - Okay.
I delivered it as per your instructions.
But we haven't found the ledger yet.
Won't it be difficult without it?
Director Chae is the only person we can count on now.
Sir.
Director Chae is...
I hereby pronounce...
Mr. Chae Jong Woo...
dead at 1:55pm on June 10.
(President Hwang Se Woong)
Director Chae is dead.
Okay.
Let's get moving.
Yes, sir.
I've finished checking the data.
(Ministry of Land, Infrastructure and Transport)
What do you want?
We need you to make sure the investigation...
of Mr. Hwang Dae Woong is conducted fairly.
Right now.
Hey, what time is it? How come Mr. Shin isn't back yet?
What if I have to go into the meeting by myself?
He said to follow President Hwang's orders until we hear from him.
Let's trust Mr. Shin.
Mr. Yeom, don't be nervous. You got this.
Stop it. My gosh.
It's about to begin. Let's go.
Yes, I know. I'm going.
- Don't push me. - All right.
- I told you not to push me. - I didn't.
(JU Construction, Extraordinary General Meeting)
My gosh. When will he be here?
Are you all right?
Darn it.
Here I go.
Hello.
We will now begin JU Construction's extraordinary general meeting.
President Hwang Se Woong...
will explain what we are here to discuss today.
(JU Construction, Extraordinary General Meeting)
Hello, I'm Hwang Se Woong.
I'll cut straight to the chase.
Today, we're here...
to file a motion to dismiss Vice President Hwang Dae Woong.
Please look at the screen.
(Suspected of Murdering Former President Hwang Gun Woong)
Vice President Hwang has been arrested...
for allegedly murdering his brother, which is an abhorrent crime.
It has greatly damaged the company's reputation.
The case hasn't gone to court yet.
Don't you think this is a little harsh?
These articles and the fact that people are talking about it...
are wreaking havoc on the company.
On top of that, this isn't...
the only thing Vice President Hwang did.
(How the illegal slush fund was created)
He wanted to get me ousted and replace me as president...
using the slush fund Director Chae Jong Woo had created.
To do that, he tried to bribe the board members.
Am I right, Mr. Yang?
Well...
When Mr. Hwang Gun Woong passed away,
Vice President Hwang gathered up the board members to comfort...
No, I mean...
That's right. He did invite them out to a casual meal once,
but I assure you that there was no money involved...
- whatsoever... - I see. Thank you.
As you heard just now, he tried to exploit the slush fund...
and bribe the board members.
That is a serious breach of duty,
and therefore I suggest we dismiss Vice President Hwang.
Then we'll vote.
All in favor, raise a hand.
Announce the result.
Yes, sir.
The votes are in and Vice President Hwang Dae Woong...
will be dismissed.
I think that's done.
Wrap things up.
JU Construction's extraordinary shareholder meeting...
is concluded.
Thank you.
It's not concluded!
Did you think I'd be detained?
What a shame.
The meeting's over.
You were dismissed.
I'm still a shareholder who owns 13 percent of the company.
I expect a discussion on the agenda I put forward.
Sit back down, everyone.
Please.
Don't close the doors!
I'm expecting someone.
Shin's no longer on the Audit Team,
and he has no right to be here. Don't you see that?
He has...
- a right to be here. - What?
He's a witness who will make a very important statement.
Shall we begin?
Embezzling from an illegal slush fund,
bribery,
and murder of an older brother.
You want me gone for destroying the company's reputation.
That punk there...
is a piece of trash.
Whoever did that deserves to be dismissed.
Right?
Right.
For the exact same charges,
I suggest...
we vote to dismiss President Hwang.
What are you on about?
President Hwang Se Woong...
should be fired for embezzlement, amassing a slush fund,
bribing a high-ranking government official,
and also...
for murder.
That is my agenda.
Can that be proven?
Are you saying we should listen to this nonsense?
I can prove it.
That's why I brought with me...
a witness.
Let's begin.
Take a seat.
I'm Audit Team Manager Shin Cha Il.
(Motion to Dismiss President Hwang)
This is how Director Chae Jong Woo and President Hwang Gun Woong...
put together the slush fund.
Even after President Hwang was admitted to the hospital,
Archcle Design continued to operate.
In other words, the slush fund increased.
That must've been Director Chae's doing.
You're right.
But the actual owner and spender is someone else.
Archcle's money went into developing J-BIMS and research...
at Yulnyeong Factory.
Both projects...
were President Hwang Se Woong's main objectives.
Is there proof...
that Archcle's money went to those two projects?
It was laundered via many routes before flowing to the two projects,
so it's impossible to trace.
So you have no proof?
Director Chae left these records.
These accounts and ledgers record the cash flow.
There's also a taped call...
with President Hwang Se Woong.
I need to make J-BIMS again.
Send the money within the week.
Send a million dollars to fund Yulnyeong Factory's research.
Give more business to Archcle Design.
We need to collect more money.
Hurry.
Do you admit to misappropriating the slush fund?
The slush fund...
was put together by Gun Woong.
I only spent it to better the company.
Yes, that's correct. Hwang Gun Woong put together the slush fund.
But after he passed out and was admitted,
you managed it yourself.
Yes, I did.
Mr. Shin.
You said yourself that the money...
went into developing J-BIMS and modular building research.
Yes. I spent it all on company business.
Is that a problem?
Cut out the nonsense.
That's embezzlement!
Embezzlement?
Can you prove I spent a single cent on myself?
That doesn't matter.
It does matter.
There's a court ruling that if a slush fund's spent on business,
it's not embezzlement.
If the court doesn't say it's illegal,
who are you to say it is?
Is that true?
It is.
There is judicial precedent.
Will you fire me...
for working hard for the company?
You didn't spend the money solely on the company.
What?
Recently, JU Construction's President Hwang Se Woong...
sent me a gift through someone from his office.
But I swear on my sons' lives...
that I accepted it...
thinking it was a gift set that cost under 30 dollars.
However, I checked last night,
and found cash in the box.
I reported it immediately to MOLIT.
I plan to sue President Hwang...
for deceiving me and giving me a bribe.
I will cooperate with authorities in the investigation,
and if anyone were to attempt the same with me,
I promise before the people that I will not turn a blind eye.
How did you get Undersecretary Ahn to flip?
Director Chae made recordings...
whenever he delivered a bribe.
There are three large. Please do us the favor.
Put it in the back.
This isn't all.
It's not all?
No. Wait and see.
I was trying to get him to lift some restrictions.
I'll say this again.
I spent it all for and on the company.
If restrictions are lifted,
it will benefit...
not just us but the whole industry.
Who would dare condemn me?
He told me to look into the Chungon Sports Complex deal.
He wants to keep Hwang Dae Woong in line.
He didn't hesitate to harm the business in order to ruin...
Hwang Dae Woong's chances at taking over.
That's professional negligence.
It's obvious what will happen if he were to take over.
I had to take him out...
like you would a cockroach.
Am I wrong?
You fools.
You don't know what's truly right.
Hwang Se Woong.
What?
Do you want me to watch as they vote to dismiss me?
I'm not interested. Do what you will.
I'm not done listing what you did wrong.
- What? - I said...
the exact same charges.
You...
took a life.
Are you...
resorting to framing me now?
What did we just watch?
I want an explanation.
I will...
explain for you.
No way.
When Audit Team found out...
about the slush fund, Mr. Hwang Se Woong tried...
to kill me and Mr. Shin.
Director Chae.
But Director Chae and I didn't die.
When he heard we were recovering,
he attempted to murder Director Chae again.
Mr. Shin predicted you would do this...
and gave me a warning.
You must be prepared.
Mr. Hwang Se Woong will stir up trouble again.
So I got prepared.
They say he's improving.
I had to persuade the doctor as well as my wife...
to act like I was dead for a day.
Then we passed over the flash drive,
hoping you'd get the punishment you deserve.
You should come clean now.
"Come clean?"
What is he talking about?
This wasn't the first time Mr. Hwang tried to murder someone.
He already killed someone else using the same method.
Former president Hwang Gun Woong.
Stop your nonsense!
On the night of June 4th,
Mr. Hwang Se Woong arrived at the hospital before his brother.
After Mr. Hwang Dae Woong left,
Mr. Hwang Se Woong entered the ward carefully...
via the security cameras' blind spot.
Just like that, he murdered Mr. Hwang Gun Woong...
and left the hospital room.
These needles were found in his office.
Hello, Vice President Hwang.
The president is away at the moment.
I left something here. I'll be quick.
Okay.
The safe is now unlocked.
Gosh.
The same drug in the needle...
was found in the body of the late Mr. Hwang Gun Woong.
He'll be charged with bribery,
attempted murder, and murder.
How could you do that to your own brother?
It's over for you.
It looks like the tables have turned.
President Hwang!
He brought it upon himself.
(JU Construction)
I'm curious about something.
Why did you scout me?
(President Hwang Se Woong)
I'm someone who would audit you too.
Are you okay with that?
If you need to clean up what's stopping JU from progressing,
feel free to do it.
I wanted...
to develop JU Construction...
in fairness and justice.
But corruption was everywhere.
When facing evil,
sometimes you need to become evil too.
Isn't that your theory?
I was the same.
That's sophistry.
No matter how hard you sugarcoat it,
you're the biggest and the most dangerous rat.
And there are no other options for you...
aside from having the law punish you.
Mr. Hwang Se Woong.
You're under arrest...
for murder, attempted murder, and bribery against public servants.
You have the right to remain silent...
and refuse to answer questions.
You have the right to consult an attorney...
Arrest him.
Let's go.
What? Hey, look at that.
JU Construction has a new president.
Will it be okay now?
(Hwang Dae Woong appointed as president)
(JU Construction announces roadmap for overcoming crisis)
Please allow me to be over the top today,
Vice President Hwang. No, President Hwang.
I'm feeling cheeky today.
Go, President Hwang Dae Woong!
Yes!
A big congratulations to you.
My son had to repeat his senior year three times...
before finally getting accepted to the university I went to.
I'm even happier today...
because that's his life.
You becoming president is directly related to my life.
I'm so ecstatic.
By the way, the position for the vice president is vacant.
Someone should fill...
I'm certain someone was suspicious...
of me being a murderer before.
Wasn't that you, Mr. Yang?
Me? Gosh, no.
There's no way.
When I asked you if you trusted me, you hesitated. Right?
Mr. Hwang, at the time,
there was so much fog surrounding me.
I couldn't see anything before me.
I'm weak, I'm just a human.
However, I held on...
to that string of hope.
If it wasn't for my respect and trust in you, I wouldn't be...
You're not made to be a vice president.
Please, Mr. Hwang!
I've been supporting you for over 30 years.
We worked together for over 30 years!
Pour about this much.
(Lemon)
You must all be tired. Please have a drink.
- Thank you. - Nice.
What is this? It's not coffee.
We've been having too much coffee.
- I'll enjoy it. - Okay.
Lemon tea.
Hey, this is nice.
Did you make it yourself?
To wash each lemon one by one...
and to slice them takes too much time.
- So I bought it. - I see.
Han Soo, this is so refreshing.
Things have been so dramatic.
I don't ever want to go through that again.
Seo Jin.
- I'm in your care. - Gosh.
I'm not the one being promoted.
What's with you? Seo Jin's not the President.
- But I'm in your care, too. - Oh, my.
Mr. Shin. Drink one.
Let's have our meeting.
Right.
- Let's go. - Okay.
The sum of the amount spent...
and the amount contracted also match.
The papers had no issues.
Great work. We'll end the meeting here.
Mr. Shin.
We had a lot of work until now.
How about a team dinner to loosen up a bit?
It sounds like a good idea.
We have yet to hold your welcoming party, Mr. Shin.
I'm in.
I'm in, too.
All right.
Did you come here...
to feel a sense of superiority?
- Tell me the truth. - About what?
When Gun Woong lost consciousness for the first time a year ago.
Was that really an accident?
Why do you want to know that?
Answer me.
It was an accident.
(1 year ago)
What brought you all the way here?
Why did you promote Dae Woong to an executive?
He was to be transferred to the province.
That was the plan.
But he turned out to be perceptive...
and sharp.
Right. I can drive him hard.
Is it because he grew up being cautious?
Don't you know he's lobbying people in secret?
He's a piece of trash.
That's the least anyone does in business. It's a custom.
He's better than you who's doing nothing but acting all clean.
Don't you agree?
So what?
Are you using the slush fund as well?
- What? - Did you think I wouldn't know?
Archcle Design.
You created a shell company to raise slush funds.
What? Are you planning...
to increase your share by collecting stocks with that?
You may not know it, but a president needs such money.
"President?"
You're one simply because you were born earlier than me.
This jerk...
You deluded yourself your whole life.
Se Woong.
You didn't lose the presidency because you were younger than me.
Guess what Father said.
"Hwang Se Woong is like a snake."
"He's wicked."
"I'm unable to read him."
"Keeping him by my side is too risky."
Woong.
Even Father cast you aside.
Goodness.
Gosh.
What's this?
Se Woong.
Help me, Se Woong.
I feel dizzy.
Come help me, Se Woong.
Hey.
Call...
Call the ambulance, will you?
Listen. I feel weird.
The world is spinning.
Se Woong...
It's tough, so don't withstand it.
I'll take care of everything from now on.
I'll change everything, including the company.
So...
Stop withstanding it.
That was an accident.
An inevitable...
accident.
Look at you, Shin Cha Il.
You seem a bit relaxed.
Is it because I'm the President?
Can't you respond when someone makes a joke?
I didn't know it was a joke.
I'm the immediate superior of the Audit Team now.
We'll be very busy from now on.
(Letter of Resignation)
What's this?
Are you quitting because I'm the President?
No.
It's because my job here is done.
No. You're not done yet.
So work here for at least another year.
I know how much you care about the company.
However, how you're devoted is quite dangerous and aggressive.
Be careful.
You can continue to act arrogant while working for me, all right?
Excuse me.
(President Hwang Dae Woong)
(Letter of Resignation)
Cheers.
Aren't you going to drink, Mr. Shin?
I'm good.
I've always been curious.
Is that how you usually talk?
I know, right?
Because you're always too formal,
there's a wall between us. You feel very distant, Mr. Shin.
You're doing that on purpose, right?
I've always been like that.
I was joking.
- It was a joke. - You're like an auditing robot.
Mr. Shin. Let's often have meals together.
It's nice and all, isn't it?
He's right.
I have something to inform everyone.
I handed in...
my resignation letter to the President today.
As of today, I'm resigning from the manager position.
What...
So, today is your last day of work?
This is a farewell party, not a welcoming party.
Are you transferring to a new company?
Nothing has been decided yet.
Then can't you work with us longer?
I still have a lot to learn.
All of you have done...
more than enough until now.
Great work, everyone.
Thank you.
Come now. What's with this low spirit?
Let's toast. Come on.
Okay. Let's do that.
What should we toast to?
Let's audit. How about it?
Okay. Here we go.
One, two, three.
- Let's audit. - Let's audit.
Good job, sir.
You did great, sir.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'll walk you to your car.
Do you think...
I'll do well?
You asked...
why I risked my life to audit.
Something happened not long after I started as an auditor.
I noticed...
the amount of rebars we bought didn't correspond with the expenses.
What about this?
Your audit report on the procurement of construction materials.
We did purchase 300 tons of rebar.
Why did you pay the company for 420 tons, then?
Why? Do you think I'm taking a cut...
to let someone steal rebars?
- No, but... - That we'll use less rebars...
and let our buildings crumble?
That's not what I'm saying.
Let's get back to work.
I believed my superior's vague explanation.
No.
It was more like I didn't want to cause trouble.
I should trust someone on my team.
I shouldn't doubt.
A building under construction collapsed?
At which site?
Dad.
It's dangerous. You can't get closer.
You can't go inside.
- Hey. - No.
Stay with me!
Will you get more help?
We'll all die at this rate!
Father.
Father. I'm here.
Father!
I never supported you the way other dads did.
And you still got into a great construction company.
Good luck.
Father!
Help!
And so...
because I turned from the truth,
- Father! - a building project collapsed,
and I lost my father.
That's when I realized...
that auditing...
involves human lives.
I also wish for the world you want...
where trust means something.
But until then,
you must keep a clear outlook.
Goodbye.
Sir.
For everything so far...
Thank you so much.
Goodbye.
(JU Construction)
What's going on?
Shall we do the interview here?
What?
That's a list of transactions on your company credit card.
Do you admit to using it...
for personal expenses?
Don't you think Han Soo has changed?
Yes, totally.
He's no longer Gu Han Soo.
He's Gu Cha Il.
That's what I thought.
I still feel his presence.
"Let's have a meeting."
Oh, well.
I wonder when this desk will have an owner.
My feelers tell me...
- one thing is for sure. - What's that?
That desk...
will not be yours.
Ms. Ok. Attack me all you want.
I am merciful.
Are you?
I am. I'm merciful.
I wonder...
- if Seo Jin's settling in. - Come on.
Why worry about her?
She's smart and hardworking...
and will do great anywhere.
(Housing Team)
(Tahyeon District Happy Town Business Plan)
Seo Jin.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I shudder a bit whenever you say that.
Can you finish the business plan within the week?
Yes.
Hello.
Seo Jin.
- Long time no see. - Yes.
How's your new team?
It's fun.
Building something to help others.
I find it worthwhile.
I was really upset when you said you'd transfer.
It's nice to see you're happy there.
I heard you got a new manager.
Your team will get back on track soon.
Yes. We must work even harder.
They are accepting volunteers to transfer to the Florida office.
Did you apply?
Here we go.
- The main dish is here. - Gosh.
It looks even nicer today.
Didn't you go a bit overboard?
I wanted to cook this for you...
as soon as I heard you got promoted. Eat all you want.
It's awesome today.
It's extra tasty.
I think you should...
open a restaurant near my office.
I'll eat there every day.
Will that make me a president too?
Yes, it will.
Hey.
Two out of three people here will be business owners?
I feel left out.
All you have to do is work hard...
and serve the two business owners.
Okay, kiddo?
Yes, sir. I'll do that, sir.
- Enjoy your food. - Thank you.
It's different now that I'm a company president.
There are extra ingredients today.
To celebrate my promotion.
Should I find a place to open a restaurant?
- I'll find a place for you. - You will?
Han Soo.
No more embezzling from now on.
What?
- Hey. - You can't steal anymore.
Here, Mother.
Thank you.
You've changed, Han Soo.
I haven't.
He's a traitor.
You should change a bit too.
I'm way too cute already.
You're what?
You still haven't grown up.
- That hurts. - Darn you.
My gosh.
Mr. Shin Cha Il?
Who are you?
My name is Kim Si Hyun. That's where I work.
You've caught plenty of little rats.
Now, let's go and catch a big one.
(Director of Public Sector Inspection, Kim Si Hyun)
(The Board of Audit and Inspection of the Republic of Korea)
(The Auditors)
(Special thanks to Jung Dong Hwan, Jung Jin Young, Heo Joon Seok, )
(Lee Gyu Hoe, and Jeon Su Ji)
("I'll Be There" by Kim So Yeon is available...)
(on all music streaming platforms.)
(Thank you for watching "The Auditors".)