1 HOUR AFTER THE ZOMBIE OUTBREAK
AT THE TEMPORARY QUARANTINE FACILITY
It's safer on the second floor.
I'm scared.
I don't feel good about this.
Be careful.
Close the door.
- Close it.
- Close the door.
Close the door.
EMERGENCY! THE BAG IS CAUGHT IN THE DOOR
What's wrong?
Oh, no!
Hurry!
No way!
No!
Go!
Unbelievable.
It's behind you.
QUEST: DEFEAT THE ZOMBIES
AND ESCAPE THE ENDLESS LOOP OF DEATH
Be careful! Go!
The cabinet!
What is it?
What's this cabinet for?
I don't know. Behind you!
STORAGE CABINETS
ARE PLACED THROUGHOUT HALL
EACH IS LARGE ENOUGH TO FIT A PERSON
Careful! Behind you!
Keep running.
Don't stop.
Watch your step.
This is endless.
A LOOPED SPACE WITH
THE START AND END CONNECTED
THERE'S NOWHERE TO HIDE
EXCEPT IN THE CABINETS
There's another one here.
They are coming.
THE ENTRANCE IS BLOCKED BY THE ZOMBIES
Watch out!
What?
THE CABINET IS LOCKED
We need to get in.
QUEST OBJECTIVES: FIND THE KEYS,
HIDE IN THE CABINETS, ESCAPE THE FLOOR
We need to find the keys?
The key box.
Look for the key.
MUST FIND THE CABINET KEYS
Find the key.
The key!
Where's the key?
Thank you!
Do you see it on the zombies?
- The key box!
- Is this it?
It's here.
FIND THE KEYS
Open them one by one.
One by one.
Did you find it?
- I'm looking around.
- Unlock it.
Try unlocking it.
- It's unlocked.
- Is it?
I'll leave it ajar here.
- He unlocked it.
- Get in.
Get in.
- Is it unlocked?
- Yes!
I have the keys.
Wait, close it.
NICE! HIDING IS EFFECTIVE
TAEYEON, get in there.
You'll find the keys there.
Where?
Get in now!
Over here.
I'm scared.
THE ZOMBIES CAN'T OPEN THE CABINETS
- Let's go.
- Okay!
Turn it.
- Okay.
- To the left.
Okay!
FIERCE ORDERS FROM THE FORMER SERGEANT!
How many cabinets?
How many?
One, two, three, four, five!
- Five?
- I see five.
There are six of us.
Run.
THE ENTRANCE IS BLOCKED,
AND THERE AREN'T ENOUGH CABINETS
IF YOU DON'T HIDE, YOU'RE IN DANGER!
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
We need one more to open.
THE LAST CABINET ISN'T OPENING EASILY
Let's just catch them.
Let's catch them.
TAEYEON TAKES A NEW APPROACH!
Let's lock that zombie in.
- Lock it in here.
- What?
Leave the two open.
Leave them open right now.
They're open.
More zombies incoming.
Hurry this way.
MORE ZOMBIES APPEAR OVER TIME
We have to put the zombies in the cabinet.
Let's lock them in here.
THEY'RE CHOOSING TO FIGHT INSTEAD
We've got to get him in.
Teamwork.
THEY CHOOSE TO DITCH THEIR TEAMMATE
THANK YOU FOR YOUR SERVICE, ANDRE RUSH
HE TAKES ON BOTH SIMULTANEOUSLY
Chef!
Run!
Andre, run!
FIGHTING 3 ZOMBIES
IS DIFFICULT EVEN FOR HIM
We need to lure them away.
Why don't we…
Leave it open.
Okay, got it.
Got it.
IT'S NOT EASY TO LOCK THE ZOMBIES AWAY
Hold the door open.
Open it.
HE'S NOT FALLING FOR IT AGAIN
- Block them.
- Good idea.
Wait.
Wait, turn it this way.
Let go of it and turn it.
Let's turn it around.
Turn it around.
Turn it now.
Hey.
Sae-ho, just go.
Leave it and go.
Let go of it.
Hey! There's more?
Let's just leave it. Let go!
- More!
- Open it.
Behind you! Block them.
Block them and push this one in.
Push it in.
- Okay.
- Hold on to it.
Okay.
Block them.
- Are you blocking?
- Yes.
- It worked.
- Okay.
Push.
Push!
- There are 3 of them.
- No.
THE BLOCKAGE IS CAUSING ZOMBIES TO PILE UP
Where's Chef?
Chef!
Let's go.
THE ROK-US ALLIANCE STILL STANDS!
WE GO TOGETHER!
Let's go.
Push.
Push it in.
- More!
- Okay, great.
Stay still.
Hey!
What is it?
It's not locked.
Go.
Run!
Oh, my gosh.
BREAKING NEWS! ALLIANCE TERMINATED
Shoot.
This is ridiculous.
It's open?
- Darn, it is.
- Let's try again.
THE FREED ZOMBIE LOOKS A BIT SMUG
Let's add one more to that.
Can I take a break?
- My knees hurt.
- Hide.
Okay.
EXHAUSTED FROM THE BATTLE,
THEY TAKE A BREAK
I need to catch my breath.
Andre, please take a rest.
THE SMUG ZOMBIE NEARS THE CABINET
THE ZOMBIE IS VERY ANGRY
THE ZOMBIE IS BEYOND ANGRY
How do we lure him away?
They're a team. Tear them apart.
How do we do that?
I will use this. I have a stocking.
Somebody can hide in here,
go behind, open this door?
Right? Have her go up this way.
THE FORMER SERGEANT ADJUSTS THE STRATEGY
This person come out with stocking.
- Push him.
- What?
AN INTERPRETER IS NEEDED
Somebody get in here.
We've got to trap 'em.
Let's get the double… The one door.
Yeah, she'll be here…
No, she runs this way.
THE ALLIANCE FALLS APART AGAIN
Let's run one more lap first.
One more time.
One more lap.
Baby, one more time.
This won't work.
MORE ZOMBIES INCOMING
What?
What's going on?
CODE KUNST IS STUCK
That door is open.
It's that door.
BE QUICK! ZOMBIES WILL KEEP MULTIPLYING
Why are there more?
We need to lock them up.
Get it over with.
This way!
How are we supposed to lock them in?
Push them in.
Hold on to it here.
Shoot.
Go in.
Run!
Grab her and take her down.
THE HANDMADE ARM GUARD PROVED INVALUABLE
- This way.
- In here.
This way!
Okay, I'm grabbing onto it.
NOW, ONLY THREE ZOMBIES REMAIN!
It's empty.
Block them first.
Block them.
Grab it.
- Here.
- Use this.
Chef!
Hug him from behind.
Chef, hug him.
Hug!
- Andre.
- Catch him.
Hug, please!
Get out now.
Grab it.
- Open.
- Hold on!
- Wait?
- Where are the keys?
I'll just hold onto it.
Let go.
Let's go. Hurry!
- Behind you.
- Okay.
Hurry!
No, quickly!
Let's go.
Okay.
Look.
Okay!
It worked.
- Great job.
- Gosh.
Damn zombies!
I hate damn zombies!
Andre!
- We did it.
- I hate zombies!
You did great.
DESPITE THE UPS AND DOWNS,
THE ALLIANCE REMAINED STRONG
It was worth making this gear.
One, two, three, we got this!
QUEST COMPLETE
EVERYONE SURVIVED
- Should I climb up?
- Yes.
MEANWHILE, ON THE NET OUTSIDE THE FACILITY
No zombies here.
There are no zombies here.
No, not this way!
Be careful, Si-young!
Watch out!
THAT WAS A CLOSE CALL
Hold on.
Head to your left!
My left?
THE SECOND FLOOR HAS ZOMBIES EVERYWHERE
We have to stay in the middle.
But there are more above.
Above?
Dex!
Should I go to the middle?
THE THIRD FLOOR WINDOW IS THEIR ONLY HOPE
I'll climb up another floor.
There are more above you.
DESPITE THE SHOCK, SHE TAKES THE LEAD!
There are more.
Geez.
Okay.
Careful!
It's clear here.
Here too, Si-young!
Gosh.
She managed to break it!
- Hey, Dex.
- Yes.
Will it break if I hit it?
Softly? Will I get hurt?
No…
- Use your foot.
- My foot?
Are you sure?
- Kick!
- Kick it?
Kick it!
TSK-TSK! YOU NEED TO ACT YOUR AGE AT 31
Shoot, I did it!
He did it!
SUCCESSFULLY FOUND THE ESCAPE ROUTES
- We're heading in.
- Okay.
Follow her lead.
Let's help Tsuki first. Hold her.
Okay, hold on.
QUEST COMPLETE
DinDin!
Let's bounce.
Smoke grenades!
This is it! Fire in the hole!
Hey! Careful!
Second!
Smoke grenades!
- Smoke grenades!
- This is the third one.
Let's go, stay close.
Who was that?
Let's go!
Come on! Run!
Run!
Watch out! Behind you!
They are coming!
Be careful.
Let's go.
ZOMBIEVERSE
NEW BLOOD
THE NEXT DAY
A BURGER JOINT BY THE BEACH
AFTER ESCAPING THE QUARANTINE FACILITY,
THEY ARRIVE AT SI-YOUNG AND DEX'S LODGING
Hey, Patricia.
How did we make it alive?
Tell me about it.
JOINED
I'm so drowsy and hungry.
I'm exhausted.
They seem to get along like siblings.
Patricia hasn't been this happy in ages.
- Ready? Let's go, this way.
- Yes.
She must have more energy than us.
She wouldn't have survived with us.
Good thing she stayed.
That's why we told her to wait here.
That was just yesterday.
Are they trustworthy?
Well, they're experienced with zombies.
I'm a bit wary since we don't know them.
Understandable.
I'm wary of them.
Who's that guy?
Chungju Man…
A civil servant.
Level 6 civil servant.
We aren't sure
how they will benefit us yet.
We need a few days.
So you weren't originally with them?
Yes, we met them in Jeju.
I haven't seen you two around.
How did you get here?
Patricia, Dex, and I got lucky. We got in
an amphibious vehicle and came here.
ESCAPING WOLMIDO
We got to this burger joint
and have been staying here since.
- After the quarantine?
- Yes.
It was peaceful until yesterday
when we saw a suspicious truck
and chased it down.
Then came the zombies out of nowhere.
It's your first time with zombies, right?
- Yes.
- It's my first time.
- Me too.
- That was my first.
How did you get here?
Everyone here?
I was here for a music video production…
- Music video?
- What?
That's news.
I didn't bring it up because…
- You're hiding a lot.
- I was shy.
The last music video with Chang-hee was…
Where's Chang-hee?
He's gone.
THE STORY IS STILL A TEARJERKER
No, there was this sudden crisis and…
What's so funny?
CRYING FROM EMBARRASSMENT
I'm sure…
He's crying.
I'm sure you all know this,
but his fiancée also…
Yes.
I've always been curious,
does your fiancée even exist?
What?
That's rude of you to ask.
Well, I've never met her before.
This is why I wear
these sunglasses, to hide my tears.
The glasses are too clear.
We can see through them.
Anyways, this should be our base camp
since we have food here.
We still need to prepare an escape plan,
just in case there's a zombie attack.
How do we get out of here?
Realistically, it's either
by boat or a plane.
That's all.
Do you know how to fly a plane?
He's not a jack-of-all-trades.
HE'S BEEN MISTAKEN
You fell for him yesterday.
Please don't grab me.
Wait. Excuse me, Dex!
- Hold on.
- Wait.
AMID THE CHAOS, THEY FOUND A PRECIOUS BOND
If you don't mind me asking,
how old are you?
- I'm 30 years old.
- You're 30?
Me too.
You guys are the same age.
Nice to meet you, friend.
- Nice…
- Can we be…
Can we be friends?
Of course.
It's the start of our friendship.
WE ROOT FOR THEIR NEWFOUND FRIENDSHIP!
He's sharpening his knife.
ANDRE IS ABOUT TO SHOW HIS SKILLS!
Thank you.
Look at his blazing eyes.
- Oh, okay.
- Let's do this.
Smells delicious!
- Smells good.
- Wow, patty.
I love patties, wow!
I'm hungry.
Patricia, can you ask him
how much longer it'll take?
She can't speak English.
How many long…
WHY IS SHE CLAPPING?
How long will it take?
Tell them to count to 100 in English.
Oh, one hundred.
One hundred minutes?
COMMUNICATION FAILURES CONTINUE
Chef, how long will it take?
Count to 100 in English. It'll be done.
Count to 100 English, it's down.
THIS ISN'T PRO-WRESTLING
- Done.
- Done!
Count?
Yes.
Let's go!
Okay, just give it to me.
- That's teamwork, right?
- Yeah, teamwork.
What does that mean?
Yeah, teamwork.
What does it mean?
Teamwork.
What is teamwork?
Teamwork, we are a team.
Teamwork…
- Thank…
- Thank you.
JUST BETTER TO END IT HERE
Thank you.
- Little salt?
- Salt.
Okay, ready to feed them?
Finished.
Time to eat!
Oh, please!
- Time to eat.
- Please, Andre!
- Please!
- We're so hungry.
So hungry, let's go.
Thank you! Brother, thank you!
There are two flavors.
Yes, that's great.
It's delicious.
Every meal could be our last meal.
It's so damn good.
HE CAN'T HELP BUT RAVE
THE CHEF'S ROLE IS CRUCIAL
IN A SURVIVAL SITUATION!
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
You're my treasure.
I love your burger.
Thank you.
This is what the American presidents had.
- Really?
- Yes, he cooked for them.
Chef, whose favorite is this?
Donald Trump or Biden?
Obama's favorite?
Sensitive topic?
HE'S TAKEN ABACK!
Oh, sorry!
It's a touchy subject.
Thank you.
I love it here.
Can we stay here
until the rescue team arrives?
I agree. I'm so happy here.
Let's just stay here.
Officer, is there a bunker nearby?
A bunker for national emergencies?
There should be one.
There is an evacuation facility
at the provincial office.
Provincial office?
Is everyone allowed in?
Not everyone.
But they let most citizens in.
I've done Ulchi Freedom Shield exercises.
They all operate the same way.
The provincial office
is the safest during a crisis.
If there's a crisis,
do we run to the provincial office?
- Yes.
- Always?
Yes. All the forces will unite.
Really?
All the forces will unite there.
I wasn't aware.
If the office collapses, we're doomed.
- We're doomed?
- Yes.
We need to make sure
if it's safe there first.
Yes, you're right.
But how?
Communication is key in times like these.
How about that radio?
CAN THIS OLD RADIO HELP?
They broadcast
emergency alerts on the radio, right?
- It might help us.
- True.
THEY ALSO FOUND A RADIO
AT THE QUARANTINE FACILITY YESTERDAY
Should we turn on the radio?
IT JUST ENDED WITH A SING-ALONG
We need the right frequency.
All broadcasts are currently suspended.
We apologize for any inconvenience
caused to our listeners.
All broadcasts are currently suspended…
That's it?
Try changing it.
Is it in Chinese?
IT'S DEFINITELY ENGLISH
Isn't he speaking English?
English?
Do we have to head to the States?
Should I write this down?
Seoul was hit the hardest,
then Jeju Island after that.
What?
The quarantine facility took a big hit.
DUE TO THE INCREASE OF EVACUEES,
JEJU HAS TAKEN A MASSIVE HIT
Jeju? Second most infected.
Second most infected…
We fled to a place
that's even more dangerous.
Okay.
Some NGO has sent out helicopters
to rescue people but…
We have to evacuate.
RESCUE HELICOPTERS ARE BEING SENT OUT
BY THE GLOBAL URGENT RELIEF ALLIANCE
But did the radio mention
where we get on the helicopter?
We need to find out
where we get on the helicopter.
Wait, what's our location?
JEJU PROVINCE MAP
Wait, hold on.
Wait…
THEY'RE ANNOUNCING
THE COORDINATES OF THE RESCUE POINT!
Bring it here.
Write it down.
Does anyone have a pen?
We need to listen for Jeju Island.
I'll give you a tip,
just write down anything you hear.
Don't write that down.
DON'T MISTAKEN JEBU-DO FOR JEJU!
NOW'S THE TIME FOR JEJU ISLAND!
I got it!
Thirty-three degrees!
Twenty-seven north.
- One hundred twenty-six degrees.
- And thirty-two.
- Thirty-two.
- Thirty-two minutes!
- Six seconds.
- Sixty east.
THEY GOT THE COORDINATES!
- Is it 126 and 32?
- Yes.
It's here!
It's six.
It'll take about 32 minutes.
Oh, it's the coordinates…
HE'S FALLING BEHIND
If you go straight like this,
it's Odeung-dong.
It's Odeung-dong.
There's a rampart here.
Wouldn't we get there quicker on that?
I saw them nearby.
Go!
Let's go!
Here we go!
1 HOUR LATER
HEADING TO THE RESCUE COORDINATES
Are you okay?
No, are you okay?
You're too close.
WATCH OUT FOR FRONT AND BACK VIBRATIONS
Can you back off a little?
I'm too close.
- What?
- I'm too close.
I've been meaning to ask,
did you stuff peas in your pants?
What?
Zombie!
- Shoot.
- There are more!
It's a solider zombie.
ZOMBIES IN ARMY UNIFORMS
Go!
Sit properly.
Move.
Shoot!
More zombies!
Darn!
Shoot!
- Wow, gosh.
- Patricia, we've got to go.
Dang!
Are we on track?
It's this way, right?
It must be somewhere here.
I hear the helicopter!
Helicopter!
I see it!
Where is it going?
- Hey!
- Over here!
Here!
We're here!
Chase it!
Here!
Go after it!
It's an actual helicopter.
We're here.
- Over here!
- Here!
- We made it!
- Over here!
- We did it!
Here!
- We made it alive.
- Here!
Here!
It's landing!
It's coming down!
- Here!
- We are safe now!
- We did it.
- Yes, we did.
- Here!
- We're alive!
We're here.
- Here!
- The helipad.
- Over there.
- Here.
Do you have smoke grenades?
Smoke grenades?
- Is it landing?
- Here!
- We did it.
- It's coming.
Let's go. Go!
We did it.
Let's head there first.
- Come on!
- Let's go.
We did it!
Go!
- Please save us.
- Hold on!
- No!
- What? Why?
Why?
The fuel tank is empty.
It's empty.
We don't have fuel.
No fuel.
- No more fuel.
- Empty tank.
No fuel.
Come this way!
They need to fill the tank.
There's no fuel in the tank
so takeoff isn't possible.
No fuel?
There should be a fuel depot there.
- Beyond that building.
- Okay.
Please bring the fuel over here.
There's none here.
We need to bring the fuel here.
We can get on it, right?
Yes, you can.
Now, hurry along!
- Hurry.
- Run.
Run!
I see the fuel depot!
QUEST: FILL THE FUEL TANK AND ESCAPE
THE FUEL DEPOT IS LOCATED
ON TOP OF THE HILL
500 L OF FUEL NEEDED
THEY NEED TO FILL THE TANK
USING 20 L CONTAINERS TO TAKEOFF
The tree is in our way.
WATCH OUT FOR OBSTRUCTIONS
Zombies might appear again.
HEADING TOWARDS THE FUEL DEPOT
We need to pump it out
into the containers.
Let's use this.
Pump it out.
Do you know how?
It's going to smell bad.
Oh, it's working.
It's working.
- Use both hands.
- Okay.
Faster!
What if we roll the barrel there?
We can't do that.
The tree is in the way.
You're right.
Wait, another container.
- Bring it!
- Come on now.
WHAT A WASTE OF THE COUNTRY'S TAX MONEY
Hold on, this is heavy.
It's full.
I'll take this first.
We need 500 liters worth of fuel.
Is this okay?
Yes, leave them here and bring more.
25 CONTAINERS TO FILL UP THE TANK
Let's go!
THE CIVIL SERVANT IS STEPPING IN
What's he doing?
He's moving it. Let's help him.
Clear the way!
Here we go. Hop it over!
We'll pull it, easy. Pull it.
Pull it, push it.
No!
- Push it.
- We need your power.
It's okay.
Let's go!
THE CHEERLEADER IS THE STRONGEST
Please hurry!
We need to fill up to 500 L!
Here we go.
Pick up high!
There you go.
Perfect.
THE CHEERLEADER SEEMS LIKE
THE MOST EXHAUSTED ONE
Thirty more to go.
I was told that we need 500 L.
Let's go!
NOW, THEY CAN DELIVER IT WITH THE ATV
So this is how it feels
to be on an ATV with a man.
You're getting too close.
Don't misunderstand.
I'll just carry them.
I can do it.
Why does it need so much fuel?
WITH THE OBSTACLES GONE,
EVERYTHING'S MOVING SMOOTHLY!
It's all over me.
We need to check the gauge.
This is taking quite a while.
You push the tab.
I got it.
I got mine.
It's filling up.
We're close.
- Get moving.
- Hurry.
Let's hurry up!
- Run.
- Go.
10 MINUTES EARLIER
Did you see its size?
Yes.
Hey, let's go.
It's a small helicopter.
We are not going to fit.
There are 12 of us.
Really?
It can only fit nine or ten people.
THE HELICOPTER IS TOO SMALL
Leave it here.
It's unsettling.
What do we do?
What's up?
We can't all fit.
Not all of us.
We are too heavy…
Just by looking at the size of that,
it's clear this many people won't fit.
Hold on.
NOT ENOUGH SPACE FOR 12 PEOPLE
Can it fit the 12 of us?
- Is it possible?
- We might exceed the limit.
- Really?
- Yes.
EVEN IF THEY SQUEEZE IN,
THEY WILL EXCEED THE WEIGHT LIMIT
I'm worried about the limit.
Consider the worst-case scenario.
We might have to part ways here.
But they're working so hard.
It feels wrong to talk behind their backs.
- Yes.
- Start.
Grab it.
Slowly.
What a chaos.
But it's clear that your experience
is helping the team overall.
We'll make it out together.
Of course.
Should I just call you Si-young?
- Sure.
- I was born in 1982.
- Me too!
- What?
- I was born in 1982.
- Not 1981?
Year of the Dog.
That's right!
We're the same age.
A START OF ANOTHER FRIENDSHIP
We're friends. We are the same age.
How old are you? What year were you born?
I'm 22.
- What?
- I'm 22.
What?
- You're 22?
- Yeah.
That's crazy.
DIFFICULT AMERICAN HUMOR
Which year were you born?
- No.
- You're 22?
Yeah.
- You're 22 years old?
- Yeah.
ANDRE, BORN IN 1974
AND JOINED THE ARMY IN 1993
What?
I could pass as his aunt.
What, why?
- Okay.
- You're 22?
- Oh, no, I'm 32.
HIS AMERICAN HUMOR IS CONFUSING THEM
You're ten years younger than me?
- I'm 43.
- Okay.
Andre is born in the year of 1993.
What?
Andre? Born in 1993?
- You're a baby.
- Yeah.
A baby!
72% OF FUEL LEFT FOR TAKEOFF
Hey, captain!
Does the helicopter
require this much fuel?
- Hold on.
- Yes.
Here…
How many of us can fit in this?
I'll explain later.
Just give me a rough number.
I need to know as
I'm the leader of the pack.
- If lighter people board…
- Got it.
- Lock it.
- Yes.
Okay, I'll carry it.
Now, one, two, three!
Captain…
We will check the gauge
after we have everyone on board.
Also…
Please know that I have a wife and kids.
- Do you?
- What?
SO DESPERATE THAT HE MADE UP
A VIRTUAL FAMILY
- We'll be back.
- Okay.
We're almost there.
Defconn's been talking
to the captain for a while.
Something's fishy.
How much do you weigh?
- I'm 45 kg.
- Oh, 45 kg?
- Yes?
- And you?
- I'm 53 kg.
- Hey.
Don't worry, I won't ask you.
Why not?
I'm checking people who are lighter.
You're 45 kg?
I'm 52 kg.
I'm 57 kg.
And yourself?
Well, I did lose weight.
Ninety?
I'm 73 kg.
That's nonsense!
You're risking our lives by lying.
That's around my weight.
It doesn't make sense.
It's the truth…
How heavy are you?
He said 73 kg.
I'm 72 kg.
I'm wearing a lot of layers.
I'm 140 kg.
OH MY! THE HEAVIEST OF THEM ALL
Now, listen up.
Andre weighs 140 kg.
That's four times TAEYEON's weight.
- Four times.
- Don't say that.
We could fit four of her.
What's happening?
HE URGENTLY NEEDS TO LEARN KOREAN
One hundred forty.
One hundred forty?
Patricia, listen up.
Andre…
- What is it?
- He's going to survive no matter what.
THROWS ANDRE UNDER THE BUS
So we should leave him behind?
Be quiet!
- Hey!
- Yes.
Thank you.
HE NEEDS TO RELEARN KOREAN
Why are you guys looking at me?
Because your muscle is my type. Okay?
Thank you.
- That was random.
- But…
What's going on there?
Talking about their weights.
But Defconn is lying that he weighs 70 kg.
Can't we just use TAEYEON as our standard?
Keep it simple, that's complicated.
How about using Patricia as our standard?
What?
I don't know her weight.
From what I see,
Patricia is similar to Andre.
What are you talking about?
It's true.
But we must remember,
the world needs comedians
to keep humor alive.
The world needs humor.
In that case, we have Sae-ho…
This should be enough.
I feel anxious being away
from the group like this.
Come on, it's a life-or-death decision.
We'll all die at this rate.
You should stay then.
Wait.
Hold on, listen.
I know what you're saying.
I know what you're talking about.
Not me, he said…
I know you said
I'm too heavy for the helicopter.
HE FINALLY UNDERSTANDS KOREAN
No, you're very light!
Come with me.
- No, that's not it.
- Okay, go with you.
No, no.
You know, I fly helicopters.
- I know helicopters.
- You do?
You can fly helicopters?
No, I fly in the helicopter.
I'm from the military.
Let's get rid of the pilots.
A NEW APPROACH
- Can you fly one?
- Wait.
He can fly one.
We have a pilot.
No, he doesn't know how to fly
a helicopter. We need a pilot.
Okay, we've got to take a vote.
- A boat?
- Yeah.
- Boat?
- Where's the boat?
Andre knows where the boat is.
No, he wants us to vote!
INTERPRETER NEEDED!
We're going to vote.
If people think I'm too heavy,
just say yes.
Let's be honest.
You know, honestly?
The heaviest should stay.
Lighter people can board.
Let's sort this.
We don't have time for this, keep moving.
If we balance the weight right,
we can fit more people, right?
We can leave everything behind.
Please keep moving!
- Bring fuel!
- Let's empty our bags.
Bring more fuel!
We have more here.
Bring the empty ones.
Please hurry!
Load it.
48% OF FUEL LEFT FOR TAKEOFF
We can't have everyone on board.
I'm worried.
We should assess the situation.
I think we should use
this fuel to make a deal with them.
PLOTS ARE BEING HATCHED
If you want the fuel, guarantee us seats.
How much fuel does it need?
This is bad though. We can't all fit.
Come here.
Are you going to stay?
I don't want to part ways with you.
The three of us need to get on.
- Of course.
- Got it.
What if everyone's
already on the helicopter?
Then we don't give them the fuel.
So this is what Defconn meant.
What did he say?
Get over there.
Strange plots are going around.
Why are you so skeptical?
That no one can be trusted.
But what's he doing?
He's not helping out.
He's talking to the captain.
- He's playing politics.
- Exactly.
You're on my side, right?
Think about it rationally. It makes sense
for the heavier ones to stay.
But if we go by weight, I'm in trouble.
HE SHOULDN'T HAVE SAID THAT
What do you think of Sae-ho?
Well, Sae-ho is…
He's trying to impress Andre.
To survive?
YOU'RE A TARGET ONCE OUT OF SIGHT
Is there a way to lose weight
in half an hour?
22% OF FUEL LEFT FOR TAKEOFF
Please hurry!
It feels like we're in an action movie.
We can all go.
We saw a few zombies
in the forest just now.
I'm worried
that the sound of the helicopter
will attract the zombies.
We have to speed up.
Start the engine.
There's no time!
- Let's bring them all.
- Wait.
We have to go!
Should we take these?
Should I?
Go!
We've got to go faster.
We need about three to four more.
Now, hurry!
It's empty now.
Wait, hold on…
TANK FULL
Number two engine start.
What?
It's moving.
- What?
- It's moving.
This should be the last container.
Yes, bring it.
I'll do it alone.
Are you sure?
I'll be fine.
Stay alive.
Alive?
I'm just looking out for you.
We're almost done.
Is it enough?
Hold on.
Should we get on?
- Everyone, get on.
- We can, right?
- Can we board now?
- Call them.
- We're done.
- Do we go back?
Call them back.
Wait, do we have to?
- Do we?
- Stay here.
Are you all going?
- Wait.
- Bring them.
Stay here.
Do we need to?
Hurry up!
What?
- Tsuki!
- Hurry up!
Over here, quickly!
Quickly!
- Run quickly!
- Hurry!
It's moving!
What?
- Bro!
- Okay, let's go.
Hurry!
- It's moving!
- Let's go!
- Come quickly!
- Quick!
Let's just leave it.
Let's go!
What?
Code Kunst! Hey!
Stay alive.
What was that about?
Ladies, get on first.
Get on!
- Just in case.
- Get on first.
Get in! Hurry!
The helicopter?
What?
Leave it!
Oh, no!
Step on this.
Quick!
- Get on.
- Get in now!
Get in!
Hurry up!
Tsuki!
Hurry!
Get in.
Be quick!
Run!
Defconn!
Shoot!
No!
First engine, clear.
Is the engine on?
Wait!
No!
Let's go!
He's going to survive no matter what.
I know what you're saying.
You said I'm too heavy.
Oh, no. Come with me.
Consider the worst-case scenario.
We might have to part ways here.
LATECOMERS MIGHT MISS THE RIDE
No!
Can we all get on?
Just get on first!
This way.
How did you get in there?
THERE'S NOT A LOT OF SPACE LEFT
There's no space.
Run quickly!
No! It's over!
I'm sorry!
Just go.
10 PEOPLE ON BOARD
EXCEPT SAE-HO AND DEFCONN
I don't want to part ways with you.
Of course.
Just go.
- Let's go.
- What?
- Hey.
- Bro!
- Save yourself.
- Let's go.
Bro!
Sae-ho, just get on.
Let's go.
Get on first.
- Bro!
- Get on.
You can't get on!
- Defconn, no!
- Get out!
We don't have room!
Sae-ho…
Get off.
You get off!
Defconn, no!
Let's go.
You'll fall.
Come on, right here.
Code Kunst, are you okay?
Hey, right here.
Wait.
Are you okay?
Sae-ho, get off if it hurts too much.
No, I'm fine.
What's wrong?
My pinky finger…
Hey!
Is it me?
I almost lost my finger.
Well, if that's the case,
- isn't it better if you get off?
- I'm fine.
EVERYONE IS ON BOARD
We did it!
It worked out!
We made it!
We made it alive!
We did it!
- Check.
- Okay.
- We made it.
- We lived!
- Good job, guys.
Great job!
It worked out!
Good job!
Let's go!
We're going home.
It's moving.
It's in the air!
It's flying!
We're off the ground.
Here we go!
Why?
It can't take off?
What's with the beeping?
Is it not going to take off?
Captain, why aren't we going?
Weight limit exceeded.
- Why?
- It's going back.
- What's going on?
- What?
- Why?
- We're going back down?
Why?
- Hey!
- Why?
- What is it?
Turn off the engine.
Where are you going?
He got off.
- Why did he get off?
- Why?
- Everyone, please get off.
- Everyone, get off!
- Why?
What's happening?
It can't bear our weight.
Do we get off?
Yes.
Please get off.
Everyone, get off now.
What's the issue?
- Why aren't we going?
- Listen up.
What's the matter?
We exceeded the weight limit.
There's a weight limit.
We can't bring everyone with us.
MAXIMUM WEIGHT LIMIT 2,720 KG
−HELICOPTER 1,500 KG
−FUEL 400 KG
−TWO PILOTS 160 KG
THERE IS ONLY ROOM FOR 660 KG
Is another helicopter on its way?
Yes. Please decide quickly.
RESCUE IS ONGOING,
ANOTHER HELICOPTER WILL COME
QUEST: MEET THE WEIGHT LIMIT
AND ESCAPE JEJU ISLAND
How much do we weigh altogether?
How heavy are you?
I'm 75 or 76.
Dex is 76 and I'm 52.
She weighs 53.
- And 72, 76…
- Are you adding it up?
I have my phone.
- His has power.
- Yes.
Use your phone.
I'll calculate it.
Here, 53, 52.
- He's 76.
- Add 76…
I'm 72.
I'm 45.
- Officer?
- I'm 69 kg.
I'm 140 kg.
We've reached 507 kg.
THEY STILL NEED TO ADD FIVE MORE PEOPLE
Just finish calculating.
- I'm 71.
- He's 71.
- DinDin?
- I'm 57.
- Patricia?
- Me?
CONFIDENTIAL
Is there room for 91kg?
- Adding 91.
- I'm 70.
- Seventy?
- Don't lie.
I'm not lying.
That can't be right.
I'm telling you the truth…
NO ONE BELIEVES HIM
Geez.
We've reached 869 kg in total.
We are 209 kg over.
Really?
No point lying about your weight.
Yes, it's dangerous.
EVEN AFTER DITCHING THE LOAD,
THEY'RE STILL ABOUT 200 KG OVER
That means we need to leave three behind.
Three?
But it's better to carry
as many people as we can.
It's right to take
the maximum number of people.
That's right.
I agree.
MAXIMUM NUMBER OF PEOPLE MEANS…
If Andre decides to stay behind,
we just need one more person.
Andre can take that role.
There's no need for three to stay.
If Andre stays, only one stays behind.
Is there any chance
that you could take the next one?
I'm going in the helicopter.
- Why?
- I'm from the military.
I do combat.
Iraq, Afghanistan,
strategic, fight, strong, big…
THE TEAM WOULD BENEFIT FROM HIM
He's proving that he's useful.
I can save everybody.
That's why I'm going.
This is inevitable. The will to live.
Okay, let's respect his decision.
We don't need to overthink this.
It's difficult now
but another helicopter's coming.
So arguing over this is pointless.
- It might be quicker to go and come back.
- I agree.
DinDin, if we say it's around 70 kg…
So this combination
could be a possibility.
And these two.
- What?
- Out of nowhere?
That's right. Sae-ho too.
Hey, Sae-ho!
GET YOUR EMOTIONS UNDER CONTROL!
Why are you crying?
Add 72.
I'm 72 kg.
How heavy is Defconn?
Add 140 to 91.
You're talking
as if you're at the butcher.
Refrain yourself.
We might as well end up as meat.
That's one way of putting it.
THAT WAS HARSH!
We aren't going anywhere
if we continue this.
If Andre gets on,
three of us are left behind.
If you have family, get on board.
Hands up if you're single.
- I just want a rough idea.
- Hey!
What if you have a pet?
Okay, how about this?
If you have pets or family,
stand over here.
I have a pet dog.
One pet dog.
- I have a pet dog.
- I have a cat.
Involving pets doesn't seem right.
Pets are 0.5 points.
- What if I have two?
- Then one point.
I have a pet brother!
Hold on!
Figurines don't count.
- They don't count.
- They're my companions.
Once a civil servant, always one.
I have not one but two kids.
They have their mom.
LOSS FOR WORDS BECAUSE IT'S TRUE
Do you need those sunglasses?
I might if I have to stay.
How about a round
of rock, paper, scissors?
Let's exclude the women.
- First…
- Okay!
Let's do it.
- Let's give it a go.
- I agree.
It's fair this way.
Rock, scissors, paper!
This won't work.
- Split into six.
- Split up.
If you're late you lose,
rock, scissors, paper!
But I wasn't late.
Can I smash the rock with scissors?
Nonsense! Hurry up.
Why not?
No, that would hurt the rock.
EVERYONE IS SLOWLY LOSING THEIR SANITY
Rock, scissors, paper!
Listen!
You go in.
I am going to stay here.
You're staying here?
- You're staying?
- Yes, I'm staying.
Why?
I'm going to stay. I'm the strongest.
I can handle all of these zombies.
Trust me on that part, okay?
It's no problem.
THANKS TO THE SERGEANT,
ONE MORE COULD BOARD
I'm very strong.
I can handle this.
- One more has to stay.
- You can't be alone.
One more has to stay.
DESPITE ANDRE'S DECISION,
TAKEOFF IS STILL NOT POSSIBLE
I need one person.
I need one person to come with me.
Make your decision.
We're taking off.
We don't have time!
Let's get on and see if it takes off.
- We don't have time.
- Let's go.
- Why?
- Go, brother.
I'm okay.
Okay?
I'm so sad.
- Why, bro?
- No, don't be.
This is easy.
You're our captain.
Now, you're the captain.
I'll be back.
- You'll be back?
- I'll be back.
- Please. You'll be back.
- Yeah.
Okay.
- Defconn, get on.
- In the middle.
IT'S TIME FOR ANDRE TO CHOOSE A COMPANION
Hug, please!
- Amazing!
- Thank you, Andre.
I'm okay.
Andre.
Thank you.
I love Chef.
Wait…
- No way…
- Patricia.
Patricia?
What?
- What?
- Let's go.
You're with me.
- Why?
- You're with me.
- Me?
- Yes.
Really?
Don't worry.
He chose to protect one person.
I've got you. Let's go.
- Really?
- Trust me.
- What's your name?
- My name is Patricia.
- Patricia?
- Yes.
- Can you help?
- Yes. I'll help you.
- Okay.
- Yes.
They look like an uncle and his nephew
cooking together.
What the…
Teamwork.
Shoot.
- That's teamwork, right?
- Yeah, teamwork.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
No, are you okay?
I'm not okay.
Okay.
- Guys!
- Oh, Patricia!
Patricia!
You'll be fine.
- We'll come back for you.
- Oh, no.
Andre!
Start the engine.
Okay.
You know what, Patricia?
- What?
- I'm hungry.
It's going to be okay.
Okay, left is clear.
- Clear.
- We're ready.
Come on, take off.
Just take off already.
Let's go!
It's taking off!
Take off.
This is unreal!
We're off!
Finally!
I'll be back.
This is making me sad.
If Andre is by her side, she'll be fine.
We survived, thanks to Andre.
Patricia!
Oh, no.
I hate zombies.
Come on.
Subtitle translation by: Hye Min Eom