(Sound of Keisu)
(Kotaro) It's like the world of Yokomizo Seishi.
(Tatsumi) Yokomizoseishi?
-(Tatsumi) Isn't he a shogi player? -(Torataro) Yeah, sorry.
- (Tatsumi) No, no... - (Torataro) I'm sorry, you can forget about it.
(Kirie) That to Mr. Okayama's lawyer.
(Okayama) I was smart.
(Torataro) This is the will of the deceased... Tadayoshi Utsugi.
(Kirieda) Yes, the probate procedures have been completed⸺
Can this content really be considered a will?
(Torataro) Yeah?
I'll take a look
Huh! ? This is...
Is the will a chess game?
This is exactly the case for me.
♪～
～♪
(Kasumi) Heritage division discussion?
Yes, at the old house in Tamaicho⸺
The head of the family passed away⸺
I received a request for procedures regarding inheritance.
(Tatsuo) Indeed, inheritance is...
There are many cases where problems arise when it's just relatives.
I think asking a lawyer is the right thing to do...
(Kasumi) Why did you come to Kotaro-sensei's place?
No, that's it⸺
Suddenly, a request call came to my office.
I'm sure Tamai-cho is a place with hot springs.
Yes, it seems quite difficult to take a day trip in the mountains.
This week, we will be together on Saturday with Ryumi Sensei⸺
I'm thinking of going.
It's bound to be no good! My daughter before marriage went on a business trip...
Division of inheritance is one of the great duties of a lawyer!
As it is a business, we will proceed with caution.
Sounds good?
I admit
What is Tsume Shogi...
Ah, Tsume Shogi is a type of puzzle using Shogi.
The first player continues to make moves within the set number of moves⸺
You must block the opponent's balls.
Was there anything else?
No, what was in the safe was⸺
There was only that one letter.
(Matsuhiko) No matter how much he is a shogi fanatic,
How can you leave such a ridiculous will?
There is a limit to making fun of people
Do you hate shogi?
(Shiko) My father was the only person in this house who liked shogi.
Everyone else is playing shogi⸺
I hated it.
(Sugio)...I mean, that's what it is.
It has no effect as a will.
(Tatsumi) Ah, no, in this will⸺
Date and testator Tadayoshi Utsugi⸺
The name is written and the seal is affixed.
If it is in your own handwriting⸺
The conditions for a handwritten will are met.
Above all, in the margin⸺
For everyone that is not found in ordinary Tsume Shogi⸺
I have a name
(Shiko) It's true, my sister is the rook and I'm the money.
Am I silver?
(Okayama) Me and Shiori's names are also there.
(Torataro) Yes, I am sure that the butler, Mr. Okayama⸺
Two more names
(Shiori) I passed away⸺
She is the daughter of Chairman Utsugi's niece, and her name is Makino Shiori.
I have been working at Utsugi Kenzai for many years...
Oh, this is my son Yuuma.
(Okayama) Um...
Having a name means heritage⸺
Does that mean you can share it?
Not only me, but also Shiori-sama.
No, the inheritance I can receive...
In this house with Yuma⸺
It's enough just to let me live there.
(Matsuhiko) In other words, a will like this would be invalid.
Isn't it a good idea to divide one-fourth among the four siblings?
- (Shiko) Let's do that - (Sugio) That's right.
(Shiko) 1/4
-(Sugio) 1 2 3 4... -(Tatsumi) Please wait!
It has not yet been determined that this will is invalid.
There is a possibility that a message from the deceased may be hidden in this⸺
The inheritance will be divided after solving this chess game.
Yeah? Isn't it because you want to solve it?
Can I borrow a shogi board?
It's a large mansion
Amazing, there's even a floor plan
(Torataro) Wow!
Come to think of it, why did you ask our office?
Ah, a lawyer I know has filed various lawsuits.
For some reason, I solved the problem by relating it to shogi⸺
I heard that there is a teacher who is knowledgeable about shogi.
Become famous before you know it
Ah, um... Kirie-san also plays shogi...
I don't like it
(Torataro) Why do you all hate shogi?
It's all my father's fault
My mother who passed away was often sick⸺
I was repeatedly in and out of the hospital.
Because of that, my father...
He took care of the four of us when we were young.
Oh, aren't you a good father?
My father is⸺
Shogi was my only hobby⸺
They tried to force it on us.
(Loyalty) This is the end. Kirie. Read further.
If I lose, I'll definitely say "I'm here"
(Junior high school student Kirie) It's boring if you can't win!
If that happens, you'll never be able to become stronger!
(Kirieda) He just teaches children harshly...
That's why everyone started hating shogi.
10 years ago Even after retiring from work⸺
I live a life full of shogi, traveling around Japan as I please.
Then last month, I suddenly collapsed...
After causing so much trouble to our family⸺
In his final moments, he died alone.
This is my father's study.
There are also shogi tools inside, so please feel free to use them.
(Tatsumi/Torataro) Thank you
(Torataro) What do you think? Do you think you can solve it?
It's quite a difficult question
Is there really a hidden message in this Tsume Shogi?
The fact that I purposely specified the 25th move is⸺
Maybe it's guiding you to a specific shape of blockage.
What I'm curious about is⸺
That's the name of the person in this house on the margin.
-(Torataro) Ah-(Tatsumi) Huh...
It's a jam, right?
It'll come out in a little while
- (Tatsumi) Yes - (Torataro) Yeah.
(sound of sliding door opening and closing)
(sound of cutting branches)
(Torataro)…This house is spacious.
Ah, the tree care is really sloppy.
Looks like my father's house
Hey, listen to me
-(Torataro) Ah, ah... -(Shiko) You're so sloppy.
yes
Ah, I'm sure Shiiko-san...
I am the representative of an NPO that engages in forest protection activities.
Ah, my late father is from the sawmill⸺
You founded Utsugi Kenzai and served as chairman.
(Shiko) When my father started a sawmill, all you had to do was cut as much wood as you could.
There was no idea that trees and humans could coexist.
Perhaps that reaction led to my current NPO activities...
(Shiko) If you understand, please share a lot of your inheritance with me.
yes?
The answer to that Tsume Shogi game is more than 1/4⸺
Could you please do what I said I would give you a lot?
It's obvious that the other three people won't be able to use it properly.
So please give me the largest inheritance!
Please stop it.
Shiiko Shiiko! Stop it, you!
- (Torataro) Ah... Ah, good - (Matsuhiko) What are you doing?
(Torataro) Good, Matsuhiko-san.
If I were to divide the majority of my inheritance, of course it would be me.
ah?
I'm not bragging, but the quality of our furniture manufacturer is good.
However, sales have been sluggish in recent years.
ask
(Shiko) You can't do that. If you're going to spend a lot of money, please do it to me.
At least half? Just like this!
Just a moment...both of you calm down.
(Matsuhiko) Haa, is it okay to say such carefree things?
While I was doing this, my younger brother Sugio...
Maybe he's trying to trick her into it.
She... no, only Ryumi-sensei is like that...
Before opening Sugio's restaurant⸺
There are even rumors that he was the host⸺
I might not be able to let my guard down
(Matsuhiko) Hey, you, that's a little... lower it, you, that.
(Shiko) I don't like it.
(Sugio) In Ryumi-chan's Tsume Shogi game, I won silver.
So silver is the strongest?
I answered as if I had the biggest share⸺
Can you give it to me?
As the saying goes, “Silver is an attack, and gold is a receiver”⸺
Silver is by no means the strongest piece.
(sound of sliding door opening)
a little bit! What are you doing! ?
Even if we bring our lawyers to tears⸺
You cannot change the contents of a will!
Tatata... please, okay? If it stays like this⸺
The store that I worked so hard to open is now in the hands of someone else.
(mobile phone vibrator)
Oh no...
Yes, sorry, I'll return it right away!
Yes, what now? Ah, okay, I understand. I'll go right away!
What on earth are these people in this house like...ha...
(Yuma) Amazing! I'm solving Tsume Shogi
Ah, no, that doesn't mean it's solved yet...
If so, come here and I'll show you a hint.
Oh, wait a minute...
- (Yuma) Here, here - (Tatsumi) Huh?
(Torataro) Wow... Wow, there's even a storehouse like this!
It's my loyal grandpa's and my secret base.
Hey, wow...
Looks like something will come out
What does it mean to come out?
(Torataro) Speaking from Yokomizo, ghosts of demobilized soldiers and fallen warriors...
-(Tatsumi) Ah! -(Torataro) Wow!
What?
It's a shogi board
Wow~ The pieces too, huh?
Chess match flyer
Wow~
Ah, the fact that he was flying around all over Japan⸺
You were chasing a local title match.
I really lived a life full of shogi.
(Yuma) Let's play shogi
Eh, oh, ah, I can play shogi.
Yeah, but why me?
Because the older brother seems weaker
(Torataro) Hoho, let's do it.
Okay
Huh? here
(Torataro) Hmm, I guess this is it.
Yeah? This is...
(Torataro) Here we come.
Huh? Already?
No, I lost
Oh, that's a great loss.
No, this won't work unless the losing side also makes some bad moves.
In a sense, Kotaro-sensei is also brilliant.
I don't feel like I'm being praised though.
Yuma-kun, you're strong, aren't you?
I'm training with a shogi app.
It's not these days.
Ah, what do you think? Did you find any tips for Tsume Shogi?
(Tatsumi) Ah, no, I don't know if this is a hint or not...
(Torataro) Is this Chairman Utsugi's wife?
I heard that he passed away from an illness about 30 years ago.
I think the four children are Kirie-san and his siblings.
Ah, even in this house⸺
I guess he had time to play shogi so happily.
(Tatsumi) I can't believe that's gone now.
I feel sorry for Shogi somehow.
Do you feel sorry for Shogi?
It seems like everyone in this house is unhappy because of shogi.
It's kind of sad
(Torataro) Yeah.
I don't want to see anyone get hurt playing shogi again.
That’s it⸺
Are you talking about Towa?
How do you know?
Ah ah no
I heard from my mom and dad the other day.
Could you please not say that name in front of me?
Yes, sorry, I understand.
(Front) Welcome.
(Torataro) Ayuda and Tendo made an appointment at the Ayuda Law Office.
(Front desk clerk) 2 people, 1 room, 1 night.
It will be here
Huh! ? I... 1st room?
(Torataro) I think there was some kind of mistake.
After all, I had asked Toshie-san to reserve two rooms for me.
Yeah yeah?
Ah... Ah, no, this is some kind of mistake. Yeah.
It's great I'm happy
Huh?
This is the 4th match of the 60th championship match 12 years ago⸺
A deadly battle unfolded between Akira Watanabe and Yoshiharu Habu.
This is a long-established inn that is famous among shogi fans.
Moreover, this is the room where Kudan Hanyu stayed.
I'm moved to tears to be here.
Huh...
Ah, that's why I was so excited about this business trip.
-(Tatsumi) Wow, that's amazing-(Torataro) Huh?
(Tatsumi) The frame in the alcove is also the same as it was back then.
Huh? Maybe even this bed⸺
I wonder if Hanyu 9-dan was used...
Well... I guess I'll leave the bed for now.
(Kasumi) Oh, you were both so quick.
Ahhh...
Ah... oh...
- (Torataro) Ah... - (Tatsuo) Ah...
Oh… even mom and dad.
No, that name is misleading, so what do you think?
Oh, it's a nice room, and the view is nice too.
(Torataro) No, no, no, why are you two here?
No, even if it's a business trip, you're alone with Ryumi⸺
I'd rather spend the night in agony at the thought of spending the night⸺
Until I realized that it would be safer to stay with him and keep an eye on him.
So I consulted Rie-san.
If you're going to book two rooms anyway, it's cheaper for two people to stay together.
That means two people each...
Me and Tatsumi in this room
...And next to me is Torataro-sensei and Tatsuo-san.
(Tatsuo) Oooh
Huh? It doesn't feel any different from any other dinner...
(Tatsuo) Huh? The purpose is to monitor, but like this⸺
Is it really a good thing to create a feeling that the family doesn't need water?
Even if you say that, me and Ryuumi-sensei⸺
I'm here to work as a lawyer.
Indeed, to reveal the wishes of the deceased⸺
I have to solve that Tsume Shogi as soon as possible.
Not a place to eat
I'm trying to figure it out
(Tatsumi) Solving that Tsume Shogi is also a competition between the deceased and me.
This inn should also have a shogi board, so I'll look for it.
Wait... Tatsumi
Well, let's all eat this together.
Ryumi really likes shogi.
(Tatsumi) I don't want to see anyone get hurt playing shogi again.
Are you talking about Usagi-san?
Could you please not say that name in front of me?
(Katsuragi) Thanks to you for using us in many title matches⸺
See... Many people who are ``viewing generals'' have come to visit us.
This is a collection that was put together on this occasion.
Ah! No, that's amazing
-(Katsuragi) Hahahaha... -(Torataro) Hey, oh.
There are also records of the encouragement meeting.
…That means
This was before Ryumi-sensei became a lawyer...
Later in 2020
Atta Tatsumi Tendo
(Katsuragi) Tatsumi Tendo 3rd dan?
Oh, ah, do you know?
Yeah, I think I might become the first female professional shogi player⸺
It was highly anticipated
But I couldn't get used to it, so I quit the encouragement group.
Hmm, I heard that it was a voluntary resignation.
Voluntary withdrawal?
The encouragement session is a tough place⸺
I need to become 4th dan at the age of 26 or win in the 3rd dan league⸺
I have to force it to stop
But you were forced to stop because of that rule, right?
Tendo 3-dan was only 23 years old⸺
I'm sure my grades were pretty good, but you know what?
here!
(Torataro) It's true.
However, I voluntarily quit the encouragement group.
Ah... the hot water was nice.
Ryumi?
As expected, there is also a long-established inn shogi set that was used in the championship game, which is helpful.
I wish I could take a hot spring bath.
(Tatsumi) Hmm...
(Tatsuo) You saw the record of the encouragement meeting, right?
I was surprised
Ryumi-sensei couldn't become a professional shogi player⸺
I just assumed that I had given up on shogi.
There were many reasons why Tatsumi stopped playing shogi.
Um...that's what you told me the other day⸺
Isn't someone named Toba-san involved?
What the hell happened?
In the last match with her
Tatsumi pointed the finger at losing friends.
Will you lose friends?
(Tatsuo) Since that match, Tatsumi no longer plays shogi with anyone.
(Torataro) No, but many times in court...
(Tatsuo) Even if you use shogi moves to win in court,
I've never played shogi with anyone.
Ah... I think I talked a little too much, sorry.
Ah, no
(Kasumi) Because my stomach is full...
(Tatsumi) Huh...
Is this the message of the deceased?
- (Torataro) Good morning - (Tatsumi) Good morning
Ah, I solved Tsume Shogi.
Ho… Really! ?
(Tatsumi) Yes, 27 moves
In the end, there were several ways to close it⸺
It looks like a classic shogi game.
...So, was there a message about the distribution of inheritance or the deceased?
(Tatsumi) That's still not clear...
I see.
(mobile phone vibrator)
Ah
Who could it be?
Yes, I'm Ayuda.
Ah, Yuma-kun's mother
Huh! ?
(Torataro) There is no legacy left! ?
Ah, that's Chairman Utsugi...
Ah, as I mentioned earlier, I work with Utsugi Kenzai⸺
I worked in finance under the chairman.
In fact, 10 years ago, the company's management was at a standstill.
I was on the verge of bankruptcy.
That's... Huh, but Utsugi Construction Materials is still...
The chairman invests all his personal funds into the company for the sake of the employees⸺
I saved him from that predicament.
All my personal property...
As a result, the chairman has almost no assets left.
This land and house are also mortgaged.
I guess that's what happened after all.
Eh, “as expected”?
Ah, when we first talked about heritage, Shiori-san...
Not only me, but also Shiori-sama.
No, the inheritance I can receive...
(Tatsumi) “There is no inheritance that I can receive.”
I thought you were about to say it and I was curious.
(Torataro) Huh? That means there is no legacy left.
Don't you know Kirie-san and his brothers?
For the past 10 years, you have been estranged from Chairman Utsugi⸺
I didn't even come to this house⸺
If you don't know...
(Torataro) Why did you write such a will when there was no inheritance left?
(Shiori) I don't understand.
What was Chairman Utsugi thinking?
Above all, all my brothers changed their eye colors like that...
ask
That's no good. If you want to spend a lot of money, please do it to me.
(Shiori) Chairman Utsugi wants us to fight!
I can never imagine what you wanted
In other words, the deceased was expecting something different⸺
He must have left a message in Tsume Shogi's will.
I'm going to see Kirie-san.
Sorry, excuse me
I heard Shiori-san's story.
that…
I found this photo in the warehouse.
This is...
(Tatsumi) I'm pretty sure about the people in this house.
I always thought that I hated shogi.
(Torataro) But there were times when that wasn't the case.
No way...
(Kirieda) My father plays shogi⸺
They tried to force it on us.
(Loyalty) If you do that, you'll never be able to become stronger!
(Kirieda) My mother is often sick⸺
I was repeatedly in and out of the hospital.
(Tatsumi) There are everyone's names that are not found in regular Tsume Shogi.
There is even a floor plan
I found it in the warehouse
Solved
All messages in the will
(Sugio) What do you mean you don't have an inheritance?
(Yuma) Mom, why are you angry?
(Kirieda) 10 years ago⸺
I poured everything into rebuilding Utsugi Kenzai.
It looks like this house and land are mortgaged.
(Shiko) If that's not a joke, then what are we for...
(Matsuhiko) Ah...
(Torataro) I brought a kimono.
What? That
(Shiko) I don't know.
The will of the deceased Tadayoshi Utsugi, playing Tsume Shogi⸺
I was finally able to solve it
Due to the nature of the will, this Tsume Shogi is⸺
I decided it was essential for the whole family to find the answer.
So from now on, I would like everyone to solve it together.
That's ridiculous...
If you don't have an inheritance, it's a waste of time.
Then I'll do it
It starts with the first move, right?
Is this the first one?
(Tatsumi) 5 triangles In contrast, this one on the draw is⸺
5 Eryu
(Yuma) It matched.
So what's next for 62 squares?
Yuma-kun really has a good plot.
Kyo is the second mover for 6 two angles.
It can't be helped, look, Yuma.
In Tsume Shogi, you keep making the winning moves⸺
5 in three steps
It seems different
-(Shiko) Huh? -(Matsuhiko) Huh?
Isn't it quite difficult? this
(Okayama) Aren't you saying that you should use the pieces you have?
Ah, yes, yes, of course the rook is the only choice.
Yeah yeah
32…
Not oh?
22 rooks prepared to be taken by silver
2 Two rooks have the same silver
(Sugio) Yuma You are amazing.
(Shiko) Eh, wait. Then me too.
No, the next move is move 7...
Eh, this is 53...
Maybe 5 Sanpo Sei?
(Okayama) Is that okay?
Well, what about 5 three golds?
yes
(Yuma) Yay! Correct Next Mom's turn
Well, the ball has dropped⸺
Ah, Keima here?
That's correct
- (Matsuhiko and others) Oh - (Yuma) Mom, that's amazing!
(Sugio) Next, my sister's turn
(Shiko) Well, 72 steps.
(Tatsumi) That's correct.
(Matsuhiko and others) Oh!
(Tatsumi) After all, everyone can point.
(Okayama) I'll worry about it next time.
(Yuma) If so, what about Keima?
(Sugio) Ah, I see. That's it.
(Loyalty) Kirie Read further ahead
(Matsuhiko) 8 Rokuka
8 Rokko has 7 balls on the draw.
(Yuma) There are only three moves left.
(Okayama) “The 25th move is⸺”
It says “94 rooks”
Is this okay?
If the pieces match, it is the same dragon, so the draw is 7 triples.
(Sugio) Okay, one more move then?
The last move is⸺
Thank you to Kirie-san.
Huh?
Ah
Even the incense car would get stuck, but if it were me...
This way
(Yuma) 8 three dragons!
(Loyalty) This is the end.
If I lose, I'll definitely say "I'm here"
Dad has arrived
congratulations
I got stuck on the 27th move.
-(Sugio) Oh!-(Yuma) Yay!
-(Sugio) Seriously?-(Shiko) Does that mean it's solved?
(Matsuhiko) Well, it's been a while since I used my brain.
(Okayama) Hahahaha…
I believe this final diagram contains the wishes of the deceased.
Chairman Utsugi's last will?
(Tatsumi) Yes, this is a message from Tadayoshi Utsugi.
There are now 8 pieces left on the board.
When you connect the pieces other than the last dragon you put your hand on⸺
Don't you notice that it looks similar to something you've seen somewhere before?
(Shiko) The balance is poor for an inverted T.
Is the katakana letter lying down?
Oh wait! This is⸺
Maybe it's the shape of this house?
yes
It resembled the floor plan of this mansion in the hallway.
Sorry, I brought it without permission.
(Tatsumi) This Tsume Shogi is for classic Tsume Shogi⸺
There were multiple ways to escape from the blockage⸺
In all filling diagrams including this shape⸺
In a common position⸺
Existing piece found
That is the 21st Katsura and the 11th Incense.
These two pieces are⸺
From the positional relationship with this mansion⸺
It seems to indicate a storehouse in the garden.
(Tatsumi) Using this Tsume Shogi to point out that storehouse⸺
It was the deceased's first message.
Mr. Tadayoshi, who was a shogi enthusiast, works in this warehouse.
Items purchased from all over the country are carefully stored.
(Matsuhiko) Oh? You think this junk is a legacy?
For example, this piece is by a famous author⸺
Currently, I think a market value of several million yen is worthless.
Millions! ?
(Tatsumi) Yes.
There are also pieces that were actually used in shogi battles⸺
There were also boxes with the autographs of the players who played against them.
What was also interesting was⸺
This is a locking move from a very old chess game.
(Sugio) A similar seal⸺
There are great prices on the auction site.
(Matsuhiko) Huh?
(Torataro) Probably while traveling around the country for the title match⸺
I guess it was bought all over the place.
(Shiori) Well, the chairman is⸺
I didn't just live a life full of shogi...
(Torataro) Better than everyone expected⸺
It may not be much, but⸺
There was definitely a legacy.
(Tatsumi) And that's not all.
Tadayoshi has one more thing⸺
You left an important message
What is it? That's it
In Tsume Shogi's will⸺
Everyone's name was there.
The player has 7 types of pieces, from foot to rook.
Tsume Shogi is⸺
These are all rules that must be used.
In other words, they have four children: Shiori, Yuma, and Okayama.
I can't point out if any of these people are missing.
(Torataro) Everyone while solving Tsume Shogi⸺
We forgot about our heritage and worked together as one.
That moment when everyone was passionate about Tsume Shogi⸺
It was something that my father wanted to leave behind.
Yeah
I want us to come together and protect this house.
That's the message my father really wanted to leave behind.
What, are you asking me to play shogi now?
Even though I used to tear my family apart by playing shogi.
I'm surprised you love shogi so much.
you guys are misunderstanding
Dad is me, you and mom⸺
He tried to connect with me by playing shogi.
I was reminded of this when I saw this
I also always misunderstood my father.
I completely forgot that my mother loved shogi.
(Matsuhiko) Is this photo us?
(Shiko) Mom is playing shogi with us?
My mother always liked shogi even before she got married.
But I have no memory of playing shogi with my mom.
Huh... I can't help it.
At this time, Sugio was only 4 years old and Matsuhiko was 8 years old.
To make matters worse, my mother was admitted to the hospital shortly after this.
Now that I think about it, my mother didn't have much time left to live⸺
Dad knew, right?
surely…
(Hiiragi) Thank you
(Kirieda) That's why...
(Hiiragi) What if you?
When I couldn't come back from this hospitalization...
Don't say anything more, you'll come back
When I come back, I'll let you play shogi with those kids to your heart's content.
Don't ever say you're not coming back
(Torataro) The one who really liked shogi in this house was⸺
It was your mother
So my father tried to connect the four of us with my mother, who wasn't there.
I want you to get better soon
I hope so...
You can't become stronger!
(Kirieda) You treated us harshly.
I'm really clumsy
(Tatsumi) Shogi has the power to connect people.
The person who believed in this more than anyone else was the late Tadayoshi.
Come to think of it, it was a fatherly will.
Mr. Kirie, as a representative of the heir⸺
I hope that the inherited assets will be managed in accordance with Chairman Utsugi's will.
Yeah
This is a treasure left behind by my father.
I won't let you easily exchange it for money.
Shiori-san, Yuma-kun, and Okayama-san too⸺
Please accept my father's wishes.
Such wasteful words...
thank you
You guys are good too, right?
Ah I understand
I don't really mind though
If my sister says so, I can't help it.
How can I really express my gratitude to both of you?
Oh, no, I was just doing my job as a lawyer.
I'm glad I could help you
It's not a battle of impressions, is it?
Yes, this time it wasn't a court battle.
Yes, then why?
I wanted to try pointing at Kotaro-sensei once.
Huh?
(Tatsuo) Ever since that match⸺
Tatsumi no longer plays shogi with anyone.
Now, Kotaro-sensei's first turn.
(Torataro) Oh yeah
Thank you very much.
please
♪～
You can't play shogi without an opponent.
Yes, that's right.
(Tatsumi) I connect with others through shogi⸺
And we can understand each other
I love moments like that
When I looked at the people in that house, I couldn't help but think that way.
That's why I wanted to point it out.
Ah... this this...
King hand? Ah oh...
…Or rather, it’s stuck?
Yes, I'm stuck with 14 moves.
Ah...
Although it took longer than Yuma-kun⸺
The drawer wins.
Ah, no, no, no... wait a minute.
Wait a minute, try again...
Rie-san, not yet.
You said you were only paid until yesterday.
(Tatsumi) Hot spring shogi sweets⸺
I was thinking of eating with you.
(Torataro) Let's wait a little bit.
～♪
(door chime)
Are you a customer? Ahhh
Yes, welcome to Ayuda Law Office
At least one is good.
(Female) Attorney Tatsumi Tendo⸺
Are you here?
Yes
Tatsumi Sensei Customer
- (Tatsumi) Yeah? - (Torataro) Please
(sound of door closing)
Usa-chan?
What?
(Usagiha) Long time no see, Dora
(Tatsumi) The way I lost my friends⸺
He still hasn't forgiven me for what I said.
(Usagiba) Dora will accept it.
Aren't you completely denying the contents of this article?
(Tsuge) This is not conclusive evidence.
(Usagiba) This is all I have now
You can't win this game
(Rie) Mr. Torataro?
Arrested!?