(Toshie) It's not a civil case, it's a criminal case.And also⸺
murder case
(Kotaro) Murder case! ?
(Torataro) Atsunobu Mikimoto
(Torataro) retired from Matsushino Construction last year⸺
Currently working at a restaurant
The incident occurred on September 13th.
Could you tell me what happened?
(Mikimoto) Yes.
That day, I wandered into a restaurant on my way home from work and had a drink⸺
A stranger happened to be next to me...
(Male) Brother, look at this.
(Mikimoto) He kept on asking me to watch the video.
Hey, just say something. Look at this...
You, don't worry about it
(Bartender) If the customers are fighting, please do it elsewhere.
(Male) Bill
(Mikimoto) After that, I also left the store and went straight home⸺
The next morning at a park on a hill...
(shutter sound)
The man was found dead.
(Torataro) The victim is Haruto Sakaeda, 37 years old.
Brain contusion due to head contusion
Estimated time of death is⸺
Between 11pm and midnight
It is believed that he died after falling down the stairs in the park.
The police located the bar where Mr. Eida had been drinking just before⸺
I found out that I had an argument with you.
(Tatsumi) Did you kill the victim?
A little too straight!
This is so important that you need to check it before playing...
-(Mikimoto) I haven't done it-(Torataro) Huh?
i am innocent
(Rie) Are you denying it? Even though he was charged with murder?
(Torataro) It's a pretty difficult case, isn't it?
(Rie) Of course.
In domestic criminal trials⸺
The rate of conviction is⸺
After all, it's 99.9%
‪99.9％
(Rie) Guilty is almost always determined at the stage when the prosecutor indicts the person.
The rate of being falsely accused or acquitted is only 0.1%.
‪０.１％…
(Torataro) If you continue to deny it, you can't expect extenuating circumstances.
As a director whose credo is to put the client first⸺
It's tough, but this time the other person is at fault.
Please take a look at this prosecutor's name.
(Torataro) Yeah?
Ah... Ichiro Asamura! ?
Always remain calm and collected in any court hearing
In the courtroom, a machine that doesn't change its expression
The nickname given is the AI ​​of the Tokyo District Public Prosecutors Office.
‪ＡＩ…
(Rie) It kind of stuck with me.
(Tatsumi) It is true that the development of AI has been remarkable over the past 10 years⸺
Humanity has become almost unable to beat shogi AI.
Please, don't draw me to shogi.
If the probability of AI beating humans is 99.9%⸺
This trial is exactly⸺
It's like challenging an AI opponent to a game.
It's not comforting or encouraging.
The important thing is that even if the other party is AI⸺
0.1% means there is a chance of winning.
If you think you will lose from the beginning, you will never win.
If you give up, it's time to surrender.
♪～
～♪
That's the Tokyo District Public Prosecutors Office's AI
(Presiding judge) The prosecutor is⸺
Planning to request evidence examination⸺
Please give us a summary of the evidence.
(Asamura) Accused's statement record and prosecutor's report Autopsy report⸺
Live inspection record Appraisal evidence⸺
We are planning to request footage from the taxi's in-vehicle camera.
Footage from a taxi camera?
(Presiding Judge) What kind of image is that?
(Asamura) Estimated time of crime near the back entrance of the park at the scene of the crime⸺
This is from the drive recorder of a taxi waiting for a customer.
A few minutes after the victim entered the park⸺
The accused also appears to be entering⸺
It was being photographed
(Torataro) Mikimoto-san also joined! ?
As expected of AI, it is an attack with no gaps.
(Torataro) I went to the park where the crime took place⸺
Why were you hiding it?
I just walked through that park because it was a shortcut to the station.
(Torataro)...Even if that is the case, as long as there is video evidence⸺
Prosecutors will definitely pursue this.
What if...?
If you accidentally cause someone to fall, you can claim manslaughter.
Sentence can be less severe than murder
If the denial continues like this, the trial will drag on.
The jury's moral evidence also deteriorates.
Tell me about the night of the incident⸺
It would be better to finish the trial as soon as possible...
That doesn't make any sense.
no…
anyway i didn't do it
I didn't kill Eida-san.
(Torataro) According to the prosecutor's documents⸺
The victim, Mr. Eida, was an urban legend video streamer⸺
It seems like he didn't have a smartphone in his possessions.
Of course, Mikimoto-san's home and workplace were also searched.
I haven't found it
Maybe someone else took it away after the crime...
Said it didn't make sense
Huh?
As expected, Mikimoto-san
I feel like he's still hiding something important.
(Torataro) I'm sure he was at the park at the time of the crime...
Hah... I need the defendant to be honest⸺
Seriously, you can't beat the Tokyo District Public Prosecutors Office's AI 99.9% of the time!
(Sigh) (Tatsumi) Beating AI?
I'm sure...
Let's go!
Huh? Wait... where! ?
(Kasumi) Don't be so nervous.
But...
I felt like I was standing in court for a while now...
(Kasumi) Why are you wearing a robe?
(Tatsuo) To strengthen myself.
I heard that he defends criminal cases and denial cases.
(Kasumi) Before this person, I was in charge of criminal trials.
His explanation after the verdict was quite popular.
It appears many times in this book.
(Torataro) Ah...
(Tatsuo) For me, the most famous quote is...
(Coughing) (Tatsuo) The defendant...
(Tatsumi) I found it!
Have you found a way to beat AI?
Can't you just tell me...
(Tatsumi) A few years ago Even professional players can't win⸺
The most powerful AI software has been created⸺
There was a special strategy to defeat the AI.
The first player is human, the second player is AI.
(Kasumi) It looks like the pieces are set up in a normal way at the beginning, right?
(Tatsumi)...but first move
That is, the 28 silver pointed by humans.
This is a special move to defeat AI.
More advanced, 21st move
The first player is 2 Shichigin and the second AI is 2 Octagon.
(Kasumi) Huh? Even though it’s AI⸺
A move like that?
Do you understand? mother
mother"! ?
Yomoya Kasumi-san⸺
Do you have a relationship where you call her mother?
This is for AI⸺
It's a kind of trick to get people to do something wrong.
It is said to be a bug in the program.
Now that the program has been improved, you can no longer use the same method.
In any case, this is the 0.1% strategy to beat AI.
(Torataro) So in the actual trial⸺
What kind of trick can you use to beat the Tokyo District Public Prosecutors Office's AI?
Yeah? That's not yet
I just want to know that there is a strategy that can defeat even 99.9% of AI.
I just wanted to tell you
That's why you pulled me this far⸺
So you're involving your mom and dad?
This time it’s “dad”! ? How far have you progressed...
(Torataro) Don't you recognize this person?
Mr. Sakaeda insists on watching the video⸺
It seems like it was approaching
(Male) No, I've never seen it.
(Male) The guy from Sakaeda hasn't posted any videos lately.
(Tatsumi) Are you saying you were trying to quit?
That's what I said when we met last month.
(Eida) Is it possible to do video streaming now?
(Male) No, stop it. What should we do?
Is it a debt or something?
I've paid it off and I'll get the change.
- (Male) Is it really Tokugawa buried treasure? -(Eida) It's different!
You can definitely get it after October 10th.
The victim did that...
(Male) This is the preview of the last video that Eida posted.
(Tatsumi) “Celebrity Missing”?
(Male) Isn't this the kind of thing where the rich and famous suddenly disappear?
(Torataro) The building in the background...
(Male) Ah...
It's probably Matsushino Construction's headquarters building.
I'm sure it's Matsushino...
Ah...
Matsushino Construction, the company where Mikimoto-san worked until last year!
i am back
-(Rie) Good work~ -(Tatsumi) I'm back.
(Rie) Hey, hey, hey
I was looking into Matsushino Construction.
(Torataro) Huh?
Seven years ago, the company president's son disappeared and was featured in a weekly magazine.
(Tatsumi) “The heir has disappeared!?” A true celebrity missing...
(Rie) Eh~ Matsushino Construction is⸺
Unlisted family company⸺
Serving as the third president⸺
Mr. Kazuyuki Matsushino's only son⸺
This Yukihiko is the managing director⸺
It seems like he suddenly disappeared.
A missing persons report has also been filed.
She disappeared on October 10, 2017.
What Mr. Eida was investigating was⸺
So it was Yukihiko Matsushino's disappearance.
That's not all, there was also a post like this
(Torataro) “Matsushino Construction Employee M⸺”
“An affair with the wife of the fourth heir who disappeared!”
“Enraged president forces employee M to leave”
(Rie) That also coincided with the timing of Mikimoto-san quitting the company last year.
In other words, this employee M⸺
Mr. Mikimoto?
So, with the wife of the president's only son who disappeared seven years ago⸺
Does that mean Mikimoto was having an affair?
Victim Mr. Eida
Maybe this rumor is a joke⸺
Maybe he was trying to extort money.
(Torataro) If that's the case...
What Mr. Mikimoto is trying to hide is⸺
It's possible that it was something related to the affair...
(Kazuyuki) Yukihiko has died.
Isn't it a disappearance?
7 years ago Yukihiko is⸺
When he went to work, he left the house and disappeared.
Some of the cars found near the sea of ​​trees at Fuji are⸺
Only a note that looked like a suicide note remained.
...However, reports at the time said that she had disappeared.
(Kazuyuki) What the media says What it doesn't⸺
If it is written up, the company's signboard will be damaged.
I think so⸺
I even had a lawyer file a missing person report.
Um... he retired last year⸺
I would also like to ask you about Atsunobu Mikimoto.
(Kazuyuki) I can't remember every single employee who quit.
There's nothing more to talk about.
-(Kazuki) Please go home.-(Michiko) You...
Thank you very much, Taeko-san.
(Taeko) My name is Taeko, and I am Yukihiko's wife.
(Torataro) I would like to ask you about your visit⸺
Why did Yukihiko himself...
He has had it since childhood⸺
I have a dream of becoming a painter⸺
I also wanted to go to art school⸺
Thanks to my father-in-law's crane voice, I was encouraged to enter the Department of Business Administration.
After graduating, I naturally joined Matsushino Construction⸺
I was appointed as the director of the human resources department.
Restructuring and employees with poor performance⸺
I was put in charge of the demotion⸺
I think I was exposed to intense stress every day.
Still, drawing was a hobby⸺
I was barely mentally balanced.
(Taeko) Yukihiko-san, I got some coffee.
(Yukihiko) Thank you, I'll go right away.
(Taeko) But...
Don't you have any idea that you will become the next president?
(Taeko) My father-in-law didn't like my work style at the company...
(Kazuyuki) Ummmmmmmmm! Aah!
(Taeko) Your father-in-law is from him⸺
I took away my dreams and my heart.
That's why I committed suicide...
If it is recognized that the life or death of your spouse has been unknown for three years or more⸺
It should be possible to get a divorce
Why are you staying in this house?
it is…
I'm sorry to hear about your troubles.
You were in the detention center the other day.
Huh?
Did you go to meet Mr. Mikimoto?
Mikimoto-san has been my husband's best friend since his school days⸺
He was the only person in the company that I could open up to.
Taeko-san and Mikimoto-san...
Even after my husband is gone⸺
I was consulted about various things...
I was surprised to learn about this incident.
But we weren't family, so we couldn't meet.
(Rie) That's suspicious. That Taeko is your wife.
Feeling like a femme fatale or a woman of destiny
(Torataro) No, no, no, no, you don't have to decide that.
It's just a hypothesis⸺
Even before Yukihiko Matsushino disappeared⸺
Taeko and Mikimoto are having an affair⸺
If Yukihiko disappeared or committed suicide because of that...
Mr. Eida, the victim whose disappearance seven years ago was investigated⸺
I found out the truth and blackmailed Mikimoto.
Mr. Mikimoto refused, and on the contrary, Mr. Eida...
(Torataro) No!
That's Mikimoto-san⸺
Wouldn't that be the motive for killing someone with murderous intent?
Oh, sorry, I just read your hand in the wrong way.
(Phone ringtone) (Torataro) Yes.
(Rie) Yes, this is Fuda Law Office, which is struggling against 99.9% AI.
Tokyo District Court?
Yes Request for additional witnesses
Yes, yes! ?
Ah, yeah... Yes, I understand.
Yes, excuse me (hanging up the phone)
hard
Prosecutor Asamura has requested Taeko Matsushino as a witness.
Will Taeko be a witness for the prosecution?
Ah... I didn't expect it to be the prosecutor's office too⸺
Read the plot like the one I was just talking about⸺
Maybe he's trying to prove that line.
As expected from the Tokyo District Public Prosecutors Office's AI.
Important pieces we found⸺
It was pointed back to me as a move advantageous to the prosecution.
That might be really bad
(Presiding judge) The witness is on the stand.
Address Name Occupation Age...
(Tatsumi) Now that Taeko, a valid witness, has been handed over to the AI ​​side⸺
That trick won't work anymore
If we don't somehow recover from a disadvantageous situation...
(Asamura) Prosecutor Asamura asks a question.
The defendant retired from Matsushino Construction last year.
Do you know about the rumors that were spread within the company at that time?
- (Taeko) Yes, I know - (Asamura) What kind of content is it?
Me and Mikimoto-san...
If it's between a man and a woman
But it's unfounded
Objection!
Prosecutors violated the privacy of witnesses unrelated to the case...
This case is not a case of manslaughter⸺
This is an important question to prove that it was intentional murder.
(Judge) The prosecutor continued.
You are from the defendant⸺
Have you heard anything about the victim, Mr. Yoto Sakaeda?
Please answer “yes” or “no”.
yes
(Asamura) What was it about?
I feel like I'm being blackmailed...
(Asamura) In other words, the defendant⸺
Does this mean that you were being blackmailed by Mr. Yoto Sakaeda?
- (Taeko) Yes - (Asamura) That's all.
(Rie) After all, he was being blackmailed.
But isn't it a bit too honest?
- (Presiding judge) The defense attorney will cross-examine - (Torataro) Yes.
(Torataro) Attorney Ayuda will ask a question.
I heard from Mr. Mikimoto about Mr. Eida's blackmail⸺
When did that happen?
On the phone on the night of September 13th
what! ?
That was the day of the incident, right?
What is the time?
It's after 11:30 p.m.
That's the estimated time of death...
(Torataro) About that time⸺
Please speak as accurately as possible
That night⸺
I received a call from a public phone...
(Mikimoto) Hello, Taeko-san, this is Mikimoto.
(Taeko) What's wrong? At a time like this
It was then
-(Eida) Wow! -(Taeko) Mikimoto-san?
what happened? Did something happen?
(Mikimoto) It's tough, a man named Eida was pushed down...
Huh?
“As for the person I pushed down⸺”
“It was dark and I couldn’t see well.”
Mikimoto said so.
(Tatsumi) That fucker is still alive.
(buzz)
(Judge) Quiet!
(Torataro) In other words, Mikimoto-san was at the phone booth in the park⸺
When I'm talking to you⸺
Someone else pushed the victim down and killed him.
(Asamura) Objection!
The defense attorney's questions are simply asking the witness to speculate...
The witness pointed out by the AI ​​at the back is Taeko⸺
Exactly 2 octagons...
It's long overdue for AI⸺
The corner that was supposed to be driven into the enemy camp⸺
If you make one move, you will be taken first⸺
Become a pawn and fall into the enemy's hands
This is it⸺
The biggest aim of this game is
(Torataro) Bento No. 12
Shows a drawing of the park where the incident took place.
According to this drawing, the phone booth is quite a distance from the stairs.
...If so, the defendant who was calling from there
Is it possible to kill the victim?
I don't think it's possible for Mikimoto-san.
(Rumor) (Presiding Judge) Quiet!
2 Octagon is the worst move to offer the horn to the opponent.
Truly an AI bug...
That's all
(Presiding Judge) Is there anything to add?
So that's it.
(Torataro) Why did you say you witnessed the culprit?
Didn't you say that?
Why are you making that face?
Huh?
(Tatsumi) According to Taeko's testimony, which exceeds my reading⸺
There is a possibility of a not guilty verdict.
Normally, this is a phase where you are sure of victory.
Why aren't you really happy?
(Mikimoto) No...
It was so sudden that I couldn't feel it
Is that enough? I'm kind of tired
Excuse me
I'm going back (sound of door opening)
(Ebato) Today, October 10th⸺
Seven years have passed since she disappeared.
Procedures for declaration of disappearance tomorrow⸺
Let's start
Will this finally lead to Buddhahood?
He's an unfilial guy until the end.
(Taeko) Um...
I have a favor to ask of you.
(Torataro) Why so late...
This is to confirm the situation at the same time as the crime.
That's the phone booth where Mikimoto called Taeko.
It's definitely a long way from the stairs.
(Torataro) In the initial investigation by the police⸺
The reason why they didn't check the call logs from the phone booth on the night of the incident was⸺
That was a painful mistake
Indeed, because of that mistake, the case is going in our favor.
(Torataro) Yeah.
But that's just the other party's fault.
The biggest mistake was calling Taeko as a witness.
So does this mean your victory was saved by your opponent's mistake?
It just feels like it was set up for me.
Was it set up?
(Tatsumi) It was just after 11:30 p.m. The time of the crime.
At the place where the Torataro-sensei victim was pushed down⸺
try standing up
Huh?
(Taeko) “As for the person I pushed down⸺”
“It was dark and I couldn’t see well.”
-(Tatsumi) It looks really good! -(Torataro) Huh?
...Does that mean Mikimoto-san saw the culprit's face?
If there is a piece that has not appeared yet in this game...
-(Tatsumi) I'm home-(Tatsuo) Ah, it's quite late.
Tatsumi's favorite paella with plenty of shrimp⸺
Take it properly...
(Kasumi) Oh, it looks like you're in competition mode again.
(Tatsuo) Yeah.
- (Tatsumi) Good morning - (Torataro) Good morning
(Tatsumi) Please look at this.
(Rie) Yeah? This is an article about Yukihiko Matsushino's disappearance, right?
(Tatsumi) The problem is the date.
(Torataro) Missing on October 10, 2017
On October 10th, Mr. Eida will be there⸺
It was the day when I told my streaming friends that they would receive money.
And today is October 11th, which means⸺
Seven years have passed since she disappeared.
If you apply for a declaration of disappearance and it is approved⸺
Legally, he should be considered dead.
(Tatsumi) In that case, Taeko can inherit Yukihiko's inheritance.
(Torataro) Mr. Eida will have to wait until the day when he can be declared missing⸺
trying to extort inheritance
In that case, Taeko is aiming for an inheritance⸺
Even after Yukihiko committed suicide, he remained with the Matsushino family⸺
A femme fatale relationship with Mikimoto...
(Rie) Even so, it's strange, isn't it?
(Torataro) Huh? What, strange?
(Rie) It seems that no application has been filed for Yukihiko Matsushino to be declared missing.
Haven't you applied?
(Rie) Normally, after 7 years⸺
I was supposed to apply soon so I was preparing for it⸺
I want you to wait
Huh? Maybe...
(Tatsumi) 25th move, first move, restart from 39 gold...
You can definitely get it after October 10th.
(Mikimoto) A man named Eida was pushed down...
“It was dark and I couldn’t see well.”
(Torataro) Did you mean that Mikimoto-san saw the criminal's face?
This one game⸺
I finished winning
Why are you dressed like that...
(Tatsumi) This time's match with the AI ​​prosecutor⸺
This side won with 79 moves.
In a shogi game⸺
There may be pieces that are never used.
This time it took only a short time⸺
There were some⸺
For example⸺
The 91st incense on the draw was a fixed piece.
That piece is it⸺
My name is Yukihiko Matsushino.
Huh... what are you trying to say?
Yukihiko should have definitely committed suicide seven years ago...
Mr. Mikimoto, enough of the lies.
(Tatsumi) Among Mr. Eida's belongings⸺
There was one flyer that was out of place.
(Torataro) Actually, I met Yukihiko Maematsu Shino, who came here.
- (Child) Goodbye! - (Child) Goodbye!
(Child) Goodbye!
- (Children) Hello - (Tatsumi/Torataro) Hello
(Tatsumi) Yukihiko Matsushino, right?
It's called by that name⸺
How many years has it been...
(Tatsumi) Mr. Yukihiko⸺
You told me everything
I was the one who pushed that person named Eida down.
(Tatsumi) Ah... this smartphone is the victim's...
(Yukihiko) Yeah.
It contained a number of videos of me secretly filmed.
How do you find your place?
Parents of students⸺
It seems like he posted a photo of me on SNS.
Mr. Eida caught wind of that...
(Yukihiko) That man is not satisfied with just threatening Mikimoto⸺
That night⸺
I called you to that park too.
-(Aeda) Wait, Yukihiko Matsushino-(Yukihiko) Please stop.
(Mikimoto) Hello, Taeko-san, this is Mikimoto.
(Torataro) And you⸺
Between Yukihiko-san and Eida-san⸺
Did you witness what happened?
(Eida) Hey, take a look at this.
-(Yukihiko) Please stop it! -(Eida) Wow!
Ah...
(Taeko) Mikimoto-san?
what happened? Did something happen?
(Mikimoto) Hahahaha...
Yukihiko
were you alive?
(Yukihiko) Oh
-(Mikimoto) What are you planning to do? -(Yukihiko) What, I have to call the police.
(Mikimoto) No!
If you do that, the last seven years will be ruined.
Just a little more!
What do you mean?
(Mikimoto) If your disappearance declaration is accepted⸺
Taeko became a free person⸺
I can get out of that Matsushino house.
Taeko is⸺
Are you still there?
I'm sure Taeko is already living a different life...
(Mikimoto) Because you disappeared⸺
Taeko, on the other hand, ended up being tied to that house.
Don't you even know that? ?
Like that...
(Mikimoto) Take this and run.
Until October 10th⸺
Don't let anyone know you're alive
Please run away!
it's not for you
For Taeko-san
For Taeko...
(Tatsumi) To Mr. Mikimoto⸺
It was necessary to extend the trial beyond October 10th.
That's why you told us like that.
It would be better to finish the trial as soon as possible...
That doesn't make any sense.
(Tatsumi) Before 7 years pass⸺
If we find out that Yukihiko is alive⸺
The declaration of disappearance is not accepted⸺
Taeko will also not be able to receive her inheritance.
You were afraid of that⸺
I tried to hide Yukihiko's existence no matter what.
This is⸺
This is the trick we have read through
(Torataro) Why are you so...
Have you been charged with murder?
Taeko-san⸺
He's a good person to be happy with.
The only way to do that is to do this...
Taeko-san⸺
Can that really make you happy?
She has not applied for Yukihiko to be declared missing.
Leaving Matsushino's house with Yukihiko's inheritance in hand
That's for Taeko⸺
I think it's because I wasn't happy or anything.
(Torataro) As lawyers, we cannot provide defense that the client does not want.
So I can't talk about Yukihiko in court.
(Tatsumi) What will you say in your final statement? The last move will be⸺
Mr. Mikimoto, you can decide for yourself, right?
(Tatsumi) Yukihiko-san is alive...
And pushing Eida-san down⸺
You knew that, right?
(Mikimoto) It's tough, a man named Eida was pushed down...
Yukihiko...
Huh?
Ah... no! Taeko didn't know anything
Sounds good? Keep this phone call a secret!
What do you mean? Eh, Yukihiko-san, why?
It's okay!
The rest...
wait a minute! Hey hey!
Wait, wait...
Hey... wait...
(Taeko) To testify to Mr. Mikimoto's innocence⸺
I went to court
But...
I just can't say anything about Yukihiko...
I'm sorry
Heritage wasn't the goal.
Huh?
(Tatsumi) The reason why I didn't apply for a declaration of disappearance is⸺
I heard that was Taeko's wish.
I don't have that qualification.
qualifications?
Yukihiko is being cornered little by little⸺
Even though I was by your side⸺
I can't help anything...
Because of that, that person...
well⸺
For guilt and regret⸺
Stayed with the Matsushino family for 7 years...
There's nothing else I can do⸺
I can't even move
Yukihiko said something like this.
(Yukihiko) For the past seven years, I have escaped the yoke of the Matsushino family.
I was able to enjoy a fleeting moment of freedom.
Taeko also forgot about me a long time ago⸺
I told myself that I was becoming happy.
but⸺
It wasn't like that
That night⸺
I learned this from Mr. Mikimoto.
Even though Mikimoto is suspected to be the culprit⸺
The fact that they're trying to get a declaration of disappearance means me too.
I can't shake that determination
That would also be compensation for Taeko...
That's what I thought
...but
I finally understood
I can never atone for the sins I committed
i was stupid
I just...
I just wanted Taeko to be happy no matter what.
But I...
All I do is make Taeko suffer...
cry)
(Tatsumi) The past seven years⸺
There's nothing I can do⸺
You said you couldn't move.
but⸺
Isn't it finally possible to make your next move?
Second-rate?
(Tatsumi) In the midst of long and painful thoughts⸺
Yukihiko faces himself⸺
You are fighting to move forward.
Taeko too⸺
The time has come to point out the hand that will set you free.
I think
♪～
Because Torataro-sensei isn't here⸺
Why am I playing an impression game...
(Tatsumi) Thanks to Yukihiko Matsushino's appearance⸺
The prosecution canceled the charges.
The court decided to dismiss the prosecution.
As for the game⸺
I think it can be said that we won.
Well, certainly⸺
We broke the 99.9% AI wall.
These two octagons pointed to by AI
At first glance, it looks like a very strong hand⸺
That was the worst move
(Rie) Stunning handjob⸺
I guess I'm hooked.
The one that turned into a horse in 19⸺
If you move even one square⸺
Easily taken by the other party⸺
Can't move anywhere
This piece is it⸺
She is the wife of the wealthy Matsushino family⸺
The wife of the missing husband
I couldn't escape that label⸺
Maybe that's what Taeko was.
(door chime)
(Rie) Yeah? Maybe a customer
I thought it was an exquisite impression.
(Sound of door closing) (Rie) Very difficult.
Someone who looks really dangerous might have arrived.
What?
～♪
(Rie) No matter how you look at it⸺
You're not just a normal person, are you?
(Tatsumi) Certainly
(sound of tapping on sofa)
(Gouda) Hey!
(Goda) Bring out Torataro!
Where is it!?
(Torataro) I will handle this lawsuit by myself.
(Tatsumi) Against the landlord⸺
Do you mean to sue?
(Goda) I won't lose at all!
(Tatsumi) If you don't point in the correct order⸺
Unbelievable things will happen
(Torataro) I absolutely believe that⸺
I decided
(Tatsumi) There might be a scuffle off the board.