I saw that.
Good morning.
Oh, you came.
Episode 14
Team Leader.
When on earth will I receive my official passcard?
You came?
- You came?
- Why...?
You look handsome.
You came!
What is up with you all?
Did you all go for drinks in the morning, or what?
Oh my, what is that? What?
On the desk!
It looks a little familiar... what's this again?
Congratulations, Hyung.
Ah, it finally feels like he is a member of our team.
Team Leader, don't you think it is too early to give a probationer a card?
How can I bear looking at this arrogant guy more?
I am not giving it to him.
The Captain is rewarding him for saving two people.
Lies. He told me to make the card.
He's coming up with excuses now.
Ahem... we gotta go clean up...
Don't interfere.
Don't be annoying. Don't act like Kang San Hyeok.
Let's see if you're capable of that.
There's still a long way for me to see you as a member of my team.
Either way, thank you, Team Leader.
This is a serious waste of my abilities,
but I shall gladly devote my body for the Miryeong Forest.
Not the rescue team but Miryeong Forest?
Sir, I am going to the work you ordered right now?
Yes. 47.
What? 47?
No, we have to do it properly. We have to finish this properly.
47....
Died during transport
Died during transport.
This, too. Death.
Death...
Golden time?
Yes.
I thought the rescue team's location was a bit strange.
The other rescue teams are located at the center of their jurisdictions so they are able to stay within the golden time.
The Miryeong Rescue Team here is only close to Miryeong Village and
the west side of the mountain is rather far from us so the Southwest rescue team can get there faster.
Well, that is why we now share mobilization with the Southwest rescue team depending on the circumstances.
Of course, most of the time we go, but
in the event of a serious injury, the Southwest team will go.
When you say "now," does that mean that the Miryeong team used to always go in the past?
Then, if they missed the golden time
would there have been deaths?
Yeah.
Actually, at the start of this place's construction,
there were frequent deaths during rescue or transport.
Hey.
This information among insiders even is a bit hush hush, but this place's location is a little... iffy.
Not only the distance,
but there's a serious disadvantage to us air rescue paramedics, who have to move by helicopter.
Gust zone!
A gust zone?
The Miryeong Mountain is topographically prone to gusts of wind.
Our rescue team is right at the center.
Don't get me started. Ever since I transferred here, it's been gust and fog day after day.
We often have to put our lives at risk to go rescue!
Why do you think helicopter captains comes first on the least wanted jobs list.
Why do you think they would have chosen to place the rescue team here of all places, when there's such a problem?
Who know? Well...
Maybe because of the forest fires?
There's no rescue agency in the Miryeong district.
The residents didn't stop complaining about how we couldn't stop the village from burning down.
Yes.
Hey, hey. hey. Don't ever mention the Miryeong fire in front of the team leader.
He must have gone through a lot at the time, and he's very feisty about it.
Yes.
Yeah, I will be going that way.
Forest fires and gusts...
Is your father a land owner in Miryeong?
Not knowing now when something happens to your elderly mother,
wouldn't it be safer to move her to a city with a large hospital?
"Real Estate Contract"
We can move those who have passed away to a memorial park.
Should you really leave this land with great value unrealized, just because it's your family gravesite?
How much does it cost to care for a child!
Isn't that right?
- That's right!
- That's right.
What was the result?
I've convinced all parents in Miryeong who say they will sell their land.
Director, you really.
It's a lot quicker to make deals with kids who have a lot more expenses than the rural old folks..
If we add the villagers who already agreed on selling, I think that should do it.
There is only one person left.
Choi Jeong Mok!
That land leads to the road. If we can't obtain it,
we will have to divert the drive to the resort too far.
Get Choi Jeong Mok's land. No matter what.
I understand.
What are you doing here?
Are you in charge of the catchment too, Ms. Oh?
If there's ever a fire in the Miryeong forest,
this is where the helicopter would get the water from. Of course I've got to take care of it.
I'm guessing you're here to inspect the catchment.
Yes.
Give it to me.
I'll do it.
Am I having a fling with this guy?"
When he just looks at me, he keeps on grinning foolishly.
He took my tools, saying he would give me a hand. But where he laid his hand was only 3cm away from mine!
Congrats! on getting out of the Forever Single Club!
3cm for sure!
It's a fling! Hahahaha
I have given it much thought.
I am in trouble.
What?
Last time I was fishing,
You grasped my waist, when my arm was available.
And earlier too, you could have placed the notebook
on a rock, on the grass, or laid it on the sand. But you handed it to me.
I know the meaning of that, I understand but
I can't.
I've got to separate my private life from my professional one.
Wow!
I guess he must be really hurt.
Naturally, he would be hurt.
He is a pain in the neck.
Yeah, yeah, Please keep smiling that way,
So we can comfortably see each other.
In public.
Then, how does it seem if you separate your private life and professional one?
Can I hand my notebook to you, privately?
What?
His flirting skills are on another level.
I should be careful.
Our Naseong Development is planning on building a training institution.
We'll get you a better price than the market value, Sir.
Why don't you hand the mountain and factory over to us.
Oh my, is that so?
You're quite young, to be in charge of such a big business.
But you're not a major company,
why are you building such a large training center?
Naseong Development's already got more than enough land,
to build a couple of training centers. But that ain't enough for you?
What? Are you coming after me after you bought all that land?
But since I feel bad, I'll tell you something.
I have one flaw.
I have no greed for money.
I don't know if people are willing to sell their land for money
Not in my case.
My grandfather's burial and my parents' burial.
They're all lying down here in Miryeong.
How could I sell that for money?
This is all Miryeong.
This Miryeong forest.
Do you know how much I have taken care of and developed it?
Every day, I have shed so much blood.
How could I exchange it for money?
If you were to give me the money, how much would that be?
Several hundred billions?
How much billions (of won)?
Just leave.
As for my land, no matter how much fortune you give me
you can't have it.
Well, that's it.
You'll have to go through my land to connect to a major highway.
That amazing value.
How would you calculate such value with money?
It sounds like there's an amount you desire, so if you negotiate with us in detail...
You don't get me at all. I'm saying that's not it.
Merchants can smell other merchants.
If you're a businessman of such a huge scale,
there has to be a strong smell. The blood and sweat you've shed all this time.
But since you came to me, it seems that the smell of blood is rather weak?
For sure. It seems you are following the orders of another person.
Please go.
What is the problem?
What are you doing blocking the street?
Oh, is that so?
I mean, I almost fell because the wheel was loose.
I will take care of it.
The hub is loose.
You are strong self-sustaining man, huh?
You look like you'd order people around not lifting your finger.
Do you think I could've come up to this position without lifting a finger?
In anything you do, you have to know how to do things well if you want to order others around.
Do you know that the majority of corporate CEOS who frequent the psychiatrist office happen to be perfectionists?
Thanks to their perfectionism, they were able to climb up the ladder,
but they're only happy when they do everything themselves. So, they're suffering from high stress from overworking.
"It's okay if I do less..."
I've seen a case where someone who said that to himself every morning got better very quickly.
I guess that person must've had someone to fall back on even if he didn't get to do things himself.
I--
I what?
Pass me the wrench.
I what??
I have seen a completely opposite case.
I have an orphan friend.
He was abandoned by his parents as a child
and said this to himself every morning looking at the mirror.
"I'm my protector."
Only I can save myself.
Do you know how much that friend has been able to succeed now?
A protector, a rescuer...
He can do less?
Of course. I'm sure you speak of fairytale-like stories since you don't know.
The psychology of a person who has to endure without anyone to depend on in this world...
How could Jeong Yeong Jae know–
It's about the adopted daughter from the forest.
I guess you know. Since you studied psychiatry for a short time.
Why are you riding the bicycle everywhere when you can't even fix something so simple?
- It's all about looking cool, huh?
- In any case...
You always cut down the other person.
I ride it because I can't drive in this narrow and rough road.
At first.
That's why I started riding the bike.
But.
On the road that felt like I was going on exile...
What I saw.
See? What
I won't tell you.
It's kind of like not wanting others to know about a truly great restaurant.
That's it. It's perfect now.
Gosh, you're such a high maintenance woman.
WOW!
I'll fix the rest of the bike and bring it back.
Is that so?
Then I will go in and do my work.
The location is the truck parking lot at a highway rest stop.
It's a blind spot for the CCTVs, so there won't be any evidence.
Politicians are sensitive about bribery.
When you meet him, take the black box and exchange it.
It's a sign of trust symbolizing that you're not secretly recording them.
I delivered it to the partner.
Assemblyman Kim
- Let's have a drink.
- Yes, sir.
I have arrived, partner.
Sit.
Assemblyman Kim received scholarships from Taeseong, so he’ll definitely join hands with Director Cho.
We’ll change our partner. It’ll be more expensive, but he’ll be more helpful.
He has a bad relationship with Taeseong. They’re enemies.
I’m honored to work with you, Governor.
Nice to meet you.
Even if I release the provincial forests, if you can’t move the special rescue squad,
won't the development be impossible.?
You don't have to worry about that problem.
I’ve found problems that will justify a relocation. I only need your permission for the development.
I am sure I will be able to move the Special Rescue Team.
What is that?
Backward! Go back!
Bastards.
How did it go?
After you left Assemblyman Kim, he went directly to meet someone nearby.
The pictures our staff took, I sent them to you right now.
Why is he meeting with Mr. Bong?
Don't mention the Miryeong fire in front of Team Leader.
He must have gone through a lot at the time, and he's very defensive.
I can deal with the other areas, but the special rescue squad is a problem.
Memories of the Miryeong forest fire will cause a lot of opposition from the residents.
You must bring me a complete plan to move the base.
Miryeong forest fire?
Whatever it is, I am sure.
Even though he has a temper.
I mean, why is this in Kang Sanhyeok's belongings?
Why is there a stone wall here?
Is this where the old Miryeong village was?
Jeong Soon Ae
Kang San Hyeok!
Choi Jeong Mok.
Someone’s trying to buy Mount Miryeong, to build a resort.
It's been a while since we have met.
About 25 years.
Kang San Hyeok!
I have some emergency pain relief medicine. I’ll give you an injection.
It will be fine in a bit.
Don't do it. Don't give me a shot. I will endure it.
I’ll find out what’s causing this without falling asleep.
I have to do it.
Even if it’s phantom pain, it will be the same as the real thing!
You’ll feel like your arm is actually burning right now, Kang San Hyeok!
This is right. No one should go through this.
Don't do it.
I can endure it. I must endure it.
The boy who was abandoned by his parents when he was young, looked into the mirror every morning and said...
“I am my own guardian. Only I can save myself.”
How would you know what goes on in the mind of someone who is alone and has no one else to lean on-
You are wrong, Kang San Hyeok.
Why are you alone under the sky?
You know I am here.
Kang San Hyeok, whenever you are sick and come running, I am here, you know?
I am the girl next door who cannot let you suffer alone.
♬ Sometimes holding my breath, I approach closer. ♬
So, don't get hurt.
Don't endure it.
♬ Without a word of sweet comfort ♬
♬ Just scatter ♬
♬ and disappear. ♬
♬ My feelings, my loneliness, my silence ♬
Don't choose to suffer, Kang San Hyeok.
Please.
♬ In spite of my effort♬
♬ to get closer, you coldly push me away. ♬
Jeong Soon Ae
♬ Please take me now ♬
♬ Towards the light which shines on me ♬
♬ Please take me ♬
♬ Please take me now ♬
♬ The hope that is felt ♬
♬in the cold breath ♬
Forest Preview
I started wanting to know everything there is about Kang San Hyeok.
You don’t have to remain here with the rescue squad.
I’ll start crossing your line now, Kang San Hyeok.
Let’s meet for personal reasons.
This is my chance to ditch him.
Who is it?
It’s not your memory?
The Yeong Jae that is with me tonight, is it the doctor or the person?
Which one do you want her to be?
You must do something for me.
San number 23, Mount Miryeong, fire reported.
Where are you Yeong Jae?!
Jeong Yeong Jae!
♬ Because My feelings, my loneliness ♬