Orange color.
Episode 23
It's high... My God!
My God!
What brings you here, Director...
Didn't I tell you, Dr. Jeong?
That I'd be seeing you again real soon.
You must've been up to something interesting.
Interesting? It's just something I was studying.
But what brings you here without calling first?
My sweetie
At Miryeong Hospital?
Including the trauma center you proposed, I'm planning on a business to provide great support for all the village residents.
If we expanded this place and brought in the latest equipment, I think it will be a great medical center for Miryeong County.
You came here at this hour to tell me that?
Thanks to you, the foundation finds the project meaningful and is moving forward swiftly.
It was worth making my hasty trip down here.
The hospital site is spacious and I even got to see you studying.
I'm glad that the trauma center will be built so fast. But I'm not sure about the medical center.
There's already Gangwon Myeongseong Hospital and isn't this area too out of the way for the county residents?
That's why it's even better.
The neglected area like Miryeong is being reborn as a symbol of medical welfare.
Is Miryeong your hometown? Or is it the foundation's executive director's?
It seems like you love Miryeong County very much.
It's all thanks to you, Dr. Jeong.
You changed Miryeong, Dr. Jeong.
Jeong Yeong Jae!
Yeong Jae!
Gosh, you scared me!
I thought you were running late. What brings you here?
I went home, but you were there. I kept calling, but you didn't answer.
It was on silence.
Did you see a patient at this hour? I saw a car I didn't recognize drive by.
He looked around the hospital saying he'll expand the hospital.
So, why did you call me?
My God!
I found it on my way over.
I guess you've seen that somewhere.
- Let's go. To our home.
- Okay.
You have to let me go to go home.
I don't want to. Let's go like this.
Let's go, shorty.
What are you doing?
But you know, you yelled out, "Yeong Jae" earlier.
So what? You're mine, so I'm calling you by name.
You're so funny. Who says I'm yours?
Aren't you? Who do you belong to then?
Will you really be okay?
Sleeping alone?
No!
Without you, Oppa, Yeong Jae will...
will be so, so scared.
Did you think I'd say that?
Hurry home and go to bed. I have lots of work to do.
This place is good. Where is this?
I won't be scared at all since the rain stopped. Right?
I'm going to bed first.
The rice cake is the best during summer. Don't you think?
Geez, so dry.
So dry, so dry...
Yes, this is Jeong Yeong Jae.
I'm sorry to call you so late, Dr. Jeong.
Our foundation would like to have you as the director of the medical center.
Me?
Why me?
For what you symbolize.
We want to use your pure intention as the medical center's marketing point.
So, I wanted to ask you if you could send me a document
on a specific area of study that you're interested in.
A document?
It's a formality to produce a profile on the medical center director. You can make it simple.
For example, what you were studying earlier...
Well, things like that.
I'm only a resident now. What do you mean a medical center director? That's over the top.
There are specialists at Miryeong Hospital who have worked there for a long time.
I'll discuss that with the foundation.
In any case, I need some information on your profile. So, please send me that document.
Okay, I'll do that.
Why does he want me to write up a document?
And he called me about that at this late hour?
About AQU6 Test Kit
Model: AQU6
Test kit – About arsenic substance
Director, a doctor from Miryeong Hospital requested a water quality analysis report.
Miryeong Hospital?
Take care of it as per usual.
Find out what Kang San Hyeok's critical weakness is.
It's Kang San Hyeok's fiancée.
And they live in Miryeong village together. It's the same doctor who requested a water quality analysis report from Miryeong Hospital.
The managing director wishes to donate quietly behind the scenes.
I ask that you move forward with everything under the foundation name without revealing the managing director's name.
Hello, Director. Long time no see.
- We've been waiting. Have a seat.
- Yes.
Jeong Yeong Jae.
Miryeong 119 Special Rescue Team is celebrating its 25th anniversary today.
To recognize our team members' hard work night and day for the safety of the people...
Move, I can't see him.
He's a bad boy.
For the past 25 years consistently,
the village residents have lived side by side with our rescue team.
And we've prepared this celebration with gratitude.
For a helicopter, especially behind the helicopter...
You can't stand behind it.
You can't see the propeller rotating on its tail end.
- Something terrible will happen.
- So scary...
Team Leader.
I think the trauma management system will be worked out.
Trauma management?
You had asked me about it last time for your team members.
When did we talk about that? Are you sure you're not mistaking me for someone else?
It was you, Team Leader.
No way. I'd remember it if it were me.
I see...
Ma'am!
Her mom and dad had already drowned.
And the little girl was not moving.
Yeong Jae!
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
What are you doing here?
You're up.
The tranquilizer was about to wear out. I didn't think I should leave you alone.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm proud of you, Jeong Yeong Jae.
You must've been scared. But you're awake now.
I'm so proud of you.
I'd like to be alone.
All right. Do that.
100 Questions and Answers for a couple
Jeong Jeong Jae, Birthday, Schools attended...
I'm not going to value.
I'm not going--
What's this?
You're such an expert. The best.
"What I want to do most: Camping." That's what you wrote.
It's the weekend. Get in.
- Go camping? Now?
- Yeah.
You don't have to prepare anything. Just go like that.
Hurry. Hurry up.
Wait. Just a moment.
Wow, it's so nice.
♬ Oh at the sound of a whistle ♬
♬ I hum without realizing it ♬
♬ Drunk on a cup of coffee ♬
♬ I also don't realize ♬
♬ I'm sitting and thinking of you ♬
♬ I try saying anything. ♬
♬ Rather than what you want ♬
♬ Listen to the answer I've prepared ♬
♬ By the time the sun sets ♬
It's so nice.
♬ We will sit and face each other blankly ♬
- I got it.
- Wow!
- So pretty.
- You could eat it.
- Can you eat that?
- Of course.
♬ Even doing nothing at all I feel good ♬
- Is it good?
- Yeah. Super sweet.
♬ Anytime with you ♬
♬ That is how I want just you ♬
♬ In my heart, it's only you ♬
So sour.
♬ Only you in my heart ♬
♬ Only you always in my heart ♬
Whoa...
♬ Will you come to me? ♬
What color is the tree then?
♬ Sometimes on rainy days ♬
♬ we remember together walking together ♬
♬ An intimate ending ♬
Really?
You've never taken a nap?
Don't you feel guilty if you lie down during the day?
There are so many people who are trying to catch up with me. How could I sleep?
What do you mean how? You just close your eyes.
Try it and see if the world collapses or not.
I guess you don't understand my position.
The size of the investments I'm managing...
♬ We will sit and face each other blankly ♬
♬ We can fall in love ♬
♬ Always ♬
Geez, I can't take a nap.
♬ Only you in my heart ♬
Fireflies.
It's my first time seeing them.
They're so pretty when you see them in person.
Thank you.
It would've taken me a long time for me to come out of it.
I'm paying you back.
When I wanted to hide behind the wall,
you barged right in and made me laugh.
I owe you a lot.
To that pretty person.
You know...
I... when I was nine years old...
You don't have to struggle to tell me. I know already.
No.
I want to tell you.
That day, with those hands that used to stroke my head and embrace me every day
and the hands that held me underwater
and seeing them float limply in front of my eyes...
Their last.
Whenever I think about that,
I hear a whisper in my ears.
"You're cursed."
"You're cursed, so you're miserable."
I keep whispering that to me.
That's how I was.
But I have the confidence to fight, thanks to you.
You're the proof that I'm not cursed.
♬ Suddenly, like a tree that has grown, you're always there ♬
♬ Always ♬
♬ Only your warm breath ♬
♬ fills me up ♬
♬ Because I will love you ♬
♬ Like a day that will never come back to me ♬
♬ I love you ♬
That devil.
♬ Always ♬
♬ Accidentally, the times you face me, ♬
♬ I will seep into your heart ♬
♬ Always ♬
♬ Yes, with your warm breaths, ♬
I'll go.
♬ you fill me. ♬
♬ Because I will love you ♬
♬ I love you ♬
♬ As always at that spot ♬
♬ Always ♬
Description of incident: I, Bong Dae Yong, holding the hoist...
Good morning, Team Leader.
Oh, good morning.
Team Leader, about yesterday's accident...
The hoist adjuster must put away the rope after the training.
But why was it left out dangerously and got tangled with our visitor's foot?
I forgot. It was my mistake.
Why did you make a mistake?
Good morning!
You could've told me to put the rope away. But you even forgot that as well.
You've worked as an aviation rescuer for 25 years.
How could you have forgotten that?
By chance, did you measure your alcohol level yesterday morning?
What are you doing, Kang hoobae? It's not necessary.
It's not unnecessary. I'm trying to prevent an even bigger incident.
After the incident yesterday, you couldn't give out any orders. You were acting strange, Team Leader.
Did you measure your alcohol level?
- Two nights ago, I...
- Team Leader!
- Team Leader, wait, Pilot Jeong is looking for you.
- Give me a moment.
You know, he's in a huge rush due to his flying schedule.
Where have you been? I've been looking for you all over. Hurry, hurry.
Hurry, hurry!
- Two night ago...
- I was looking for you all over.
Why couldn't I get in touch, Team Leader?
When will you be done with all the files?
I'm almost done. I have a little bit more.
What do you mean you're done? You have this much left. Why bluff?
That's all done. I just have this much.
You've done this much already? Does that make sense?
I took them home when I had to. I even pulled all nighters.
I'll finish them today. Please wait.
You pulled all nighters?
What choice do I have? My high and mighty sunbaenim asked me to do this.
I should do it right away.
Sunbaenim?
Sunbaenim, I'm not good at kissing up to people.
I know my weaknesses very well.
But you know, I don't play dirty to steal someone else's cake.
I went to the conference only because the higher-ups told me to go.
I'm doing my best to undo an unnecessary misunderstanding.
The shuttle bus doesn't come today. So I'll organize everything and hand them over to you quickly.
Whatever! Then do that.
Let's do this.
Director, I'm going in to catch the rats.
You made sure to set the trap, right?
I planted infamous experts.
You don't have to worry.
There will be an introduction by the Director Kwon Joo Han as the chair of the shareholders' meeting.
Hello to all the shareholders whom I respect. I'm Kwon Joo Han.
As a result of the audit, Taesung High Tech's finances and
accounting, there were no corruption nor important issues relating
to the breach of the corporate by-laws.
Wait a minute! Wait!
Please be quiet!
For a company that manufactures electronic parts,
I see evidence of planning a resort business.
What do you mean there were no important issues?
How did you get to start the Miryeong Forest Resort project
and how is it moving forward?
Please explain, so the shareholders can understand.
I address you respectfully, shareholder.
I don't know why such a rumor is going around.
But I have never been involved with a resort project.
You've never done that?
You hired a fixer named Jo Kwang Pil, a former gangster,
and order him to move forward with the business.
The flow of the funds to that Jo Kwang Pil's service company is clearly shown here.
Will you continue to deceive the shareholders?
Respectfully, shareholder, I don't know someone by that name.
Who's spreading false information? Provide proof!
There's a photo.
Melanoma?
Particularly in this village...
And this village has a history of manufacturing pesticides.
Lung cancer.
Deceased.
Sepsis.
Why is this stupid vending machine so slow?
Dr. Park, why did you keep the photos of these patients?
What are you talking about?
Among the records from last ten years, you kept only these two patients' photos.
- Why did you do that?
- Geez...
Who are they?
Well, just because. It felt weird to me.
What was strange about them? Their skin condition?
This grandma had a bad cold, but
she had these blood clots, bruises, and dark spots. So, I took some pictures.
But she passed away in a week with high fever and sepsis.
This grandpa was diagnosed with lung cancer. And he had a strange melanoma on his back.
But what about these pictures?
Their addresses are both Miryeong village.
By chance, do you know if they used underground water for drinking?
How would you know that, Dr. Jeong? By chance, are you thinking that's it?
Metal poisoning?
How do you know about that, Dr. Park? Did you figure that out then?
See? You should've pressed the issue.
Back then, Dr. Park thought it was strange.
But nothing was detected through water quality analysis
and they passed away pretty quickly. So, he just let that go.
So what else could I do? I was demoted to this tiny hospital.
They'd look down on me for saying something ridiculous.
It's not ridiculous, Dr. Park.
They found arsenic in the analysis.
What!
What's going on with this situation?
Then why wasn't anything detected on the water quality analysis?
There's something strange going on in Miryeong village.
Episode 24 will air soon