Episode 13
♬ The chaos which unfolds in front of me ♬
So should I cry?
The time we broke up? Am I supposed to cry about that?
Although it might sound strange, but did you care as little as that?
I was the one who got dumped so why are you mad?
I'm not angry...
Did you like me?
What are you so unhappy about?
Saying you wanted to go out with me and then setting up an impassable wall.
Have I set up a wall?
Doesn't dating someone and liking each other mean getting close and becoming an important person to each other?
You hate that. The feeling of developing our relationship.
If we are starting to make progress, you'll use that and make us back away.
I want my girlfriend to look at me with more special eyes
Just how I look at you.
I do focus on you. Why do you keep saying that I don't?
So can you tell me you love me?
Have you ever said it?
♬ Take me now ♬
I get it. You chose to break up so I'll respect your decision.
What the hell have I
♬ Towards the light which shines on me ♬
been doing with you that whole time?
♬ Please take me now ♬
Are you sure that you don't want to go with me?
Your heart sounded like it was on a roller coaster.
Are you sure you won't pass out?
Whether he is bragging or not, why did I ever played a true-false game?
Did you stay overnight here because of the rescued patient?
I don't know. I must have gone crazy.
Why is she like this?
What is it? That cringey look?
Breathalyzer Record
Kang San Hyeok None
Good morning, Subaenims.
Hyung, is your shoulder okay?
What? I told you to take a break. Why are you at work?
Now that I'm eligible for award, how can I take a break for my shoulder?
An award citation?
I saved a colleague's life in the spirit of a saint sacrificing himself but I shouldn't be given one?
Well then, it should be given to me as someone who is on probation.
Saving one's life, my foot.
How is it saving someone’s life when some materials just fell from the ceiling?
You're bragging too much.
After being injured and hospitalized, you disappeared without a word. Why did you leave?
Something urgent happened.
You've lost your position as the ace rescuer to me.
Do you think the rescue team is some kind of neighborhood foot volleyball team? Someone on probation rashly mentions the ace?
Aigoo, it's time to take a med.
Our Yeong Jae, prescribed me these with love, wishing a speedy recovery.
Do what you wanna do.
As I'm enjoying several victories, I can take it to some extent.
Victory? What kind of victory?
I have some kind of victory.
What is that satisfyingly bragging look?
What is it? It's suspicious.
- Member Yang?
- I didn't see him.
He must have forgotten. Take him to me.
Cheol Sik admires this lecturer the most.
Member Yang!
Yang Sunbae?
Crew member Yang, the guest lecture is about to begin.
I don’t think he heard you.
Oh, sorry. I’m just so used to checking that my colleagues got the information they need, I was meddling.
I don’t know who you are, but this isn’t a rescue.
I’ve told him multiple times, it’s his responsibility now.
Making others remind you about the lecture, it’s an inconvenience.
Team Leader Jeong?
You are Team Leader Jeong, right?
I have heard a lot about you. It is an honor to meet you, Team Leader.
An honor? What??
Let’s go to the lecture hall, I’ll take you there.
Please go this way.
- Yes, I’ll escort you.
- Is it this way?
Yes, sir.
Team Leader Jeong?
He is someone who turned down a promotion and comfortable office position,
to volunteer to work in Mountain Rescue and be in the field for over 20 years.
Please welcome, Team Leader Jeong Byeong Yeong, a living legend of Unam Rescue Squad 6.
Nice to meet you all.
Th man we had to rescue was stuck between the rocks, so we were unable to see him.
In cases like this, it’s very important to check how much battery is left in the cell phone,
of the person you’re rescuing.
In his case, he had about 4% left.
So I asked this person to turn off the phone.
Then after getting him to send a few texts,
I carefully approached him.
The mountain rescue squad does everything on foot without using helicopters.
It is so difficult and dangerous that everyone avoids working there long-term.
Is there a reason you volunteered to work there for over 20 years?
What made that possible? I really want to know.
Well....
I just liked this job.
About 20 years ago... I responded to a scene where a family attempted suicide together.
When we got there, the parents were already completely submerged and suffocated.
There was also a little girl, who wasn’t moving either.
When I pulled her out of the car and held her...
I could feel her heart beating.
However, I knew that it would stop before I could get her out of the water.
So I quickly took my oxygen mask off, put it on her, and then swam and got her out of the water.
And from my heart, I said this to the child...
Thank you.
Thanks for surviving.
You are such a great child to overcome this.
Please hold on more.
And then surprisingly, she opened her eyes and starred at me.
Just like she heard my mind.
How grateful it was...
Her eyes starring at me...
Little hands holding me tightly...
I still remember that feeling.
I think that's the reason
why I couldn't leave this field.
It is about his adopted daughter's story in his essay.
What’s the matter?
Look at that!
Do you know what it is?
You like it, don't you?
Wait, what is this? What’s this?
I found this!
Do you want this?
Ta-Da!
You’ll need to come back to remove the stitches.
- Does it hurt here?
- Yes.
What about here?
This part hurts too, right?
“Family Relation Certificate (General)”
“ Miryeong Resident Services”
Kang San Hyeok
There is no record of transfers to the outside of Seoul.
Why do I have a memory about Miryeong Forest?
My parents whom I even don't remember at all have no presence.
There's just blank on the record.
Who am I supposed to ask?
What these things are...
How did I know they were inside of that tree? Is this just a coincidence?
Everything is just coincidence, grandma?
"Kang San Hyeok"
What is this? We are not in a relationship where we can call each other.
I know you are embarrassed but come here quickly.
Embarrassed? Who is embarrassed? What is the matter?
I’ll say nothing happened, so just hurry back.
I have to shower!
This guy! Why do I need to hurry because you need to take a shower? That’s ridiculous!
What are you thinking?
My boiler is broken but the repairman is going to come and fix it tomorrow.
Let me use your bathroom.
Just skip the shower until tomorrow.
Do you regard my house as a public sauna?
Or just use the bathroom as the door is not locked.
Public sauna?
I bet she couldn't expect me to come here!
Password?
Would it be the same as before?
Yes, the house should be like this for my princess.
It looks good.
Oh, dear.
What’s that?
I wanted to surprise her, but I’m too late.
She's already here.
My daughter’s clothes.
There.
Aren't you finished yet, Jeong Yeong Jae?
What is it?
You must be surprised! Come out!
Your dad is here!
D..dad??
Dad? No way...
Ta-Da! Our princess’ favorite seaweed chips...
Dad? Dad!
Let's eat!
You’re not criminals. Hurry and eat.
What’s wrong with living with together?
We're not living together! We are just living in a connected house.
It’s really not like that. It’s just that his furnace broke down.
So, it’s really nothing at all, and you still hid it from me?
Nice... Very nice...
I...I didn't intend to deceive you...
There was no need to talk about it.
Why are you hiding your mouth by the way?
Just like a person who kissed to someone.
Food is stuck in your throat, hurry and have some soup.
How cold it must’ve been, being naked like that.
Ye-Yes... Team Leader Jeong.
You know, I thought I was an open-minded person.
But today, I now know what it’s like to feel the urge to kill.
Where are you going? You have no sense of humor.
Sit back down.
If you run from the table, you’ll be hungry for the rest of your life.
Hurry and eat.
Alright, here. I dried and fried these myself.
It’s our Yeong Jae’s favorite. Here, try it.
Our Princess, here you go!
Hurry and eat. Have some fish as well.
Eat.
- It’s good.
- Right?
So, how long have you been in the rescue squad?
A little over two months.
- Is it worth it?
- Yes.
Hey. Don’t let her drink too much water.
She’ll pee a lot.
What?
She wet her bed until she was 13 years old.
Dad! Until I was 3.
Don’t lie. I found her bed wet a few times until she was 13.
- How could a 13 year old—
- I wasn’t 13!
Have a red pepper. It’s delicious.
Not peppers.
- Why?
- I can’t eat spicy food.
- Dad, it’s spicy!
- No, I...
- Is it?
- What?
- Don’t.
Have one.
Stop it.
Does it make sense that we aren't staying the night after coming all this way?
I told you I have a morning shift. Team Leader Kim also came to see his mother.
It's already been decided that I'll be taking that car.
Look. There it is.
Hurry and go back in.
Team Leader.
I had a great time. Please take care of yourself.
Take care okay?
It would have been so much better if you just stayed the night.
In any case, the rescue team is all you care about.
What did I say was the most important thing when living this life?
Never back down?
Well the way I see it, it applies to relationships as well.
There is only something to gain if you go all the way without backing down from the war.
As long as you're not taking the other's happiness, what is there to be afraid of?
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
Just, I'm just saying that I believe in you.
Do you know how exceptional you are? Knowing that you take after me?
I am going.
Dad.
Call me often!
What was I doing all that time with you?
Consultants opposing removal of Miryeong 119 SRS
Here, too, they didn't answer.
Something is really fishy.
All the consultants and city council members who opposed moving the special rescue squad 119,
are all avoiding our calls. Like they’re colluding.
Then we’ll go catch them.
What? Where are you going?
Shouldn’t we hunt? The slimy evaders.
He left Naseong Development and went to work.
Yes, sir. I understand.
As you instructed, I put two fast guys on their tail.
Don’t lose them.
Do it right, and catch a rat.
1, 2
3, 4
Do it faster!
At this speed, when will you finish connecting it and spray the water?
8, 9, 10.
Again!
What? We did it within the time given?
The front part of this control head...
“ Control Head: A pendulum control device for steering large freshwater bags for fire extinguishing”
It should be facing up when connected. Didn’t you learn this in firefighting school?
You don't like this feeling, huh? Again!
-2
-He didn't even tell me when he was going to start.
The golden time is going.
The very beginner is going to burn down the house.
Taesung
What is this? Isn't this Taesung Group?
Taesung group?
You come.
No... I just wanted to look around here. That's it.
Stop, stop, stop!
Why is your leg like this?
I have my knees swollen.
You're limping.
What? All the villagers are coming?
I don't want to get his treatment.
- You condescending jerk. I’ll rip your face off!
- Oh, wait. Calm down.
-Your leg! Let's start by going in.
You should walk slowly....
I’ll rip his face off!
Did I beg her to get treatments from me?
She said that!?
Until your knee got this swollen, you didn't come to the hospital? What have you been doing?
I didn't wanted to come here because of that guy outside.
That man is a total disgrace.
As he isn't kind to the elderly, no one wants to come here.
But I thought that you are not like him,
When I saw you're being kind to Jeong Bae's father.
You did well in coming.
Let's talk about it after taking an X-ray.
It just seems like a recurrence of your arthritis. So don’t worry too much.
There you go.
Is your hand also being abnormal? Is it shaking?
It's been like that. I must be because I drink a lot of coffee.
Is that so?
Yes, this is Miryeong Hospital. I am Doctor Jeong Yeongjae.
It's Gangwon Hospital.
The previous blood test results showed the presence of leucocytosis and blast cells.
Leucocytosis: increase in number of white blood cells
Blast cell: myelogonic cells
The elder man whom we had a smear screening test done on, Heo Choon Shik?
- Yes.
The results are out. It looks like acute leukemia, for sure.
Leukemia: acute blook disease
Acute leukemia?
Ma’am, is Mr. Heo at home right now?
Jeonb Bae's father?
He is heading to his family house.
'Family house'? What is that?
Dr. Park should have come with us! How can I drive on this road when I hardly drive?
You do have the life insurance, right?
Don't you talk to me. Just look ahead.
I think it’s this way.
We didn’t used to live here, but across the mountain.
But our whole town burned downed due to a fire, so we moved here.
- Mr. Heo!
It wasn’t just Jeong Bae’s father, but almost everyone used to live there.
- Mr. Heo! Mr. Heo!
- How do you think he would have felt,
- Sir, do you hear me?
- after seing his parents grave burn to dust like that?
- Sir!
Mr. Heo Choon Shik!
Grandfather!
Grandfather, can you hear me?
Can you open your eyes?
We have got to give him a transfusion, right away. It's petechia.
Petechia: a small red or purple spot caused by bleeding into the skin
We should go directly to the hospital.
Don't be surprised, Grandfather.
You are okay.
I am here.
Slowly, go slowly.
Be careful.
Watch your step.
Yes, this way.
“2nd floor under repair”
His name is Cho Yong Pil. He’s a new director Taesong Group brought in for the resort project.
He's known to have belonged to organized crime and when he gets involved in a business that seems utterly impossible,
things proceed flawlessly, so he's become quite infamous in the industry.
Anyone who stood in the way of his projects ended up dead, disguised as suicide.
No wonder. I thought he seemed quite a large scale of a character to be used as Chief Han.
They even took the professor away from the restaurant last time.
I mean, we took Naseong Development from them awhile ago. Why is Taeseong Group giving us all this trouble now?
A corporation like that would try to bargain the cost down to the penny. Have you ever seen those people pay more than the market price?
They looked down on Chief Han.
He's not the one to lead the project properly. So they probably thought Naseong Development would give it up at a lower cost.
But in the midst of that, I jumped in and brought it thus far. So, Taesung is in a rush.
Seeing how they've hired a gangster like him, I don't think Taesung would give up on Miryeong Forest but go all in.
What should we do? Looks like it'll be a headache.
We should hurry up and get out. Before those people do anything funky.
Starting today, operate headquarters 1 to full capacity. We'll put everyone in and speed up the Miryeong Forest business process as much as possible.
Yes, sir.
"In a little bit, episode 14 will be airing."