Operation Room
Episode 31
Director.
The surgery went well, but he lost too much blood.
I think getting past tonight will be crucial.
Patient!
Patient, are you okay?
Are you conscious?
VIP Ward
Kang San Hyeok!
San Hyeok!
Patient Bong Dae Yong is awake and patient Kang San Hyeok is...
He can't seem to wake up from his sleep. I think it's psychological.
His CT scans show no abnormality. I thought he'd recover soon.
Well, Director...
Someone locked the hospital door from the outside and set the hospital on fire.
I'm sure it was payback for Kang San Hyeok whistleblowing the contamination case in Miryeong Village.
Kang San Hyeok is in danger. Please help him, Director.
The Miryeong Hospital was destroyed from the fire
and 200 hectare of Miryeong Mountain was burnt.
But fortunately, no fatalities occurred.
So where is the corpse?
I searched through the hospitals in the area just in case, but there was no patient by the name, Kang San Hyeok.
The probability of his survival is extremely low.
You never know. Search thoroughly.
You must confirm his death.
I understand, Managing Director.
Yes. Sleep as much as you can at times like this.
You lived feeling guilty about sleeping all this time.
Sleep well.
Rest.
And after that, look at me. Let's open your eyes.
All right?
It's unfortunate what's happened to the Miryeong Hospital, but I'm glad you're all safe.
You need to treat Miryeong Village residents. Until we rebuild the hospital,
you can work here.
I have prepared a separate office for you to look after Miryeong Village.
You all went through a lot in many ways.
He smiled at me.
Just because he's requesting this of me, does he think I'll stay on here?
It's too late, you know. Way too late.
In any case, the hospital can't run properly without me.
Hurry up and come. Our Miryeong residents are waiting for us.
The elevator is this way.
This is my turf. This one is not as busy, so it's faster.
We should get the heavy metal poisoning results first.
Executive Director
Yes, Executive Director.
Yes, I'm listening.
Yes, I got it.
It's me.
Are the heavy metal poisoning results on the Miryeong residents out?
[Blood Cell Heavy Metal Test]
Under the suspicion of heavy metal poisoning of the Miryeong residents,
all the test results show that the poisonous element was not detected.
[Heavy metal not detected in Miryeong Village residents]
The Miryeong county will continue to conduct the test quarterly going forward...
I'm sure Kang San Hyeok is dead.
Please forget our ill-fated relationship of the past
and give me the provincial forest development rights.
- He's here! He's here!
- Managing Director, is it true that the contamination in the Miryeong Village is connected to Taesung Group?
Is it true that you started the forest fire in order to cover up the contamination?
Please say a word!
That is not true.
Putting my father's honor on the line, I insist that I have nothing to do with this incident.
- Were you aware of the heavy metal poisoning in Miryeong Village?
- Director, did you know?
Director, one word, please!
San Hyeok! San Hyeok!
San Hyeok, it's me. Do you recognize me?
VIP Ward
Aside from the external wounds from the surgery, he's fine.
You went through a lot, Go Na Kang.
Thank you.
Go Na Kang? (Means Kang Toffee)
I changed your name and the date you were hospitalized.
You never know when the secret will get out. We should hurry and move you to a safer place.
People who were looking for Kang San Hyeok came by.
Jeong Yeong Jae was my protector?
Was?
I'm currently your protector and I'll continue to be your protector. What are you talking about?
Lean on me. I'll carry you.
You just stay safe.
Don't jump into the fire for my sake.
Just stay safe.
Promise me, okay?
Okay.
I promise.
Team Leader.
You finally pulled a big one. Crazy bastard.
- Team Leader, you're not normal either.
- Geez...
it hurts so badly.
Hey, you, don't even think about resigning, man.
I'll count all your unexcused absences, and you will only ride the rappel.
I got to see your sorry behavior.
Get out now.
It hurts so much that I want to cuss you out, man.
Director! Are you all right?
Dr. Jeong Yeong Jae told me not to come by in case your identity might get revealed.
I was dying of curiosity all by myself!
Stop fussing around. Hurry up and get ready.
Get ready? You just got out of the hospital. Get ready for what?
Managing Director Kwon Joo Han of Taesung Group, likely to succeed as the chairman
Get ready to catch and kill Kwon Joo Han.
Wow. You take my breath away.. So cool.
Director, you're alive and well!
I thought the ground underneath our station is contaminated.
So why is the county office telling us there are no problems?
They said they didn't find anything on the soil test.
Geez, I don't know if they want us to believe that or not...
The elders who drank underground water have cancer and all kinds of diseases.
But they say the test didn't detect any heavy metals.
This is serious.
All our tests also said they didn't detect anything.
But that makes me feel more uneasy.
Geez, we need our team leader at times like this.
Hyung San Hyeok would be the expert at fighting against things like this.
- I wonder when Hyung San Hyeok will wake up.
- Hey...
Aigoo, aigoo!
What if someone hears you?
Why? Is my name taboo?
San... oh, S hyung!
What the heck? Why is S here?
I'm awake now. So you're excused from not mentioning my name.
You can bring back Kang San Hyeok and curse me to your heart's content.
Wow, you took quite a vacation.
So, you're coming back to the rescue team now, right?
- Who says we'll take him back?
- Aigoo...
Geez, you look cool now.
We'd know for sure if we dig the grounds of the rescue team headquarters.
But I think the superiors want to let this slide quietly.
I need evidence to support cause and effect.
Were there any cases of cancers or leukemia in the rescue team?
I'm not sure. We take rotations on duty in different areas, so we don't hear of each other's condition too much.
From way before I started working here,
the rescue team started using tap water rather than underground water.
By chance, does paralysis count?
- Team Member Jang?
- Yeah.
He loved Miryeong Mountain. So he moved to Miryeong Village and worked here for ten years.
But suddenly, he started having paralysis in his legs.
In the end, he went out on a rescue mission, but couldn't move his legs.
So he got his leg amputated when a boulder fell on him.
If you look at it that way, don't you have more serious issues? You're from here.
I don't notice any problems myself. And my tests came out normal, too.
But then, I'm worried about my hyungnim. Did he get his medical exam?
You can't exert yourself yet.
The lesions and burn wounds are pretty serious.
Yes, scary Dr. Jeong.
Don't take this lightly.
If you overdo it, I'll take you and shut you in a hospital room.
See? Where? Where is it?
I'm okay. This is nothing.
I didn't know you'd be like this.
As soon as you woke up, you're chasing around the contamination issue in your condition.
- I think I misunderstood you a lot...
- Yeong Jae.
You didn't misunderstand me.
The night you packed up. You're correct about how you felt.
I was going to cover up the residents' poisoning issues and was going to start
the rare earth metals business.
The reason I'm doing this is completely for my personal revenge.
I don't have a sacred sense of duty like you're thinking.
Why don't you take a look at yourself again carefully?
Is Kang San Hyeok really that selfish?
Yes, I'm his son.
I wanted to know the result of the detailed medical examination that he took last time.
Pardon?
Did the test results come out?
As you instructed, I distributed fabricated test results.
And the real ones?
They're all here.
Blood Heavy Metal Test Results
They show 50% more than the safe level of arsenic in the residents.
Here you go. Hello.
Not detected
Everything looks normal.
You don't have to worry.
Detected
We, at Seoul Myeongseong University, must prove that we ordered the fabrication of the test results.
So, keep both sets of the test results secure.
I'll turn everything over to the Prosecutors' Office.
I understand, Director.
You asked to meet me but suddenly went awol.
Something urgent came up at my office.
Who is it?
The tiger cub who'd put the managing director in jeopardy if we don't kill him off right away.
But those guys who started the fire...
I thought they went to China.
But they came back and threatened me saying they'll reveal everything.
So, where are they?
I gave them some money and drove them out. No need to worry.
I saw them get on the airplane myself.
But it's so strange.
How could there me another fire as soon as that news comes out?
I guess you must've started the most recent fire yourself?
Why? Do you think I'd record you or something?
You'd better not try to pull anything.
I'm telling you that considering our old friendship.
Didn't you say you were going to build a resort?
When you told me to start the forest fire 25 years ago,
you said you were only trying to relocate the residents. That it's a simple task.
You completely deceived me. Right?
About those things being buried on our grounds.
Are you blaming me for what you did back then?
Don't you know me? I'm talking about money!
You deceived me when you bought the land with those expensive elements buried here.
You should pay me more.
I'll speak to the Managing Director.
He caused this illness for me. How dare he say he'll do another business?
I'm sure he has no idea that the child who was in that fire was Kang San Hyeok.
The brother of the kid you guys killed.
Take it from that tiger cub, Kang San Hyeok.
Those bastards deserve to be fried in the heavy metal s*** water!
Hey! Hey, you! What are you doing here at this hour?
How long have you been standing there?
Hey!
Why couldn't I think of that? Now that I think about it,
we were struggling to have three meals a day. But we suddenly got rich
right after the Miryeong forest fire 25 years ago.
What should I do, Father? Should I yell and scream and say how could you do such a thing?
Should I ignore it since the statute of limitation expired already?
What do I have to do?
Hey, if I turn myself in at the police station,
will you forgive me?
If you'd forgive me. If my Chang can live without being tormented all your life,
I'll... I'll do anything. Just say it.
Why do you live like that, Father? Don't you have your own life?
What did you gain by not having a life of your own?
What are you left with, but a sick body?
You... Do you know about my cancer?
You... I'm not scared of dying!
I'm your baby. The one you gave birth to with your aching belly.
No matter what you did, I'm always on your side.
Why don't you know that? Why don't you know that like an idiot?
- Father, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- Let go.
I'm sorry I made you that way. I'm sorry...
I'll get better.
I don't have any pain. I'm fine.
The entire grounds of the rescue team have been contaminated? I also have arsenic poisoning?
The reason you were having frequent memory lapse is not due to alcoholism,
but it could be from arsenic poisoning.
So I didn't only lose a friend in that forest fire from long ago.
Back then, your friend had gone in to rescue a little girl, right?
By chance, did you see anything strange?
The sound of an helicopter.
Not the rescue team helicopter. But I heard another helicopter.
But strangely, the portion about the helicopter got deleted in the rescue journal.
What's going on? Why are you being so serious unlike you?
I think kneeling will be too dramatic.
Even if I were to say, "How much money do you want?", you already have more money than I can compare.
I have no answer no matter how much I think about it.
What the heck is he saying?
The reason I have no answer is because I don't think I can ever forgive myself.
My father did something that's not forgivable.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
To you, Kang San Hyeok, and to your little sister...
I'm so sorry that all I can say is sorry.
Let go.
Yeong Jae might misunderstand if she saw us.
You shouldn't say the word, "Forgiveness," so carelessly.
I'll talk to your father directly.
The governor seems to be avoiding our calls.
All right.
He reappeared, huh? Kang San Hyeok is alive.
I'll take care of him myself immediately.
No. Seeing how well he is going around interfering with my work,
I'm sure he's prepared for that.
Then how should we proceed? There are only a few days left until the Chairman's deadline.
Then we should draw our last card.
The hostage card that we hold.
It's a list of Miryeong residents who were cremated since the 1994 forest fire.
1994 - A List of Deceased People in Miryeong Village (Cremated)
I met with every single chief mourner of their family.
All of them?
I was right.
I was suspicious since there was no record of funeral payment at the county office.
As expected, they all contacted a different party.
Deokin Foundation Social Contribution Team
Someone came out from this organization
and paid them a funeral fee only after confirming the cremation. Saying it's a welfare fund.
Deokin Foundation?
He helps us out with our hospital's medical services.
He's Director Jo Kwang Pil of the Deokin Foundation.
It's nice to meet you, Dr. Jeong Yeong Jae. I've wanted to meet you.
I looked into it and found out that there is no Deokin Foundation among the foundations that are registered nationally.
A fictitious organization has been paying the funeral cost for that long length of time.
Director Jo Kwang Pil
The number you dialed does not exist.
Please confirm and dial again.
There you go. Make sure to take your antibiotics.
- Is something wrong?
- Huh?
No, nothing.
By chance, do you know someone named Jo Kwang Pil through this contamination case?
How do you know Jo Kwang Pil?
He took my signature stamp saying he's building a trauma center.
I wasn't suspicious at all since he was introduced to me by the hospital director in Seoul.
It looks like the Deokin Foundation paid for the deceased Miryeong residents' cremation.
Why would he take my signature stamp?
I'll take care of it.
What are you going to do?
I'll take care of it. So, don't worry.
No. This is my business.
You can't be in a bind or compromise with them because of me.
- I got it. So, you just...
- This is my business.
Don't do it your way.
People who ignore evil are evil, too. I will never compromise.
If he's plotting something, I'll face him to the end.
Don't butt in with my business.
All right, I got it.
Deokin Foundation Executive Director, Jeong Yeong Jae
This is Kang San Hyeok.
I believe it's time we meet again, Managing Director Kwon Joo Han.
I guess being in love is an amazing thing.
You knew full well that you'd die here, yet you came voluntarily.
First, keep your promise.
Are you talking about this?
The proof of embezzling the slush funds that Executive Director Jeong Yeong Jae signed off.
I should give it to you.
If you can take it with you.
There's a question I get asked very frequently.
What is the meaning behind your smile on your face even in dire situations?
Is it composure or mockery? What do you think it is?
The only emotion that can be felt by Taesung Group's Kwon Joo Han.
Do you think the ordinary commoners dare even imagine it?
The sin of imagining something you don't dare imagine.
And the sin of challenging the power you should never attempt to challenge.
That's the reason you'll die.
The last episode will air soon.