Episode 28
How dare you show up here?
I'm here to investigate the arson committed by Miryeong Forestry's employees.
The police were here and did all the investigating. What more is there to investigate?
Do you think you're a cop or something?
It's also my job.
Did you really not know that those people were going to commit arson?
That's why I was so shocked myself.
I couldn't believe such evil punks were hiding in our Miryeong Forestry.
I was so shocked. Ever since that day,
I could neither eat nor sleep.
What's wrong with me?
President Choi!
Excuse me! Is anyone here?
Father! What's wrong?
What happened? Are you okay?
They'll observe him for a day and he can go home.
Thanks, Bo Mi.
What do you mean, thanks? I collapsed because of this Officer Oh.
Why did you have to get me all riled up?
- I couldn't just stand back and watch my future father-in-law fall into the depth of evil.
- Aigoo!
Who's your father-in-law?
Then, should I just say, "Father?" Or "Dad-in-law?"
Aigoo, give me a break.
That's nice. Dad-in-law.
So cute.
Go. Don't get me riled up and leave.
Do you know how much of a shock I was in?
My heart is still pumping fast and the back of my neck hurts. Aigoo...
Aigoo...
You're holding onto your stomach when your heart is pumping and the back of your neck hurts.
If you're this full, of course, you're in pain.
Geez, I was worried you were skimping on your meals without me. I worried for nothing.
This is from aging, man.
You're way too old then.
- You're full of energy.
- Ouch!
I was actually relieved when I saw my father calling the police first.
I guess I was suspicious of my father subconsciously.
The father I know wouldn't do such a thing.
Is something wrong?
Chang, I think Miryeong Village has been contaminated.
So, how about President Choi also gets his complete medical examination?
Contaminated? No other villages are cleaner than our village.
And my father is so healthy.
He still lifts lumber without any problems.
But still. You never know.
I was locked up in the hospital because of that psycho.
Did she leave?
Why? You miss her already?
Why would I miss that psycho?
Father, why don't we get a complete physical since we're here?
Do you think that's free? Why bother with a physical?
I'll pay for it.
- Man, don't you know that your money is my money? Forget it.
- Geez...
Fine. I'll come back home.
So, let's get a physical.
I said I don't need it.
- Stop spewing nonsense.
- Come on...
I know you're happy. Then, we'll get a complete physical, okay?
I'm hot. Get away from me.
I don't want to. Don't want to.
I'm hot. It's hot!
- I don't want to. Don't want to.
- I'm hot!
Seong Il, did you look into what I asked about?
I looked it up, but I can't view Hwang Hyeon Bok's file.
You can't view it? Why not?
I don't know. I can't view it with my ID.
That can't be. It's not like she's a politician or a celebrity.
I know. There's no reason why I can't view an ordinary citizen's file.
All right. Thanks.
Dr. Jeong, do you have the list of residents who took the heavy metal poisoning test?
Yes, it's at home. I took it home to organize the file.
I'll give it to you tomorrow.
Miryeong Village seems very unsettled.
Of course.
Heavy metal poisoning, contaminations. I'm sure they've never even imagined it.
Not about that. I heard a resort development will take place here.
The village land and Naseong Development's land...
I heard they were all sold.
Didn't your boyfriend tell you?
About what...
He did work in that industry before, but he got out of it now.
He's a member of the special rescue team. You know that.
Really? I heard that a young man from Seoul went around purchasing the land, so I thought...
But you know, why did he quit such a great job...
and why? Why did he become a rescuer?
Isn't that weird? It's weird.
It's weird.
For me to give you a permit to use provincial forest land at this point in time,
it only shows them what we discussed that day.
We'll have to watch ourselves for now.
I even had someone follow the governor that day. When did they photograph him?
A drone. They were watching us through a drone.
What? A drone?
For them to be so blunt about it means they know we wouldn't be able to do anything about the contamination.
Wouldn't we have to cover up the contamination issue if we want to dig up rare earth elements?
For symptoms like these to appear, I'm sure it didn't happen in a short amount of time.
You can say it was accumulated over a long period of time.
I'm sure a large amount of mineral waste is buried somewhere.
Mining 25 years ago and a large amount of mineral waste, huh?
If we find critical evidence, we can be the ones in control.
Someone in the Miryeong Village must know that fact.
The call is not going through. After the beep...
Why do I feel so uneasy as if I got swindled?
He'd better not stab me in the back.
On the Miryeong Mountain, 1994
It's strange.
I'm sure I left it here.
San Hyeok.
He's not off work yet?
Plans to Mine Miryeong Forest Rare Earth Elements?
Rare Earth Elements and Environment Pollution
Blood Cell Heavy Metal Test
Arsenic level
Why would he look at this...
You've been selected as a beneficiary for the medical welfare program that our company sponsors.
Why did he quit such a great job...
why did he become a rescuer?
It's weird.
I'll take these.
Just a moment, please.
You're home.
- You're late.
- Yeah.
I prepared a bribe.
Ta-da. Aren't they pretty?
I had a hard time picking them out because I wanted to buy you the prettiest pair.
Try them on.
They're so pretty.
How do they look? Do they look nice?
Yeah. They're beautiful on you.
Put these on and let's go back to Seoul.
Let's go back. I'll look into a hospital position for you.
Let's go back to Seoul and...
Should I?
To look wealthy and elite. Should I live like that?
Just like these high heels.
Just like Kang San Hyeok?
Did something bad happen?
I thought that you had the same mindset as me.
But you're faithful to the desires that your eyes can see.
Ms. Hwang Hyeong Bok. Did you hide her?
Why? To deceive the sick lady and get involved in the rare earth element business?
I'm not deceiving her. I'm treating her at a place with the topnotch medical professionals in that field.
Right. You're hiding the fact that the residents are sick from arsenic poisoning.
If that is found out, it will be an obstacle to the rare earth element business. Isn't that right?
Let's think rationally, Yeong Jae.
Just because you reveal the cause of their sickness, their ailments don't go away.
Even if it weren't for me, Miryeong forest's rare earth element will be dug up.
If I develop it, I'll use the method that is least invasive to the environment...
So, you're saying you're different than people who contaminated the land of Miryeong?
Different from extremely evil people, you're just slightly evil?
Is that what you want to say now?
After crumbling many walls and beyond them, I thought I saw
the real Kang San Hyeok who is so friendly and warm.
But when it comes to your work, you're still the coldhearted man who sees nothing else besides your goal.
Yeong Jae...
Could you fix your eyes on me?
I'll ask you one thing.
The rare earth element business you're about to launch...
could you give it up if I opposed it?
I have never lived any other way. I don't even know how.
If you trust me and wait a little longer...
Don't play with words. Don't try to get out of this at the moment. Give me a straight answer.
If I oppose it, could you give up on this business?
That's right. How could I rescue someone else?
I can't even rescue myself.
But at least, I don't want to become someone who causes others to die because of my desires.
I want to become someone who can ask myself, "Why do you need that much money?"
And now, I don't want to stay with someone whose direction in life is different from mine.
What do you mean by that?
Should I move out or will you?
♬ Without feeling anything,  ♬
♬ it seems hard to smile ♬
♬ Although that's what everyone says  ♬
♬ Every moment is too much so I turn my head away ♬
♬ As one grows older ♬
♬ The dream gradually grew smaller ♬
♬ Oh, how are you doing? ♬
♬ Yes, don't get tired. ♬
♬ In the many nights which were brilliant ♬
♬ I'm sure there was a star shining on me ♬
♬ I open a dusty book ♬
I'll never deceive you again.
Give me a chance.
This world has never been friendly to me.
But when you smile, the world smiles at me.
♬ In the many nights which were brilliant ♬
Yeong Jae, I like you.
I found out this time around.
How precious you are to me.
I really like you.
♬ I open a dusty book ♬
♬ In there is the dream I am looking for. ♬
♬ Send to the dark sky ♬
You'll only focus on your goal.
I'm afraid of that obvious outcome.
I have confidence to fight thanks to you.
It's proof that I'm not cursed.
♬ I'm sure there was a star shining on me ♬
You have me.
When you smile, the world smiles.
I, Jeong Yeong Jae, is always by your side.
♬ In there is the dream I am looking for. ♬
Even including romance... oh, yeah...
It's a movie with all types of genres combined.
I like it.
I warned Kang San Hyeok with photos. Should I carry it out into action?
Please wait. We have to figure out the forest permit issue anyway.
Let Kang San Hyeok be our hunting dog and bring it to us. Just watch him for now.
After our hunt is over, we'll eat the dog.
We'll boil him and eat all the meat
and the bone marrow.
How do you feel, Grandma?
For having me in such a nice hospital...
I'm just so grateful and I'm comfortable here.
Until your treatment is over, you can rest at ease.
Our company will pay for all the costs. Do you understand?
I'll be back.
Grandma, by chance, these people...
Director, where are you right now?
I looked into it and the guide that Kwon Joo Han hired when coming out to Miryeong to hunt
was Choi Jeong Mok of Miryeong Forestry.
He'd blow a whistle of some kind and gather around the animals.
If you look at the files, right after the fire at Miryeong Mountain from 25 years ago...
Miryeong Forestry has been supplying lumber to Taesung Construction.
And the arsonists for that recent fire were workers from Miryeong Forestry as well.
I think there's a deep connection among the forest fire, Choi Jeong Mok, and Taesung.
The call is not going through. After the beep...
How much did you receive?
How much did Taesung pay you for you to do such a thing?
What are you talking about coming here out of the blue?
Starting the forest fire.
Did you think you wouldn't get caught?
Did you get your memory back?
Did you think I'd never remember?
A**hole! It wasn't me. It was you!
You started the fire! How dare you try to put it on me?
Stop it!
I said I remember everything!
Shut up, you a**hole!
Let go of me!
Did you start the forest fire, punk?
No, it wasn't me.
- There's a proof.
- I said I didn't!
How dare you. Let's go to the police.
I said, no!
Where are you going?
I won't let you win, rock-paper-scissors!
Got you!
- How can you let it go?
- It's okay. But still...
San Hyeok. I'll be right back. Make sure you stay here and wait for me.
You can't go anywhere, okay?
Tickets
Oppa.
What are you doing?
We're playing hide and seek.
Count to ten starting now.
One, two...
three, four...
five, six...
seven, eight...
nine, ten.
- Stop!
- Mom said she'd come back on my birthday.
She's not coming. She abandoned us.
She won't come.
Kang San Yoo, your only family is Grandma and me.
Oppa... I hate you.
Hey!
You kid. Hey, what are you doing hiding here?
Man, you started a forest fire. A forest fire!
It wasn't me.
What do you mean it wasn't you? Hey, look here.
Look at this here. Here's the proof.
I said I didn't!
Hey, this can't be. Let's go to the police.
You started the forest fire! You're in deep trouble...
Hey! Stop right there!
Hey! Stop!
It was you...
The one who started the forest fire...
It was you.
San Yoo!
Kang San Yoo!
Oppa!
San Yoo!
Kang San Yoo, stay there. I'm coming.
If you photograph like that, you won't get a good picture.
Give it to me.
Over there. Like this. Zoom in.
Like that over there. It's firing up.
That's right. Right, right.
Okay.
- You have to capture stuff like this.
- Help us!
A village that's about to disappear and tragic children.
Doesn't it sound more meaningful?
- Help us!
- Save us!
Save us! Save us!
- What should we do?
- Let's go home.
Help us! Help us!
Help us!
- Help us!
- Save us!
Help us!
- Help us...
- Oppa, I'm scared...
It's okay. I'm here.
Hold my hand tightly.
Oppa!
- San Yoo!
- Oppa!
Oppa...
San Yoo, San Yoo, San Yoo!
San Yoo! San Yoo!
Oppa...
San Yoo, San Yoo...
It's dangerous! Dangerous!
No, San Yoo...
- San Yoo...
- It's dangerous.
- San Yoo.
- Oppa...
- I'll save you.
You guys killed her.
You guys killed San Yoo!
My sister!
♬ You filled up a small empty spot ♬
♬ Where are you? ♬
Forest
Keep your eyes wide open and watch.
How Choi Chang is thrown into the fires of hell.
I truly wanted to hold your hand.
CEO Kang San Hyeok, you're family now.
Conduct epidemiology investigation in Miryeong Village?
I'm sure they tried to cover up the poisoning as another symptom.
You can curse me. I just wish you were in front of my eyes.
I have to get rid of the cub.
I'm sorry.
Let's make it a great night.
San Hyeok!
♬ Come to me ♬