Episode 21
Don't go far from me.
Stay with me.
You are, you are someone who only focuses on your own goals.
The obvious result is ... I'm afraid.
Be my goal next to me.
I need you.
Are you up?
Are you put makeup on?
No.
I think you did.
Come. Let's have breakfast together.
You made all this from stuff form the mountain? You did it this morning?
They are all common on the mountain in back.
The wrap is made with gondaeseori. (taro leaves, the doewnjang (fermented bean paste soup) has day lilies in it, some leafy vegetables.
Try it. It was easy and it's good.
Yum. The scent!
That's why we eat wild greens. Because they have a fragrance that can only be held in the deep forest.
But don't you usually just have a simple cup of coffee for breakfast?
I always like stuff like this better.
I haven't made it because I didn't have anyone to eat it with.
There is now.
I want to buy this robot. On an installment plan? 360 months.
As if ...
It's a 3,600 months plan.
Does that make 300 years?
♬ Oh at the sound of a whistle ♬
♬ I hum without realizing it ♬
♬ Drunk on a cup of coffee ♬
♬ I also don't realize ♬
♬ I'm sitting and thinking of you
♬ I try saying anything. ♬
♬ Rather than what you want ♬
♬ Listen to the answer I've prepared ♬
♬ By the time the sun sets ♬
♬ We will sit and face each other blankly (I'm in love, I'm in love) ♬
♬ We can fall in love ♬
♬ (Yeah. We can fall in love.) ♬
♬ Even doing nothing at all I feel good ♬
♬ Anytime with you ♬
♬ (Whoa) That is what you will say. ♬
♬ That is what you will say. ♬
♬ Only you in my heart ♬
♬ Only you always in my heart ♬
What shall I do?
- That's okay.
- You don't need to do that.
- Ill do that.
- It's alright.
I can wipe it though. I'll do it.
It's okay, I'm done.
When did they get so close?
- Take a walk every day. It's a must!
- I will.
All right.
- Bye.
Here. Look at this.
What's this?
You like to study.
These are the medical records I didn't organize. Just a few.
- Ten years' worth.
- Ten years?
You want me to organize them now?
Even if I want to help, what kind of help can a has-been like me give?
You are a rising star who was already invited to an international scientific society meeting, aren't you?
But, why are you suddenly doing this?
Don't you know they are already in the electronic system?
No. Miryeong Hospital and Gangwon Myeongseong Hospital are not compatible with the electronic system.
File attachments like x-rays have to be manually entered.
While I was busy treating patients, I fell a little behind.
Gangwon Medical Center wants them to be submitted.
Do it, wherever.
That's what I said. Every time I told you to submit them.
I think a person should take care of his own business.
Did you hear that? Then you do it!
Was that meant to be funny?
Somehow I don't have a way to get you to say "Yes".
I ask you do something but you refuse.
How can you refuse the request of your far higher superior?
That's not so. That's exactly what you said.
I am busy with other things, so Dr. Jeong, newbie at Miryeong Hospital, take care of it.
My decision on how you should think of me will depend on how you take care of it.
Really.
Actually, it's not that I asked to be sent to the academic society meeting.
Is dragging me down connected to the ten years of records?
Yes, Professor.
Did everything work out for the urgent patient you had yesterday?
Yes. I'm sorry it was so sudden.
Not at all. I'm fine.
Then, anyway, could you come to Seoul?
Excuse me, Professor. Could I ask what this is about?
I don't know the details
but the Director of the Hospital wants to see you.
I think it's an important task, so this time make sure you keep your promise and come.
Understand?
Yes. I will. Yes.
Important task?
What about the "love letter"?
All done. I am about to send it.
Shareholder Resolution
Are the "fireworks" ready?
Yes. They will explode as soon as they are dispatched.
Do a good job.
Our Director Kwon who has never been surprised in his life
is letting my heart experience some fun.
When you sign the MOU  (Memorandum of Understanding) Taesung guarantees to provide
the basic infrastructure for the IT industry and an international city.
We will provide all integral parts.
Activist's Future Fund, Crown Prince Jeong Jo Jun
Acquires 29% Interest in Taesung High Tech Future Fund
In expectation of a management rights dispute. Taesung stock increases 7.44%
I left the High Tech task entirely up to you as the managing director
so what is happening?
A stockholder resolution? This is the first I have experienced.
Haesung Precision's Chairman Hwang secretly set up a fund and has been acquiring shares.
It happened out of nowhere so suddenly I couldn't respond.
I'm sorry.
They are demanding the selection of directors recommended by the Future Fund to improve management transparency.
They are demanding that I give up management rights.
I leaked information to the press as soon as the shareholder resolution was issued.
It's obvious they are seeking a profit due to the stock purchases to defend management rights.
I am asking you the reason, not the purpose.
Why are they coming after High Tech, out of all companies, now, out of all times?
That ... that is ...
"We demand the disclosure of the reason for the Miryeong Forest Resort,
its progress and all expenses."
This is not an attack by Chairman Hwang.
Find out who designed and proposed the fund.
I'm thirsty after we trained to exhaustion today.
Shall we all have beer?
I'm leaving work.
Is this what you would call the "out the door at 6"?
[Leaving the office right on time]
San Hyeok is acting strange today. Seriously strange.
Did you see him smile earlier today? I almost mistook him for Choi Chang.
It's giving me the goosebumps. Geez.
What are you doing here?
I'm waiting.
How do I look?
You're pretty.
100 Questions and Answers for Couples
100 Questions and Answers?
I told you I'd make an effort. But I've got to start somewhere to do that.
A very good attitude.
You must fill in yours too. Got it?
Let me see.
"What would you do if a good-looking man/woman asked for your number, saying you were their type?"
Will this question also help you 'make an effort'?
Of course it will. It's part of my effort to fully understand what kind of person Jeong Yeong Jae is.
Give an answer, hurry.
I'd treat them the same way Kang San Hyeok would treat another woman.
"What do I fear the most?"
Swimming, going underwater.
I've got another one, lightning and thunder. Gosh, they scare me so much.
You're not a child, seriously.
"The nickname you've saved my number under?"
Why, what is it?
- Why?
- Let me see.
It's nothing.
- Let me see
- No!
Hand it over— what did you save me as?
The mutt that...
The mutt that lives next door
The  mutt  that lives next door?
I was going to change that, I completely forgot to.
I did that when we weren't so fond of each other, that's why...
Then what about you, San Hyeok? What did you save me as?
- D-don't.. don't call it. Don't call it!
- Well, well.
Look at you. Look at your reaction.
- Hang up—
- How bad is it?
My Pretty ❤
What's "My Pretty ❤"?
Smurf? Pomp?
[Words all ending like 'pretty']
- Winnie the Pooh?
- Gosh!
Wi-fe!
Wife?
It's pouring!
- What shall I do?
- Hurry, go faster!
♬ like a tree that has grown, you're always there ♬
♬ Always ♬
- What's with the rain?
- Right? All of a sudden.
Looks like it's gonna rain quite a bit.
- I'm cold.
- You must be so cold.
♬ Only your warm breath ♬
♬ fills me up ♬
♬ Because I will love you ♬
Still, the rain makes it quite charming. Doesn't it?
♬ Like a day that will never come back to me ♬
♬ Because I will love you ♬
Gosh!
You're all wet.
What is this?
♬ Always ♬
♬ Yes, with your warm breath ♬
♫ you fill me. ♫
♬ Because I will love you ♬
♬ Like days that will never come back to me ♬
♬ I love you ♬
♬ As always at that spot ♬
♬ On that radiant day ♬
♬ Hold me in your arms ♬
♬ Because I will love you ♬
♬ I love you ♬
♬ As always at that spot ♬
♬ Always ♬
[Rehabilitation of the Beast, for the Success of Abstinence]
[Devil's Hell entered the chat.]
Today's quite a difficult day.
Try to write the 'patience' characters three times on the palm of your hand.
It'll do wonders.
I don't know how to write that character.
I suggest beans that are known to help suppress male hormones.
Fried beans, soy sauce beans, bean soup
Beans?
To make 10 go down to 9, I'll need to consume at least 5 sacks of beans.
I'd rather look at pictures of my ex-girlfriend.
Great!
- Thumbs up!
- Yes!
Such strange things on the internet.
Devil's Hell, are you also having a hard time?
I'm not having hard time...
I'm no beast.
But she is so pretty.
Such strange things on the internet.
Let's hold back.
[Writing the 'patience' characters]
What am I doing?
Ah.
[Signal for shooting]
The press is talking and we must hold the shareholders' meeting.
The one who's behind all of this.
Who the hell is Kang San Hyeok?
He's the director of investment at RLI who intercepted our Miryeong Forest project.
I can't even move forward on my project due to a mere director from an investment firm.
And you're telling me I'm even having to endure this humiliation right now?
Director, what have you been doing till now?
I'm sorry.
I had no idea Kang San Hyeok would dare do such a thing...
Director. I must get my father's approval to acquire the funds to secure the shares.
You're well aware what that means to me, Director.
My apologies, Managing Director.
I'll take care of it right away.
Director, you've always been on my side for the past 20 years,
and you're like my family.
I'll trust that you'll make sure I never hear the name Kang San Hyeok ever again.
As part of my family.
Ah.
How are things going with Director Kwon?
They've hurried to go and secure their shares.
However, I think they're lacking the funds as you anticipated.
Due to the anticipation that the values of the shares will go up, the shareholders aren't being forthright.
In any case, they're psychics.
How did you ever find out that the Crowned Prince was totally broke?
Can't you tell by how he plays in a corner store like High Tech to escape his father's nagging?
I'm sure he has to get any large amount of money from his father.
Like an elementary kid at his age.
What should we do with President Choi Jeong Mok?
We should purchase all the land from the townspeople while Kwon Joo Han is preoccupied.
But he's insisting that the real president meets with him.
Pull up all the info you've gathered on President Choi on the monitor.
Yes, sir.
Choi Jeong Mok, Male, 61 years old, Graduated from Miryeong Elementary School
That kid...
Was his last name Kim?
Or was it Kang?
You were out, sir.
What brings you here now?
Didn't you ask to meet me?
Ever since you joined the rescue team,
Naseong Development started to roam around this neighborhood wanting to purchase all the land.
People who want to build a resort in Miryeong.
CEO of Naseong. Park Hyeong Soo.
As expected of President Choi Jeong Mok.
The real owner of Naseong came to see you as you requested.
So, shall we get down and discuss our business?
If you intend to negotiate, I'm sure you wouldn't have asked to meet me.
Please tell me what you're asking for.
No, you should tell me your conditions.
Well, if I hand over an agreement from the townspeople that they stand together,
what will you give me?
For your information, our neighborhood is different than any other neighborhoods.
We almost all perished in a mountain fire. Yet, we all survived it together.
We always discuss everything together and we act on them together.
Well, you'll be wasting your time no matter how you poke them around.
I know that.
Also that you're the leader of the group.
That's why...
I brought this here.
What's this?
With your influence in the area, I'm sure you would've become a local politician already.
But you couldn't.
Why? Because the fact that you only graduated from the elementary school held you back.
Of course, there is no educational requirement, but it must've been tough to get the party nomination.
I'm sure you were looked down upon.
Money can't fix that. But I'll take care of that for you.
I will make you a district assemblyman.
After that, I'll support you to enter the national assembly.
This is fake for now. But you'll soon put on a real gold badge.
How could that be done? To the national assembly?
I'll bring you a recommendation letter from the governor right away.
I'm sure you know that Jo Kwang Pil would never do this for you.
To ensure your livestock works for you, you pull out their teeth.
You don't give them more teeth to bite you.
National Assembly
Choi Jeong Mok took the bait.
Of course. We just need a signature on rescue team relocation papers.
I need some time to work on that. So, we must stall with High Tech.
I'll make sure to tighten our grip on them during the shareholders' meeting. So, make sure to be prepared for that.
Yes, sir. I'm on my way to Naseong to prepare.
Did you find out what Managing Director Kwon and Director Jo are up to?
Any changes there?
Yes, not yet.
Naseong Development
Episode 22 will be starting shortly.