I might not be able to do what I want.
You envy that?
That's not what I meant.
- Kim Ha Na.
You came in first in the mock exam.
- Congratulations!
- Thank you!
You're pretty, kind, and even get good grades.
Your grandma must be proud of raising you.
I hope she really is.
I'm sure she is.
By the way, she needs to come for teacher-parent counseling.
Did you ask her when she has time?
But my grandma has been...
She has been having a hard time walking around.
I see.
Then I'll give her a call.
Okay, sir.
Okay. Take good care of your health.
- Thank you.
- You can go now.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Bye.
Joo Ha, come on in.
- Oh, Ha Na.
- Yes?
Can you put this up in the hallway on your way out?
Okay.
It's your test score, so you should be proud.
Joo Ha, let's see...
Hey. You didn't leave yet?
Were you waiting for me?
No, it's just...
I have something to ask you.
What is it?
Did you...
hear everything?
Hear what? Your counseling?
Or...
The guy from the convenience store saying he likes you?
What?
Class president? Class president!
- That's awesome.
- Thank you.
Gosh, it's impossible not to like you.
- What?
How do you know that?
Well, I somehow found out.
Please don't tell anyone else.
Oh.
Is it a secret that you're popular?
Don't worry. I won't tell anyone.
Okay. Please keep it a secret.
Okay.
Something only I know about.
Wait for me. We're in the same class.
I have to put this up first. I'll see you later.
Guys, someone is attaching the mock exam scores in the hallway.
Darn it. Who?
The class president of Class 3.
Gosh, her.
I heard she came in first place again.
Something only I want to know about.
What, again?
- Come on, let's go see.
- Let's go.
I told you that I'd come with you.
You're not tall enough.
I'm tall.
I didn't say you were short.
I said you're not tall enough to reach.
That corner too.
Did you do well on the exam?
Yes.
- Ha Na came in first place.
- Done.
- She comes in first every time.
- Thanks.
- I envy her.
- How can she always be first?
- First place.
- Exactly.
- What about you?
- I don't know.
- Why is Ha Min in 20th place?
What are you staring at? Your name is right there.
What?
It's nothing. Let's go.
- Anyway...
- What about you?
Where do you go after school?
- The library.
- Come and see this.
Hey, have you guys seen this?
Where is Ha Min's name? I can't even find it.
He was top in the liberal arts department.
I guess his scores dropped after changing majors.
I know.
You can just do better next time.
Right. Or you can go back to the liberal arts department.
I'm not going to go back.
Okay. See you later then.
Hey, I think your watch stopped.
I know. I'm going to fix it.
By the way,
why did you decide to be a veterinarian?
Why do you ask?
It's just, I envy you.
You envy me?
Yes.
I have nothing I want to do, so I have a lot on my mind lately.
You came in first place in the mock exam.
I might not be able to do what I want.
You envy that?
That's not what I meant.
I heard Ji Woo told you that he likes you.
What?
Why are you so startled?
Did Joo Ha tell you that?
You must be close to Joo Ha.
Not really.
I just have to take care of him as the class president.
How responsible of you.
I should've been the only one who knew about it.
- Here.
- Thanks.
Why are you sitting here?
- I...
- Should he sit separately then?
How could a vice president not care for a transfer student?
Someone else will take care of him.
We should take care of him.
We even played games at an internet cafe together.
Please, you only play RPG games.
What's wrong with RPG games?
He plays 'League of Legends' too.
He's a Diamond rank player.
Diamond?
What's that?
It means he's about a level 2 player.
He's a Silver rank player. That's about a level 7.
I'm good enough to be a Gold rank player.
Wow!
What was your rank again?
I'm a Diamond. My goal is to become a professional gamer.
Although my mom is opposed to it.
Still, it's admirable that you have a dream.
What about you?
What? What about me?
What is your dream?
Me?
I...
Grades matter the most for seniors.
What use is a dream?
It's fine since she has good grades.
No need to worry about her.
I see.
But...
I wasn't asking you.
Does it make sense that seniors need to attend P.E.?
Come on, don't say that.
Our bodies need to be healthy
in order to go to a good university.
You just want to play soccer.
Ha Min. That meant, "Hi, Min."
Get off me.
Do you have P.E.? Where is Kimha?
I don't know. She said she had something to say to Joo Ha.
I wonder what they'll do alone in an empty classroom.
Let's go.
What is it you want to say?
Did you tell him?
Tell him what?
About that guy telling me that he likes me.
No. Why?
Never mind.
What is it?
Did someone else find out besides me?
Yes.
Who found out?
Never mind. Okay, then.
I'm sorry for suspecting you.
Let's go.
Something only I know about.
It turns out, that wasn't the case.
What's wrong? It's like you're hiding something.
Were you having a secret chat or what?
What? Oh...
- Well...
- Yes.
With me.
I see.
With you?
I wish I were the only one...
who knew about it.
But...
I wasn't asking you.
♫  To not regret the choice of day  ♫
♫  Trust yourself at this moment  ♫
♫  I'll be next you  ♫
♫  At the end of one and only nineteen  ♫
♫  999teen  ♫
Our handsome student, Joo Ha. Are you adjusting well here?
Yes. Thanks to the class president.
Ha Na is a nice girl.
If there is anything you don't know or you have
anything that bothers you, ask Ha Na anytime.
Okay.
Anyway, since you took your first
mock exam at this school,
I need to talk to your parents. When will they be free?
Oh.
I don't think they'll be able to make it.