Are you crying?
- Are they fighting?
- It looks like it.
Are you suspecting me just because I did well on the exam?
You always copy what I do.
You always blame other people.
You're a liar who's toying with Joo Ha and Min!
Are you done?
- Min Ji.
- "Min Ji"?
- Is that all?
- Kim Min Ji?
- No way.
- I copy everything you do and flirt with the boys.
Are those it?
I'm right.
- Last year, you and Min...
- Hey!
- Who is she?
- What is she doing?
- Me?
- Yes, you.
You don't deserve to be shown respect.
What's wrong with her? Are you insane?
Was I ever not?
- Stop causing a fuss.
- Be quiet.
Hey.
When did she toy with them?
Who are you to interfere in our business?
Do you know me?
No, I don't. Just answer my question.
When did she toy with those guys?
That's what the rumors say.
I should've known when there were rumors about you on the school's anonymous page.
"Anonymous page"?
Oh, that page?
How about if I read you something interesting?
- What is it?
- What is she doing?
"Kim Ha Na, a senior in Class 3."
"She's already busy flirting with Ha Min and Ryu Joo Ha."
"Now, she's become even busier copying Kim Min Ji."
"Written anonymously."
"Sent by Kim Min Ji."
- She sent that?
- I had no idea.
- I know.
- What has she been doing?
"Kim Ha Na from Class 3."
"She's being nice to the transfer student just to flirt with him."
"Since when was she such a responsible person?"
"I hate that she's the class president."
"Written anonymously."
"Sent by Kim Min Ji."
No.
- No.
- It was her?
No. No, it wasn't me!
How can you prove that it was me?
Who are you?
Me?
I'm the administrator of the school's anonymous page.
- She was the administrator?
- This is shocking.
Has Min Ji been pretending to be nice all along?
"Kim Ha Na from Class 3."
"You'd better not act up and get on our nerves."
"What is she? An attention-seeker?"
"She's so annoying. By an anonymous student."
"Sent by"
"Kim Min Ji."
What is she going to do?
This is what happens when you try to cause trouble
without fully understanding the situation.
Guys.
It wasn't me.
It really wasn't.
I didn't write them.
I'm telling the truth.
What? Do you want me to read more?
Min Ji, calm down. Let's talk in private.
I don't need to talk to you in private.
Quit acting all nice!
This is all your fault.
You pretend like you don't know anything and act nice.
But in fact, you make sure you gain something!
Because of you...
people like me suffer.
Min Ji, stop.
- I can't believe she wrote them.
- I know.
- Ah Hyun.
- Wait.
I didn't do it for you.
It was for Min.
I see. Thanks.
But...
I hope you won't do that next time.
Do what?
Putting someone on the spot
even if they did something wrong
could really hurt them.
She was in the wrong first.
Aren't you mad?
Why wouldn't I be?
She spread false rumors about me.
But still...
she's probably the most upset right now.
Why? She has no right to be.
She probably knows best that she was wrong.
I've been through this before.
She's probably suffering the most right now.
Right.
I see.
I should go now.
Let's not talk over something like this again.
So?
Is Kim Ha Na okay?
She is.
Min Ji is the one who was completely destroyed.
You're right.
I saw Min Ji going to the teachers' room.
Ah Hyun was so amazing.
"I'm the administrator of the school's anonymous page."
Oh, right. Give this to your sister.
Why do you have this?
Bye.
Hey, why do you have this?
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- What's going on?
Come on.
- Explain this later.
- There's nothing to explain.
You have to.
Why did Gi Hyun give this to me?
- Should he not have?
- No.
Why not?
You're completely clueless.
There's no point in giving it to my brother.
I still don't get it. Why not?
You should've given it directly to me.
That way, we can become closer.
Our alliance is over, so there's no need for us to meet.
We don't need to become closer.
- What?
- That's why I gave it to Gi Hyun.
Hold on.
Why is our alliance over?
Because the girl I like and the guy you like
are dating someone else.
I'm going to be busy studying.
So don't call me.
Why are you doing this to me?
What do you mean?
I mean...
We've become quite close lately.
But now, you're saying that our alliance is over and that I shouldn't call you.
Does that make any sense? Are you putting a wall...
I am.
I like Kim Ha Na.
So of course, I should put up a wall between you and me.
Our alliance isn't over yet.
The guy I like
isn't dating anyone.
You have no idea.
Give this back to me later.
Hey, there's a couple I'm suspicious about.
Me too. No, wait.
It's a bit too early to call them a couple.
Have you caught on as well?
You're talking about those two, right?
He's always taking care of her.
And they're always going around together.
It seems like they have a secret between them.
I'm sure there's something going on.
What did you two whisper about?
It's a secret.
Give this to your sister.
Why do you have this?
Bye.
Even for a slow-witted girl like you, it's fishy, right?
It's so obvious...
You're more slow-witted than I am.
Hey, why are you coming home so late?
I don't want to listen to you.
Are you crying?
What? What's going on?
Why are you crying? She's crying.
Don't tease me.
"Don't tease me."
So why are you crying? Tell me.
Is she really crying? Hey, are you crying?
Yes, I am. Are you happy?
Are you?
"Yes, I am."
- Stop it!
- "I'm crying."
- My gosh!
- That hurts.
If you're slow-witted, at least behave well.
What? What is it?
I'll go and comfort her. You stay here.
What's going on?
Hey. Why did you cry yesterday?
I don't know.
Tell me. I'm going to ask until you tell me.
Tell me, tell me.
Because I was dumped! Are you happy now?
- You were dumped?
- Yes, I was.
That's why I cried. Do you want me to repeat it?
I cried because I was dumped!
- By whom?
- Who do you think?
By the tall and handsome, young and rich guy!
Who is that?
I don't know. If you don't know anything, just get lost!
You have no idea.
Even though I know now.
I know that "rich" means you have a lot of money.
Are you crying?
Ha Min!
Min, do you want to die?
- Hey!
- Hey.
- Let me go first.
- No!
- What's wrong with you?
- Talk it out.
- Let me go!
Gi Hyun.
♫  To not regret the choice of day  ♫
♫  Trust yourself at this moment  ♫
♫  I'll be next you  ♫
♫  At the end of one and only nineteen  ♫
♫  999teen  ♫