MAY IT PLEASE THE COURT
EPISODE 3
BASED ON THE ESSAY
MAY IT PLEASE THE COURT BY JUNG HYEJIN
Did you bring the car?
It's behind the restaurant.
Hey, stop!
That's for a customer.
You asked me to bring the car over
so early in the morning. Whose car is it?
Are you hungry?
Should I steam some more dumplings?
No thanks. I'm off.
No, wait. They'll be done in no time.
I noticed before
that Mr. Do really enjoys them too.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
Chisik, steam me a whole bunch.
-Why?
-We have a new attorney.
-Really?
-Yes.
Hey, that's great news.
Mr. Do was worried that people
avoided that office because of you.
What's the new attorney like?
She's a bit...
odd.
Odd?
She's really odd.
JUNGHA DISTRICT COURT PUBLIC DEFENDER
Good morning.
Hello.
Hand.
Mm-hmm?
These are silk, so tell them
to be extra careful with them.
This one is tweed.
Right, I need one iced decaf dolce latte.
With soy milk instead of dairy milk.
I told you not to put on that apron.
You're getting treated like a servant.
You need to get your own coffee.
And get your clothes washed
on your own time.
-Why?
-Why? What do you mean, why?
Why should I waste time getting coffee
or going to the cleaners? Time is money.
Isn't that why we have a secretary?
Where?
There is no secretary here.
Ms. Noh, you don't have
a private secretary here in this office.
If you want to save time,
do your laundry at home
and quit drinking coffee.
So you're saying Mr. Do isn't a secretary?
No.
Okay.
Mr. Do.
How much?
How much will it cost?
-Sorry?
-How much
will it cost for me to have you?
How much can you give me?
-Youngsoo.
-I need money. I really do.
How much...
How much can you give me?
I can give you 400,000...
a month.
Deal.
A decaf soy latte, right?
I'll make it quick.
Okay.
What the hell was that?
Do you think money can solve everything?
Oh, I think Mr. Do would find
that remark to be quite rude.
All I did was offer him extra pay
for the extra work he's doing for me.
There's no need to theorize about
how materialism has taken over
in this day and age.
Unbelievable.
Make some time for dinner on the 3rd.
We're having dinner
with CEO Park and his wife.
Why?
Mr. Park is a member
of the nomination committee.
You were serious about running
for the National Assembly?
What's next? Provincial governor?
And what's after that? President?
I'm not doing it.
I don't have any intention
of becoming an assemblyman's wife.
Can't you just play along?
Just play along? For whose benefit?
It took two years to get the central block
at the business district.
Just as my shopping mall
is about to go up,
you're telling me to play
Queen of Housewives?
Yes. Play Queen of Housewives.
Cut the crap.
If I were that kind of woman, you
would never have been able to marry me.
And if you hadn't married me,
your father would still be...
a broker for day laborers.
POLICE CHIEF JEON JAEHO
Yes, Jaeho.
Mr. Cho was murdered
at his vacation house.
Really?
CEO Cho was murdered?
Yes.
Come by the station this afternoon.
I'll be there.
Did he say CEO Cho died?
I think so.
Congrats.
You'll no longer have
to clean up after him.
Haran.
A man died.
Can't you respond
like a human being for once?
I can't pretend to care like you do.
The woman Mr. Cho called
to his vacation home
found him in the morning
and made the report.
Have you found any leads on the culprit?
We found nothing.
Seriously?
Nothing?
No.
The culprit was very careful.
It looks like Mr. Cho
opened the door for the culprit.
And they didn't even touch
the safe in the house,
so they're most likely an acquaintance.
Someone whose sole purpose
was to kill Mr. Cho.
As you can see in the photos,
he wasn't simply killed.
He was tortured,
and then he was put in that position.
Why did they do that?
And why that position?
They probably wanted an apology...
for a sin Uncle Hyunsik committed.
What sin?
I'm not sure.
What kind of sin did Uncle Hyunsik commit
against the culprit who killed him?
You know what Mr. Cho was like.
He committed more sins in his life
than you could count on both hands.
I guess so.
Will you be all right?
The election is around the corner.
Once Mr. Cho's stories get out...
You should worry about yourself first.
All right.
Don't worry about the investigation.
Right.
We have Mr. Cho's call history.
The last person he talked to
was one of your attorneys at Jangsan.
The call went on for about ten seconds
while he was being tortured.
OUTGOING CALL, ATTORNEY NOH CHAKHEE
Ms. Noh. The defendant is...
Your client is here for a meeting. Yes.
"Client"?
Is that so?
Yes. This way. Come on in.
Oh...
Mr. Lee Guidong.
You were in the isolation wing
for a long time.
Yes.
Right.
In the isolation wing,
you and Mr. Kang Myungsub,
a schizophrenic patient
who was hospitalized for ten years...
What's this? Chips?
You began to fight over chips.
Then Mr. Lee Guidong kicked
Mr. Kang Myungsub with his foot.
Because of that, Mr. Kang Myungsub
suffered from a stomach perforation
and passed away in the emergency room
from acute sepsis.
Is this correct?
I'm not quite familiar
with the name of the disease.
All I know is that he died
because of Guidong.
Ah...
Mr. Lee Guidong.
Guidong.
Mr. Lee, let's stop eating that.
That's mine!
-That's mine! No!
-No!
-My goodness.
-Good Lord.
There, there.
It's yours. There, it's yours.
It's mine.
-Oh, no. I'm... My goodness.
-I'm fine. I'm okay.
Goodness. I'm so sorry.
Mr. Lee Guidong.
Gosh, it got all over you.
Is this why you hit Mr. Kang Myungsub?
Because he touched your chips?
They were mine, but that idiot stole them.
So you got angry.
Yes.
Mr. Lee.
Do you know that Mr. Kang Myungsub died?
Mr. Kang is dead.
Did you know that?
Am I bad?
Am I...
-No!
-I have to get beaten!
-I have to get beaten if I am bad!
-My goodness! Stop it.
That's enough.
-I'm a bad person! I have to get beaten!
-That's enough. There, there.
That's enough.
There.
My Guidong is a good boy. There, there.
Yes, that's enough.
There, there.
Oh, man. What a day.
Ma'am, I looked over his case.
Mr. Lee has an IQ of 67.
Right?
He can't conduct himself properly
in social settings.
Yes, you're right.
Back when he was in college,
he made deliveries on his motorcycle
in the early mornings
to make some money
for our living expenses.
He became like this
after he got into a hit-and-run accident.
Before that, he never failed
to get a scholarship...
Yes, anyhow, that's his condition now.
The judge will take
his condition into consideration.
But despite his condition, a man has died.
Right.
First off, what's most important
in cases like these
is how well you settled the case
with the bereaved family.
Have you met with the victim's family?
Well, the thing is...
He didn't have any family.
Both of Mr. Kang Myungsub's parents
have passed away,
and his son has no confirmed address.
So he was cremated without a funeral.
Yes, which is why I feel
even sorrier for him...
Don't. Mr. Lee should be thankful
that the victim doesn't have any family.
There is nobody who wants him punished.
What?
However, although the deceased
doesn't have any bereaved family,
there is someone else
that still wants to punish him.
Who...
The state wants to punish Mr. Lee
even though he doesn't have the capacity
to understand what he has done.
According to precedents, the accused
were mostly given prison sentences.
But that'll change if I defend him.
Sorry?
I won't let Mr. Lee Guidong go to prison.
My goodness. But how?
Now, how are we going to send Mr. Lee
to a psychiatric institution
instead of a prison?
We must show the judge.
Words aren't going to cut it.
I'm not sure what you mean by that...
I'm talking about
how slow Mr. Lee Guidong is,
how he's completely unaware
of what he has done,
how he's unable to make sound judgment
regardless of the time and place.
I mean, that's why he hit his attorney
on her head to take back his ice cream.
I'm sorry.
No, that's why it's a relief.
-What?
-Look, Your Honor.
As you can see, Mr. Lee Guidong
only follows his instinctive desires.
Mr. Lee didn't intend to kill Mr. Kang.
He had merely acted on instinct.
We'll put on a show to amuse the judge.
Goodness. I'm not so sure...
You don't need to know the specifics.
Just remember this.
"My son has a great public defender
so he won't have to go to prison."
Just be thankful.
I'll just put
my full trust in you, Ms. Noh.
Okay.
The page won't turn.
Don't be so sure of anything.
You'll only end up hurting
the elderly lady.
A psychiatric institution?
He won't make it there.
You're right if you consider
the precedent cases.
But we're talking about me.
I'm Mr. Lee's attorney.
Good grief.
You're like a little baby.
Completely oblivious.
The state is much harsher
than you think it is.
That's especially true for the consultees
who end up coming here.
The rich consultees of Jangsan...
Those rich clients live
in a completely different country.
In Jangsan, sure.
"However, the defendant shows remorse..."
"However, they settled
with the bereaved family..."
"However, the defendant
was too drunk to remember..."
These arguments can get them released.
But it's impossible here.
You don't know anything.
Is that the excuse public defenders use
for having a 3% win rate?
-What?
-You shouldn't denounce the state
that's paying you six million a month.
Wait.
You've been working for over two years,
so you get eight million, right?
That's how much a section chief
of a big corporation makes.
Nobody gets on you for your 3% win rate,
and you get paid eight million a month.
Look at how benevolent the state is.
Yes, sure. To me, it is.
However, to the consultees
who end up here,
the state is neither benevolent nor fair.
You don't know anything.
Mr. Jwa Sibaek.
Do you know why the world is fair?
Why?
Because it's unfair to everyone.
Sure, one person's dad
might be an assemblyman
while another's is an ex-con.
But that's just how the world works.
However, at times,
those consultees who would never
get another chance with a "however,"
get to meet
a great public defender like myself.
If you think about it that way,
it could mean the world is fair.
A fair world,
because it's unfair to everyone.
What kind of bull is that?
You just got that?
I've been talking bull
for about five minutes.
Now, go on your way. I'm busy.
I will.
Ah!
Thanks for this.
This makes it so much easier.
Name, Jwa Sibaek.
Occupation, lawyer.
It rained on that day, so it wasn't easy
to identify the license plate number
with the footage on Cho Hyunsik's dashcam,
but it was identified via the CCTV footage
of a nearby alley.
-Jwa Sibaek?
-Yes.
-A lawyer?
I've heard that name somewhere.
PUBLIC DEFENDER
JWA SIBAEK
I'm an attorney.
Ah!
PUBLIC DEFENDER
JWA SIBAEK
It was Noh Chakhee.
She was in Mr. Cho's car.
That's mine!
-That's mine!
-My goodness.
No, this is so wrong.
I can't spend a year like this. Come on.
REPORTER PARK BYUNGJAE, JOJOONG DAILY
Hello, Mr. Park. Have you been well?
This is Noh Chakhee from Jangsan.
Why don't we meet up?
I have a great news topic for you.
No, it's not something
I can discuss now.
Okay.
-Director Oh.
-Yes?
Y CONSTRUCTION SUSPECTED OF BRIBING
OFFICIALS TO WIN BID FOR BUSINESS DISTRICT
-Who wrote this?
-Park Byungjae from Jojoong Daily.
Park Byungjae?
So you can run one photo
of the public defender's office's front
that sits by an apartment complex.
And the office here.
Include a photo of me
talking to a client by my desk
and a solo shot of me doing
the interview in my office.
I think that's about it.
The headline can read,
"Large Law Firm's Ace Attorney
Worth 45,000 Every Six Minutes,
Turns Public Defender for a Small City."
Something like that.
It'll probably draw more readers
if you throw in numbers into the headline,
so please do that.
Everything sounds good. This sounds great.
But why should I write this article?
I should have brought that up first.
I got ahead of myself.
So...
How much?
Are you trying to bribe me
to write this article?
Yes.
I need to get going.
I'm sorry.
That was too blunt of me,
wasn't it? Please sit.
Jeez.
What can I do to get
you interested in my story, Mr. Park?
Well, two years ago,
when you were sued for damages
after spreading false information,
the evidence on your phone
was omitted by gross negligence.
Would that be enough for you
to take an interest in my story?
Are you threatening me?
Well, my feelings are hurt.
Mr. Park, have you forgotten already?
I worked so hard
to save you from that lawsuit.
Oh, come on.
Fine.
Then, as a token of my gratitude,
I'll just work on the article itself.
I don't want to take money for your story,
only to get another threatening offer
like this two years from now.
Okay. It's not like I'm asking you
to turn a drug dealer into an angel
or write some other fake news like that.
Bring me an actual story.
The article you just suggested
only shows the circumstances.
What has the ace of Jangsan done
in the midst of the common folk?
If you show me something you've done,
I'll look at that and write an article.
Right now,
I'm working on a case involving
a man with an IQ of 67
who killed another man in an altercation.
If you look at the precedent,
it's obvious he'll be imprisoned.
However, I'm going to have him sent
to a psychiatric institution instead.
Again, let's discuss this
when the results are out.
This is Park Byungjae
of Jojoong Daily.
This is Director Oh Haran
of Yulhu Construction.
Director Oh.
Goodness. Yes.
-Mr. Park? Mr. Park, one second...
-Yes. Right.
-It's fine.
-I'm not done yet.
Wait, Mr. Park.
Yes, okay. I understand.
That was Reporter Park.
Noh Chakhee asked him
to write a story about her.
Did she?
She wanted to do
an interview ahead of time
because she'll become a star
among public defenders.
It's obvious that she doesn't want
to be stuck there for a year.
If she'll return
to the ESG department anyway,
she can make up some story
and return as a pro bono icon.
How amusing. She doesn't know her place.
And...
Haran called Reporter Park...
Haran, it's been a while.
Was it you? Did you put him up to this?
Would you leave the room?
I have to talk to my husband.
Sure.
Excuse me.
Y CONSTRUCTION SUSPECTED OF BRIBING
OFFICIALS TO WIN BID FOR BUSINESS DISTRICT
-Sit.
-Did you think I wouldn't know?
Of course, I knew you would.
I told Mr. Park to write it
for you to notice.
I can always stop articles like these.
You can't force my hand like that.
I know.
It won't be enough.
That's why I prepared the next story.
"Yulhu Construction is under suspicion
of lobbying MH during the bidding process
of the central block
in a large business district."
That's the story you've read so far.
The prosecution is in the process
of investigating to confirm
if there was any type of lobby in
from Yulhu Construction.
How's that?
That's the next article.
Are you threatening me by saying
that the prosecution
will come after Yulhu Construction?
Now, the next article.
"Following the investigation,
the Central District Prosecutors' Office
has arrested a certain Director Oh
of Yulhu Construction for embezzlement
and professional negligence."
Should I go on?
The next article is
about Director Oh, who went to prison
-after getting sentenced to three years.
-What are you trying to do?
You already know what I want to do.
You can't send me to prison.
Haran.
I could've sent you to prison whenever
I wanted for at least a decade now.
I was the one who cleaned up
after the corruption
Yulhu Construction was involved in.
I did that because you wanted me to.
Did you forget?
You can't become an assemblyman
if I go to prison.
No, not right now.
But do you think that'll be the case
in five years? What about in ten years?
However, if you go to prison now,
you'll never take over Yulhu Construction.
There are people swarming around you,
waiting for you to fall flat on your face.
Dinner is on the 3rd.
Don't forget.
BACKWOODS HOMEMADE DUMPLINGS
Hey, Mr. Kang, have you been well?
It's me, Noh Chakhee of Jangsan.
Yes.
-I'll take half kimchi and half meat.
-Sure.
So you heard the news.
Right, yes. I'm working
as a public defender right now.
I mean, that's why I called.
How did this ace at Jangsan
become the savior of the average Joes
in the blind spot of the legal system?
This great journey...
You must be busy.
Okay, then. Give me a call
when you're free. I'll be waiting.
Yes, okay.
Man. Kang, this jerk.
I guess he forgot who saved him
from the defamation suit.
So Noh Chakhee is no longer
a Jangsan attorney. Is that it?
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
What was your order again?
Half kimchi, half meat.
-That's right. I'm sorry.
-That's okay.
An incoming order.
The order was...
What did she say?
What would you like?
Half kimchi, half meat.
How many times do I have to order?
Yes, all right.
-I'll get those ready for you quickly.
-Okay.
Man. This is driving me insane.
The king-sized dumplings are on the house.
You should try some.
Sorry about earlier.
You don't need to...
Thank you.
Hey. This...
Why? Is there a problem with the dumpling?
No.
It tastes just like the dumplings
made by someone I used to know.
Is that so?
My gosh. It's just like
how Grandma used to make them.
Please enjoy.
I will.
I can't believe it.
JUNGHA DISTRICT COURT
It was over
a simple bag of chips.
We probably wouldn't have had
to face this unfortunate incident.
The defendant, who has
the intelligence of a six-year-old,
and the victim,
who tried to take the defendant's chips,
may both just be victims
of their unfortunate, ill-fated destiny.
Honorable Judge.
So please, have mercy on him.
Okay, good.
-Hello, ma'am.
-Yes. Hello.
Hi, Mr. Lee.
Ma'am.
Can you put this on him?
Sorry?
Goodness, no.
I can't take something like this.
He needs to put this on
for me to create his story.
What?
Put this on him.
-Mr. Lee, you have to do well today.
-Uh-huh.
Let's see. Your hair.
Okay.
Mr. Lee, this is your favorite
bag of chips, right?
It looks good.
Mr. Lee, don't let anybody take this.
If someone tries to take it from you,
get angry at them like a tiger. Okay?
Okay. I won't let anyone take it.
This is mine.
Ma'am, don't worry.
You wouldn't know this,
but if I had taken on
Mr. Lee's case at Jangsan,
I'd be getting paid
hundreds of millions of won.
But I'm doing this for free right now.
My gosh. Thank you, Ms. Noh.
Goodness.
How can I repay your kindness?
Well, if you want to repay my kindness...
When a reporter comes by
to interview you later,
tell them about the abundant gratitude
you felt today, just as you felt it.
Okay.
Therefore, the defendant, Lee Guidong,
is charged with the suspicion
of causing death by bodily injury
under Article 259 of the Criminal Code.
PROSECUTOR
DEFENSE ATTORNEY, DEFENDANT
Your Honor.
Mr. Lee has an organic brain disorder
caused by a head injury,
and he currently has
the intelligence of a six-year-old.
What would happen if you took
a bag of chips away from a child?
The child may cry, throw a fit,
or even shake around
their cute little hands.
Well, the defendant's hands
aren't cute and little.
They're as big as pot lids.
But does that mean the child is trying
to kill the person who took the chips?
Mr. Lee's frontal lobe
was damaged in an accident.
So when the bag of chips
was taken from him,
he probably had no choice
but to react instinctively.
Just like this.
Get angry. Roar.
Mr. Lee, you have to go, "It's mine."
It's okay. You can have it, Ms. Noh.
I like you, Ms. Noh.
You bought me clothes and combed my hair.
No, not that.
You have to yell and hit me.
Right here. You have to push me around.
I don't want to hit you, Ms. Noh.
No, Guidong.
Your Honor. The bag of chips
isn't important at all.
What's important is that
the victim, Mr. Kang Myungsub,
does not have any bereaved family
Mr. Lee can apologize to
and settle the case with.
Gosh, Ms. Noh. Thank you so much
for your hard work today.
Yes, sure.
Ma'am, I turned in the notes
from Mr. Lee's doctor
and the victim's personal information.
I'm sure the judge
will look over everything.
I mean, even if we wanted to settle,
there aren't any bereaved families.
Thank you, Ms. Noh.
You have my full trust.
We'll get going.
-Goodbye.
-Say goodbye.
I like Ms. Noh. I love these chips.
Yes, that's right.
-Yes, goodbye.
-Goodbye.
Why would you like me?
Man, that chip performance
definitely would have worked.
Damn it, Guidong. Why did you come
to your senses at that moment?
God, this is seriously driving me insane.
What are you doing?
What's it to you what I do?
Mr. Jwa Sibaek.
Do you still hold the opinion
that Mr. Lee Guidong
will end up being imprisoned?
-Yes.
-Man, darn it.
Wait, no.
If he was going
to be imprisoned from the start,
then my defense
wouldn't really matter, right?
That's right.
It doesn't matter if I did well or not.
The state is already harsh,
so they were already going
to lock up Mr. Lee. That's right.
Right?
Wasn't the state benevolent?
What are you saying?
The state is much harsher
than you think, Mr. Jwa,
especially for those
who come to our office.
The laws are different
for the poor and the rich.
Since when has it been like that?
I wonder. If you're that curious,
go look online to see
when the law started treating
the rich and the poor differently.
Be on your way now.
-Go.
-Okay.
I paid for that shirt for nothing.
It was all for nothing.
Hello?
Is that you, Chakhee?
-Mr. Jang.
-So?
How's life as a public defender?
I'm doing my best.
I see.
You recently met with CEO Cho, right?
Mr. Jang,
I'm not sure what you heard from Mr. Cho,
but it's all a misunderstanding.
-I can explain everything in per...
-Uncle Hyunsik...
is dead.
What?
He was killed at his vacation house
two days after he met with you.
The man you were with on that day.
Who is he?
Mr. Jwa, CEO Cho was mur...
I just heard.
We need to talk.
Mr. Jwa.
You're in a lawsuit against Kangsung,
and that incident happened with Mr. Cho,
so things might get troublesome for you.
That day, it was all because of me...
Cho Hyunsik.
Did I...
kill him?
There will be no trouble,
so don't worry about it.
SEOUL SOUTHERN DISTRICT POLICE STATION
How do you know each other?
We work in the same office.
-That's all?
-Yes.
You're involved in a suit against Kangsung
that's worth billions of won?
-Yes.
-And the opposing attorney is Noh Chakhee.
Despite all that,
when Ms. Noh Chakhee got arrested
for suspicion of instigating
Ms. Lee Soonyoung's suicide,
Mr. Jwa, you were Ms. Noh's attorney.
Then she got fired from Jangsan
and became a public defender.
But of all places,
she started working in the same
law office as you.
I find you two suspicious.
On top of that, on the day Cho Hyunsik
met with Ms. Noh Chakhee
and was in the same car with her,
you also happened to be on your way home.
Is that correct?
Yes.
As you are well aware, Mr. Jwa,
most murder cases have one of two motives.
Money or women.
However,
you and Cho Hyunsik have entanglements
that involve both money and a woman.
That's why
I thought very rationally
about this situation.
Sure.
You and Ms. Noh are in love.
Oh, my.
Ms. Noh gets fired from Jangsan,
and then she begins to work with you
in the same office.
That's when Cho Hyunsik
offers Ms. Noh the chance
to become his mistress.
That's why she was
in the car with Mr. Cho.
Then, Mr. Jwa, you found out about it.
You chased after Mr. Cho
and made him stop the car.
Enraged, you drag Mr. Cho out of his car.
You tried to attack him.
But Ms. Noh stopped you, so you couldn't.
And you were probably concerned
about nearby security cameras too.
I'm sure the chauffeur
was watching as well.
-Hmm.
-I mean, think about it.
Mr. Jwa, your anger...
Hmm?
...didn't die down that easily.
So I couldn't contain my anger
and murdered Cho Hyunsik.
Is that it?
Doesn't the story
work itself out perfectly?
Isn't it more like you have
to make the story come together
because that's what you assume?
I mean, everything
matches up too perfectly.
If you want to make me a suspect,
bring me the evidence.
Not some story.
You're good at writing stories.
SOUTHERN DISTRICT POLICE STATION
-Good morning.
-You're here.
Ooh!
Good. Very nice.
Ms. Noh. I printed out Mr. Lee Guidong's
sentence and left it on your desk.
Of course, he got institutionalized.
JUNGHA DISTRICT COURT
CRIMINAL DEPARTMENT 10
1 YEAR AND 6 MONTHS PRISON SENTENCE
Damn it, it's a flop.
I didn't think the state was like that,
but it's rather harsh.
How can they send
someone like him to prison?
Right? The state is rather harsh.
Well, back when you were with Jangsan,
people who embezzled tens of billions
all got freed on probation.
Are you already picking a fight?
Of course not. I wouldn't dare.
I wanted to brief you
on different laws for the rich and poor...
I got a call.
Take it. Please.
Hello? This is Attorney Noh Chakhee.
Yes, Ms. Noh.
It's me. Guidong's mother.
Right. How can I help you?
I know this is
very presumptuous of me, but...
You're the only one
I can ask for help.
I thought you didn't drink instant coffee.
Ah.
I have no other choice
if I want to connect
with the clients at our office.
Hmm.
You should... do her that favor.
What favor?
Mr. Jwa Sibaek.
I get that you hear all kinds of stuff,
but how can you eavesdrop on my call?
Ah! I just overheard.
It sounded like Mr. Lee Guidong's mother.
It's not like I sold her a home appliance.
I don't offer customer service for trials.
What?
I'm sure you've done lots of favors
for the clients at Jangsan.
It's normal customer service.
Sure, because they paid me
a lot of money for that service.
But this trial
was a total loss on my part.
I bought Mr. Lee's shirt, chips, and food.
Why should I deliver money
for his commissary fund?
Wait.
If you knew it was a loss,
why did you buy him a shirt,
chips, and even food?
Why do that?
It was to...
win the trial.
But I didn't think Mr. Lee
would stab me in the back...
Anyway, I'm not going
to give her free customer service.
And I'm not obliged to,
so let's stop here.
Then don't do it for free.
If you like money that much,
then you can ask to be paid.
If Mr. Lee's mother
called you herself,
it would seem she really
doesn't have anyone else to ask.
If you request that she pay a fee,
she'll pay you.
Wow!
What a great idea.
Why didn't I think of that?
Oh, my. Thanks for calling, Ms. Noh.
I'll go to the detention center to pass on
the money for his commissary fund.
But I'll have to charge you a fee.
Is that all right with you?
Jwa, that jerk.
14-1 BUSEOK-GIL, HANSOL-EUP, JUNGHA-SI
Hello?
Ma'am.
Goodness. You're here, Ms. Noh.
Oh, my.
I would do it myself if I could,
but my leg is like this.
I thought you might have to visit
the detention center sometime soon.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
So, well...
How much will the extra fee be?
Ma'am, we would normally
charge you an extra fee,
but because this was my first case,
I received government aid.
So you don't have to worry.
Is that so?
Goodness. What a relief.
You see, I've been worried sick
about how much
that fee might cost me.
Well, here you go.
It's for Guidong's
commissary fund.
I had given him a month's worth of money,
but he already spent all of it.
Why? What did he spend it on?
I have no idea either.
Someone might have stolen it from him
or he might have spent it all
on something.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll make sure Mr. Lee gets this.
-Okay.
Right.
-Oh, my.
-Well...
You know, this is...
Goodness.
Well, this is...
This really isn't much.
You bought Guidong a shirt
and came here for free,
but this is all I can give you.
Please know that...
my gratitude is much greater
than what I can offer
in return.
GREEN GRAPE CANDY
Mr. Jwa Sibaek.
Open.
-Why...
-Please.
CORRECTION OF HOPE FOR A BETTER TOMORROW
CIVIL AFFAIRS OFFICE
ATTORNEY VISITATION APPLICATION
JWA SIBAEK
JUNGHA DETENTION CENTER
-Goodbye, then.
-Wait.
Well...
How do you do that?
-Do what?
-Apply for a visitation.
How do you do that?
I'm sure you visited countless clients
when you were at Jangsan.
I visited them, but I never applied.
-What?
-Do you think the ace of Jangsan
had time to be concerned
with applying for that?
My secretary did it.
I just went and visited them.
Were you royalty or something?
It sounds like how the royal servants
used to clean up the mess
after the king went number two.
Fine, then don't tell me.
It's not even a big deal.
Come on.
Tell me.
Please tell me.
You said it's not a big deal.
Case number.
ATTORNEY VISITATION APPLICATION
NOH CHAKHEE
It really is no big deal.
Next time you come,
make sure you apply online first.
Otherwise, the reservations might be full,
so you might have to wait a while.
So why didn't you?
Yes, sir.
You must put your full trust in me.
Good, turn it in.
Yes, sir.
Good.
And be polite. Two hands. Good.
ATTORNEY-PRISONER INTERVIEW ROOM
What? Mr. Lee,
what happened to your socks?
He stole it. An idiot did.
Someone stole your socks?
Your mom sent you underwear
and undershirts too, right?
Were those stolen too?
My underpants weren't stolen.
It's okay. All right.
I got it.
Hey, Mr. Lee. You know...
Your mom gave you
a month's worth of money for your fund.
How did you use it up?
I bought this.
Mr. Lee...
No matter how slow you are,
how can you buy a watch with that money?
Why did you get that watch?
Because I had to know the time.
What time?
The time to go see my mom.
The time to leave this place.
So that's why you bought that watch?
To count the time until you leave?
Yes.
Mr. Lee, do you know how to tell time?
-I do.
-What time is it?
It's 1:08.
Mr. Lee. You knew how to read a watch
before your hit-and-run accident.
Your mom said you were
a good student who won scholarships.
I don't know.
Look.
The short hand is for the hour.
Each mark signifies one hour.
Look. Do you see this long one?
That one is for the minutes.
Each mark signifies five minutes.
Now, let's go back.
Let's say this short one went forward
ten marks. Then what time is it?
-Ten o'clock.
-Yes. You're right.
Then what if this long one
goes forward double the marks.
How many minutes is that?
Double minutes.
Uh...
Well...
Okay. Do you see
how the watch is looking angry?
It's angry.
Yes, when this watch gets angry 30 times,
I'll visit with your mom.
Can you stay healthy until that day?
Yes. I'll stay healthy.
Okay.
Then I'll get going now.
Ms. Noh, you are...
...a good person.
No, I'm not a good person.
You're wrong. You are a good person.
Other people beat me up.
They steal my stuff.
They think I'm an idiot.
But, Ms. Noh, you're kind.
You taught me how to read a watch
and you bought me a shirt.
You're kind.
So I know.
Ms. Noh, you are a good person.
COMMISSARY FUND DEPOSIT APPLICATION
NAME: NOH CHAKHEE
PURCHASE APPLICATION
FIVE SOCKS
Are you Attorney Noh Chakhee?
When he heard that you'd be visiting,
he told me to make sure you got this.
GREEN GRAPE CANDY
My fee for my first case is just amazing.
Instead of a stingray-skin wallet,
I got a stingray-shaped kite.
Mr. Lee made this kite
during the occupational therapy class.
When he heard that you'd be visiting,
he told me to make sure you got this.
Wow!
It's flying really high.
Chakhee.
Are you done writing?
Yes.
Come and hold this.
Write everything about how you miss
your grandma and how sad you are,
then let it fly away into the sky.
Okay?
All right.
Here we go.
Don't cry anymore from now on.
With this, let's say goodbye
to your grandma.
It's all right.
Don't cry.
You'll be all right without her.
You have me.
Don't worry about anything.
Grandpa will keep you safe,
my dear Chakhee.
Oh!
What do I do?
What do I do now? Come on.
Okay.
Ow.
All right.
Oh!