♪Eager to change the planet's orbit♪
♪Unexpectedly, you've become
the planned orbit♪
♪I can't avoid the end
designated by you♪
♪Yet you're nowhere to be seen♪
♪I'm determined to look for
your trace♪
♪At last, I turned into an unknown star♪
♪Wandering silently
on the edge of the Milky Way♪
♪Still, I can't see you♪
♪How to get rid of your gravity♪
♪I'm both fascinated and suffocated♪
♪The cycle is disturbed and
the flight is out of control♪
♪Eager to crash on the earth
with a shooting star♪
♪How to counteract your gravity♪
♪Pull away from each dimension♪
♪Forget everything before I sink♪
♪Even though I don't know
my own whereabouts♪
=Yan Zhi's Romantic Story=
=Episode 11=
(Wind Entertainment)
Practice more while you're at home.
OK.
Hi, Mr. Shen.
Why are you still here?
Yan Ning,
let me give you a ride.
No, Mr. Shen.
I'll give her a ride.
Don't bother.
It's late.
What if you two are photographed?
I think it's even worse that
you two are photographed,
right, Yan Ning?
Gu Han,
would you give me a ride?
OK. Let's go.
See you, Mr. Shen.
He's everywhere.
You go upstairs.
I'll go home.
Let's talk later.
Would you like to go upstairs?
May I?
Have a seat.
OK.
Wow, it smells good.
Absolutely.
I lived in a dorm when I was in college.
When I didn't feel like going out,
I made instant noodles
in different ways.
Oh?
I didn't expect that the melancholy prince
was so down-to-earth.
The prince is also a man,
right?
Try it.
How do you like it?
Yummy.
Then have some more.
Wait.
What's up?
Turn around.
When you get close to him,
do you feel butterflies in your stomach?
Don't move.
Let me hug you.
Yan Ning,
let's be together,
shall we?
Who is it?
I'll go take a look.
OK.
Yan Ning.
May I help you?
I assume you're tired practicing guitar.
I've brought snacks for you.
No, thanks.
We have food.
Hey.
More is better.
Yan Ning,
how can you eat instant noodles
at night?
It isn't nutritious.
Hey.
Mr. Shen,
what do you mean?
I've added lots of fixings.
Why isn't it nutritious?
Even if you have,
it's still instant noodles.
I love instant noodles.
It's none of your business.
Yan Ning,
here.
Have some more
and enjoy a nutritionally balanced meal.
You know what,
the dishes are very delicious.
Here.
Gu Han.
Yeah.
Would you make me another pot?
No problem.
I have to take this.
Where are you?
Are you with Yan Ning?
I'll wait downstairs.
If I don't see you in three minutes,
I'll go to her apartment and catch you.
Well, a piece of cake.
No problem. I'll be there soon.
Don't worry. I'll be there soon.
Is everything OK?
I have some business to attend to.
I have to go.
OK.
Wait.
What's wrong?
The apron.
Stay safe.
Remember to practice our song.
OK.
I'll call you.
Yeah.
Bye, Mr. Shen.
The snacks are delivered.
I appreciate your kindness.
You should leave.
Ah?
Well,
we haven't finished eating yet.
You can take them back if you want.
Well...
- If you're busy...
- I'm not.
Fine.
Get some rest after dinner.
♪The past is scattered
all over the place♪
♪I remained where I was
and waited for you♪
♪Doing my one-man show♪
♪The deeper the scar,
the more involved I am♪
♪The more I try to forget,
the more I miss you♪
♪Losing you♪
♪I sunk in there myself♪
♪I crash on an isolated island♪
♪Covered in scars, I need the antidote,
while the rain is pouring♪
♪You don't care about the thing
I treasure most♪
♪In an instant my heartbeat is frozen♪
♪Broken pride♪
♪Once impulsive, then regretful,
does it matter♪
♪You turn around,
leaving me nowhere to go♪
♪Be your disciple and beg for love♪
♪Broken pride♪
♪Once impulsive, then regretful,
does it matter♪
♪You turn around,
leaving me nowhere to go♪
♪Be your disciple and beg for love♪
=Yan Zhi's Romantic Story=
(The right of communication through network)
(is exclusively owned by Tencent)