=Ruan Xiaofeng's Royal Love Quest=
=Episode 12=
(Qixia Pavilion)
Welcome to
today's showdown
between the two pavilions.
First,
let's give a round of applause
to the Beauty Trio from Yeyang Pavilion.
Bravo!
(Never stop loving Yang Qiong)
What's going on?
- What's happening?
- What's going on?
- Something's not right.
- His voice sounds off. It's different.
Could he be lip-syncing?
Is it really him singing?
- It's not him.
- He's fake singing.
I've been observing Yang Qiong.
I noticed that every time he sang,
his eyes kept looking
toward the side of the stage.
I suspect
he must be lip-syncing.
He can't seriously be lip-syncing.
Listen to the voice.
How could it be?
He's fake singing.
- Lip-syncing!
- Get off the stage!
Awful!
Unbelievable.
- Bravo!
Even though Liu Yu
is tall
and has long legs,
he always seems unsteady
whenever he dances.
There must be something
inside his boots.
How do we expose him?
He's easily affected.
All you need to do is...
Liu Yu!
Liu Yu, show us a roundhouse kick.
Roundhouse kick!
Once more!
He's wearing height insoles!
Shorty!
What about Songke?
Songke?
He's handsome!
Bravo!
Such a wonderful performance!
Coming up next is
Qixia Pavilion.
Let's give them a round of applause.
Bravo!
(Do I really have to do this?)
Maybe they're just shy.
Let's give them
a warm round of applause.
Please.
Bravo!
Whatever.
♪Amidst the twinkling starry sky♪
♪Your graceful figure
bathed in moonlight♪
♪The moment I turn back,
I will never forget this sight♪
♪If love overwhelms me♪
♪How could I ever resist?♪
♪I only wish for you to be well♪
♪May the blowing wind
and falling rain♪
♪Never dampen
the corner of your robe♪
♪May you stay afloat♪
♪Through the ups and downs♪
♪May you sleep peacefully♪
♪Unaware of the dawn
and free of worries♪
Excellent! This is interesting.
Bravo!
Excellent!
Your Majesty, the results of the vote.
Qixia Pavilion narrowly won.
Do you accept this?
No, I don't.
They cheated.
It wasn't a fair win.
Strategies should be employed in wars.
The world of business
is no different from the battlefield.
Xiaofeng's tactics are clever.
As expected from someone
born into a military family.
You flattered me, Your Majesty.
Actually, it wasn't all my efforts.
If they had played fair and open,
I wouldn't have had a chance
to use such tricks.
Your Majesty,
these performers
have been spreading rumors
in East Market.
They're arrogant
under Aunt's indulgence.
I ask you to uphold justice,
Your Majesty.
Since a pact was made,
Aunt, as the Princess Royal,
I believe you'll honor your word.
Your wise judgment convinces me,
Your Majesty.
I accept
your decree.
But I'm getting up in years,
and nearing death.
Suffering such humiliations
from the younger generation
is truly...
Your Majesty,
Aunt is getting up in years.
She shouldn't be disturbed
by worldly affairs.
The capital isn't a place
for a peaceful rest.
Heishui is serene and pure
and is blessed by our ancestors.
It'd surely be a perfect retreat
for Aunt.
That sounds good.
I decree that Yeyang Pavilion
will be closed at once.
Princess Luyang will be sent
to Heishui for rest.
Aunt, please return to your residence
and prepare for your departure.
Your Majesty.
Be on your way, Aunt.
Your Highness.
Let's go.
Seeing both of you
supporting each other
makes me glad.
I'll grant you one wish.
Speak it
if there's anything you want.
Your Majesty, I'd like to ask
for your permission
to reopen the investigation
into Imperial Concubine Wan's fall.
Rumors are spreading
throughout the capital.
Unless we uncover the truth,
rumors won't stop.
It would also help
restore the honor
of the imperial family.
Please calm down, Your Majesty.
It's my idea.
Please don't blame Xiaofeng.
♪The wind lifts fallen leaves
and carries them to the riverbank♪
♪The scattered past
drifts further with each step♪
♪Too shallow, too faint♪
♪Memories still follow♪
♪Entwined, refusing to let go♪
♪I don't want this freedom♪
♪As long as you don't go♪
♪Like drifting sand
slipping through my grip♪
♪The tighter I hold, the more I lose♪
♪Spring goes, autumn comes,
as day and night take turns♪
♪I guard my obsession♪
♪Let me be drunk in dreams
and ache when sober♪
♪Every single word is
etched into my heart♪
♪In the silent world♪
♪Only a true heart can be heard♪
♪Let me love madly
and hate irrationally♪
♪I bury this vow in my destiny♪
♪And fight against it♪
♪I will bet everything
on your next fall♪