[LIVE UP TO YOUR YOUTH]
[Episode 32]
Zhuang,
the shipments are all out.
What are you busy with?
Weren't we hit hard
by counterfeit goods recently?
I'm working on
a new anti-counterfeiting method.
This is a big deal.
You have to get this right.
By the way...
Xu mentioned yesterday
that your grandmother is sick.
Just a small token.
It's not much.
No, no.
No, Zhuang.
I can't take this money.
You and Mr. Xu
are already tight on money.
-I really can't take it.
-Enough.
Her treatment comes first.
If it's not enough,
we'll figure something out together.
Thank you, Zhuang.
Help me watch the shop.
I need to go out for a bit.
Mr. Xu, Zhuang.
What did Chen Guangfa promise you?
Did he say
that after ruining our business,
this place
would be handed over to you?
Mr. Xu, what did you say?
You've got me all wrong.
Then what are you copying?
I...
You still don't know
how your store went out
of business, do you?
[Product Return Form]
[Order Confirmation Receipt]
Isn't this
the batch that got canceled on me?
You already suspected back then
that it was malicious competition.
But you never thought through
why that person
could know
your restock timing
and pricing so precisely.
You mean
the one who ruined me
was Chen Guangfa?
The same way he brought you down back then
is how he plans to take us down now.
You're being used as a pawn.
Mr. Xu, Zhuang,
since when did you know—
That's not important.
If you knew I was trouble,
then why place
that 20,000-unit order?
Those 20,000 units
were
for our Russian friends.
We knew early on
that Chen Guangfa set a trap.
What Chen Guangfa asked you to do
is illegal.
He used you
to keep his own hands clean.
In the end,
you'd be the one taking the fall.
Mr. Xu, Zhuang.
I was really used by him.
Really, believe me.
Please forgive me, okay?
I won't dare do it again.
Hello?
Okay, got it.
Just as expected.
The shipment's been held at customs.
Mr. Xu.
Chen Guangfa did this.
What do we do now?
That's 20,000 units.
What now?
There is no customs declaration.
The declared category
is second-hand textiles.
Actually, they are all
newly produced export down jackets.
Xu, you are here.
I heard
one of your shipments got held.
They were about to seize it.
I quickly asked
Mr. Kozlov
to wait for you.
Hurry up and explain yourself.
Is there any misunderstanding?
Then I should thank you.
What a coincidence.
You're here, too.
I'm here to pay additional duties.
As business people,
the most important thing
is that we cannot evade taxes.
Russian Customs Notice No. 12:
Undeclared goods
will be confiscated.
Wait a moment.
Hello.
This is our customs clearance document.
Please take a look.
Okay.
Customs clearance documents
must be checked carefully.
There are too many fakes.
Everything checks out.
These are your goods.
You can take them.
But we don't handle transport.
Don't worry. I'll handle it myself.
Thank you.
Take them?
These are smuggled goods.
And you're letting him take them?
Who told you
my goods are smuggled?
I'd like to file a report.
Guangfa Commerce
has copied MRX brand designs,
is selling counterfeit goods,
and is engaged in large-scale smuggling.
You remind me of an ancient figure—
Lyu Bu.
You're very meticulous
and smart.
But who can prove
which of the goods held at customs
are yours
and which are mine?
You've been to my warehouse, right?
They're identical.
Do you really think your goods
are exactly the same as mine?
What else?
Did you embroider flowers in the pockets?
Indeed.
I admit
that your goods can pass
for the real thing.
But speaking of this,
I have to thank you.
You were the one who said
in business,
you have to cut costs.
A successful businessman
must maximize profits.
And that's exactly
what made me realize
the biggest difference
between us.
Your goods are not bad.
They are top quality.
But the cost is too high.
And there are taxes
and quality inspection procedures.
To put it bluntly,
it's all for show.
Because of that,
your cost has increased by half.
Is it worth it?
In business,
you have to balance the short-term gains
against the long-term value.
Mr. Chen,
why don't you also get
international certification?
Then all the goods outside
will be yours.
Mr. Kozlov,
the serial numbers on this list
match the ones
on our labels.
Feel free to verify.
Indeed.
These formal quality inspections
and customs procedures
increase costs a lot.
But that's exactly why
no matter how hard you scheme,
your fakes will never be real.
All right.
I've accepted your report.
Chen Guangfa,
you can't take your goods away for now.
You must cooperate
with our investigation first.
China-Russia trade
still has a long way to go.
Yes.
We must
strictly inspect such matters
in the future.
We will absolutely not hurt
the feelings of the Chinese friends.
Yes, yes.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
So this season
comes to
a successful close.
For the new season,
our main focus is to address
everyone's issues with down jackets...
Alright, let's call it a day.
Meeting adjourned.
This house
is yours
now.
Take a look.
Have a seat.
When did you do the paperwork?
This morning.
Didn't you say before
[Building Ownership Certificate
of the People's Republic of China]
you wanted to
renovate this house?
How do you want to renovate it?
I want to divide the bedroom into two.
Agreed.
It'll be easier
when we have a kid.
What I meant was
one bedroom for you and one for me.
You snore so loudly.
Do you dislike me that much?
Give me the house key.
No.
Give it back.
Give me the key back.
No!
Give it back to me.
Aren't we missing
our certificate?
What certificate?
What certificate do you think?
Should we go back to Wenzhou
or Yantai for the certificate?
I'll listen to you.
Okay, then we'll go back tomorrow.
I still have a meeting tomorrow.
A meeting?
Then,
why don't we "have a meeting" first?
[Fortune]
Come on, tourists,
keep up with me.
Just a bit further ahead
and we'll reach the Seine River.
You can take out your cameras now
to snap some photos for memories.
Stay close, don't fall behind.
Look, those pigeons
aren't afraid of people at all.
♪ I heard you sleep alone now ♪
♪ That marriage put you through so much ♪
♪ Hearing that breaks my heart ♪
♪ Makes me want to protect you again ♪
♪ They say you go quiet
when I'm mentioned ♪
♪ Always using alcohol
to sort out right and wrong ♪
♪ I don't understand
how deep your love runs ♪
♪ And you don't understand
how much I miss you ♪
[Name: Tao Liangliang]
♪ Maybe we should meet again ♪
♪ Even just for a glance ♪
♪ There's too much
in this world left unresolved ♪
♪ You're the arrow
that pierces through my longing ♪
♪ Maybe we should meet again ♪
♪ Even just for a glance ♪
Buddy,
are you okay?
♪ Looking back on those years
we held each other up ♪
Hello.
♪ When we loved recklessly,
no matter the cost ♪
♪ Sometimes I wonder, in this world ♪
[Ambulance]
♪ Are there other versions of me ♪
♪ Still foolishly clinging to love ♪
Excuse me.
♪ Clinging to other versions of you ♪
Have you seen this person?
♪ If somewhere out there ♪
Hurry up.
♪ Other versions of us exist ♪
♪ I truly hope their story ♪
♪ Gets a happy ending ♪
♪ Maybe we should meet again ♪
♪ Even just for a glance ♪
You can check it out over there.
Thank you.
♪ There's too much
in this world left unresolved ♪
♪ You're the arrow
that pierces through my longing ♪
♪ Maybe we should meet again ♪
♪ Even just for a glance ♪
♪ Looking back on those years
we held each other up ♪
♪ When we loved recklessly,
no matter the cost ♪
Hello?
Hello, Ma'am.
This is
the Paris 7th District Police Station.
Are you Shen Ranran?
We found a deceased Asian male,
Mr. Tao Liangliang,
at Les Invalides Square.
When he was found,
he had already stopped breathing.
We found your contact information
in his pocket.
If you are a relative,
please come to assist
with the investigation
and handle his affairs within 48 hours.
How did you end up getting this disease?
Wishing Liangliang and Ranran
a happy marriage!
Ranran.
In any place
and in every way,
I will love you forever.
In the future,
if anything goes down in Sijiu City
within my power,
just let me know.
No one stands forever in this world.
My name is Liangliang—
don't you forget it.
Hello, Director Weng.
How have you been lately?
Xu.
I'm doing very well.
I'm in Chengdu now.
The filming is about to start.
What are you filming this time?
"The Late Love"
has finally started filming.
"The Late Love?"
Yes.
You're going to shoot it?
That's right.
Well, this is real?
Hey, Director Weng,
what's going on?
It's so sudden.
I'm totally confused.
Hey, didn't the studio
have a lot of issues with the script?
Yes,
so I have to mention
your master, Mr. He.
He did a lot of work
for this film.
Hello.
Director Gao.
I am He Sheng.
I heard
the studio is collecting
good original scripts.
I would like to recommend
the one
my apprentice and I wrote five years ago—
"The Late Love."
This is
my last script.
I won't be writing
any more scripts from here on out.
If you have any suggestions,
I'll revise accordingly.
I'll go through it word by word,
even down to every punctuation mark.
I really want
it to be filmed.
[The Late Love]
[Screenwriter: He Sheng, Xu Shengli]
Xu Shengli.
I've seen it.
[The Late Love]
[Screenwriter: He Sheng, Xu Shengli]
Come here.
Let's take a photo.
Go over there.
Ready. 1, 2, 3.
Done.
Let's take one together.
Okay.
Let me find someone to help us.
Hello.
Could you help us take a photo?
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Hey, look at the camera.
1, 2, 3.
["The Late Love"—Now Showing
in Theaters Nationwide]
This group of characters
has been through so much.
Shouldn't this farewell
feel a bit more meaningful?
That's not refined enough.
Think about it again.
God
is the cruelest screenwriter of all.
This is a script written
by Xu Shengli and me together.
It's as good as it gets.
Slow down. Slow down.
Slow down.
From now on, we will
go our separate ways.
In this world,
a lot of things just can't be avoided.
What we can do
is
protect what we want,
carry what we're meant to carry,
and keep moving forward.
[Screenwriter: He Sheng, Xu Shengli]
[Director: Weng Xingguo]
[This film is dedicated to the memory
of Mr. He Sheng]
[The Late Love]
[Screenwriter: He Sheng, Xu Shengli]
Cut.
Good job, everyone.
That's a wrap.
Thanks, Director Cui.
Come, let's take a group photo.
Come, everyone, come.
Happy wrap!
[Hostel]
Northeasterner. Happy New Year.
Happy New Year.
You're so hardworking.
Let me plug it in and see.
[Hostel]
Let me check on my girl.
She sleeps so soundly.
Let's go back to the room. Hurry.
[Hostel]
Let's go.
[2018]
In the end,
it's all the same no matter
who you're with.
There you go again,
making a big deal out of everything.
Hey, have you ever stepped in
when your son got into conflicts
with others?
I'm the one handling everything.
while you're the one playing the good guy.
Did I say I wouldn't handle it?
Don't I need to make money?
You sit here every day,
pretending you're working.
How many times
have you been to our kids' school?
How many parent-teacher conferences
have you attended?
Big things, small things—
I manage them all.
If it works, we stay.
If not, we split.
Honey, don't be angry.
Don't be angry.
You just
said what you really think.
Look,
are those lines even in the script?
Isn't it written like that?
Alright.
You don't need to run lines with me.
You're too into character.
I was kind enough to help you run lines.
You've got no conscience.
I will keep
your great kindness in mind.
But then again,
you're actually quite suited
to write family dramas.
Just listening to couples talk
like this is annoying.
Art comes from life.
Mr. He said
-Comes from what?
-if you want—
It comes from life,
but it must be higher than life.
You must fully use your imagination
to shape it into art.
Which parts are crafted,
and which come from real life?
This...
this script of mine
d-doesn't come from real life.
It's all fictionalized.
It... It's all fictionalized.
Your pen is so old.
I'll get you a new one later.
No need, I like this one.
But isn't  your script
too pessimistic?
Isn't it good
living an ordinary life
like the two of us?
Being able to live an ordinary life
is already very lucky.
Life is full of trivial,
messy details,
but that doesn't mean
there's no real love in it.
People make different choices,
so their fates are different.
To be honest,
having lived for most of my life,
I'm very content.
You're right.
There's more than one standard answer
to happiness.
Right now,
I just hope our parents
stay healthy,
and Dongdong and Chunchun
grow up well.
That's all that matters.
Right.
The most important thing is that you
don't make me mad.
When it comes to me,
I'm the one making you mad.
I make you mad.
Okay.
Chunchun, give me back
my roasted fish fillets!
Give them back!
Chunchun, give them back to me.
Listen.
They're fighting again.
Don't fight!
Grandpa, look at him.
What's going on?
Chunchun took my roasted fish fillets.
Is that so?
As an older brother,
you should give in to your little sister.
She's already eaten a lot.
There's only one bag left.
Only one bag?
That's impossible.
Go.
-Go ask your dad for them.
-It's not like we don't have more at home.
Go ask your dad for them.
Go. Go.
No more fighting.
These kids
are exactly like Shengli
when he was little.
Dad,
are there any roasted fish fillets left?
Yes,
they're in the drawer under
the TV cabinet.
Dad, give them to me first.
Grandpa sent me.
You're not a little kid anymore.
Get them yourself.
Look,
every time they come,
the first thing they do is call for Dad.
And you still said
I don't care about them.
How else should I care?
[Shichahai]
Is this still the old
Shichahai private room?
It's still the original
Shichahai private room.
It's just that
we knocked through
the adjacent rooms.
This way, your dining experience
will feel more spacious and comfortable,
won't it?
Pretty good.
Mr. Xu,
not only has our hotel
been recently renovated,
but we have also
introduced many new dishes.
We have "Abundant Wealth",
"Rolling in Money",
"Happy Marriage", "Pure and Clear",
"Rising High," and "Flying Together."
I want to eat Beijing roast duck,
braised pork balls in gravy,
shredded pork with sweet bean sauce,
braised pork joint,
braised mutton strips, quick-boiled tripe,
and old Beijing noodles
with soybean paste.
Sir,
the dishes I just mentioned
are exactly
the classic Beijing dishes you asked for.
We just changed the names.
Just keeping up with the times.
Okay, as long as you have them.
So we're still booking lunch
for tomorrow, right?
Right.
Our people will all be here tomorrow.
Mr. Guo, have something to eat first.
Is this your first day at work?
When have I ever eaten stuff like this?
Isn't it a waste?
I'll eat it.
Xiaobao is really something.
He even got himself a secretary.
Drink this.
Thank you, Mr. Guo.
Have some of this.
Hello.
Pizza, rice, or a hamburger?
Rice.
Okay.
Hello, ma'am.
What would you like to order?
[Steak]
This one.
Then, how would you like
your steak cooked?
Well done.
Are you sure?
Are you trying to be difficult?
I want it well-done.
Give me a well-done one.
Heat it up right now.
Remake it.
Yes.
Okay.
Honey.
Did I scare you?
Wait inside.
It's fine.
Hey, it's not fine.
You've been waiting forever.
And you're wearing high heels.
You'll be exhausted soon.
I want to wait right here.
Alright, then I'll wait with you.
Okay.
Zhuang, Mr. Xu.
In the blink of an eye,
over a decade has passed.
You haven't changed a bit.
You've gotten so thin.
He hasn't been giving you
a hard time, has he?
Come on, after all these years,
neither of you has changed.
You both are still pretty and young.
Ranran.
Are you leaving again this time?
Now that I'm back,
I'll stay and work in Beijing,
so I can take care of the elders.
That's wonderful.
Then...
Then, we can see each other often.
Of course.
In that case,
you two can see each other every day.
You two can even live together.
Don't be jealous.
I won't be jealous. Me, jealous?
The great screenwriter and big star—
You're all here?
Little Northeasterner, the big boss.
A small boss. A small boss.
Long time no see.
Big star?
I changed careers a long time ago.
You will always be
the big star of Seasons Change Hostel.
In my heart,
none of the current stars
can compare to you.
I heard
you've turned Seasons Change Hostel
into a big hotel.
I opened a new place.
It's just a small hotel.
What about
the original Seasons Change Hostel?
The new place
is managed by our chairman.
As for me,
if I have time,
I still like staying
at our old Seasons Change Hostel.
Yeah.
That's our roots.
Without Seasons Change Hostel,
we wouldn't be who we are today.
Yes.
For the meal today,
Little Northeasterner
should take the seat of honor.
How can I take the seat of honor?
I'm so young.
What do you mean, young?
You must take the seat of honor.
You're paying.
Sure, I can pay.
But let me tell you,
you're always welcome
to stay at our hotel anytime.
Okay then.
When we go,
we'll still just give him six yuan.
I'm fine with that.
Chairman.
-Is that Okay?
-Is that Okay? 6 yuan.
I'll listen to you.
Thanks for the face.
It's a deal then.
6 yuan per bed.
I'll sell
my house
and move into Seasons Change Hostel.
Shengli.
Zongbao.
Zhuang Zhuang.
You haven't changed a bit.
And I'm here, too.
Ranran.
How are you? Good?
Good, good.
Zongbao.
You've moved to Beijing.
Why are you so late?
I was halfway here
when I realized I forgot this corn juice.
So I went back to get it.
It's this year's new product.
Have a taste.
See if it's any good.
You changed the packaging.
I have to keep up with the times.
Everyone is here.
Which room are we in?
Still Shichahai.
[Shichahai]
Let's not fight today.
We are too old to fight.
Alright, everyone's hungry.
Let's go in.
Let's go.
Go inside
and eat together.
[Shichahai]
After lunch,
let's go check out
the Seasons Change Hostel.
Luogu Hutong has really changed,
hasn't it?
Lin's bun shop
Bun Shop.
is now run by his daughter.
They have several locations now.
They even opened a branch over there.
We used to
always eat buns here.
How about
going check out the new hotel?
Let's go and take a look.
Let's head back to the hostel first.
-I agree.
-Okay.
I also want to see
what Seasons Change Hostel
looks like now.
I have to say.
This whole vibe
really takes me back
to those days when we were all wasted,
stumbling our way
toward Seasons Change Hostel together.
Right now,
we are like a senior tour group
visiting the hutong.
What do you mean, senior?
You are the senior here.
I'll take a picture of
that white hair of yours.
-The tour group is missing something.
-Let me take a photo.
A tour guide.
Are you hinting at me?
Yes, let's see what you can do.
Do you still remember your lines
from back then?
I can remember them even in my sleep.
Alright, alright.
I-I'm recording this.
Come on, you say it.
Come on, senior tour group, follow me.
What senior tour group?
North, south, all around.
Visiting kin, visiting friends.
On business, on vacation.
-Chasing fortune or chasing dreams—
-It's the same line.
-It's exactly the same.
-We
Right.
come from all corners of the country.
At Seasons Change Hostel,
we are one family.
Seasons Change Hostel
helps your dreams come true.
Are those the words?
Yes.
Come on, stay close, everyone.
It hasn't changed much here.
Come on, let's go home.
We're home!
[Seasons Change Hostel]
Hurry up, come on.
Northeasterner.
W-What are you doing?
I hurried here. I'm not late, am I?
I'm back.
Is everyone here?
Hurry up.
I'm coming.
You're taking a group photo?
[Seasons Change Hostel]
Come on.
The camera is really expensive.
Cao?
I'm late. I'm late.
[Seasons Change Hostel]
I took a detour.
Should I
[Seasons Change Hostel]
change clothes today?
You look very sharp.
Isn't this your
best-looking outfit?
Uncle Guo looks the best.
Nonsense.
Is everything ready?
-Come on.
-We're ready.
Come on.
Let's begin then.
You took a photo without me?
♪ Should auld acquaintance be forgot ♪
♪ And never brought to mind? ♪
♪ And auld lang syne? ♪
-Liangliang?
-Liangliang.
Come here.
Liangliang.
♪ We twa hae run about the braes ♪
You are here?
I kind of missed you today.
Don't know why.
♪ And pou'd the gowans fine ♪
Hurry up.
We have to go eat noodles after this.
Liang.
Mr. Tao, stop putting on airs.
Hurry up. We're waiting for you.
♪ But we've wander'd monie a weary fit ♪
Come on
-Come on.
-Hurry.
[Seasons Change Hostel]
♪ Sin' auld lang syne ♪
♪ For auld lang syne, my dear ♪
5-second countdown.
5.
[Seasons Change Hostel]
4.
♪ For auld lang syne ♪
3.
2.
1.
Seasons Change Hostel!
[Seasons Change Hostel]
♪ We'll tak a cup o' kindness yet ♪
♪ For auld lang syne ♪