[LIVE UP TO YOUR YOUTH]
[Episode 5]
Why are you just standing there?
Get to work!
Go, go, go.
Stop dilly-dallying.
What are you looking at?
Move aside.
Stop right there!
Who allowed you in here?
What are you doing?
What are you measuring here?
Stop measuring!
Measure it properly for me.
What are you doing?
I have something to do here.
I'll be back in a bit.
Be gentle with it.
It's done?
We're measuring.
Big Bro.
Hurry up.
Measure everything clearly.
Note it down carefully.
Write down
the size of each room,
how many beds,
how many tables.
Go on!
Okay, Sir.
Come down.
Who allowed you in here?
Get lost!
Let me tell you...
[Seasons Change Hotel]
Gentlemen,
we have no grudge in the past
and no hatred today.
I don't even know
what kind of act you're putting on here
at my Seasons Change Hotel today.
But whatever it is,
we can talk it over calmly.
In this world,
there are no conflicts we can't resolve.
Maybe it's all a misunderstanding.
Don't you think?
Are you the boss of Seasons Change Hotel?
I, Little Northeasterner,
mean it when I say something.
Alright,
my word carries weight too.
If I finish speaking
and you still can't make the decision,
I'll make sure you end up
drooling in your sleep in your next life.
Understood?
You're telling me I get to decide.
So what exactly do you want?
I'm here to do business with you.
I brought you customers.
Customers?
Sure.
How many people?
And how many days are they staying?
I
just saw your
basement.
I can fill it up
completely
and keep it full for a whole year.
How about that?
Then where will we live?
Shocked now, huh?
You've seen it too.
The basement
is mostly full now.
If it's full,
no problem.
Kick them all out.
-Yeah.
[Guest Room]
Kick them out.
Why should we?
Let me hear how you plan
to educate people.
I'd like to hear how they educate people.
What are you saying?
Say it again!
Didn't you understand what I said?
-Where do you come from?
-Let's figure out the situation first.
Okay, okay.
Talk to me. Keep talking.
We're working on a project
nearby,
and I need to find a place
for my guys to stay.
I think
your place is pretty good,
so I want them to stay here.
They're not here to
demolish the guesthouse.
They're working on a project
and want to stay here,
not to tear it down.
But I'm really sorry.
My guests are all regulars.
I can't just kick them out
-because of you.
-How dare you!
Don't think that your beard
scares me.
If you dare lay a finger on me today,
I'll call my friend Tang
at the police station
and have him
deal with you properly.
Do you believe me?
I've got a bad temper!
What happened?
There's going to be a fight.
What? What?
My bad temper!
You're asking for a beating!
Enough.
What are you doing?
They can't really pluck them.
You have relatives
at the police station, huh?
If I didn't have someone watching my back,
would I dare do business in Beijing?
We pay to stay here too.
We'll pay whatever they pay.
I'll even add extra for each room.
How about that?
It's not about adding the money.
These people,
aren't ordinary guests.
They are like my brothers and sisters.
I can't just
throw them out
for a bit more cash!
No amount of money will do.
Yeah, exactly.
That won't do.
Besides, how much more can you add?
I'll add 20 yuan a day per room.
How about it?
Twenty.
Plus 20.
How much?
20 yuan a day per room.
One bed costs 6 yuan.
He adds 20 yuan for a room.
That's several yuan more per bed
than before.
But I can't just
kick everyone out at once.
Look.
If you can't kick them all out at once,
then kick them out slowly.
If you do it quickly,
I'll add another 10 yuan per room.
Is that a deal?
Whether you make this money
is up to you.
Little Northeasterner.
Then where will we live?
Little Northeasterner?
Where are we supposed to live?
Little Northeasterner.
Wait, wait.
If it really doesn't work,
I'll talk to them.
Talk to me!
Wait,
what are you even doing here?
Is it your place to speak here?
Are you the Big Bro?
Are you blind?
My Big Bro is right here.
Big Bro.
Hello.
You've got style.
Are you from Nancheng?
I'm from Xuanwu.
What do you do?
Me?
I play the saxophone.
An artist.
More like the one being played by art.
It's like this.
I've been at Seasons Change Hotel
for almost two years now.
I heard
you're going to tear it down, right?
No.
They're just trying to
kick everyone out.
Kick everyone out?
I treat this place like home,
and I treat the people here
like family.
Forget whether they agree or not—
I won't
allow it.
Right, Mrs. Wang?
Yes!
Right, Mr. Zhao?
Who's kicking us out?
Come.
Fine.
Saxophone player,
you've got guts.
I heard that clearly.
I'll count you in.
So what?
Anyone else?
Are we about to hear from
your whole extended family?
Hello.
Come. Come here, come here.
Next time you try to show off,
get your facts straight first, okay?
Nice to meet you.
From your hairstyle,
I'm guessing you're also in the arts?
I'm a painter.
Do you like paintings?
If you like paintings,
I'll give you one.
Once I become famous,
my paintings will be priceless.
What are you laughing at?
My paintings are currently
featured in a
huge art exhibition.
I might just
become famous overnight.
I get it.
You're a fraud?
Fine.
I'll count you in.
Does anyone else at Seasons Change Hotel
still want to speak?
Who?
Zhuang.
Here comes a little Mu Guiying.
You know Mu Guiying;
that means you're someone educated
and polite.
I don't deserve that.
Anyone can stay
at Seasons Change Hotel,
but we've got to be reasonable.
You can't just plant yourself here
and act like you own the place.
Are you saying I'm unreasonable?
What do you do?
It doesn't matter what we do.
As long as we pay the rent,
there's no reason
to kick us out.
Zhuang Zhuang is right.
-Yes.
-You're right.
That makes sense.
Look at that girl's
sharp tongue.
I always tell you guys to read more books,
but none of you listen.
Little girl,
you really can talk.
Alright.
I get it.
I'll count you in, too.
Go ahead, laugh all you want.
Big Bro, I was wrong.
Speak!
Go on!
Those guys are like bandits.
They all have thick beards.
They're terrifying.
What should I do?
Tang, you have to help me.
Look.
They want to stay in your place.
Whether you let them or not is your call.
I said no, but they insist.
Does your big boss,
your uncle,
know about this?
I haven't had time to tell him yet—
that's why we called you here.
Alright.
You
should go discuss it
with your boss
and see whether this deal
is going to be done or not.
Also,
regarding those people,
if they do anything
other than business,
call the station immediately.
We will intervene right away.
Alright, that's it for now.
These guys are basically thugs—
crude, vulgar,
completely unbearable.
I've been wanting to hit him
for a long time.
I... I almost did too.
I held myself back,
then I thought
that wouldn't work.
If we strike first,
they'll have leverage against us.
Didn't you pick up a brick today?
Why did you put it back?
I told you.
If we strike first,
they'll have leverage against us.
Zongbao,
didn't you just go to the restroom?
Did you fall in?
I didn't see you the whole time.
What?
I was at the stairwell entrance.
Those ladies
were shaking with fear.
I was there comforting them.
Were you comforting them,
or were you there
shaking right along with them?
I...
I even grabbed a mop.
I was ready to charge.
For mopping floors?
Mopping.
They've already pulled knives,
and we're all just people
living on the edge here anyway.
Are we really?
Who wasn't?
Alright, alright.
Say no more.
If they want us to move,
then we move.
Tomorrow we'll quickly find a
cheaper place
and try to stay together.
You guys can look for a place if you want.
I'm not moving.
That guy surnamed Feng
is a ruthless one.
A wise man knows when to yield.
Tie,
you can't treat my place
like your workplace
and show up on time every day.
Who can stand that?
Give us a chance to breathe,
let us...
Bro,
I just took the brothers
for another look around.
This place
is perfect for us to live in.
The brothers are all super happy.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Then we'll stay here.
Stay here.
You'll even get married here
and make it your wedding home.
What exactly do you want
to do with my place?
Just stay here.
There are so many shops
and guesthouses all around—
why did you choose us?
What's so special
about our place?
The location is good,
the size is right,
and it's cheap.
That's low cost,
high return.
Most importantly,
I like you.
Really.
Don't be a coward.
I just like you
stiffening your neck like that.
Come on. Stiffen your neck.
Tie,
stop teasing me.
You...
Just...
Let me off the hook, will you?
Let you off the hook?
I'd need to have a hook first.
I'll tell you one more time.
We are staying here.
We are staying here!
Do you understand?
Stop talking nonsense.
-Don't you scare when he acts like this?
-Come here.
Go over there!
Little Northeasterner,
let me tell you,
I don't like to bully people.
Seeing how aggrieved you look
makes my heart ache.
Really.
How about this?
Let bygones be bygones.
From now on,
I'll give you three days
to drive them away.
Okay?
How can I kick them out, Tie?
They've already paid rent.
They won't leave just because I say so.
What can I do if they won't leave?
Then do this.
Call them all out.
If you can't handle it, I can.
I'll talk to them.
Okay?
Are you pulling a long face now?
Zhuang,
take the brothers
downstairs and round everyone up.
See who is here
and call them all over.
Then tell them
Little Northeasterner
is going to give them money.
Okay, Brother.
Come back.
Go back and stay put.
You just keep stalling here.
I have plenty of ways to kill you.
Why are there so few people?
Why are there only a few people?
Everyone staying here is decent—
they go to work during the day.
There aren't that many unemployed loafers
or vagrants.
Who are you talking about?
Did I mention you?
Don't assume I'm talking about you.
Don't be afraid.
I've been here
several times,
and you all know
what I'm here for.
Today, I want to properly
talk with you all.
Okay?
Can you move out?
Why should we?
We've paid.
Then if Little Northeasterner
refunds your rent
and gives you an extra half month's rent,
will you move?
Why should I pay an extra
half month's rent?
Okay. I... I'll move.
Thank you.
What about you, Sir?
I'll move. I'll move.
Thank you.
What about you, miss?
I'll move.
I'll move tomorrow.
I'll go back and pack in a bit.
Move.
I'll move right away.
I'll move tomorrow.
It's settled.
See? It's settled.
Talk to them nicely.
Go back with them
and pack up their things.
Thank you.
-Okay, brother.
-Thank you.
Let's go.
-Let's go.
Go!
You...
You should talk to those artsy,
talkative ones
the same way too,
alright?
If it still doesn't work out,
come back to me.
Keep your head up.
That's how I like you.
Uncle,
let me fill your cup.
Anyway, at Seasons Change Hotel,
you're the big boss.
I really have no other way now.
Please tell me what to do.
Is there a problem?
Didn't they already raise the room fee?
Remember,
we're running a business to make money.
An extra 20 per room per day—
multiply that by a month,
then a year. Do the math.
That makes sense.
But these regular guests—
I brought them in one
by one from the train station
and long-distance bus station
myself.
I've been maintaining these relationships
day after day,
and that's how they became regulars.
If I kick them all out like this,
I just can't feel right about it.
They'll be hurt too.
So,
you'd leave the money on the table
and make me sad instead?
You just
go talk to everyone.
Refund or compensate them however needed.
Hurry up and clear the rooms
for these guests.
Look,
listen to me.
I hired you as the manager
to help me run the place and make money,
not to play the loyal brother
and get emotional with people.
[Guest Room]
Which bastard pulled the switch?
It's so hot.
This power cut...
I never said I wouldn't move.
Little Northeasterner,
are you actually in charge or not?
It's so hot.
Is there no end to this?
No warning for the power outage,
and now the water's cut too.
I just put shampoo in my hair.
Line up.
[Seasons Change Hotel]
[Emergency Water Supply]
Make room.
The neighborhood committee
sent water for everyone.
Over here.
Bring the booze.
After tonight,
we're moving to Seasons Change Hotel.
Is that good?
Good!
I found a place for you.
Bottom up!
-CBottom up.
-Bottom up.
Mrs. Xu, Mrs. Wang,
are you leaving today too?
Luo, here are the keys.
Okay.
If you forgot anything,
just give me a call.
I'll mail it all to you.
Luo, you stay safe too.
Don't worry.
They can't do anything to me.
Take care, sis.
Okay.
Bye.
Seasons Change Hotel will always be there.
Lei.
Thank you.
Mr. Xu.
Have you packed your things?
[Guest Room]
What's the rush?
You should be in a rush.
[Guest Room]
I've been thinking about something today.
Do you really believe that guy Feng Tieyou
will actually pay the rent
he promised?
First of all,
our place
is decent,
but it's not exactly
upscale.
With an extra 20 yuan a day,
he could get a proper double room.
Is he a sucker?
Second,
with such a big deal
and so many people involved,
If I were you,
I'd at least ask for a discount.
Discount? I'll break their legs instead.
Exactly.
Third,
if they can't get any advantage on rent,
then they'll try to take advantage
of the rooms instead, right?
What do you mean?
What do I mean?
Upper bunks, lower bunks,
even sleeping on the floor.
They're treating my place
like a sleeper train carriage.
Anyway,
you need to be clear.
No proof, no deal.
See you around, Luo.
Get the hell out of here!
Chen Yan.
Go back to where you came from.
Chen Yan, who wants your junk?
Take it back.
Listen to me, Chen Yan.
Go back to where you came from.
Chen Yan.
Feng Tieyou
really knows he was wrong this time.
Just see him, will you?
Every day now,
he doesn't eat or sleep.
If you keep this up,
this guy is
gonna kick the bucket.
Shut up.
Who is your sister-in-law?
We divorced ages ago.
That's great.
That way he can make
a contribution to society.
You...
Xu.
Sis, you're busy. Go ahead.
I'm not busy.
Come, let me see.
What do you have in your hand?
It's nothing. Just some dried clams.
A specialty from my hometown.
That's wonderful!
I just love dried clams.
I'm telling you,
get the hell out of here.
If I see you again,
he will never see me in this lifetime.
How is setting up the stall going?
Pretty good.
That's why I came
specifically to thank you.
No need to be polite.
Just let me know if you need anything.
Alright, go on.
I'll get back to work then, Sis.
So nice.
Get lost!
Room rates 50% off?
[Cash and payment method]
Right.
No need to shout.
I wrote it. I know.
Didn't you say before
that you'd pay extra for every room?
Now you...
I kicked everyone out,
and now you want a discount?
Did I say that?
Bro, you did say that.
Do I keep my word?
That depends on your mood, Bro.
I'm in a really bad mood right now.
I've booked the whole place.
If I buy a truckload of cabbage,
shouldn't there be a discount?
Just sign it already.
How many people are you planning
to put in one room?
I knew you kid
had a sharp brain.
I've booked the whole house.
I can stuff as many people in as I want.
Right?
Tie,
you can't do this.
Then how should I do it?
If you do this,
I definitely can't agree.
Northeasterner,
you just said it yourself.
The money you lost
from refunding the rooms,
adds up to quite a lot, doesn't it?
Right?
And your reputation for kicking out guests
has already spread.
If I don't take over this place,
will the people living here now
feel at ease?
They'll definitely look for a new place.
Once they find a new place,
they'll pack up and roll out.
Right?
When that happens,
the old ones leave and no new ones come.
Whether it's a loss or a gain,
weigh it in your heart.
Isn't that right?
You don't
need to think about it.
Just sign.
This contract
is out of my hands.
Didn't you say
you were in charge of
Seasons Change Hotel?
Are you playing me?
I may be the manager,
but this inn
doesn't belong to me.
I'm going to check the rooms.
Are you trying to push your luck?
You want to hit me?
Fine.
If you hit me today,
then this becomes a police matter—
and I'll be saved the trouble.
Come on.
Look,
stop trying to scare me
with that police relative.
Business
is about mutual consent.
If you weren't willing,
would we have gotten this far?
I'm afraid the longer you drag this out,
the more you'll lose.
Right?
Hurry up and sign.
Call me when you're done.
♪ Where are you from? ♪
Sis.
♪ My... ♪
Xu.
What brings you here?
How are things with you and Zhuang Zhuang?
We're good. Everything's fine.
I wanted to ask you something.
Do you remember
the dried clams I brought you last time?
I was just about to ask you about that.
Those dried clams were delicious.
Do you have any more?
Yes, I do.
I'll bring some over later.
Okay.
I wanted to ask…
Was there a guy with a big beard that day?
Is he someone you know, sis?
No, he isn't.
You're a grown man.
You're snooping around now?
Sis, I'm not snooping.
It's like this.
A construction team came
to the small hostel
where Zhuang Zhuang and I stay.
They insisted on staying there.
They want to kick out
all the previous guests.
It's totally unreasonable.
These past two days,
they cut off the water and power.
Many guests were afraid of trouble,
so they already left.
But I'm young.
I just don't believe
they can do anything to me.
We live in a society of laws.
That bearded guy.
That bearded guy
is with the construction team too.
I was wondering if you
knew him,
could you...
could you put in a good word?
Xu.
Let me tell you.
About this,
they really went too far.
I know.
It hasn't been easy
for you and Zhuang Zhuang.
But I can't get involved.
Besides,
Beijing is huge.
You can live anywhere.
If you come here for business,
we'll talk business.
If you run into trouble,
I'll still help.
But if you insist on bringing him up,
let's pretend we never met.
♪ Like a butterfly ♪
♪ Flying into my window ♪
Take care.
Luo.
Here's your key.
Call me when you get there.
Will do.
[The rights and obligations
of both parties]
Let's not be strangers.
Mr. Xu.
How did you know
they'd try to underpay me?
And...
How did you guess
they'd make people sleep in
bunk beds?
Whichever character you write,
you have to play that role.
You have to follow
that character's logic
to think things through.
This is called
putting yourself in their shoes.
I really underestimated you.
Fine.
I'm definitely not signing this.
I'd like to see what he can do to me.
If he dares to touch me,
[Guest Room]
I'll get Tang
to handcuff them.
Fine.
Then you've got a feud on your hands.
They have plenty of ways to mess with you.
Then what should I do?
I know it's a trap.
Am I supposed to just jump in?
I might actually have a solution.
What's the plan?
Little Northeasterner.
[Guest Room]
Mr. Tao.
I've got a plan
for the Seasons Change Hotel.
What plan?
I know that because of
the contract,
you're in a tough spot.
Leave it to Room 108.
But Room 108
has nothing to do with him.
Stop keeping me in suspense.
What is it? Tell me.
I'm dying to know.
Do you know why Guo didn’t show up
when that Feng
came over?
Why?
Let's step aside.
Walls have ears.
What's the plan? Just tell me.
[Guest Room]
Let's talk inside. Walls have ears.
Section Chief Wang should be on his way.
Today,
he has a very important meeting.
He mentioned earlier
that he might be a little late today.
So is he coming or not?
He is.
He's a leader. Just wait a bit.
This dump of yours
is actually hosting a big shot?
Tie,
this isn't just some dump.
Not just any hostel
can open in this area.
Luogu Hutong.
This Section Chief Wang
grew up playing with my dad.
My dad helped him get where he is.
Technically,
I should call him Uncle Wang.
You two keep chatting.
I'll go welcome Uncle Wang.
-Let me pick up Uncle Wang.
-His neighbor.
-He watched him grow up.
-You’ve already...
Talked big.
Don't poke me.
What?
It's expensive. What if you break it?
I've already set up the dinner.
If he doesn't show up,
it's going to be hilarious.
It's not funny.
Don't.
I'm telling you.
Today is serious.
It's serious business.
He's here.
Uncle Wang is here.
Section Chief Wang is here.
Hurry.
-Section Chief Wang.
-Uncle Wang. Uncle Wang.
I heard
the District Construction Committee
is repairing roads.
You must be very busy.
You took time
out of your busy schedule
to meet us.
Thank you for your trouble.
They're not here yet?
Tie, hurry up.
We've been waiting for a long time.
Feng Tieyou.
Section Chief Wang, nice to meet you.
Section Chief Wang, please come in. Come.
-Uncle Wang, please come in.
-Section Chief Wang, how about...
Sitting here?
Tired from the morning meeting, huh?
A bit tired.
Why don't you sit back a bit?
I'm afraid you might slide off.
Alright. Alright.
Section Chief Wang.
Have a seat.
What was the meeting about this morning?
Uncle Wang is my neighbor.
Right next door.
I'm asking what the meeting was about.
Well,
it's the leaders' business.
Don't pry.
It was an internal system work meeting.
Internal system work meeting?
Why are you whispering?
We are in the same system.
Section Chief Wang,
listen,
I haven't introduced myself properly.
I
am in engineering.
We're actually in the same system.
Now we know each other.
Since we're acquainted now,
things will be easier.
If you have any instructions
or anything,
just come to me directly.
My men
can handle things smoothly.
Right.
When I first took office,
Luo's hostel
was expanding.
This hostel
has my blood, sweat, and tears.
I get it. Your blood, sweat, and tears.
Section Chief Wang, you're from He'nan?
Isn't he your neighbor?
You're from He'nan too?
No, I...
Well,
Section Chief Wang
lived with his grandparents
since childhood.
It's hard to change a local accent.
Right.
Uncle Wang's ancestral home is He'nan.
Feng.
Don't interrupt.
Let Section Chief Wang finish.
Well,
you see,
I...
before I came here,
I told Liangliang
that today,
we shouldn't be extravagant.
It's a family dinner.
Just a simple family dinner.
Understood.
Right.
Keep it simple.
Okay.
Then
tell the kitchen
to cancel the softshell turtle.
You got it.
The softshell turtle is great.
Great.
Section Chief Wang.
I heard nowadays all the leaders
play golf.
You play too?
I see you're quite tanned.
What's your score?
Fifty strokes?
Forty?
Thir...
No, it can't be lower.
It's not possible.
He plays 5 times a week.
Five times a week?
Is there time for work?
Work is work,
golf is golf.
He plays during lunch break.
During lunch break?
Let's have the food served.
Section Chief Wang.
Let's have another drink.
Drink.
Bottoms up.
Come on, bottoms up.
Come on, young man.
Uncle Wang.
I'll return the toast.
Come on.
Fine, you return the toast. Come on.
Cheers.
No need, no need.
Enough.
Come on.
You can really drink.
Uncle Wang, stop drinking.
Have a rest.
I can't drink anymore.
Rest a bit.
This wine is good.
-Come on.
-Stop it.
Let's have a drink.
Why would I drink with you?
Luo, come.
Drink.
Let's have one.
-Section Chief Wang.
-This wine is good.
Well,
let's drink later.
Tell Tie
why he can't
kick the regulars
out of my hostel.
Right.
What?
The regulars in my hostel
can't be driven away.
Okay, okay.
Tie.
You know what?
At my unit,
the young people
asked me,
"Boss,
why do you protect
Luo's
inn so much?"
Why?
I told them
the young people living there
were all
crouching tigers
and hidden dragons.
Right?
In the future,
they will make it big.
That place
can be treated as a tourist spot.
They can sell tickets.
So,
the young people in this hostel
are my family.
No one is allowed to move in.
No one is allowed to take it.
Calm down.
Section Chief Wang.
Tie.
Do you understand my difficulties?
I got it.
I understand completely.
Section Chief Wang.
You have to stand up for us.
If an official doesn't serve the people,
he might as well go home
and sell sweet potatoes.
I, the magistrate,
laugh with joy.
From a small hole, I pulled out
a big crab.
That's enough. That's enough.
Look at this.
Section Chief Wang.
Isn't that strange?
Enough.
Who can see
me, a petty seventh-rank official?
I can interrogate the Madam.
I don't care for your gold ingots.
When you die, Madam,
I'll buy you a coffin.
Bravo! Bravo!
Bravo!
Uncle...
Uncle Wang is tired.
I'm tired. I'm tired.
Rest a bit.
Bravo!
Backswing.
Swing.
Watch it go.
Now that is golf.
You know?
Look at you.
Feet apart.
Stick your butt out.
You think I'm not talking to you?
Feet apart.
We've had food and drinks.
I paid the bill.
I've seen enough of this show.
It hasn't been easy for you three.
Little Northeasterner.
You're playing tricks on me.
Acting.
Let me tell you.
I'll go to
your little hostel tomorrow.
If you don't sign the contract,
I'll tear it down.
Section Chief Wang, right?
Why are you dodging? Come closer.
You sing He'nan Opera well. Not bad.
Put your glasses on.
I can't stand that darn face of yours.
I wasn't talking about you.
Put the glasses down.
Stop acting.
Aren't you a neighbor?
Where are you from?
Zhengzhou.
No, Xuanwu.
Look at you all.
Act. Keep acting.
Watch them.
Make them play.
Keep playing.
Until they can't lift their chopsticks.
That's when they stop.
Don't worry, bro.
Backswing.
Swing.
Watch it go.
Backswing.
Swing.
Watch it go.
This is
a nightmare.
Mr. Tao.
Take a break.
Haven't you played enough?
I have to master
this technique.
Otherwise, I suffered for nothing today.
I'm telling you two,
don't tell anyone about this.
Take it to the grave.
That meal was so embarrassing.
You're all back.
What did you eat to get this drunk?
Did you get the job done?
We seemed to
be eating a softshell turtle.
A softshell turtle?
You ate quite well.
No, I mean the job.
It's really a setback.
He suffered it.
Can you do anything right?
He's here.
You're here, Bro.
Everyone's here?
Yes.
Tie.
No music?
Come on.
Bring the booze.
Thanks, Bro.
Whose girlfriend is this?
The new girl.
What's her name?
Hui.
Hurry up with the skewers.
Okay.
Who are you?
How does it taste?
It's okay.
Bro, there's no one else.
Just him.
You've got guts, kid.
Coming here alone to start trouble?
Looking for a beating?
I've told you everything I can.
Feng Tieyou
has made mistakes,
but it was all for his brothers.
He's all bluster.
You don't need to be afraid of him.
If it weren't for the child
wanting to call him Dad,
I wouldn't have
held out any hope for him.
Take this.
This is as far as I can help you.
Where did you get this?
He's asking you a question.
What's your relationship with Chen Yan?
I call her Sis.
Break it up.
Have you seen her and the child?
Did Chen Yan
tell you to tell me anything?
Not really.
Tie, I came here
for my own business.
I live at the Seasons Change Hostel.
Oh, that.