[LIVE UP TO YOUR YOUTH]
[Episode 4]
Come on.
Look. I braised these myself.
-You're being too kind.
-Go ahead.
That's really too kind of you.
It's my pleasure.
Go ahead and try it.
Thank you so much.
Here. Try some.
-Duck tongue.
-It's okay—
You know the motto
of Wenzhou people?
"No matter how poor,
never work for others.
No matter how hungry, never beg for food.
We'd rather sleep on the floor
than not be our own boss."
You're young,
always busy and never tired.
You'll definitely make it.
What you just said,
could you say that again?
Why would you want to write that down?
I am a screenwriter.
When I hear something interesting,
I write it down.
Really? A screenwriter?
He's a screenwriter.
I'm studying to become a singer.
We just arrived in Beijing.
We're setting up a stall
to make ends meet.
We're in it for the long haul.
Not asking your family for money.
That's great.
Such good kids.
I really should
give you some proper advice then.
We Wenzhou people
have our own formula for doing business.
The way you're displaying things now
isn't quite right.
Let me show you.
"If you display it,
people will buy it."
You should have them high.
Right?
"If you display a lot,
people will check them out.
If the goods are neat,
the customers will be pleased.
If the quality is good,
the business will last till you're old."
Right?
Makes sense.
These here
aren't enough.
Not enough to choose from.
Come on, have them out.
Put them here.
Okay.
Right.
Don't make it too crowded though.
It'll make them look cheap.
Look at this one.
This is a great brand,
you shouldn't put it here.
Nobody will see it.
Let's hang it up.
Yes, hang it up.
Exactly.
What did I just say?
"If you display it,
people will buy it."
And?
"If you display a lot,
people will check them out."
Right.
Here, let me put this up for you.
And also,
the most important thing—
you need to hawk your wares.
Which of you two can do that?
You?
I... I'll do it.
Yeah?
Alright, here we go.
Arm up, hand on hip.
Check this out! Don't miss out!
Louder! Louder!
Check this out!
Don't miss out!
Head up, chest out. Confidence!
Confidence!
That's it!
Check this out! Don't miss out!
Come and take a look!
Good.
How much?
Twenty yuan per piece.
Twenty.
Twenty per piece!
Check this out! Don't miss out!
Very promising.
You won't get ripped off!
Thank you so much.
We're both from Wenzhou—you're so welcome.
Twenty. It's a bargain.
This is from Guangzhou.
A silk blend.
Great quality. Wrinkle-free.
-Here comes business.
-You can try it on.
Feel free to try it on.
This looks really nice.
Yes!
This one is 20 yuan.
Check this out! Don't miss out!
You won't regret it!
You won't get ripped off!
Why are you cleaning it here?
You can't clean it here.
Leave.
Okay.
I'm in the way, aren't I?
Why are you still sitting there? Move!
Move it!
I am, I am.
I am moving.
Do you need your range hood cleaned?
No, I don't.
Go clean it outside.
Okay.
You're blocking the entrance.
Thank you.
How much is this one?
This one?
It's our first day of business today—
what about 45?
Okay, 45.
Okay.
Does it fit well?
It fits perfectly.
Let me tighten this for you.
Okay.
Take the money.
Here.
Thank you.
Please pack this one up for us.
Okay.
-Okay. Thank you.
-Just a second.
I'll put it here.
Very nice.
Okay.
It really suits you.
Thank you.
Here.
Here, I'll take it.
Would you like
a denim shirt for yourself?
Yeah.
Not enough money left.
Okay.
Next time then.
Next time.
-Okay.
-Next time.
Tell your friends about us.
Will do.
Twenty, thirty, forty—
I'll be right back.
Five.
My hero.
Thanks, boss.
So, starting today,
our little stall
is officially up and running.
Partner, looking forward
to working with you.
Me too.
But let's get this straight first.
I have classes from Monday to Friday.
I can only come on weekends.
If I hear from the film studio,
I have to go too.
But I'll ask for leave in advance.
No problem.
Mr. Zheng said
I need to take care of my voice.
I'll handle styling and sales,
and you do the hawking.
Sure thing.
But while I do that,
I might also jot down notes
about life from time to time.
No problem.
Just say you're bookkeeping.
We'll closely work together
to negotiate a good price.
How do we split the money?
Five hundred in total;
400 from me, 100 from you.
Let's split it 20-80.
Who gets 20 and who gets 80?
I get 80 and you get 20, obviously.
That won't do.
No?
I should get less.
I borrowed my 100 from you.
If I wanted more, I'd be doing it alone.
I won't take advantage of you.
That 100 yuan,
you can pay me back later.
Let's keep things separate.
Business is business.
As befits someone from Wenzhou—
very shrewd.
Song?
Song, Little Song?
Little Song?
Little Song,
my child.
-Keep it down, we're sleeping.
-Keep it down.
What are you doing this early?
Zongbao,
Little Song...
My son, Little Song, is missing.
I can't find him.
Good riddance. He stank.
What are you saying?
Did you get rid of him?
I don't have time for that.
Keep looking.
Little Song?
I did.
I've looked
literally everywhere, Zongbao.
-Little Song?
-Song?
Song?
Was he here last night?
Yes.
This... this is the dinner
I prepared for him last night.
Might have gone out at midnight.
Go check the hallway.
Anyone got up last night?
I didn't.
Me neither.
What about you, Xu Shengli?
I went to the bathroom.
It was him then.
You came back after midnight, no?
Okay, case solved.
The squirrel
got out of the cage
by itself last night.
Then the door
opened and closed,
and it went out to play.
Let's go look in the hallway.
Was it you, Xu Shengli?
I'm talking to you!
Was it you?
What are you doing?
-I'm sleeping. Can you guys talk later?
-Zongbao.
Zongbao, you probably don't know,
one day when neither of you were around,
he...
he said Little Song has germs
and isn't sanitary.
He's never liked
my son!
Can you guys talk later?
Get up.
No.
I said get up!
I won't!
Get up now!
Zongbao, it's Little Song!
I knew it was you, Xu Shengli!
Move!
Those nightmares in 108—
what are they up to now?
Coming through. Move, move.
Sounds like a homicide.
Call the police.
Don't talk nonsense.
Open the door!
It's me, Little Northeasterner.
If someone really gets killed,
we're not going to stay here anymore.
I'm going to get the key.
Officer Tang is here!
Little Northeasterner!
Mayday!
Officer Tang is here!
You guys are going to
ruin my business!
Can't you manage
your little hostel properly?
It's causing trouble every day!
I come here eight times a week,
you know?
Right, right.
[The memory lives on, the legacy endures,
forever with us]
Xu Shengli.
Have you been here a week yet?
The police have come twice already.
I really regret
bringing you here
from the train station.
Whatever is going on in 108—
just let me know today
if you can sort it out.
If this place is too small
for a big shot like you,
I won't try to keep you.
For six yuan a day for the bed
I get 600 yuan's worth of hassle.
Can anyone stand this?
Sorry for the trouble.
I'm really sorry.
I'll figure something out.
My condolences.
And another thing.
It's not easy for anyone out here.
Don't back people into a corner.
Even a worm will turn!
Zongbao,
Liangliang,
Little Song was just like you.
You're all my closest family.
He came to Beijing with me
all the way from Shanxi.
We traveled thousands of miles together.
Okay.
In so many lonely moments,
he was there with me.
[The memory lives on, the legacy endures,
forever with us]
On so many cold nights,
he warmed my heart
with his warmth.
In the scorching summer,
its playfulness
brought me true relief.
Song...
we were friends.
We were father and son.
[The memory lives on, the legacy endures,
forever with us]
We were fellow sufferers
and family.
But since you've been with me,
we've only shared hardships—
we never got to share any good time.
I haven't been able
to give you a single day of happiness,
and now... now you've been killed
by a bad guy.
-Okay. Okay.
-Here's my word—
if I don't avenge you,
I'm not a man.
Okay, okay...
My condolences.
Cao Ye,
I really didn't mean to.
I really don't know
when it got onto my bed.
But...
I did crush it.
I apologize.
Okay now.
I'm someone who
doesn't usually drink.
Take this as my apology.
What do you mean "take this as"?
Even at a grave, you pour three cups.
One cup?
Who are you trying to impress?
Is this how you Shandong people do things?
Don't... Stop, stop.
Why are you covering my mouth?
Tell me then.
What do I have to do
to put this behind us?
Listen, Xu Shengli.
In this world,
it's not like for everything that happens,
you just say "sorry,"
and I have to forgive you.
Alright now.
I don't accept your apology.
I don't accept it!
A life for a life.
That was a life.
A life!
Okay, okay, okay.
A life, yeah?
My condolences.
Why are you drinking—
Let him drink.
But... the liquor...
He's finishing it!
Leave it.
Alright, alright, alright.
Stop drinking. Stop drinking!
Hey, stop drinking.
You'll harm yourself...
If this is not enough,
I'll go buy some more.
No, no, don't.
I'm laying my life down
right here today.
Enough with your drunken fit!
You were asking
how to put this behind us?
Fine. I'll tell you, Xu Shengli.
Bring Little Song
back to me safe and sound,
and I'll put this behind us.
Can you do that?
You can't!
I know,
you guys have a problem with me.
You think I'm arrogant.
I admit it.
When I first came here,
I was arrogant.
But I have never
looked down on anyone.
We met by chance.
Getting to live under the same roof
is serendipity.
Why can't we just
live in peace...
in peace...
Shengli?
You're going to get yourself sick.
You two are really something, aren't you?
A Beijinger
and a Shanxi guy
got a Shandong guy this wasted.
-Going to brag for the rest of your lives?
-He drank it himself.
Xu Shengli.
A call for you.
What's going on?
He drank
half a bottle himself.
Xu Shengli.
A call for you.
Shengli.
It's Director Weng.
What...
What's going on now,
my lords?
Zhuang...
Why are you here?
Director Weng called me yesterday?
No, no.
What are you doing?
I have to call him back.
What are you doing? Sit down!
Sit down. Are you out of your mind?
You got yourself acute alcohol poisoning,
are you aware?
You had a fever over 40 degrees.
Even your trachea got swollen.
I still have to call him back...
When you're back later today,
can you call Director Weng back for me?
Lie down first.
Don't worry.
I'll explain it to him when I'm back.
But please don't tell him
that I'm hospitalized because of drinking.
Now you're scared?
Why did you drink so much?
Did the guys in 108
force you to drink?
No.
It has nothing to do with them.
Drinking so much when you can't.
Reckless.
I think we've taken this
a bit too far.
How so?
Are you betraying us?
No, no.
It's just, after all this trouble,
I'm feeling kind of guilty.
Zongbao.
Well,
one thing led to another,
and we ended up here.
He's in the hospital now,
isn't he?
Saying this now...
is too late.
Maybe in the future,
if there's any
Tom, Dick, or Harry
who joins us,
we can give him some—
You didn't knock.
Is that polite?
With unreasonable people,
there's no need for politeness.
Who's being unreasonable?
Is it fun for you guys
to bully people all the time?
Do you have to drive people out
for your own enjoyment?
We're all from out of town.
Is this necessary?
He's very sick right now.
You're all
responsible for that.
You should pay the medical bills.
Discussing money is a bit too much.
Well... my son, Little Song,
was crushed to death by him.
I didn't ask him for money.
Who's responsible?
Who's paying?
He drank the liquor himself.
Why should we pay
half the medical bills?
Right.
Besides,
he grinds his teeth, farts,
smacks his lips,
and talks in sleep.
Who could stand all that?
Exactly.
If you can stand it,
let him stay in your room.
Tell me about it.
So he...
he just didn't sleep well for one night.
He drank a bit and got like that.
But what about us on a daily basis? Right?
Exactly.
Are you going to sort this or not?
Are you going to sort this?
Don't think just because
you're a girl,
you can yell at us
and we have to
indulge you
and put up
with you.
A girl gets to
blow up
and kill?
I'm curious to see, here in Beijing—
What...
What are you doing?
Zhuang Zhuang!
I... I...
You planning to move out of here
or what?
Such a waste!
Zhuang Zhuang.
Stop walking.
Messing with a young master of Beijing—
you'll have nowhere to go in this city.
I don't care if you have anywhere to go.
You have to pay for that jar
of chili sauce.
You...
What now?
What do we do?
Let's go back and discuss.
What are you doing? Why are you shouting?
Why are you at our door?
Isn't this Miss Celebrity?
I was just about to report to you.
Our wish
is about to come true.
What are you talking about?
That annoying guy in our room
is moving out soon.
This one in your room
won't stay long either.
She can't leave.
She is my sister.
If you two dare to bully my sister,
you're dead.
Wait, your...
-Her sister?
-Your sister?
How did she become her sister?
You've fully recovered?
My vitality is surging back.
A registered parcel for you.
Let it surge back slowly.
Or just don't hold me
responsible for anything.
Sign here.
I know nothing about scriptwriting,
but looks like you're getting
better and better at it.
I mean, look,
these letters with Capital Film Studio
are going back and forth.
Two cents for radishes.
Get me a bunch a those.
Why are you here again?
Our backlog of scripts
have all been sent back.
Didn't you receive them?
Mr. Wu,
I'm not looking for Director Weng today.
I'm looking for you.
But why are you looking for me?
I received the script.
I just wanted to ask you,
did you read this script?
Isn't it obvious?
Just tell me, did you read it or not?
Look, I...
Well... what do you want?
Within the script,
I glued three places.
I don't assume you read it
and glued them back, or did you?
Mr. Wu,
everyone,
I really regard you as my seniors.
I just hoped
that you could give me some guidance
and advice.
That's all.
I am just
a young man with a dream.
I so longed to meet
mentors like you,
seniors who could guide me.
Like seeing a lighthouse in the dark,
showing me the way.
Are you not willing to shed
even that little bit of light?
What dream? What lighthouse?
This is a studio.
We have a heavy workload.
Young man,
I'll tell you the truth.
Director Weng never asked us
to read your script.
Do you understand?
If you want to wait,
go ahead and wait.
I don't mind.
But don't wait in the office.
We're all just trying
to make a living.
No one is here to play house with you.
Young man,
take the script back
and polish it some more,
and send it to us again.
Trust me,
we will definitely read it.
Unbelievable.
Reading it again?
How many times have you
read it now?
You must know it by heart now.
Fancy playing a role?
I haven't finished it yet.
I have to say,
my son wrote a pretty interesting script.
As I read it,
I really got into it.
I think you are interesting.
-Why?
-Well,
when he was home,
you were always against him.
Now he's gone,
you tore up his script,
and now you taped it
back together to read it.
I mean, that's
all in the past now,
can't you just let it go?
I tore it up, yes,
but now I've taped it back together,
okay?
Am I not allowed to make mistakes?
Fine, fine.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm selling these books.
You... you can't sell these.
These are all his things.
If he comes back and can't find them,
he'll be upset.
Is he coming back?
Why wouldn't he come back?
Where else would he go?
Didn't you drive him away?
So what?
You're going to drive me away too,
and be...
and be the only one left in this house?
I'm not trying to drive you away.
I'm just saying,
all these books in here,
you bought him every single one of them.
Throughout middle school and high school,
you bought him whatever he wanted.
Now he's grown up
and wants to write scripts,
you tell him,
writing doesn't pay the bills.
You even tore up his script.
Now he's gone to Beijing,
and you're suddenly reading the script.
Aren't you saying one thing
but doing another?
I tore it up, yes.
But I've taped it back together, no?
I've fixed it. Okay?
Okay, okay.
You just won't let this go.
Fine.
Alright, alright.
Stop... stop this.
Let's just eat, okay?
I've got it all ready for you.
Going to Beijing...
It's not that I don't support him.
But what kind of place is Beijing?
It's full of talented people.
I'm just worried about him.
I'm worried he'll face rejection there.
So,
I'd rather he curse me in his heart,
than have him suffer.
No parent
would not want their child to do well.
Alright.
I'll go get your food.
Can I help you with anything?
No need.
Don't be mad.
What are you mad about?
Honestly.
You keep the light on all night.
Trying to keep us all up
until we drop?
It's just a light.
I'll adjust it for you,
okay?
What good
is all the whining?
Seriously? Isn't that selfish?
That's how you do it?
How is Zongbao
supposed to sleep?
You should adjust it like this.
You like the light so much?
Can't live without it, yeah?
Then shine it on yourself.
Right on your face. There.
Hey, what are you doing?
The light's gone, noise is on?
Shut your mouth.
-Are you done?
-Is the noise my fault?
Listen!
I quit my secure job
at the state factory
to come to Beijing.
Director Weng
is my lifeline.
I missed his call.
That is my fate.
If I can't see Director Weng,
I won't know
what to do next.
But I have to stay in Beijing.
I have to support myself.
So I sell clothes during the day,
and I write at night.
Whether you can put up with me
is your business.
And I don't know how you guys
make a living.
But let me ask you—
if someone
tries to ruin your livelihood—
tries to ruin your livelihood,
would you fight them to the death?
Honestly, you two.
Everyone has a place in their heart
that is
more important than their life.
You can't touch that.
You two know that better than anyone.
All of us
left home
on our own.
It hasn't been easy.
Right?
This kid is a good kid.
Look how angry he was just now.
But he didn't touch your sax.
He didn't touch your painting.
Let's just let it go.
Okay?
Screenwriter Xu, that speech just now
was quite impassioned.
I'm sorry.
I got a little carried away.
You should be passionate.
How can you create without passion?
Right.
Why are you still up?
I came up for a stroll.
If it's too noisy down there,
I think this place is nice.
It's quiet.
Perfect for writing scripts.
Yes...
Here.
Try it.
This...
I...
Does it feel right?
This... this works.
Work hard.
Make a name for yourself.
Show everyone what you can do.
Very nice.
You look like a model student.
Work hard.
Get famous soon,
and pay me back.
Okay.
Goodbye, Teacher.
[Yingkelai Beijing-Style Cuisine]
Honey,
get some spiced beef.
[Food Pickup]
Hello,
two bowls of porridge and
four fried dough sticks.
[Beijing-Style Homemade Dishes]
Let's sit here.
[Food Pickup]
Hello, a bowl of soy milk
and two fried dough sticks.
[Yingkelai Beijing-Style Cuisine]
Throughout Russia,
over half of all the "Bulajis"
were imported by me.
You don't know what a "Bulaji" is?
A "Bulaji" is a dress.
The dresses... You...
[Honest Owner That Returns Lost Items]
Listen,
I make tens of thousands a day.
Would I default on that little bit?
I'm still answering your call,
I'm still here.
Hello? I can't hear you. Hello?
Hello?
I can't hear you. Talk later.
Hounding me all day long.
What can I get you?
Mr. Tao,
don't you recognize me?
Jun?
You changed your hairstyle.
Wasn't it slicked back?
I'll get a perm afterwards.
Where's your own son, Liangliang?
That little brat.
I don't know where he went.
Probably went to do art.
As long as he's alive.
He doesn't come here as often as you do.
I'm visiting you on his behalf.
What can I get you?
The usual.
About 150 grams of beef.
And noodles with soybean paste.
I don't have change. Only hundreds.
Next time then.
Generous.
Don't be shy to ask next time.
A bottle of soda.
You sure can eat and drink.
I'm off, Mr. Tao.
Money is on the table.
Check this out. How is it?
Why are you
wearing a raincoat on a sunny day?
I'm wearing a raincoat on the outside,
and a short-sleeved shirt inside.
I'm trying to display our clothes
as much as possible.
Don't be silly. Take it off.
Aren't you hot?
Not at all.
Look.
I'm not hot.
Funny dude, huh?
Don't mind him.
Take a look at the clothes.
I like this one.
Check this out!
Don't miss out!
Come visit again.
Okay.
-Sure.
-Here.
Thank you.
Are you hot?
No.
Take it off. You'll get heatstroke.
No, no. I'm not hot.
Is there any water?
Water?
I want some water.
Did we finish our water?
No water left?
-Forget it. It's fine.
-Let me buy you a bottle.
It's fine.
Really, it's fine.
You look like you've been poisoned.
-There will be water later.
-Put away the money.
It's raining.
It's raining!
Boss.
Here, put this on.
Hurry, hurry. The clothes.
Okay.
Done.
I'll show you a magic trick.
Watch closely.
Come on.
Raincoats!
No extra charge in the rain!
Over here!
Come on!
Raincoats!
No extra charge in the rain!
One for me.
All kinds of styles
and colors!
One for me.
Five yuan. Five yuan each.
Here.
Over here.
Five yuan.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Here.
Come buy raincoats!
Come on!
Xu.
It's wet.
Pack our stuff up, quick.
Pack all these clothes up.
Pack them up. Put them inside.
Here.
Xu.
You two
really came out on top
on the street today.
How much did you make?
I haven't finished calculating yet.
Tell me now,
how did you come up with this idea?
It was a gift from above.
Playing mysterious with me? Seriously.
Spit it out.
The weather forecast.
I checked the weather forecast.
It said it's going to rain
for the next few days.
I remembered no one sold raincoats
in this market.
So I decided to stock some and try.
Aren't you clever. Seriously.
You made money.
Shouldn't you treat me
to a drink?
Of course.
I want something ice-cold.
Okay.
Great.
Get one for Zhuang Zhuang too.
For sure.
Tell me.
What's going on between you two?
We're business partners.
Business partners? Who are you kidding?
It's true.
I saw you two just now,
working in the rain like that.
My mind,
whoosh, went straight back
to when I was young.
Speaking of back then,
I had so many guys chasing me too.
That was awesome.
Really?
Of course.
Go on and tell me about it.
Anyway, good men are scarce.
Grab him when you see one.
The next one might not be as good.
Here.
-You're so beautiful.
-It's chilled.
Open your eyes wide and take a good look.
What are you talking about?
I'm saying you have big eyes.
My eyes aren't big.
Your eyes are.
I know.
That's why I was so popular.
Look at him, obsessed with money.
Finished calculating yet?
We made 250.
That much?
It suits you well.
Boss,
Little Northeasterner snatched
a lot of customers
at the train station again today.
The owners of the other hostels
have begged me several times.
They want to buy you dinner
and discuss how to deal with
this Little Northeasterner.
Do I look like I'm starving?
They buy me a meal,
and I'll do their bidding?
Understood, Boss.
I'll go press them
and see
just how sincere they really are.
Tell them,
we are out here to make money.
The greater the sincerity,
the bigger the job.
If they are sincere enough,
I can uproot Seasons Change
entirely.
Let's go.
Take care, Boss.
Listen up!
You all look like decent people
on the surface.
He's starting again.
But you act
with no manners!
Throwing trash everywhere.
You just don't
treat this place like your own home.
If you piss me off,
I'll kick you all out
to sleep on the streets.
Calm down.
It's bad for your health.
You two went out to eat?
Didn't I tell you?
You need to be careful.
People will get jealous.
Jealous of what?
We made money from doing business.
Can't we celebrate?
I even brought you a dish.
Forget it. I'll have it.
I was saying that for your own good.
Those people inside,
looking all shifty,
are all tough nuts.
If I don't scold them every few days,
they'll turn the place upside down.
Mr. Xu,
I see you've fully recovered.
Don't take it to heart.
Don't lower yourself to their level.
How about this—
I'll switch you to a different room.
No need.
I'm digging my heels in.
I'm staying put.
I'm staying in that room.
Are you sure?
Well...
Mr. Xu,
just let me know if you need anything.
This liquor,
and these dishes—
as Xu said,
he got these specially for us.
Here.
It's not poisoned.
Did you have any?
I had a bite
of everything.
Just a small bite.
He's being too nice for no reason.
He must be up to no good.
What are you talking about?
This is good food.
It's already been reheated once.
If we don't eat it now,
it won't taste good reheated again.
"Hoeing millet in the midday sun,
every grain is hard work."
If we throw this away,
it would be a real pity.
Corruption and waste
are the biggest crimes.
Come on.
If you put it that way...
No.
What I mean is,
Zongbao
has already had a bite of everything.
We can't let him be
the only one compromised,
right?
If he eats and we don't,
it makes us look disloyal.
So you mean
we should share the blessings
and the burden?
Just eat.
Wait a second.
What?
Just like Zongbao,
we'll only take one bite of each.
Okay.
That bite is way too big.
It counts as a bite if I can stuff it in.
Don't waste it.
You're wasting it.
Oh my god.
You...
Why are you eating so much, too?
This is your second round.
That was just a taste test.
Now I'm really eating.
You two got
all the slices.
I'm only left with crumbs.
It's tasty.
Drink up.
Come on.
Cheers.
Don't move!
Is he delirious?
Or is he awake?
He's keeping score.
You're awake?
Then the three of us
should get some more sleep.
I'll go drain my bladder first.
Is it good?