[NORTHWARD]
[Episode 31]
Hit me all you want.
I won't fight back. Come on.
Does it kill you to
stay out of trouble?
You didn't even ask me why.
I don't care why!
You beat someone up
and they posted it online right away!
I had a hard time stopping it from trending!
He didn't see us as human.
He deserved it!
Shao Xingchi.
Even now,
do you still not get the severity of the situation?
I'm ignorant.
I don't understand the strange rules
of your big company!
Then
you can ask me.
Forget it, Xie Wanghe.
I wish you'd hear me out instead.
Go ahead.
I'm listening.
Let's hear what grievances you have.
I hope
that everyone who follows me
can be treated as human beings,
be accepted
and respected.
But you...
you just treat them as tools
for profit and expanding capital.
And then?
You weren't like this before.
You were tough on the outside but soft-hearted.
You were kind to everyone!
I thought even if nobody understood me,
you would!
So what?
We can't talk if you're going to be like this.
Listen up.
Do you know
how many job opportunities
Bee alone provides in a year?
Do you know how many people
make a living by delivering food?
I understand you have a kind heart,
but you can't be selfish!
Back then,
you said you wanted to be the station chief.
I used stock options as collateral
to make that happen.
But what did you do?
You led everyone with a heart of gold
and almost
ran the station into the ground.
And your subordinates couldn't make money!
All you talk about is making money.
What about your conscience?
Is making money that important?
When you're very rich,
you have the luxury to think money isn't important.
But when everyone
is waiting for their next meal,
money
is very important!
I know
you mean well.
And then?
They don't appreciate it.
Then you
pity their misfortune
and bemoan their lack of ambition.
You feel your well intentions are being treated like dirt.
Do you feel particularly wronged?
Delivery riders are humans too.
They also need care
and someone to protect
their legal rights,
you know?
Did I withhold their pay?
I even enhanced their commission and rewards!
I provide job opportunities.
If they take the job, they have to work.
If they don't like it, they can leave.
No one is forcing them to work themselves to death.
The rules you set are inducing them to do that,
you know?
Listen up.
In a competitive society,
you're compensated according
to the effort you put in.
We're adults now!
We're not kids playing house!
We still can't satisfy everyone!
Shao Xingchi.
We're both Beijing drifters.
After all these years,
you know how much we've suffered.
That's why I especially treasure this opportunity.
I want to do a good job
and prove myself.
But what about you?
With the opportunity I fought hard for,
you want to realize a utopia.
No problem.
I support you.
I hope your dreams come true.
But...
use your own money and resources to play house
from now on.
I wish you success!
Where are you?
What are you doing?
I'll come find you.
Don't.
Where are you?
[Haikuo]
Guess.
I'll tell you if you guess right.
What's wrong with you?
We broke up.
Who dumped whom?
What do you think?
Why?
Speak up.
Because I'm poor.
What else could it be?
Did you tell her you have stock options now?
Do I need money to keep her?
What else do you think you could rely on?
Your good looks?
Your abs?
Do you have any?
Stop trying to test human nature.
It's pointless.
Cut the crap.
What's the matter?
Xingchi and I...
fell out.
Aren't you surprised?
How many times have you two fallen out?
And you always say,
"I'll never see him again!"
And what happens?
This time
might be different.
This incident
has seriously
damaged our company's image.
Public opinion is spreading the issue.
Mr. Meng.
Come in.
The Series D funding was about to be finalized,
but because of Shao Xingchi's incident,
it's been delayed again.
I'm sorry.
He's already resigned.
As for his issue,
I'll handle it appropriately.
It's about time.
That bastard
is a bad apple.
Alright.
Let's talk business.
Lately,
the competition with Yuntu has intensified.
The pressure is immense.
I plan to apply for subsidies.
Finally caved in, huh?
Who was it
who insisted on not taking subsidies?
Times have changed.
This time, the subsidies
aren't for the delivery riders
but for the businesses.
We'll subsidize three to five yuan each
for businesses who've worked with us.
Also,
we'll require them
to sign exclusive contracts with us.
That won't be easy.
I've done some research.
It's promising.
Haikuo has analyzed it based on big data.
Your buddy again?
Can we trust him
not to harm us this time?
I firmly believe
it'll work out this time.
Who'll be in charge of this ground promotion?
Give me some time
to find someone suitable.
Don't end up choosing another buddy of yours again.
For a big company at our level,
nepotism
cannot happen again,
okay?
Mr. Qiu, what's your zodiac sign?
Dog.
No wonder.
What do you mean?
You bark madly
and like to bite people.
Have you had your shots?
Xie Wanghe.
Are you okay?
Do you believe I can bite you to death?
Mr. Qiu.
In the business world,
it's about capabilities.
Tattling not only fails to accomplish anything
but also makes others look down on you.
I agree.
I know I'm not very capable.
If I can't succeed, I'll make sure you don't either.
Behave yourself.
Don't you dare cross me.
[He Tianming]
Hello?
Mr. Xie.
There's trouble at the station. Come quickly!
Guys!
We're done here. Let's go!
All of you, come back!
You can't leave!
Move!
Move, don't stop me!
Get off!
Get off the bike!
Let go!
Move!
What's all this fuss about?
Mr. Xie.
I quit!
Why can't I leave?
This bike isn't yours!
You didn't stop the others.
Why just me?
What's going on?
Mr. Xie.
It's like this.
You... Get back!
Explain!
After Station Chief Shao's incident,
many riders quit
and even took the bikes with them.
Back then,
Station Chief Shao didn't collect
deposits from them
as they were young and poor.
Are you serious?
Before,
Station Chief Shao vouched for them.
I think he can get them back.
He has resigned.
Now,
you'll be the chief of Station 203.
I can't do it.
It's not up to you!
[Top Ten Exemplary Stations in China]
Bravo!
[Fenghua Express]
[Loading Area]
Bravo, bravo.
Xia.
Congrats.
Thank you, Mr. Luo.
Bravo!
The company
not only gave your station
a certificate of honor
but also awarded you 100,000 yuan.
-Bravo!
-Thank you.
[RMB 100,000]
That's great!
Bravo!
Xia.
Don't bother. I'll be off soon.
Why the rush?
Thank you.
Besides giving you
the bonus and certificate,
I'm here on behalf of the company
to invite you back to HQ
to conduct training
with your experience
on business management.
Is it long-term or...
Let's sit and talk.
It's like this.
Be it the training or the PR department,
you can join anytime
to take charge of culture development.
The senior management came to a unanimous consensus
that you're the best candidate.
I really want to go.
You have concerns?
Don't worry
about the compensation.
It'll definitely be improved.
I don't have concerns.
I have to go back to my hometown.
Your hometown?
Honghuai City
in Jiangsu.
A small city by the canal.
Why so sudden?
Did something happen at home?
I've been drifting in Beijing for too long.
I feel a bit empty.
But thank you,
and I appreciate the company's recognition.
This certificate
[Certificate of Honor]
puts a perfect end
to my life as a Beijing drifter.
[Fenghua Express]
Are you getting a promotion?
But I didn't agree.
Why not?
I have more important things to do here.
Auntie,
add two more main dishes for dinner.
Let's celebrate.
Sure.
What do you want to eat?
I'm fine with anything.
Make something everyone likes.
Mom, Fenghua.
Tianming?
Back so early?
Xingchi is in trouble.
Eating fried bean sauce noodles in a bar.
What refined taste.
What's wrong?
Xie Wanghe came here last time too.
He said the same thing as you.
Don't tell me you're here to...
help us patch things up?
I'm not that idle.
He and I...
haven't been in touch for a long time.
Why?
We're busy.
But weren't you two...
Weren't what?
Nothing.
Xie Wanghe and I just aren't friends anymore.
We're not enemies.
That's just how it is.
So what do you want to do next?
I have a buddy who opened a shop,
modifying off-road vehicles.
I want to give it a try.
Is it profitable?
I don't know. We'll see.
How about...
you come work with me?
First, when loading, put small items inside the vehicle
and secure large items on the roof.
Second,
during scanning, pay attention to sorting loose items
and residential items.
Third,
[Sorting Area (Urban Area)]
report problems you can't solve
to the problem department promptly.
It's that simple.
I believe you'll be set in one afternoon.
[Zhongguancun South Road]
Ms. Xia, you really want to recruit me, huh?
What, you want to back out?
I wouldn't dare.
Then get to work.
If you don't do well, you won't get dinner tonight.
You've really been a boss for too long.
You're getting more and more
like Liang's dad.
[Fenghua Express]
[Express delivery makes your life more efficient]
Okay, okay. I was wrong, I was wrong.
Do you surrender?
I surrender!
You're breaking my neck!
If I'd known it'd be like this, I wouldn't have come.
Even more brutal than Xie Wanghe.
Brutal?
Wanghe?
You said I'm brutal?
Don't like that?
I'll say something you'd prefer.
How about I call you cold-blooded?
You can say it to my face.
But talking behind someone's back
isn't classy.
[Fenghua Express]
[We're the experts in shipping parcels]
You know his temper.
Will it kill you to lay off him?
[Fenghua Express]
Wanghe.
Wanghe!
Wanghe, wait up.
I can't run anymore.
Fenghua, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Here.
Have some soup.
Feeling better?
Why are you so weak now?
Out of breath after a few steps?
I'm just a bit anemic.
It's your fault for running so fast.
I couldn't catch up.
I almost couldn't catch my breath.
Xingchi wasn't happy working for you,
so I asked him to come help me.
He caused such a big mess,
but he still won't admit it.
He's unhappy?
Yes.
Hitting a customer is a bit too much.
A bit?
It's way too much.
If it were me, I'd fire him too.
I didn't fire him.
He resigned on his own.
Because of this incident,
I have to keep my head down at the company.
I'm swamped with work stuff every day,
and I still have to chase after bikes for him.
Why should I have to do that?
So you think you've done nothing wrong?
What did I do wrong?
He's your buddy.
When he does something wrong, talk to him properly.
How else am I supposed to talk to him?
Why does he listen to me then?
If you told him to jump off a building, he'd do it!
Fenghua, I know you mean well,
but you can't take sides.
How am I taking sides?
You think I'm just a heartless capitalist.
I'm doing better than Xingchi,
so you unconsciously assume
that I'm bullying him.
Right?
But I'm not.
I'm just an employee too.
My business card says "CEO Assistant,"
but in fact,
I don't even have the authority
of a VP!
I had to use all the credibility
I've built up
to resolve the huge mistake Xingchi made!
Fenghua.
You can side with your friend over reason,
but please don't think I'm bullying him
just because he's weaker
and deserving of sympathy.
That's unfair to me!
[Wankelai Supermarket Community Store]
You're earning quite a lot.
That's enough.
Always rushing us. Do it yourself then!
Or you could fine me.
Time's so tight, you know?
Some customers call me just to rush me.
It isn't even time yet,
but they have to call me.
Isn't that unfair?
Xingchi!
Why are you here?
Xingchi.
How have you been?
Good. Not bad.
Why are you eating out here?
Um... the cafeteria is closed.
Closed? Why?
Maybe the superiors think it wastes time.
What?
How's having your meals wasting time?
Besides, that cafeteria was cheap
and clean.
Xingchi.
Since we
go back just to eat a meal,
it wastes a lot of time on the road.
Well, just to save a few pennies,
it's not really worth it. So we're here.
If you can't have a proper meal,
how can you have the energy to work?
Ridiculous!
I just bought some bread and drinks.
Have it if you're still hungry.
[Wankelai Supermarket Community Store]
Xingchi.
Take a look.
[Bee Delivery]
[Proposal to modify the employees' meal management]
[How to manage daily meals of employees]
[Notice on the implementation of employee meal subsidies]
Is this necessary?
Executives' meals can be invoiced and reimbursed.
Why do we have to stick to one specific restaurant?
They offer a discount
of 40% for bulk purchases.
We can also bring our own drinks.
More importantly, it's close to the office.
We can sign the bills right after eating.
It saves us the reimbursement process.
What's the point?
Our scale is getting bigger and bigger.
We need to simplify processes.
Use our manpower only where it matters most.
Alright.
In the future, for minor matters like this,
you can decide on your own.
No need to consult me.
Um...
what about employee benefits?
For delivery riders?
Yes.
Previously, Shao Xingchi
set up a cafeteria at Station 203
to provide boxed meals to the riders.
The results were decent.
I want to promote this at other stations.
He almost messed up Station 203.
It's been proven
that his ideas are not worth following.
It didn't increase the workers' cohesion either.
Otherwise, when Shao Xingchi was fired,
the station's staff would've rioted.
Get back to work.
Okay.
Meat skewers?
How's your nose so sharp?
Can't you be wrong for once?
Look at this.
Won't you get pricked?
Stay if you want.
If not, you can leave.
Perfect.
I'm frustrated too.
I'll drink with you.
Come on.
At your station,
many delivery riders have run off.
Many bikes were taken
when they didn't pay the deposit.
Tell Xie Wanghe...
I'll get back all the stolen bikes for him.
For those that I can't,
I'll pay out of my own pocket.
Why don't you tell him yourself?
No thanks.
Even his face irks me now.
This time,
how long do you plan to keep this up?
For a lifetime, I guess.
Haikuo.
Don't try to persuade me.
Wanghe's right too.
We came to Beijing to make money.
But I don't think I'm wrong either.
I just want to live humanely.
[Shuntong Express]
Auntie, he's over there.
Thank you, thank you.
[Shuntong Express]
Wang Yuan, did you get into a fight?
Mom? Why are you here?
Your aunt saw news online
that said you beat up customers and got sued.
Listen to me first. Come here.
Mom, can you not listen to that nonsense online?
It's all rubbish. I didn't hit anyone.
So what exactly happened?
I was just delivering food as usual.
That customer was bullying me.
Xingchi saw it and realized it.
So he got upset.
Shao Xingchi?
That guy who runs a karaoke studio?
Including this time,
he's fought for me twice.
He even lost his job because of it.
[Notice Board of Fenghua Express]
Auntie.
Xingchi.
Auntie! Why are you here?
What are you doing?
Come on.
Let's talk inside. Come on.
Here.
-Have some water.
-Thank you.
My son Wang Yuan is kind-hearted,
but he's just so stubborn.
He refuses to come and apologize in person, no matter what.
I'm really sorry about this time.
You've been wronged.
It's okay, Auntie. I don't blame him.
Let's put this behind us.
Wang Yuan's done you wrong, my child.
I'm sorry.
As his mother...
Here, my child.
Take this.
Auntie, I told you this is behind us.
No, listen to me.
You've taken care of me and my son for so many years.
I remember your kindness.
Take this money
and I'll feel a bit better.
It's not much.
Just take it. Let me
buy peace of mind from you, okay?
Take it, my dear child.
Take it.
We came to live in Beijing
because we'd be closer to our son
and we thought we'd earn more than back home.
But after coming here, we realized...
it's not that simple.
♫Hometown, oh hometown♫
♫Now a distant place I can't go back to♫
♫Sitting quietly in the city♫
Why is there a flood again?
♫Listening as time drifts by♫
Hurry up!
Quick, come up! There's no more!
Niu!
Stop the water! Get the blankets!
♫The sunsets in the city♫
Get a blanket!
♫Hold no poetry, no distant dreams♫
Come on, come on!
Use the blankets to block it!
Hurry!
♫Walking through a world like a song♫
♫From oblivion to oblivion♫
♫The love that passed through those remaining years♫
♫Without complaints or piano music♫
♫The coolness after the gentle breeze♫
[Mom]
[There's a rainstorm these few days. Always have an umbrella with you. Don't catch a cold.]
♫I'm destined to be like you♫
♫Far away, so far away♫
♫The hometown I can never return to♫
♫Sitting quietly in the city♫
♫Listening to the river flow♫
What are you sneaking around for?
None of your business.
Why are you here?
Nothing.
Then get out of here.
Is it appropriate for a man and a woman to be together at night?
Huh?
Does that bother you?
Am I not a woman?
Okay, yes, I was wrong.
I was wrong. I was wrong, happy?
What do you want?
I want to go home.
What?
Want to be a deserter?
I've always been holding back...
thinking once I get settled down,
I'd bring my mom over.
But now when I look around,
others' moms who came to Beijing
all seem unhappy.
No relatives, friends, or neighbors around.
No one to talk to
when they are tired or bored.
Always one short for mahjong.
Rather than this,
I might as well go back home.
I was planning to give you this station.
Give it to me?
Then what'd you do?
Go home.
That year,
all of you were coming to Beijing.
I thought...
I'd be the only one left behind.
How boring.
You'd all be broadening your horizons in Beijing,
while I'd be stuck at home.
When we meet again in a few years,
I'd have become all reserved.
I'd have to bow to you all
and call you "Sir."
It wouldn't be that bad.
I didn't know back then.
I was just scared
of being left behind.
That's why I came to Beijing.
But after all these years in Beijing...
I'm really exhausted.
Every day is exhausting.
Now I feel...
it's not worth it.
Then go back.
Let's go back together.
Come on.
When we get back, I'll take care of you.
Following Typhoon Huahuo,
Typhoon Haike'er, the seventh of the year,
has formed this morning.
In the future,
it'll either circle back or move slowly.
Rain will spread from the eastern part of northwestern Sichuan
all the way to the North China region.
The deeper the area, the stronger the rainfall.
In Beijing,
in the afternoon,
it will even be as dark as night.
Are you confident
in this battle?
I don't know about confidence,
but our entire team will fight to the death.
That's not enough.
To win this battle,
the company has invested heavily.
They've raised the subsidies to the max limit.
If we lose,
the investors will abandon us.
We'll have to forget about Series D funding.
So if we fail this battle,
we'll be doomed.
Understood.
Okay. Okay.
Got it.
Definitely.
There will be heavy rain for the next three days.
It's a tough battle ahead of us.
Delivering food in this heavy rain?
The higher-ups are just thinking about themselves.
Do they have any idea
how tough it is on us riders?
We have no choice.
Who orders food when the weather's good?
Let everyone know that
tomorrow morning's meeting starts half an hour earlier.
Get everyone mobilized.
Chief, shouldn't we hire more people?
Many have quit in the past few days.
The new hires are all rookies.
When the orders start pouring in,
we can't handle it.
I've brought this up with them.
The company is in a tight spot too.
We're already short-staffed.
Other platforms are poaching people everywhere.
We have to figure it out ourselves.
An order for two.
Sorry, Mr. Xie. Thank you for waiting.
Take a look.
Isn't business booming?
When lunchtime comes around,
our dozens of franchises receive
thousands of orders.
Your platform alone
might not be able
to handle such a large volume.
Why don't I sign with some others too?
Don't worry about that.
We can handle any number of orders.
Either we're exclusive
or we terminate our cooperation.
The choice is yours.
Must it be this way, Mr. Xie?
I think if everyone does business
the way you do,
our industry will eventually be ruined.
Just make your choice.
No need for opinions.
Mr. Xie!
Give me more time to consider.
-Mr. Xie.
Mr. Xie.
Our market share in Haidian
is basically on par with Yuntu now.
The last leg of the journey is the toughest.
We've just caught up with them.
There are even tougher battles ahead.
This noon, we're basically on par with Yuntu,
but they're pushing hard on their delivery speed.
They've reduced it to 32 minutes.
Are they out of their minds?
The weather forecast shows
heavy rain in Beijing for the next three days.
Did everyone hear that?
For the food delivery industry,
bad weather is our peak season.
Even the heavens are helping us.
Issue a notice immediately.
Mobilize everyone.
We have to face the challenge of the upcoming bad weather.
Within these three days,
we must take our business volume to a new level.
Got it.
Listen up.
We're just one push away
from defeating Yuntu.
Are you confident?
Yes!
Let's go to war!
Tianming!
Mom, go home.
It's raining so hard. Why don't you take a day off?
Go with your wife for a prenatal check-up.
I can't.
Everyone's working, I...
I can't rest. Bye.
Does the world stop spinning without you?
Enough, okay?
I'll come back once I'm done.
Don't worry, go ahead. I'll go with her.
Be careful. Please be safe.
Thanks, Fenghua.
Such heavy rain!
Be careful on the road.
Okay, okay.
Be careful in this heavy rain!
Starting from today,
we're on call 24/7 for the next three days!
This time, we absolutely can't have a single order cancelled!
Got it!
Set off!
Be safe!
[Data Center] [Dispatching Center]
Mr. Xie, there are too many orders today.
We can't handle it.
Make it work, no matter what.
How about extending the delivery time by one minute?
Now's the time to compete on speed.
Whoever is faster wins.
Do you know how important one minute is?
[Data Center] [Dispatching Center]
Close-range deliveries done.
Assign these two. Here. Here. Quick!
Chief! Chief! We have a problem!
Several of our riders' batteries are soaked.
Spare batteries. Hurry!
Take it easy.
Be careful.
I'll go grab orders.
Go, go, go!
[Everyone is responsible for fire safety]
Grab orders now.
Dispatch mine too.
[Data Center] [Dispatching Center]
Your prediction was spot on.
Today's orders have increased by 30%.
Same for Yuntu,
but their absolute numbers aren't as high as ours.
Good, keep pushing.
Tell everyone
that no one stops until the very last moment.
Understood.
[Data Center] [Dispatching Center]
Has my meal been delivered?
Right away. Sorry about that.
Okay.
[Data Center] [Dispatching Center]
I really envy you.
Leaving just like that.
At this age, you're still so willful.
I couldn't make it anymore and got eliminated, okay?
Excuses.
It's true.
I used to think I was just unlucky.
Now sometimes, I think I'm just stupid.
I've really failed at everything I've tried.
You just haven't learned your lesson.
Is that it?
To get things done, it's not about your capabilities
but patience and perseverance.
Wanghe is indeed better than us in this regard.
That's why
he's more successful than us.
He knows you're leaving.
He wanted to come see you off,
but he's really too busy.
It's okay.
It's not like you won't be coming back to Flower Street.
Take care.
See you at Flower Street.
Next time when you go to Wanghe's place,
remember to stuff a bubble gum
into his keyhole for me.
[Security Check]