[NORTHWARD]
[Episode 36]
How did it go?
I was right, wasn't I?
It's too sudden.
They're just shocked.
Once they adjust
and accept the reality,
they won't object.
Guess what my mom said?
She said if I got cancer,
I should pack my things
and find a place
to wait for my death.
That I shouldn't be a burden,
which will make people miss me more after I die.
It's okay.
Anyway, I know you love me too.
I'm very happy.
All these years of waiting
are worth it.
It doesn't really matter if we get married or not.
Fenghua,
you love me
because
I'm stubborn, don't you?
It's the same with this matter.
I've made up my mind.
What others say can't change it.
Don't be silly.
We're both adults.
Don't be childish.
So you know
we're adults.
We're of legal age for marriage.
We have the right to get married.
No one can stop us.
Yesterday…
I told Xingchi about our situation.
Guess what he said?
If you can't make the decision,
don't push yourself too hard.
Leave it to me.
Although I'm not as rich as you,
I can still afford
the betrothal gifts.
You want to marry her,
but she won't agree.
If you
truly want to marry her,
I'll support you
and wish you a happy marriage.
But I beg you
to treat her well.
If you treat her badly, I…
I'll just take her away.
I won't care about brotherhood or anything.
He's put it like that.
What am I supposed to do?
If I'm careless,
my wife might be stolen.
Who could I turn to for help?
In the past,
when I encountered problems,
you always told me
that time smooths things out.
Today, I'm saying those words to you.
As long as we truly love each other
and wish to be together,
any problem can be solved.
It's just a matter of time.
I never expected
that getting sick
would make me so popular.
Don't be afraid.
I'll always be by your side.
[Examination method: cranial CT scan]
[Consider: possible tumor or meningioma tumor]
Is this disease
treatable?
I asked.
They said she needs brain surgery.
The success rate
is very low.
How low?
It's one in ten.
How can it be?
It can't be.
I…
I want to trade my life for our daughter's.
I want to switch places with her.
I want to trade my life for hers.
Why is God so cruel?
Please take my life instead.
It really hasn't changed much, has it?
Are you sure you can find it?
Let's just look.
Here it is.
Come here.
[Wanghe, have you succeeded?]
You wrote it?
The day before we left school,
the three of us all wrote something.
So,
have you succeeded?
By the standards back then,
I guess I could be considered successful.
What about by today's standards?
I'm in my thirties
but still haven't gotten married.
How can I be considered successful?
Where is your desk?
Have you found it?
I didn't write anything.
Impossible.
I really didn't.
Why would I lie to you?
Look for it.
Stop looking. I didn't write anything.
Why don't you believe me?
I must find it.
I want to see what you wrote.
Here it is.
This was your desk, right?
No.
It was!
Come here.
Take a look.
It was not my desk.
Take a look first.
It was not mine.
Look at this.
Look.
It's missing a piece. It was your desk.
Let me see what you wrote.
You really didn't write anything?
I told you I didn't.
Stop looking.
Here it is!
I wish the boy I love
could love me too.
Who's that boy?
I didn't write that.
This is your handwriting.
I can recognize it.
I'm officially informing you now:
the boy you love...
loves you too.
Miss!
He's harassing me!
I'll get beaten up when I get home anyway.
So I might as well
just do whatever I want now.
How dare you mess with me?
So… so audacious!
Miss!
Tell… Tell this boy to stop!
Dad.
You're back.
I just arrived.
Where's Mom?
Asleep.
You should go to sleep too.
Come here.
You and Fenghua...
We're together.
Your mom told me
that
there's a tumor
in Fenghua's brain.
Right?
I've asked the doctor.
It can be treated,
but there are risks.
Are you
truly in love with her?
Or is it because of…
I just love her.
I'm serious.
I know
you and Mom don't approve.
Did I say that?
I don't disagree.
Back then,
when I married your mother,
my parents
didn't agree.
They said your mom was from a poor family
and of humble origins.
I chose my wife myself,
right?
I flipped out at the time.
I-If they wouldn't accept her,
I'd just get your mom on a ship
and live our own life.
At worst, we just wouldn't come back again.
I don't have your courage.
It's alright.
You have me.
You know your mom.
She has a bad temper sometimes,
but she has a kind heart.
I'll handle her.
Really?
Miss,
can I have your number?
I already have a boyfriend.
Who's your boyfriend?
Is he as handsome as me?
Not really.
My boyfriend is a little strange.
He staggers when he walks.
His face twitches,
and he drools when he talks.
Like this?
Go on.
I'm recording it.
Stop.
It's so embarrassing.
Why didn't you open the beers?
Our wives are not home.
Let us
have a drink,
just the two of us.
In-law,
cheers.
Well,
how long
have we
known each other?
36 years.
That's a long time.
We're still good buddies now.
It gotta be fate, right?
This is what they call destiny.
Let's drink.
Boss Xie.
I won't let Fenghua marry Wanghe.
Don't listen to Yan on this matter.
I made this decision myself.
Really?
You don't know.
Fenghua...
If she's sick, get her treated.
It's not a big deal.
Fenghua's condition is not a minor ailment.
We don't even know how long she can live.
You're her father.
You can't jinx it like that.
Let me tell you.
I've talked to Wanghe.
He's head over heels
in love with your daughter.
H-He won't marry anyone but her.
Besides,
when we married our wives back then,
didn't our parents disapprove too?
What did we do?
We were rebellious,
but our children can't be?
Who do you think you are?
Let's drink.
Boss Xie.
I've followed you since I was young.
I listen to you on everything,
big or small.
But this time...
You'll listen to me too,
okay?
Okay?
Okay.
I'll listen to you.
I feel so sorry for Wanghe.
Nonsense.
Don't say that.
It's our children's marriage.
Let them decide for themselves.
It's their fate.
Whether it'll end well or badly…
none of us can decide.
They've spent so much time together
since they were little.
How come I never noticed
any signs between them?
Then,
it's settled.
In-law.
Good.
Yan.
Yan, do you have a moment?
Yeah.
Let's
have a chat.
Okay.
Our children…
Don't say it.
No need to say it.
I don't agree
with them getting married either.
Don't worry.
I'm well aware of
Fenghua's illness.
I won't let her
become a burden to Wanghe.
Haihong.
We've been friends for so many years.
I understand.
I know.
If I were you…
I wouldn't agree either.
We're the same.
Haihong.
When you have time,
accompany me to the temple.
Okay.
Let's go early
to burn the first incense.
I'm going there
to smash the temple.
That old monk in the temple
once read fortunes for Fenghua.
He said she'd live a great
and happy life.
He said she'd have many children and grandchildren.
It all seems impossible now.
Where is…
Fenghua's happy life?
You know Fenghua
has been a good girl since she was little.
You know that.
Fenghua
has been hesitant to have the surgery
because of her parents.
Now she's finally agreed.
Before she goes into surgery,
can't we give her something
to look forward to, some hope?
You…
You think I want this?
What I'm doing
will make everyone hate me.
You think I want to be the bad guy?
That's Fenghua.
We watched her grow up.
Of course I know she's a good girl!
Mom,
I know
you want what's best for me.
I'm sure you hope
I can be happy
and content.
You don't want me to suffer.
I won't.
Put yourself in my shoes.
If this happened to you,
would you give up on Dad?
I would.
When you're young,
you think love is everything.
But marriage
is like sailing a ship.
The ship has just left the harbor,
but it's already leaking.
So tell me,
how long can you keep sailing?
You'll just watch it sink?
At this moment,
will you abandon the ship
or keep struggling
and then sink with the ship?
You can't understand now
because you haven't realized
how messy life can get.
You guys want to help her,
but it's too big of a favor for anyone to accept.
After all the struggle,
we might not even be able…
to maintain our long friendship
with the Xia family.
Have you thought about that?
You're overthinking it.
-Xia Lao'er and I…
-Shut up!
I've already
made my point clear.
Whether you listen or not,
as long as I'm in this house,
Fenghua can't be part of this family.
♫Who will be there to gently♫
♫Pat me on my shoulder when I need it the most?♫
♫Who is willing to share with me♫
♫Our happiest moments?♫
♫Life is long♫
Mom.
Here.
♫I'm by your side♫
I made you some soup.
If you don't want to eat,
at least have some soup.
♫Witnessing your growth♫
This soup is very nutritious.
♫Gives me strength♫
It took me hours to make it.
I don't have an appetite, Mom.
♫Who can forget the past?♫
Just one sip.
I can't.
♫I've been with you all the way♫
I've also made you some lotus seed soup.
♫Who can predict the future?♫
I'll go get it for you.
♫Long and far, where are you?♫
Mom, stop fussing.
I'll tell you when I'm hungry.
♫With a smile on your face♫
Don't worry.
♫Just like you♫
♫Singing loudly♫
♫Applauding for yourself♫
♫I'm just like you♫
♫I'm strong like you♫
Please, Mom.
♫I'll give my all♫
Can you stop looking so sad all the time?
♫In pursuing my dreams♫
I'm not dead yet.
♫Even if I get hurt♫
Don't say that.
♫Even if there's a storm♫
That's nonsense.
♫Only after the storm♫
♫Will flowers bloom with charming fragrance♫
Don't worry.
♫I'm just like you♫
You'll definitely get better.
♫I'm kind like you♫
Look at you.
♫I need someone just like you♫
You've lost weight.
♫To create a paradise♫
Is it because my cooking is bad?
When I was little, you complained about my baby fat.
♫Our voices are wings♫
Do you remember?
♫That will convey hope♫
Now you're complaining that I'm too thin.
♫All of our efforts♫
Just tell me,
♫Becomes powerful with love♫
am I beautiful?
Yes.
♫Just like you♫
My daughter
is the most beautiful.
That's enough.
When I go out now, I turn heads everywhere.
Just today,
a punk
asked for my number.
Look.
Like this?
My name is Fenghua.
Stop filming.
It's so embarrassing.
Stop filming!
Mom.
Fenghua.
Sorry.
I really want you to be happy.
But…
we can't pursue our own happiness…
at the expense of others.
I know.
I know we're not...
Mom, stop.
I know what you mean.
My heart aches for you.
[Tea]
Morning.
You just got up?
I didn't sleep.
You have something on your mind?
Don't you?
I'm not sentimental.
You know that.
Do you have a moment?
How about taking a walk
with your boyfriend?
Where to?
Wait. What are you doing?
Well, I still have work to do.
Meng said
there's a lot to do before Bee goes public.
He wants me to go back as soon as possible.
He hopes
I can go with him to ring the bell at NASDAQ.
That's great.
Join me.
In what?
Going back to Beijing.
You need to get treatment.
You can't delay it any longer.
If you have any other concerns,
tell me now.
I'll see what I can do.
Even if I tell you, you can't do anything about it.
That's not necessarily true.
[Honghuai Civil Affairs Bureau
Marriage Registration Office]
What are you doing?
Xia Fenghua,
as a citizen of the People's Republic of China,
I sincerely invite you
to get married to me.
[Honghuai Civil Affairs Bureau
Marriage Registration Office]
[Honghuai Maternal and Child Health Center]
Get up. No.
[Honghuai Civil Affairs Bureau
Marriage Registration Office]
You're being so reckless.
What are you worried about?
How about this?
Since we're already here,
let's go in and take a look.
Consider it a rehearsal.
[Honghuai Civil Affairs Bureau
Marriage Registration Office]
[Honghuai Maternal and Child Health Center]
It's okay.
The gesture is enough, right?
Mom, Dad.
Come on, quickly.
Hurry.
Here.
Take this.
What do you think?
I didn't lie, did I?
Take this card.
After the company goes public,
most of my income will be transferred here.
Your dad and I have money.
Keep it for yourself.
I'll live in Beijing
and won't need a lot of money.
I just need enough for daily needs.
This money
will be enough to support
you and Dad for the rest of your lives.
What do you mean?
Mom.
I understand
all your concerns.
All parents care for their children.
Every parent
wishes the best for their children.
You're not wrong.
As your son,
I understand you.
But as a man…
my woman is sick now.
You're asking me to give her up.
Would I still be a man if I did that?
Would I still be your son?
Mom.
That day when I came back from Beijing,
I saw Fenghua sitting alone on the bridge
and crying quietly.
Do you know how much it pained me?
I wish I were the one who was sick.
Mom, don't worry.
I'm not marrying Fenghua
out of a sense of duty
because she's sick.
I truly love her.
She means happiness to me.
Without her,
I don't know how to move on.
I can't live without her.
She needs me too.
I've decided.
Early tomorrow morning,
I'll take Fenghua back to Beijing.
We'll live
our life together first.
When the day comes
that you approve,
understand,
and accept us,
I'll bring her back again.
[Household Register]
♫The words you said linger in my mind♫
♫I keep asking myself why♫
♫I'm not good with words♫
You know
Wanghe.
♫Once again, I was knocked down♫
He's smart but stubborn,
and a bit macho.
♫The light you see♫
In that aspect, he takes after his dad.
♫Is not my light♫
N-N-Nonsense.
♫What does it even look like?♫
If you marry a man like that,
♫The girl you spoke of♫
when things are good,
♫The girl far away♫
you'll be very happy,
♫How will her story end?♫
but when he's being stubborn,
he can drive you crazy.
♫Gazing at the stars and the distant sky♫
Be mentally prepared.
♫A faint light glimmering♫
♫I'm chasing it all alone♫
♫Watching loneliness fall like rain♫
But don't worry.
♫Shattered by them♫
From now on…
♫Blooming into flowers once again♫
you and Mom
♫But I...♫
♫From the start to the very end, I've never changed♫
are on the same side.
♫In our relationship♫
♫Who ended up the loser?♫
♫Even if we start again♫
We agreed on this. Only their second child can have the surname Xia.
♫I'll still be here♫
Alright, as you wish.
♫Every choice we make♫
♫Just leads us back to where we began♫
From now on, Fenghua is your daughter,
♫Endless crossroads♫
and Wanghe is our son.
♫Emotions out of sync♫
Okay, let's not keep talking here.
♫Look at me♫
Let's get down to business.
♫One last time♫
Yes, get it done.
♫Endless crossroads♫
Hurry.
Hello.
♫Emotions out of sync♫
Hello, the two of them are getting married.
♫Look at me♫
♫One last time♫
Okay.
Your household registration booklets.
We all agree.
I'm Xie Wanghe.
I'm Xia Fenghua.
[Name: Xie Wanghe]
[Name: Xia Fenghua]
We voluntarily become husband and wife.
From this day forward,
we'll jointly shoulder
the responsibilities and obligations that marriage bestows upon us.
We'll be filial to our parents,
educate our children,
♫The words you said linger in my mind♫
respect and love each other,
trust and encourage each other,
♫I keep asking myself why♫
and understand each other.
[Affiant: Xie Wanghe]
In the future, whether in good times or bad,
[Affiant: Xia Fenghua]
rich or poor,
♫I'm not good with words♫
[Name: Xie Wanghe]
[Name: Xia Fenghua]
in sickness or in health,
♫Once again, I was knocked down♫
young or old,
we'll weather storms together,
♫The light you see♫
share our joys and sorrows,
♫Is not my light♫
support each other through thick and thin,
and cherish each other for life.
♫What does it even look like?♫
We'll surely keep the vows we made today.
♫The girl you spoke of♫
Great!
♫The girl far away♫
Congratulations.
Let me take a photo for you.
♫How will her story end?♫
♫Gazing at the stars and the distant sky♫
[Marriage Certificate]
♫A faint light glimmering♫
Good. Good.
♫I'm chasing it all alone♫
-Mom, come. Mom.
-Come on.
-Okay.
♫Watching loneliness fall like rain♫
♫Shattered by them♫
I'll stand next to our daughter.
♫Blooming into flowers once again♫
You stand next to our son.
Next to our son.
♫But I...♫
♫From the start to the very end, I've never changed♫
Come on.
♫In our relationship♫
We're family.
One, two, three!
♫Who ended up the loser?♫
We're married!
♫Even if we start again♫
♫I'll still be here♫
♫Every choice we make♫
♫Just leads us back to where we began♫
It's so beautiful. What a good day.
♫Endless crossroads♫
♫Emotions out of sync♫
Yeah. It looks so beautiful.
Oh, right.
♫Look at me♫
What are your plans for the future?
♫One last time♫
We'll focus on her treatment first.
♫Endless crossroads♫
Other things can wait.
♫Emotions out of sync♫
I think
♫Look at me♫
maybe you should come back to Flower Street.
♫One last time♫
Fenghua can open another parcel delivery station.
If you want to continue doing food delivery,
your dad and I are still in good health
and can help you.
No rush.
I'm a married man now.
I'll listen to my wife on important family matters.
You can't listen to her on everything.
Given Fenghua's intelligence level…
What's wrong with my intelligence level?
I managed dozens of people in Beijing.
[Flower Street]
I can prove that's true.
Fenghua had a bit of a reputation in parcel delivery in Haidian.
A bit of a reputation?
I was once the employee of the year.
[Flower Street]
How about you?
Enough.
You're getting all worked up over a little praise.
Wanghe is a big boss,
while you were just an employee.
Who are you to brag here?
Wanghe.
Don't spoil her.
She is
getting too big for her boots.
Dad!
Most fathers-in-law dislike their sons-in-law,
but you're taking his side.
You've gone completely over to his side!
A father-in-law will only
like his son-in-law more and more.
Yes.
He's really...
[Flower Street]
I never thought in the end
we'd all have to part ways.
Our two families won't separate.
We're one family now.
We'll stick together.
Of course, no matter who leaves,
we'll stay together.
[Flower Street]
What are you getting sentimental about?
We'll stay together.
Sorry.
Sir.
You're working late?
I made some noodles.
Have you eaten?
Would you like to try some?
Is it proper?
Of course.
Come on in.
There are plenty of noodles anyway.
They'll be soggy tomorrow.
Come on in.
Try some.
Just leave the bike here.
Come on in.
Careful.
Here you go.
Your noodles.
Try them.
Then give me your valuable feedback.
What do you think?
Are they good?
They are
the most delicious…
noodles
I've ever had.
Uncle, be honest with me.
I am being honest.
You put your heart into these noodles.
I can taste that.
If you like them, have some more.
There are more in the kitchen.
Sir.
Sir!
Sir, what's wrong with you?