[NORTHWARD]
[Episode 11]
I've seen many young people like you,
full of passion and dreams.
After scraping around for a few years,
you'll end up with a broken heart
and an empty wallet, slinking away in defeat.
Some fail,
but some succeed, right?
How will I know whether I can make it or not if I don't try?
Come on.
Take a look at this.
My resume.
[Start-up Experience] [Language Ability]
[Professional Skills] [Innovation Workshop]
You created "Pet Home"?
For real?
[Pet Home: Raise Pets, Not Pests]
Feel free to browse.
The first pet supplies website in China.
Fundraising went quite smoothly,
but we burned through all the money in two years.
Then we had to shut down.
All my ideas after that
were pretty much the same story.
That's pretty unlucky for you.
It's not just me who's unlucky.
It's our whole batch of entrepreneurs.
Not a single one of us succeeded.
Some are now working in the internet industry,
paying off debts.
Some went back to their hometowns to open small restaurants to pay off debts.
Some even took civil service exams.
Starting from the bottom,
they're probably section chiefs by now.
Let me tell you,
back then, we were all graduates from top universities.
We all went to Project 985 Universities,
and we all thought we could change the world.
After failing so many times,
you must have accumulated some experience and learned some lessons, right?
Last year alone,
more than 7 million people tried to start an internet business.
How many projects do you think successfully got investment?
And how many successfully got listed on NASDAQ
from 1999 until now?
The odds of success in this
are even lower than winning the lottery.
If you're from a wealthy family,
you can use some spare cash
to burn and play around, that's fine.
If you don't have money,
then you rely on connections.
If you don't even have connections,
and the only things you have are passion
and some creative ideas,
don't bother.
Don't waste your youth on this.
Granny Ma had a stroke and has been hospitalized.
When are you coming back?
Why no reply? Did you get the message?
I'll head back right away.
Bro.
I'm thinking of creating an online smart question bank.
Do you think it has a chance?
Watch carefully.
See this?
This was made by one of my juniors.
[Smart Question Bank]
He graduated from MIT two years ago and came back to start a business.
This homepage was created by him.
This is the remnant of his entrepreneurial failure.
Wait!
Bus!
Are you deaf?
[Beijing Olympics: One World, One Dream]
♫My door is always open♫
With the rapid development of information technology,
♫Accepting the world♫
for the Chinese internet industry,
the year 2007
♫After our embrace comes our mutual understanding♫
is undoubtedly a milestone.
♫You'll fall in love with this place♫
This year, the number of internet users in China
reached 210 million,
with an annual growth rate of 53.3%.
♫Friends from far and near♫
This figure not only caught the world's attention,
♫Please don't be shy♫
but also marked China's
♫May you come back again♫
official entry into the ranks of major internet powers.
♫We will always welcome you♫
-Be careful.
-One step at a time.
Nice.
Nice!
Well done.
Take your time and try again.
Take it slow. Don't rush it.
This is a small step for Granny Ma,
but a giant leap for our entire courtyard.
That's right.
He really has a way with words.
The way those who've seen the world
speak is just different.
You should learn from him.
I... I...
I've seen the world too.
I just can't express it like that.
Come on. Keep walking.
Keep walking.
Come on, come on.
What you just said,
something about a small step and a giant leap,
I remember those words.
I've seen them in the public toilet.
Happy now?
From now on, let your grandma work less.
If you need anything, just tell me.
I know.
We can't rush this.
Right.
We can't rush it.
There's no rush.
Mr. Shao, this is for you.
Grandma, let me give you a massage.
Try walking.
Granny!
Granny.
Are you alright?
You little rascal.
So you finally decided to come back, huh?
You're getting bolder and bolder these days.
Running off so far without a word.
We were so worried.
I'm sorry.
I won't dare to do it again.
Granny.
I'm just glad you're okay.
I was so worried about you all the way here.
I'm alright.
Look.
I'm standing here just fine, aren't I?
Okay.
Let me tell you,
you're definitely going to
get a beating.
You won't get away with that.
I'll head back home then, Granny.
Be careful.
See you, Granny.
Rest early.
Mom.
He'll definitely get a good beating.
I'm back.
Don't be angry. Don't be angry.
It's good that he's back.
Mom.
Why are you hanging it up?
What can you possibly do?
What should you be doing at your age?
Studying.
Look at you. You always
act on every whim.
You just left like that.
It makes me angry just talking about it.
Right,
our family isn't well-off,
but your father and I can figure something out.
It's not your time to earn money now.
Don't you understand, Son?
But when my dad was my age,
he was already fishing in the river to help support the family.
That was a totally different era, okay?
Back then,
how many high school graduates were there in the whole country?
What about now?
Someone like you
wouldn't even be qualified to be a security guard at a factory.
-Mr. Xu, you…
-Mr. Xu?
What brings you here?
Come on in. Come on in.
Wanghe, you're back.
Hurry up and make some tea.
Please, have a seat.
Mr. Xu, please have a seat.
Alright.
Please, sit.
Is his leave request ready?
Yes, it is.
Wanghe went to Beijing to see an exhibition this time.
He didn't even inform you teachers.
Please excuse him.
-I'll go...
-What exhibition?
I went to Beijing to rent servers.
Mr. Xu.
Thank you.
Wanghe's mom, please sit.
Wanghe, you sit too.
Sit, sit.
Wanghe's mom.
The reason I came here
is to have a good talk
with you parents.
I want to know your honest thoughts.
Feel free to say anything.
There's no need to hold back.
Sure. No problem.
This kid has been willful and disobedient since he was little.
It's all my fault. I've spoiled him.
This time, he skipped school to go to Beijing
without telling either of us.
His father and I were both furious about it.
Right.
The principal was furious too.
But we all know Wanghe is a good kid.
If it were someone else,
the punishment would at least be a warning.
Wait.
Are you saying
this time,
there won't be any punishment?
Are... Are you serious?
Great! Many thanks to the principal.
Thank you, thank you.
Come on, say thank you to your teacher.
I traded my business plan for this.
What plan could you possibly have?
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Wanghe is very smart.
It's just he prefers certain subjects over the others.
When he treats math, physics, and chemistry exams seriously,
he gets pretty good grades.
It's just his Chinese grades are a bit unsatisfactory.
I think
if Wanghe starts working hard
from now on
and makes a final sprint,
it's not impossible for him to get into university.
Really?
Mom, don't listen to his nonsense.
Shut up.
Mr. Xu, please continue.
Once,
Wanghe fell asleep in class.
I scolded him,
saying "Rotten wood cannot be carved."
"Rotten wood"
means deadwood.
It's useless.
This is what Confucius
said to his student Zai Yu when he scolded him.
It's a famous quote.
The main point was to express his anger at the student's lack of effort,
hoping he could put his mind on the right things.
As soon as I finished speaking,
Wanghe
raised his hand and stood up.
He gave me a long speech,
providing examples to explain
that even rotten wood
has its own value and uses.
He gave more than ten examples.
When I heard that,
I realized each example
could develop into an industry.
Many of his classmates were stunned.
Just wait until your father gets home.
Wanghe's mom, the reason I'm telling you this
is to let you know that
I believe Wanghe is very talented.
As long as he starts working hard now,
it's not too late for everything.
I mean it.
What?
You don't have confidence in yourself?
Do you know
Google?
Yes, I do.
The best search engine in the world.
When Google started,
Yahoo was already there,
which was the world's number one search engine,
an internet giant.
Even Silicon Valley investors tried to dissuade Google,
saying that with Yahoo ahead,
they'd have no future.
But they didn't give up.
They persevered in the search engine field
and carved out their own space.
Let me ask you,
what was the key
to their success?
Technology, I guess.
And what's the source of technology?
Knowledge.
And
deep thinking.
In terms of mere knowledge,
I believe with your IQ,
even if you study at home,
you can still manage.
But systematic learning
can help you establish
a scientific and effective thinking framework in the shortest time.
It's like the foundation.
How tall a building can be
depends on how deep its foundation is,
right?
Last time,
you mentioned that ebony wood
is priceless.
It was a great point.
But have you thought about this?
For a tree to become ebony wood,
it's not just about the passage of time.
First, it has to be a tree,
and it has to grow well.
If it were green foxtail,
even after thousands of years,
it still wouldn't become ebony wood.
Right?
Mr. Xu, this...
This is great.
Did you hear that?
Mr. Xu was praising you,
saying you're promising.
Mr. Xu.
Did you hear that?
You must study hard.
If you don't study well,
your dad and I will beat you up together.
Mr... Mr. Xu.
Please take extra care of him at school.
Alright.
I'll also count on you, Wanghe's mom.
After all, with the support of parents,
we teachers
can do more with less,
right?
Sure. Sure.
P-Please take extra care of him.
Well,
since we're not at school after all,
we don't know what's going on in there.
If he misbehaves at school,
just discipline him as needed.
His father and I
don't mind.
But Mr. Xu does.
Alright, I'll be on my way.
Alright.
Thank you for everything.
Goodbye, Mr. Xu.
Alright, goodbye.
I won't hit you,
but with your father's temper,
you better think about what to do.
Mr. Xu has left?
Yes.
How was it?
Are you two alright?
You owe us both a beating.
How was Beijing?
It was alright.
Did you go to Zhongguancun?
I did.
It's not quite what I imagined.
Don't leave already.
Tell us about it.
How's it different from your imagination?
Before going to Beijing,
I thought I was smarter than everyone else.
I thought I could see further into the future than anyone.
But after I got there, I realized
there are too many smart people.
Taking a stroll around Zhongguancun,
I saw graduates
from top universities across the country
all struggling
and working hard.
Everyone already knows
those little tricks I learned online,
and they're already putting them into practice.
Only after going there did I realize
I was just like a frog in a well.
So what are you thinking now?
I haven't figured it out yet.
I think
maybe you should give it a shot
and try to get into university.
Even if it's not for your parents,
you'll have more options in the future.
That's right.
With your brains,
if you really work hard for the exam,
you could at least get into a second-tier university.
Is it a matter of taking the exam or not?
Given my family's situation,
and Siyi...
Siyi is going to try to get enrolled in a normal university, which is tuition-free.
Your dad should be able to make some money
from selling the ship.
When our parents tell us
they're doing things for our own good,
isn't it really annoying?
It's the same the other way around.
When you do things for your parents' good,
don't they get annoyed too?
They do.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but what you're doing
is called emotional blackmail.
Why are you wearing so much in this weather?
Are you going to the North Pole or what?
Wanghe is definitely going to get a beating tonight.
Your Uncle Xie said
he wanted to teach him a lesson.
I have to try to stop it a bit,
right? We can't let the kid get hurt too badly.
He won't.
Do you think Wanghe is the type to take a beating quietly?
If it really hurts,
he'll beg for mercy.
There are things you don't know.
Your Uncle Xie has been
in a bad mood lately.
I'm worried he might not stop once he starts beating him,
unable to control himself.
He's in a bad mood?
Are you really going to sell the ship?
How do you know?
My mom told me.
Has Uncle Xie agreed?
Business hasn't been good lately.
After selling the ship, we'll see if we can
find something else to do.
Besides seafaring,
what else can you do?
Why would you say that?
You're looking down on me, aren't you?
Let me tell you,
Fenghua, back in the day, your Uncle Xie and I
traveled all over the country.
We've done so many businesses,
like electronic watches and foreign cigarettes.
You don't know how many of those we bought and resold.
We even ran a video hall once,
showing Hong Kong and Taiwan films, action movies, and romance movies.
Your mom loved watching those the most.
What nonsense are you talking about?
It was "The Legend of the Condor Heroes", right?
We did whatever was profitable back then.
So why can't you do it now?
Well...
It's not that we can't do it now.
But after all, times have changed.
right?
We need to find a new way to make a living.
In recent years, so many people lost their jobs,
but I haven't seen anyone starve to death.
Dad.
I actually have an idea.
You don't have to sell the ship.
Really?
If this idea can be implemented,
Uncle Xie won't feel so bad anymore,
and Wanghe might be able to avoid this beating.
♫Girl, you sit on the bow♫
♫I tow the boat on the shore♫
♫In deep love♫
Bro.
You went drinking again.
Lao'er.
You're still up?
Yeah.
There's something I want to discuss with you.
Be careful.
Alright.
Go ahead.
Here's the thing.
It's my daughter's idea.
A floating supermarket.
That is to say, we stock up on goods
and sell them on the ship.
We can make extra money
while seafaring.
It'll be killing two birds with one stone, right?
Let me finish, bro.
Tell me, how many seafaring ships
are there on the river now?
Talking about setting up a floating supermarket.
Who are you going to sell the goods to?
You'd be better off setting up a roasted sweet potato stand by the roadside.
It would be more profitable than this.
It's not like that, bro.
About this matter,
Yan also thinks we could give it a try.
You're listening to
women's opinions now?
Don't worry.
Even if we can't do seafaring business anymore,
as long as you stick with me,
you won't be poor.
How did it go?
He didn't agree?
I'll talk to him again later.
How about we ask Wanghe to talk to him?
He's quick-witted.
When it comes to making money,
I think Uncle Xie will listen to him.
Why bother talking to him?
He used to make the call on everything on the ship,
and now we still have to listen to him about opening the supermarket or not?
It's none of his business!
We're so poor that we can barely put food on the table.
If we still don't have any income in the near future,
the whole family will be left with nothing to eat.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you saying these things
in front of our daughter?
You're just too easily swayed.
You're a grown man, yet you don't have your own opinions.
You always listen to Boss Xie on everything.
Who's listening to him?
You just won't let it go, will you?
This is ridiculous.
Don't go in yet.
I have something to ask you.
Wait until I'm done beating him up.
You're not listening to me anymore, are you?
Wanghe mentioned his idea of dropping out of school
to you before, right?
He mentioned it briefly.
Why didn't you tell me about it?
Well,
I didn't expect him to just
go through with it.
Wanghe said
you didn't object at the time.
Is that true?
But I didn't agree either.
What kind of talk is that?
Xie Tiancheng, what were you thinking?
Are your brains damaged from all the drinking?
It's his last year of senior high.
You can't wait for such a short time?
You even said we were both useless,
and we'd need our son to provide for us.
What were you thinking?
What kind of talk is that?
What are you talking about?
This... You...
Let me beat him first.
Don't beat him.
Beat me instead.
I deserve to be beaten.
What are you doing?
I don't earn money,
and I failed to raise our son well,
making him worry about the family.
Beat me. Beat me.
Just beat me to death.
Dad!
Mom!
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
I was wrong!
What are you doing?
Get... Get ready.
If you
truly realize your mistake,
make up for the time lost.
Don't make your mother worried and angry anymore in the future.
Dad.
Aren't you warm?
I am. I am.
Let's go.
Haihong.
Why did you get up so late?
Do you know what time it is?
Yan.
I have something to tell you.
Go ahead.
I don't want to run my stall anymore.
Why?
There are too few customers, so I can't make enough money.
I want to get a driver's license
and go drive a truck.
Are you out of your mind?
Is truck driving a job for women?
I've asked around.
Zhang who lives at Flower Street has a truck.
He's sick and can't drive long distances anymore,
so he rented his truck to a transport company.
He complains that the rent is too low.
I've talked to him,
and once I get my driver's license, I'll rent his truck.
I'll rent his first, then buy my own after I've made enough money.
This is no small matter.
Have you discussed this with your husband?
I'm not discussing it with him.
He won't agree to this kind of thing.
I'll get the license first.
And once I start driving and making money,
it'll be too late for him to object.
As long as it's your decision,
I'll support you.
Oh, right.
Don't worry about Wanghe's meals.
I'll take care of them.
Then I...
I'll thank you in advance.
Don't worry.
Also, one more thing.
Don't tell anyone about this for now.
Understood.
I'm off.
Oh, right.
Haihong.
There's something I want to tell you too.
Well,
I've discussed with my husband Maotian,
and we're planning to open a floating supermarket.
Can you make money from that?
Fenghua looked it up online.
It should work.
It's just we'll have to work harder.
We'll have to work from dawn to dusk.
As long as you can make money,
a little hardship is fine.
Just do it.
We've got plenty of strength, right?
I'm off.
Let me try one.
Be careful.
Be careful. It's very hot.
Look how greedy you are.
Not bad, Siyi.
Your skills are almost as good as Granny Ma's.
Mom, can you teach me too?
Whenever you do anything, I'll have to clean up after you.
Good morning, Granny.
Good morning, aunties.
-Morning, Granny.
-They're all here.
Xingchi, can't you behave yourself?
Come and taste this.
-Have a taste.
-Okay.
Come on.
You even know how to make this?
Not bad.
It looks pretty good.
And it's delicious.
It's delicious.
One more.
Amazing.
[Breakfast]
Not bad, right?
Don't get cocky.
Fried radish cakes are so simple to make.
By the time you learn how to make
our Ma family's braised meat,
that's when you'll have real skills.
Count me in.
I want to learn it.
Well,
after I learn it, I'll be your assistant.
Really?
Are you up for it?
[Breakfast]
Let me tell you.
Our Ma family's braised meat
is a secret recipe passed down through generations.
Do you really want to learn it?
I do.
Then you'll have to marry into our family first.
Then I'll learn it too.
Really?
I've loved Granny's braised meat since I was little.
Once I've learned it,
I won't starve wherever I go.
Got it.
Well, you better work hard then.
Cash.
Cage.
Captain.
Check. Check. Check.
Check. Check.
It's really English, huh?
I don't see pigs flying.
Xie Wanghe is actually studying hard.
English is important, okay?
Nowadays, top talents in Beijing and Shanghai
all speak English.
So I must learn English well.
Otherwise, when the time comes,
I won't even be able to understand financial statements.
If I go out to raise funds and meet a foreigner,
I won't even last one round.
How can I fool them then?
If you really think like that,
you might as well work on other subjects too.
And while you're at it, get yourself into a Project 985 university.
Hey, are you really serious?
Don't joke with me.
What do you mean?
Don't you want me to get into college?
No, it's not that.
But this is too sudden, isn't it?
How did you come to this decision?
It's just that one day,
you'd suddenly realize that besides studying,
there's nothing else you can do.
Mr. Xu is also to blame.
During the home visit, he went so far saying good things about me.
He gave my parents hope.
Anyway,
I'll give it my all and go for it.
I must get into college.
Otherwise,
I'll have to see my dad sulking at home all day.
It breaks my heart.
Fenghua,
why don't you give it a shot too?
By then, we'll all be admitted to universities in Beijing,
and you'll be the only one left at home.
Won't you feel embarrassed?
As if you could really get in.
What if I do get in?
If you get in,
I'll set up a breakfast stand at your school gate.
I'll tell everyone I meet that I was your first love,
and I was abandoned by you.
My girlfriend wouldn't lisp.
[Yunqi Driving School]
[Registration Hall]
[Yunqi Driving School Coach Truck]
Coach, here's the list of trainees.
Okay.
Hello, trainees.
Hello, coach.
The car training is over there.
I'm here for truck training.
You... You're here for truck training?
You?
She's here for truck training.
Are you serious?
What's wrong?
Can't women learn to drive a truck?
You might not know this,
but a truck runs thousands of kilometers on the highway,
and it requires two people to take shifts driving.
Are there other women to switch shifts with you?
If there's no other woman switching shifts with me,
I can switch shifts with men, right?
Coach, coach.
I'll do it.
I love driving at night.
Don't trust him. He's just a lecher.
What's all this fuss about?
Stop it.
Besides taking shifts driving,
sometimes you'll also have to load and unload cargo. Can you handle that?
I can.
If others can do it,
I can do it too.
At home, I can carry
50-catty bags of rice by myself.
I can do it.
There's no point in bluffing.
Get in the truck.
Try it.
Give it a try. Show me.
Come on, show me if you can do it.
She probably can't even open the door.
Take it easy.
Be careful.
[Yunqi Driving School Coach Truck]
Alright, alright.
You'd better go home already.
Don't waste your money.
You might as well go home and knit sweaters instead.
It's like the truck's self-driving.
In the future, on the highway,
her overtaking a car would scare people to death.
Have you made up your mind?
Once the training starts,
the tuition fee is non-refundable.
This isn't a job for women.
That's right.
Just go home.
Don't honk it randomly.
Do you even know how to drive?
Want to make a bet?
I'll be the first one here to get the license.
Are you in or not?
I'll bet with you.
If you get the license,
each of us will give you ten yuan.
If you can't get the license,
you give each of us ten yuan.
How does that sound?
Great!
Great! Great!
It's a bet!
Where do I press?
Furthermore,
through the general term formula of this geometric sequence,
what can we derive?
This equals this,
right?
Alright, class dismissed.
Stand up!
[Striving unceasingly with steadfast integrity]
Wait, wait.
I have a few more words to say to you.
Last time,
your classmate, Xie Wanghe, mentioned in class
about test prepping.
I've discussed it with the principal,
and we think it's a great idea.
We've decided to use our class as a pilot.
We'll organize test prep sessions during the evening self-study time.
The test papers are being prepared.
Please look forward to it.
[Striving unceasingly with steadfast integrity]
If it proves effective,
we'll promote it throughout the entire school.
If it really works as Xie Wanghe said
and can quickly improve your performance,
Xie Wanghe,
you will
be a hero to them.
Alright, alright.
Class dismissed.
Stand up!
[Striving unceasingly with steadfast integrity]
Goodbye, teacher.
Nice.
Now we know what it means to shoot ourselves in the foot.
Wanghe.
Actually, you could
continue working on the intelligent question bank after our college entrance exam.
I can't think that much right now.
I can't focus on two things at once.
The top priority now is that
I have to catch up on the coursework
I missed in the first two years.
No matter what, I can't get lower grades than Xiaopang, right?
Give it a rest.
I could score higher than you with my eyes closed.
Not necessarily.
Wanghe got full marks on that function word problem yesterday,
while you failed to answer it.
Seriously?
Of course.
[Striving unceasingly with steadfast integrity]
Let's go eat.
Fenghua, aren't you coming to eat with us?
[Breakfast]
Young lady.
Come on, have a bowl of tofu pudding.
Yuling.
What do you think Fenghua
can do after graduating from high school?
She won't be able to get into college.
I'm so worried.
She can do anything.
But no matter what,
we can't let her set up a stall like we do.
That's for sure.
If she starts setting up a stall like us at such a young age,
her life will be ruined.
Yan!
[Breakfast]
Yan! Yan!
Let's go.
Mom.
Why are you here?
Why can't I come?
I miss my son.
Is there any soy milk?
My mouth is dry.
Mom is thirsty.
We'll need another bowl here.
Don't take others' food like that.
You have to pay for it.
It wasn't made by me.
Why don't you just pay for it?
We're all family.
Why do we have to stand on ceremony?
Eat more.
It's okay.
Haikuo, I'm going over to your house for dinner tonight.
Sure, but bring your own dishes.
Why are you so stingy?
Okay.
I was just kidding.
The last one to arrive buys drinks.
Xia Fenghua.
How dare you come again?
You've got some nerve.
It's him?
Can we talk?
What's there to talk about with you?
I'll let it slide that you got physical with me.
But she must pay back the 10,000 yuan she took from me.
What if we refuse?
You're students.
Your main task is to study.
Don't make trouble for yourselves.
Trying to frighten me?
You did such filthy things,
and you still have the guts to come ask for money?
How can you be so shameless?
So you're not paying back, huh?
She'll be expecting a summons then.
What summons?
For breach of contract.
It's not just that 10,000 yuan.
You also owe me 50,000 in liquidated damages.
50,000? Are you insane?
Then go ahead and sue.
Don't you know
what you've done?
What have I done?
I merely had students model for advertisements.
That's not illegal.
It's not up to you to decide whether it's illegal or not.
By the way,
we've already taken screenshots of that album of yours.
We'll hand them over to the Public Security Bureau
and let them decide whether what you did is illegal or not.
What album?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Are you legally illiterate?
It's called lingerie advertising.
It's legal.
Is that so?
Alright.
I guess I'll see you in the newspapers then.
I've even thought of a headline for you.
"Minors
Coerced by Unscrupulous Photographer to Take Indecent Photos,
Tearfully Forced to Have Drinks with Adults."
What a sensational news story.
Local portal websites,
photography sites,
advertising sites,
and any site related to your business,
I'll make sure
every single one of them sees the news.
Let's see how you'll manage after that.
Don't you dare!
You started this,
and I'll finish it.
We're students.
We have nothing to lose.
Try it if you dare,
and see if we dare.
Let's see who has more to lose.
I'm warning you.
If you dare to bully Xia Fenghua again,
I'll beat you up every time I see you.
Let's go.
Next time, it'll be the three of us who beat you up.
What's wrong?
You confronted him like that.
Are we going to be okay?
As I said,
we've got nothing to lose.
But I'm scared.
Don't worry.
They wouldn't risk losing their business over 10,000 yuan.
Anyone with half a brain wouldn't do that.
I'm just worried they might do something desperate.
What could they possibly do?
Ambush us?
Rob us? Kidnap us?
They wouldn't dare.
Fenghua.
Remember this.
Except for the three of us,
no one can bully you.
If anyone dares to bully you,
we'll take him down.
We'll destroy him!
We'll pour tar on his head
and pluck out all his hair.
What, are you preparing a roast suckling pig?
Let's go home.
You eat.
Eat.
I'll eat it then.
Eat up.
♫At moonset cry the crows♫
Don't be stubborn.
Just do as I say.
How much do you think she makes in a day?
Who cares how much money she makes?
As long as she treats Fenghua's father well.
♫Streaking the frosty sky♫
Granny, Auntie.
When did you arrive?
We just got here.
Fenghua.
It's only been a few years since we last saw you,
and you've grown so much.
Girls really do change a lot as they grow up.
♫Dimly lit fishing boats♫
I remember back then, Sister-in-law, your daughter
was only about this tall,
and now she's grown so tall.
She's getting uglier as she grows.
Not even as good-looking as she was when she was little.
♫Sadly lie beneath maples♫
Back then, she still looked like a girl.
But now,
look at her.
What did she do to her teeth?
She's doing great, okay?
Just the other day, someone invited her to shoot a commercial.
They even wanted to sign her as a model.
Her, a model?
She even shoot a commercial?
What kind of commercial?
Pig feed?
Mom, where's Dad?
♫Beyond the city wall♫
He left early this morning.
Do you need something?
What are they doing here?
What else? Of course for money.
♫From Temple of Cold Hill♫
They called last time,
saying the village was going to build two-story houses,
all part of a unified plan.
Just different ways to trick me out of my money.
Who's that child?
Who cares? It doesn't matter.
I'm not giving them a single penny this time.
♫The sound of bells in the midnight♫
If they really push me too far,
I'll flip the table on them.