[NORTHWARD]
[Episode 10]
All right.
Hey,
you don't look bad with makeup on.
Here you go, for the two of you.
Let's eat something first.
Then, we'll find an internet cafe
and stay up until dawn.
We'll take the first bus tomorrow morning
to go back to Flower Street.
Here.
How did you know I would be in trouble?
When your mom asked me to look at the contract last time,
I felt a bit uneasy.
So I asked Haikuo
to investigate this studio.
They have a website. From there,
we found an email address from their contact.
[System Management Log-in]
With that, we found out
that this email
was also registered to an online photo album.
Zhou Haikuo hacked into this online album.
When we looked at it,
we got so furious.
This is definitely a gang of perverts.
Let's call the police.
The extent of this isn't illegal yet.
Calling the police won't help.
They can't file a case.
If Fenghua takes these kinds of photos,
the school will definitely expel her.
If she doesn't take them, they'll say she breached the contract
and make her pay a penalty.
These bastards are really despicable.
Then I rushed to your house,
but your mom said you had already gone downtown.
So I hurried over here in a panic.
Fortunately, I arrived in time,
Fenghua.
Otherwise, the consequences would have been unimaginable.
How did you know I was in this hotel?
You even knew the room number.
Haikuo and Xingchi went to the police station
saying you were missing.
They gave them your ID number.
The police looked it up.
That old police officer who arrested you last time?
Yes.
We're lucky to have him this time.
Otherwise, you'd have been done for.
Where are those two?
Why didn't they come?
We've already agreed.
They're waiting at the police station entrance.
If anything happens here,
I'll call them
and they'll alert the police.
They'll come over with the police.
Come on,
let's celebrate your narrow escape.
I thought my luck would finally turn around this time.
Who knew...
It's a blessing nothing bad happened.
You should be grateful.
Can you stop getting involved in these things from now on?
Even if pies were falling from the sky,
you wouldn't be the one to catch them.
Hey, I saved you!
Was that all for nothing?
I didn't ask you to come save me.
Who told you to meddle in my affairs?
Fine.
Fenghua,
this is the last time I'm helping you.
From now on, even if you're in deep trouble,
I won't care.
I'll just stand by and watch.
I'll make you so angry.
Make you so angry.
Sir, thank you for the medicine.
Come again.
I'm here to rescue you.
Let's forget about the cab fare.
I still have to pay for the meal. Seriously?
I'll pay for the internet cafe. How's that.
Drinks too.
I want iced tea.
I'll drink until you go bankrupt today.
♫What would I do without you?♫
Wrong.
It's "what would you do without me?"
All right, stop singing.
You sound terrible.
♫What would you do without me?♫
♫Who would wipe away your tears?♫
♫Who would hold an umbrella for you?♫
♫Comfort you when you're troubled♫
♫On sleepless nights, you fear loneliness the most♫
Sounds good.
No fun. Forget it.
Let me carry you on my back instead. Come on.
Come on.
What would you do without me?
Who would wipe away your tears?
Do you think I should return the money?
It's best to do so.
Otherwise, they might cause trouble.
Why would they? After how that guy treated me...
I'll report him to the police and have him arrested.
The problem is it's hard to gather evidence.
Didn't you find the photo album?
Hand it over to the police.
Those are just photos of people in underwear.
It's all over the internet.
It's not like they're nudes.
But he forced me to drink with people.
But it didn't happen, right?
Even if you report it, there's no evidence.
The key is, I'm worried if this gets blown out of proportion,
it could damage your reputation.
As rumors spread,
who knows what they might turn into?
Fenghua,
money can be earned again,
but I don't want you
to be in any more trouble in the future.
I can't just let this go.
If you don't return the money, he'll come after you.
Let him come.
If he dares to come, I'll fight him to the death.
How about this?
If he comes, you tell him
to apologize to me sincerely.
Otherwise, he doesn't get his money.
Is that okay?
All right.
If he really dares to come,
it won't be your fight.
That's my business.
I...
What? Let's go.
We're almost home.
You should head back.
I'm going to Beijing.
Going to Beijing?
I told you before,
I'm going to start a business.
Go back and tell my parents
not to worry.
This time, I'm sure I'll succeed.
How long will you be gone?
It's hard to say.
I'll come back when I succeed.
Are you crazy?
Do your parents know about this?
I'm acting first and reporting later.
They wouldn't agree to me going.
Then why are you bothering with this?
Do you think I can succeed?
You can.
Then save your breath.
Fenghua.
I'll buy you a car when I come back.
Here you go.
Be careful.
Okay, we are departing.
Fasten your seatbelt.
[Jixiang Passanger Transport Co., Ltd.]
What?
Your son skipped school
and went to Beijing!
It's a leave of absence.
He went what?
What...
What did he go to Beijing for?
To start a business.
Start a business my ass!
Start a business?
Go, go, go.
Go get Haikuo
and Xingchi here.
He's got some nerve.
Leaving without saying a word.
It's all because you've spoiled him.
What do you mean I've spoiled him?
I'm the one who spoiled him then?
All right, all right, enough.
I'll beat him when he gets back this time.
Don't try to stop me.
I won't stop you.
Beat him to death.
If you cripple him, I'll take care of him.
Seriously.
Your son.
Where are we going?
Here.
Uncle, Auntie.
You all know that Wanghe went to Beijing, right?
I don't.
Yes.
You've all conspired together, haven't you?
Uncle,
Wanghe went to Beijing for something important.
You are students.
The important thing you have now is to study.
Skipping school in 12th Grade,
does he have a death wish?
Fenghua said he went to Beijing to start a business.
What kind of business?
What is he thinking?
What do you two know?
Tell us.
You want to
keep it a secret for him?
Speak up!
You think if you don't tell me now,
I won't find out later?
Um, Uncle,
I promise you
this business plan
can benefit
all middle school students across the country.
We firmly believe
he will definitely succeed.
Do you know this old saying
that goes, "Failure is the mother of success"?
For your success,
I'll show you
what failure is.
Why are you hitting someone else's child?
What are you doing?
What are you hitting someone else's child for?
Are you all right?
Darn brat.
♫Cheers, the heroic warriors♫
What are you doing?
What? You don't know what?
Let's just talk.
♫Please accept my sincere congratulation♫
Why pick that up?
No, no, no!
Dad, Dad, Dad!
Don't "no" me.
Let me tell you,
beating you is the least I could do.
♫Because of bullfighters and warriors♫
No, no!
Why are you hitting me for Wanghe skipping school?
If I don't beat you, you'll be out of control.
♫We all get happiness from fighting♫
You should focus on studying!
You'll have to support him when he grows up.
♫Today is a festival♫
♫The bullfighting arena is filled with audience♫
♫Look how passionate they are♫
♫They can't help shouting♫
Let me take a look.
It's not too bad. It should be gone by tomorrow.
My face is fine.
It's mainly my legs.
Look at this, and my buttocks too.
I won't show you two my buttocks though.
Did your dad kick you?
He whipped me with a belt.
So he's learned to use a belt now.
He's picked up bad habits from Uncle Xie.
When Wanghe comes back,
Xingchi and I will give him a good thrashing.
We'll beat him to within an inch of his life.
I'm going to check on Xingchi.
What are you laughing at? Stop laughing.
♫Welcome to Beijing♫
♫Open up the world for you♫
♫The charm in the flow is full of vitality♫
[Hailong Building]
[Zhongguancun e-World]
♫Welcome to Beijing♫
♫Breathe together under the sun♫
$50 million is not enough for anything.
♫Achieve new things on this yellow land♫
Wouldn't that burn through in just one round?
Wait. Listen to me.
Tell them
anything less than a hundred million is not worth discussing.
♫My door is always open♫
Hello.
♫Accepting the world♫
How do I get to Fumao Building?
Turn left ahead.
♫Time blooms and youth smiles♫
The tallest building there is it.
Okay, thank you.
♫Welcoming this day♫
No problem.
[North Haidian Bridge]
♫We're all friends♫
♫Please don't be shy♫
In 2008,
♫A bright smile♫
the world will focus on Beijing.
♫Waiting for you♫
A hall that symbolizes hope and dream
♫Welcome to Beijing♫
is being erected
♫Touching you like music♫
on this ancient yet
energetic land.
♫Let's try our best to surpass ourselves♫
♫Welcome to Beijing♫
[Fumao Technology]
♫Anyone who has dreams is amazing♫
Hello.
I'd like to rent a server.
♫There will be miracles if you have courage♫
Where do I complete the paperwork?
I have a reservation.
My name is Xie Wanghe.
In the micro-client area.
There happens to be a vacancy.
Thank you.
Our server service
can handle ten million users without any issues.
Even fifty million users won't be a problem.
For your scale,
you'll need at least a hundred servers to meet the demand.
Of course, it depends on what you think.
What do you think?
No problem, let's start with a hundred servers.
We can always add more if needed later.
All right,
we'll set up a hundred servers for you then.
[Fumao Technology]
Let me know if you need anything else.
Hello.
How can I help you?
I'd like to rent a server.
That's such a small capacity.
That's not enough for anything.
A personal website?
it's for personal use at the moment.
I'll need to expand capacity when the scale grows.
Why don't you share one with others?
Several people can use one server together.
You can split the annual fee.
That won't work.
There's no guarantee for data security.
Do you usually live in Beijing?
I'm in Honghuai.
Honghuai...
Insufficient funds.
How about this?
You could get a domestic server.
Although...
the configuration is lower, but the price is cheaper.
It's just that the maintenance and migration costs afterwards
might be more expensive than foreign servers.
The maintenance fee is calculated separately.
All right, it's sufficient for now.
Um, can I see the server room?
Sure.
ID card.
[Name: Xie Wanghe]
[Pass]
Come here.
The third one in the second to last group of servers.
Their website just shut down.
It's used.
About a year old.
But the performance is fine.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Hello, teacher.
What did Xie Wanghe go to Beijing for?
What's he up to?
Are you performing a choir performance?
You won't tell me, huh?
None of you will say anything, right?
Fine then.
This matter has now become serious.
Expulsion from school is not out of the question.
I'm going to the principal right now.
Don't, don't!
Mr. Xu!
He went to...
rent a server.
What did you say?
Wanghe wants to set up an online–
Teacher,
Wanghe will only be gone for a few days.
He'll be back soon.
Don't worry.
It's a good thing he's not doing anything bad this time.
If this project really succeeds,
not just our school,
the whole Honghuai area could benefit from it.
You're just blowing hot air.
Don't I know him well enough?
He's always got big ideas but no skills to back them up.
He's got plenty of ideas,
but what can he actually do well?
If he becomes the CEO
of that website,
he'd run it into the ground in less than six months.
You,
go to Xie Wanghe's house tonight.
Have his parents write an excuse note.
The reason
absolutely cannot be "starting a business."
Otherwise, I won't be able to cover for him.
All right,
we'll get it done tonight
and submit it first thing in the morning.
Thank you, Mr. Xu.
Thank you, teacher.
Okay, okay, hurry back now.
Quick, quick, quick.
Thank you, Mr. Xu.
Keep your mouth shut.
Let's think about the reason for taking leave.
His grandmother is critically ill.
He's accompanying him.
Didn't his grandmother already pass away?
The school doesn't know that.
This won't work.
It'll be more troublesome if someone reports him later.
Let's think again.
Think of a reason that the school can accept.
I've got one.
Let's say Xie Wanghe has a brain tumor.
He needs to go to Beijing for surgery.
You're the one with a brain tumor! Your whole family has brain tumors!
I was just kidding.
I'm warning you.
We're talking about serious matters here. Don't be an idiot.
I just don't understand. With Xie Wanghe's brain,
he can't even figure out basic arithmetic.
Who gave him the confidence to start a business?
Even your dad can start a business with his brain.
What did you say?
Say that again!
Ouch, ouch!
Fenghua, let go. Let go, let go.
It hurts.
[Striving unceasingly with unwavering resolve]
Wanghe went to take care of important business.
If he succeeds,
everyone will benefit.
He'll explain the details when he returns.
But before that,
if anyone dares to snitch behind our backs,
and I find out about it,
they'll face the consequences.
If you have issues with Wanghe,
confront him face to face.
Don't gossip behind his back.
It's not manly.
You're right.
I'm indeed not manly enough.
The manliest one must be your Wanghe.
[Striving unceasingly with unwavering resolve]
Who poured ink on my shoes?
My new shoes!
Was it you?
Fenghua!
I was talking about him, not you.
My... My dad bought me new shoes.
Fenghua, let me tell you,
this thing today, between us two...
It's still our Fenghua who's the best.
Fenghua is awesome!
Everyone, be quiet. It's self-study time.
[Striving unceasingly with unwavering resolve]
Even if you aren't studying, there are people who are.
What are you doing?
Get back to studying, come on!
I've thought of a reason.
For an exhibition?
What exhibition?
Canal culture.
I saw it online.
For the World Heritage application,
the province has an exhibition in Beijing
for these few days.
But he can't just skip school to go for it.
It doesn't make sense.
It's fine.
I'll ask Haikuo to write an essay later.
Then I'll have Grandpa Zhou help revise it.
We're all from By the Canal.
This school
is very supportive of historical
and cultural activities.
Is this appropriate?
The teacher didn't want to give him a hard time.
Otherwise, he could have been expelled.
All right then.
So for this matter,
keep a close eye on it, will you?
It's driving me crazy.
Just wait until he comes back.
I'll teach him a lesson when he returns.
Why do you need to punish him?
He skipped school.
Is this what a student should do?
Ms. Liang.
You mustn't think that way.
Wanghe went to Beijing for something important.
We should all support him.
He can only fool you.
You're the only one who believes him.
Silly girl, you need to wise up.
Don't end up being sold by him
yet you have to count the money for him.
Bastard!
[Breakfast]
Let me...
-Let me do it.
-Move it...
One, two, three.
You two are here so early.
Good morning.
Take it easy.
How's your back?
Be careful.
It's fine, it's fine.
Come this way.
I'm not that delicate.
But I still don't dare
to lift heavy things.
You
shouldn't all the heavy work yourself.
Let your Xingchi do it.
What's the point of raising such a big son?
Let him do it.
Him?
If he could just take care of himself,
[Breakfast]
I'd wake up from laughing.
Still better than ours.
At least you don't have to worry about his studies.
Ours isn't any better.
It's only because Shao keeps a close eye on him.
Shao said this time,
if he doesn't do well in the exam,
he'll disown him.
I've made threats too,
but it's no use at all.
Fenghua
is just thick-skinned.
She gets sleepy as soon as she picks up a textbook.
Why hasn't Granny Ma arrived yet?
Yeah.
Did she oversleep?
[Clock Fixing]
Ma'am, two youtiao please.
All right!
Do you understand this?
First, calculate this angle.
Then plug it in.
That's it.
How's the studying going?
Mom.
Ms. Gu.
Why so formal?
Call me auntie.
Sit down.
Stop studying and eat.
It's getting cold.
I've hired a tutor for Chen Rui.
He's a first-class teacher in our city.
But he's already retired.
On Saturdays,
he'll come to our house to tutor Chen Rui.
If you're free this weekend,
come for extra classes too.
No need. My grades are okay.
I don't need a tutor for now.
You've helped Chen Rui so much.
I feel I should help you too.
Besides, your grades are so good.
If you push a little harder,
you'll definitely get into a good university.
In this era,
the best way to change your fate
is through the college entrance exam.
I'm not hungry, thank you.
Just agree.
Otherwise, she'll keep pestering you.
Okay.
I'll come every weekend from now on.
Thank you.
Don't be so polite.
If you're not eating, at least have an apple.
Thank you.
Granny Ma!
Ma–
G-Granny Ma!
Granny Ma!
Granny Ma, what's wrong?
Let me help you up.
Don't touch me yet.
I just felt dizzy for a moment.
Give me a minute to recover.
Then let me help you up first.
Yanzi!
Yuling!
Hurry, hurry!
Granny Ma is sick!
Granny Ma?
Come quickly!
You're not doing business anymore?
Take the things yourself!
Granny Ma! We're here.
We're taking you to the hospital.
Yanzi!
Get the stretcher ready. Bring it quickly!
Yes, yes, yes. The stretcher, the stretcher.
The stretcher is here.
What if the three of us can't lift her?
I'll go find Mr. Zhou for help.
Okay.
Get everything ready for the hospital!
All right! All right!
The stretcher is here.
I'm going to find Mr. Zhou.
You watch her.
I'll go pack the things.
Mr. Zhou!
Mr. ZHou!
What?
Siyi...
Siyi!
Don't worry, we're here for you.
Look, they're here, they're here.
Come on, come on.
Turn that stretcher around.
Turn it this way. Come on, come on.
One, two, go.
Exert some strength.
Slow down, slow down.
Here.
Put your hands down, put your hands down.
Give me a hand.
Come on, come on.
One.
Careful.
All right.
Three!
Let's go.
Yuling.
Go get the things.
Okay!
Hurry.
Watch out for the steps.
Slow down, be careful.
Slow down, slow down.
Be careful.
Yuling, take over for me for a moment.
Okay.
What's wrong?
You guys go ahead.
Where are you going?
I'll be right there. I'm just grabbing some things.
All right, let's go, let's go.
Go ahead, go ahead.
Siyi.
What are you doing here?
Grandma.
Grandma, what's wrong? Grandma.
Siyi, I'm... I'm fine.
I'm not dead yet.
It's nothing.
Why is my grandma suddenly hospitalized?
What's the illness?
It's a cerebral thrombosis.
But the treatment was timely.
The doctor said she should recover with proper care.
Oh, child.
Don't cry, don't cry, don't cry.
That's enough.
You see, normally you seem so...
strong.
Why do you panic when something happens?
Don't panic.
Granny Ma's illness...
Fortunately
the rescue was timely this time.
Moreover,
recovery will also take some time.
So I think
she can't be left alone.
That's not a problem.
Our neighborhood has nothing
but plenty of people.
Exactly.
Let's discuss and arrange a schedule later.
Our families can take turns.
Don't worry.
You should hurry back to your busy store.
Go quickly.
We're here.
Rest assured, rest assured.
Go, go, go.
Hurry up.
Let Siyi stay at your place tonight.
With Fenghua there,
she'll feel more at ease.
They'll have each other for company.
I just need to remind Fenghua.
She tends to speak without thinking.
I've already paid the hospital fees,
but I'm not sure how much it will cost this time.
Granny Ma.
be able to afford it?
Definitely not.
We will
help cover the costs for now.
We can consider it as prepaid rent.
All right.
Granny.
Then it's settled.
What would you like to eat?
I'll make it for you.
No need,
Ms. Liang and Ms. Yan are here.
You don't have to do this.
I'm already 17 years old.
Stop treating me like a child.
In ancient times, I could have been married with children by now.
That's true.
When I gave birth to your father,
I was 18.
When your mother had you,
she was 20.
You know, when you were just born,
you were as small as a kitten.
So tiny,
with big, watery eyes.
You were so beautiful.
I was so fond of you.
But you know,
I was afraid to hold you.
My hands and feet are rough,
I was worried I might hurt you.
When I have children in the future, I'll let you hold them.
You'll let me hold them?
Grandma, I'm scared.
Don't be afraid.
See? I'm fine, aren't I?
It'll be better in a couple of days.
The family wasn't well-off to begin with.
Siyi would need money
for college.
And now with this illness...
This child, Siyi,
has really been through a lot.
Don't be afraid, Siyi.
♫When the moon hangs in the sky♫
My mom made some black chicken soup.
♫And it's cooling in the yard♫
Want some?
I've already eaten at the hospital.
♫Who is still by your side?♫
Cut the crap. Come with me.
I haven't finished my homework yet.
♫As time passes♫
Do it at my place.
Stay with me tonight.
I'll give you a 200 yuan tip.
♫Is a lifetime really that long?♫
What are you standing there for?
♫When youthful company fades, leaving only small talk and pleasantries♫
Let's go.
♫Spring feels short, while autumn lingers♫
[Families along the canal]
Granny Ma's illness
will only get worse in the future.
She definitely can't run her business anymore.
♫A gentle breeze carries dreams away♫
She still has a child to raise at home.
If it's just about taking care of her,
♫Of sweet dreams♫
every family in our courtyard can lend a hand.
But that's not a long-term solution, is it?
The main issue is Granny Ma's personality.
♫Life is long♫
If we keep helping her like this,
she definitely won't be able to accept it.
♫No need to dwell♫
So let's think.
♫Like moonlight♫
Is there any other way we can help?
We're renting Granny Ma's house.
♫Don't forget♫
Starting this month, we plan to increase the rent by 100 yuan.
But this small amount of money
♫Life is long♫
is definitely not enough.
Let's think if there are any other solutions.
♫No need to dwell♫
Well, it's definitely up to us few families here.
We can contribute money and effort together
to help them get through this difficult time.
♫Like moonlight♫
I don't think it's appropriate
As Mr. Zhou just mentioned,
♫The old times♫
people always have their pride.
Think about it,
if Granny Ma has to rely on our families' support to live,
how can she hold her head up in this courtyard?
♫Life is long♫
♫No need to dwell♫
I have another idea,
♫Like moonlight♫
but I'm not sure if it's feasible.
Hurry up and tell us.
Well,
♫Don't forget♫
we could apply for a minimum living allowance for Granny Ma.
It's at least a few hundred yuan a month.
♫Life is long♫
Mr. Zhou, do you think it's possible?
I...
I still think it's not appropriate.
♫No need to dwell♫
♫Like moonlight♫
This minimum living allowance
is designed for those who have no means of support,
for these vulnerable groups.
♫The old times♫
Granny Ma still has a house she's renting out.
This doesn't comply with the policy.
Mr. Zhou,
you run a restaurant
and know a lot of people.
Can you look into what Yanzi just suggested
and see if it's possible?
If it's possible, what should we do?
Could you ask around?
It seems Ms. Gu is in charge of this matter.
But
we need someone familiar
to put in a word.
Why are you looking at me?
I'm a colleague of her husband,
but I don't know her personally.
A colleague is fine too, Mr. Shao.
Why don't you take the trouble to go?
As long as District Chief Gu
is willing to come
for a meeting,
we'll take care of the rest.
Okay?
I'm not going.
Whoever wants to go can go.
It's annoying.
I'd rather avoid it if I could.
Chen,
there might have been some misunderstandings between us before.
It's my fault.
I apologize to you.
I'm sorry.
Grandma!
Grandma.
We came to see you.
We've come to visit you.
You've come from so far away.
Please, sit down, sit down.
Siyi, show them to their seats.
♫Stepping on the old time♫
Have you eaten yet?
No, we haven't.
♫The wind blows gently♫
Since you fell ill,
we haven't had any appetite.
♫It blows through the the forest and the city♫
Grandma, don't listen to him.
No appetite? He stole my pork chop at lunch.
I was just worried you couldn't finish it.
♫It blows across your face♫
Hypocritical.
♫And my heart♫
Be careful.
It's alright, it's alright.
Thank you for your hard work.
Ms. Liang, Ms. Yan.
♫The wind blows gently♫
You're back.
How's your grandma?
♫Blowing through summer♫
Much better.
What are you all doing here?
It's such a hassle
♫Blowing through the eaves♫
to install a telephone in your place.
Quick, quick, get inside.
♫Blowing through me♫
Sir, there's sound.
♫Warm love♫
Master Liu, it's done!
Good, good.
Your grandma
wouldn't install a phone previously.
♫After all these years♫
But now times have changed.
♫You have not changed♫
If there's anything,
you can directly let us know with a phone call.
♫After all these years♫
It's convenient.
It's good that it's installed now.
♫How far has the old times♫
This phone, you know,
was covered by Mr. Zhou.
We called the telco
♫We love gone?♫
It was an urgent installation.
♫Lost in a distance♫
I'll go thank Uncle Zhou again.
I almost let it slip.
♫Can't be forgotten♫
Look at me.
♫The first growth♫
Don't let the child worry about it.
Sir.
[Flower Street]
This way.
Ms. Gu,
It's right here.
Take a look.
[Families along the canal]
This...
The one in the middle.
Yes.
This is it.
This is Granny Ma's stall.
She sells radish pancakes, right?
Yes, that's right.
Granny Ma,
you need to use your left hand.
From now on,
let's not use your right hand to eat.
Didn't the doctor just say
using your left hand regularly is good for your health?
Come on,
Okay.
Look.
♫Stepping on the old time♫
Excellent!
Have another bite.
Good,
this crucian carp soup is very nourishing.
♫The wind blows gently♫
Crossing the red line and violating policies,
♫Blowing through the forest and the city♫
I can't do it,
nor can it be done.
How about this?
♫Blowing through your face♫
All of you
write a report together.
Describe Siyi's situation
♫And my heart♫
in detail.
Have the neighborhood submit it up the chain.
Because Granny Ma's family situation
♫The wind is blowing gently♫
is indeed quite special.
♫Blowing through summer♫
We will definitely pay attention to it
and try our best
♫Blowing through the eaves♫
to resolve the actual difficulties.
That's great, Ms. Gu!
♫Blowing across my♫
Let's do it this way.
We'll go to the neighborhood center.
♫Warm love♫
But how should we write it?
I'll write it, I'll write it.
Okay, okay.
Thank you, thank you.
Give it a try.
Thank you so much.
I really can't accept this.
♫After all these years♫
I can't take it
[Breakfast]
♫Have you changed?♫
This is for the tofu pudding.
Thank you.
♫After all these years♫
Well,
ask the doctor later
♫The old times of love♫
how you should take this.
Angong Niuhuang Pill.
♫How far has it gone?♫
It's an old medicine from 1982.
I saved it for my wife.
♫I was lost in a distance♫
She never got to use it.
No, no.
It's yours now.
No, no, this is too expensive.
♫I can't forget♫
Mr. Zhou, I can't accept this.
Please take it back. I can't take it.
♫The first growth♫
Listen, I don't like polite refusals.
Siyi is still young.
♫The world♫
For her,
♫How many emotions are there?♫
you need to take good care of yourself.
♫I love you♫
I know.
♫In dreams or in the south♫
♫Wind blows gently♫
♫On you♫
♫That's me♫
♫Thinking of you deeply♫
Administrator!
Manager!
Come here.
The server is done.
All right.
Hurry up.
Qiang.
I'm saying, take it easy.
The way you're doing it,
no amount of keyboards will be enough.
Why are you so talkative?
Just change it quickly.
When are you coming back?
Still playing around? Why aren't you looking for a job?
I want to look around a bit more.
What's the rush?
The financing environment is so bad right now.
Take a little more time to regroup.
Qiang,
if you ask me,
you should just give up on starting a business.
You'd better come back soon.
Your parents are going crazy.
Just find a steady job to work.
It's better than now, right?
Xingchi and I, because of you,
both got a beating.
We can still take it,
but our butts can't handle it anymore.
All of them will be from the elite universities.
Do you believe that?
Okay, okay, Qiang.
I know.
That website you had before,
the idea was really good.
It's a shame it didn't work out, right?
What's the use of creativity in the Internet?
You don't know anything.
Ideas are useless.
Then what's useful?
Sir,
excuse me.
I'm also in the internet business.
You're a senior in the field.
I'd like to ask for your advice.
I've been starting businesses since 1995 until now.
I've failed four times.
Are you sure you want to hear my opinion?
Failure is the mother of success.
Even in the toughest times,
Ma Huateng wanted to sell Tencent.
But it turned out well in the end, didn't it?
You just came to Beijing, right?
How did you know?
I've seen many young people like you.
Carrying passion and dreams,
struggling for a few years,
you'll end up with a broken heart
and an empty wallet, slinking away.
There are those who fail,
but aren't there also those who succeed?
How will I know if I can make it if I don't try?