[NORTHWARD]
[Episode 12]
No.
I want to play with the dog.
Fenghua!
Look.
Here.
This is your little brother.
When you have time,
take him for a walk around the street.
It's his first time here.
Fenghua is busy.
She needs to do her homework.
The college entrance exam is next year.
She doesn't have time.
I have time. I have time.
Homework can be done anytime.
Let's go, little brother.
I'll take you out to play.
There's no need to be polite with your sister.
I want to go play by the river.
Fenghua.
You don't have to buy too many of those osmanthus cakes that I like!
Two catties would be enough!
I haven't heard her call me Grandma since I got here!
Who taught her such manners?
What do you mean she didn't?
She called you as soon as she came in.
You didn't hear it?
My ears are deaf. I didn't hear it!
Sister-in-law,
I didn't hear it either.
Then your hearing must be pretty bad.
Alright, Mom,
don't be angry.
What kind of mother is she?
She's just a bad person.
Can't even raise a child properly.
Like mother, like daughter.
She's always been like this.
What's your name?
You mean my original name or my current one?
How many names do you have?
I used to be called Xiaojun,
but now Grandma calls me Xiaobao.
Bao as in "baby."
Here you go, kid.
Are you from the same village as my grandma?
Then where do you live?
I forgot.
Adopted?
What were you thinking?
Calm down.
Aren't I here to discuss it with you?
What's there to discuss?
It's already been decided!
I'm going to talk to Maotian.
Why isn't he back yet?
Mom.
I'm in charge of this family now.
If there's anything going on, you should tell me.
What is there to tell you?
It's a major matter of the Xia family!
Outsiders should keep their mouths shut!
Mom, Mom, calm down.
Let me talk to my sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law.
I have to criticize you a bit.
Our Xia family has three branches with over a dozen people,
with my brother being the only male...
Wasn't it originally five branches?
Why are there only three branches now?
Where did the other two go?
Whatever, it doesn't matter.
Whether it's three branches or five,
shouldn't we all live our own separate lives?
When Maotian and I first came here,
life was so hard,
yet I didn't see any of you guys caring about us.
Who told you guys to leave back then?
If you didn't drag him away,
would Maotian have left home to make a living?
Why don't you take him back then?
I'm not getting involved in this.
Mom.
Honghong.
Son, you're back!
I missed you so much.
Gosh.
You've lost weight.
Look how thin you've become.
Look at my brother, he's all sweaty.
-He's sweating all over.
-Mom,
there must be a reason why you and Honghong are back, right?
You're finally back.
Listen to what your mother has to say.
It's good news, wonderful news!
Wonderful news!
You couldn't find better news even if you searched with a lantern!
You couldn't!
What good news?
Your mother
thinks Fenghua isn't good enough because she's a girl,
so she bought you a boy from someone else
to be our son.
Isn't it great news?
It's great, isn't it?
Now you have a son.
The family line will continue.
You're a father again!
I'm an aunt again!
I have a grandson now!
Look how happy my brother is.
What?
Is that true?
Grandma told me that
your family only has one daughter
and there is no male heir, so I'm here to be the son.
In the future, I'll get all the family inheritance.
Family inheritance?
Did my grandma not tell you
about our family's situation?
Your family has a big ship,
weighing around a thousand tons, right?
This kid is so mischievous.
Fenghua, who is he?
Mom!
What were you thinking!
What era are we living in?
How can your thinking still be so feudal?
I'm not being feudal!
It's because
girls
can't be recorded in the family genealogy!
If you don't have a son,
who will continue your family line when you get old?
Who will?
If it can't be continued, then so be it!
I don't even know what I'm doing with my life yet!
Isn't that Fenghua's grandma?
Who can control what happens after death?
Son!
Then our Xia Family
will have no descendants!
Back in the Jiajing period, our Xia Family
was a prestigious clan!
The family genealogy is this thick!
I can't allow our bloodline to stop here
just because of you
and your good-for-nothing wife!
Aren't you worried that your father wouldn't be able to rest in peace?
Our father wouldn't be able to rest in peace!
My father wouldn't be that petty!
God! God!
Mom. Mom.
Oh, my darling!
Come out and see this!
Mom.
Stop crying. Stop it.
Look at your good-for-nothing son!
Mom.
Get up.
You're just upset that we don't have a son, right?
It's simple. Just let your son divorce me
and find someone else to give birth to a son for your family!
What are you talking about?
Let me tell you.
I, Li Yan, am content with just having a daughter.
I absolutely won't raise someone else's child!
Enough, can't you just endure a little?
Haven't I endured enough?
You don't get to decide!
You don't get to decide.
I don't get to decide my family's affairs?
What, so you're to decide them?
Mom, look, the neighbors are all here.
Let's talk back inside.
I'm not going inside! I'm not going inside!
Look at her! Just look at her!
She's doing this on purpose!
It's all your fault!
Stop it, okay?
You wicked woman!
What do you want?
All of you, stop it!
Who are you putting on a show for?
Sister.
Don't call me that.
I'm not your sister.
My father won't let you in our family.
Why?
You're just a little kid.
I don't need to explain myself to you.
I don't eat much, and I'm easy to feed.
I also won't take the family inheritance away from you.
Then why are you here?
Before Grandma bought me,
I hadn't eaten for three days.
I want to live. I don't want to die.
What do you want to eat?
Let me think.
Let's go.
Fenghua!
Do you know something happened to your family?
Yeah, he just told me.
So it's you.
Behave yourself, you hear me?
Pretty impressive.
Your grandma must be crazy.
How can she do something like this?
You once said
that you'd fight anyone who dared to bully me.
My grandma, I'll leave her to you.
You guys, give up already.
I won't give birth to or raise any more children.
I'm content with having one daughter in my life.
If you want to complain about only having one male in three branches,
you can raise him yourself.
Let him be Maotian's little brother.
Listen to her. Just listen.
Is that how a human being talks?
You're right.
I'm not a human being.
Ever since I married into Xia Family,
I've been treated like a dog.
I'm even worth less than a dog!
The year I gave birth to Fenghua,
during my postpartum confinement,
did any of you ever cook a meal for me
or wash a single diaper?
Fenghua would cry all night long,
and I would spend night after night
pacing back and forth in the room, holding her.
How many days did I go without a full night's sleep?
But did any of you guys ever help me?
Poor Fenghua had it even worse.
Other children were loved by their grandma and grandpa,
but not her.
As soon as she was born and you saw she was a girl,
you didn't even look at her.
You just left.
Whenever you saw her, you always belittled her with snide remarks.
How do you think that made she feel?
When she was little, she used to ask me,
"Why does Grandma hate me so much?"
"Am I really your child?"
"Was I picked up by the river?"
I wouldn't have picked her up even if I found her.
I wouldn't have taken her even if she were given to us for free.
I dare you guys to say that again!
What if I say it again?
I wouldn't have taken her even if she were given to us for free.
Don't you dare
say things like that about my daughter again!
If you are so capable, give birth to a son yourself!
What nonsense are you talking about?
You know what?
He is my son!
I can't stand you people anymore!
If you've got the guts, give me a boy!
I'm very happy with the daughter I gave birth to!
Why must I have a son?
-Enough!
-I'm not ashamed at all!
Will you guys ever stop?
I'm begging you guys.
Save me some face, okay?
We'll discuss the child matter later.
There's no room for discussion!
Let me tell you, Xia Maotian.
I, Li Yan, will only have one child in this lifetime,
and that's our Fenghua!
As for other people's children,
whoever wants to raise them can do so.
If you dare to give in,
I'll divorce you!
Brother.
You are the head of the household.
Eat slowly.
Here you go.
[Special price for a set: 18 yuan]
What are you going to do?
Don't worry.
My mom will never agree.
If she really gets pushed to her limit,
she will divorce my dad.
That's exactly what makes it troublesome.
Your dad is filial.
He always listens to your grandmother.
If they really end up divorcing,
you'll feel guilty, right?
This kind of thing would never happen in your family.
Things would be so much better if I were a boy.
I think,
your dad might not be able to handle this alone.
We need to get help from the outside.
What kind of help?
Maotian.
Maotian!
Don't be a coward this time.
Otherwise, your wife and daughter
will be bullied to death by your mother.
Boss Xie.
I'm not stupid.
How could I possibly agree to such a ridiculous thing?
What did you tell your mother just now?
You said you'd discuss it later!
That's my mother.
How can I disobey her?
Well, disobedience,
in the ancient times and
in the Confucian culture,
was considered unfilial.
If you were unfilial,
people might laugh at you,
and you might even end up in jail.
But what era are we living in now?
You need to have a broader vision
when tackling issues.
You can't just stick to the old ways.
No matter how society develops,
people still need to be filial, right?
Sure. Of course you should be filial,
but you can't be blindly filial.
Exactly!
Let me tell you,
at a time like this,
if you don't think from your wife and daughter's perspective,
and their hearts end up getting broken,
there will be no turning back.
It's too late already!
Xia Maotian, listen to me.
Go back and be your mom's filial son.
From now on,
I'll take care of Fenghua,
and we'll live on our own.
You go your way, and I'll go mine.
From this point on, we part ways!
Mom!
What are you doing?
You guys...
Alright, stop it.
We can live just fine without a man!
Let's go! Let's go!
Mom!
Dad! Talk some sense into Mom!
She's not just saying this out of anger!
You see?
She's always talking about getting a divorce!
Always threatening to divorce me!
I can't live like this anymore!
Hey, you guys...
Stand up!
Act like a man!
Mom, I...
What kind of photo is this?
So ugly.
Mom.
I've made up my mind.
Yan and I can't raise this child.
You must raise him!
Our Xia family
can't end with your generation.
If you don't raise him, I'm not leaving!
I'm going to live here!
Living here seems quite nice.
The bed is so soft and comfortable.
Brother, why didn't you buy one for Mom?
He doesn't care about me at all!
Brother,
don't get so worked up.
We're not asking you to raise this child for real.
We're going to take him back to the village with us later.
All you need to do
is transfer money to my card every month.
This child's name
will still be recorded in your family genealogy.
Isn't that great?
What era are we living in?
Who still cares about family genealogy?
I do!
Your children
and every following generation will!
When we're alive, we are members of the Xia family,
and even after we die,
we'll be buried in the Xia family's ancestral grave!
We... We cannot forget our ancestors!
We can't.
There are no outsiders here.
You don't have to keep up the act anymore.
What are you talking about?
What act am I putting on?
Stop acting, okay?
Last week,
the village secretary called me.
What's a village secretary?
He explained everything very clearly.
What did he tell you?
He said someone's interested in our village's land
and wants to invest in developing a photovoltaic base.
What's a photovoltaic base?
Stop talking.
The relocation compensation
isn't a small amount, is it?
Don't listen to
his nonsense!
Nothing has been decided yet!
It's not even close to being finalized,
yet he's already making plans for it!
Don't listen to him!
Don't you worry.
I won't take a penny of that relocation money.
You and Honghong can take it all.
Brother!
Keep your voice down!
Brother...
Brother, sit down.
Don't be anxious.
Listen.
I won't agree with this.
No matter what,
you're still a part of the Xia family,
and you're the only male. As long as...
Let me finish first.
We won't take the money,
but you have to take the child with you.
If you don't trust me,
we can go to the notary office
and sign a transferring contract for the relocation compensation.
But I'm begging you guys,
from now on,
don't come and upset my wife and daughter anymore.
Can you do that?
Those two... They're my life.
Brother. We won't do that. We won't.
Mom is just looking out for you,
you know?
Don't interrupt.
Does Yan agree to this?
If you take this child away,
we can earn the money ourselves.
So, this is settled then.
Don't come saying that I forced you into this.
Do you hear me?
I'm doing this willingly.
I won't go back on my word!
Fenghua.
It's okay.
You know,
your father actually loves you very much.
Don't worry.
He won't let anyone hurt you.
Why are you crying?
You're usually so talkative,
but you fall apart at crucial moments.
Alright, alright.
I'm scared...
Why are you scared?
Your parents are still alive!
Whoever dares to bully my daughter,
I'll fight them to death!
Fenghua.
Let me say a few words.
A good dog doesn't block the way.
Sorry, I'll make way for you.
I'm not talking about you.
Fenghua.
Grandma was thoughtless this time.
I'm sorry for the trouble I've caused you two.
I was wrong.
From now on,
just
listen to your parents
and be filial to them.
Grandma's leaving now.
You talk.
What about the child?
Didn't you say you wouldn't raise this child?
I'll take him back, and someone will raise him.
Our family isn't the only one in the village short of male heirs.
If you don't want him, others will.
Sister!
Let's go, let's go.
We're leaving.
Take care.
Come on.
Maotian.
This... I just bought this!
Buy another one.
The rice is still in the cooker!
Mom! Mom!
Alright, I'm leaving now.
I was cooking, too.
Alright. Alright.
So they gave in?
Yeah, they did.
Hey.
We'll buy another one.
Don't give everything...
Alright, alright.
Go back, no need to see us off.
Give this to me.
Hurry up and go.
No need to see us off.
Uncle, it's that kid!
Okay.
Don't block the way.
If we're late, we'll miss the bus.
Don't rush, old lady.
Excuse me, may I ask
what your relationship with this child is?
He is...
He's my relative's child.
Do you have his ID card?
He's too young,
so we haven't had the chance to get him one yet.
She bought me...
Don't talk nonsense!
If you keep talking nonsense, I'll beat you!
I'll actually beat you!
Come here.
Come on.
Little boy.
-I'm a police officer.
-What's going on now?
Don't be afraid. Say whatever you want.
Officer.
I lied to you just now.
We actually picked up this child on the street.
I've heard of picking up money,
but picking up a child?
You think police officers are that easy to fool?
Officer, please save me!
Bad people kidnapped me.
My dad's name is Zhang Liangyong.
My mom's name is Liu Cuiying.
I don't know where my home is. I've forgotten everything.
Come on.
Come with me.
Come here.
Child trafficking, huh?
No, Officer!
Get up first.
Come on, get up.
Stand up and talk.
Our family needs a male heir,
and the neighbors had two boys,
so they gave us one.
I even had to pay them!
I don't know anything else!
Brother, help our mom!
Shen.
This must be a misunderstanding.
This must be a misunderstanding!
My mom is uneducated and doesn't understand the law.
She's old and muddled.
We'll leave the child to you.
Please forgive my mom.
Whether to forgive her or not is not up to me to decide.
It depends on what she's done.
-Old lady.
-I didn't do anything!
You can't leave now.
You need to come back to the station with me
and clarify the situation.
I won't!
Stop right there!
I said stop!
You have to come back with me!
Dad!
I won't go!
I can't go.
Isn't this going too far?
As I said before,
I'll fight anyone who dares to bully you.
But she's my grandma.
Having second thoughts?
Alright then.
I'll ask the court to reduce her sentence by a few years.
Fenghua, don't always repay kindness with ingratitude, okay?
Next time you're in trouble, don't come to me.
I'll just watch you cry yourself to death.
You wouldn't be able to bear it.
Why wouldn't I?
I was born to be wicked,
and you're destined to be tortured.
Your tears are my medals!
Try saying that again!
[Flower Street]
Stop right there!
You... I dare you to say that again!
Don't catch a cold.
The police looked into the situation
and gave your grandma a punishment and a reprimand.
It almost scared the old lady to death.
Whether it's the buyer or the seller,
child trafficking
is morally wrong.
They should all be sentenced to death.
Don't talk nonsense.
Fenghua.
I...
I'm sorry.
Rest assured.
If anything like this happens again,
I'll confront them right away
without giving face to anyone.
It's not necessary.
It is.
I don't have much in this life
that I can be proud of.
The only thing I can boast about to others
is
my daughter.
Dad...
Thank you, Daughter,
for allowing me to
stand up
and be a real man at the crucial moment.
Be careful, Boss Xie.
You're having a day off today?
That's right.
Boss Xie, come take a look at the vegetables.
I've bought everything.
I see.
Boss Xie, you're done shopping?
Buy from me next time.
Alright, I'll buy from you next time.
Hey...
Boss Xie, you're here.
These fish need some oxygen.
Look, their bellies are already facing up.
Don't get me started.
I can't even sell the live ones.
Boss Xie, why don't you buy some?
Given our relationship,
I'll give you 40% off.
40%?
Then if I buy the ones with their bellies up,
can you make it even cheaper?
Boss Xie, the belly-up ones don't taste good.
Buy the live ones.
They're all going to die in the end anyway.
I'll just buy two of these belly-up ones.
Give me a better price, okay?
Welcome.
I'll pick two out for you.
Big sale today. Welcome.
Flower Street Floating Supermarket.
[Floating Supermarket]
-Maotian!
-Boss Xie!
I see
the floating supermarket is really up and running now.
Yes, yes.
Right?
That's great.
Buying groceries?
Just our for a stroll.
Alright.
Keep up the good work!
Okay.
Big sale today. Welcome.
Flower Street Floating Supermarket.
Come on.
Press the clutch all the way down.
I did.
Come on, let me help you shift gears.
Move your hand away.
Release the clutch slowly.
Step on the gas slowly.
Step on the gas.
Step on the gas!
I've never seen anyone so clumsy.
Instructor!
Give me one more chance!
What's wrong with you again?
Go do your homework.
Dad.
Is it because Uncle Xia opened a floating supermarket
and you're not happy about it?
Get lost!
Dad, why don't you open one, too?
With your connections, you'd definitely make money.
If you have something to say, just spit it out.
Don't keep it bottled up and make yourself sick.
It's not that I can't open one,
but if I do,
wouldn't I be stealing your Uncle Xia's business?
That's called being shameless.
So what do you plan to do?
What are you looking for?
The invoice for the ship I bought.
Your mom should have put it here.
This one.
It should be this one.
I'm thinking,
if things really don't work out,
then I... I'll have to...
[Yunqi Driving School Training Price List]
Who... Who went to learn driving?
Why aren't you asleep yet?
You went to learn how to drive a truck?
Why didn't you discuss this with me beforehand?
Driving a truck is not a job for women.
Take Zhang as an example. Driving a truck
caused him so many health problems,
like kidney stones
and herniated discs.
This...
The money he earned wasn't even enough to cover his hospital bills.
Why did you do that?
Have you checked our family's finances?
Do you know how much money
our family has left now?
If we're short on money, I can go out and earn some.
How?
Besides seafaring,
what else can you do?
You're right. I can't do anything else.
I can't do anything.
Even Xia Maotian knows to find a backup plan.
What about you?
You do nothing every day,
just sitting around.
If it were just our family struggling,
we could manage by being frugal.
But our family
still owes
so many dividends to the neighbors.
Are we not paying them back?
Then what?
Our whole family just
run away from debts?
I know you care about me
and worry about me suffering.
But now,
we really have no way out.
In the past, you carried the burden alone.
Now,
let's carry it together.
You can save some energy.
Xia's floating supermarket
has already started making a profit.
How about...
[The main framework of China's national highway network, the "five vertical and seven horizontal" national trunk lines, is basically connected.]
The traffic industry development statistics announcement
released by the Ministry of Transport in 2006 shows that
by the end of 2006,
the total length of highways in China was
3,457,000 kilometers.
The number of commercial vehicles on highways nationwide was
8,025,800.
The completed highway investment was
623,105,000,000 yuan.
The total investment exceeded 1,500,000,000,000 yuan.
It is estimated that by 2010,
the operational mileage will reach 85,600 kilometers.
The highway mileage in various regions continues to grow.
The length of the expressways in the eastern region
is 20,279 kilometers.
The length of the expressways in the central region
is 13,339 kilometers.
The length of the expressways in the western region
is 11,717 kilometers.
New achievements have been made in expressway construction.
Sir. Sir.
The results are out.
Our class's results.
Please stop writing and take a look at this first.
How is it?
Drilling is starting to pay off.
For this set of practice test from Jiangxi,
I initially estimated the average score to be be around
84 points or so.
But it turns out to be
[Average score: 92]
92!
Our class's average score has passed 60, Sir!
For real.
There's another joint exam next week.
No. 1 High School will also be participating.
I'm already looking forward to it.
If you can really catch up with No. 1 High School's scores,
that would make me so proud.
It seems I'll have to make a visit
to Principal Fang's school next to us.
I'm looking forward to it.
As long as your class's average score passes 60,
I'll treat you to a meal.
Alright!
If we pass, you'll treat our whole class to a meal.
Deal.
What?
Isn't that what you just said?
Treat us to a meal.
Thank you, Sir!
[Striving unceasingly with steadfast integrity]
Alright, alright.
Stop writing now.
Time's up.
Hand in your papers.
Well...
There's another set of practice exam tomorrow.
It's from Jiangxi Normal University Affiliated High School.
There's more?
Drilling every day, we're going to die from this!
Teacher, I haven't slept well for over a week.
I didn't sleep well either.
Alright, alright, everyone stop complaining.
You're just being delicate.
Do you know how much effort
the principal put into getting these test papers?
Don't take your blessings for granted.
Everyone, be safe on your way home after school.
Okay...
Why are you looking at me?
Is there something on my face?
Your grades are poor,
so of course you need drilling.
Why are you dragging us down with you?
You can slack off if you don't want to do the practice test.
No one's forcing you.
They rank our scores after each practice test,
three times a week.
Are you trying to drive us mad?
Hey, this is the school's arrangement.
What does it have to do with me?
You wrote the proposal, didn't you?
Fine, you can blame everything on me.
Alright, alright. I wrote it.
It's my fault for dragging you down.
I apologize to all of you.
How about I treat everyone to a late-night snack?
Drilling every day is so exhausting.
No one will be grateful to you for this.
When the time comes
and everyone gets into college because of this drilling you proposed,
they still won't be grateful to you.
I will.
I'll thank your whole family.
Let's go. Let's go.
Fenghua.
Go home and sleep. You've been sleeping all day.
Where's my test paper?
Already handed in.
Why didn't anyone wait for me?
Stop laughing.
I'm going to the internet cafe
to look up some information on ship selling.
Also, there's a test problem from today
which I think has a better solution to it.
You can't be serious.
Are you planning a chakra explosion or something?
What else can I do?
It's not like I have Sharingan.
If I don't power up soon,
who am I going to copy from during the official exam?
What...
I'm coming, too.
What's wrong with these guys?
Xie.
It's not that I don't want to help you.
But, indeed,
I'm willing but unable to.
You know that I used to have over a dozen ships.
But later,
I didn't make any profit, you know?
I've gradually sold six of them already.
I'll be honest with you,
I don't know
what to do with the rest.
So,
as for your ship,
I really can't take it on.
Well,
how about a discount?
How much of a discount?
15%.
How much? 15%?
Xie.
Let me tell you something you might not want to hear.
That old ship of yours,
how many years has it been running?
Do you know that no one would take it even at half price?
When you have time,
go out and see the world more.
Who's still
using ships for cargo transportation these days?
Every trip by ship is guaranteed to lose money.
Alright.
I'll do you a favor and ask around in Taizhou.
Convert that old ship of yours
into a fishing boat.
But converting the ship costs money, too.
Where am I supposed to get that kind of money?
Look.
I'll be honest with you.
The money from my neighbors,
the dividends, I haven't paid them back yet.
My wife asked me whenever she saw me
when
I could bring the money home.
What kind of life is this?
Xie.
At least
it's a desperate solution, right?
G-Give it more thought.
Eat.
You eat.
[Ship Trading] [Ship Building] [Ship Repair] [Ship Agency]
[Comprehensive Search] [Contact Information]
Will it work now that we put this online?
It's better than just waiting at home, right?
Ships are hard to sell these days.
It might be able to sell
on the internet.
Hey.
If you really sell it,
what about your dad?
We'll see about that.
A grown man can't be defeated so easily.
I don't have any other ideas right now anyways.
I'll give it one last shot.
If I can get into college,
my dad will definitely be able to pull himself together.
I'll set an example for him.
Your dad is a capable man after all.
He doesn't need you to set an example for him.
Have you guys seen what my dad looks like on the ship?
Head held high,
full of vigor,
as if he dug the canal himself.
When the ship was sold,
my dad would be dispirited.
I can't bear to see him like that.
My mom is suffering, too.
New gray hair grows at her temples every day.
Can't even pluck it all.
When I see the gray hair,
my heart feels like it's being pricked by needles.
Right now,
I don't have any grand plans.
[Comprehensive Search] [Contact Information]
I just wish
my parents don't have to work so hard.
As for everything else,
I don't think it's that important anymore.
Why did you drink so much?
Here, water.
Son...
I
am sorry.
If only
I were more capable
and could make money,
I wouldn't...
I wouldn't hold you back in your studies.
But
But I
really tried my best.
I've done my best.
In my life,
apart from seafaring,
I don't know how to do anything else.
But...
But you... You have potential.
Y-You can do it.
Your father...
Your father is useless.
Looked down upon by others...
But my son...
Y-You must be successful.
You need to...
Regain the face I've lost
for me.
Please.