[NORTHWARD]
[Episode 19]
Siyi.
Why haven't you gone home yet?
I'm not you,
so I can't
really understand how upset you are.
I just feel that if Granny were here,
she definitely wouldn't want you to be like this.
Granny would want you
to be happy.
Actually...
Actually, I'm not that upset anymore.
It's just that there's this anger inside
that I can't release.
It's suffocating.
You're angry, huh?
Wait.
[Final battle in June, let's meet at Tsinghua and Peking]
If we can't say it, just write it.
Write what?
All the emotions, the pressure,
and everything you want to express.
You can even curse if you want.
[Final battle in June, let's meet at Tsinghua and Peking]
Liu Chang,
idiot!
He didn't do anything to you.
Isn't it just about the class monitor election?
How did he not do anything to me?
He's always tattling on me.
Come on!
Write whatever you want.
[DIE, FUNCTION!]
My...
Mom...
[I HATE MY MOM!]
I agree!
Mine too!
Same.
Let's erase it.
Erase all these negative things
that affect our mood.
Why is there a pig head?
Put some effort into it.
♫Running with all my might♫
♫I don't care about what others say♫
♫My blood is burning hot♫
♫I won't let myself fall♫
Thank you.
You're welcome.
♫I don't want endless nagging and chatter♫
♫Words that make no sense♫
♫Head up, I race forward with a roar♫
♫Facing all those staring eyes♫
♫Years from now♫
The Olympic flame will return to Beijing
[Wang, Reporter]
♫Time will prove it all♫
on August 6
and be relayed through various districts and counties,
♫The charm that we gained and lost♫
passing by 56 scenic spots.
It will arrive at the Bird's Nest
♫Time gently chases on♫
on the evening of August 8 to ignite the main cauldron.
♫I'll never regret♫
Beijing
is the longing of everyone
from that year.
♫Our prideful youth♫
And it is also the final stop of the canal
♫Nothing else mattered♫
that the rising new generation from Flower Street
♫Time quietly flies by♫
had been longing for.
♫I don't want to regret♫
Where will the waves they encountered
♫The pride among the stars♫
as children flow to when they are
♫Keep running♫
in their 20s and 30s?
What did the water that passed through
♫Keep running♫
Flower Street become in the end?
No matter what circumstances we face,
with direction
comes hope.
The canal gave them guidance.
The future, however, is something they must seek for themselves.
The great river
flows northward.
♫Running with all my might♫
The vitality of youth
is like the rushing river,
♫I don't care about what others say♫
surging
with passion.
♫My blood is burning hot♫
♫I won't let myself fall♫
♫Years from now♫
Alas!
♫Time will prove it all♫
How steep! How high!
♫Everything gained and lost♫
The road to Shu
is harder than climbing to the sky.
Since the two pioneers, Can Cong and Yu Fu...
♫Time gently chases on♫
♫I'll never regret♫
♫Our prideful youth♫
What's wrong?
♫Nothing else mattered♫
♫Time quietly flies by♫
♫I'll never regret♫
♫The pride among the stars♫
My child has really suffered.
♫Keep running♫
Mom...
Draw the sword
♫Blood burning hot♫
and show its sharp edge!
Fight for glory in the college entrance exam!
♫Blood burning hot♫
One, two, three, four!
[Striving unceasingly with steadfast integrity]
Zhou Haikuo.
Qin Qi.
Yang Dahong.
Here.
Shao Xingchi.
Xie Wanghe.
Here.
Qiu Min.
Everyone, stop chatting.
Stop chatting.
Everyone, quickly lower your heads
and check your admission ticket
Is your name written correctly?
[Admission Certificate]
Is your admission ticket number correct?
This is your last chance.
After you go home,
make sure to keep your admission ticket safe.
Don't lose it.
Otherwise, the past three years of high school,
or even the past ten years of study,
will be in vain!
Later,
I will take you to see the exam venue.
Afterward,
go home and get some good rest.
Don't try to cram in the next few days.
If you haven't worked hard before, cramming now won't help.
Don't stay up late.
Conserve your energy
[Striving unceasingly with steadfast integrity]
and get prepared for the final sprint!
Do you understand?
Yes!
Come on!
Let's shout our slogan
one last time!
Youth's passion,
strive for strength!
With determination and fighting spirit, we charge forward!
Draw the sword
and show its sharp edge!
Fight for glory in the college entrance exam!
Dad.
You're back.
Hurry up and eat.
Where's Mom?
She's not back yet?
Your mom is on her way.
She'll definitely make it back tonight.
You have the exam tomorrow.
She'll definitely rush back.
Stop dawdling.
Hurry and eat.
What are you doing?
They...
They are all over the wall.
It's really annoying to look at.
Besides,
these things are all in the past.
Look.
[Motor Vehicle Driving License of the People's Republic of China]
You got your license so quickly?
It was not that hard.
[Motor Vehicle Driving License of the People's Republic of China]
From now on,
your mom and I
will take turns
driving the cab.
Hand me that rod.
Your mom and I will take shifts
to drive the cab.
As for the affairs at home,
don't worry about them.
Just focus on your studies.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
What trouble have you gotten into now, you brat?
Dad,
I've grown up.
When I get into college
and start earning money,
I'll buy you a big ship.
Alright, I'll be waiting for you.
I want the biggest ship.
How about a 10,000-ton ship?
Cut the crap.
Can a 10,000-ton ship even run on that river?
You're making empty promises again, aren't you?
You little brat!
Come here!
Put the knife down!
How dare you!
Xingchi, what are you doing?
He hit my mom!
You...
Why did you drink during the day?
Indeed.
Your kid is taking the college entrance exam tomorrow.
What are you doing?
If you want to kill me, just do it!
I've long since stopped living like a human anyway!
What are you talking about?
What... what's going on here?
Don't pull me!
Mr. Zhou,
do you know that I'm writing
The Story of Flower Street?
Yes, I do. I've been looking forward to it.
I was halfway through writing this book
when I went to apply for a cultural project,
but it got rejected.
Today, I found out
that the only spot at the cultural museum
went to Chen Bo.
Guess what he said about me?
He said I was jealous of him.
What does he have that I should be jealous of?
Why would I be jealous of a guy
who lives off his wife?
Alright. Why did you mention this?
Mr. Shao, Mr. Shao.
Hurry up and go back to studying!
I rely on my own abilities to make a living,
yet my son keeps making sarcastic comments by my side.
Who wouldn't feel bad...
Xingchi, Xingchi!
You were the one being sarcastic first!
If you're so capable, get into a good university first,
then come and mock me!
To hell with good universities!
You're from a good university, aren't you?
But you have to pay to publish your own books!
How proud you must be!
You bastard!
Stop it!
Both of you, stop it!
Mr. Shao, what's more important now?
Why are you saying this now?
Don't take frustration you feel at work out
on your wife and kid.
Exactly.
Listen to me.
Apologize to your child.
Go on. Go, go, go.
You just need to apologize to him.
Apologize.
Apologize to him.
I apologize to him?
A father apologizing to his son?
Is there any justice in this world?
I raised him for eighteen years for nothing?
Shao Bingyi!
Remember this!
From now on, I won't need you to support me anymore!
You're selfish and self-centered!
All you have is a degree,
but you're useless at work!
Every time you drink, you end up hitting my mom!
You want me to succeed, right?
I'm not taking the college entrance exam!
Don't move!
Kid!
Xingchi!
How did this...
Yuling, this...
What should we do?
Let's go, let's go.
Quickly, carry her into the room!
Get her inside the room, hurry!
Hurry!
Gosh.
Hurry up.
Mom,
I'm not going to college.
Let me take you away.
Where to?
As long as it's away from here and away from him,
we can go anywhere.
Your dad just has a bad temper
and speaks harshly,
but he did a lot for us!
No matter how much he has done for us, he has worn down our gratitude.
Mom, trust me.
I have hands and feet.
If we leave him, we'll live better.
I won't let you suffer.
Are you trying to give your mother a heart attack?
You think you've got it all figured out, huh?
College is right around the corner,
and you said you wouldn't go!
You even tore up your admission ticket!
You're unbelievable.
You're so childish.
What am I supposed to do with you?
Going to college or not isn't that important, Mom.
As long as we leave that drunkard,
life will definitely be better than it is now.
Mom, I know.
I know you're afraid I'll suffer,
or be mistreated.
I was a kid before
and couldn't take care of myself.
But I'm different now.
I've grown up.
From now on,
you have to learn to live for yourself.
Here.
Take a break.
Have the soup before you go back to studying.
I'm not hungry.
You didn't have dinner.
Are you cultivating?
Drink it up.
What university do you want to go to?
Honghuai Normal University.
With your grades,
you could get into a top university.
I'm going to a normal university because it's close to home.
You want to stay with your grandma, right?
Well...
now,
you don't have to.
You can choose a university that suits you.
Normal universities suit me just fine.
How much money can you make as a teacher?
Listen to me.
Choose finance,
or accounting.
Go to a university in a big city.
After graduation, work hard
and get a household registration in a first-tier city.
Then you can bring your brother there too.
And I'll...
You don't need to take care of me.
Really.
But your brother is your blood after all.
You should take care of him.
Come on.
How do you want me to take care of him?
Take him everywhere I go?
Spend all the money I earn in the future on him?
When he gets married, should I
buy him a house?
You left me to my grandma because you didn't want the trouble.
Now you want to leave Siwei to me.
If you don't want to be a mom, why did you have us?
This kid. We were just having a normal conversation.
Why are you getting worked up again?
We're family.
I'm doing this for your good.
Have you eaten gunpowder or something?
Why do you throw tantrums at me from time to time?
Who spoiled you like this?
I gave birth to such a heartless child.
Son.
Mom?
When did you come back?
Last night.
I couldn't
miss today.
Thank you, Mom.
Have a seat.
Dad.
Scholar Congee.
Number One Scholar Cake.
I got these recipes
from a cookbook from the Ming dynasty.
Hurry up and try them.
They might not taste good, though.
Thank you, Dad.
ID card.
Admission ticket.
Ad... Admission ticket?
This is the admission ticket.
Isn't it right here?
Ballpoint pen.
Pencil.
Eraser...
-Pencil sharpener.
They're all here.
All set?
Are you done?
I'm feeling better now.
Son,
we've checked again.
Everything's in there.
If you don't know the answer, pick B.
If there are too many Bs, pick C.
Just pick one.
Don't leave it blank. Got it?
He knows. He doesn't need you to tell him.
Fenghua,
just do your best.
You got this.
He's my son. Of course, he's got this.
Haikuo!
Hurry up.
Coming.
Do your best.
Deserter.
I can't take the exam this year...
But I still have a chance next year.
You two are just
graduating a year earlier than me.
Beijing welcomes you.
We'll create a new world for you.
The charm in motion is vibrant with energy.
Beijing welcomes you.
Those with dreams are extraordinary.
Where there's courage, there's a miracle.
Today is the first day of the 2008 college entrance examination.
This year, the national plan for university enrollment
[News Simulcast]
is 5.99 million,
with 10.5 million applicants, making this the year
with the highest number of applicants
in the history of the exam.
Let's turn our attention to the Jiangsu exam venues.
This year's college entrance exam plan
has undergone multiple adjustments and refinements,
aiming to be more scientific and fair.
Another feature of this year's exam
is a greater emphasis on assessing comprehensive qualitie
and innovative abilities.
While students are striving hard,
the construction of venues and preparations
for the Beijing Olympics are also nearing completion.
The main stadium of the Beijing Olympics,
the National Stadium, Bird's Nest,
is expected to hold its completion ceremony at the end of this month.
[Giving our best to prepare for the college entrance exam]
Everyone,
in this year's college entrance exam,
two students from our school
have scored high enough
to surpass the admission score thresholds
of top national universities!
They are
Xie Wanghe and Zhou Haikuo
from Class 3, Grade 12!
Let's extend our sincerest congratulations
to them.
[Giving our best to prepare for the college entrance exam]
Congratulations!
Everyone,
this is also the highest score
in our school's history for the college entrance exam.
Xie Wanghe and Zhou Haikuo
have proven to us that
as long as you have the strength
[Chi]
and take action,
there is no mountain too high to climb.
You scared me.
What's wrong?
Are you reluctant to graduate, just like me?
I can't wait to leave here.
Then why are you here?
There's constant fighting at home, and it's annoying,
so I'm just getting away for a bit.
What are you writing?
Give it to me.
Wanghe,
have you succeeded?
What does it mean?
It's for my future self.
One day,
when we come back to school
and see these words,
I hope that by then,
I'll be so poor that all I have left is money.
Well, I'll write something to my future self, too.
Haikuo,
be yourself.
Don't compromise your principles for a mediocre salary.
What about for a slightly higher salary?
Well, I'll say thanks.
Your turn.
Don't regret it.
Be nicer to your mom.
So you know that.
[Chi, don't regret it. Be good to your mom.] [Haikuo, be yourself. Don't give in to reality.]
[Certificate of 2008 General College Entrance Examination Results of Honghuai City]
Let me tell you,
like father, like son.
With our son's score,
aside from Peking University and Tsinghua University,
he can choose any other school in the country.
Chen Rui, Chen Rui,
come.
Come out.
Tell us, which school are you applying to?
Chen Rui!
Which university are you applying to?
Honghuai Normal University.
Wait.
Why?
Because of Ma Siyi.
Are you sure she can get in?
I'm sure.
When I went to pick up your report card at school,
I heard about her situation from the teacher.
She handed in blank papers for every subject.
That's impossible.
Her total score is zero.
Liking someone
really is a beautiful thing.
[Ma Siyi]
Your dad and I
were also once at this age.
But when you like someone,
you can't let that
ruin your own future.
You and Ma Siyi
are destined to miss each other, son.
Wait, this...
Ma Siyi, what do you want?
Why didn't you take the exam seriously?
Why did you hand in blank papers?
Do you know how much it costs
to repeat a year?
Who said I'm going to repeat a year?
Can't I choose not to go to university?
Not...
Not going to university?
Are you going to find a job?
What can you even do?
You can barely support yourself.
You don't need to be concerned about my life.
You didn't care before,
so don't bother me in the future either.
Fine.
You're not going to university, huh?
Okay.
Then quit school.
Just quit.
I should sell this house
as soon as possible.
Why are you selling it?
Flower Street has no future.
And the canal is in decline.
The house prices are dropping day by day.
I've already inquired about it.
This house is worth at least a hundred thousand now.
We can just live off the interest.
Get out!
Get out of here!
Let go of me!
Wait!
It's not your house!
What's going on?
Why are you arguing?
I'm not insisting on doing this.
Why are you getting so worked up?
I have no intention of discussing this with you.
This house is absolutely not for sale.
If you want to invest,
use your own money!
Have you gone crazy from being poor?
This house was left to Siyi by Granny.
What right do you have to sell it?
Siyi, don't worry.
We're all here for you.
She can't take this house away.
We won't let her take it!
I never said I was going to take it.
I'm just trying to discuss this with her reasonably.
Come on, you guys.
Besides,
this house belongs to my mother-in-law.
Technically, I have a right to use it.
You've remarried.
Legally,
Granny Ma is no longer your mother-in-law!
That's right!
Exactly!
Siyi is my own daughter.
Everything I do is for her own good.
If you really want what's best for her,
just keep the house.
Let's not talk about the financial aspect for now.
Emotionally,
this child surely can't bear to let it go.
Yes. Keeping this house
will at least leave this child something to hold on to.
No matter where she goes in the future,
if she gets tired or feels weary,
she'll have a place to return to.
Exactly.
Although the rent from this house doesn't bring in much,
it's still Siyi's home.
You, as her mother...
A home is where family is, okay?
They are my real family!
You abandoned me
when I needed you the most!
How can you expect me to treat you as my mother?
Blood is thicker than water.
No matter what,
I'm still your biological mother.
Grandma is gone,
but I'm still here.
No matter what happens,
I won't
leave you all alone, uncared for.
You?
How are you going to take care of me?
By selling the house, swindling all the money,
and disappearing again?
In the past, you always went to Grandma when you were in trouble.
Now it's me.
You have to squeeze every last bit out of me
before you're satisfied, don't you?
How could you say that?
Every family has its own difficulties.
Then don't be my family!
Who asked you to?
From now on,
you are you and I am me!
We'll live our separate lives.
No matter how difficult or tough it gets for me,
I will never ask you for help!
Siyi,
you didn't even get into university.
I'm not well-off either.
Who's going to support you in the future?
I will!
From now on,
you don't need to worry about Siyi.
She has me,
brothers and sisters,
and the neighbors.
As long as we're here,
we won't let Siyi suffer!
The kid is right!
Yes.
Exactly.
We're all here for her.
You're all family.
Is that enough?
I'm her only enemy here.
You heartless kid.
Fine. I'll get lost.
Siwei!
Your sister finds you annoying!
Let's get lost!
Come on, pack your things!
Pack your things!
Siyi,
don't make me leave!
I'll be good!
I'm not trying to make you leave.
When I get back on my feet,
I'll come to pick you up, okay?
No!
I don't want to go with her,
Siyi.
I'm not capable enough right now.
But when I am,
I'll come to get you, okay, Siwei?
No!
Pinky swear, pinky swear.
I'll definitely come.
Cross my heart, hope to die. Stick a needle in my eye.
Take good care of yourself, okay?
I gave birth to her, and now I'm the bad guy.
Isn't it just because I'm poor?
I'll get lost. Is that enough?
Stop crying!
Take this!
Siyi!
Let's go!
Take good care of yourself, okay?
Siyi!
I'll just pretend I never gave birth to her!
Let's go!
Siyi!
Be careful not to step on his face.
Both of us are going to Beijing.
What about you?
I'm going to Beijing too.
To work and make money.
You're really not going to repeat the year?
Let's talk about the future when it comes.
Anyway, I can't stand staying in Flower Street for even one more day.
Because of your dad?
Now, whenever I see his face,
I get so angry I can't hold it in.
I'm really afraid that one day I...
Actually, your dad is pretty good to you.
He's just a bit naggy,
but he's not a bad person.
I know.
But every time he's drunk, he hits my mom.
I really can't stand it.
I tried to persuade my mom to leave,
but she refuses to.
Why?
Maybe she just can't let go.
I don't know either.
I'll go to Beijing first.
When I make some money and buy a house,
I'll bring my mom over.
They call that capable?
Slow down!
The whole of Flower Street is picking on just me?
Hurry up!
If you don't move fast, your sister will kick you out!
Have you no shame?
Are you bullying me because I don't have a husband?
Siwei.
You're picking on me alone!
Brother-in-law!
What Brother-in-law?
Let's go!
Brother-in-law!
What's wrong?
I want Brother-in-law!
You little shameless brat!
You're so young and already calling someone Brother-in-law!
What's wrong with her mom now?
Brother-in-law!
When I make it big one day,
you won't be able to kiss my ass!
What's going on?
What brother-in-law?
Where is she taking Siwei?
You ungrateful little brat,
let's go!
Your sister likes you, huh?
Then go and live with her!
Get lost!
You said it yourself.
Brother-in-law!
Come back!
Ge Siwei!
Come back here!
Little brat!
Come back!
Ge Siwei!
Don't climb over!
Get down!
-Siwei, it's dangerous!
-Stop!
-Siwei!
-Get down! It's dangerous!
-It's dangerous!
Get down!
There's a ship!
Don't jump!
Siwei!
Siyi!
Your brother...
What happened to my brother?
Your brother, he...
What happened to him?
Why did you call him?
Auntie!
Give me back my son!
Auntie, calm down!
If you hadn't called him, he wouldn't have jumped!
Calm down, calm down!
What do you want?
Give me back my son!
Where's Siwei?
They're still conducting the search and recovery.
So far, only some of his remains have been found.
My condolences.
Your brother's fate...
was so tragic.
They killed him!
Nonsense!
He died because you were chasing him!
He jumped off the bridge to get away from you!
No!
Siyi,
it was not like that.
They killed him!
You bastard!
It was all your fault!
Bastard!
Bastard! Bastard!
Auntie.
Why did you call him?
Calm down, calm down.
If you hadn't called him, he wouldn't have died!
Give me back my son's life!
Siyi!
It was not your fault.
If anyone's to blame, it's his mother.
She actually had the nerve to turn things around and blame us.
I shouldn't have called him.
If he had just walked straight over,
maybe he wouldn't have jumped.
I've told you
several times
that it wasn't your fault.
Are you out of your mind?
Are you a nagging widow?
If his mom hadn't chased after him,
would Siwei have jumped?
The root cause is his mother.
Stop it.
Siyi,
my mom made wontons
with shepherd's purse filling.
Have some.
At least eat a little.
Otherwise, you won't be able to hold up.
I'll have to go to the hospital to take care of you.
Be good. Just eat ten of them.
I'm just worried she won't be able to handle it.
Why don't we...
go down and talk to Siyi for a bit?
What should we say when we see her?
Then what should we do?
Fenghua is with her.
Siyi won't do anything drastic.
Mom, hurry up.
Get me two more.
Siyi,
open the door.
Siyi?
Siyi.
Have some wontons.
I'll leave them here for you.
My mom said,
if you want to cry, just cry out loud.
Don't hold it in.
It's bad for your health.
I've already cried.
How come I didn't hear you cry?
If you don't know what to say, then say nothing.
Let's sleep together tonight.
You can hide under the blanket and cry.
And I'll be with you.
No need. I'm really fine.
Stop it. You've always been like this since you were a kid.
When you're hurt,
you always keep it inside and never tell anyone.
My mom said it can cause breast cancer.
Can I ask you a favor?
Go ahead.
Go out with me for a walk.
Before the college entrance exam,
Siwei dreamed of Grandma.
He dreamt of her
riding a bike with Grandpa.
I was so angry.
Why were you angry?
Grandma appeared in his dream
but ignored me.
She didn't want you to be sad.
She couldn't bear to see that.
Look ahead.
Granny's gone,
but we're still here.