[NORTHWARD]
[Episode 27]
[All departure gates except for direct flights to the USA]
[Departure Time]
[Arrivals]
Grandma.
I'm finally in Italy.
Do you remember
the story you told me
about Marford when I was young?
What kind of person was he?
Why did he go to China from Italy?
Who am I?
Where am I from?
This time,
I want to figure them out myself.
Venice has a canal too,
but it's different.
With each passing day,
I miss Flower Street more and more.
I also miss
the courtyard where you used to be.
Mayor Gu,
you didn't have to come in person.
We've confirmed that
this ship was just an ordinary cargo ship.
It's less than 100 years old.
I suggest we…
Are you sure?
Are there no other possibilities?
Mayor,
Curator Chen is right.
Actually,
the district government has been informed
to stop the excavation.
It's going to keep raining.
The drainage and protection work
will consume a lot of manpower and resources.
Our budget is limited.
Let's stop
excavating this ship, shall we?
We should spend the money on
more meaningful projects.
Alright.
I respect your opinions.
Let's stop then.
Guys.
Today is our last day
at the 116th shipwreck
archaeological site.
Mom!
We shall…
complete all
-the related paperwork
-Mom!
by 5 p.m.
The excavation finally restarted.
Why are you suddenly stopping it?
Who are you
to ask me that?
My son?
Or…
I'm a volunteer at the shipwreck site.
The decision has been made
and announced.
The shipwreck excavation is stopped.
Don't waste any more time here.
I'm wasting my time?
Then what isn't a waste of time?
Should I sit in an office drinking hot tea
and doing field research
or stay in a library traveling around
through a few hardcover books?
That's not a waste of time?
Yeah, I know you're not satisfied with me.
I didn't listen to you about which college to attend
or about what job to take.
But do you think I'm here today
just to stand against you?
So you know what you've done.
Yes.
You're my son.
I am very disappointed in you.
But today,
we'll only talk about work.
Nothing personal.
I didn't make this decision.
The experts have confirmed
that this ship
has no excavation value.
Mayor Gu.
What does this ship mean to you?
Is it just a cultural site for show
and a mere tool for Honghuai City's application for World Heritage status?
Now that the canal has become a World Heritage Site,
it's of no use to you anymore,
so you're just throwing it away?
You're going too far!
That's total nonsense!
Do you know
what happened on this ship
and who lived on it?
You don't!
They don't!
How can you say it's worthless?
There were real people living on this ship.
They might have been insignificant.
They might have been
of no value at all
in the long history.
But to their descendants and loved ones,
they were of immense value.
And we've been looking for traces.
They could very well be the ancestors
of the uncles and aunts,
grandpas and grandmas in the courtyard.
If I can prove that,
I can prove…
But the government's budget is limited!
Now that the canal has become a World Heritage Site,
the entire Honghuai is facing renovation and reconstruction.
Let me ask you.
Should the government
spend the money
on reconstruction that's closely related
to people's lives
or on a sunken ship
that experts have said
to be worthless?
Okay.
I got it.
Then please allow me,
on behalf of Grandpa Zhou,
my family in the courtyard,
and Ma Siyi to whom I made a promise,
to formally request
that you transfer the excavation of the sunken ship
to me.
I'll raise funds myself to complete the subsequent work.
I'll prove to you
that the place you think is meaningless
will turn out to be meaningful;
on top of choices you think are wrong,
there will be new choices;
the boy
who is worthless in the eyes of the world
will be recognized by his family.
All he needs is just a little trust.
Unload!
Hurry up with the delivery.
Recently,
there's been traffic control.
The driving restriction was only lifted yesterday.
We expect another batch tonight.
[No smoking]
We're already overloaded.
We can't take more parcels.
[You can trust us with your parcels.]
Every station is overloaded now.
You're the last link in the chain.
If you don't release the pressure,
it'll be more chaotic upstream.
♫The words you said linger in my mind♫
Hurry up.
♫I keep asking myself why♫
Parcels are pouring in,
but we can't let our service slip.
♫I'm not good with words♫
[We're the experts in shipping parcels.]
Be careful when sorting.
♫Once again, I was knocked down♫
Leave some time for the delivery colleagues.
I know the workload has been intense lately,
♫The light you see♫
♫Is not my light♫
but we have to get through it.
You hear me?
♫What does it even look like?♫
Yes!
♫But I...♫
♫From the start to the very end, I've never changed♫
[Fenghua Express]
♫In our relationship♫
♫Who ended up the loser?♫
♫Even if we start again♫
[Fenghua Express]
♫I'll still be here♫
♫Every choice we make♫
♫Just leads us back to where we began♫
Lunch at midnight.
♫Endless crossroads♫
Work a bit longer,
♫Emotions out of sync♫
and we'll save on breakfast too.
♫Look at me♫
Eat up.
After eating, get back to work.
Alright.
♫One last time♫
Hurry up and eat.
Fenghua.
♫Endless crossroads♫
Here.
♫Emotions out of sync♫
Eat something.
I'm fine. You eat first.
♫Look at me♫
I'll sort these parcels first.
♫One last time♫
They can deliver them after finishing eating.
It'll get cold if you don't eat now.
It's okay.
Don't worry about me.
You…
♫The words you said linger in my mind♫
♫I keep asking myself why♫
♫I'm not good with words♫
♫Once again, I was knocked down♫
Be careful.
♫Gazing at the stars and the distant sky♫
Have some water.
Have some water. It's already noon.
♫A faint light glimmering♫
♫I'm chasing it all alone♫
♫Watching loneliness fall like rain♫
Fenghua, do you want some water?
♫Shattered by them♫
I'll get it for you.
♫Blooming into flowers once again♫
♫But I...♫
♫From the start to the very end, I've never changed♫
♫In our relationship♫
♫Who ended up the loser?♫
♫Even if we start again♫
Careful, careful!
♫I'll still be here♫
♫Every choice we make♫
♫Just leads us back to where we began♫
♫Endless crossroads♫
♫Emotions out of sync♫
♫Look at me♫
♫One last time♫
♫Endless crossroads♫
♫Emotions out of sync♫
♫Look at me♫
♫One last time♫
The extremely hot weather
ushers in the peak season for food delivery.
We expect that within a month,
our order volume will reach a new high.
Headquarters requires us
to take advantage of this opportunity
to become more competitive.
We should see this month
as the final battle
against other platforms.
Within this month, we need to
narrow the gap with other platforms
and expand
Bee's market share.
We're having this meeting
to discuss
whether we should temporarily raise the commission
to boost the delivery riders' motivation.
An extra yuan per order.
I disagree.
Why?
The so-called temporary solution
can't be temporary.
If we raise it when it's over 38 degrees Celsius,
at what temperature will we lower it?
The reality is that
the commission is easy to raise
but hard to lower.
Once we raise it,
it'll become the new standard.
The money for the delivery riders
can't come from the customers
or the merchants.
It can only be deducted from our profits.
The current situation is that
our profits are as low as they can be.
If we give delivery riders
an extra yuan for each order,
the company will be losing money.
We can tell the delivery riders
that this extra yuan
is a high-temperature allowance.
High-temperature allowance?
What about a low-temperature allowance?
What about allowances for stormy weather?
Mr. Wanghe,
you'll only stay here for a year.
If you set such a high standard for us,
after you leave,
how are we supposed to move on?
Right?
If you insist on going your own way
and raising the commission,
I hope you can get the head office
to make rules about it.
Each district will
strictly follow the rules.
That's no problem.
Am I right, everyone?
Mr. Meng, what do you think?
Rules are rigid,
but people are flexible.
In fact,
in the company's commission standards,
there are already provisions
about temporarily raising the commission during extreme weather.
We're just specifying them.
Let's do this.
Wanghe,
you'll be in charge of raising the commission.
But
after it cools down,
you need to lower
the commission back.
No problem, Mr. Meng.
Next,
our top priority
is to make preparations
to prevent heatstroke.
Each station
needs to prepare
heatstroke medicine and mung bean soup.
In this regard,
Shao Xingchi's
Station 203 in Haidian District
has done a great job.
The delivery riders there are very satisfied.
Additionally,
the system needs to be optimized again.
Haikuo.
How long is the gap
between the time we give to delivery riders
and the time customers expect?
Usually three minutes.
The time shown to customers is 40 minutes,
while the time shown to delivery riders
is 37 minutes.
Mr. Meng,
I suggest we shorten the time
given to delivery riders by another minute.
Everyone,
great rewards will bring forth brave men.
If they can't do it, they don't have to take the order.
Wanghe,
simply shortening the system time
can only bring extensive growth.
Then what's your idea?
It's okay. Just speak your mind.
Mr. Meng.
The delivery riders of Bee
currently use third-party mapping services.
The odds of them providing the optimal routes
haven't reached 90% yet.
To some extent,
this has affected the delivery efficiency.
So I suggest
we launch our self-developed map ahead of schedule.
I've tested it.
It's already very stable.
It only needs final-stage debugging.
Isn't that too risky?
Haikuo,
if you dare to take responsibility for your advice,
I'll dare to heed it.
Do you dare?
Of course.
If anything goes wrong with the self-developed map,
I'll pack up and leave immediately.
Any other suggestions?
If not,
we'll proceed with this plan.
Meeting adjourned.
Haikuo,
stay for a moment.
I want to talk with you.
Sit down.
You're more excellent than I thought.
You flatter me, Mr. Meng.
Are you interested in coming to the headquarters?
Headquarters?
To do what?
To be the Chief Technology Officer.
The previous CTO
was poached by Eat Well.
Well,
compared with having a headhunter poach someone,
I prefer
to promote someone in the company.
Mr. Meng,
Wanghe still needs help.
I need help too.
Haikuo,
you're a genius programmer.
Running around for business with him
is a waste of your talent.
How about this?
Think it over.
Come to me when you've made up your mind.
It's too sudden.
Please let me think about it.
Whether you come or not,
you must keep it a secret.
It involves backend data.
Safety first.
[Bee Delivery]
What's going on?
Mr. Meng just asked me…
to keep up the good work.
That's all.
He didn't mention anything about a raise?
No.
It's okay.
Keep working.
Once our self-developed map is running smoothly,
I'll apply for it for you.
Where's Xingchi?
Downstairs.
[Fenghua Express]
Fenghua!
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Sit down for a while.
I'm fine.
I didn't have breakfast this morning.
I think my blood sugar's low.
Oh, you silly girl.
How could you skip breakfast?
Have some water.
I'm fine.
Why are you so worried?
You're our backbone.
You can't go down.
I won't.
Don't worry.
Finish the work you have on hand.
I must see it tomorrow.
Even if it means working overtime.
Mr. Xie,
working late?
I'll leave soon.
I'll head off then.
How's the progress on your end?
It's alright.
What do you mean by alright?
Where did you find those people?
They're all so lazy.
Working overtime is killing them.
Just pull your weight.
Why think so much?
If the sky falls, the tall will hold it up.
Alright then.
You hold on.
I'm leaving.
Aren't you having dinner with us?
Another time.
I have plans with Xiaohui.
Your girlfriend before friends, huh?
Zhou Haikuo, you've changed.
You should date someone too.
I know you like being single,
but you can't stay single forever.
Get lost.
Do I look good?
Yes.
Do you like it?
If you do, let's buy it.
It's over 3,000 yuan. Too expensive.
It's fine.
This month, I have overtime pay
and a high-temperature allowance. I can afford it.
And then live off scraps?
I can always earn more in the future.
I'm competent anyway.
You haven't established yourself at Bee yet.
I have.
Mr. Meng had a private talk with me.
What did he say?
He wants me
to work at headquarters as the CTO.
Really?
What exactly did he say?
I didn't agree.
Why?
Wanghe brought me into the company.
I need to discuss this with him first.
Wanghe doesn't know how to code.
What's there to discuss with him?
You don't understand.
No.
I don't understand.
I don't understand anything.
Then from now on,
you don't need to tell me about these things anymore.
Wait.
What did I say?
Why are you upset?
You're on your period?
How about I get you some hot water?
What do you want to eat?
My treat.
How about a barbecue?
I know
you and Wanghe are good friends,
and he's helped you a lot.
But you're an adult.
You can only depend on yourself in the future.
I don't want my husband
to be someone who can't even decide
the direction of his own career!
Lion's head meatballs.
Braised shredded tofu.
Stir-fried shredded eel.
Here's rice.
Two servings of rice.
Did you plant a bug on me?
I mentioned this morning that I wanted to eat hometown food,
and you brought it to me.
Don't flatter yourself.
I want to eat it too.
Here.
Eat up.
How's it?
Not quite there,
but not bad.
Haikuo's grandpa used to say that
when you crave hometown food,
you're not missing the food
but feeling homesick.
What?
You feel homesick?
Don't you miss home?
Occasionally,
when I feel wronged.
I barely think about it other times.
What about you?
How did Xiang Yu die?
Surrounded by enemies on all sides.
If a soldier keeps thinking about going home,
he'll lose the courage to fight.
I'm still fighting.
You're a girl.
You can be vulnerable sometimes,
but I can't.
Everyone under me is watching.
I can't let them see
my vulnerable side,
not even once.
I want to eat eel noodles.
I'll make some for you.
Please don't.
Given your cooking skills,
I'd have a fishy taste in my mouth afterward.
And I'd have to praise you against my better judgment.
What's Xingchi been up to lately?
His cooking skills aren't good either.
He learned to make eel noodles from Uncle Zhou.
And lion's head meatballs.
Then go to him.
♫When the moon hangs in the sky♫
♫And it's cooling in the yard♫
♫Who is still by your side?♫
Are you angry?
♫As time passes♫
Seriously?
Do you have to be so possessive?
♫Is a lifetime really that long?♫
Shut up.
Fine.
I'm the one who's possessive.
♫When youthful company fades♫
Let's imagine
we're in a period show.
♫Leaving only small talk and pleasantries♫
Your Majesty.
It's time to take your medicine.
♫Spring feels short, while autumn lingers♫
Are you alright?
♫A gentle breeze carries dreams away♫
What's wrong?
Nothing.
♫Dreamland and dreams♫
-I haven't eaten all day and…
-Sit down.
I'm tired.
♫Life is long♫
What are you thinking?
You're the manager.
You pay people
♫No need to dwell♫
to work for you.
Why are you exhausting yourself like this?
What's the point?
♫Like moonlight♫
Your Majesty…
♫Don't forget♫
Stop fooling around.
I'm serious.
I can't rest.
♫Life is long♫
Why not?
The team is already falling apart.
♫No need to dwell♫
If I don't lead by example,
their resentment will only grow.
♫Like moonlight♫
I planned
to tough it out first
and then hire someone who knows management.
♫The old times♫
When He was here,
he helped me a lot,
so I wasn't so tired.
It's just me now.
I'm struggling to keep it together.
I'll ask He to come back.
No need.
Without him,
I can still keep the station running.
Delicious.
[Bar]
Anyway, she thinks I'm Wanghe's underling.
So she basically thinks I'm a dog.
Why have you come alone?
I just have.
You had dinner by yourself?
None of your business.
Let's drink.
What's wrong with you this time?
You fought with Xiaohui again?
I suspect
Xiaohui has started menopause early.
What's the reason this time?
She's jealous of you.
Jealous of me?
What did I do?
Meng wants Haikuo to be the CTO at headquarters.
Haikuo said he needs
to ask for your opinion first.
Xiaohui is upset about it.
When did that happen?
The day
when Meng talked with me alone.
I asked you what he said,
and you said nothing.
He asked me to keep it a secret
for data security.
I didn't really understand it.
He told you to keep it secret, so you did?
That's not the point, okay?
Shouldn't you be asking
why Xiaohui is upset?
Why is Xiaohui upset?
She thinks…
I don't even want to say it.
Anyway,
recently, every few days,
she picks a fight with me.
It's wearing me out.
Leave her if you can't stand her.
Just break up with her.
You handled things like that,
and you're still single now.
Aren't you single?
I won't be soon.
Wonderful.
Congratulations.
Why are you drinking so fast?
I'm happy.
Waiter!
A 12-pack of beer, please.
Enough. No more drinking.
We still have to work tomorrow.
Worry about yourself.
I know what I'm doing.
It won't affect anything.
Wanghe,
I've thought it through.
Don't worry about Xiaohui.
I won't go to headquarters.
Haikuo.
To be honest,
I really need you right now.
I hope you can stay and help me.
But Xiaohui isn't wrong.
You should decide
your career direction by yourself.
Whether you succeed or fail,
you need to learn
to take responsibility for your own decisions.
You also need to be responsible for Xiaohui.
Why are you looking at me?
Don't you already have the answer in your heart?
Just follow your heart.
What I say goes!
I say I'm not leaving, and that's that!
Come on.
To our friendship.
Cheers!
[Bar]
Mr. Zhou!
Uncle Shao.
Bingyi, slow down.
Look at him.
Wait for me.
Mr. Zhou.
It's confirmed.
One of my ancestors
indeed worked as a porter.
Really?
But the name is no longer traceable.
Why?
My family genealogy records
were burned during the war.
Only some fragments were left.
Look.
The writing is all blurred.
-Yeah.
-How do I know
this person worked as a porter?
It's because at the end of the Qing dynasty,
this person made a fortune
by selling tea.
He went back and built an ancestral hall for his clan.
That's why it was recorded.
This is history,
the folk history of people living by the canal.
I think
we shouldn't just look into our families.
Our neighbors on Flower Street,
we should ask them all.
Maybe every family has their own
stories.
-Yeah.
-Right?
So this is oral history?
Oral history is still history.
When Sima Qian wrote "Records of the Grand Historian,"
from emperors and generals
to peddlers and porters,
he went door to door to make inquiries.
Yes.
Jing Ke's assassination attempt on Qin Shi Huang
was only recorded in detail
because he ran into Xia Wuju
when he was visiting a neighbor.
Yes, indeed.
We don't have his talent,
but if we put in the effort,
we can also contribute to filling in
the blanks in official history.
Absolutely.
So this will also be considered history in the future?
Of course.
You'll become part of history too.
Gosh.
My dad,
Uncle Shao,
Grandpa Zhou, and I
naturally formed
a four-person research team.
Fueled by passion,
♫At moonset cry the crows♫
we roamed the streets and alleys,
visiting over 100 families
along the canal,
encountering many rare antiques,
and recording countless fascinating stories.
To our surprise,
♫Streaking the frosty sky♫
after the canal's successful World Heritage application,
various folk museums,
big and small, began popping up along the canal.
This gave us a more comprehensive
understanding of its history.
The four of us,
♫Dimly lit fishing boats♫
driven by our obsession with the sunken ship,
somehow became the talk of the neighborhood
around Flower Street.
More and more people
began approaching us,
♫Sadly lie beneath maples♫
offering their help to solve the mystery.
And just like that,
I felt
I was finally getting closer to the truth,
and closer to fulfilling my promise
to Siyi.
Why am I so tired?
It's just the beginning.
It's only been a few days.
You can't handle it already?
♫At moonset cry the crows♫
When I wrote books,
at least I knew the direction.
I was in control.
But now,
♫Streaking the frosty sky♫
everything is uncertain.
Hello?
Yes.
♫Dimly lit fishing boats♫
Really?
Okay, okay.
We'll come right away.
Alright, thank you.
Grandpa.
The town chronicle office says they have new leads.
Is that so?
Then let's pack up and go.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
You may find the information
you're looking for
in their genealogy records.
If you can't find it here,
there's even less chance elsewhere.
This way.
They've been waiting for a long time.
Yes.
Great.
Come on.
This old man is a descendant of the Dong family.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
Welcome.
They're looking for some information.
Thank you for coming.
Nice to meet you, sir.
Welcome, welcome.
One of my ancestors had a friend surnamed Shao.
There is a record of him.
I've kept it
but forgotten which book it's in.
Help them look for it.
Then let's look for it together.
Okay.
Let's look together.
Okay, thank you.
Sir, is it this?
This.
[I have a friend called Shao Sheng whose father was a canal porter. After leaving, he has not returned for a long time. The chances of survival are slim.]
You found it.
This is it.
Is it?
Great!
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
Wonderful.
Record it, record it.
It wasn't easy.
Record.
Let's take a picture together.
Take a picture.
Come on.
"I have a friend called Shao Sheng
whose father was a canal porter.
After leaving, he has not returned for a long time.
The chances of survival are slim.
I'm so worried that I can't sleep."
Why are you laughing?
This is your ancestor.
Look, it says, "The chances of survival are slim."
Why are you so happy?
Don't be so insensitive.
It's precisely because he was my ancestor
that I'm happy.
I know he was fine.
Otherwise, we wouldn't be here, right?
Yes.
That's right.
Were porters paid well at that time?
Of course not.
Is that so?
Grandpa…
Where's Grandpa?
Mr. Zhou.
Grandpa!
Oh, no.
Let's go.
Is that him?
Did he go out?
Let's go take a look.
In the first stage, he's forgetful, and in the second stage?
Memory problem.
I see.
So he can't remember anything at all?
-Yes.
-So he'll need someone with him
around the clock?
Yes.
I gotta go.
Is this what it's like when he…
Look.
Mr. Zhou.
Grandpa.
Rui.
Where are you going?
Grandpa.
♫Sitting quietly in the city♫
What are you doing here?
We finally found you.
♫Listening to the river flow♫
Mr. Zhou.
Why are you here?
Siyi.
Who?
It's Siyi.
Listen.
♫Hometown, oh hometown♫
It's her.
♫Now a distant place I can't go back to♫
♫Sitting quietly in the city♫
♫Listening as time drifts by♫
♫The sunsets in the city♫
This girl came a few days ago.
You know, the kind of person who travels on a budget by bike.
♫Hold no poetry, no distant dreams♫
That night at the gathering,
she sang a foreign song for us.
♫Walking through a world like a song♫
When she paid the bill,
she gave me a CD
♫From oblivion to oblivion♫
and said it was her own recording.
Thank you.
♫The love that passed through those remaining years♫
Do you know her name?
Her name?
How could I remember that?
♫Without complaints or piano music♫
So many people come here every day.
Oh, right.
Before she left,
♫The coolness after the gentle breeze♫
I took a photo of her.
♫I'm destined to be like you♫
This one.
[It's You]
Do you have her number?
No.
But she should be abroad by now, I guess.
How do you know that?
She told me.
She said
once she saved enough money, she'd go to Italy
to trace her roots.
Quite interesting.
I'll go back to work.
♫You never hesitate to let me lean♫
♫On your shoulder♫
When I saw the blurred writing that day,
♫The cover page hides this story♫
I doubted we could find anything.
But we did.
♫So many imagined dreams♫
What a relief.
Yes, it's a relief.
♫But I...♫
♫I just want to hold your warm hand♫
♫And gently press it against my chest♫
[It's You]
♫But I...♫
♫I just want to hold your warm hand♫
♫And gently press it against my chest♫
[Flower Street Kids]
♫A faint light shines through the window♫
♫Glowing on a young face♫
♫Nurturing dreams, yet leaving confusion behind♫
♫Time isn't a cure♫
♫But the most bitter truth♫
♫I want to say goodnight to you♫
♫So we won't get lost in the sea of dreams♫
[Flower Street Kids]
♫You loved my fearless youth♫
♫Only sober love remains pure and clean♫
[Flower Street Kids]
♫No matter what's good or bad♫
♫I wish you find love in this lifetime♫
[Flower Street Kids]
♫Don't walk away with regret♫
♫Reunions always come too late♫
[Flower Street Kids]
♫When the heavy rain falls♫
♫I'll be there to hold an umbrella for you♫
♫I want to say goodnight to you♫
♫So we won't get lost in the sea of dreams♫
♫You loved my fearless youth♫
♫Only sober love remains pure and clean♫
♫No matter what's good or bad♫
♫I wish you find love in this lifetime♫
♫Don't walk away with regret♫
♫Reunions always come too late♫
♫When the heavy rain falls♫
♫I'll be there to hold an umbrella for you♫
Eating fried sauce noodles in a bar?
How classy.
The boss made the sauce himself.
It's not for sale. Try some.
No, thanks. I've already eaten.
This is He.
From now on, he'll work in Station 203
as the dispatcher.
Hello, Shao.
Nice to meet you.
Work hard.
Don't embarrass Fenghua.
Alright.
You two shall work together from now on.
You can go back to work.
We need to talk about something.
This guy is very capable.
He can help you.
Whatever you say.
I have no objections.
Cut it out.
Your hostility towards him
is so obvious.
He was trained by Fenghua.
I'm not comfortable using him.
I've already
discussed it with Fenghua.
Don't worry.
Since you've already discussed it,
there's no need to ask for my opinion.
I'll just do as you say.
Thank you, Li.
You're welcome. Come anytime.
Xingchi was just angry for me.
He knows He once worked for me.
Job-hopping is illegal, huh?
Just be grateful that I have a big heart
and let him go without a fuss.
What would you do
if you wanted to make a fuss?
There are countless ways
to give an employee a hard time.
It's not that I'm not capable of it.
I just don't want to do it.
If we weren't close,
and I poached your staff with high salaries
and publicly humiliated you,
what would you do?
It's simple.
I'd use shady services.
I'd rent hundreds of phone numbers
to place orders continuously.
When the delivery riders arrive at the restaurants,
I'd cancel the orders.
If I did this every day during peak hours,
you'd be out of business in no time.
You're ruthless.
It's just the beginning.
There are plenty of ways
to screw with someone.
You have no idea
what I've been through all these years.
Ms. Xia,
I hate to trouble you, but…
Could you write down all those dirty tricks
for me?
I'll have them patch up the system right away.
Okay?
What's in it for me?
What do you want?
The Mid-Autumn Festival is coming up.
You know.
No problem.
Here.
Here is a spare battery.
Don't charge it.
There are more inside.
What's wrong with your bike?
The brakes seem to be broken.
Brakes?
The tires need changing too.
Chief, Chief.
I need to use your bathroom.
You bought a new car?
It's rented.
Tomorrow is the Mid-Autumn Festival.
I've already arranged leave for you and Haikuo.
We'll drive home.
Now?
Get off. Make room for the new driver.
Next,
let's welcome
Shao Xingchi, the driver for the Tongzhou section.
I see.
You just need me to drive.
Nonsense.
-You're important.
-Haikuo.
Hurry up.
Coming!
The driver has changed?
I'll give it a try.
You don't need to use the bathroom?
Maybe you should.
Get ready.
Let's go!