♪ I'll try to be a cat ♪
(According to the Literature Reading Group author monster monster if the fire novel work "today also want to be a cat" adaptation)
[Episode 6]
stain
shame
Black history.
He wanted to laugh at me.
Fu Sichen and I are enemies.
Every minute here,
It's a disgrace and a torment.
I want to escape.
When he comes back,
I rushed out immediately.
What we need to do now
Waiting for him to come back.
If he doesn't come back,
I'm definitely not sleeping.
Are you waiting for me to come home?
I missed the best time to escape.
What is this guy doing?
Where are you looking?
What kind of weird look is that?
You used to be a female cat.
No wonder you're so naughty.
So you haven't been sterilized yet.
I'll take you to the pet hospital.
Kittens
I'm going to the pet hospital.
He can't see me if he hides here.
What are you doing here?
Can't you find me?
Can't find me.
So you like to play hide and seek.
Who has the time to play with you?
Be good. It doesn't hurt at all.
I'll reward you with a cat bar after I finish.
Who cares about your cat strips?
Take it away.
It seems that today is doomed.
So you want to visit your savior.
Xiao Nian is so sad for me.
The female lead is too miserable.
The man is a scumbag.
You should be with a man.
(Xiao Nian)
I'm sorry.
Pei Pei is like this. I'm still watching TV.
It's okay.
You can't keep staring at Pei Pei.
What did the doctor say this morning?
The doctor said Pei Pei was fine.
When Pei Pei wakes up.
So,
You can take Pei Pei home.
Take it home.
I think we can consider this.
It's really inconvenient here.
This morning, I want to clean Pei Pei's face.
Just barged into a few paparazzi.
And then I gave it to you.
Hold it there.
We won't consider it.
Take it home and take care of it.
(Yes. Ask Fu Sichen to take me home.)
I'll take care of Fu Sichen.
What's going on?
If you insist on it,
It's a deal.
I'm talking about my own home. What are you thinking?
Did something pass just now?
I saw a cat wearing a sheet.
No animals were harmed during the filming.
(The right to rebroadcast the play on the Internet belongs to me.)
(Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)