♪ I'll try to be a cat ♪
(According to the Literature Reading Group author monster monster if the fire novel work "today also want to be a cat" adaptation)
[Episode 15]
Brother Si Chen.
How's Jerry doing with you?
It's my cat now.
Not Jerry.
Jerry is not a pretty name.
I saw you and its top search.
You almost spoil it like a cat.
I spoil them.
Is there a problem?
no
no problem
You should go to the crew party.
You didn't go too.
Why don't you go to my room later?
Let's talk about tonight's script.
Miss Lin,
Don't think I didn't know your tricks.
Didn't I warn you?
Please don't
To challenge my bottom line.
We are all in the same circle.
There are some things
I don't want to be too good.
In that case,
I don't have to hide anything.
Commander Fu.
I advise you to cooperate with me honestly.
It's not embarrassing to make a fuss with me.
Miss Lin,
I feel ashamed.
you
One last word of advice.
If you want to stay in this circle,
To improve your work and capabilities.
Take leave
Fu Sichen is really difficult.
But it's okay.
Every man has his weakness.
We'll see.
Pei Pei, you have a cold.
"Cute Pets Go Forward."
Think of a way.
Turn me back into a human.
I don't want to be kissed by Fu Sichen anymore.
Why are you resisting Fu Sichen?
I think he's nice to you.
It's possible that he has fallen in love with you since childhood.
What happened to me
Turn me into a human.
I don't want to be kissed by Fu Sichen again.
Xiao Nian, you're going too far.
You're always sneaking around.
"Cute Pets Go Forward."
Brother Si Chen, listen to my explanation.
Do something. Hurry up.
I just saw that you wanted to delete something.
You're fast.
I want to be kissed by Fu Sichen.
Xiao Nian
actually
I'm a straight man.
therefore
Actually, Brother Si Chen,
Year after year,
If you don't go to hell, who will?
No animals were harmed during the filming.
(The right to rebroadcast the play on the Internet belongs to me.)
(Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)