♪ I'll try to be a cat ♪
(According to the Literature Reading Group author monster monster if the fire novel work "today also want to be a cat" adaptation)
[Episode 19]
I just came to bring you some breakfast.
If there's nothing else, I'll leave now.
to sit properly
Agent Xiao.
Have you figured out how to answer my question?
This time,
Don't lie.
Why did you go after the cat
Your cat became Pei Pei.
Why is Pei Pei so smart?
Why did you take her to escape?
Why is it that every time you buy something,
Pei Zhen likes them.
Why do you like to talk to Pei Pei so much?
When I kissed Pei Pei,
You would scream to stop it.
Why is it that every time Pei Pei looks at me,
The way Pei Zhen looks at me.
And these problems
I need answers.
Brother Si Chen.
Can you ask one by one?
You have too many problems.
We can talk later.
No need
I recalled that
I've listed all the problems.
Don't try to make up a lie.
You only have two minutes to organize the language.
then
From the first one,
this
Why are you two arguing in the early morning?
Let her sleep.
It's annoying.
I know.
original
You are Pei Zhen.
According to this reasoning,
The person who kissed me secretly last night
It's you.
therefore
You like me.
It's annoying.
It's so embarrassing.
It turns out that the person Fu Sichen likes
but
I like his things.
He found out so quickly.
It's so embarrassing.
I want to find a hole to enter.
Run away.
No, no.
If he runs away, he will catch him.
He's strange. No cat can't sleep.
What should we do?
The world will be destroyed.
very good
He finally went to bed.
Do you have anything to drink?
Commander Fu.
you
You pervert
What are you doing?
No animals were harmed during the filming.
(The right to rebroadcast the play on the Internet belongs to me.)
(Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)