[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 31]
I've actually imagined many times
what it would be like for us
to be together.
I could talk about art with you,
take you to see exhibitions
all over the world
and give you everything you want.
You'll just need to stay
by my side with no worry.
So, Miyu,
can you give me a chance?
I'm sorry, Mr. Tan.
I cannot accept your pursuit.
Do you have someone you like?
Alright. I got it.
When we spent time together before,
I didn't keep proper boundaries.
I've always said we're friends,
but
actually, I've used you.
To some degree, I've never
been completely honest with you.
I'm sorry.
Actually, you don't need to feel guilty.
Wasn't I also just playing along?
We're even now.
Cheers.
But we can still be friends, right?
Of course.
That's good then.
Let's eat.
-I'm sorry.
-You're here.
I'm late because I overslept.
You guys are doing pretty well.
Is that steamer of food ready?
Bring it over here for Chef Jiao
to take a look.
I created a new dish today.
Please taste it.
This one.
[Position and Employment Term]
[Employment Term: 3 Months]
The contract is for 3 months.
Then what will happen
after these 3 months?
By that time,
it depends on whether the hotel
wants to renew your contract.
Why didn't I think of this earlier?
Just like the beans
spilled from a bamboo tube,
I held nothing back.
I haven't even been paid for 2 months,
and my apprentice
is already fully trained.
What should I do?
What can you do?
If the hotel
doesn't want to renew your contract,
then you'll just have to go home.
Are you kidding me?
My unique skill
is only worth tens of thousands of yuan?
This is not okay. I have to call your dad.
Gosh.
Welcome.
Hello, sir.
You can check in at the counter.
I-I'm here to find...
Xu...
Xu Miyu.
Okay.
Miyu.
Please wait a moment.
It's done.
Thank you.
Dad.
You're busy, huh?
When did you arrive?
I just got here.
Well,
I don't even know where to start.
Last time, I was just too angry
and took it all out on you.
It was my fault.
D-Don't...
It's okay. Dad, don't mention it anymore.
It's all in the past.
Okay. I won't mention it again.
I've heard you're doing well at the hotel.
You're even a manager now.
That's great. I'm happy for you.
As for your live stream,
wow, all the neighbors watched it.
They all said you looked even prettier
and more elegant
than those superstars.
I knew you would be successful.
You've really won honor for our Xu family.
You're much better than Miyao.
Ms. Xu! Ms. Xu!
The switchboard room
needs you for a moment.
Copy that. I'll be right there.
Dad, go wait in Mom's room first.
I've already booked a table for you
at the Chinese restaurant.
Just mention my name later.
Come on.
Okay.
Follow me.
Well,
let... let me carry this.
-It's okay.
-It's quite heavy.
Let me carry it.
You have something else to do.
Give it to me first.
Let me carry it.
Why didn't you stop your dad
from coming here?
Aren't you afraid the two of them
will stop Mr. Ji at the office door
and just ask him for money?
I know, but he's my dad after all.
What's more, he said my mom's contract
would expire soon,
so he wanted to come and pick her up.
He also said
he wanted to take this chance to visit me.
How could I refuse?
Anyway, judging by this situation,
it's definitely nothing good.
You have to be careful.
Qiaoqi.
Just take them.
Thanks.
I thought about it carefully later.
What you said makes sense.
All these clauses
were written by lawyers.
There are no loopholes we can make use of.
I should be content.
Having worked as a chef in such a
five-star hotel,
I'll have much
to brag about for the rest of my life.
Come on.
Let's drink a toast to our teacher.
-Thank you! Cheers!
-Cheers!
This portion of boat pastries
is called Qinhuai Lifestyle.
Please enjoy.
This is created by my apprentice,
Chef Bao.
I've tasted it.
It's quite delicious.
Taste this to see how it is.
What kind of nonsense
have you been blabbering about?
What did I say wrong again?
"Teach the apprentice, starve the master."
Don't you know this old saying?
You're stupid and undereducated.
What should I do then?
I'm here to get justice for you.
None of them can take your cooking skills
lightly.
Ms. Xu.
Are you looking for someone?
I'm looking for my parents.
I've just promised them
I'll take them out for a walk after work.
But they're not in their room.
I thought they came to the lobby
to wait for me.
They haven't been here.
There aren't many people
in the lobby this morning,
and I've been here the whole time.
If they had come,
I would definitely remember.
Where are they?
They're not in the restaurant, either.
Nor did they reply to my WeChat messages.
Where... Where are they?
[Purong Hotel]
Mr. Ji, regarding my skills,
if you take them away just like that...
We agreed to properly thank Mr. Ji
before we leave.
What nonsense are you talking about now?
Didn't you tell me to say...
I...
What did I tell you to say?
You've been chattering to me
in the past few days,
saying how well
the boat pastries are selling,
and that what you've contributed
isn't physical labor
but an intangible cultural heritage skill.
I only asked her this one question.
I said, "Isn't your hotel's revenue
connected to the employees' performance?"
Didn't I only ask you this one question?
And what are you doing now?
You're here asking for money.
I don't know.
I think I understand what you mean.
Chef Jiao's boat pastries
became a smash hit,
directly contributing to half the success
of our F&B Department.
Although our hotel generously offered
the highest pay in the market to hire her,
Chef Jiao is still not satisfied.
Right?
Yes, yes, yes.
That's exactly what I mean.
Look.
Mr. Ji is a perceptive man.
Mr. Ji,
please don't blame me
for talking too much.
Regarding the pay offered to hire her,
the hotel has indeed been generous enough.
We've witnessed it
and kept it in mind.
But after the success
of the boat pastries,
the hotel hasn't shown any appreciation,
which definitely hurts our feelings a bit.
-We just feel...
-I feel quite upset.
It feels like you'll get rid of us
once you've finished using us.
Right?
[Purong Hotel]
Look. We've contributed
the cooking skills.
The employment term
will also be over soon.
Then we'll just take
tens of thousands of yuan
of employment fees
and leave with nothing else, huh?
So what is the price in your mind?
100,000 yuan.
200,000 yuan.
With the revenue brought by
Chef Jiao's afternoon tea snacks,
according to the regulations,
if it's converted into a bonus,
the hotel can offer 150,000 yuan.
The remaining 50,000 yuan
will be considered as my personal
gratitude to Chef Jiao
for her valuable guidance.
200,000 yuan, deal.
But I have a condition.
Go ahead.
What?
We need to use this 200,000 yuan
to pay off my daughter's debt?
That's right.
Mr. Ji,
I-I understand what you mean.
You've helped us arrange the use
of this money in advance.
However,
as they say,
every family has its own problems.
T-This debt is
our family's private matter after all.
As for who will pay the debt,
how we'll pay it
and how much should be paid,
you really don't need to worry about it.
But these personal debts
have affected
our hotel employee's work performance.
She's always worried,
being unable to focus on work,
which has affected
our hotel's performance and revenue.
If I don't care, who will?
Don't worry about that, Mr. Ji.
I know my daughter's personality
perfectly well.
Even if the sky were to fall,
I'm sure she would still work earnestly.
So you just think it's completely fine
to throw the burden on her?
Do you know
she used her own credit
to guarantee for you?
Due to her trust in you,
she made the sacrifice.
Mr. Ji, we country folks
don't know how to talk properly.
But please rest assured.
She's our own daughter,
and we know her well.
She has the ability to pay off this debt.
After all, when she borrowed the money,
she was still a rich man's wife,
wasn't she?
But she isn't anymore.
Since she has moved on,
why are you two
still stuck in an illusion?
W-We...
Today is a great day.
The three of us
should celebrate properly.
Come on. Cheers.
Cheers.
Cheers!
Let's drink a toast.
Cheers.
What are we celebrating?
We're celebrating your mom's successful
completion of her job at Purong Hotel.
Alright. Let me tell you.
I've thought it over.
While the boat pastries are still popular,
let's hurry back to the guesthouse
and do some marketing, too.
Firstly, we can set up a decorative wall
and cover it with photos.
What kind of photos?
Your work photos at the hotel.
Your photos
with the hotel management staff.
And previously,
weren't there some large-scale events
in your hotel?
Didn't you take photos with those VIPs
and guests?
Wouldn't that be too vulgar?
Don't worry.
The vulgarest things
are the most effective.
Right? Guests just like that.
Oh, by the way.
when we get back there,
I also need to see Li first.
Isn't his son running
a matchmaking agency in our town?
We'll pay him some money
and ask him
to shoot a good promo video for you.
We'll just play it on a loop
in the guesthouse restaurant
to promote our place properly.
That's a great idea. I like it.
Okay.
Dad, Mom.
There's still a network loan
of over 200,000 yuan for me to pay off.
Don't you have to pay
only 5,000 yuan a month?
Only 5,000 yuan? Will you pay the money?
Of course.
If we have the money,
we'll definitely pay.
Then pay the debt now.
Don't you have money now?
-What... What money?
-You asked Mr. Ji for 200,000 yuan.
I know everything.
That sum of money is another matter.
You know what? Now we've met another...
Just treat me as a nuisance, too.
Consider that 200,000 yuan
as my hush money.
I'll figure out a way to pay off the rest.
In the future, I won't ask you two
for money anymore.
This network loan of over 300,000 yuan
can be paid off with just 200,000 yuan.
You can even make a net profit
of 100,000 yuan.
It's such a good deal, isn't it?
W-What are you talking about?
Why do you sound so distant?
It sounds as if you were trying to
distance yourself from us.
Hearing you say that,
I feel a bit hurt.
Don't make such jokes anymore.
I'm not joking with you.
This 200,000 yuan is yours.
The network loan of over 300,000 yuan
I've borrowed
is also yours.
Even I am yours.
Does it matter
who I am?
When I had the ability,
I helped you two build a guesthouse
and pay the network loan.
After I lost that ability,
I have to make a living myself
and survive on my own.
Dad, Mom.
When you were using me,
had you ever loved me for a moment?
Miyu,
what you said isn't nice.
No matter what,
we've brought you up after all, right?
Yes.
You've been telling me you brought me up
for as many years as you raised me.
I was just too grateful
and felt too guilty,
so I tried so hard to leave the village
and marry into the city
to repay your kindness.
Only until now have I realized
I was so stupid.
All you want is money.
Gratitude and guilt
were the password
you used to withdraw money
from me, who was like an ATM.
From today onwards,
this password is cancelled.
From now on,
if it's about money, we discuss money,
and if it's about matters,
we discuss matters.
This way, it's easier for us all.
Miyu,
aren't you my daughter?
Yes, I am.
Of course I am your daughter.
I am your biological daughter.
I will always be grateful
to you two for raising me.
But that doesn't mean
I have to spend my whole life
paying for both of your lives
and bearing
your self-righteous plundering.
[Message]
[Consumer Finance:
Your business loan has been paid with]
[5,000 yuan ahead of time successfully.]
[The payment has been settled this month.]
Are you off work, Ms. Xu?
Get in the car.
Thank you.
Ms. Xu, I'm sorry
for suddenly asking you
to have a meal with me.
It's alright.
Ms. Jiang,
I should thank you for the invitation.
I'm not very good at cooking.
I usually either order takeout
or cook a small pot of rice
and eat it with some side dishes
to grab a bite casually.
Oh, by the way,
let me formally introduce to you
my favorite side dishes for rice.
If you like quick pickles,
you can taste this bowl of sour celtuce.
Is this celtuce?
It's a kind of mixed pickles.
It's a very common brand in supermarkets.
The radish inside is soft,
and the cabbage is a bit too salty.
But only this celtuce
is pickled just right.
It's crisp and sour,
just like a breath of fresh air
in the mess.
Pickles are really amazing.
They don't wait for anyone.
If you eat them at their best time,
it's even more wonderful
than winning the lottery.
At their best time.
Ms. Xu.
You always say things that deeply move me.
Ms. Jiang,
aren't you at your best time now?
Speaking of a person's best time,
perhaps only the person knows it himself.
Maybe it's not the most glorious moment
that outsiders can see.
Nor is it the time
when one is full of hope for the future.
It's not even the time
of financial freedom
or spiritual freedom.
Rather, it's the time
when that very person is by your side.
Ms. Xu.
I asked Mr. Ji
to get back together with me.
Is that so?
What do you think?
I think it's great.
You two are a good match.
Aren't you going to ask if he agreed?
I don't think
this has anything to do with me.
Ms. Xu.
You must have heard
that I've been
having some problems lately.
For a moment,
I even thought
it would be better to just die.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
Fortunately,
Ji Feng found me in time.
I was so happy at that time.
I felt that
he still cared about me.
Even if that wasn't the case,
I thought
seeing me in such a miserable state,
he would at least
say something nice to comfort me.
Guess what
he said to me at that time?
He said
it was impossible between us.
The person he likes is you.
Even though Ji Feng
is usually quite shrewd
in the workplace,
actually, in his daily life,
he's just that simple.
If he likes someone, he just likes her.
If he doesn't like someone,
he just doesn't.
There is no middle ground.
He brought me back here that day
and left right away.
Hailin was also at home at that time.
Being photographed by reporters
was purely an accident.
I hope you won't misunderstand.
Also,
previously,
after the live stream,
I told you those things
because I actually...
wanted to persuade you to leave Ji Feng.
I acted too despicably.
I owe you an apology.
I'm sorry.
Ms. Jiang.
Miyu.
Don't you think
you owe yourself an apology, too?
You're clearly so nice to everyone else,
but not to yourself.
You hold back your hatred
and even suppress your love.
Don't you think that's too cruel?
Those who truly care about you
and want to love you
don't even know what to do.
Look.
The best time
always slips away quietly.
When I was at my best time,
I failed to grasp the essence of it.
Now that I know the essence of it,
everything has changed.
I'm like this
over-pickled radish,
instead of the perfectly pickled celtuce.
But you are different.
Don't let hesitation
make you miss the right time
and the right person.
I got it, Ms. Jiang.
Thank you.
Time cannot be turned back.
Once a path is taken,
it's just taken.
For example, if those documents
are blown away by the wind,
♪ Love is truly not easy to obtain ♪
what we can catch
can only be the next page.
♪ I can't hold on to you
if you want to leave ♪
This is not fair.
I've clearly become better.
Yes.
♪ I tell myself I'm not hurt
once things settle down ♪
The better Jiang Zhichun
deserves a better future,
instead of being trapped
in the past assumptions.
♪ But I realize I can't deceive myself ♪
Yeah.
I should have understood it earlier.
A businessperson
should solve problems in a business way.
♪ I always say
life is already hard enough ♪
For example?
For example,
if they use cyberbullying as a weapon,
♪ So what else is there worth trying for ♪
I should show them
what a real public opinion war is.
♪ Friends comfort me,
telling me to have a drink ♪
That's more like you.
Let me ask you one last question.
♪ But I've already started living
like I'm not myself anymore ♪
♪ I feel reluctant ♪
For all these years,
have you ever had a moment of...
Yes, I have.
♪ I feel reluctant to recall
or forget those memories ♪
But it was exactly those times
that made me more certain
that the best distance between us
♪ I feel reluctant ♪
is just like this now.
♪ I feel reluctant to grab on to anyone
and I can't breathe ♪
♪ I've been indulging myself ♪
Thank you for your honesty.
♪ I feel reluctant ♪
This time,
♪ I feel reluctant to recall
or forget those memories ♪
it's really time to say goodbye.
♪ I feel reluctant ♪
Ms. Xu.
Love is troublesome,
♪ I feel reluctant to grab on to anyone
and I can't breathe ♪
but it's worth our courage.
♪ I've cut myself some slack ♪
[Purong Hotel Staff Apartment]
Hello.
Ji Feng.
Where are you?
I'm on my way to the hotel to find you.
I-I have something to tell you.
I'm downstairs at your dorm.
Wait for me.
-I have something to tell you.
Let me say it first.
Okay.
I admit
in terms of starting a new relationship,
now I'm a bit afraid
and reserved.
I have let myself down for too long.
Right now,
I just want to give all my love
and expectations back to myself.
I am very afraid.
I'm afraid that if I fall in love
with someone again,
I will repeat my past mistakes,
so I've been
looking for all kinds of excuses
to avoid my feelings for you.
But now,
I don't want to
and I can't avoid them anymore.
Ji Feng.
I want to start over
with you.
I'm glad I'm with you finally.
I've also always wanted to tell you
I like you too.
♪ Bury everything in your mind ♪
♪ Hope love blossoms as wished ♪
♪ Rainwater silently nourishes flowers ♪
♪ At its own expense ♪
♪ That fleeting moment I tried to hold ♪
♪ Let it go when the glass runs dry ♪
♪ Unfinished longings ♪
♪ Drift like fading embers ♪
♪ Still longing for yesterday's glow ♪
♪ Yet sailing into
the ocean's depths at night ♪
♪ Questions without answers ♪
♪ Let them go with the wind ♪
♪ Let them go ♪
Morning.
Wait.
I don't want to
bring personal feelings into work.
You're still Mr. Ji, the general manager,
and I'm Ms. Xu, the manager.
We're both very professional.
Thank you.
Then let's just talk about business.
You said you wanted to transfer
to the sales department.
Can you give me a specific reason?
I think,
from the jazz performance
at the Western Restaurant last time
to the planning
of the college entrance exam rooms,
I do have some talent for sales.
You do have sales intuition
and execution ability.
But competing with those
top sales reps
who specialize in developing business
is a different thing.
Besides,
sales is
also completely different from
the work you've done before.
As for the methods and tactics
it requires,
are you able to use them?
Everyone is different.
A thousand people have a thousand faces.
I don't think I might be able to be
that kind of aggressive sales rep
who people can't refuse,
but I can understand the products
and learn about the clients,
trying to facilitate a mutual choice
between them.
Well,
what about Lu Zhenzhen?
Her maternity leave is almost over.
How will you deal with her
when she returns?
I've never thought about
how to deal with her.
She's not in my plan.
I have my own mountain to climb.
Okay.
I used to think the hotel industry
was just a
temporary job for me.
I had no career plan.
But it's different now.
My current goal is
to become a professional hotel manager.
Alright.
Then you have to think it through.
If you join the sales department now,
you'll need to start
as an ordinary employee
with a demotion
and a post transfer.
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
Come in.
Mr. Ji.
Mr. Wei is here.
I was just passing by,
so I came to see you.
Am I disturbing you?
No, not at all.
What can I do for you, Mr. Wei?
There's no need to be so formal
between us.
I heard some gossip about you.
Have a seat.
Let's talk. Come on.
I've recently heard people in the hotel
gossiping about you.
They say you
and Xu Miyu,
the Front Office's lobby manager,
have an unusual relationship.
Actually, I understand.
As a boss,
it's normal
to have a few capable subordinates.
But Xu Miyu seems a bit different.
Look. I remember that
shortly after she started
working in our hotel,
she joined the management team.
Now she's suddenly being transferred
to the sales department.
Her speed is a bit fast.
It's inevitable that people would gossip.
As a housewife
who had never worked before,
she joined Purong Hotel
and then suddenly became
an influential figure.
Not to mention everyone else,
even I don't quite understand it.
Mr. Ji,
do you know
what the subordinates are saying?
Ten years of hard work at Purong Hotel
is not as good as
a glance of favor from Mr. Ji.
Mr. Wei, I'm flattered.
How would I have such great capabilities?
As for how Xu Miyu
became the forewoman
of the executive floor,
I guess no one knows it
better than you, Mr. Wei.
Is that so?
How come I don't remember?
I must be getting old and forgetful.
Perhaps
you've played the role
of talent spotter too many times.
You're teasing me again.
But since Xu Miyu
joined the management team,
everything she did
has been worthy of her position.
Some even exceeded
everyone's expectations.
And now she has been transferred
to the sales department.
It's also because
she has shown ability in this field.
Therefore,
her career path is a natural progression,
and it has nothing to do with me.
However, if there is any controversy,
your criticism and guidance
are always welcome, Mr. Wei.
Mr. Ji,
now that you're saying this,
I understand completely.
There must be some subordinates
who don't understand the situation.
And with people's jealousy,
it's inevitable
that there's some unpleasant gossip.
Please don't take it to heart.
Mr. Ji, speaking of
your dedication to nurturing elites,
I deeply admire it
and can truly understand it.
However,
I think when it comes to eating,
you still need to take one bite at a time.
Don't pull up seedlings to help them grow.
Losing your favorite aide
is a small matter,
but ruining the hotel's development
would outweigh the gains.
Am I right?
Mr. Wei,
you're right.
I've learned a lot.
I wouldn't dare to teach you anything.
Mr. Ji, you've seen a lot
of the world outside.
I'm just showing off
in front of an expert.
But I still want to ask about one thing.
As for Xu Miyu's specific
work arrangements in the sales department,
will you have any special...
There are no special arrangements.
Do everything in accordance
with the sales department's rules.
Got it.
It means she should do what she has to do.
Right.
In that case, I am a bit
looking forward to her work performance.
Mr. Ji,
I won't take up any more of your time.
No need to see me out.
Goodbye.
Alright.
Mr. Lin.
Xu Miyu.
So you're transferred
from the Front Office?
Yes.
So you've had no experience in this field?
No.
Alright.
Make some phone calls.
You want me to make phone calls?
Telemarketing.
You can do that, huh?
[List of Potential Clients]
[Call]
Hello.
Is that Jingkun Travel Company?
This is...
[Shanghai Experimental Exploration
Food Company]
[Shanghai Life Ark
Medical Supplies Company]
Hello.
This is Xu Miyu,
a sales rep from Purong Hotel.
What business would you like to handle?
No, I just want to ask whether you
have any need for hotel services.
No.
[Shanghai Kangyu Future
Textile Technology Company]
Hello.
Hello, this is...
[Shanghai Polaris Ship Hotspot Company]
[Shanghai Sunlight Epoch
Renewable Energy Company]
[Call]
Hello, this is...
Hello.
This is Purong Hotel's...
[Shanghai Genetic Blueprint Company]
[Shanghai Recycle and Regeneration
Chemical Company]
[Shanghai Golden Stone
Mining & Thermoelectricity Company]
Hello.
Is that Rongfei Trading Company?
Yes. What's the matter?
This is Xu Miyu,
a sales rep from Purong Hotel.
I'd like to ask whether you
have any need for hotel services.
We can discuss the details.
Purong, right?
Yes.
Send us some info. We'll take a look.
Okay. I'll add you on WeChat right now.
Alright.
Thank you.
Good job, Xu.
It's all thanks to
your good guidance, Mr. Lin.
By the way, when will you be available?
They want to talk to you directly.
No need.
I won't meet with such small potatoes.
No matter how small the business is,
it's still business.
The smaller the business is,
the less reliable it might be.
We'd rather miss it
than take the risk.
Do you understand?
But...
The scale of this company
may be small now.
What if it grows bigger in the future?
I've seen too many tricks
from such small companies.
If they could sign a contract with you,
why didn't they just sign it?
They just want to come here
for free food and drinks.
That's how telemarketing is like.
The success rate is low.
It's mainly to train you newcomers
so that you guys can open your mouths,
step forward
and unleash your true nature.
Also, Xu,
our department
doesn't expect you to bring in sales.
Don't put too much pressure on yourself.
Okay?
Thank you, Mr. Lin.
I'll think about it further.
Keep it up.