(Episode 14)
Let's be partners. Just you and me.
What? You want us to do what?
Mamdaerozip has...
over ten turnkey project inquiries already.
I was thinking you could take on those turnkey projects.
- No, I'm not interested. - Just hear me out.
You can keep doing your own projects and just oversee the turnkey ones.
Mamdaerozip gets five percent from your jobs.
Turnkey projects are a 70-30 split.
You'd get the 70 percent.
No, thanks. I'm not interested.
What do you mean, you're not interested?
You don't want to partner up with anyone,
or you just don't want to work with me?
Both.
I don't get it.
But you worked as a coordinator for me before.
That was when I was so desperate I would've done anything.
And you're not now? Don't you want to make money?
You need money so you can breathe a little...
and start living your life.
This is exactly why I don't want to work with you.
Because you're always crossing the line.
I'd do one project a year on my own. Why do what I love with you?
We've been partners before.
Why won't you work with me? I don't get it.
I can't just let it go until I understand why.
I don't understand what it means.
I don't get it.
When I don't understand, I can't solve the problem...
and find the answer.
I won't get tangled up in business with someone I don't trust.
I'd rather we just be strangers.
You're already treating me like a stranger.
Eun Oh. With the turnkey projects, you can pick the best ones.
You need to grow Eunoism anyway. And I know you'll make it.
But until then, your chances are few for projects you truly care about.
This is a shortcut, so why refuse? Plus, you could make a lot of money.
Come on. Aren't you the breadwinner? And you need a car, don't you?
Why are you throwing away a chance to make good money?
Stop worrying about my family and worry about your own.
You've even got investors now. So when do you get your own office?
I'll take care of myself, so stay out of my business.
Is that why you're thinking about taking on some copycat project?
Hey, Lee Ji Hyuk!
The funding really went to your head.
Suddenly, you have a lot to say.
At this rate, you'll be a tycoon in no time.
"Lee Ji Hyuk?" Watch it, Ji Eun Oh.
My point is,
let's stay out of each other's way and do our own work.
You're being incredibly stubborn for no reason.
You know none of what you're saying makes any logical sense, right?
Something's wrong with her thinking.
Arrogant? Stubborn? Spiteful? What is it?
Just how disappointed in me could she be...
to do a complete 180 on me?
And she manages to get on my every last nerve.
Hey, what are you picking out? You've been at it for a while.
I'm going to the movies today, so I'm deciding what to wear.
With who?
What? Just a friend.
I see.
Hold on a second.
What's all this?
What? These are your old office clothes.
Wear this. And stop wearing Gang Oh's clothes.
What? You kept all of this? I thought you threw them out.
My gosh, why would I throw out perfectly good clothes?
Also, you haven't gone out properly in a while.
Dressing up helps lift your spirits.
You're right. I guess I dress too casually at work.
Then, maybe I'll dress up for a change.
She's beautiful.
What?
I think I just heard you bad-mouthing me.
Me?
No, of course not.
Well...
So if I wear a dress like this,
you'll open doors and be a gentleman?
I've always opened the door for you.
Actually, Eun Oh...
I said you looked beautiful.
Gosh, so cheesy.
Don't say things like that.
Well, don't wear a dress like that, then.
I couldn't do that. I haven't been asked out in forever.
I guess I'll have to ask you out more often then.
It must be nice being the director. You get to go out on a weekday.
Hey, what are you talking about? I took a personal day for this.
Hop in.
Then let's make good on that movie promise.
Of course. When would be a good time?
Since when did she get so comfortable around Seong Jae?
How did they get so close?
So, I'll see you on Wednesday, then?
So that's it. They're going to the movies today.
When the heck did they make plans to see a movie?
This is ridiculous.
I feel like I'm in another world. Like a parallel universe.
Where another version of me is living in a whole other world.
I feel the same way.
I can't believe I'm having this meal with you, Eun Oh.
It's surreal for you too, right? I feel the same way.
Well...
But it's not bad, right?
Not at all.
This fusion food is new to me. It's really delicious.
Changing the subject.
What?
It's nothing. Eat up.
But why did you suddenly decide to call in that promise?
That was ages ago.
As a businessman, if I forget debts, I'd be out of business.
Everything about my situation just came out all at once.
I was too overwhelmed to even think about dealing with it.
Why feel like you have to manage it? We're all adults who can handle it.
Thank you for not prying.
And for not tiptoeing around me, asking if I'm okay.
That feeling of not wanting anyone to know you're struggling...
I know it all too well.
You do?
Well, you know.
As a certain someone said,
there are some things you can't tell just anyone.
That kind of thing.
I don't think I've ever heard you talk like that before.
Sounds like there's a tragic backstory.
They say everyone's got a story.
- Come on, eat. It'll get cold. - But I'm full.
Oh, no. Don't say that. You have to finish this.
We've got a bit of a walk to our next destination.
The weather is amazing today.
You didn't notice the seasons changing.
It's been a while since you've been out.
What, you think I spend all day cooped up on-site?
Does just running back and forth count as getting some sun?
You have to take a moment to enjoy it.
These were a lighter green before. The leaves have gotten darker.
You're right.
My, this is so nice.
Oh, my.
Yes! Oh, I got it!
I think I'm actually really good at this.
Nice, I hit it!
- My gosh. - Oh, my.
Thank you. Oh, it's so cute.
(Song Ha Bin, Education)
- Thank you for your time. - Thank you.
The more I think about it, the more absurd it gets.
Seong Jae, that jerk. Doesn't he know any better?
Why is he so selfish, making it harder...
on someone in distress?
Especially after I told him, point-blank, to back off.
Hello. I'm here for the interview.
Yes. Come on in. Please have a seat.
Oh, this breeze feels nice.
Eun Oh is like a bright, warm ray of sunshine.
And her laugh is like a cool, refreshing breeze.
You've got your spirits back. I can hear it in your voice.
Yes.
I received a sign.
A sign telling me to live my life to the fullest.
What do you mean by that?
I have a bestie.
A few days ago, I met up with my bestie and got to vent.
And today, thanks to you, I got to soak up some sun...
and feel the gentle breeze.
I've laughed a lot, and the food was amazing.
I think it's all a sign telling me that life is still worth living.
Is that so?
When the time is right, everything falls into place.
But knowing that, we still walk into that moment of pain.
Willingly.
Willingly?
On your own?
We'll let you know our decision by text.
All right. I look forward to hearing from you.
My eyes are so tired, it feels like they're about to burst.
I can finally have my cup noodles in peace today.
- Enjoy your meal. - Thank you.
Lee Ji Hyuk, you're moving up in the world.
Coming out for beef bone soup and everything.
Nice.
Now, I feel better.
Oh, yes.
(Application for Web Designer Position)
"No content?"
Goodness. As if I'd hire someone who sends an empty email.
Good grief.
What? Neiro?
Wait, he worked at Key Life?
So why would someone like him apply to Mamdaerozip?
This is Cha Cheol Min.
Yes, this is Mamdaerozip.
Did you apply to the correct place?
Yes.
So, why'd you quit Neiro?
Did you get into some trouble there?
They asked me not to leave, and you can call and confirm that.
I applied of my own volition.
If you don't want to interview me, we're done.
No. Of course, I'll interview you. Let's do it.
I really appreciate everything today.
I had a great time today.
Me too.
Get home safe.
Okay, I will.
You just got here?
Are all the interviews done?
I need to get some work done.
She was out having fun all day, and now she has to work here?
And what's with that dress?
That's totally a date outfit.
I was going to drink both, but... Do you want one?
Thanks, I'd love one.
Wait, where are you...
What's with her? Why is she suddenly so cheerful?
Is it because she saw Seong Jae?
I thought they just saw a movie. Did they go to an amusement park?
She's not a little kid. Getting excited over that...
Was that a date or what? What were they doing? Seriously.
(Power Converter)
Welcome.
- What? - My gosh!
- Wait, Ms. Ji? - What?
Mister, you work here?
- Yes. - Someone else is usually here now.
Right, that person had an accident and had to quit.
I've been working here since that day.
About 2 or 3 days a week.
I see. I'm actually a regular here.
- You are? - Yes.
It's on a backstreet, so it's quiet.
- So the walk over is always quiet. - Is your office nearby?
Yes, just up that way.
I see.
- I guess I'll see you often, then. - Yes.
- Okay, just this then? - Yes.
- That'll be 1.20 dollars. - Okay.
Here, let me bag that for you.
That's okay. I might just eat it on my way.
- All right, then. - See you around.
You too. Get back safely.
Ms. Ji! Wait up!
Wait, hold on.
- Here. - What is it?
- Here you go. - What's this?
Don't worry. It's free. We were about to throw it out.
Oh, come on.
I know you're not supposed to throw this out yet.
- Sorry? - It's not past midnight yet.
I used to work part-time at a convenience store too.
Well, it's just...
(Staff: Lee Sang Cheol)
You just remind me of my son who ran away.
Pardon?
I hope my son gets help like this when he's having a hard time.
Well, now I have to take it.
Thank you. I'll enjoy it.
I just can't help myself.
She's like a wilting violet, revived by the rain.
(Coordinator, Shin Ji Yeon)
(Application)
Okay, that makes ten of you.
Perfect.
(Su Jeong)
Hey, Su Jeong.
So, how was your day? Ji Eun Oh's first outing in ages.
- It was fun. - No kidding. You sound happy.
After talking with Woo Jin and Director Seong Jae,
Gang Oh is his own person, and I'm just his sister.
I realized that fact isn't going to change.
So I'm just going to wait for him to come back.
While living my own life as Ji Eun Oh.
It's quiet where you are, though.
Are you home?
I'm at the cafe.
Before I start on the copycat project,
I wanted to finish Director Ko's plans.
- Did you set a meeting? Any news? - No, not yet.
She said it'd take some time to select artists...
and told me to focus on my work for the time being,
but you never know when the call might come.
Yes, I'm heading home soon.
I'm scared walking home at night, so I leave before the last bus.
I even wear my dad's jacket and a hat.
What? She left?
Couldn't she have at least said goodbye?
I'm her lifesaver, after all.
Right. I saved her life. Why not be partners?
(Damga Charcoal Grill)
Looks like I'm right on time.
What? You finished work already?
I finished what I needed to.
Okay. Did you enjoy the movie?
Let me just change my clothes, and then I'll help you clean up.
Did something good happen today?
Why do you ask?
Would you rather I be like you, Mom, moping about Gang Oh all day?
No.
Mom.
I've just decided...
to wait for Gang Oh.
They say time heals all wounds, right?
So...
you need to be patient too, Mom.
Because...
I'm your daughter.
It's like a tunnel we just have to get through.
Besides, what choice do we have?
He'll come back when he gets tired of it.
Right.
Of course, he will.
So, Sun Hui,
stop looking at me like you feel sorry for me.
Okay?
My goodness.
Okay.
All right.
Hey, I said no crying.
Thank you.
It's strangely slow today.
Hey, let's do a deep clean!
- Hey, they're all leaving. - Yes, we have to go.
I thought you said we'd deep clean.
You're the one who's going to do it, the deep clean.
You have to earn your keep, Gang Oh.
Hey, I already wait tables out front.
Did anyone ask you to?
Make it spotless.
Let's go.
Mean jerks... Darn it.
You think I'm going to deep clean this place?
Seriously. Darn it.
- What are you doing? - When is your mom coming?
It's too cramped. I can't sleep in here.
(Cafe Agit)
I'm Cha Cheol Min.
Isn't your interview in an hour?
I came early to have some tea and happened to see you.
Wait, how did you know I was the CEO?
Just a hunch.
Are you psychic or something? Should we do the interview now?
- Sounds good. - Okay.
Your major, your university, and your skills are not in question.
I just have one question.
Why the move to such a small company?
I want to work somewhere quiet.
You've seen our website, right? It's just a landing page.
You'd have to expand it and manage all the forums as well.
Understood.
The sooner you start, the better. When can you start?
There are no shoe samples?
- Didn't they keep an extra of each? - No, sir.
Apparently, we have some old models still left in inventory.
They didn't keep any in storage?
Well, then, Ms. Kim, you've got some work to do.
Tell Mr. Kim in Management Support to come up.
Yes, sir.
(Shoealls)
You wanted to see me?
What are you playing at?
What's your angle here?
I doubt you've suddenly found a passion for the business.
When you inherited the company from Grandfather,
did you do it because you thought it would be fun?
What?
You're the one who told me running a company isn't about fun.
Because I'm the eldest and only son,
it was the path I was fated to walk. That's what you told me.
So,
I'm going to walk this path,
and I'm going to do it right.
That's a pathetic excuse.
I refuse to become a toothless tiger.
As much as I'm happy to hear that,
I don't trust a man who changes overnight.
You must have an ulterior motive.
(CEO Park Jin Seok)
Still,
since you seem to be finally getting your hands dirty,
I'll be watching.
Very well.
I'll get back to my work.
(Winter 2015)
- I'm here! Ji Eun Oh is here. - Yes!
- There she is! - And I brought a homemade cake.
Thank you so much.
I'm off.
- Hey, you made this yourself? - Yes.
Hey, nothing to see here. Don't even bother trying it.
We'll see about that.
- And now, drumroll please. - Oh, my.
Ta-da!
- Hey! - Doesn't it look amazing?
Ji Hyuk, if this tastes good, stop calling me "The Spring."
And trust me. It'll be delicious.
You may not believe me,
but I've been making my parents' birthday cakes...
since I was ten.
The Spring won't stop talking, as usual.
Just light the candles already.
- Yes, light them already! - Come on.
I'm serious, Ji Hyuk. You have to promise me first.
Wait, what?
Isn't that... No, wait.
What's he doing here?
- Why? - What's wrong?
What's going on? You two know each other? How?
Hey, do you know him?
Well, it's...
No, it's... It's just that...
I asked her for directions once.
- I see. - That's right.
Yes, you did, didn't you?
I'm so forgetful sometimes.
Goodness, this is so frustrating that I could just scream.
She was like a ray of sunshine.
A breath of fresh air.
I had no idea she was...
stuck in such a deep hole, in such grim circumstances.
(Shoealls)
(Younglim Kitchen, Bath, Home and Living)
Hello.
- You're here already. - I am.
The flooring is on the second floor, so let's start up there,
and then we can come back down to look at the kitchen sinks.
- The colors depend on the floor. - Sure.
This way, please.
This place is huge.
- Oh, I'm sorry. - My gosh.
Hey. What a coincidence.
- What? - Ms. Ji Eun Oh?
Yes, well...
He's renting a workspace in the cafe.
Hello. I'm Lee Ji Hyuk, the CEO of Mamdaerozip.
Oh, I've seen your work. On your weblog.
Oh, you have? Thank you.
What are you doing here?
I heard this was a good showroom to check out.
Oh, you must be her client for the Mapo apartment, right?
- You know about that? - Of course.
I saw on the schedule...
that you're checking out kitchen cabinets and closets today.
Do you mind if I join you? I'm on your project, so I can help.
Especially with the furniture colors for your five-year-old son's room.
You really don't have to do that. Please look around by yourself.
Ms. Ji. If it's about me, I don't mind.
I can learn from you too, Ms. Ji. We can all learn from each other.
Well, let's get in.
(View Plus Frame, Standard Frame)
I think this gives you that bright, yet warm feeling you're after.
I agree.
It looks even better in person. I'm glad I listened to you, Ms. Ji.
We've taken the final measurements,
so you just need to pick the material and color.
And remember, we can also set the sink height to match yours.
If a tall guy like me lives alone, can you adjust my sink height too?
Yes. We've had many custom requests for that.
We can create a perfect fit even if the dimensions vary between homes.
Nice.
I totally lost track of time.
I'll be late for my next meeting. I'd better get going.
I'll walk out with you.
Take care. See you next time.
What are you doing?
You're here, so look around the rest of the second floor with me.
I'm serious. I really need to ask you something.
You can just ask the staff here. They'll tell you everything.
Look. I'm doing interiors for 29 units,
and I only know a few suppliers. So I need recommendations, right?
But I see that clients can browse everything at once here.
But I need to know the materials before I can negotiate a discount.
So?
So, please take a look with me. Your input would be a huge help.
That window frame I glanced at seemed unique.
Hey, in the time it took to beg you, we could have already taken a look.
Thirty minutes.
Okay! Let's go.
See? It's different, isn't it?
It's because of the slim frame design.
It gives you a much better view.
You're right. It really opens up the view.
Was this what you were so curious about?
It sets the house apart. Didn't you say details are key?
My clients would love to know that these windows are available.
I'll ask for a bulk discount. What do you think?
I've already worked things out with the moving company.
We partnered up, and they agreed to give our clients a discount.
If we consolidate our material sources like this,
it'll save clients a ton of hassle, right?
What?
You're awfully talkative today.
I am, right? But ideas keep popping into my head.
This stuff is fun.
So what's your cut from the moving company?
I'm not taking one.
Aren't you in this to make money?
Of course, I am.
But it's no fun if I'm the only one who benefits.
Shouldn't my clients get something out of it too?
"I don't want to go with this jerk, but I can't say no after he helped,"
"so I can't just brush him off." That's what you're thinking, right?
Oh, you're so clever.
I'll stop asking for a partnership, so just let me drive you.
Going to the same place in two cars is a bit childish, Ms. Ji.
Did you have fun yesterday?
Yes.
Looks like you and Seong Jae got pretty close.
Wait, since when? When did you get close to Seong Jae?
How did that happen? Did you get close by trashing me?
Did Seong Jae say anything specific to you?
Why do you keep staring at me?
What?
If you have something to say, just say it.
No. It's nothing.
- Okay. - Keep your eyes on the road.
Right.
So, did you have fun with Seong Jae yesterday?
You already asked me that.
I did?
Right.
It's like my memory just reset.
Seriously?
Seong Jae, didn't you see me?
I saw you working late,
so I waited for the lights to go off.
And what can I do for you this time?
I'll give you a ride home,
so we can talk in the car. I'm exhausted today.
Just go on ten dates with me.
I can't just give up like this.
What?
Is there a reason why not?
You've been talking to my brother, haven't you?
He's back in Seoul, isn't he?
Otherwise, you can't say you're going to tattle on me to him.
We need to talk.
Su Bin, you little...
Trying to set a trap for a grown-up, are you?
Why, you...
Don't talk to me like that. I'm not a kid. I'm a grown woman.
Not to me, you're not.
We're only 9 years apart. It's not like there's a 19-year gap.
Stop acting like such an old man.
I'm 24 years old now. Why won't you even give it a shot?
So you're shutting me out for being your friend's sister or a kid?
- You're serious about this. - Of course, I am.
Su Bin.
Even if you weren't Ji Hyuk's little sister,
and even if I hadn't known you since you were seven,
I don't see you that way. And I never will.
How can you be so sure? What makes you so confident?
Don't you remember me telling you there's someone I like?
If you've liked her for a long time, you would've made a move,
which means she must've rejected you.
That's why you're not dating,
and you're stuck with this crush. Am I right?
And for the record, a one-sided crush isn't a rival.
Good grief...
I completely forgot.
You've been a hardhead since you were a kid.
Right. But I don't hold grudges, so just go on ten dates with me.
And if I still don't feel a spark, I'll go back to how things were.
To being just your friend's little sister.
You're making me say it, aren't you? You little hardhead.
Yes, say it! Go on, say it.
What is it?
Su Bin.
I've been married before.
- What? - I'm divorced.
Oh, come on.
Ask Ji Hyuk later. He was my best man.
Back when I was in ninth grade, during summer break?
That time my brother came back from visiting you in the US...
and brought me those gummies and stuff from Soul and Body Works.
Was that when it was?
None of our other friends know. It's a secret only Ji Hyuk knows.
Sorry to spring this on you, but...
so what do you say now?
No way. A divorced man is a total deal-breaker for me.
Okay. I get it.
- Let's just forget it. I'm leaving. - No, let me take you home.
No, it's fine. I can go by myself. I'm going. Bye.
She's really something else.
Man, is that how kids these days feel about divorce?
Seriously, nothing is going my way.
Why did Seong Jae marry at my age? When he was so young.
Seriously...
What I told you to memorize today will definitely be on the exam,
so make sure you all know them. And before we wrap up,
- the exam sign-up is closed now. - Yes.
Who here signed up?
The written exam is coming up soon, so please review past questions.
I'll upload a practice test online, so please download and try it.
- Okay. - See you all next time.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- You registered for the test? - Yes.
Gosh, you're jumping the gun a bit.
I've failed it three times.
Okay. So what?
I take it you haven't heard how tough this exam is?
We'll see about that.
Where did Ji Hyuk's suitcase go?
I wonder if Ji Wan took it.
Thanks for continuing to be my bodyguard.
Why aren't you saying anything?
I'm just trying to focus...
on my duties.
Your duties?
Look, I'd quit in a heartbeat, but now that I know your situation,
I can't just quit,
you see.
We're sticking to our "Young Lady and Her Driver" roles.
- No, you don't have to go that far. - I'm going that far.
I mean,
Ms. Park.
I'm sorry,
Ji Wan.
I take it back. The "Young Lady and Driver" part.
Stay put.
Get out.
Let's go.
(Run!)
(Screech)
A zombie webtoon? That doesn't seem like her.
- Who's that? Her boyfriend? - He's handsome.
I'm her driver.
I'm her driver, all right?
A grad student with a bodyguard? Isn't that a little much?
No, it is not. She has her reasons.
So cut the snide remarks, okay?
He's so cool.
Shall we, Ms. Park?
Hey, Park Yeong Ra. What webtoon was on your tablet?
I've never seen it before.
You went through my tablet? Without my permission?
No. Your jacket was sticking out, so I saw it when I tucked it in.
It's not like I was trying to snoop. Seriously, I only saw one webtoon.
It was so good, I got sucked in. Your alarm snapped me out of it.
You what?
Okay, fine. I'm sorry I went through your stuff.
But where did you get it? Is the artist a friend of yours?
Did they send you the file? It hasn't been released yet, right?
What are you talking about?
The one you were reading. "Take My Heart." That's the one.
Where can I find it? I tried searching but found nothing.
Can we just go? Why so curious about that?
I'm curious because it's awesome! Seriously, it's incredible.
It's so good.
- It is? - Well...
They're after the one they can't bite.
So if they catch him, will they slice open his brain?
I don't know.
What do you mean? You have the file. There must be a next chapter, right?
You really think it's that good?
I'm dying to know what happens next.
There is no next part.
What do you mean there isn't? If your friend is the artist,
they must have the rest of it. If not, tell me the artist's name.
Aren't you going to drive? I need to get to my studio on time.
If you don't tell me the name,
I'm not driving.
You're so petty, hiding every little thing.
Well...
I drew it.
What?
You have to promise me this will be our secret, okay?
For real? You're the one who drew it?
What in the world...
Hey, you scared me!
Why are you so jumpy?
The light in your room was on, and my shoes are right by the door.
I guess I was lost in thought and didn't notice.
Thinking about what?
Ji Hyuk's suitcase?
What?
You're the one who brought Ji Hyuk that suitcase full of his clothes.
What? Me?
That's what Ji Hyuk told me.
Oh, so he called?
I knew it was you.
Where's Ji Hyuk?
Mom.
Come on, Mom.
Mom, you're jumping to conclusions, aren't you?
I asked you. Where is Ji Hyuk?
I don't know.
Lee Ji Wan.
I have absolutely no idea where he is.
And Mom, I completely understand where he's coming from,
so I think we should wait and just give him some time.
Wait for what?
Well...
Gosh, this is ridiculous.
Hey, why are you just standing there?
Oh, come on in.
What's going on? Why the long face?
Honey, don't be surprised.
Apparently, Ji Hyuk is in Seoul.
He's supposedly starting a business and staying in a warehouse.
So what?
What do you mean, "So what?" We have to bring him home.
Bring him home? He's not a kid.
That's exactly why we have to drag him home.
He must be embarrassed too. How can he just show up on his own?
As his parents, we must be the ones to reach out.
Imagine what a state he must be in.
He's doing just fine on his own, so just leave him be.
Doing fine? Yes, right.
What's with your tone?
You knew about this, didn't you?
I saw him once.
You met him?
No, I just saw him on the street. He didn't see me, though.
Unbelievable!
You saw him, and you just ignored him?
And you didn't say a word to me? When you knew how worried I was?
If you saw him, you should've dragged him back here!
How could you see him after so long and just ignore him? Some father.
It's not that I ignored him. I couldn't get a word out.
He looked like he was doing fine without us.
What did you just say?
Even if you find out where he is, don't think of bringing him back.
- This... - I don't want him back. I don't.
What's he going on about?
Oh, I give up.
Fold it this way,
and then this way.
Do you really mean that?
You don't want Ji Hyuk to come home?
You really don't?
You heard me. Why do you keep asking?
Because I don't understand.
No matter how much he's let us down, he's still our son.
Maybe you can,
but I can't forgive him. No, I mean,
I can't accept it.
He said, "I was only getting married because of you, Father."
"I was only marrying a rich woman because of you."
He drove a dagger through my heart. And he never regrets his choices.
I'll never be able to forget that, honey.
Ji Hyuk...
never said it was your fault.
That rotten kid.
You and I were worried he was holed up in a cheap room,
living on cup noodles and drinking all day,
like a total wreck.
Though we were mad, we were so worried...
that we couldn't even sleep.
But he was doing just fine. He was dressed sharp and smiling.
And I'm supposed to just go up to him?
If he'd looked messy and defeated, I'd have grabbed him right away.
But I couldn't.
I was just too ashamed to say anything. You know?
How do I stop him when he's so proud?
What would I even say to him?
Apparently, he said he's starting a business.
A business?
No wonder he looked so prosperous. In just a few months.
Well, good for him, then. Right?
He was always talking about moving out anyway.
He said he hated living here.
Don't you remember?
He told Ji Wan...
that he wanted to come back after becoming successful.
Tell him to save it. All right?
His success is for his own good. When did we ever ask for his money?
What does "success" even mean?
That's just how his mind works.
He thinks if he makes lots of money, we'll be falling all over him.
That's why he resented me so much and why he looks down on me.
Even if he comes crawling back, I swear I'll kick him back out.
Mother will hear you. Keep your voice down.
Goodness.
What's gotten into you?
I'll check in on Mother and then go study.
I have to study for my exam.
Ji Hyuk was smiling?
Yes.
Okay, please be on time tomorrow.
Okay.
(Director Ko Seong Hui)
Yes, Director Ko.
Ms. Ji, would you be free today? Around 8pm today.
Today?
I know it's not right to keep you waiting any longer,
but I just happened to have an opening today.
I was wondering if we could at least have a quick meeting.
Yes, today works for me.
What time and where should I be?
We've always met outside before to see different studio styles.
Since the timing is awkward today, how about you come to my office?
Yes, of course. I'll be at Gaon Foundation by 8pm.
Here it is.
- Mom. - Eun Oh!
Feed me.
My meeting got pushed back, so I had a free hour and stopped by.
Just sit tight. I'll bring you some right away.
Mom.
The owner's daughter has to serve herself.
I'll get it.
Thank you for the meal.
- Yes, thank you. Have a good day. - Bye.
You too. Thank you.
Eat up. What else can I get you?
No, I'm stuffed, Mom. Besides, I have to go.
- Already? - Excuse me.
Are you Gang Oh's mother?
Yes, I am.
We're friends of Gang Oh's from high school.
Gang Oh mentioned you run a Korean BBQ place around here.
I think I remember seeing you at school back in the day.
Really? Oh, my goodness! So nice to see you. Please sit down.
His mom runs a place like this, so why's he working at a pickup bar?
- Mom, I'm off. I'm late. - Okay.
A pickup bar?
Where is that?
It's called Couples' Bar, over in Hongdae.
Okay. And...
Here you go.
Ms. Ji, you're a real hard worker.
Until the artists have been selected,
you could've just worked with some vague ideas.
You mentioned 2 painters and 1 for stationery or home goods.
So I was working on two versions based on that.
That's right.
You're so ahead of the game.
It's unbelievable.
We'd all but settled on two artists, a painter and an illustrator,
but one is under investigation for drug use.
What now?
We have to start over with a new list.
So that's what happened.
Life's just so complicated, isn't it?
I do like this layout,
but we might only have one painter and an artist from another genre.
Let's use this as a baseline, but pause until my side is sorted.
Will you do that for me?
But...
if we do that, the studio space will just be sitting empty.
So that's what you were worried about.
Don't worry about that.
What's more important to us...
is making sure we support truly deserving artists.
Okay. Then I'll wait for your decision.
I'll pause all work on the floor plans until then.
Sounds good.
You can focus on your other projects in the meantime.
Understood.
One moment, Ms. Ji. Please have a seat.
Here you go.
It's a calming candy.
"Calming candy?"
Not really.
It's just a name I made up. I eat one when I'm feeling sad...
or down because of old memories that resurface.
It actually cheers me up.
Okay.
I can't. I just can't hold it in.
Just tell me everything, Eun Oh.
Pardon?
Is that thing that was bothering you still not resolved?
No, that's not it.
This is different from before. How can someone so young be so hurt?
You seem so bright on the outside, but you're completely hollowed out.
That's how you seem today.
That's not it.
I think I'm just a little tired.
I'm so sorry for worrying you.
I really am. I'll be leaving now.
What if I told you...
my own buried secret?
How does that sound?
I have a daughter I lost.
No one knows.
No one but me.
A tragic story, isn't it?
Can you imagine what it's been like for me, living with that?
Director Ko...
But it's so strange.
This secret... It's a massive one, isn't it?
And yet, why am I telling you of all people?
Is it because you looked so empty inside today, like a ghost?
I...
I don't know my birth parents.
But that's not what bothers me.
But...
my younger brother just found out that I was adopted.
He says he doesn't see me as family anymore.
Oh, my goodness.
So that's what's been scaring you, Eun Oh.
I'm so scared he won't come back.
I'm worried about my mom,
and I keep wondering if I really did steal his place in the family.
Until my dad's business failed,
we were actually pretty well-off.
Did your parents make you feel that way?
No, not at all.
Even after I learned I was adopted, I wondered about my birth parents,
but I never missed them.
My mom and dad are my parents.
You're so mature.
I grew up with a lot of love.
Then I guess you'll just have to wait.
After all, those loving parents are his birth parents too.
So your brother is probably a lot like you.
Just be patient.
You think so?
(Bus Stop, Gaon Foundation)
Hello. Welcome.
- Hello. - You can take this table.
It's called Couples' Bar, over in Hongdae.
Mom. My birth mother wouldn't be like this.
Gang Oh, I'm sorry.
Is it me or Ji Eun Oh?
It's Eun Oh.
My daughter.
(Couples' Bar)
Your offer to be partners. Is that still on the table?
At this hour?
I have to go to the Mapo site.
Eun Oh.
Ms. Ji Eun Oh.
Fine, Ms. Ji Eun Oh.
You came all this way to say yes? At this hour?
So, are you in or out?
I'm in.
Let's do it.
I have some conditions. Three, to be exact.
If you accept my conditions and we get them notarized,
then we have a deal.
Notarized?
(Our Golden Days)
Aren't you going too far? What am I, your servant?
Looks like you'll be one for a while.
Since your mom isn't giving you money.
Did I just hear you right? This is your only webtoon?
Look. I can't do it.
They say I'm not qualified.
Forging papers to meet a guy. Should I let you become a criminal?
No, not gukbap. I don't like it.
Why is Ji Hyuk being so formal with you?
It's like he only sees you as a business partner.
What am I doing? She's not my junior anymore.