You should...
marry me, Ji Hyuk.
What?
Marry me.
What got into you?
I'm not asking you to marry me...
because I don't know
you announced to everyone...
that you won't marry.
I'm so flabbergasted
that I don't want to respond.
If this is nonsense, quit it.
If you have an ulterior motive,
just say it.
I will respond
after hearing the whole thing.
You know, I've been in love before.
Seriously enough to risk my life.
I thought
I'd never be able to forget him.
I mean, I loved him so much...
that I decided to stay with him
for the rest of my life.
If I knew where he was,
I'd want to run to him right away.
I was in love
that had so many lingering regrets.
But just because I love him,
it doesn't mean I can be with him.
You know that.
Now that the man I love is gone,
I have no choice
but to give up on love,
but I don't want to give up
the background offered by my father.
I think you want...
to stay single
because the losses outweigh...
the gains from marriage.
Are you done?
I agree with you, Ji Hyuk.
Now, I know that
marriage isn't just about love.
That's why I'm suggesting a deal.
Why would you refuse to get married
when you could gain a lot from it?
It's not like
I want us to be lovebirds.
But still...
You wanted to stay single
because you thought...
you wouldn't find someone to love?
That's not it, right?
Then there's no reason
not to marry without love.
Besides, you are not
the type of person who loves anyone.
You say
you can control your feelings.
What is it that...
I get from this marriage
at this point?
Should I start
negotiating or something?
I'm the only daughter
of the Haneul Construction family.
My father, CEO Jung Ho Yeong,
has his ironclad rule
of not letting a woman...
take over control of the company.
You are already aware of that.
Because there were
rumors going around.
And who knows?
We might develop feelings
for each other...
while living together.
Then we could be a real couple.
Or...
we could get a divorce.
After my father passes away.
I don't know
when that will be, though.
Aren't you laying your cards
on the table too easily?
So, you know
that I'm not just saying this.
I'll give you some time
to think about it, then.
I'll see you here next week.
(Episode 4)
I've never seen anything like that
in my life.
Hello, Father.
Ji Hyuk, do you have plans
for tonight after work?
You knew?
No. I don't have any plans.
Then meet me outside after work.
Where should I go?
Should I go to Mr. Yeong Bo's place?
- Here.
- Hey.
I'll pour my own drink.
Don't take the fun away from me.
We haven't done this
for a long time.
I know.
All right.
Gosh, I'm so jealous.
You have a son
who can drink with you.
Mr. Choi has terminal cancer.
That's why it turned out this way.
I see.
His son is quite young.
So he probably thinks differently
from his father.
He was acting all condescending,
so I taught him a lesson.
I see.
I'm meeting with people
in the industry now.
I believe I'll get a job soon.
I was going to tell you
the whole thing after that.
Okay.
Do Ji Wan and Su Bin know too?
Not yet.
I think you should tell them
as soon as possible.
No.
I'll tell them after I get a job.
I don't want to disappoint them.
We don't know when it will be.
What?
Finding a new job
after retirement isn't so easy.
Pull yourself together.
That's what happens
after you retire.
That's reality.
Right.
It's not easy. It will be hard.
It's not like I don't know that.
I have a lot of colleagues...
who left the company before me...
and are now struggling
with harsh realities.
Still, I was hired
by another company...
even before my retirement.
There must be a reason for that.
I'll tell Ji Wan and Su Bin
about this.
Mom and Grandma
will have a hard time...
pretending everything's fine.
Don't say anything.
Don't tell Ji Wan and Su Bin.
And don't show it
to your mom and grandma.
It's not the kind of thing
that should be kept secret.
It's something
that happens to everyone.
Try as we might,
but we're just employees.
Don't be so quick to assume
that your dad will end up like that.
It's not like we have to worry
about living expenses now.
You have your job.
And Ji Wan doesn't need my support.
I just need to support Su Bin.
What's there to worry about?
I'm telling you
it'll take 2 to 3 months at most.
Where are you planning to work?
Of course,
it's the textile industry.
It doesn't have to be
the same industry.
Keep your options open.
Come on.
I'll take care of it myself.
Where do you spend your time
outside?
Where do you think?
I'm busy meeting people
in the industry...
and asking for a job.
I go hiking sometimes.
I also go for a game of pool
here and there.
I meet my friends from college too.
- Here.
- Okay.
Oh, dear.
How long has it been since
we last walked together like this?
It's been a long time.
Hey.
By the way,
why am I looking up at you now?
It feels like just yesterday
I was looking down at you.
That was a long time ago.
It's been a million years
since I got taller than you.
Really?
Fine. You're tall.
Of course. I'm your son, aren't I?
(Jung Hyeon Su Architecture Lab)
Do you mind if I leave now?
I need to run.
If you can't hide how upset you are,
you'd be better off
quitting the cafe.
Fine, Lee Ji Hyuk.
I will forget everything.
I'll end things completely.
I've thought all about it.
Do you think
I haven't thought about it?
Why don't I deserve to be with you?
Because I'm not feminine?
Because I don't dress myself up?
Because I have a bad personality
or a strong personality?
Because we have different tastes?
That wasn't the case.
Then the only reason remaining is...
Because of my background?
Because I'm from a poor family?
Because I don't make good money?
That can't be the reason.
You don't want to get married.
You have no reason
to care about my background...
when you have no intention
of getting married.
What on earth is it?
I don't know
why you are not telling me.
(Buy 8 cans of beer
and get 3 dollars cash back.)
No.
I won't drown my sorrows in drink.
I can get over it myself.
Oh, dear.
We have ginseng wine
left over from the ancestral rite.
I saw Gang Oh
make highballs in secret.
I feel so weird.
My leg hurts.
This is killing me.
Isn't that your sister?
- I think it is.
- Oh, no.
What...
Eun Oh.
My gosh.
- Eun Oh.
- Ji Eun Oh.
My goodness. Eun Oh!
Da Jeong.
When people say,
"The elderly are welcome,"
what age range do they mean?
Where are they welcome?
I was walking by...
a restaurant or something,
and they were looking for help.
Wouldn't they mean 65 years old?
People aged 65 and over
can use public transport for free.
Sixty-five?
They're babies compared to you,
if they're 65.
(Library Village)
How much did she drink
and how hungover is she...
that you called a part-timer?
She was at the ER all night.
She passed out after drinking...
way too many
different kinds of liquor,
and they pumped her stomach
thinking she'd overdosed.
On top of that,
she's overworked and fatigued,
so she needs to take
a week or so off.
(Park Seong Jae)
Ji Hyuk.
I think Eun Oh is really sick.
She went to the ER.
(Incoming call: Park Seong Jae)
So what?
What?
I got the text about Eun Oh.
Where is she now?
She's resting at home.
She's fine, then.
Bye.
Hey.
Yes, sir.
Call Yurim Korean Medicine Clinic,
please.
(Apple mangoes)
Goodness.
Eun Oh.
Someone sent you
some expensive gongjindan.
My gosh.
There's fruit and tea as well,
not to mention various snacks.
Hang on.
"Park Seong Jae."
Who's this?
(Get well soon.
From Park Seong Jae.)
Get well soon.
A cafe regular.
What?
You never run out of things to eat.
Someone sent bread
from a new bakery.
They must know you well.
You can have it.
- What?
- For real? Thank you.
Don't touch it.
Let her pick first.
You can eat later.
Eun Oh. You had some porridge.
Pick out what bread you want
and eat it when you feel like it.
Take a bite at least.
- Sit up.
- My gosh.
Here.
Pick something out.
My goodness.
They have bread
shaped like a coal briquette?
They're serious about marketing.
- Look at what they wrote.
- What?
"We hope the sweet aroma..."
"is deeply comforting."
I'm getting goosebumps.
You can take those.
Oh, dear. Lie down and rest.
Do you have a fever?
Mr. Lee.
My knees hurt so bad.
Your feet are almost parallel.
Stand so your toes face outward.
Keep them shoulder-width apart,
and go straight down.
When you squat,
you want to feel
your hip joints fold.
When you get up,
use your thighs and glutes.
Where are my glutes?
Your glutes are right...
Right here?
What?
What are you doing?
I apologize.
Hey.
You refuse female clients
because of your girlfriend...
when she isn't even watching,
and you won't even touch them
when helping them exercise.
What kind of instructor does that?
That wasn't
because of my girlfriend.
That's just what I'm like.
Pack your things.
I can't quit when I have clients...
Report me to the Ministry of Labor.
No, sir. I'll pack my things.
Why did I even buy you?
(Calling: Lee Ji Hyuk)
The person is not answering.
Don't run!
Come here. I'm so sorry.
Jeong Eun.
I want to be alone for a while.
I'll be in touch.
What do you think?
It's a lovely early-summer look.
Sleeveless tops
are for midsummer only?
No.
A true fashion-forward person...
dresses ahead of the season.
Cut. Okay, good.
It's so cold.
Darn, it's freezing.
Is this even necessary
when it's freezing outside?
I said we should film
once it got warmer.
You have goosebumps
all over your body.
I'm fine.
I could shave my own skin
if it came down to it.
I'm going to gain more subscribers.
Never will I be humiliated
like that again.
I have to ask.
Suppose you marry a rich guy...
after reaching
70,000 to 80,000 subscribers.
Where does that leave me?
Ha Eun, come on.
And you call yourself my friend?
I'm not doing this
just to marry a rich guy.
Why else did you join
a matchmaking service...
when we're only 24?
Well,
that's where all the wealthy
and capable men are.
And men like women
who are young and pretty.
That's exactly what I said.
It's not.
I won't marry a guy
just for his money.
I'll marry someone
who's "also" rich.
To do that, I need something
to show for myself...
other than looks, youth,
and a toned body.
That being said,
give this channel your all
without any worries.
I'll make sure we hit
a million subscribers.
Sure.
I'll change into a different outfit.
(Cook wanted)
(Age limit: 70)
Why is Da Jeong's father
in this neighborhood?
We should hurry.
We only have until 1 p.m.
I know.
Hello, Mr. Lee Ji Hyuk.
Congratulations on becoming
an assistant manager at SSP Company.
I knew it.
I'm starting out again
as an assistant manager.
Darn it.
That shocked me to the core.
Shoot.
Should I just go home?
Ji Wan, why are you home so early?
Oh, right.
My client canceled our session
for today.
If you keep working out like that,
you'll gain thicker thighs,
not a booty.
Why did you hit me?
Anyway,
why the sudden weight training?
Hey, you said you'd give me
free training sessions at your gym.
I'll start tomorrow.
Oh, that?
You see...
Ji Wan, don't tell me...
you quit again.
Hey, what's the matter
with old ladies?
I was going to tell you...
to start giving Mom
living expenses next month.
Why?
Why do I need to give her money?
Dad's job offer at Seongil Weaving
was canceled.
It was canceled?
He hasn't been able to tell us...
and goes out each day
searching for a job.
Su Bin, don't tell the family
I was home.
It's one hurdle after another.
Our family's in trouble.
How come Ji Hyuk is
the only normal one around here?
What do I do?
I still need to pay the lease
for this car.
It's not like
I can borrow money from Mom.
Lee Ji Wan, you crazy fool.
How can you even think
about borrowing money...
when you leased this car
just to impress a girl?
On top of that,
your dad is jobless now!
If you hear back
after applying for a job,
you'll take it
regardless of the position.
Got it?
Nod if you understand.
(Deposit: 1,000 dollars,
Lee Ji Hyuk)
What? Ji Hyuk wired 1,000 dollars.
(My eldest son)
Yes, Mother.
Hey, Ji Hyuk.
You must've made a mistake
and wired me 1,000 dollars.
It wasn't a mistake.
Wasn't it?
Why did you wire 500 dollars more?
No reason.
As if that makes sense.
I know...
Dad's job offer was canceled.
Oh, dear. You knew?
How did you find out?
By accident.
Use that to cover
our living expenses...
until Dad finds a new job.
Come on. This isn't necessary.
I'd feel better, that's all.
Anyway, I'll hang up now.
Oh, sure.
How did he find out?
This sure feels strange.
Actually, no. I feel relieved,
like a weight has been lifted.
Why do you feel relieved?
You're home early today.
Why are you relieved,
and what made you startle
at my presence?
Oh, that.
Well...
Father.
We need to talk.
You.
How can you be so careless?
I told you to ignore it...
since I'll get a job
in a month or two.
Why didn't you listen to me?
There's my position to consider.
What about the position you're in?
No one asked you
to worry about living expenses.
I'm the father
and the breadwinner of this house.
I didn't give her the money
to help you out.
What?
I gave her
more than I normally do...
to give her stability.
It didn't sit right with me.
It killed me to see her
act like this wasn't affecting her.
How can you go behind my back
just to feel at ease?
So that your pride isn't hurt,
do Grandma, Mom, I,
and even you have to act
like everything's fine?
Like you're set to start work soon?
I believe you'll find...
another job.
Still, that may take a while.
Longer than you realize.
And having your job offer canceled?
That isn't a big deal.
Not in this day and age.
This could happen to anyone,
and you were just unlucky.
So,
you don't have to make us
tiptoe around you.
You brat.
I'll call you
when your food is ready.
Okay.
Are you sure you're all right?
I told you
to take two more days off.
I'm totally fine, times a hundred.
Okay? I'm sick of saying this.
You had such a hard time
that you got dead drunk.
I just tried to drink it all away.
So did it work?
Are you feeling better now?
I'll be fine.
Now, I know the reason.
What reason?
The reason I felt so flustered...
and embarrassed
when Ji Hyuk turned me down.
So, why? What's the reason?
Su Jeong.
Didn't Ji Hyuk come today?
Ji Hyuk didn't come.
Instead...
Eun Oh.
You know,
even if he'd reject me,
I thought
he'd still give me a chance.
So...
I never thought
about what would happen next.
"What happens after he rejects me?"
That thought never crossed my mind.
I just thought...
I wanted to tell him
about my feelings.
You...
trusted Ji Hyuk.
I guess I did. What a fool.
I was mistaken.
So after he rejected me,
I was flustered and confused,
not knowing what to do.
That's why I was being pathetic.
I was being so lame.
How are you feeling now?
I accepted it and gave up on him.
I'll try...
to go back
to how things were before.
Can you do that?
I have to.
I caused this trouble by myself.
It's not a situation
I can call fortunate,
but I'm still glad to hear that.
I know.
I should go check out the cafe
that I renovated. It's newly opened.
- Are you done talking?
- Yes.
I have a question for you, Mr. Park.
Why did you keep asking me
if Ji Hyuk stopped by all week?
Isn't he answering his phone?
Did you two fight?
Is something wrong with Ji Hyuk?
There's something I'm worried about.
What is it?
I can't tell you that.
Mr. Park, is it that...
you have a crush on him?
Is that why you're single?
Hey.
You mean, Ji Hyuk?
My goodness.
I can say...
that he's my second favorite person
in the world.
If he's
your second favorite person...
when you don't have a girlfriend...
When I was about to wither away,
he was like a stream of water to me.
He was the first person
to stand by me.
I didn't know
you two had such an eventful past.
Hey.
Why are you using
the back gate today?
Seong Jae,
I told you not to do that.
You don't have to be afraid of us.
You came wearing new sneakers
to give them to me.
Why would we bully you?
Seong Jae.
Wear these today.
These are the limited-edition
collaboration sneakers.
Aren't they pretty?
I like wearing these.
What are you talking about?
How would I let you
wear them to school?
I know your shoes got swapped
by mistake,
but you can't keep wearing
those worn-out shoes.
If your dad finds out,
you'll be in big trouble.
I won't tell him...
that you lost your shoes
several times.
I'll keep it a secret.
Here. Put these on.
- You brat.
- No.
No.
What do you mean, no? You little...
Hey. Let him up.
Darn it.
Park Seong Jae.
Take off your shoes.
Hey!
That's enough.
You let him run errands
every morning,
steal his shoes,
and even take money from him
every Monday. Isn't that enough?
Look at you.
Lee Ji Hyuk, you nerd.
You're not watching your mouth
because you get good grades?
He's in my class,
and I'm the class president.
So what? You are the class president
only at school.
Are you the president
of the neighborhood or what?
Hey.
- Trample on him.
- You are so cool, Go Dae Yong.
Why?
Can't you beat me on your own?
What?
If you want to fight,
do it man-to-man.
You pathetic coward, Go Dae Yong.
You can't deal with me
on your own, can you?
Lee Ji Hyuk, you...
Is something wrong
with your brain today?
Just answer me.
Let's fight one-on-one.
Lee Ji Hyuk, don't regret it
even if you die today.
I'll smash you to bits.
If you lose to me,
don't mess with Park Seong Jae
ever again.
- Hey.
- Go easy on him.
- Cool.
- Nice.
Hey.
What? Stop it already!
Let go. Get off me.
Hey.
Hey, Go Dae Yong!
Hey! Wake up.
- Darn it.
- Hey.
He's no big deal. Let's go.
- Hey, wake up.
- What's wrong with him?
Did you all see that?
You can't mess
with Park Seong Jae anymore.
Shut it.
It's not like you got hit.
Darn it.
He was a good person back then too.
But why did you let them
bully you like that?
Were you too scared?
I guess I was.
I should get going.
(Park Seong Jae)
Let me ease your worries.
Eun Oh came to work today.
You rascal.
That's a relief.
(Congratulations on your opening.
From Eunoism Design)
You didn't have to bring this.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
This space is crazy.
- Really?
- People are posting...
photos of this on social media.
I thought...
the wheel seemed familiar.
I heard you were sick.
I knew you'd be like that.
You shouldn't skip meals.
You're annoying.
I guess I am.
Are you feeling better?
After getting some good rest,
I feel even better
than before I got sick.
Where have you been?
The cafe I renovated is open.
I went there to deliver a gift...
and check on any issues.
When does the next project begin?
I don't have any plans yet.
By the way, I got an email
from our university juniors.
They came up with 30 ideas...
because it's our 30th anniversary.
Are they going to skip
lectures and exams...
and spend...
the whole semester doing club stuff?
It's just a club, not a calling.
That's exactly what you were like.
That was because
I was thinking of...
becoming an interior designer.
They want to redo two places
this time...
during the whole summer vacation.
I don't mind
drawing the floor plans,
but we'll need to blackmail
the technical majors, right?
Eun Oh.
Don't try too hard.
- What?
- To keep talking.
You don't have to.
I always talked a bit too much
whenever...
we were going somewhere.
Not this much, though.
You took time to breathe.
Did I?
You can be so mean sometimes.
You're too honest.
Not all the time.
I'm mostly honest.
But sometimes,
I pretend to be honest.
When you do pretend to be honest?
When I need to.
When I feel uncomfortable.
When I'm a coward.
You're like that too.
We're all human.
Do you think some are different?
You fool.
Go on inside.
You're not coming to the cafe?
Seong Jae told me
you were back at work.
I dropped by to see you.
I see.
The next guy you choose...
should be kind,
not simply someone you like.
Liking someone is about feelings,
and feelings...
are powerless.
That's some cool-sounding advice.
Eat regularly. You've lost weight.
Okay.
Take care, Ji Hyuk.
Would you like to order?
Not exactly.
Is this your design portfolio?
No, it's not mine.
Here she is. It's hers.
Aren't you...
Are you...
Hello. Do you feel better?
It really is you
from the subway station.
I'm fine, thanks to you.
That's good to hear.
Eun Oh. Do you know her?
- Well...
- I was curious about this designer.
It was you.
Well, yes.
If you don't mind,
could we perhaps talk for a bit?
Well...
It's quiet right now.
I can spare a few minutes.
I didn't know you had company.
Our business was done.
I accepted it...
and gave up on him. I'll try...
to go back
to how things were before.
You care about Eun Oh so much.
Why did you make her ask me out
and get hurt?
Whenever I tried to approach Eun Oh,
you tried to stop me.
You said I couldn't be with her.
That I didn't deserve her.
You said...
I didn't deserve her.
You don't need to follow me in,
and I don't need tea.
It's a sudden raid.
There's talk that you go out
for 30 minutes to an hour.
This is inappropriate as a father...
and as a superior.
I'm here for two reasons.
"I'm going to marry the person
I naturally end up dating."
"If I marry, that is."
It's pretty vague.
Tell me clearly
if you intend to marry or not.
Are you slacking off
because sales went up?
Did you make me a director
without allowing me...
to manage my own schedule?
And about marriage.
It's as I said.
You have until the end of the year.
If you don't find someone
until then,
that's a shortcoming on your part.
I expect you to marry
the woman I find you.
(Shoealls)
I'm preparing a project, you see.
I was looking for someone
to design the interior,
and I happened to...
Sorry. What's your name?
Oh, my name is Ji Eun Oh.
I see.
That's why the company's called
Eunoism Design.
Yes.
My name is Ko Seong Hui.
(Gaon Foundation, Ko Seong Hui)
I guess you could call it
a space for art and design.
I was planning something like that.
I happened to see your portfolio,
and I quite liked it.
Oh, I see.
I'd like to give you the job.
You don't seem to have
much experience.
No. I got into interior design
about a year ago.
Then three businesses and this cafe.
- You designed four spaces?
- Yes.
I did the interior
of a few studio apartments,
but those were friends' places
I did for free for the experience.
I don't know how big
the project you're planning is,
but you should look into others
with more experience too.
If you tell me the image you want,
I'll sketch something
for you to look at.
You can decide then.
You can even decide
after I give you an estimate.
Why would you say that?
- Pardon?
- I like you, and that's it.
I want you to do it.
Me?
I got the feel
when I saw your portfolio.
I have another appointment.
I'd like to discuss
the details in person.
When are you free?
I'm free whenever you are.
What about this cafe?
I accepted the manager role
because I'm allowed to come and go.
A senior of my university club
invested in the cafe.
I thought it was a nice place.
It's where cool people gather.
My number's on that card.
Text me your number.
Okay. I'll do that.
I hope to see you soon.
Yes.
(Gaon Foundation, Ko Seong Hui)
This is insane.
It must be true
that deities bless good people.
It's not official yet.
She could've given me the job
impulsively...
because I'd helped her.
I really hope she calls.
Me too.
I need something to concentrate on.
I gave an estimate for an apartment,
but the person didn't call.
You should place it there.
(6 a.m., Alarm)
Who's calling this early?
Dad's job offer at Seongil Weaving
was canceled.
He hasn't been able to tell us...
and goes out each day
searching for a job.
Shoot.
Pull yourself together.
You can't afford to sleep in.
The family can't know
you were fired.
I'll catch this punk
the second I see him.
So don't worry, and head inside.
Right.
Thank you.
It's been a while, Yeong Ra.
You know how I feel about you now.
- Let go!
- Yeong Ra!
- No...
- Yeong Ra, wait.
Come on, Yeong Ra.
Haven't I done enough
to prove how I feel?
I gave you a flower like this
at your graduation exhibition.
Don't you remember that?
No...
I'm not a scary person.
- Please don't hurt me.
- Yeong Ra.
Please don't hurt me. Please.
What's going on?
Who are you?
Ms. Park.
Who was that man?
Should I call the police?
You can't get caught up
in any kind of scandal.
No, please don't.
He's probably a fan,
and I was just startled
that he suddenly came by.
A fan who shows up
out of the blue like that...
is most likely a stalker.
No, it's not that.
I'm fine, Jeong Hui.
I'll be fine.
How long are you going
to think this through?
What will it be?
What are you going to do?
This is Ruche General Contractor.
We were impressed by your resume...
and will contact you next week
to schedule an interview.
Way to go.
Didn't you quit tennis
over three years ago?
What are you even doing here?
How did you know I was here?
I tracked your GPS. Happy now?
What's gotten into you?
Eun Oh, it's about Ji Hyuk.
Stop. Don't mention his name.
Isn't it strange
that he hasn't been at the cafe...
and hasn't even contacted Mr. Park?
It's odd. Very odd.
But since I need to move on
with my life,
I won't think about it.
Got it. I won't mention
Lee Ji Hyuk from now on.
You've been ignoring
my texts and calls,
and you still refuse
to talk to me in person.
Am I even still a friend to you?
I texted saying
I wanted to be alone.
Why did you come find me
instead of just letting me be?
I searched for you
at the pool you go to,
at the Han River,
and at the free diving pool,
and then came here just in case.
Why? Is something up?
What is it?
As if something would be up
with someone as boring as me.
I looked for you to give you this.
What's this?
This is the guest studio apartment
owned by our company.
You've probably been
wandering around...
after leaving home
saying you were headed to work.
Spend your time there instead.
You're being generous...
despite not knowing
the situation I'm in.
You...
Don't waste your time
at places like this.
It's pathetic.
What's so pathetic?
Playing sports is the best way
to clear your head and think.
Head to the unit starting tomorrow
and look for jobs.
You still haven't decided on one,
have you?
A job?
Doesn't your line of work
hire people with experience?
(Libeore)
It's not my work but another matter
I had to think about.
As in what?
Is something else up
with the family?
I was thinking about
how it would be...
to marry Jung Bo A.
Jung Bo A?
Hold on.
Jung Bo A at Haneul Construction?
Yes.
She asked me to marry her,
and that's what I was considering.
Quite seriously, too.
She asked you to marry her?
Jung Bo A asked you to marry her?
Yes.
Why?
Because she wants to marry me.
Did she really ask you?
She did.
I couldn't care less
about her state of mind,
but you don't seem
to be joking about this.
But how is this even up for debate?
Can't I consider it?
There's nothing
between you and Jung Bo A.
How can you be sure...
that there's nothing between us?
I'm sure.
You don't love her,
and she doesn't love you either.
Am I wrong?
Love?
Sure. We're not in love.
Exactly.
So what the heck am I even hearing?
Why did she propose
something so ridiculous,
and why are you...
even considering it?
Is this a comedy sitcom?
Lee Ji Hyuk, what's gotten into you?
Pull yourself together.
Why can't we marry
if we're not in love?
- What?
- Why can't you marry...
without love?
Who says you have to marry
someone you love...
when not every love
leads to marriage?
What is this nonsense?
Why would you marry without love?
What for?
I'm asking why you must love someone
to marry her.
Fine.
Why are you thinking...
about marrying someone
you don't even love?
I may not love her,
but I might need the marriage.
Why would you enter
into a marriage like that?
Just live alone,
for crying out loud.
Do that.
You're anti-marriage, after all.
- "A marriage like that?"
- You heard me.
As if I don't know
why Jung Bo A wants to marry you...
and why you're considering
marrying her.
Actually, you're clueless.
I know why.
I knew you'd never understand,
no matter how hard you tried.
But this is funny,
how you're objecting
until you're red in the face.
Because we're friends.
I'm objecting because we're friends.
Are you?
Ji Hyuk.
This isn't right at all.
Hearing you talk made me realize...
it's not a bad idea.
Yes. I can do it.
- What?
- This is why I didn't tell you.
It's why I couldn't.
It's not a topic for us.
Because you...
could never understand.
Lee Ji Hyuk.
Is this the extent
of our friendship?
There are things
that can't be shared.
There was.
Between us, even.
What does that mean?
Take care.
You're here.
I'm here.
Take a seat.
Then we can...
discuss our marriage.
You've made up your mind, then.
Some got married three days
after meeting on a blind date.
Thank you.
I feel reassured now.
My future won't be as bleak.
I feel the same.
We're getting married
because we both have a need.
Let's make this a win-win.
Do we have to...
sign a contract or something
before we get started?
That sounds horrific.
We're getting married for real.
It's not a contractual marriage.
You must have a boundary, though.
You seem to have one.
A boundary.
Tell me.
My father and I...
want you to work at our company.
That's the biggest thing.
Then...
here are my conditions.
Are you nervous?
I didn't think I'd meet him so soon.
Welcome. He's waiting for you.
I'm Lee Ji Hyuk.
He's the chief secretary.
Chief Secretary Cha Mun Seok
and Mr. Kim, the chauffeur.
You have keys in your pocket.
Yes.
They make a noise.
Leave them with him.
Okay.
Come this way.
Nice to meet you, sir.
I'm Lee Ji Hyuk.
I'm Jung Ho Yeong.
I'm Bo A's father.
Please speak freely.
I can't do that
until the handshake's over at least.
Let's sit down.
There's no need
to feel awkward or uncomfortable.
That goes for now and in the future.
The truth is,
we're not dating.
I know that.
I know why you want to get married.
I like you, still.
You're just the right man for Bo A.
Don't take it to heart.
Rumors about me have spread,
and no one at our level
will date me.
I know that much.
Does love come first
when it comes to marriage?
No.
I married my wife
after we'd met just three times,
and we're still happily married.
Right.
Bo A will give you...
a few dates to choose from
for the wedding.
I'd like it to be sooner
rather than later.
How about two weeks from now?
(Haneul Construction)
I guess
Mr. Kim picked up your car for you.
I'll go home with my father.
- Get in the car.
- Okay.
Call once you have
your parents' permission.
That will kick-start
the preparations.
Okay. I'll be in touch.
(What can I do for you?)
Text Ji Wan and Su Bin.
What do you mean...
you want to change the theme?
I have an idea.
I'm going to bring on a guest.
A guest?
(Oldest brother)
Be home by 6 p.m.
What?
I have something important to say.
Be there.
I got caught?
He found out?
Yes.
It was too stressful.
I'll come clean...
and get smacked just once.
But Ji Hyuk's punches really hurt.
What's the occasion
that all three of you...
came home around the same time?
It has been a while
since we gathered for a meal.
Ji Hyuk told us to come home early.
He texted us.
You did, Ji Hyuk? What for?
Is something going on?
Let's finish dinner first.
Tell us now.
What's going on?
Why did you want
Ji Wan and Su Bin here too?
Are you in trouble?
- No.
No. I have something to tell you.
Are you free this Thursday
around lunchtime?
Yes.
Mother, you must be free.
You two. Free up a few hours
even if you're busy.
- Okay.
Ji Hyuk.
Tell us what it's about first.
I'd like you...
to meet the parents
of the woman I'm going to marry.
I'm...
getting married.
(Our Golden Days)
I'm not asking
for permission to marry.
When did you schedule
the wedding for, then?
You held back and didn't get angry.
It didn't bruise your ego?
I look forward to
a new and impressive design.
How about 30,000 dollars as a fee?
I'm getting married.
You won't regret it?
Ji Hyuk's getting married.
This was why Ji Hyuk and I
didn't suit each other.
I'm off to sort things out
one last time.
I'll say goodbye
to my one-sided love.
Here comes the groom.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)