Garden
Episode 16
Dr. Gu,
this child has been waiting for treatment.
Please wait.
If Mo Deng Hospital
has economic needs,
my boss can help.
Thank you.
Tell me,
why don't you want to treat the patient?
You're in the same group as them.
Why do you ask me?
You mean,
your mother?
She doesn't deserve to be my mother.
I don't have a mother or a father.
I only have a master.
Now I even forget a lot of people I know.
Do you think I'm more talented?
I have two fathers,
two mothers,
and a lot of brothers and sisters.
They all want me to live.
Look,
so many people care about you.
Why do you still make them worry?
They want me to live
just to keep the money
my grandfather left me.
If I died before I was 18,
the money would be donated to the rescue fund.
So, Dr. Gu,
they don't really love me.
How could this happen?
Do I know him?
Why did you hide it from him?
Because you didn't take good care of him.
You don't deserve it.
I'm taking him away.
He won't go with you.
Do we know each other?
How can we know each other?
Then, is there anything between us...
Xiaofeng.
Why did you hide it from him?
Renyi,
Gu Xiaomei is mine.
Brother,
are you sure you saw that person?
You can tell me first.
How many Gu Xiaofengs did you draw?
I swear,
I only drew the one in the doctor's office.
I didn't do anything.
I just drew the one in the doctor's office.
I drew one Gu Xiaofeng in the book
of Life with You.
There's no second one.
Then why did you draw only one?
But he doesn't recognize me?
I don't know either.
Don't ask me.
I never thought that the character
could come out of the book.
Brother,
there must be a reason why Gu Xiaofeng doesn't recognize you.
Gu Xiaofeng.
He's a comic book artist.
Why does my heart ache?
Gu Xiaofeng.
I'll give you an apple.
Will it be better?
You know me?
I'm Gu Xiaofeng.
I'm the one who killed him.
Gu Xiaofeng.
After Ms Gu and Renyi
saved my grandma,
they often come here to visit us.
On diet,
the brain telomeres weak.
lovely not to see.
The
meaningful
wake
up
Now, your life is our life.
You agree, he can live.
You don't agree, he only disappears.
I warn you to stay away from Gu Xiaomeng.
Don't forget, Gu Xiaomeng is not a human in this world.
The Wujigian Pellet.
Then you should see if what I said is the Wujigian Pellet.
Only I know how to control Gu Xiaomeng's life.
Gu Xiaomeng, how can I protect you?
Did I really know how to use the Wujigian Pellet?
I will kill you.
Our boss said he would give you three days.
Don't blame me for being cruel.
Go.
You...
If you want money, don't touch him.