delayed hold
well
You know what I mean?
I just see you as my senior.
I've always called you Gu Xiaomei.
But I've never treated you as a sister.
That's your own business.
When you were together, you were far away from me.
Now that you've broken up,
you should consider me.
I'm not your sister anymore.
I'm your senior.
I'm not your senior.
You're my senior.
We should be together.
Mu Haoqian, let go of me.
I know who's the best for me.
Let go of me.
Mu Haoqian, let go of me.
Gu Xiaomei, I won't let go of you this time.
Mu Haoqian, if you don't let go of me,
I'll die for you.
I'm sorry.
My sister's illness has worsened.
Xiaomei, you must get better.
Because I need your help.
Although it sounds ridiculous,
it's the truth.
So we shouldn't give up, okay?
The situation is not optimistic.
You should let her have a good rest.
She can't run around.
How's she sleeping recently?
She's been sleeping well.
She's fine.
What's wrong?
Are you feeling unwell?
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Under their eyes,
I secretly treated Miao Zishi.
Don't be discovered.
Otherwise, I'll be the one who died.
Why did you avoid me?
No fate.
I can't meet you.
You don't want to meet me?
We've broken up.
Even if you die,
it's none of my business.
You care about me.
I...
I care about the world.
I care about you.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to say sorry.
Shen Ye,
I have one more thing to confess to you.
Whether you believe it or not,
it's all true.
Tell me.
I believe you.
Actually, I...
Xiao Feng.
Wu Xiao Feng.
What's wrong with you?
Please wake up.
It's been three days.
Why haven't you woken up?
Stop looking.
You have no chance.
As long as I don't have him,
I'll have a chance.
Why are you resting in the ward?
I'm worried about Sister Wu.
Brother,
you haven't slept for three days.
If Sister Wu sees you like this,
she will be heartbroken.
I believe her more.
Dr. Ren,
the director is calling you.
I'm sorry.
You're recovering.
Don't stay too long.
Those memories are starting to choose
The heart is silent
You said you remembered me
How can I stop
You said
I can't hear you.
I heard it all.
Why did you fall in love?
I will remember you
Remember me