[Previously on My Love Mix-Up!]
Why not confess to him during this outing? I'm sure it'll go well.
Be courageous and take one step forth.
I'm... going to confess to Ida.
I've come to actually like you.
Should we try dating?
Since you confessed your love sincerely, I want to respond to your feelings.
A-Are you serious? Way to go, Aoki!
Akkun, you're too loud.
Oh, sorry.
Well, good for you.
Yes.
That's only... if I'm remembering it correctly.
Hey.
Was that camping trip a dream?
- What are you so anxious about?
- I never thought he' would accept me.
- I wasn't prepared.
- What a pain.
You were the one who liked him first, right?
I know, but...
You would never understand my complex emotions.
I originally wanted to get confessed to by a cute girl,
- then go on dates with her.
- Isn't this fun, Hashimoto?
That's how I imagine my high school life would be.
It is fun, Aoki.
It's so much fun, Aoki.
Now am I doing that with Ida?
Your imagination has gone haywire.
Nothing else matters as long as you like him.
I wonder if he is serious about me.
So that's what you're worried about.
Stop moping and just go ask Ida.
- What are you doing?
- Come on.
- Where are we going?
- To the gym.
- Right now?
- Yes!
Ida...
Now, go find out how serious he is.
Aoki?
Gather around!
Okay!
You idiot, what have you done?
Why are you so upset?
Before the practice game against Shiroyama High School tomorrow,
there are a few things I want to remind you of.
- Does he have a game tomorrow?
- The player you should look out the most is...
You should go cheer for him.
Like hell I will.
You're so dishonest with yourself.
And there's one more person who could really distract us.
That's right. Their beautiful manager, Kokomi Matsuuchi.
What is he going on about?
That has nothing to do with volleyball.
I heard Ms. Kokomi Matsuuchi has a crush on someone
on our team.
What?
You all know that Toyoda has a girlfriend at Shiroyama High, right?
Apparently, she heard the news from Kokomi personally.
She's going to give him a gift at tomorrow's game.
Toyoda... Is this true?
- Yes.
- Who could it be?
We've never had girlfriends except for Toyota. Who could it be that she likes?
The most likely candidate has to be...
Well, it has to be Kosuke.
What?
You're in trouble, Aoki.
Your rival has appeared.
I don't care. Not one bit.
Your legs are shaking like crazy.
[My Love Mix-Up!]
[Episode 6]
What are you going to do?
What do you mean? About what?
The beautiful manager might steal Ida away from you.
Ida will be fine. He's not a player.
I don't think he would cheat on me.
Cheat? You don't even know if he's serious about you.
Good point.
- Did you ask Ida how he feels?
- What?
About if he really likes you or not.
I... can't ask him that.
If you're going to date him, shouldn't you confirm his feelings?
No way! I could never ask him that to his face.
- Then why not ask him via text?
- What?
Just text him casually.
- What do I say to him?
- How should I know?
- This is between you and Ida.
- You're right.
That's right.
Good luck.
I don't have the leisure to give you advice.
Hasshi, we're going without you.
Okay, I'll catch up with you soon.
Hey, Aoki?
"Do you like me?"
No, that's too direct.
Should I sound him out with a sticker?
After giving you all that advice, you brushed me off when I need advice.
[Are we dating?]
Oh God, it sounds so lame.
I shouldn't send this.
Sota?
Take a bath now, so the water won't get cold.
Okay!
Seriously...
What? N-No way. Crap.
He read it so quickly.
I wasn't even ready to send it.
But he didn't respond...
Maybe it was just a dream, after all.
I'll tell to you at school next time.
Next time?
When is next time?
Is he putting off his answer
and taking up with the pretty manager?
Calm down. Ida isn't that fickle.
Sota, do you know where my opera glasses are?
Watch them closely.
Yes, Sir.
She's folding them perfectly right.
She is amazing.
I want a manager like her in our team.
- What a beauty.
- She's perfect.
She's devoted and a hard-worker.
She is the kind of earnest that doesn't slack off even when no one is looking.
A true beauty that would sacrifice herself for someone else's sake.
Kokomi Matsuuchi, you're incredible.
This is bad.
Ida may be thickheaded, but she'll surely win him over, too.
Here it comes! The present!
Crap, there it is.
Hello, Mr. Taniguchi.
I'm looking forward to the game.
Likewise.
Here's our starting lineup.
Oh, thanks. Here's ours.
Sir?
Well...
You see...
- Gather around!
- Okay!
Well, excuse me.
Sure.
Mr. Taniguchi, what did she say to you?
She was holding something like a present.
Oh, yes. I guess there was someone she wanted to give it to,
but I told her to give it to them in person.
I knew it. She likes Ida.
She definitely has her eye on him.
That was close.
He almost saw me.
Aoki?
Busted.
Oh? Ida, what are you doing?
We have a practice game today.
Aoki, did you come to cheer for me?
N-No way!
I just forgot something, yo! I'm not interested in your game!
Well...
I was curious about your text yesterday.
Right.
I thought it would be quicker for us to talk at school.
You thought wrong.
That defeats the purpose of texts. You should've given me a hint, at least.
I'm not really good with phones.
What are you, a grandpa?
You know, I realized something when I read your message.
Pardon?
About what?
I don't think I ever properly told you.
Properly told me...?
Is he...
going to say that we should stop?
I'm looking forward to it.
We're dating, aren't we?
What?
O-Oh, yes.
Me, too.
Well, I have a game to play.
Wait. Is that it?
Nothing's really changed between us, though.
You're right.
Listen,
Ida, do you...
li... li...
- like me?
- I don't know.
What?
I've never liked anyone before.
I don't have any experience to compare you to.
It's weird to date someone without liking them.
Hi, Kosuke.
- Kosuke...?
- She is on a first name basis?
Matsuuchi.
What? Do you guys know each other?
Yes. I hung out with her before with Toyoda and his girlfriend.
You're not on the volleyball team, are you?
Is he your friend?
Well...
I'm Aoki, his classmate.
- Are you mad or something?
- Not at all.
So what is it?
Right. Well...
I wasn't sure if you heard
my conversation with Mr. Taniguchi.
- Not really.
- He's a bonehead, and not interested in that kind of stuff.
He's also bad at using phones and barely replies to messages.
According to him, I'm a grandpa.
I like that about you.
You are calm and mature in my eyes.
He's mature because he's a grandpa.
- That's exactly my type.
- What?
I wore makeup and dyed my hair to look more mature,
but it didn't work.
- Isn't dying your hair against school rules?
- Are you a model student?
- You're so straight-laced, Kosuke.
- What?
- I think it makes you so cool.
Please... use this if you want to.
- What is it?
- A bag for your shoes.
I worked hard making it, but don't use it if you don't want to.
Well, good luck with your game.
Matsuuchi, wait.
Kosuke, the game is about to start.
Is that you, Aoki? Why brings you here?
Oh, I heard a pretty manager would be here, so I came to check.
But Ida snatched her up now.
Good for you, Ida. Good luck!
Thank you.
We're no match for them.
Is something wrong, Kosuke?
Nothing, really.
Oh, there you are.
Matsuuchi.
- Were you looking for someone?
- What?
You look down. Is something troubling you?
Well...
Listen.
Listen, do you...
like me?
I don't have any experience to compare you to.
It's weird to date someone without knowing that.
Kosuke!
Yes?
You weren't even listening, were you?
I'm sorry. What were you saying?
I said I think you're a really great guy, Kosuke.
So...
do you want to go out with me?
Why?
Because...
- I like you.
- What?
Why?
- Weren't you listening?
- But you like someone else, don't you?
- What?
- Sorry.
I actually overheard your conversation earlier.
It's a bag to carry your shoes.
Teacher, please use it, if you like.
I appreciate it, but I can't accept this.
Isn't this important to you? I'm returning it to you.
Why didn't you say so before?
Aoki was there. I didn't think you would want him to know.
You're very considerate.
You're like Mr. Taniguchi in that regard.
- The first time I came here for a match,
- Are you all right?
- an out-of-bounds ball hit me.
- I'm okay.
Mr. Taniguchi was worried and stayed with me the whole time.
I started talking to him after that,
and even told him how I felt a few times,
but he always treated me like a child.
I decided to give up if he rejects me today.
You're so much like him, that's why I asked you out.
I'm really sorry. I didn't think it through.
I must look like an idiot, liking him so much.
You're not an idiot.
It's amazing that you like someone so dearly.
- Do you think so?
- Yes.
You're great.
I see.
Oh, there you are.
Mr. Taniguchi.
Everyone from Shiroyama High is looking for you. You guys are leaving soon.
Okay.
Do you think he and I are similar?
I do.
- Let's both do our best.
- What are you talking about?
You also have someone you like, right?
Your mind was elsewhere when we were talking. It was obvious.
You can't help watching them or thinking about them, right?
Is that what it means to like someone?
That's right.
I see.
If you need my advice, talk to me anytime. See you around.
Bye.
I can see you.
Are you still upset?
I'm not upset.
I mean... I'm sorry for being a nuisance earlier.
I hope you'll be happy with Kokomi.
There is nothing going on between her and me.
Besides, Matsuuchi likes someone else.
What? For real?
Yes. You saw me giving her back the shoe bag, right?
I did, but what about you?
What?
You would be better off with a cute girl like her,
don't you think?
Try comparing her to me, as you mentioned earlier.
I understand now.
The feeling of love cannot be compared to one another.
What is that supposed to mean?
I started to understand
the feeling of liking someone.
I...
wonder if I like you, Aoki.
What?
Don't ask me.
I think it's amazing that you're so honest about your feelings.
Cut it out! Stop complimenting me all of a sudden.
Maybe it's too early to say we're dating,
but I hope that...
we will date one day.
♫ I didn't know she was setting ♫
I'm glad you told me your honest feelings.
♫ I want to know true feelings of hers and mine ♫
♫ The timeline I read repeatedly, my embarrassing hotline ♫
♫ Ah, what do I do if someone sees? ♫
I think
I would like it if, one day,
you asked me out for real.
I mean it.
Okay.
♫ I want us to fall in love. It wasn’t supposed to be this way ♫
You have a good fashion sense.
- You think?
- Yes.
Thanks.
Morning, Class President! Please take good care of our class today.
Vice President, Morning! Your hair's as cute as always.
What's wrong with Aoki?
Who cares, as long as he's happy.
A morning text from Ida?
[Mio Hashimoto]
- Aida turned me down.
- What?
Where are you now?
On the rooftop.
[Next Episode]
Aren't we dating?
You're the mean one here.
[The ups and downs of another first love!]
Don't cry, Hashimoto.
- Good morning.
- Sorry, I'm in a hurry.
You sure do like a lot of people.
[Can love be compatible with friendship?
I'm just a terrible meddling jerk!
I'll help whenever you're in trouble.