[Previously on My Love Mix-Up!]
I'm curious to know. When high schoolers date, they want to hold hands and kiss.
- Wow!
- I won't do it again.
There's no way I would think of you as gross.
We are dating! What's wrong with that?
I didn't pick a random guy to date.
I like Ida.
The time has come once again,
for Higashigaoka's biggest event.
[Ten Days until the Illumination Festival]
Is the Illumination Festival spectacular?
- Are you a 10th grader?
- Yes, Sir.
The courtyard will be filled with lights. Look forward to it.
- Wow, that sounds exciting.
- Yes, seriously.
At last, the Illumination Festival is coming up soon.
Our class, Grade-11th Class-3,
would like to hold a Christmas party.
- Yes!
- That sounds great.
Drinks will be paid via admission fee, so please bring food for a potluck.
- Okay.
- All right.
By the way, it was me who suggested the party.
Hashimoto, are making sweets for Akkun?
- What?
- After all, the Illumination Festival is a chance for confession.
Is it?
- You didn't know?
Legend says if you give your crush a cake during the Illumination Festival,
your love will be fulfilled.
Ida, you seriously have no interest in these things, do you?
Anyhow, why not confess again during the festival?
You two seem to be getting along well lately.
He might accept your love this time.
I know, but I just got rejected not too long ago.
What are you guys talking about?
Oh, we're just excited for the Christmas party.
Are you making sweets?
Y-Yes, with the home economics club.
I'm planning on handing out sweets at the party.
Hashimoto, this is your chance. Seize the opportunity.
I'm debating what to make.
Oh? Only the cupcakes have an X mark on them.
Oh, I already made them to hand out
on last Valentine's Day.
They look delicious.
I'll make these again.
Oh, nice!
I'm glad you came to a decision.
Yes.
I'll do my best.
Let me borrow that.
It's decided.
It looks like they'll do fine.
The homemade cake she gave me on Valentine's Day was really delicious.
Did she give you one?
D-Don't get the wrong idea. She didn't like me.
They were leftovers that were supposed to be for Akkun.
Rather, are you "jelly"?
What's "jelly"?
(T/N: Yaku means "jealous" and "to bake".)
[Kitchen]
That's crazy.
So is he making a request?
Not at all!
He just suggested making cupcakes.
That means he wants them.
He even marked the page.
Aoki, did Aida say anything afterward?
Not really. We just talked about games.
That's it? Whatever.
Was I called here to be asked about the silly questions?
- Aoki.
- Let's have a little chat.
Am I... popular now?
At least, that's what I thought.
I hope he likes it.
- I'm starting to feel nervous for her.
- Why you?
Aoki!
Good luck, Hashimoto. It'll be a success this time for sure.
Thank you.
How are things
- with you and Ida?
- What?
How are things?
We've... held hands.
You have?
I'm at a loss over what to do next.
I see.
After all, the next step is...
that, right?
It's definitely weird if we did that.
Not at all.
But... I wonder how Ida feels.
If that's what you want,
then I'm sure Ida feels the same.
Not that I'm the expert.
- Sorry for not being very helpful.
- No, no.
You're the only person I can talk to about this.
It seriously helps me out. Thanks.
What's most important is...
Ida's feelings.
[My Love Mix-Up!]
[Episode 9]
Do you want some?
What? N-No, not really.
It has... become quite cold lately.
True. From now on, should we eat in the classroom?
- I strongly oppose to it.
- Why?
Because it would be bad if weird rumors spread around.
You're too cautious.
And you're not cautious enough.
Do you think so?
Let's just eat on the rooftop.
It's fun since we can talk leisurely.
At least, that's how I feel.
Same here.
So Ida also has fun being with me.
When I think about it, it's rather surprising
that Ida and I are dating, and being together like this.
Because I feel unsatisfied with everything!
I may sound like a fool, but
I sincerely fell in love.
I'll give a serious thought about it. So please, wait a bit.
Don't sell yourself short, by saying, "someone like me."
I've... come to actually like you!
I'm well aware that you're serious.
Should we... try dating?
- Hup.
- You're close! What's up?
It's cold.
Oh, right.
Don't use me as a heater!
Not that I mind.
Wait a second. Are you sure about this, Ida?
Are you giving the okay?
Fine time for a picnic!
- I wonder if my lunch will be all right?
- Let's go.
Close one...
That was a close call.
What was?
It'd be bad if people found out we were dating.
Ida, you don't pay attention to the surroundings at all.
Stay sharp, and make sure no one catches on.
Next Sunday, I don't have practice.
Should we go somewhere together?
- What?
- Outside of school, you won't be so worried about others, right?
What? Is that a date?
Are Ida and I going on a date?
No way, does Ida also want to make progress with me?
Is that a no?
Well, that might be nice.
Then it's decided.
We're riding a ropeway.
Don't zoom in so close.
- Whoa, amazing!
- They're right below us.
- You can see the Ferris wheel too.
- Whoa, cool! I got a good picture.
I'll take one for you.
You're wearing a similar jacket as mine.
- Look over here.
- Okay.
- Yay!
- Say, cheese.
Good picture!
♫ Two umbrellas form the shape of a heart
when walking side-by-side ♫
♫ I can't believe it. Miracle was waiting for me ♫
- Crap.
- What is it?
- It's ending soon.
- It sure is.
- Was that fun?
- Yes, I also had plans.
Don't do that. I said, no.
Shoot, the movie starts in 30 minutes.
Movie?
I made a reservation. Look at this.
Looks just like Mametaro.
[Pochi's Story]
Since when did Mametaro become a movie star?
It got good reviews.
Whenever I saw the trailer, it reminds me of your Mametaro.
D-Don't misunderstand.
- It's not like I was always thinking of you.
- I get it.
Thanks.
I don't think you do understand.
Forget it.
Let's go.
Did he put a lot of thought into this?
Aoki's amazing.
What's wrong?
What are you staring at?
It's nothing.
By the way, is the movie a tear-jerker?
- What?
- It looks like the dog goes to heaven in the end.
No, I don't think so.
In conclusion,
Pochi went to heaven.
It was a good movie.
I'm sorry. All because I didn't search up the ending.
It's fine.
I'll give Mametaro lots of love when I go home.
You should do so.
- Aoki, you're such a good guy.
- Excuse me?
You only met Mametaro once, yet you're so worried about him.
Anyone would worry after watching that!
Do you want to stop by my place?
What?
Seeing a lively Mametaro may lift your spirits too.
Ida... thank you.
Don't cry.
I can't help it.
[Ida]
Mametaro!
I'm so glad you're in good health!
I feel so relieved.
Make yourself at home.
My family won't be back for a while.
What?
Is no one home?
Is that okay for me to be here?
Sure. No need to be considerate.
B-But...
Do you feel uncomfortable being alone with me?
Like I said, don't ask me stuff like that.
I have no idea how to react.
Wait a second.
This is a huge opportunity.
Or maybe,
Ida was also after that, and invited me over?
Want to play some games?
Yes.
Let's do that.
Aoki is easy to read.
Sometimes watching him makes me feel shy.
Is this what happens,
when you like someone?
I lost again.
I was confident that I could play the game well.
Are you laughing? You seem awfully pleased.
Sorry, I couldn't help it.
Hey, trade controllers with me, and let's rematch.
- I do better with the red one.
- They're the same.
They're totally different! Come on, hand it over.
- Are you a child?
- Just hand it over—
Oh my, I'm sorry.
It's fine, it's only tea. I'll just change.
W-Wait!
You spooked me.
- What's the matter?
- It's not, "what's the matter,"
put your abs away! Don't strip in front of me.
Don't we change for P.E.?
Fine.
Hurry.
Are you done?
Not yet.
Are you not done yet?
Nope.
You're so slow.
You are done!
Don't make fun of me.
Is it fun
to laugh at my reactions?
- That wasn't my intention.
- That's exactly it.
You didn't go easy on me when we played games.
You're totally calm, even when we're close and alone.
This is serious for me!
You're not serious about going out with me, are you?
That's why you tease me.
- My bad.
- At least deny it.
- I'm sorry.
- Get out.
I got it.
Wait, this is your house! I'm leaving!
- Wait up, Aoki!
- I want to be alone.
Thanks for having me.
Aoki is right.
If I was seriously in love, I wouldn't tease my partner like that.
Oh, here it comes.
Looking good.
Good, good.
I see. Your precious first date was ruined.
I wonder if we're actually dating.
He's treating you like a friend.
That's not true! Be confident, Aoki.
Treating me like a friend...
I guess you're right.
- Don't let it get to you.
- Don't listen to him.
Actually, Ida has never told me he likes me.
Has he not?
He doesn't even know if he likes me,
but he can't leave me alone, so we're dating.
Was Ida always such an irresponsible person?
That's not irresponsible. There are things you don't know till you date.
As I thought,
I knew Hashimoto would be dissatisfied with that.
Are you saying I'm uptight?
She's snapping at me.
I'll be heading home first.
Aoki, let's make a cake together.
What?
Try handing it to Ida, and confirm his feelings.
- Water is over here.
- Oh, that?
- I'll pour it in.
- Thanks.
Okay.
After all, I like Ida.
Please go out with me again.
Thanks, Aoki. I like you, too.
Has he lost his mind?
I bet he's having a blast making cake.
I'm going to cheer him up.
- He seems depressed.
- What should we do?
Kosuke.
If you're worried about something, I'll listen.
Come with me.
Where are they going?
Are you worried about Aoki?
What?
I kinda noticed you two were in a romantic relationship.
- Did you?
- Yes.
Kosuke, did you convey your feelings to Aoki?
Did you date him without knowing if you liked him?
Kosuke, I hope this isn't one of your "I can't neglect people" disease.
- "I can't neglect people" disease?
- Yes.
You have a soft spot for people in need.
It was the same reason when you picked up Mametaro and your previous dog.
[Adopt me]
- Please, we're short on members!
- Join the team!
- I've never played volleyball.
- No worries, we're all beginners.
- It was the same when you joined the volleyball club.
- Please, Ida!
All right, I'll join.
I did it of my own will. Besides, Mametaro and volleyball are both important parts of my life now.
You see, those are totally different from a relationship.
Since he likes you, it's disrespectful to date Aoki out of pity.
Pity...
It's not pity.
I have fun being with Aoki.
Is that the same as Aoki's feelings of affection?
Isn't your "fun," the same as hanging out with me and the volleyball team?
You should properly figure out your feelings.
If you date him half-heartedly,
it would only bring pain for the both of you.
- Chocolate.
- And this is store bought.
- Store bought?
- It's delicious, I promise.
- Try it.
- You sure?
- Oh, it's good.
- Good chocolate, right?
It's delicious as it is.
- It's good, isn't it?
- It's a good flavor.
Ida?
Ida...
What brings you here?
That's my question. What are you doing here?
Making a cake for the Christmas party.
They asked me to help.
I'm finally becoming popular.
Are you now?
Good... for you.
Aoki.
Well... good luck.
Sure. I'm having lots of fun here.
I'm totally motivated.
So which flavor would it be?
- Chocolate, right?
- No, blueberry.
I'd have to choose chocolate.
♫ I'm happy and want to cry ♫
♫ The flowers that bloomed are still small, Strawberry ♫
♫ I just wanted to love you ♫
Ida, do you have a minute?
You know, we went to Yokohama on Sunday and saw you holding hands
with Aoki. Ida, are you...
dating Aoki?
[This is a work of fiction]
[Next Episode]
There's something I need to tell you, Aoki.
[Their loving hearts wavered, by decisions made]
I've decided not to interact with Ida anymore.
Is that really how you want it to end it?
[A Christmas of feelings, that miss one another]
I'm sorry
[A first love, which began from a misunderstanding, heads... ]
for taking too long.
Who cares? We don't need to be with them.