[Previously on My Love Mix-Up!]
I hope you're perplexed as much as I have.
Does that mean you've been thinking of me the whole time as well?
Aoki liking you was just a misunderstanding.
- That's not true, I...
- Look, it's fine.
I'm relieved about this, too.
Now that I can't take back my words, I've finally realized.
My feelings for you... were real.
I'm so glad that the misunderstanding was resolved.
He's a real bonehead, but please continue to be friends with him.
You're really touchy-feely.
That's right.
Aoki?
Oh, my bad. Sorry for causing you trouble.
What's the matter?
Well, you were spacing out for some reason.
I wasn't. I just feel at ease.
It freaked me out when you took me seriously.
You're the cause of the trouble. Show your remorse.
- Wait, ouch!
- Let's go!
- Don't hurt him.
- Stop it. I'm going to die.
- Cut it out.
- Do you bear a grudge against me?
And that was how my fleeting love came to an end.
The end.
No, you can't end it like that.
It was my own fault,
because I wasn't honest with my feelings,
and I lied to him.
I'm a piece of trash.
I just want to disappear.
Don't say that.
You kept your promise to me by not telling anyone about the eraser.
That's right.
It'll be our little secret, okay?
That's why...
That's why I was punished.
I had you, yet I started to have feelings for Ida.
What? Aoki, did you like me?
- I'm sorry!
- What a quick rejection.
I'm really sorry, Aoki.
No, it's fine.
I know you like someone else.
It doesn't surprise or hurt me.
That must be the proof of you seriously liking Ida.
Well, I guess you can say that.
But it's over now.
I don't want to bother Ida anymore. The misunderstanding was cleared up.
It wasn't cleared up.
I mean, your feelings for him were real, right?
You shouldn't lie to yourself.
Thanks.
But Ida was relieved to learn that it was a misunderstanding.
You don't have to worry about it anymore.
I'm glad it was just a misunderstanding.
I can't tell him... how I really feel about him.
Aoki...
Where are you going?
- I'm going to seclude myself on a mountain.
- A mountain?
Hashimoto, be happy for both of us.
Wait, Aoki!
You can't entrust me with that, Aoki!
Sorry! Are you okay?
- Why were you in such a hurry?
- Well...
A big problem. Aoki is going to seclude himself on a mountain.
What? That's so eccentric of him.
What do we do? He's gone.
Don't worry about him. It's probably nothing serious.
It is serious.
Aoki was really depressed.
Is that because of Ida?
Yes.
Is he still sulking about that? What a pain.
He should've told him the truth right away.
But it's hard to tell the truth sometimes.
Is it?
Considering the mood, or how the other person reacts,
there are lots of things you have to consider.
I suppose... there are things that are hard to say,
but being so worried about the other person's reaction that you can't say it, is just an excuse.
You're afraid of getting hurt.
He shouldn't have deceived him in the first place. He deserves the punishment.
He should reflect on his action.
By the way, don't you think you're being too soft on him?
What? What was that for?
Not everyone is as strong as you are.
There are things people can't say. And...
I used to respect that about you, but now... I hate it!
Why is she so upset about me?
[My Love Mix-Up!]
[Episode 4]
Mama, what's that guy doing?
You shouldn't point a finger.
I had a feeling this was your mountain retreat.
Akkun?
Hey, Mr. Hermit.
Why are you here?
Hashimoto slapped me because of you, so I came to complain.
Did she slap you?
She smacked me when I dissed you for waffling the Ida thing.
That's when the Great Detective Akkun had a bright idea.
What do you mean, the Great Detective Akkun?
According to my amazing assumption, her criminal motive was...
Hashimoto likes you, so she snapped when I criticized you.
Don't ever say that to Hashimoto. You're way off the mark.
- But according to my assumption—
- Whatever, that's enough.
Your assumption is wrong, anyway.
I don't care about liking someone, and whatnot.
- I've made up my mind.
- Aoki?
I should get rid of my feelings for Ida.
I'm returning your midterm test.
[Grade-11 Class-3]
If I do that, I won't get hurt anymore.
Aoki?
I'm sick and tired of love.
Good job.
Is this for real?
Ida! Ida! Look at this!
It's all thanks to the study group.
What are you laughing at?
Because you seem so happy.
Great job. You did well.
No! Why am I mesmerized by him?
Why did I even start the conversation? I'm an idiot!
Ida is treating me as a friend.
I decided to let go of my feelings for him, didn't I?
I want to forget, but...
it's hard when he's right in front of me.
Here's the new seating chart. I picked it randomly as always, so take a look.
What? Sir, my seat didn't change at all.
What are the odds? You're rather lucky.
- Hiro.
- Don't go, Rumi.
- Stop playing and just sit down.
- I don't want to be apart from you, Hiro.
Aoki?
Come on, get moving. Your seat is over there.
Oh, okay.
Now we're totally separated.
I guess my wish came true.
Now I can go back to my uneventful life.
Aoki, we're neighbors again.
Aoki?
What's that for?
Don't you think you're staring too much at Ida?
What? I wasn't looking at him! Stop being weird.
Hey.
Tell me why you slapped me.
I'm not going to apologize.
I don't need your apology. Just tell me the reason.
Does he...
like Ida for real?
Seriously?
I can't believe it.
Don't be rude. It's the truth.
- My method of studying?
- Yes.
You only scored six points on the practice test,
but it jumped up to ninety-two on the midterm.
So I was wondering how did you do it.
Are you... suspecting me?
- Of what?
- Well...
- I know other classes had a cheating incidence.
- No, no.
That's not it. I simply want to know your miraculous study tips to go from 6 to 92.
I didn't cheat.
I know that, just calm down.
But you think I did, don't you?
- Now you're acting a little suspicious.
- I did not cheat.
Aoki didn't cheat.
We studied together.
Besides, Aoki isn't someone who would do that.
Ida, why...?
I'm here to give the club journal to Mr. Taniguchi.
I see.
That makes sense. So Ida tutored you.
Well, yes.
Ida, thank you. I know teaching students is my job.
No, it's fine.
But it'd be a huge help if you two kept studying together.
Thank you.
I'm glad you didn't get in trouble.
Yes, but it wasn't Mr. Tachiguchi's fault. I just misunderstood him.
You're always getting into trouble.
Don't say that so seriously!
You knocked over the bucket at the culture festival.
Next thing I know, you're playing the role of Cinderella.
If you find me annoying, just leave me be.
Even if you say so...
Don't look at my face and sigh.
Well, I'm going to my volleyball practice now.
Wait, Ida.
You see... thanks about earlier.
You're very welcome.
Ida...
It's too late now.
I have no choice but to give up,
for Ida's sake.
♫ Two perplexed silhouettes ♫
♫ Feel uneasy in the sunlight filtering through trees ♫
♫ When I think only the two of us are in the world, ♫
♫ Why does it make me feel uneasy? ♫
Before I knew it, I liked the person. I have no real reasons.
Look, I'm not asking for an apology. I'm fine, really.
Since you stood up for me.
I thought I was the only one spinning my wheels about this.
I hope you'll be perplexed as much as I have.
Ida! Ida! Look at this!
This is all thanks to the study group.
Here I go!
What's wrong, Kosuke?
Sorry.
Are you still pretending to be a detective?
Let's go home, Akkun.
- I solved the mystery.
- Yes, whatever.
Aoki, you really do like Ida, don't you?
He finally got something right.
That reaction tells me I'm correct.
About what?
I don't know what you mean.
I almost got slapped by Hashimoto again.
It's true, all right. How rude of you!
Wait! I didn't mean it like that.
But if that's true,
I've said a bunch of terrible things to Aoki.
I'm a failure as his friend.
Aida.
That must be why he never tells me anything.
That's not it.
I bet he didn't tell you because you're an important friend to him.
Indeed! In other words,
the culprit that made you unable to tell your truth
is me.
Aoki, I'm sorry.
A great detective doesn't turn himself in.
Come on! I'm seriously apologizing here.
This is the first time I've seen you look so down.
It's fine! I think your reaction was normal.
Normal?
Commonly, people would think it's weird, right?
That I feel that way about Ida.
Then... the normality is wrong.
Get angry. You can hit me.
But on this side, because I got slapped on the other side.
I'm not going to hit you. I'm not mad.
I'm happy.
I never knew that you felt that way.
It doesn't matter who you like.
You'll always be Aoki, right?
I'm starving! Let's get something from the convenience store on the way home.
Sure.
- There you go.
- What? I don't want it.
I assumed of my own accord,
that he'd hate me if he ever finds out.
I should've known he's not that kind of guy.
It's too embarrassing to tell him in person,
but I'm really glad I'm friends with Akkun.
By the way... what happened with Hashimoto after that?
We totally reconciled.
Sorry!
I'm sorry for slapping you.
You didn't do anything wrong.
No, I was wrong. I totally deserved the slap.
Aida...
Hashimoto...
Yes?
I...
am going to apologize to Aoki.
Thanks for slapping me. It made me see the light. See you!
That's how it happened.
You probably gave everyone around you the wrong impression.
You know, Hashimoto is unexpectedly cool.
She had the strength of a gorilla when she slapped me.
I wonder what she eats to get that strong.
Akkun,
never say that to her.
It's a compliment.
No, it's definitely not.
Kosuke?
Did something happen?
Well...
What is it? Tell us.
Someone confessed to me recently.
What?! Confessed?
- I was seriously considering how to respond, but...
- Yes?
I guess it was my misunderstanding.
Now that I think about it, I don't think they ever told me they liked me.
That's terrifying!
How could you misunderstand something like that?
Can't you tell if someone likes you by how they act?
I couldn't tell at all.
But you liked the person, right, Kosuke?
That's how falling in love with someone.
You've known this guy your whole life, Toyoda. Knock some sense into him.
Kosuke has always been thickheaded to romance.
I may be thickheaded, but...
What does it mean to like someone?
I don't quite understand it even at my age, so I wanted to find out.
I never thought the day would finally come for Kosuke to brood over love.
Look at how much you've grown.
Just forget about it.
A lost love is like a tossed volleyball... you should strike it down.
- Captain.
- Ida!
You can always come to me for advice.
All right, let's go clean up.
He's always so full of confidence despite having zero dating experience.
That's because he reads so many "light novels".
(T/N: Short novels)
Anyway, now that you're sure of your feelings,
- let's go tell Ida you really like him.
- What?
If things remain unsettled, you'll keep being gloomy.
Forget it. I've already decided to give up.
He said he was glad it was a misunderstanding, anyway.
Come on, lighten up.
I feel so guilty when I see you so depressed.
Besides, you've got the world's most encouraging ally with you.
It'll definitely go well this time.
I don't want you meddling with it anymore.
I've just thought of a great idea.
The perfect chance is coming up for you to confess your love to him.
What perfect chance?
The school's camping trip.
Camping trip?
Camping trip is a magical trip where love will bloom.
The refreshing great outdoors will soften his heart and your feelings will flow into him.
Anyone would instinctively answer, "Yes!"
Really?
With the help of the air's negative ions and the God of the Mountains,
you'll start dating Ida for sure.
I told you, it's impossible.
Are you really okay with giving up?
If you act quickly, you might be able to start over with him.
Try telling him how you really feel.
Whatever his answer may be,
I'm sure Ida will give serious thought to it
before he gives you the answer.
♫ Two umbrellas form the shape of a heart
when walking side-by-side ♫
♫ I can't believe it. A miracle was waiting for me ♫
You're right. He is that type of person.
♫ I want us to fall in love. It wasn’t supposed to be this way ♫
♫ It disheartens me but it also excites my innocent heart ♫
♫ Just like a magnet, we stick together and then
we separate, oh my god, oh my god ♫
♫ Love isn’t easy ♫
♫ I’m smitten with you. You’re my sunshine ♫
Dear god of the Mountains,
please lend me your strength.
♫ Let us be Romeo and Juliette that never give up ♫
[This drama is a work of fiction]
[Next Episode]
Our precious outdoors experience, will only be flooded with these memories.
Ida!
I'm going to confess my love to Ida.
[He finally made up his mind to confess!?]
- Li... Li...
- Li?
I'm well aware that you're serious.