Kaneko-san said he was quitting!
Keep it down.
Ouch, that hurts.
Kai.
I'm sorry.
I am
not the same as before.
I'm not cool anymore.
You must be disillusioned, right?
I didn't want to
be seen like this by you.
The current me
can't help you at all.
You asked me
to make dinner, didn't you?
But
Kai has been the same
as always afterward,
unchanged.
To be honest, I'm kind of grateful.
I still haven't been able to
answer or respond to his feelings.
I need to think about it.
Hirokuni.
When did you come back?
Oh, around 3 a.m.
So, you're going to work today too?
Are you a masochist?
Shut up.
Hey,
don't worry about my meals for a while.
I'll return around this time every day,
and I don't know if
I'll be able to come home,
it would be a waste if I couldn't eat.
No.
Come home soon.
Kai,
you see...
How gullible.
Give up, give up,
give up.
- It'll fall.
- He's always like this
and always taking care of me.
I really shouldn't be
depending on him anymore.
Give up, give up, give up, give up.
Give up.
"Perfect Propose"
"Episode 5"
Watari.
Yes?
The one you did yesterday isn't working.
Ah, I'm sorry,
I'll check it.
Get it together,
you're the team leader.
Yes.
Sakamoto-kun,
there's an error in the file
you shared with me.
Sorry, I'll fix it right away.
If there's anything you don't get,
feel free to ask anytime.
Yes.
Why am I the leader?
My juniors work much faster and are
more talented than me.
You're excellent, you always have been.
Get it together,
you're the team leader.
I don't get it.
(Dinner)
Looks delicious.
Bon appétit.
Oh, good morning.
You didn't go home?
I'm constantly causing trouble.
No, it's not like that.
It's okay,
I just took a nap earlier.
Umm...
Please don't overwork yourself.
Yes.
Hey, cut it out.
Ah, sorry,
my PC is lagging.
Are you shutting it down properly?
Sometimes.
Well, we can't even put it
to sleep though.
(Dinner)
Again?
Looks delicious.
(Food)
It's always my favorite
dishes every day.
What kind of harassment is this?
I want to go home.
I forgot
I had such feelings.
Since when did not
being able to go home become the norm?
Umm...
I brought some snacks.
Wow.
- Is it alright?
- Feel free to take some.
Thank you so much.
Wow, amazing.
There's so much.
- What is in here?
- What would you like?
I'll go for the chocolates.
Oh, Sakamoto-kun, take some...
Watari-san.
I can't finish it.
It's impossible.
I want to quit.
Let's go home!
Everyone, leave for today,
and get some rest!
But the work...
It's alright,
don't worry about work.
I'm sorry. I really...
It's okay,
just focus on resting,
don't worry about anything else.
I'm sorry.
Is Sakamoto-kun okay?
He might not come back anymore.
Umm...
Everyone, please leave early today.
But...
If you don't get enough sleep,
mistakes will only increase.
I've made him cry.
It's because of me.
No,
it was impossible from the start,
this kind of schedule.
Even Kaneko-san said so.
But...
If Kaneko-san were the leader...
(Midnight snack)
Again. What is it this time?
Yes?
You, cut it out already!
- What are you...
- Do you feel like coming home?
Come home.
Hirokuni.
Ah, no...
Hearing this voice
after so long...
I bet you haven't had
anything decent to eat.
Well, I do want to go home.
When I visited Hirokuni's family home,
Auntie seemed worried.
She mentioned that you
always comes home late.
She said she'd appreciate it if someone
could check on him from time to time.
So,
if you collapse or something,
I'll be in trouble.
You won't get in trouble.
I don't think you would
get in trouble either,
if you quit your job.
No,
I'm not staying because
I'm afraid of getting in trouble.
Then why?
Well...
You don't have to say it,
but it's a problem if you
collapse like that old man,
so don't overdo it.
Got it.
Okay then, I'm hanging up.
Ah, wait...
Hmm?
No,
well...
I was just wondering about
the uncle's condition.
No idea.
I'll ask his son about it next time.
Oh, is that so?
Well, sorry.
It's fine.
Well then,
goodnight.
Why did I try to keep him on the line?
My head must be messed up
from exhaustion.
I just wanted to hear
his voice for a bit longer.
Hello.
It's me.
I see.
I'll be discharged this weekend.
Are you listening?
I see.
That's good,
really.
So, about the shop...
I've decided to close it.
I see.
You're going to your son's place, huh?
Sorry about that.
That's not like you.
You haven't healed yet, have you?
Yeah.
That's all. Goodbye.
See you.
Watari.
Yes?
Where's Sakamoto?
Huh?
Are you doing his work?
Yesterday Sakamoto seemed unwell,
so I asked him to go home,
and I decided to take over.
What?
Don't just do as you please
when you have your own workload.
- I'll handle that as well...
- You can't possibly handle it.
(Release date)
It's release weekend, you know?
And what's this about
Sakamoto feeling unwell?
Hey, call Sakamoto now.
Call him over.
Come on.
But...
It's because you coddle them like this
that they develop
a habit of slacking off.
A habit of slacking off...
- Sakamoto is...
- Enough. Just make the call.
And tell him.
"Do it, even if you can
only work half as much."
"Tell him it's for his own good."
Come on.
Come on, hurry up.
I refuse!
Huh?
Sakamoto has been working hard enough.
I don't want to push him any further.
I'll get it done, no matter what.
Just so you know,
'I tried my best but couldn't finish'
doesn't cut it in the real world.
Um, are you okay?
If it's not okay,
if you want to run away,
it's better to run away
before you end up like me.
Watari-san, excuse us...
It's okay.
Good job.
Please don't overwork yourself.
- Good job.
(Hirokuni)
How long have you been running?
Hmm?
Were you on the first train back?
Yeah.
Good job.
Thanks.
Being here with you like this
reminds me of when we were kids.
Yeah.
Back then,
I never imagined I'd end up like this.
Like what?
Everything like sleep,
good food,
time with friends and family,
being with someone special,
I sacrificed everything for work.
But I don't feel anything anymore.
Not getting any satisfaction from work.
How should I put it?
It's like living a futile life.
I wonder if there's a life that isn't.
Guess not.
Honestly,
I think I'm afraid.
That's why I can't quit.
I'm afraid of worrying my parents,
of not having another job lined up.
There are many things to consider.
I think in the back of my mind,
I believe that if I quit,
everything will be okay,
I'll feel better.
It's like having something to hold onto.
That's why I want to keep it.
If it's gone, I don't know
what will happen to me.
Stupid, right?
I kinda get it.
That's how it was for me with Hiro.
What?
I think that was kind of cute.
Like...
What are you...
What are you doing?
You seduced me.
I did not.
But
you didn't resist, did you?
Where do you get the confidence from?
Hirokuni-san,
have you found your answer yet?
No,
not yet.
Sorry.
I...
might not be able to wait much longer.
The old man is going to be discharged.
We agreed it would be until then, right?
That I'd stay at your place.
(Next episode)
What do you want me to do?
Don't ask me.
Next Sunday, I will move out.
Hey.
Hirokuni.
I wanted to make you wait for a while.
Being involved with
other people is serious.
It's all futile anyway.
You said it yourself,
the rest of my life,
I'll hand it over to you!