How about this one?
Check out how I look with these.
This one.
Excuse me.
Hello.
- How much is this?
- This one's 2,800.
2,800.
What about this one?
This one's 3,200.
3,200.
Right.
Which do you think looks better?
Jiang Qiao Xi, what's wrong?
Why aren't you talking?
Didn't you tell me I should express my feelings
and rely on you more?
Fine. What do you want then?
How about you pick one?
I'll get it for you. What about this pair?
I don't want sunglasses. I want something else.
What else do you want?
Alright. After buying sunglasses, we'll still
have 6-7k left. Pick whatever you want.
Let me buy Yu Qiao's sunglasses.
I actually want to give him a gift.
Why?
Last time Yu Qiao came to Hong Kong,
he said some things to me.
Factually speaking, he's spent more time
with you than I have.
Maybe he really understands you better than I do.
Why... why are you saying such weird things?
I just want to say thank you.
Cherry, you never gave up on me.
Don't talk like that anymore.
Actually, Yu Qiao considers you a friend.
He's also worried about you.
You know what? He's the one who found me
and gave me your Hong Kong address.
Without him, finding you
would've been much harder.
So I should thank him too.
You two are so similar.
Both of you want others to be happy.
Check this out.
Looks good.
Do you want me to go back to Hong Yang to study?
What do you mean?
Nothing. Just thinking out loud.
Want to buy something? We won big.
Shouldn't we spend some?
I've thought it through.
I want to buy Ruo Cheng some plants.
Having plants at home after discharge
will lift his mood.
I also want to get Ya Lin some fine wine.
Shouldn't we celebrate properly
when Ruo Cheng gets discharged?
And Rui Rui, right?
Let's buy Rui Rui some toys and new clothes.
And your uncle and aunt, I think they...
Haven't you thought
about getting something for yourself?
Ruo Cheng and Ya Lin told me
to shop more with you.
What? Buying lipstick and heels?
That works too.
I don't need lipstick. I'm pretty enough.
I don't need heels. I'm tall enough.
Let me stand here.
Listen, those things mean nothing to me.
They only matter because they're from you.
Cherry, you're so wonderful.
It makes me not want to let you go.
Your reluctance won't change anything.
I'm leaving the day after tomorrow.
I know.
So let's make the most of
our time shopping. Don't be upset.
Let's visit Ruo Cheng and Ya Lin tonight.
Okay.
Okay, I have something to discuss with them.
Ya Lin, we're here!
Come in!
Ya Lin.
Ya Lin, you look absolutely stunning today.
That's our Cherry! Thank you.
Let me through.
- Money tree!
- A money tree. Thank you.
Auntie, Uncle.
- Uncle, I got you supplements.
- Ruo Cheng.
I'll stay seated.
- Cheers!
- Soup for wine.
Cherry, thank you for the wine.
Thank you.
You really won the lottery? Over 9,000?
Yeah, never expected to actually win.
You were right, Cherry. People should have hope.
Let me say this, Qiao Xi, thank you
for your hard work these two years.
Thank you, and everyone's care
for me hasn't been easy.
Especially my wife.
No need to say all that.
It's necessary. I still have
some old debts to collect.
Though collecting them now won't be easy,
if I go personally,
they'll at least show some respect.
No big issue. So our family matters are settled.
Therefore, Qiao Xi, quit all your part-time jobs.
I've noticed you've always had a talent for math.
Don't waste your chance. Study hard.
Use this time to really think
about your future plans.
Ruo Cheng, I've actually already decided.
Good to hear.
I want... I want to return to Hong Yang.
Don't you want to study at Hong Kong University?
I've only studied here a year.
Haven't forgotten what I've learned yet.
So going back to Hong Yang,
I could still get good grades.
But you're studying finance now.
If you enter this industry in the future,
having Hong Kong education background
gives you an edge, right?
Ruo Cheng, I understand Qiao Xi's intentions.
Think about it. If he stays here,
he'll be apart from Cherry for three more years.
Alright, getting Ruo Cheng home for dinner today
took me convincing the doctor endlessly.
We need to take him back soon.
Let's not discuss
Qiao Xi's crucial studies during dinner.
- Let's eat.
- Eat.
Let's eat first.
Qiao Xi, listen to me.
Eat.
I know emotions matter sometimes,
but what's more important
than feelings is acting on them.
Don't just focus on the present.
Consider your future, right?
Now nothing I say matters. You won't listen.
No heavy talks during meals.
Fine. Let's eat.
Cherry, eat up.
Cheers.
Be happy.
Cheer up.
Eat whatever you like.
I... I can understand a little.
When I was little, I loved watching
The Return of the Condor Heroes with my parents.
I adored Little Dragon Maiden in that series.
Are you saying I look like her?
- Yes. Many say that.
- Really?
Lots of people think so.
No wonder I felt an instant connection
when I met Ya Lin.
Exactly. I'm so lucky to have married a fairy.
You're really planning
to retake the college entrance exam?
I've already made you wait two years.
I can't idle away another three.
But you're already at HKU. Why restart?
Retaking the exam will be stressful.
Cherry, remember what I told you
in Hong Yang after your exams?
I said I wanted to attend college, study
in libraries, and eat at cafeterias with you.
Even if you attend a college in Hong Yang,
we'd only have one year together.
That's okay. I'll take any chance, even a year.
Your 18th birthday gift was getting kitchenware?
Yes. I always enjoyed cooking.
But I've been too busy these past two years.
Now that Ruo Cheng's better,
I want to revive this hobby.
Don't save money for me.
I've earned plenty tutoring.
We have contest prize money too.
You could ask for nicer things.
How about this?
You said Ya Lin thinks lipstick and heels
mark a girl's maturity.
Ask Ruo Cheng what marks a boy's maturity.
I could buy you suits or leather shoes.
You'd look handsome in them.
I don't want suits or shoes.
Real maturity for boys
is owning a full kitchenware set.
Seriously?
Really. Also, you're leaving tomorrow.
I want to cook for you.
Alright, but what if you mess up this grand plan?
You haven't cooked in two years.
Underestimate me? My brain's full of recipes.
Why memorize recipes if you don't cook?
You wouldn't get it. They fuel my daydreams.
Daydream fuel?
Stare at recipes when hungry?
No.
You said you imagine alternate-reality versions
of me when apart.
Me too.
I imagine different versions of us
when you're not by my side.
In that world, we're always together.
I cook you countless meals.
Well, try harder. I grew up on Ms. Juan's cooking.
I won't eat if it's bad.
Surpassing Ms. Juan's impossible.
But I'll practice until you want my cooking.
Remember what I told you?
Pick oranges with round, pretty navels.
They're sweeter. Got it?
Noted.
Wait. Look at this.
Cherry, doesn't it feel
like we've lived this way forever?
Obviously! We grew up together.
You mooched meals at my house daily.
Couldn't shoo you away.
But grocery shopping together,
planning dinner, that's new.
It just feels familiar to me.
Like we've done this countless times.
Jiang Qiao Xi, I never realized
you're such a quiet daydreamer.
Your mind's full of whimsical ideas.
But reality's better than my imagination.
I want to make all those daydreams real.
Get this.
Okay.
Cherry, I... I won't make you wait long.
Even if I stay at HKU,
I'll return to Hong Yang quickly to find you.
Promise me, come running back soon.
You really want to buy it?
Just buy it.
You think I don't know?
It's fine. I understand.
Are... are you serious?
I saw them.
Cigarettes on your windowsill. You smoke, right?
It's okay. My dad smoked too.
He quit for my mom using gum.
I don't smoke much. I can quit soon.
This should be good, or...?
Excuse me, Sir and Miss. Ready to check out?
Coming.
♫ Spreading sunlight ♫
♫ Warmly kissing her ♫
♫ Open your eyes, little prince ♫
♫ Riding a white horse ♫
♫ Looking up at the sky ♫
♫ The distant clouds stay silent ♫
♫ Quietly spinning ♫
♫ Waiting for his reply ♫
♫ A ray of moonlight ♫
♫ Gently ♫
♫ Brushes against the cheek ♫
♫ She timidly ♫
♫ Hides into the clouds ♫
♫ The serene blue sky ♫
♫ Muttering ♫
♫ Lying in the grass ♫
♫ Unintentionally ♫
♫ The dragonfly ♫
♫ Lands on my nose tip ♫
♫ Aye aye oh ♫
♫ Aye oh ♫
♫ Sunflower tiptoes ♫
♫ Shaking head and saying goodbye ♫
♫ Aye aye oh ♫
♫ Aye oh ♫
♫ A little straw hat ♫
♫ Hitting the road with me ♫
Are you two being this innocent
even when you're dating each other?
Do you want to grab dinner together later?
Sure.
Yin.
You brat! I've been good to you for nothing?
You won't even cook a meal for me?
Yin, tell me how he's been these past two years.
You really want to know?
I'm scared you'll cry.
He had it rough. No, better not.
I don't believe you can make me cry.
I've got a high threshold for tears. Go ahead.
Wait, don't fall for her act. She cries easily.
So are we telling it or not?
We're telling it.
Let me tell you how clueless
he was when he first arrived.
He thought everything here was super complicated.
Tried to act tough by putting on this macho front.
The scar on his head was so tiny
you needed a magnifying glass to see it.
Every day he'd flip his hair to show that scar,
thinking it made him look intimidating.
Why are you spilling everything?
He looked absolutely ridiculous doing that.
When I first saw you, I couldn't stand you.
Barely scraping together rent money
but acting all high and mighty.
If my dad hadn't taken a liking to you,
I'd have kicked you out on the spot.
See how kind Yin is?
Even when you were putting on airs back then.
He still took you in and treated you well.
I wasn't putting on airs!
Don't listen to his nonsense.
Cherry, I'm the landlord here.
Shouldn't a landlord evict tenants
who can't pay rent?
I helped him not because of that.
Then why?
Don't they say men can't bear to see women cry?
Actually, men can't stand
seeing other men cry even more.
One night he was watching Titanic and cried.
Right, Titanic's a real tearjerker.
But most people cry
when Rose sees Jack sinking. Not him.
He cried when Rose and Jack
promised each other a beautiful life together.
That's the most hopeful part,
yet he sobbed like a mess.
That's when I realized
this kid was actually pitiful.
So I figured I'd look after him in my free time.
Yin, I'll toast you. Thank you
for taking care of Jiang Qiao Xi these years.
No need.
Don't spit it out!
My reserve whiskey isn't cheap.
Well? How is it?
So hot!
Stop drinking.
- Burning up.
- It's too hot, right?
Bottoms up.
I'll add some ice.
Yin, I've tried lots of fine drinks in Hong Kong.
Had wine with Jiang Qiao Xi's sister-in-law,
and now your whiskey.
All top-shelf stuff, really expensive.
But honestly, I just can't acquire
the taste. Don't like it.
Why do you all love alcohol so much?
Nobody's born liking alcohol.
I drink out of necessity.
Not everyone's like Vincent,
having a sweet girl like you to care for him.
I have nobody. That's why I drink.
Who believes that?
Jiang Qiao Xi says you're a player.
That's just acting for
the occasion. Doesn't count.
I treat them badly, they treat me
badly too. Fair's fair.
Eat.
Don't... don't be sad.
You'll definitely meet someone...
Stop pitying him.
You actually believe his stories?
He owns this building and land in Lok Ma Chau.
He stays up all night counting property deeds.
You don't get it. Pretty clouds scatter easily,
tall buildings collapse quickly.
The things you can see are the least valuable.
They can disappear in an instant.
You've had a tough journey. Cherish each other.
You're the lucky ones.
Jiang Qiao Xi.
Cherry.
What's wrong, Cherry? Are you a repeater?
I just realized tomorrow
I won't hear you answering me like this.
I want to keep saying your name while I can.
Cherry, do you know
what I was thinking when I heard you call my name?
You were thinking,
"How can Lin Cherry's voice be so sweet?"
No taste.
Cherry, all these years,
I've been trying to prove that I'm Jiang Qiao Xi.
Before, I had good grades.
Used silence to abandon math,
relinquish guaranteed admissions.
Even... even used that method
to prove I'm Jiang Qiao Xi.
But now I suddenly realize
the moment I heard you call my name,
I truly existed.
Hello.
Qin Ye Yun.
I'm in Hong Kong.
I know.
I found Jiang Qiao Xi.
I know that. Lin Cherry, it's 3 AM right now.
I...
I get it. Are you feeling happy or not right now?
I don't know if I'm happy or not.
Just feel...
different from before,
but somehow everything remains the same.
Then wasn't this call a waste?
No.
It's like
I suddenly discovered a secret.
That kind adults seemed to share
when I saw them on the street before.
They always seemed to have some shared secret.
But now I know that secret too.
It's frustrating, Lin Cherry.
How did you know this secret before me?
I told you immediately.
You should be secretly thrilled.
What should I do, Lin Cherry?
Now you're making me a little scared.
There's something you're afraid of?
I'm a girl too, you know. I get scared too.
Don't be afraid. Just make sure
to find someone you love.
Being with someone you love
makes the fear go away.
Cherry, are you sure you don't want me
to take you to the airport?
I don't want you to send me off, because I don't
want you to return alone from the airport.
I want you to pick me up at the airport,
so it'll feel like you are meeting me there.
Not seeing the airport as the place
where you said goodbye to me.
Stop it, you're making me want to cry too.
Should we find a place
to cry our eyes out together?
Jiang Qiao Xi, you promised to come back for me.
You promised. I'll really wait for you.
You made that promise to me. You promised.
We agreed. I will definitely come find you.
Promise me.
I promise.
♫ The unspoken wishes of that year ♫
♫ Familiar shadows lengthen ♫
♫ Beyond sight ♫
♫ Your silhouette is so gentle ♫
♫ The world is spinning ♫
♫ The breeze is shouting ♫
♫ The scenery in amber ♫
Jiang Qiao Xi, I really like you. You know that.
♫ You're the key to who I am ♫
I know. I really like you too.
Beyond that, my dream is
to become an excellent teacher.
Whether it's kindergarten, elementary,
or middle school teacher, all good.
I want to use my abilities
to help students gain more knowledge,
help them understand and accept themselves,
and discover their future paths.
What about you? What do you want to do?
The old me wanted to abandon math
and leave my parents.
But after what happened with Ruo Cheng's family,
I want to work in finance.
I know finance can elevate someone,
but also easily destroy them.
But with you by my side, I'm not afraid.
I will become someone who lifts others up.
Then go do it. Do what you want to do.
I want you to become yourself,
and I'll become myself.
Though we might not be together
on our separate journeys,
as long as we know we love each other,
distance doesn't matter.
Nothing will change, right?
I've already waited two years
without hearing from you.
Things can't possibly get worse from here.
Our future will keep getting better.
So stay in Hong Kong and pursue your dreams.
That's the situation. Jiang Qiao Xi said
he'll come find me immediately.
You two are so good together.
So at the end of the story, do the prince
and princess live happily ever after?
The princess is still in Hong Kong,
but her rescuing prince
is returning to Hong Yang to study.
No one can predict the future.
It's okay. Didn't the princess say
he'll always come find her from now on?
Besides, any princess who shares birthday wishes
can't be a bad princess.
Good princess stories always have happy endings.
Yu Qiao, I'm back from Hong Kong
and brought you Ray-Ban sunglasses.
Originally, I wanted to buy them for you,
but Jiang Qiao Xi insisted on paying.
He said it's to thank you.
Yu Qiao, I also want to thank you.
Are you still busy? Should I deliver them to you?
Thanks, Cherry. I'm still preparing
for the aviation academy exam.
Have a Canada interview coming up. No time now.
Tell Jiang Qiao Xi one pair isn't enough.
When he comes to Hong Yang, have him
personally bring the glasses and bow in thanks.
Okay, I'll tell him.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
You two have been busy all day. Take a break.
Let me see how I can help. What can I do for you?
No need, Ms. Cao.
I won't feel confident shipping these clothes
without personally checking every stitch.
Besides, my dad finally found
something he enjoys doing.
If you ask him to stop,
he won't be happy about it.
Shuang Yan.
This thing lets people chat with customers
from all over the country. It's pretty fun!
Cherry?
Yun, Cherry sent you a QQ message.
Cherry found Qiao Xi?
Yeah, Jiang Qiao Xi hid all the way in Hong Kong,
but she still tracked him down.
So Cherry and Qiao Xi, are they...?
Ms. Cao, they're exactly what you're thinking.
They just look well-behaved.
What about you?
Dad, my mind isn't on that.
Yu Qiao...
Dad, what are you talking about?
Buying a car is my top priority now.
Buy a car? What's that about?
Yes, buying a car.
Why are you thinking about that?
Cars are so expensive now.
You don't even have a driver's license.
I'll get the license. No matter how expensive
cars are, I'll work hard to buy one.
I just want to buy my dream car.
When I drive this car out, everyone will know
I'm somebody important.
I want to take the wheel of my own life.
Listen to my favorite songs,
drive long distances, and see beautiful views.
You'll ride shotgun with me, or Cherry,
Cai Fang Yuan, Du Shang, even Yu Qiao.
And of course, Ms. Cao should come too!
I want to take all the people I love
to every corner of the world.
- I'm here! How long were you waiting?
-  Just a while.
I got stopped by some juniors
in the hallway asking questions.
Did you miss me a lot today?
Of course I did.
I missed you too.
Jiang Qiao Xi.
What is it, Cherry?
I just really missed you.
When I get back, I'll take you
to the amusement park.
Jiang Qiao Xi, I just showered.
The shower room was so crowded today.
Go! Who let you in?
What are you doing?
-  Who's this?
-  What?
Hello.
-  What stage are you two at now?
-  Jiang Qiao Xi.
Let's all enjoy
the beautiful dance moves together.
♫ Always extinguishing hope ♫
♫ But dear friend ♫
♫ You are all I need ♫
♫ You are my matchstick ♫
♫ You're always humming a song softly ♫
♫ Facing the sunset ♫
♫ Memories drift in my pupils ♫
♫ Through the window of time ♫
♫ Summer cherries are a bit cool ♫
♫ I gaze from afar ♫
♫ The unspoken wishes of that year ♫
♫ Familiar shadows lengthen ♫
♫ Beyond sight ♫
♫ Your silhouette is so gentle ♫
♫ The world is spinning ♫
♫ The breeze is shouting ♫
♫ The scenery in amber ♫
♫ Clear as yesterday ♫
♫ Reality is in front of me ♫
♫ The future folds in the palm ♫
♫ You're the key to who I am ♫
♫ Accompany me to become myself ♫
♫ The night is long ♫
♫ My stubbornness grows wildly ♫
♫ I can't stop running ♫
♫ The silent call of the dream ♫
♫ You're the sparkling of my dreams ♫
♫ Accompany you to become yourself ♫
♫ Boundaries dissipate ♫
♫ Loneliness melts in an embrace ♫
♫ I've always been here ♫
♫ Rotating light in my palm ♫
♫ Illuminating your cheeks ♫
♫ A smile that ran too fast ♫
♫ Unexpectedly preserved ♫