OUR GENERATION
EPISODE 6
QIN FAMILY MART, GENERAL GOODS
Lin Yingtao, are you out of your mind?
You went that far for Jiang Qiaoxi?
I already told you, it wasn't for him.
It was for the kitten.
It was all white,
all cute, right?
Stop making excuses.
Even if you care about animals,
you can't deny
that kitten meant
something different
because of Jiang Qiaoxi.
I… I didn't come here
for a lecture.
Just help me find a clean shirt.
If my mom sees me like this,
she'll be worried again.
Grab the one we bought together,
the matching set.
Right now,
what you really need
is to get a straight answer
from Jiang Qiaoxi.
Does he still want to be
friends with you, like the old days?
If he keeps acting hot and cold,
then tell him to back off.
You stay away from him too.
I have been staying away.
I've kept my distance for long enough.
Why are you yelling at me?
If you've got the guts,
go yell at Jiang Qiaoxi.
All bark, no bite.
Wanna grab some breakfast?
Jiang Qiaoxi.
What exactly is Lin Yingtao to you?
A friend?
I don't get it.
Don't play dumb.
Aren't you besties with Cen Xiaoman now,
leaving Yingtao all behind?
Definitely not. How could I?
Yeah, whatever.
Wait.
So
does Yingtao think that too?
You should go after her.
It'll be hard to explain at school.
She can't have gone far.
Jiang Qiaoxi!
- Jiang Qiaoxi!
- Uncle, we switched rides.
You did?
Yingtao!
I haven't changed!
I still want to be your good friend!
Yingtao!
Stop chasing!
Jiang Qiaoxi.
What are you even doing?
Do you know how dangerous that was?
You are reckless.
And you're laughing?
Are you stupid?
That was seriously dangerous.
Stop laughing.
What do you want?
Yingtao…
I'm sorry.
Let me give you a ride.
Who wants a ride from you?
If you're ready to talk,
then say it.
Why didn't you contact me
all those years?
It all started
that winter break
when I came back from Qunshan.
Once I was home,
each morning started with Mom
dragging me to Olympiad math class.
Endless homework.
I worked hard every day.
I kept thinking,
if I finished early,
I could call you.
I could go back and see you.
But when I got home,
I realized my mom had cut the phone line.
That Spring Festival Eve,
I begged her
to let me make a phone call
to Qunshan.
But she said,
after winter break,
I would be transferred back
to Jialin Experimental.
Jiang Qiaoxi!
- Jiang Qiaoxi!
JIALIN TO QUNSHAN
Stop right there.
Let's go.
You're coming home.
I bet it hurt a lot.
You've got baby-soft skin.
I'm kinda forgetting the pain.
Nothing to worry.
I guess it didn't sting that much.
What's wrong?
You're unbelievable.
You went through all that,
and I had no idea.
And here I was, blaming you all this time.
If you'd just…
If you'd just written back.
Or called. Just once.
So I'd know you hadn't forgotten me.
That would've been enough.
Let go of me!
I'm going to Qunshan!
How can you be so selfish?
Your brother would never act like this.
Jiang Qiaoxi,
why are you like this?
Because I'm Jiang Qiaoxi.
If you dare reconnect
with anyone from Qunshan,
I'll make sure they all disappear
from your life.
Try me.
You're being quiet.
I don't want to give you hope
only to disappoint you again.
I just want to give you
a final answer.
A final answer?
Don't start throwing
math metaphors at me.
I won't.
That winter,
I promised I'd come back.
And I didn't.
I want to make sure I can follow through
on everything I say to you.
Like my cousin in Hong Kong.
He treats his wife right.
Every promise he's made her,
he's kept.
But I know
I've got nothing right now.
I'm stuck under my mom's thumb.
You give everything
when you care about someone.
I don't want you
to keep doing that for someone
who can't even decide his own life yet.
I felt just as helpless.
I didn't even know
what I could give you in return.
Why bring up
your cousin and his wife all of a sudden?
Jiang Qiaoxi.
Back then,
I couldn't figure it out.
Why you stopped writing.
Why you never called.
Why
you just disappeared.
I was never asking you
to give me anything.
I just wanted to hear from you.
To know how you were doing.
I knew that.
I wanted to reach out too.
But even if I had,
it wouldn't have helped.
It would've made things harder for you.
Then what about now?
Now you're
showing up for me,
even chasing after the bus.
Clearly, you've been trying
to get close to me.
Isn't that contradictory?
It's not.
Now there's a variable.
I didn't expect you to come find me.
Didn't expect you to pass out
from the heat.
I definitely didn't expect you
to think I was with Cen Xiaoman.
So it's my fault now?
My fault.
Heart over head.
Here we are.
Watch your step.
Does that clear things up?
Well,
if you're wondering
whether I've forgiven you,
I haven't decided yet.
So yeah,
that's the story.
So it was his mom
who didn't want him hanging with us.
At least he still has some conscience.
I've always thought Jiang Qiaoxi
wasn't the heartless type.
Just a coward
with some conscience.
Coward?
You don't even know
what his family is like.
That's a fast turnaround.
You just found out,
and you're already on his side?
Yu Qiao.
- Yu Qiao, what are you smiling at?
- Eh?
What?
Why are you grinning like that?
You look happier than Lin Yingtao.
You and Jiang Qiaoxi close or something?
- I…
- And by the way,
your laugh is horrendous.
It's not like that.
I just remembered this joke.
It was really, really funny.
Let's hear it then.
Okay.
One day,
a steamed bun got into a fight
with a noodle and totally beat him.
The next day,
the noodle came back
with his buddy, Instant Noodles.
But the bun just said,
"You think I won't recognize you
just because
you've got curls?
I'll still hit you."
I agree. That's hilarious.
Jiang Qiaoxi!
What are you doing? Stop shouting.
I still need to talk to Jiang Qiaoxi
about how we'll act around each other.
We need to make a plan.
Yeah.
After all that drama,
suddenly we're just friends
with him again?
His mom's gonna lose it
if she finds out.
Heard from my dad
she's still at the Laishui site.
Hasn't come back yet.
Then…
Hey,
maybe tonight?
You guys figure it out.
Qin Yeyun.
What's up with you?
Hey, from now on,
you're eating lunch with us.
Just like today.
Boring.
Who said I want to eat with you?
Boring? You were laughing your head off.
Yu Qiao.
Your job now
is telling her one joke every lunch.
You two clearly share the same
weird sense of humor.
Jiang Qiaoxi,
can I ask something?
Do you know how to do this question?
- This one…
- Hey, look.
- Yu Qiao is asking Jiang Qiaoxi for help.
- I noticed.
ASKING FOR YINGTAO: MEET TONIGHT?
11 PM, AT THE GARDEN?
So this has two cases,
positive and negative. Work through both
and solve the equations.
I'll write out an example.
SURE!
That's it there. You get it?
Yeah.
This is actually really clear.
JIALIN CITY POWER CONSTRUCTION
HOUSING COMPOUND
What's in your hand?
I'm listening to music.
And the other hand?
My diary.
Let me guess.
It's all about Jiang Qiaoxi?
What else? You?
You ever heard of subtlety?
Subtlety? What for?
Why can't you keep a little mystery?
You lay it all out like that,
and you lose the upper hand.
You don't understand.
I just wanted him to know
when he was thinking of me…
of us,
I was thinking of
us too?
All of us were thinking of him too.
- I…
- But is it really us and we?
Or did you mean
when he was thinking of you,
you were thinking of him?
I should go.
Hey,
how do I look?
Isn't it
too short like this?
Nope. Trust me,
this is much better.
- It's too much. I feel exposed.
- It looks good.
- My stomach is showing.
- Just leave it.
No tugging it down, okay?
Who's still out playing ball this late?
Who cares?
Probably some idiot.
Who?
So are you
going to see Jiang Qiaoxi or what?
Yu Qiao!
What are you doing out here?
Isn't it past your bedtime?
Couldn't sleep. Figured I'd walk a bit.
Didn't think I'd run into you.
Roaming around in the middle of the night,
all dressed up?
Are you dating someone?
Your jokes really suck.
You laughed at mine this afternoon though.
Are you feeling the same
about my joke?
It wasn't funny.
Not funny, but you laughed?
Well,
now you are kind of funny.
I think so too.
Then
what were you laughing at?
I was laughing at you.
Really?
Yeah, I think I'm funny too.
I told you a hundred times,
red's not your color.
I like red.
You're still young.
You don't know what you actually like yet.
You think I'm that clueless?
That I don't even know what I like?
You're trying to pick a fight
over this?
I've only been gone
a few days on business,
and you're already at it.
Can't you give me one break?
Was it really a work trip…
or did you visit your perfect son's grave?
Every time I do well in school,
you run to tell that son of yours,
the one I've never even met.
You want my good grades
to be his, right?
I also wish he could…
be the son you actually wanted.
If you're going there…
I swear I'll go straight to
Lin Haifeng's house
and ask them
how they raise their daughter.
Sneaking out to meet a boy late at night?
They deserve to know
how off-track their family's gotten.
What's messed up is our family.
A site in Fujian
is looking for engineers.
Why don't we let them go
where they belong,
and you go where you belong?
Problem solved.
You don't think I'll ever grow up?
That you'll always be able to control me?
Of course I want you to grow up.
Because only then
will you understand
everything I've done for you.
I'm tired.
I'm done
explaining myself.
Pack your things.
You're going to the training camp tonight.
No more distractions.
Math has to be your priority.
I'm not going.
I have school tomorrow.
Jiang Qiaoxi!
I could hear you from outside.
Why are you yelling at Qiaoxi?
What is it this time?
What now?
If you hadn't taken him to Qunshan
for your promotion,
he wouldn't have turned out like this.
Liang Hongfei,
why are you digging this up
again?
Now it's a problem
I'm trying to parent?
When he was little,
you wanted nothing to do with him.
I had a job.
What else could I do
but take him with me?
Don't act like I didn't care.
I worked too.
That's why I had to
bring him to Qunshan, remember?
- This one.
- Right.
Look at that smile.
Her smile really lights up a room.
Let's put that over there.
Since Qiaoxi
switched schools in fifth grade,
we haven't seen
Yingtao smile like that.
Tonight,
when she brought him up,
she really looked like
the little girl she used to be.
You actually agreed?
I though you weren't going to let her go.
But now look, it's this late,
and she still isn't home.
That girl…
You know,
even if you'd stopped her,
she would've found a way to go.
And honestly,
if she really
had something on her mind,
she wouldn't tell us anyway.
At their age, friendships like this
are the purest.
They deserve to be protected.
Yeah.
Who is it this late?
Cai.
Hello, Manager Cai.
Is something wrong?
Lin,
Mr. Jiang and Mrs. Liang
are fighting again.
The whole compound can hear it.
Apparently,
it's about Yingtao and Qiaoxi.
What?
You've been a father twice.
Not once did you get it right.
Are you really planning
to ruin both kids?
This happened over ten years ago.
You're still clinging to it?
What do you want from me?
What do I want?
- What I want?
- What do you want from me?
You keep using it
to punish me.
Tearing open old wounds.
If I gave my life to Mengchu,
would that
make it right?
- Would it be over then?
- Auntie Juan.
No one in this world
can pay for my son's life.
Can you keep Jiang Qiaoxi in check?
Lin Haifeng's daughter
is sneaking out at night
to meet your son.
If you still consider yourself his father,
go to their house
and tell them
to keep their daughter away from my son.
- You want that?
- You want to lose it? Go ahead.
I'm not going crazy with you.
Why are you here?
I…
I was just passing by.
And I saw you
standing here alone.
Jiang Qiaoxi still hasn't come.
Are you sure you gave him the right time?
I gave him the exact time.
He's still not here.
And it's late.
Well…
Look.
Go home. We can talk about it tomorrow.
Come on, I'll walk you home.
Qiaoxi.
Uncle, Auntie, I'm sorry.
This was my fault.
I asked Yingtao to meet me.
I was going to tell her something,
but I can't make it.
Please,
tell her I'm sorry.
Jiang Qiaoxi.
I'm heading
to Olympiad camp tonight.
Well,
Lin, Shengjuan,
kids seeing each other after school,
chatting and hanging out, is normal.
Sorry we made you come
all the way out here
because of our family's mess.
Is it just our family issue?
Mom,
let's just go.
I promised you.
I'll keep my word.
I'll believe you this one last time.
Yingtao.
Yingtao, Yingtao…
Don't go, Yingtao!
Yingtao.
Heard it was because
he was seeing Yingtao.
That's why things got messy.
Mom.
Auntie Juan, Uncle Haifeng,
Yingtao didn't do anything wrong.
She didn't.
Thanks.
Yu Qiao, it's late.
Head on home.
Get back safe.
Sorry.
I…
It's okay.
Don't worry.
Mom and Dad don't think
you did anything wrong.
Let's go home.
Come on.
Come on. Let's go home.
It's cooling down lately, huh?
Right?
Autumn's coming.
I'll make you some pear water
with rock sugar.
Bring it to school with you, okay?
Mom.
Did Jiang Qiaoxi's mom
say anything nasty
to you and Dad?
Yingtao,
don't forget who your dad is.
I'm the top electrician in the unit.
No matter how high up
she is,
she'll still treat me
with polite.
Am I right?
But I brought you all
so much trouble.
Someday
when you're a parent,
you'll understand.
Kids grow up
through all kinds of trouble.
Well…
Is… I mean…
Is Jiang Qiaoxi in trouble?
Yingtao,
Qiaoxi's a good kid.
Just like you,
he cares deeply about what you two have.
But a lot of the time,
especially like you,
at your age,
it's hard to change things around you.
Hard to make choices all on your own.
It's true
we can't always
change things around us.
But friendship is around us.
It is something hard to change,
right?
Of course.
Let's go.
GENERAL GOODS
Yun.
Uncle Jiang.
Grab me a pack of cigarettes.
QIN FAMILY MART
Need anything else?
Yun…
you're close with Yingtao, right?
Could you
maybe talk to her?
Right now,
your top priority is studying.
But besides that,
it's also important
to build healthy relationships.
That includes friendships.
That's to say.
Something can wait.
For example, romance.
All of that needs to happen
at the right time.
At their age,
it's best for them to
not affecting one another.
Uncle Jiang,
if you ask me,
it's Jiang Qiaoxi
who's been affecting Lin Yingtao.
Subtitle translation by: Jiaxin Wang