The Best Hit
♫ The stars floating in the night sky ♫
♫ Twinkle even more today ♫
♫ Like your eyes, like your lips ♫
Yoon Si Yoon
♫ They make my heart flutter  ♫
♫ Beautiful day  ♫
Lee Se Young
♫ And I have something to say ♫
Kim Min Jae
♫ Something to tell ♫
Cha Tae Hyun
♫ I wanna shout out your name to the sky ♫
♫ I’ll tell you ♫
♫ I love you ♫
♫ It’s a beautiful day ♫
Choi Woo Seung
Lee Ji Hoon!
Is it because you're an intern? You finished work early.
It ended early only today.
- But did you wait for me?
- Yeah.
- For you to keep your promise.
- Promise?
You said you'd see a movie with me. I found a movie that I want to see.
So you're joining your dad's company?
I thought it would be better than in other places.
My father is taking a break now, but he was a very famous manager once.
Well, I heard that he was great when he was J2's manager.
What?
Come to think of it, it's been a while since I saw you like this.
There you go again at making me get goosebumps.
It's okay if it's like this sometimes!
Well, it does seem like it's been a while since we laughed together like this.
You're going to eat popcorn, right?
Caramel-flavored popcorn with Sprite.
Friend, you seem to know me better than I know myself sometimes.
- Let's go together.
- No, you already bought the tickets.
I'll be back soon. You can sit down.
The last scene was really awesome, right? How did they come up with such a story?
As expected, movies with good audience reviews are also really fun.
Right?
This is about Thumbs Up.
What?
What do you think of him?
Do you like him?
I don't really kno—
It does seem like that.
How would it be if we hadn't been friends from the start?
What?
What if we hadn't met as childhood friends but met just like you and Thumbs Up?
In the midst of a series of strange coincidences and unusual situations... like a movie.
If we met like that, would our relationship be different?
♫ After a long night passes ♫
♫  And tomorrow comes ♫
The fact that I met you as a friend
♫ Will I be closer to my dream? ♫
is something I regret now.
♫  Or will I be frozen like my clock? ♫
♫ Light in the sky ♫
♫  The sky of my youth ♫
♫  My dreams that I always wanted ♫
♫  Some day, fly fly fly ♫
World Entertainment
Logistics Center
Daily work Journal
- You drink a large-sized iced caramel macchiato with two shots, right?
- Ah, geez.
Hey, why are you more like a person here than me?
I always put in my best effort no matter whatever it is or wherever I am.
You never put in any effort at all.
Is everything going well?
The investments are almost confirmed.
Who are you supposed to get them from?
Half of it will be from Chairwoman Kathy, and the other half will be from Chairwoman Oh from Jongno.
If it's Chairwoman Kathy, is she the Kathy we know? Are you sure it'll be okay?
I'm in the middle of looking into everything right now, don't worry.
So does this mean you've overcome the biggest problem and you're over the hump?
But, music is the most important.
You already overcame that the moment you asked me for a song.
- So, when do you think the song will be ready?
- It's almost finished.
- It'll be great, right?
- It'll be great for sure!
Who do you think the song I wrote will take after? It'll be smooth because it'll take after me.
Right. By any chance, did you ask Yeong Jae to pay off our debt?
It's me, Hyeon Jae. Have you ever seen me ask anyone for something? I demanded it.
You did something useless.
Why was it useless? If you think about it, isn't it all our money?
How is that our money, it's Yeong Jae's.
There's something you don't know, but it's okay.
Yeong Jae can still give us more than what he gave.
How do you always make things so simple?
What if it's complicated?
Did you decide to have Ji Hoon debut after all?
I'm going to try it once.
If that happens, then both Ji Hoon and I would debut under you.
One of them was the biggest mistake of my life.
And the other one will be the biggest hit of my life.
Listen to yourself.
By the way, this is about me. No matter how much I think about it,
I think there's only one person associated with my disappearance.
The one who got the best profit after I disappeared.
Who is that?
No way!
Not that, but Park Yeong Jae.
I got it, so
CEO Park Yeong Jae
- please contact Chairwoman Oh.
- Yes.
Hey, honey. I heard you agreed to invest in Gwang Jae's company.
You can't do that.
Do you know how hard things are for the company?
In a bit, it'll cost you a lot of money to renew MJ's contract with us.
I'm going to tell him that it won't be possible. Do you understand?
I got it. I'll forget about Bo Hee and I'll pretend that didn't happen.
This means we are even. Okay?
Chairwoman Oh of Jongno is on the line.
Aigoo, Chairwoman. I haven't been in touch with you for a while, have I?
Aigoo. I'm calling you because I have a great investment opportunity for you.
I'm only telling this to Chairwoman and no one else.
This time we are going to release MJ's album in collaboration with an American company.
Is your investment in World Entertainment confirmed?
If it's not confirmed, why don't you join us?
Of course.
Thumbs Up.
There's no one but you?
It seems like it. Why? Who did you come to see?
- Producer Yoon asked me to bring this.
- I see.
Okay then.
Right, Part-timer. You said you were in a band, right?
Oh, it was really ages ago and only for a short while.
Then that means you know how to read music.
Can you sing the guide track for me?
Hey. Do you want me to?
Can you do it for me? It's in women's key, so it's too high for me.
Hey. No, no, no way.
No, no.
You can wear headphones from there.
- These ones?
- Put those on.
Hey, Part-timer. You really look like a singer now.
Don't tease me.
Can you hear the instrumental accompaniment?
- What?
- Put those back on. Put them back.
What did you say?
Don't be nervous, just relax.
Who is nervous?
But, does an intern have to do this?
Okay, let's start.
♫ This feeling is a little awkward ♫
♫ Like a secret to tell you ♫
♫ I don’t know about love ♫
♫ But I feel fluttery about you ♫
♫ I have not told you yet ♫
♫ My lips tremble making me nervous ♫
This song... I wrote while thinking about you.
What?
I thought about you while writing this song.
What did you say? Can you say it again?
I wrote this song thinking about you.
Thinking about you.
♫ If you ♫
♫  If you come to me ♫
♫  I’ll feel like I have the world ♫
♫ I’m shouting to the sky ♫
♫  It’s only you ♫
♫ I’m closing my eyes, with all my heart ♫
♫  I’m calling out to you ♫
♫ I love you, I really want you ♫
- Goodbye.
- Yes, goodbye.
♫  Are you listening? ♫
Bro.
What are you doing here?
How did you know I was here?
Did you get a job?
No. It's just a part-time job.
What about the company?
You aren't there anymore, so I don't have any reason to be in the company. I have no regrets, so I also quit.
So what is it? Tell me honestly.
Bro. They kicked me out.
I did my best...
You did a good job. You did well.
Bro.
Okay.
Lee Ji Hoon | World Entertainment
This much, I think it's great.
Why am I so awesome?
I'm hungry.
Lee Ji Hoon
World Entertainment
I'm hungry.
Here it is.
Is this the song that the general manager has been working on?
Yes.
I'm sure because I swapped it with the original one.
Then, let our guys tweak it a little bit and work with this one.
It'll be MJ's title song.
But, can we do that?
We'll release the song first,
and both our company and the singers are much bigger.
If they released it later, who would people think has copied it?
Also, they'll probably have a hard time getting the money to produce an album.
But still, how can you do this all of a sudden?
Someone I know told me there was a position available here.
Even though the work is hard, I get paid well.
Why did the company let you go all of a sudden?
There is the age problem, so I guess I'm useless to them now.
While working part-time like this, whenever I get a chance, I'll also go up and perform on a stage.
Do you believe in me?
Bro, of course.
Then, let's try one more time. With me.
Where? Did Ssen Entertainment contact you?
- Not at Ssen Entertainment.
- If it's not Ssen Entertainment then a better place?
At World Entertainment.
If it's World Entertainment... Do you mean your dad's company? Helter-Skelter's company?
Never mind. Trust me.
- Instead, you can't lie to me anymore.
- Hey.
Why would I lie to you? What do you take me for?
Salute!
Marine Lee, it's nice meeting you here.
Pardon? I think you got the wrong person.
I accidentally bumped into Marine Oh. He said he would buy me a cup of coffee.
He just went to the bathroom. There he comes.
Salute!
Salute. Marine Lee, do you live near here?
Yes. That's right!
You're with your friend now. Just relax.
- Yes.
- How have you been?
Once a marine,
always a marine!
Yes!
- I'm going now.
- Yes.
Marines never die.
It's just that marines do not return.
Last summer, I went to the Marine Corps camp for a while. There I met, wow...
Have you been lying to me about your age?
Bro.
When did you do your military service?
You're amazing. You are definitely amazing. I can't believe this.
Sorry.
Woo Seung, have you decided? Are you really going to move into the room?
Pardon? Yes.
They say the sooner you go there, the better. What are you going to do?
World Entertainment
What's all this?
Let's have a get-together today.
A get-together dinner? What company are we? That we're having a get-together?
Did you prepare all this by yourself?
It's been a while since I last showed my skills so I thought I'd treat you.
I thought I was going to faint from hunger, but this is all good.
- Cheers!
It's delicious. It's all good.
- You want to die? You want to die?
- Give it to me.
Really.
Have some meat.
It is healthy to eat a lot of garlic.
The loser will eat this.
- Rock, paper, scissors!
That smells.
It's too hot.
I love this so much.
Someday...
You'll remember tonight as a long time ago, right?
I think you're right.
Why is everyone suddenly so serious while eating delicious food?
Shall we take pictures together?
- Pictures?
- Just to remember the night.
Sure then.
Here I go.
- Hurry, hurry up!
Quickly, legs up.
Here!
- Power Rangers!
Hurry, hurry up! Hurry, hurry up!
What are you doing? Aren't you going to bed?
I need to sleep...
But, there is something I need to confess to you.
What?
Tomorrow, I'm moving out.
So that's why I'm saying goodbye to my beloved hammock.
I really thought I was going to be kicked on the streets,
But... Thanks to my friend, I've been well.
- Is it because of me?
- Yes.
It's because of you.
I'm sorry I've been feeling beholden to you.
I don't care if you stay longer.
I know. But I found a room on good terms and at a great price.
Hey, I'll finally get paid soon.
Are you going far?
No. It's near here.
Is that so? Then I'll help you move your things tomorrow.
There isn't anything to move. I only have one bag.
Thank you for everything.
Lee Ji Hoon.
Come back anytime.
What do you think? How is it?
Is it tacky?
Not at all
Hey, I assure you, this is good enough to make it big.
Anyway, I was also worried about what to do if you didn't like it.
Hey, I think we should be able to get investments for this song and make an album.
Tell me if you need anything more. Don't get upset this time.
When did I get upset?
I didn't know that after you disappeared from being upset at me, I would be so bored.
You were my only friend after all.
If the soundtrack is okay, buy me a triangle kimbap.
Anyway, you're still a weirdo.
You're still the same 20 years ago and even now.
- Let's go.
- Sure.
How do you feel about it?
The feeling is great.
Hey, look at that!
Soon, after a little while, Ji Hoon will be like that too.
Who is that? He's handsome.
Anyway, Ji Hoon will also become like him soon.
Ever since you came here, this is the very first time I like you.
Do you want to eat another triangle Kimbap?
Are you going to buy me another one?
Go and get another one for free. I saw earlier it was two for one.
♫ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♫
♫ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♫
What are you doing?
Oh! It's amazing. What is it?
I'm printing out some pictures. It's nice to share them together.
♫ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! ♫
♫ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♫
Star Punch Entertainment
Are you looking for someone?
No.
Excuse me, has the general producer gone somewhere?
I think he came only in the morning today and he left later.
Do you know where he went?
I don't know either. He left work for today.
My gosh!
This is amazing even if I keep looking at it.
I really look good in this one.
I look cute.
The person you're calling isn't available...
What's with you, Thumbs Up?
Since I moved, I was going to ask him to do some house cleaning together. Where did he go?
He's not answering his phone either.
I'm definitely sure I locked it when I left.
You damned thief!
Thumbs Up!
Are you okay?
What should I do?
Hey, why did you come in secretly?
You really slap me with a frying pan whenever you see me.
What brings you here?
I heard that you rented a house from a colleague so I asked where it is.
I wanted to come here early and do some cleaning for you.
What?
So, did you leave work early in order to come here to clean up?
Forget it. I'm not the kind of person who brags about doing things like this.
Well... I've really mopped the floor so many times.
The blinds were also a mess, so I re-installed them.
The mattress too.
The bathroom was so messy and dirty too.
If you go now, you'll see it's so clean that it'll shine brightly.
Thumbs Up, that was so kind of you.
What would you like me to do in return?
Can you cook for me?
Let's have dinner before you go.
It's been a while since I had a proper meal with rice.
What do you mean by a proper meal?
Still, it's been a long time since I had this kind of meal.
This is not my story, but the story of a guy I know.
His parents passed away early when he was young.
Originally, his parents had been always busy, but they died in a car accident when he was in middle school.
So he lived alone ever since.
Because of his hot temper, he had no friends. His only hobby was listening to music.
He just listened to music like crazy.
Back then, he didn't want to go to college and he only wanted to do something related to music.
So he went to an entertainment company.
The company was the closest to his house.
He lived the way he wanted.
But...
He was still lonely.
He was always alone.
He dated women easily. He broke up with them easily too.
And...
And I guess he did a lot of terrible things to the people around him.
So, is he still living like that?
He?
Fortunately, he isn't lonely anymore.
He also got to eat some warm meals.
Come and see me often. I can cook this much.
It's upsetting. Why would you say often?
What's there to be upset about?
I'll come by without a break, so be prepared.
- With whose permission?
- My permission.
Part-timer, what is it?
It's nothing.
What is it?
I just feel happy these days.
You feel happy, so why?
I always had trouble coming right after something good happened.
I, Thumbs Up, used to be called Trouble-shooter Man. Don't worry about mood swings.
♫ Fool  ♫
What's this? Thumbs Up!
♫  Only to you, I can give my all ♫
♫ Remember my love, my eyes, my story ♫
♫  My hope, it’s all you ♫
♫  And what I wanna say is ♫
You scared me!
♫ Yes, fool, I have a lot to say to you too ♫
♫  All day, I wrote down funny things that happened ♫
I'm sure she'll be cracking up by now, right?
I should have taken pictures of Part-timer too.
Woo Seung!
Hello. I left some books on the rooftop.
I see. Go up. The guys are there too.
I heard you're going to debut in World Entertainment.
- How did you know?
- What?
Well... I heard it from here and there.
Hey, I'm also a half-time employee at World Entertainment.
Anyway, good luck.
I know you'll do well.
The song came out pretty great. And the apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
- What are you talking about?
- What?
It's nothing.
I know you're Yoo Hyeon Jae.
But, I want to make one thing clear.
I only have one father and he's the CEO of World Entertainment.
I hope you don't meddle with me.
♫ Why are you hurting me again? ♫
♫  Why are you trying to leave me? ♫
♫ You don’t know me at all ♫
Additional scenes
♫ Baby ♫
Hey. What are all these? Why didn't he organize them a bit?
Aigoo.
Why is he going to do with all these?
Aigoo. Why didn't he just throw them away?
♫ I only know you ♫
♫ Actually ♫
From: Yoo Hyeon Jae
To: Lee Soon Tae
♫ Back then ♫
From: Yoo Hyeon Jae
To: Lee Soon Tae
♫ You said you couldn’t live without me ♫
♫  Now I can’t live without you ♫
♫ My love ♫
The Best Hit
♫ Baby, I cried all day because of you ♫
I'm giving you this but instead let me ask you for a favor.
Cancel the contract with MJ that expires in a month.
I've been thinking about this for a while, why don't you two try to debut as a male duo?
Hoon's Drill. What do you think about it?
You know I can't lie because of my personality. You look pretty.
♫  Just like me ♫
No, why do I have to go camping with you?
If I order it, do as you’re told!
This time, we have a new artist we have recruited.
I'm sorry. I found out too late that I shouldn't have done that.
But still, it's nice to be able to tell you directly that I'm sorry.
♫ You said you couldn’t live without me ♫
♫  Now I can’t live without you ♫
The Best Hit
♫ The stars floating in the night sky ♫
♫ Twinkle even more today ♫