The Best Hit
♫ The stars floating in the night sky ♫
♫ Twinkle even more today ♫
♫ Like your eyes, like your lips ♫
Yoon Si Yoon
♫ They make my heart flutter  ♫
♫ Beautiful day  ♫
Lee Se Young
♫ And I have something to say ♫
Kim Min Jae
♫ Something to tell ♫
Cha Tae Hyun
♫ I wanna shout out your name to the sky ♫
♫ I’ll tell you ♫
♫ I love you ♫
♫ It’s a beautiful day ♫
What happened?
I see that you woke up. Are you feeling alright?
Sorry? Yes.
But why am I here?
It looks like you lost your footing on the stairs.
Lost my footing?
You were passed out on the street in front of the building. The residents saw you and reported it.
The bottom of the building?
How long have I been like this?
You've been sleeping for quite a long time. It looks like you were very tired.
You also talked in your sleep.
You must have been dreaming of the 1988 Olympics. You kept on saying, "Victory, Victory."
TN: Woo Seung and victory are homonyms (우승)
Dreaming of victory?
Was I badly injured?
We need to run a few more tests,
but fortunately, it doesn't look like you have any serious injury.
- What is this for?
- You had a slight bruise on your head.
Anyway, tranquility is the most important, so get a good rest.
And here ...
Mister Hyeon Jae, an autograph please.
- What?
- I'm really a fan, you see.
Why aren't you doing any activities these days?
Stop it, Nurse Park. Me first.
You see, my daughter is a big fan of yours.
Then everything until now was a dream?
Oh, Mister Yoo Hyeon Jae.
But you don't have any treatment today?
Ah, you came for the results of yesterday's checkup?
But you need to wait a few days for it, though.
Yesterday?
I came to the hospital yesterday?
Sorry?
Ah, yes. You came yesterday and got your treatment, you know.
But this is mine.
Hey! I told you not to touch my stuff, right?
What's yours?
That's my watch, you know it.
What? How is this yours? It's mine.
Then here as well, there is Yoo Hyeon Jae?
Sorry, what day is it today?
Today is the 17th.
The 17th of June?
Of course, of June.
- 1993.
- Sorry?
It's been a long time since 1993 has gone. It's 1994.
1994?
Hey.
Yoo Hyeon Jae died?
Yoo Hyeon Jae,
on the 17th of June 1994, at the age of 24, passed away.
The Best Hit
But you can't move yet.
- I'm a bit busy, you see.
- But!
Answer the phone, answer the phone.
Hello?
Gwang Jae. It's me, Yoo Hyeon Jae.
What's with you? Why do you keep—
You see, I...
I'm pretty sure I told you that I wasn't really that happy to have a phone call with you?
Hey, we already made up, you know?
What? I never!
I mean, you and I... Uh, later.
Anyway, I think you have to help me a bit.
I can't go there, so you'll have to come over here.
Ah really, you really know how to piss someone off, don't you?
Hey, Yoo Hyeon Jae! You little—
Gwang Jae. You're the only one who can help me now.
Come to Bear Coffee Shop, please. I know it's shameless, but please help me out this once.
Why would I go there? Really, tsk.
Forget it, if you've got nothing better to do then wash your feet and go to sleep. Hanging up.
Yoo Hyeon Jae? Are you in contact with Hyeon Jae, without us knowing?
No, what are you saying.
Forget it. It's fine. What were you saying?
What? Ah.
I was thinking about this while touching up the song.
It's not because I didn't have any idea, but from the start, we weren't really interested in dance or things like that,
so I was thinking about releasing a ballad album.
Are you listening to me?
Hey, Lee Gwang Jae!
What? Oh, yeah.
How come no matter if Yoo Hyeon Jae is here or not, you're not interested in me whatsoever?
What are you saying?
Hey, now our World Entertainment's figurehead is you, Park Yeong Jae.
You're saying this now that it all fell down.
Anyway, so this ballad album—
- I'll go out quick.
- What?
I'm in the middle of saying something important, where are you going?
I'll hear you out next time, okay? Next time.
You said I'm the figurehead.
You're the figurehead, you are. But later. Later.
I'm sure it was a call from Hyeon Jae, though.
These two, aren't they scheming something together?
♫  Someone is calling me. Is it you? ♫
♫ My heart is fluttering ♫
♫  I'm thinking of you again today ♫
When you said you were going somewhere quick, I thought you were going to some amazing place.
But it looks like you really just went somewhere quickly.
I just saw you, but I'm happy to see you again.
What are you saying, out of the blue?
When did we see each other?
There was something like that.
And you, really,
what's with that hair and your outfit?
Come on, really.
There was something like that, too.
Actually, it's good we met up. I had something to tell you anyway and was going to ask to meet up—
More than that, I have to find someone urgently.
Who? Who do you have to find quickly?
Yoo Hyeon Jae.
What?
I have to find me.
What are you saying? Are you drunk?
That's not it. Where should I go to meet Yoo Hyeon Jae now?
- I want to leave.
- Ah wait.
Okay, I know it's weird.
But you have a big network, I think you could find him right away if you look into it.
What nonsense is that? Finding you?
Found him! I found him, he's here, here.
That is...
Right! That is,
someone is going around impersonating me. Someone who looks exactly like me.
- What?
- So please look into the places where Yoo Hyeon Jae is now.
There will be one somewhere else, for sure. Not me, but another Yoo Hyeon Jae.
What are they saying? I can't hear a thing.
How did it go? Did you find him?
It looks like there really is someone who resembles you.
Really? Where is he, now?
That is, it looks like he was at the studio until not long ago.
He was working until this morning, and...
He was working, and?
He said he had something to do in Paju.
In Paju? Why there?
He said he had something to do with his family.
With his family?
- Let me use the car.
- What?
Ah really, I don't know why I have to be swayed around like this by you every time.
It's because you're my sole friend, you know.
Who is your friend, uh?
- Did you forget something here?
- What?
When did I go out from here?
You just went out.
Did I? Then what was I doing?
- Sorry?
- I must have been doing something, no?
- You said you would move your parents' grave.
- What?
You said you couldn't keep the grave anymore. That's what you said to me.
I did?
I did, right. Yes.
And I didn't say where I was going, did I?
No.
Sorry, is there a lake around here, perhaps?
A lake in the area? If you go a bit further, there is a lake called Water Lilies Lake.
Water Lilies Lake?
Water Lilies Lake...
The last whereabouts of popular singer Yoo Hyeon Jae has been found.
Yesterday afternoon, a month after his disappearance, on the side of a lake in Paju, Gyeonggi province,
a vehicle owned by Mister Yoo Hyeon Jae has been found.
You shouldn't go to the Water Lilies Lake.
Thank you.
It looks like I can't take care of you anymore.
You wished you had lived nearby here.
It looks like we'll be able to meet very soon, so don't be too saddened.
This is updated news on the typhoon.
We can say that it has completely entered the region of Seoul and Gyeonggi province, right?
That is how we should see it.
There must be a lot of people who remember last year's twin typhoon, Kaola.
This typhoon is also small in scale, but a similar twin typhoon—
Wh-What's this?
So there really was another Yoo Hyeon Jae!
Whoa, Thumbs Up!
What on earth? What are you?
Don't be too shocked.
Because I'm also you. That's not it, should I say that you are me?
What?
It must be difficult to believe, but I'm Yoo Hyeon Jae from 1993.
1993?
On that night in 1993 that you wanted so much to turn back,
because of a strange typhoon, I went to the future for a bit and ended up coming back here.
So that is, when you experience it yourself it's a really big deal. But now that I try to say it, it does sound quite strange, right?
Well, so, uh.
Anyway, in the end, you came here because of Mom and Dad's ashes?
So this wasn't the worst-case scenario like I thought.
What are you saying?
You come out as having disappeared here, you see.
So I was trying to stop you from coming here at any cost, but whoa!
I didn't know I would end up meeting you here.
Really, there must actually be a fate that is impossible to change.
Then, you mean, you are me?
That's what I'm saying. At first I was confused,
but I figured it out when I saw the note you left at the bank.
What note? What are you talking about?
The money and the note you stored at the bank.
You did that to give it to Gwang Jae, right?
I did think about sending it to Gwang Jae. But how do you know this?
I am you, for one,
and I came from the future, I'm telling you. No.
That's not it. That is, originally I came from the past.
Anyway, that's how it is.
So that means you're me from 1993.
On that night in 1993, we received the golden cup at the Gayo Top Ten.
That evening you wanted so much to turn back.
Right, on that night I ended up drifting away from all of them.
I thought all of it was my money. But I guess it wasn't true.
- So how are they living?
- What?
You just said you saw the future?
What about Bo Hee? Gwang Jae?
Th-That is, umm. It's a bit of a long story.
Well, I do tell stories excellently.
Where should I start?
Gwang Jae, Bo Hee and President Soon Tae, they were all living together.
And Yeong Jae this guy, he was really successful.
What's this? Who is it?
He looks really similar to Hyeon Jae.
Damn, this weather. At this rate, we might get struck by lightning.
Our fans are still the same, even though twenty years have passed.
They're as excellent as always, and amazing.
They still remember you, and they still give love to our songs.
Is that so?
Roar! ... Moo...
It looks like I don't have much time left.
What?
It's nothing.
About Ji Hoon. Can you tell me more?
What? I told you!
He's quite an okay guy.
Of course, he must be excellent since he's my son.
Right. He was really excellent.
Righteous to the point it's frustrating. Clever to the point of causing jealousy.
He also sings and dances fairly well. More than well enough to stand on stage.
With that, he could be full of himself, but he isn't at all, this kid.
And studying? Is he good at studying?
He went to the best university in the country.
He takes after me so he got smart brains.
I miss them. Gwang Jae, Bo Hee ...
and Ji Hoon, too.
Oh my! That scared me.
- Why is there such thunder?
- Because of the typhoon, of course!
Typhoon?
Perhaps, is this the twin typhoon?
I don't know!
Wait, I did kind of hear it on the radio earlier. That's right. It's the twin typhoon.
But why?
What time is it?
I left my watch at home.
If you go to World Entertainment from here as fast as possible, how long will it take?
- Why?
- I don't how it'll turn out, but let's go for it.
What are you talking about?
I'll tell you the details later. For now, start the car.
- Why is it like this?
- I brought a car. Let's take my car. Now.
I don't know, dammit.
Excellent Yoo Hyeon Jae.
What's this? The rain stopped.
There isn't much time left.
We have three minutes left. We have to go to the rooftop right away.
- So, why?
- We might have one more chance.
Quick!
You have nothing to lose, so you ride this downstairs first.
- What?
- Somehow, this might be able to send us to another world.
What are you talking about?
I also time traveled like this, from this rooftop.
There's no time. Quick.
In the future I came from, they say that they can treat your illness with medication.
No.
What do you mean, no?
I don't want this.
What?
Here is my time.
Think about it. I am the Yoo Hyeon Jae living in this world now.
If the future you talked about is the truth, there are things I need to complete here.
If there is anything I need to wrap up, I want to do it here.
♫ Will I be closer to my dream? ♫
So there was a reason why I was being like this here, I see.
♫  Or will I be frozen like my clock? ♫
♫ Light in the sky ♫
And if you meet Ji Hoon again...
♫  The sky of my youth ♫
Give him this for me.
♫  My dreams that I always wanted ♫
But you are dying.
♫ Fly, fly ♫
I'm Yoo Hyeon Jae. I won't take it just like this.
You said there's no time.
♫  Flowers that haven’t bloomed  ♫
Go back to the time you should be in.
Hey, Yoo Hyeon Jae.
Also...
♫  Will shine brightly once the sky clears ♫
Thank you for coming.
♫ Light in the sky ♫
You really...
♫  The sky of my youth ♫
♫  My dreams that I always wanted ♫
♫  Some day, fly fly fly ♫
♫ what makes you beautiful, beautiful, beautiful life ♫
♫ Life is still beautiful ♫
Lee Ji Hoon! Are you almost done?
Why are you going so early in the morning?
On public TV they usually do a lot of rehearsals, so they start at dawn.
Why aren't they coming?
It's your first time on public TV, what if you're late?
We were trying to get it right until the last moment.
Ahjumma. No, Ahjussi. That's not it.
Miss.
President. I'm sorry.
Are you alright? Your face seems a bit white.
I'm alright. My heart...
My heart...
Bro. Where is my heart?
Here, here, here.
There's nothing to be nervous about, just do as you always do.
I'm envious, you're going on public TV.
President, aren't you discriminating too much? You don't even get us onto any broadcasts.
There is a response to these two. What do you want me to do? You two wait a bit, okay?
What are you doing, get on now.
Wait a bit.
Oh you're handsome, my son.
All good. Go now.
- We'll go.
- Do well.
Oppa, Oppa!
Mal Sook. Oppa is busy, what is it?
What is this? My first autograph is for Mal Sook?
No. If you meet the oppas from Heaven Boys Crew, get an autograph for me.
- What?
- The oppas from Heaven Boys Crew,
don't miss one and get all of them.
I got it, I got it.
And...
It's something precious to me. This will protect you.
And mine, Mal Sook? I'm the one who should be protected. What about mine?
Stop it, you have to get on now. Get on.
- Goodbye.
- Bye. Good luck!
Go well.
You must do well! Good luck!
♫ Something to tell ♫
I'm suddenly hungry.
Ahjumma, I think there's a beggar in my stomach.
Mal Sook.
I told you not to call me Ahjumma but Mom, now.
Ah right. Mom.
Should we make some delicious noodles to eat?
- Okay, Mom!
- Let's go!
♫ I’ll tell you, I love you ♫
It feels weird that the kids we saw every day became our juniors.
- Their song was really good, right?
- Yeah.
It even scored a fairly high rank on the music charts.
They need to score a proper hit for real.
I would be glad if they score a hit.
Me too. A good, proper hit.
Yes, Director. It's been a long time.
- Oh, our kids?
- Good morning.
Welcome!
- Of course, they can do entertainment programs!
- What's with "Welcome"?
- I'm out because of Music Top Ten, now.
- What?
- Good morning!
- Welcome!
When the broadcast ends, I'll be going up right away.
Yes.
Hey, there seems to be a lot of directors who saw you in a good light.
It's here!
Jay B!
Chairman really made a terrific name.
Music Top Ten
JayB
Yes, Director. Ah yes, wait a second.
Old student? I didn't know I would meet you here.
Do Hye Ri, you also have a broadcast today?
What are you saying? Don't you know we're nominees for first place today?
Really? It hasn't been long since you debuted, but so soon?
Well I heard we are in the top five girl groups, but is that of any importance? Winning first place is what matters.
But why is he like this?
He must be nervous. He has something similar to stage fright.
Bro. That won't do. Should I go to the bathroom once more?
Fierce Hye Ri, are you crazy?
- Dimwit. You shouldn't let yourself be eaten up. You should be the one eating others.
- What?
There's no place for herbivores on the stage.
If you get distracted, think of the smack I gave on your back. It'll probably burn until you get off stage.
I have to go. I'll probably see you often from now on.
- Old Student, I'm leaving.
- Okay.
How is it? Is there any effect?
There's none, none! Just my back hurting!
- JayB.
- Yes.
- You'll be going on stage.
Yes.
Bro. You're ready, right?
Bro. I'm putting my trust in you.
Let's go.
♫ When I still see you ♫
♫  When I see you asleep ♫
♫  I remember when we first met ♫
♫  You’re still so beautiful ♫
♫ When I still see you ♫
♫  When I see you asleep ♫
♫  I remember when we first met ♫
♫  You’re still so beautiful ♫
♫ Do you remember when we first met? ♫
♫  I went to see you every day. Fool! ♫
♫  I went to where you worked ♫
♫  I stole glances at you every day ♫
♫  Back then, I was so young ♫
Yes, this is World Entertainment.
No, the president isn't here at the moment.
♫  I will treat the beautiful you ♫
He must not be reachable because of JayB's schedule, probably.
Yes, I will tell him to call you.
Yes.
Team Leader Choi!
You must be coming back from a workout?
♫ Though you can’t cook ♫
♫  I’ll still eat it ♫
Since I don't have any activity for the time being.
You said you're writing songs. Shouldn't you be full-on busy these days?
Well, I am looking into it. But I keep getting distracted, it's not working well.
You keep on calling me team leader when we don't even have any team members. Are you going to keep this up?
So what if there are no team members? They say you're the team leader.
There's not even one employee other than me, here.
You put team leader on your business card.
It's the president who set it up as team leader, you see?
Anyway. By the way, is there any song you wrote?
Me, what...
I know it all. I heard you're studying composition, these days?
If there's anything you wrote, show me a bit.
Well, if I show you ... are you going to take them for yourself?
Ah really! Rubbing salt in the wound.
I should go have lunch. I'm hungry so I can't think properly.
- Tell President that I came by.
- Yeah.
Right. You didn't get any contact from Master?
What?
No.
The Best Hit
♫ The stars floating in the night sky ♫