The Best Hit
♫ The stars floating in the night sky ♫
♫ Twinkle even more today ♫
♫ Like your eyes, like your lips ♫
Yoon Si Yoon
♫ They make my heart flutter  ♫
♫ Beautiful day  ♫
Lee Se Young
♫ And I have something to say ♫
Kim Min Jae
♫ Something to tell ♫
Cha Tae Hyun
♫ I wanna shout out your name to the sky ♫
♫ I’ll tell you ♫
♫ I love you ♫
♫ It’s a beautiful day ♫
I'm hungry. I'm hungry. I'm hungry.
I'm dizzy. When will we be there?
We're almost there. Don't whine.
Ah, you kept saying that from a while ago. I thought you said you've been there. How many times?
Be quiet!
Oh! Hey, hey, hey. Let's quickly go in.
Hey. If we keep walking a little further,
there is a place that is cheaper, gives more meat, and is even more delicious.
Just let's go in here. All the meat tastes the same.
I'm starving to death!
I said if we keep walking a little further, there is a place that is cheaper, gives more meat, and is even more delicious.
If we die from hunger, we can't even eat meat.
- Let's go in!
- Hey.
Hey, the place is nice.
- Here, here, here! Let's sit here.
What?
Isn't that Ji Hoon?
Hey, old student.
I think I like you too.
What should I do?
Lee Ji Hoon!
What are you doing here?
No. It's isn't like it seems. What I mean is that my plans got canceled...
What's wrong with him?
I thought you said you were busy so what's this?
No. What I mean is... Say hi to her, she is a female trainee mate.
I'm not a trainee.
I'm Do Hye Ri.
Hey, you're so pretty.
- What?
- Are you here together to eat dinner?
Yes, because someone said they were busy with a sudden appointment.
I'm glad I didn't go home to eat alone in the end.
See you later.
Eat a lot.
With wrap girl.
What? Hey...
It's been a long while since I last heard this sound.
By the way, what's a wrap girl?
A wrap girl is a girl who makes a wrap for you. It's similar to a date with a girl.
What's a wrap girl supposed to be? Ah. You're my rap girl.
- When did I make a wrap for you?
- Look at you.
You're a woman who always yells at me like a female rapper. You're a rap girl.
- Right.
- What? What is it?
The wrap girl is giving him a wrap again.
As expected, that's what a wrap girl does.
Don't care about someone else's table.
I guess that's the power of genes.
- What are you talking about?
- It's about Ji Hoon.
He looks like a geek, but this is the first thing I like about him. That pretty girl.
Awesome (thumbs up)!
Oh, it's natural that female trainees are pretty. Why are you so worked up about it?
Unlike this rap girl here who is so-so...
What? What was that? Do you want to die?
Here. Eat one too. I'll be a wrap boy for you this time.
One piece of meat, and some garlic for your health.
Here comes your wrap.
Rock, paper, scissors!
What was that?
- You eat it.
- Why?
That must be her. The girl you like.
Be quiet. Just eat some meat. It's burning.
Get home safely.
Pretty. See you next time.
We're going.
Hey. I'm hungry.
Something sweet this time. Hey, buy me an ice-cream.
♫  Twinkle even more today ♫
What is it?
Let's play on the claw machine. Hey, Lee Ji Hoon! Hurry up!
Oh, that sounds good!
♫ This world is beautiful ♫
♫  It’s so warm ♫
- Come quickly.
- What is all this?
What? Wait, let me see.
This item is totally thumbs up!
♫ Reach out your hand to touch mine ♫
Hey, choose one. I'll get it for you on the first try.
This one, this one! Please pull that doll out for me.
Okay, okay. I got it.
What are you doing Lee Ji Hoon? Your wrap girl said she wants that doll.
♫ So the whole world can hear ♫
♫  I wanna confess to you ♫
♫ And I have something to say ♫
- Here this way.
- Hey.
- I said this way.
- Here.
♫  I’ll tell you ♫
- This way. To the right side.
- That way?
♫ I love you ♫
- To the left side.
- Why?
- Hey!
- You got it.
Oh! I got it.
One more.
Great. This is the last one left.
You! Do you know how many times you've already played?
Please one last time. One last time.
All right. This the last time.
Okay, here I go.
- Let me try this time.
- Okay.
♫  I’m a little behind you ♫
♫  So I can always protect you ♫
I can do it.
Hey, not like that.
What are you doing?
♫ Like a bodyguard I will protect you ♫
Wow! I almost pulled it out after several tries but he just stole it like this from me.
This...
It's not my taste, but I'll keep it on my bed for you.
Thank you, Oppa.
Something will be frustrating again.
The Best Hit
- Let me do it, Father.
- Leave it to me.
Yes, it's Gwang Jae. You said schedule?
What schedule?
Ah, you're here. Have you eaten dinner?
I don't care about dinner.
That commercial, that digestive medicine commercial. Did you say you were going to do that?
Ah, you mean the gimbap one?
Yes. Hey, why wouldn't I do it when they're paying money for it?
If you decide yourself to do it your way, then what should I do?
But, there's an image you've been protecting till now.
So what? The Pure Fairy?
I'll take off the Pure Fairy costume,
and I'll wear the gimbap costume instead.
No way. That's never going to happen.
World Entertainment
- What have you been doing that you just now got here?
- I was at the store.
Your wrap girl is pretty.
- Wrap girl?
- The girl who gave you a wrap.
Hey! What? There is nothing going on between us.
A woman knows other women for sure. She definitely likes you.
How come a pretty girl like her happened to like someone like you?
Bro. Who is this wrap girl?
- It's Do Hye Ri.
- Poisonous Do Hye Ri?
Hey, by any chance did Poisonous Do Hye Ri give you a wrap?
You'll be late. Get out quickly.
Wow! That's awesome!
Did you like it?
Everyone is gone.
Yes, Gwang Jae.
First, let's reconstruct the day I came here.
Listen carefully.
The current me is the Yoo Hyeon Jae who came here on June 2, 1993.
- This is me now. Okay?
- Fine.
Also, the Yoo Hyeon Jae you know is the past Yoo Hyeon Jae that has been living here since that day.
Also, this person has gone missing.
Missing.
These two are different people.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
Anyway, what you need to explain to me is...
From the day I came over here, until the day I went missing,
how the past Yoo Hyeon Jae lived in 1993. That's the part in question.
Since there is no way for me to know how I lived back then either.
I don't know that either. I didn't keep in touch with you.
Perhaps the police would have investigated my case after I disappeared in 1994. How did it go?
Were you investigated, too?
Well, it was just a formality since I was your manager.
The suspect
I caught you. I caught you.
Okay then. Let me know when you remember it.
On the day of the typhoon,
after the past me went out, Chairman Soondae and his people went through this place.
You've been living here. Did you ever tear out the rooftop room or anything?
Goodbye.
That idiot!
Darn it.
Search the room. I'm sure it's hidden somewhere here.
- Yes, I understand.
No, never. Not at all.
After you left, Mi Yeong moved into the rooftop room and lived there.
- Who is Mi Yeong?
- It's President Soon Tae's daughter.
- She's Mal Sook's mom.
- That's right.
Would you come back here?
Hey. When you left, we really became enemies.
It's because of the money.
You'd have taken all the money somewhere else to use it, and you would have just splurged it on odd things for sure.
That's what we thought back then.
You know what it is, right?
Music Notes
The Great Yoo Hyeon Jae.
Oh, this is...
That's right. My composition notebook.
Maybe, this could unravel the mystery.
What do you mean by that?
My unreleased songs in this notebook...
They've become hit songs 20 years later.
Doesn't it seem too strange?
Hey, do you think it makes sense for you to talk about things making sense when you're like this?
Ah, I admit it.
Anyway.
If someone is selling the songs in 2017 that I wrote in this notebook back in1993,
then that means that guy is definitely familiar with me for sure.
Who is that guy?
- MJ.
- What?
Yeong Jae.
Well, I will have to meet with those guys soon.
There is one more important fact.
It seems like the money is still in the rooftop room.
What are you saying all of a sudden? Right. Let's hear what you have to say.
Why are you so sure that you still have the money hidden in this room?
New writings appeared here.
What did you write all these?
I didn't write them, but letters keep appearing.
After that day, Yoo Hyeon Jae in 1994 must-have written them.
And his writings are appearing one by one as time goes by.
What?
Look here. "Rooftop."
"Floor." I knocked on every single part of the floor here.
I couldn't have hidden it here because it's cement.
Then...
Hey, Choi Woo Seung.
Why are you here?
The door passcode is your birthday.
That's right. Right there.
Oppa, how come there is nothing you can't do?
Does it feel nice? Do you think it's getting better?
What?
Yes.
Oppa, do you really want to learn how to do this properly?
What?
I'm talking about massage. I'll send you to study abroad. What do you think?
Hey, what do you mean by that?
Oppa, you're so cute when you get angry.
I was just kidding. I was kidding.
How's it going on with World Entertainment's building?
Ah, I really considered our old times' sake, so I was just going to lend them some money, but Gwang Jae, that punk got mad.
I was so taken aback. He's even so prideful.
Whatever! I'll do it as I planned.
I don't understand. Why do you want to have that old building?
Just because. We can build the trainee's dormitory and we can open fan merch shops for our kids there.
It'll look great! Star Punch Town. I think that'll be awesome!
Then let's just lend them the money so that they can repay the loan.
What do you mean? It has to be foreclosed and put up for auction quickly so that we can take it away.
That's not going to work. It doesn't look good either.
We'd rather lend the money and put up the building as collateral.
Then we'd be the one holding the debenture (loan certificate) instead of the bank.
Ah, I see.
As expected, you look so pretty when you do this.
Ah! I'm late for a meeting.
You have to come in early.
What?
Yes.
Rooftop. Floor. Cash. A way to get in...
I'll be late for my first vocal training. I'll go first.
It feels strange to go to work at the company with you like this?
That's true. Then I'll be seeing you at work from now on?
I wish I could but I'm going to give up being a trainee.
I've been thinking about it for a few months.
If I couldn't debut this time around, I'd just give up.
You're the first one I'm telling you this.
Won't you regret it?
No one even knows how high up these dropouts, whom you threw in the trash, can reach in the future.
I'm an idiot for coming to borrow money from a guy like you.
Your money? Even if you lend it to me, I won't accept it for sure! You bastard!
No. I won't regret it.
It's your first day at work, but my last day at work.
It's incredible how we always miss each other.
What did you say?
Nothing.
Hey!
By the way, what are you going to do with your wrap girl?
I told you she is just a friend.
Of course, she is. She flirts with her friend and gives him a wrap!
I have someone I like.
Oh, that's great.
Who is it?
Well, it's just someone I've known for a long time.
For a long time?
There aren't many people you know.
- You know her too.
- Do I know her?
Who is it?
- Are you now happy to hear that?
- Of course.
My slave friend, I'm happy you're growing like this lately.
Did you confess to her?
It got screwed up each time.
Lee Ji Hoon!
Woo Seung!
Say Hi. He's a year above us.
Oh, I'm Woo Seung's boyfriend.
You're embarrassing me.
What? Why did you ask for me?
Oh. Just because the weather was nice.
I mean because the weather is okay.
So, what?
Hey, Choi Woo Seung. Pay attention, listen to me.
I li—
What?
I'm saying, I—
- You want to kill me?
- No!
- Then what!
I, actually, I li—
No that is, ah dammit.
Don't fret over it, and just go for it! And make it work this time.
What does she hide like this?
I have a lot to do while I'm here!
Help me out, come on.
What's wrong?
Ah really, aargh!
♫ I thought I could catch them ♫
♫  The moments I dreamed of ♫
♫  So I walked strongly ♫
♫ With faith without reason ♫
♫  I kept going without giving up ♫
♫ I thought if I gave it my all ♫
♫  It will all happen before my eyes ♫
♫ In the end, I’ll get it, I pray every day ♫
Good morning, I am Lee Ji Hoon, a new trainee.
Uh?
Aaah, sure sure, work hard!
If there's something you don't know, just ask me.
Yes, Sunbae.
Oho, Bro!
Be comfortable, comfortable.
Relax.
I like your eyes.
They're glittering, just like the eyes of a celebrity.
Thank you, Sunbae.
You're well done.
Ah.
Hello, sunbaenims!
I am a new trainee, MC Drill!
Oh, you're full of fighting spirit!
Thank you!
♫  Why must I throw myself into the responsibilities of the world? ♫
♫ Why do I have to endure that pain? ♫
♫  The world won’t leave me alone ♫
Lee Ji Hoon
♫ I can only avoid it and hide ♫
♫  If there is a God, please hear me out ♫
♫  This is all that I can do ♫
♫  And I hate it ♫
♫  I can only walk on a path of thorns ♫
♫ But I’m closing my eyes and shouting in my heart ♫
♫ I pray for my dream ♫
It's an entertainment company, but the work we do is the same as any other company.
- If you have anything you're curious about, ask me.
- Yes.
I'll diligently do everything you ask me.
Then, what kind of work should I do?
Just take everything you're asked to do as your job.
Yes.
♫  Because I still have a dream to fulfill ♫
♫ I have a dream ♫
- What the...
- I'm sorry.
- Oh!
- It's Second Place!
- Pardon?
Ooh, so you got the intern position.
Ah, well.
Where are you going?
I'll move it for you.
Ah no no, it's fine.
It's not fine to me.
- Give it.
- No give it to me, I'll do it!
Give it!
Are you okay?
That's bad.
I have to use it right away.
- My wrist.
- Sorry?
Exactly the same as your signature, and this many?
Why? Is it too difficult?
- Ouch. Give it, then.
- Ah, no.
Shouldn't he be signing it himself?
The fans would be disappointed that I'm doing it instead.
I also want to do it, but because of someone ... It became like this.
Once I've done all this, I'm done, right?
There are still some left, though. And I have a performance, of all things.
How many is that? I think it'll be fine if you do a thousand.
What?
Wait a minute.
What!
You. You'll have to do something I ask of you.
I'm busy.
What's busying you? You're jobless.
Hey, you, uhm.
Ah, forget it.
H-Hey. This little, really!
What? Is is too difficult?
Ahh, give it, give it.
It's fine, it's fine.
Okay, quickly call and tell them to bring me all thousand.
And this, and this, pile them up properly in front of me. You can do this much, right?
And give me a glass of cold water.
Sorry?
Go!
Wow, it's exactly the same.
Go.
I ...
If I start shooting commercials and being active here and there, won't we need a part-timer?
A part-timer?
Recruiting a sales person.
You have just found a part-timer.
Who...?
Ah! Hi, you're Ji Hoon's friend, right?
- Hey, do you even know what kind of job this is?
- I'll do it.
- I'll do it. What do you think?
- Mmmh...
What's your name, Ji Hoon's friend?
Sorry?
Ah. My name, uhm, Ddabo—
D-Dda Bon... Da B—
Da meaning many, Bong meaning happiness, Kim Da Bong.
Da Bong?
- It's really funny!
- What a joke, really.
Then, your age. Twenty-three? Four?
I cannot tell you more.
Everyone has something they want to hide.
That's right, everyone does.
Madam, you also do?
Well, since you're Ji Hoon's friend, well for now...
I'm against it. We'll hire a female part-timer, a female.
The delicateness of a woman, the softness and even the kindness.
I'm confident in showing them.
- No no, not possible!
- It's a pass for me!
I like that you're refreshing.
You somehow feel like family, and it makes me feel warm here.
Thank you!
Oh, and we sometimes have to do deliveries. Do you know how to drive?
Of course! I am a splendid driver.
What is it?
Ah, it's nothing.
For work, please come the day after tomorrow, Monday.
Yes.
Oh, welcome!
- What should I give you?
- What is delicious?
If you ask about what's delicious, well.
This! What you have here.
He's good.
Ah, really.
Oh, hey give me some of that deer antler thing.
My body is so feeble these days, I don't have any energy.
Have this, your energy will come back.
Okay.
But are you coming back from somewhere?
That, you know... I can't remember again. You know, where you put money, and they can lend you some too.
And it gets robbed sometimes too.
- The bank?
- That's it, the bank, the bank.
Why can't I remember words theses days? It's driving me crazy.
So, did you talk about the extension of the term?
Hey, forget about an extension. They gave you an ultimatum.
At most, you have about a week. If you go over it,
they'll proceed with the auction no matter what.
Is that so?
So why did you do that mess with Yeong Jae and create this mess, really?
Just, I don't really know, I suddenly lost my temper.
But do you really have nowhere you can get money from?
I've already borrowed everywhere I could and spent everything.
Tell me. About Bo Hee,
if she had shot that commercial, you'd be able to take care of this pressing matter.
That is, Bo Hee contacted that company on her own.
saying she'd shoot the commercial.
Really?
What? Why are you entering someone else's room as you please?
Just, I'm sorry about earlier.
Right, slave. You keep on forgetting your position.
No but, I also started a part-time job, you see.
What kind?
Well, I have to do what I can to reimburse you as fast as possible,
and they were lacking manpower at the bakery.
Ah really, why are you moving around like this?
Oh!
Get out.
Okay, I get it. I'm going out.
But what's the passcode here? Shh.
Do you think I would tell you? Shh.
Get out.
The Best Hit
♫ The stars floating in the night sky ♫