The Best Hit
♫ The stars floating in the night sky ♫
♫ Twinkle even more today ♫
♫ Like your eyes, like your lips ♫
Yoon Si Yoon
♫ They make my heart flutter  ♫
♫ Beautiful day  ♫
Lee Se Young
♫ And I have something to say ♫
Kim Min Jae
♫ Something to tell ♫
Cha Tae Hyun
♫ I wanna shout out your name to the sky ♫
♫ I’ll tell you ♫
♫ I love you ♫
♫ It’s a beautiful day ♫
I showed my skills for the first time in a while ...
Why isn't he coming?
He isn't answering his phone either.
Ah, everything cooled down.
Thumbs Up!
Why are you so late?
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I was busy the whole day.
Oh my God! What is this aroma? It smells so delicious.
I was going to eat.
Looks like you're in luck when it comes to eating.
Luck for eating? More like, I'm in luck when it comes to my girlfriend.
You can't just say that you're dating me.
- Go on and wash your hands.
- Alright.
Choi Woo Seung. Bang, bang, bang!
What is that?
Receive the gun of love!
Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang!
I'll go wash my hands.
Receive the gun of love. Bang, bang, bang!
So that's how you do it.
Bang, bang!
It's hard.
♫ No, no, no ♫
♫ After a long night passes ♫
♫  And tomorrow comes ♫
And so, and so? Can you do it?
♫  Will I be closer to my dream?  ♫
♫  Or will I be frozen like my clock?  ♫
♫ Light in the sky ♫
♫  The sky of my youth ♫
♫  Even if frozen in a long time  ♫
♫  Some day, fly fly fly ♫
♫ what makes you beautiful, beautiful, beautiful life  ♫
♫  Life is still beautiful ♫
♫  Until I reach my dreams ♫
♫  Some day ♫
CEO.
Yes? I was going to call you here. About MJ—
Yes, I'm here because of that.
Please have a look at this.
What is this?
Singer MJ puts his life on the line and apologizes out of guilty conscience, "I have never written songs."
What is he doing, this rascal!
It looks like he caused trouble first.
Related news: MJ's shocking confession ... No official stance from Star Punch
Like this, it makes the company's responsibility look bigger as if we had the central role!
What should we do?
Entertainment Scoop's Department Head Park In Woo
Aish...
Ah, this jerk causes trouble when he leaves.
Is Gwang Jae not supervising the kid, or what?
- How is public opinion on the internet?
- Half of it is not good.
But half is backing him up, saying he at least confessed his guilty conscience.
On the fans' side, they are saying they were moved by his courage to confess.
They shouldn't be! Why are they being moved by this?
This is making me so mad, really!
The reporters will keep on trying to get in touch.
Say we don't know, no matter what. Say he deviated by himself.
What's this?
Oh? Mal Sook, where's Grandpa?
I don't know. He wasn't here when I fell asleep yesterday.
And when I woke up, he still wasn't here.
Did he not come home yesterday?
Ah, how much alcohol did he consume?
Your call cannot be connected, you will be sent to voicemail.
Is he sleeping somewhere?
Right. I think President Soondae should go to the hospital to see a doctor.
Why should President do that? Who on earth is as healthy as he is at his age?
I'm not sure of the exact circumstances, but that is it. He must go.
Ah really, why is the old man not answering his phone?
Where are you, huh? Goodness.
How would I know?
You're Bo Hee, right?
What's with this ahjussi?
Oh my, what's with him?
It's not her.
How refreshing.
What are you doing, Old man?
Well, excuse me. It's because my legs hurt.
- Pardon?
- I have to get there, but
I don't know where I am.
Excuse me... When you go, take me with you.
I'm not a taxi. Where would I take you? Get off, now.
Hey person, it's because my legs hurt.
My feet hurt.
Ah dammit, this old fogey.
Hey, get out! Get out!
- Alright, alright.
- Please get out!
- Ah, wait.
- Tsk.
This young folk is quite cold-hearted.
Ah, my throat is dry and I'm hungry.
Where is this, really?
Ow, my legs. Ow, my legs.
Ow, my feet.
He didn't go there either?
No. Yes, I understand.
Ah, where on earth did he go?
Grandpa?
Huh? Yeah.
The thing is, he isn't calling to let me know where he is.
Ah, I'm s-sorry. I'm a mess.
Oh no, I am the one who is sorry. Doing that on my own accord—
Don't say that. If you did something wrong, getting it out is the right thing to do!
Then... the company has no problems, right CEO?
I told you there are no problems!
Grandfather... he's really okay, right?
Even if problems come up, I'll deal with them myself.
Isn't that something I should do?
Hey, you all shouldn't worry and instead work hard for your debut, okay?
Our MJ...
For the time being, get a good rest. Well, we can't really do anything. You should rest.
Go, go on, go.
- Okay.
The investment hasn't come in yet, has it?
Huh? Y-Yeah.
And on top of that, MJ's news blew up. Needless to say, they'll be hesitating even more.
But they promised me for sure, so it should be fine.
What if we debuted on the internet?
They do that a lot these days, I heard.
Or there is also a broadcast that Drill is doing, we could start there.
Sorry. I'm making you worry again.
I know that you're working the hardest.
And that if it wasn't for you, I wouldn't have been able to start.
I'm trying to start with others' money, without having any pump-priming funds.
Honestly, it is a bit beyond my power.
But still, it'll get better very soon.
It's just that the first step is the hardest.
Oh? Da Bong!
What's going on? You didn't come to work.
Did you come to fetch me?
Of course.
Is there something going on?
- Let's go on a date.
- What?
I want to go on a date. Where do people go nowadays?
♫ Fool, you have no choice but to love me ♫
♫  Only to you, I can give my all ♫
No, no, that's not it— Hey, hey!
♫  My hope, it’s all you ♫
♫  And what I wanna say is ♫
♫  I only love you ♫
♫ Yes, fool, I have a lot to say to you too ♫
♫  All day, I wrote down funny things that happened ♫
Yes!
♫  I’ll tell you all of it as I slowly fall asleep  ♫
♫  I’ll tell you stories cozy like the clouds ♫
♫  At night, it’s too dark but ♫
♫  I’ll be your roof, don’t worry ♫
♫ You don’t have to say anything, I have no choice but to love you ♫
♫ You wrap your arms around my neck, I have no choice but to hug you ♫
♫ I look at you but I miss you ♫
♫  When I tell myself that, I really do miss you ♫
♫  I don’t wanna miss a single moment ♫
This card means that you two meeting was fate.
♫ I can’t fall asleep until you fall asleep  ♫
Of course, it was fated.
♫  Moments I don’t wanna forget  ♫
It looks like you are very strong, Miss.
♫  I blink and capture the moment in my heart. Good night  ♫
Wow, this gave me goosebumps! Look at this.
♫ Fool, you have no choice but to love me  ♫
And so, which concerns?
Depending on how you will behave, Mister ...
♫  Only to you, I can give my all  ♫
♫ Remember my love, my eyes, my story ♫
♫  My hope, it’s all you ♫
Whoa, there is so much! So it has been completed!
♫  And what I wanna say is  ♫
♫  I only love you ♫
♫ You’re a girl who looks good in PJs ♫
♫  Fall asleep in my arms today as well ♫
♫  With that innocent face, you act like a fox ♫
♫  So I’m completely deceived ♫
♫  I think about your day ♫
♫  About how you feel these days ♫
So they couldn't win, in the end.
♫  You smile so easily, but sometimes  ♫
♫ Your tears fall on your shoes like a rain shower ♫
♫  I’ll be your summer ♫
It's okay.
♫  Like the cozy clouds in the sky, I’ll be your eternal smile ♫
♫  Will you be my painting? My ocean? ♫
♫  You shine like the stars inside of me ♫
♫ In order for the two little dots, you and me, to meet ♫
♫  We drew lines upon lines ♫
♫ And we became one picture ♫
♫ I love all of those processes ♫
♫ You make me beautiful ♫
♫ I like it when you look at me from by my side ♫
♫  I like it when you lean on my shoulder ♫
♫ Remember My love, my eyes ♫
What's that, what's that?
What's this? Sunscreen? What is it?
Wait. What is this?
- Why are you putting so much?
- You might get sunburned.
♫ Oh, oh, oh ♫
♫ Oh, oh, oh. Yeah! ♫
I forgot for a bit because of you.
What?
Who I am, where we met, how I lived.
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
Come to think of it, to me, the twenty-first century is you only.
Choi Woo Seung.
What are you saying?
To me, it's like that.
Yes. I am Lee Gwang Jae, the one who made the report earlier.
Lee Soon Tae. Born in 1948.
No, he hasn't come home yet.
He doesn't have dementia, though. He is healthy.
Yes. Yes, I will be waiting for your call. Yes.
Where is he?
Do I need to borrow money?
Once we're done paying off the debt, there won't even be much left.
Sender: Yoo Hyeon Jae / Recipient: Lee Soon Tae
Right. I heard I sent something to President Soon Tae.
- What? When?
- Huh?
It should be around 1994. I don't remember, you see.
What did you send?
When I went out that time, I said I would pay some amount for the expenses.
Maybe, because it was awkward to meet in person, I sent it by mail. I think it could be this.
How could we find it, then? It's been so many years.
Since you won't meet me, President Soon Tae, I am sending it by mail.
I have paid off the expenses you spent on me all this time, without missing a cent.
Right! I was going to send it to you in cash, but it didn't fit in the envelope.
So I'm just sending it as stocks. It's more fun, you know.
Samsu Electronics Company Share Certificate
500 shares
This, if it's Samsu Electronics, then ...
I-It's f-f-five hundred shares,
so even if it were only 2,500,000 won (≈ $2,500) per share...
1.3 billion?  (≈ $1.3 million)
I'm sorry.
I'm here now. You waited a long time, right?
No, Dad.
But why did my dad get so old?
My handsome, popular dad.
You little... You're the same as always.
It's me, well.
How long did you wait here?
Until you came.
I watched people passing by,
and I thought of the past.
I'm sorry I couldn't become a daughter you could be proud of, Dad.
I obstinately followed someone you were opposed to, to live with them.
I'm sorry about that, too.
I always wanted to gain your acknowledgment.
We didn't have a lot of time given to us.
Right?
If we'd had more time,
you would've definitely understood.
I'm sorry, too.
All of this ... I was being stubborn.
Hey... as if.
It was because you care for me, Dad. I know that.
You resented me a lot, didn't you?
Not at all.
Not even once.
There is not a moment I wasn't proud of you.
You're the best in my life, you.
You're the best thing I did in my life, you.
For taking care of Mal Sook so well,
thank you, Dad.
Mal Sook
At her school, Mal Sook
was told to draw her mom's face, but
she drew me.
You'll forgive me, right? Right?
We're family, why do you ask?
Dad, you're also the best in my life.
Hey! Where did you go? Huh?
Where did you go?
What should we do? What is another thing you want to do?
Not sure. I think we did everything already.
Your dream is so simple, what should I do?
Is a dream that important?
If I only meet you, then I'll have no time.
Slowly do things, slowly.
Is today the only day you have?
Okay. Slowly.
Door
Look here, Police Officer.
Yes, Elder?
Well, about that... I have a home.
That— My house—
Yes, please tell me.
Ah, for goodness' sake, seriously.
That house... I have a house.
I can't find the house.
My house!
You! If you look, I get bothered.
I'm trying to capture all of you in my eyes.
- What?
- Even if I close my eyes, I still see you.
Little by little...
Hey, look at this. No joke, look at these goosebumps!
You aren't even acknowledging my sincerity.
What is it?
Who is it?
Me. Open the door.
Oh!
Go in here.
My shoes, my shoes!
Be quiet.
- What are you doing, open the door!
- Okay!
Oh...
- What were you doing?
- Huh?
Studying! Studying.
How can you leave people standing in front of the door like that?
Come in, have a seat.
Wow, you said you had moved, but you've hit it big.
Why did you buy all these?
These are things you should give to people who just moved in. You're not going to do a housewarming?
Ah, I'm sorry. I couldn't focus because I have a lot going on.
When I do some cleaning...
Shouldn't you give us something to drink?
Yeah, yeah, wait here.
Ah, it's okay though.
We dropped by on our way back from the practice room. We were curious to see where you moved.
How much is the rent for this kind of room?
Ah, an Unni at work had to leave it because of a situation, so I got it for cheap.
Right! It looks like you took one of my shirts, thinking it was yours.
What? No! There's no way.
No, when you disappeared, it disappeared with you for sure.
It looks like it's with your clothes.
Later, when it comes out, I'll bring it to you.
The thing is, that was my most treasured clothing.
This is your wardrobe, right?
You— How could you open a girl's wardrobe as you please?
Yeah, she said she'd find it for you next time.
I'm saying, let's quickly take a look.
Just once, just once. Oh?
It doesn't open. Wait a minute.
Oh, that is. It doesn't open well. Next time, I'll—
Better to do these kinds of things when men are around.
Step back.
It's really fine.
I won't look inside. I'll just fix this for you.
Drill, grab it here.
Let's count to three and pull.
One. Two. Three!
I said it's fine!
It's really stiff.
We fixed it for you, didn't we? Okay, let's take a look—
Hey! Really, you two!
How can you rummage through a girl's wardrobe like this, as you please?
Even for people without manners, that's too much.
That's true, it's not right.
Wait a second. Move a bit.
Here. Found it.
Look! It did come together with you.
This shirt is limited edition.
- Let's go home now.
- What?
- But we just arrived.
- We have to go out at dawn tomorrow.
Do a proper house-warming later.
Yeah, yeah, sure. Got it.
Let's at least have some instant noodles. The detergent cost us 30,000 won  (≈ $30).
They say it'll rain soon, and there's even a typhoon coming later.
- Let's go now.
- Come on.
R-Right.
Friend. I'll see you next time.
Yeah, sure. Go well.
Here.
Too bad you're already leaving. You should have had some tea at least.
Bye, Choi Woo Seung.
Yes, go safely!
Here. Oh my.
Are you okay?
Do you think they saw you?
I don't think they did.
That was so hard, really.
Last time, Red Dragon wore this t-shirt, did you see?
Wait a second.
Here. Found it.
Gwang Jae.
What is it?
I am sorry for inconveniencing you.
But if you're ill, you should tell me! Then I would know!
Why do you always ...
Ah, I really should have stopped seeing you.
Gwang Jae, kiddo.
You see, let me make a request.
My Mal Sook, I'll ask you to take care of her.
It looks like I'm all done, now.
Is it the time for you to be worried about Mal Sook?
I'm not worried about anything other than Mal Sook.
♫  I pray with my hands together ♫
This is nice.
Still, I feel relieved now that I saw you.
Okay?
Ouch. Ouch, my leg.
Why am I feeling this uneasy?
What?
Is it because there's a typhoon coming?
What is this?
A compass.
What?
No matter where you go, don't lose your way.
I'm not a little kid.
I'm sleepy. I'm going to sleep first.
What? Okay.
♫ I didn’t know love ♫
Tomorrow, make me some omurice. I want to eat some, suddenly.
♫  I guess I’m still too young  ♫
♫ Whenever I looked at you ♫
Okay.
♫  My heart fluttered for some reason ♫
♫ Your clear eyes ♫
♫  They were so kind ♫
♫ I couldn’t fall asleep ♫
♫  I could only think about you ♫
♫ If you ♫
♫  If you come to me ♫
♫  I’ll feel like I have the world ♫
♫ I’m shouting to the sky ♫
♫  It’s only you ♫
♫ I’m closing my eyes, with all my heart ♫
♫  I’m calling out to you ♫
♫ I love you, I really want you ♫
♫  Are you listening? ♫
♫ To me? ♫
♫ Your white hands ♫
♫  Your black, pretty eyes ♫
♫  You’re the one who makes me breathe ♫
♫  You’ve always been by my side ♫
♫  I was too shy to approach you ♫
♫  To even hold your hand ♫
♫ Do you know my heart? ♫
♫ If you ♫
♫ If you come to me ♫
♫  I’ll feel like I have the world ♫
♫ I’m shouting to the sky ♫
♫  It’s only you ♫
♫ I’m closing my eyes, with all my heart ♫
♫  I’m calling out to you ♫
♫ I love you, I really want you ♫
♫  Are you listening? ♫
♫ I know it took too long ♫
♫  For me to figure out how I feel about you ♫
♫ I wanna hold your hands ♫
♫  I won’t let go of you ♫
♫ If you ♫
♫  If I lose you ♫
♫  There is no reason anymore ♫
♫ Always, until always ♫
♫  I’ll stay by your side ♫
♫ I’m closing my eyes, with all my heart ♫
♫  I’m calling out to you ♫
♫ I love you, I really want you ♫
♫  Are you listening? ♫
♫ To me? ♫
Additional scenes
Is Lee Soon Tae here?
Hey, Gwang Jae. You're here.
Goodness. What are you doing here?
Well what happened was... Things just ended up this way.
What is...
Why is this on your foot? Oh, right.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
- My goodness.
- What happened to your shoe?
- What?
That is, I'm also wondering.
I do remember taking it off just once, but not about after that.
But then you should have called me!
Why do you make people feel so anxious?
I'm sorry, guy.
You're the guardian?
Yes? Yes.
Please sign here, and then you can take him with you.
Ah, yes.
Thank you. Good work. Let's go.
- Okay, let's.
- Ah, shoot.
But I'm fine.
It's fine, rascal.
Can you walk?
Of course, I can! I've been walking all day.
Oh my.
Well then, all you work hard!
I'll be taking my leave!
Elder.
What is it?
You should leave the hat here.
But this is my hat!
- It's mine, though.
- Wh-What?
Oh my, would you look at this? Sorry, sorry.
Your hat is here, Elder.
No wonder, my hat felt a bit big.
Let's go! Let's go, let's go.
♫ If you ♫
♫ If you come to me ♫
♫  I’ll feel like I have the world ♫
♫ I’m shouting to the sky ♫
♫  It’s only you ♫
♫ I’m closing my eyes, with all my heart ♫
The Best Hit
♫  I’m calling out to you ♫
You have to help me out a bit.
How come you have zero interest in me?
I have to look for someone urgently.
What?
♫ Are you listening? ♫
♫ I know it took too long ♫
Oh wait. It's here.
Music Top Ten
JB
You're ready, right?
I'm relying on you.
Excuse me. I'm nothing. But I'll make you happy.
Thumbs up! Thumbs up!
Thumbs up. Thumbs up.
♫  I won’t let go of you ♫
The Best Hit
♫ The stars floating in the night sky ♫