♫  I like you as your presence is like the gentle breeze’s caress  ♫
♫  I’m softly embracing all the little joys I’ve treasured  ♫
♫  The sunset from the backseat becomes precious because of you  ♫
♫  All the yearnings for beauty on this day  ♫
Three, two, one... Jump!
♫  Let the kite bear witness to our tearful memories  ♫
♫  Let the wind convey the unspoken words of love  ♫
♫  I once was in pursuit of your silhouette but my timid heart held me captive  ♫
♫  Grant me one more chance to courageously meet your gaze  ♫
Hey, My Prince.
Mr. Lin, did you ask to see me?
Su Zaizai.
You can tell me if I've done anything wrong.
I'll change it.
Has A’Rang caused you any trouble when you were tutoring him?
Oh... No, he hasn't.
Well, he also gave me some tutoring. I'm the one that troubles him.
To be honest, English has always been his weakness.
His grades haven't been particularly good since middle school.
His parents have always been worried about this.
Your tutoring has been quite effective for him.
His recent progress in grades is obvious.
Thank you.
It was Rang...
I mean Zhang Lurang is a smart guy.
He's a quick learner.
I'm saying this as A’Rang's uncle.
I should thank you.
Oh, by the way, if you have any difficulties in Math,
you can ask me anytime.
Of course, you can ask A’Rang, too.
Huh?
Oh, okay.
I'll definitely ask you if I have any questions.
Thank you, Mr. Lin.
Let's go.
Bye-bye.
Hey, Zaizai.
Why did Mr. Lin want to see you during the break?
It was about tutoring Zhang Lurang.
I thought he was going to scold us for messing around.
But instead, he thanked me.
He was quite happy that Zhang Lurang's English had improved.
Mr. Lin is really good to Zhang Lurang.
He does.
It'd be great if I had an uncle like that.
Jiang Jiang, I won't be going home with you today.
- I still...
- I get it.
Tutoring.
Your happiness is written all over your face. Go quickly.
You can go back with Gu Ran.
No, thanks.
Go on now.
Excuse me. There is something on your skirt.
Hey…
Do you have it?
I only have this.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Why are there still so many people around?
Gu Ran! Gu Ran, come here.
What's up?
Jeez, say something.
Why are you over there like that?
Are... Are you ready to head home?
Can you give me a ride?
Not yet. I'm playing basketball for a while.
Uh...
Wait here for me for a while, okay?
Hey.
Gosh.
It'll be late when he's done playing.
Forget it. What am I expecting from him anyway?
Jiang Jia.
Brother Qianyu?
What's wrong?
I...
Well... I have a cramp...
Well... my uh... stomach...
What am I saying?
Where's your home?
I'll give you a ride home.
Brother Qianyu,
would it be too troublesome for you to take me home?
It's okay. My home is nearby.
So it's on the way.
Tomorrow is the school anniversary performance.
Would you be okay to do it?
Yes, I'm feeling lot better now.
Then do your best tomorrow.
Okay, let's do our best together.
♫  slowly blew past your left ear and whispered something to you  ♫
♫  The balcony is filled with hibiscus blooming in midsummer  ♫
Are you taking pictures of the sunset?
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
Today's sunset is beautiful.
♫  And there is a soul that is anxious when it's about to meet you  ♫
♫  What should I prepare?  ♫
♫  My palms are sweaty  ♫
What's the matter?
It's okay. We'll go after you're done taking pictures.
♫  Does meeting me make you happy too?  ♫
♫  The summer breeze makes our hearts beat faster  ♫
♫  I dream of castles and colorful whirpools  ♫
♫  When the wind by the sea hears you say you like me too  ♫
This is the most beautiful sunset I've seen.
♫  Don't avoid my eyes anymore  ♫
Today, we gather here
to celebrate the 60th anniversary
of The First High School Affiliated to Jiangyi University.
Today, with an excited heart,
we reminisce about the fast growth
of The First High School Affiliated to Jiangyi University.
Hey, what's our queue number?
The fifth.
Gosh, stop making noise.
I'm trying to memorize my lines.
Where's Su Zaizai?
She just went to get changed.
Her hairstyle is a little complicated.
But she should be...
Wow.
Oh, dear.
It looks so real.
Like a little Cinderella.
Stop talking nonsense.
Next time, I'll let you play Cinderella.
Actually, I think it looks pretty.
Let Brother Qianyu see it too.
Huh?
Where's Brother Qianyu?
I don't know.
I haven't seen him today.
We're about to go on stage. Don't tell me he's not here yet.
Don't worry. I'll look for him.
Relax.
Guys, you should recite your lines in your hearts.
Remember your part. Let's do this together.
Qianyu is injured?
What happened exactly?
I searched everywhere but couldn't find him.
I only got through after making several phone calls.
Brother Qianyu fell off the bike on his way to school.
He's at the hospital now. He probably won't make it.
Is it serious?
Don't worry.
He's fine.
Now we should be worried about the upcoming performance.
What should we do?
Gosh.
Coming next is the fashion show,
"Era of Painted Impressions". Please get ready.
We didn't select a backup prince back then.
Even if we manage to find someone to play the role,
he won't have time to memorize the lines.
Zhang Lurang, can you go on stage?
- Me?
- Yeah.
Why didn't I think of it? A’Rang knows the lines.
Lurang, you must not back down.
You must go on stage.
I have confidence in you.
You can do it.
A’Rang, I told my grandma I'm going on stage.
I don't want to miss the chance to go on stage.
That's right. We've been practicing for so long. Help us out, please.
Help me too, please.
Okay.
I'll try.
Rang Rang, don't be nervous.
Just do what we did in a common rehearsal.
Are you nervous?
No, I'm not.
Just admit that you're nervous.
What's the big deal anyway?
I won't laugh at you.
Actually, I'm a little nervous.
So you're really nervous, huh?
Let me teach you a method.
I guarantee you won't be nervous.
When you go on stage later,
just imagine the audience below as cabbages.
Cabbages?
Yeah.
What's there to be nervous about acting in front of cabbages?
Am I right?
And even if you make a mistake,
what's the harm in a performance for cabbages?
But you still have to be a little nervous.
You see, after all, there's a handsome cabbage like me sitting below the stage.
You're too self-absorbed.
Are you still nervous now?
Well, not really.
The fashion show segment showcasing the characteristics of the era
was truly memorable.
But the excitement doesn't end here.
It's our turn to go on stage.
Break a leg.
All the best.
Let's do this.
Coming up next, please enjoy the classic theater adaptation of "Cinderella"
presented by the Drama Club.
A long, long time ago, there lived a beautiful girl
named Cinderella.
Although her father had left her,
her mother loved her dearly.
Until one day, her mother married a selfish and narrow-minded man.
Father, who is she?
She's so filthy.
She's your stepsister.
Don't worry, my little princesses.
She...
can do the laundry and cook for you.
Why?
From today onward, you are our servant.
We have a professional videographer.
Oh, I... I know.
I'm recording it for Guan Fang's grandma.
She loves watching this.
I see.
Your Highness, no girl in this house can wear the glass slipper.
May I try it?
Didn't you say you only have two daughters in your family?
Your Excellency, I indeed only have two daughters in my family.
This messy girl is just our servant.
She's dirty and will ruin this beautiful shoe.
Take her up to the attic now.
The evil stepsister in the green dress isn't hateful at all.
She's quite cute.
Cute?
Yeah.
Why?
How is she cute?
She even stumbles while walking.
She's as stubborn as a donkey.
How is she cute that way?
You know her?
Then introduce us!
We are not close.
My dear prince, you're like the moon high above
casting a gentle light on the sea.
I admire you from afar,
thinking everything is so beautiful because of you.
But the moon doesn't belong to me, and neither do you.
I used to think that it was the fairy's magic that turned me into a princess.
But when you're standing before me, I realize
that every girl is a princess when she's in front of the one that she loves.
When I fly toward the moon,
the moon is also learning to run forward for me.
♫  I guess I’ve fallen in love with you  ♫
♫  Without any reason  ♫
♫  It’s unexplainable  ♫
♫  I guess it must be the hand of destiny  ♫
It's a reward for your good performance.
♫  That brought you into my life  ♫
Thanks.
♫  The best version of you  ♫
Rang Rang, why do you keep avoiding looking at me?
I won't charge you for looking at me.
♫  You’re the reason I believe in love  ♫
Rang Rang, do I look pretty today?
♫  I'm not afraid of having regrets as long as you’re with me  ♫
♫  Even if it makes it hard for me to let go  ♫
So-so.
You clearly think I look pretty.
♫  But now, I don’t want to hesitate anymore  ♫
I'll go and get changed first.
Hey, wait.
Everyone just finished taking photos.
But I can still take a few more with this roll film.
Shall I take a photo of you two?
Yeah, since you haven't changed yet.
How memorable it'll be.
Well, it does look like it, right?
Look like what?
Well, the prince and the princess.
What else could it be?
Okay, hurry up.
The auditorium will be closing soon.
How about that spot?
Ready.
Come on. Is there a wall between you?
Closer.
Ready. Look at the camera.
One.
Two.
Three.
Grandma.
Yes?
You've watched it so many times.
Aren't you tired of it?
Of course not.
Look how great your acting is.
I can't have enough of this.
Grandma, watch closely.
I'm not even on stage here.
Who says you're not?
See behind the red curtain.
The one who is sneak peeking.
I-Isn't this you?
Your eyesight is even worse than an old lady like me.
I can't believe you could see that.
Hey, you first performed on stage
when you were in kindergarten.
At that time, among the 20 children
who were wearing identical clothes,
I spotted you at one glance.
Don't you think it's strange?
They tried to find you but they couldn't.
But how did I manage to do it right away?
That's because you have a pair of sharp eyes.
Well.
Next time, I'll strive to get the lead role
and stand right in the middle of the stage
so you don't even have to look for me.
You want to be the lead?
To be honest, it'll be hard.
Then don't be the lead.
It's so tiring to be the lead.
They have to shine brightly and make sure everyone can see.
You don't necessarily have to become the sun.
If you're willing to,
you could be a star, a streetlight, or a firefly.
They are all capable of shining.
When they want to shine, they shine.
When they don't feel like shining, they slack off.
Even if you never shine,
some people could see you at a glance.
Grandma, where did you
learn to speak like this?
What a grand speech.
Hey, who recorded this video?
Gu Ran.
You've met him several times.
Did he record it for someone else?
Why weren't you in the video after this part?
Huh? Really?
Let me see.
I guess she does look cute.
Why am I watching her?
Are you going?
Yeah.
Oh.
What a surprise.
Su Zaizai is so popular.
I think they're asking for her contact information.
Gosh. After the anniversary celebration,
many boys have gathered at our classroom door to look at her.
Uh-oh.
Your Cinderella might be taken away.
Hey, are you jealous?
Why would I be jealous?
Hey!
That guy asked me for my WeChat today.
I don't plan to give him.
Why are you suddenly bringing this up?
I want you to trust me.
So I have to let you know.
After all, I'm...
your student.
Students should listen to their teachers.
You told me to study hard and I will.
If you don't say anything, that means you agree with me.
But as your English teacher,
I'm not very satisfied with your performance.
Why?
It's dangerous when a stranger offers drinks.
What if they're bad?
What should I do?
You should yell my name, "Su Zaizai!"
Then I'll appear to get you out of trouble.
Remember what I said?
I'll see you tomorrow.
Su Zaizai.
♫  The gentle summer breeze  ♫
♫  slowly blew past your left ear and whispered something to you  ♫
I...
♫  The balcony is filled with hibiscus blooming in midsummer  ♫
I'll try.
See you tomorrow.
♫  And there is a soul that is anxious when it's about to meet you  ♫
♫  What should I prepare?  ♫
♫  My palms are sweaty  ♫
Our Rang Rang is becoming more adorable.
♫  Does meeting me make you happy too?  ♫
♫  The summer breeze makes our hearts beat faster  ♫
♫  I dream of castles and colorful whirpools  ♫
A’Rang, I heard you're close with Su Zaizai from Class 9.
Do you have her contact information?
I want to make friends with her.
Your meal is on me tomorrow.
♫  Don't avoid my eyes anymore  ♫
Contact information?
Then do you want to give him?
I'll answer on your behalf.
No.
Rang Rang, you must keep the good things for yourself.
What are you doing?
Passers-by would think you're going to have a fight.
I thought you were fearless.
What is so difficult to enter the ward?
I think it's better for us to go in together.
Hey, where are Zhang Lurang and the others?
Are they arriving soon?
We should wait for them then.
A car hit me when I was riding my bicycle.
I just need to wear a cast for some time and it'll be fine.
It's nothing serious.
You guys are too generous.
Oh, Jiang Jia brought all these here by herself.
I told her you can't eat this much alone.
I'll share it with you.
Thank you.
My grandma made this pig's trotter soup.
She said it's good for bone injuries.
Okay.
That's right.
Brother Qianyu, take good care of your injury.
You must be so worried at that time.
Luckily, you saved the day and you guys even won the first prize.
Thank you.
No problem.
Oh, Gu Ran.
I might need your help with something.
What is it?
We need to return several props to the rental place.
Do you have time tomorrow?
We agreed on the return time when we rented them.
Okay, I'll go tomorrow.
Thank you.
Here, let me serve you a bowl.
All right.
You want to go too?
Yeah. There are quite a lot of props.
I'm afraid you might lose them and we have to compensate for them.
So I'll go with you despite the trouble.
Thanks for the help earlier.
Oh. So this is why you're going with me.
Why do you talk so much?
Oh, if I don't have to go, then forget it.
Come on.
It's good to have an extra pair of hands.
Don't leave.
What time tomorrow?
Where should we meet?
I'm almost there, where are you?
I think I lost my way.
But I'll be there soon. One more junction.
Jeez. I wonder who's the one helping out.
Isn't that the guy from before?
Yeah.
Gosh.
If Shen Qianyu were the one waiting here,
she would have probably come running.
Oh, are you waiting for someone?
Do you know me?
Really? How forgetful of you.
You defeated us by one point on the basketball court
and embarrassed us in front of everyone.
Did you forget so soon?
Oh, I remember it now.
My friend said the ball was really good.
Thanks. I'm busy, so I'll go first.
Did I say you can go?
We've been wanting to reclaim that ball for a long time.
Sorry. I'm not interested in playing today.
Wait. Who asked for your opinion, huh?
I said I'm not playing.
Are you deaf?
Say that again?
Gu Ran.
Stand behind me.
Are you protecting me?
Stop talking. Just watch.
You're protecting him?
Who are you?
Huh?
Really?
You let a girl fight for you?
You're jealous because you don't have one.
Me? Jealous?
Fine.
Let's do this.
I have just got the blue-black belt
and I haven't had a place to practice.
♫  On a summer day, a sudden encounter arises  ♫
♫  The story begins with a misunderstanding  ♫
♫  You were sitting in the front row, and I didn't quite like you  ♫
Officer, they're the ones!
♫  With the glasses, you look somewhat absent-minded, re Sol re sol  ♫
♫  I see the ocean waves dancing once again  ♫
Hey!
Stop right there!
♫  While birds fly into the scene, a delightful arrival like yours  ♫
♫  Your sincerity has purified my tears  ♫
♫  And smoothed out the wrinkled past  ♫
♫  Walking around the playground, one lap after another  ♫
♫  Quietly, only the sound of our heartbeats remains  ♫
♫  Look up and gaze ahead  ♫
Hey, what's a blue-black belt?
Well, an almost black belt.
I was worried they wouldn't believe me
if I said I'm a black belt.
What do you think? It sounded very real, right?
Well, actually,
it's supposed to be the red-black belt.
Oh, hello, Mr. Lin.
You're early.
I went to get some fruit.
I see.
By the way, Mr. Lin, in a few days,
is Lu Rang going to join the competition, too?
Yes, he has been studying these days.
He would go to the self-study room on weekends.
Oh, your nephew is the most disciplined in this area.
Hey, are you going to the self-study room this early?
No, I'm going to the aquarium.
This is what we call a balanced life.
He also likes to go out with friends to relax.
You know, boys.
They tend to be more lively.
Yes, you're right.
Are you going out with Gu Ran?
Don't come back too late, okay?
Zhang Lurang.
Hello, Mr. Lin.
Su Zaizai?
We won't take up too much of your time, Mr. Lin.
We'll get going then.
Why is it a girl?
Oh, listen.
Nowadays, girls and
boys get close pretty easily.
Mr. Lin is going to be upset now.
Wait. You said you're going to the aquarium, right?
Then you don't have to rush home tonight.
It's okay if you come home late.
But you must take her home first.
By the way, the weather is getting cold.
When you buy drinks, get something hot.
Do you have money? I'll give you some if you don't have any.
It's okay.
Uncle, I'll get going then.
Okay. Go on.
Mr. Lin, see you.
Okay, see you.
These are all tropical fish here.
Oh, really?
Rang Rang,
you haven't been to the Jiangyi Aquarium before, right?
Yeah.
It's okay. I'm familiar with this place.
I can give you a free tour guide.
Look at that.
It's called salamander.
Look how much it looks like a doll.
So cute.
Children, look at this.
This bright orange fish with two white stripes on its body
is called "clownfish"
Despite its name, it doesn't look like a clown at all.
It's really cute.
Well, I... wasn't entirely wrong.
It does look cute.
I was half right.
Oh, look at that long one over there.
It doesn't look like fish at all.
But it's also fish.
It's called "stingray".
That one is called "stingray"
and it looks like a devil indeed.
Whoa!
Rang Rang. Look at that fish. It's so pretty and cute.
Children, we should learn from this young lady who loves marine life.
- Okay.
- Yes.
The more you look at it, the prettier it gets.
It's so fleshy.
It'll make a good bowl of Sichuan Boiled Fish.
The size is just right.
My pot at home is just this big.
Miss, this young lady wants to eat it.
Don't eat it.
I... I don't plan to eat it now.
She's joking with you. She can't eat it.
She can't eat it.
The young lady won't actually eat it.
She said that because she thought it was cute and she liked it.
Okay?
Really?
Yes.
You're very cute, too.
Rang Rang, I didn't know you were so good at coaxing children.
I'm not.
I was forced to.
Well, can you coax a group of 200-month-old kids?
You don't need to coax.
Kids who are 200 old are sensible.
♫  The crescent moon looks a little like you  ♫
♫  The dazzling moonlight captures my heart like a snapshot  ♫
♫  You said this is the best scenery  ♫
♫  But somehow silently, quietly, our distance is getting closer  ♫
♫  We both realize it, yet we say nothing  ♫
Rang Rang!
♫  So quickly grab your Walkman  ♫
♫  I want to sing you a love song every morning  ♫
Su Zaizai.
♫  And count the twinkling stars in the sky with you  ♫
♫  Love is a long journey with your tender and captivating presence  ♫
♫  It feels like we’re destined to be together  ♫
Hello, we're rehearsing the script.
Beside me is my male lead, Prince Rang Rang.
Su Zaizai,
have you memorized the final paragraph of your lines?
Oh, that?
I used to think that it was the fairy's magic that turned me into a princess.
It wasn't until the clock struck twelve
that I was brought back to reality.
How can I be good enough for you?
♫  Without any reason  ♫
Have you forgotten your lines?
Rang Rang,
I think I've found the reason I always get stuck here.
Why?
It's because I can't accept it.
I think Cinderella is too lowly.
Why isn't she good enough for the prince?
Does only a princess deserve the prince?
I don't think so.
I want to ask Mr. Xiao to change the lines a bit.
Rang, what revision should we make?
♫  You’re the reason I believe in love  ♫
♫  I'm not afraid of having regrets as long as you’re with me  ♫
Maybe we can change it like this.
Perhaps, every girl can become a princess
in front of the one she loves.
♫  Too scared to tell you, “I love you”  ♫
16-year-old girls seem to be able
to constantly immerse themselves in novels and movies,
making it their sweet and lovely secrets.
♫  I guess I’ve fallen in love with you  ♫
♫  Without any reason  ♫
♫  It’s unexplainable  ♫
♫  I guess it must be the hand of destiny  ♫
♫  That brought you into my life  ♫
♫  The best version of you  ♫
♫  You gave me courage and love  ♫
♫  You’re the reason I believe in love  ♫
♫  I'm not afraid of having regrets as long as you’re with me  ♫
♫  Even if it makes it hard for me to let go  ♫
♫  Too scared to tell you, “I love you”  ♫
♫  But now, I don’t want to hesitate anymore  ♫