I want to quit.
Wait, already? It's only your first day!
I'm not cut out for the corporate life.
Huh?
Thanks for waiting.
Here's your coffee.
Thanks.
It's so bitter! And so hot!
This is way too bitter.
I'm so sorry!
Is it still printing?
Almost done.
Done! Thanks for waiting.
Thank you.
What is this?
The front and back are mixed up.
I'm sorry! I'll reprint them right away.
Oh, man.
I'm really not cut out for this.
Aren't you giving up a bit too quickly?
I can't do this.
You haven't even done anything yet.
I don't think I can handle this.
Everyone feels that way at first.
Do they?
Yeah.
What about you? How's school?
Me?
Same as usual.
- Ever since my boyfriend started working,
he's grown distant.
- I totally get it.
- He used to say things like
he wanted to be together all the time.
Students and working adults
have such different values.
I get it. All those work dinners.
They always say they have to entertain clients.
And they end up coming home so late.
I know they can't help it.
But waiting up for them is exhausting, too.
They act like putting work first
is just a given.
And if you complain,
they say you're being selfish.
I want to be understanding.
But it feels like
I'm the only one trying.
We're so understanding.
Totally.
Is everything okay?
It's the same as always.
The campus is the same for the new semester.
And I'm in the same lab.
I see.
Must be nice. Everything's going smoothly for you,
unlike me.