(Flower Boss,
Flower Delivery Service)
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
(Episode 2: I'm Sorry, I Apologize)
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry!
- What are you so sorry for?
(Episode 2: I'm Sorry, I Apologize)
(Episode 2: I'm Sorry,
I Cannot Apologize)
I should have mustered up
my courage earlier.
I hesitated for too long
and lost my chance.
Where is she now?
Why did she quit all of a sudden?
- My goodness.
- What about Mr. Smith?
You reek of alcohol.
Why are you here?
Did you get fired already?
I did see this coming.
Did Mr. Smith come here or not?
He just left. Didn't you see him?
Ro Woon!
Are you Mr. Smith?
I'm Chae Ro Woon.
These flowers are for me, right?
Yes. Well, it's...
I'm... I'm your...
Where is Mr. Smith?
- Who?
- Mr. Smith.
The person who sent me
this bouquet.
- Who is it?
- Well, the thing is...
Actually, I...
I know you can't tell me
even if I ask. I know that.
However, I must find out today.
What kind of person is he? Tell me.
Who is he?
Move the bouquet.
What is he like?
I said, what is he like?
Won't you tell me?
You can't go until you tell me.
I'm sorry.
Stop!
I want to meet him!
It's because today's the last day.
I want to meet him
since today's the final show.
Please take me to Mr. Smith. Please?
Please?
If you can't take me to him,
at least give him this message.
Tell him that I thank him
so much for everything.
Thanks to Mr. Smith,
I was able to go through hard times.
Got it?
Please forward my message.
I'll get going then.
Can I ask you one thing?
How did you know I didn't leave?
Go ahead.
Why are you suddenly
leaving the stage?
That's a secret...
even for Mr. Smith.
Why do you keep calling him
Mr. Smith?
My goodness.
- We weren't eavesdropping.
- Let's go.
That's the alias
Daddy-long-legs used.
John Smith.
My older sister...
committed suicide three years ago.
My sister used to always send me...
bouquets whenever I performed.
Although...
she was no longer in this world,
I kept getting flowers.
I felt like she was still alive.
Mr. Smith...
must be my sister's friend...
or her past lover.
Or perhaps...
Are you still there?
Do you really want to know
who he is?
Don't tell me.
Actually, I want to know,
but I also don't.
I want to remain curious
and let it make my heart flutter.
I can imagine all I want.
Even if my sister isn't around,
I'll act like she is.
I never told this anyone.
How did I end up telling it
in a smelly washroom?
And the men's washroom at that.
On top of that,
I told someone that's super quiet.
"Are you all right?"
"It must have been tough."
You don't even know how to
console someone like that.
My sister was just like you.
She had her mouth shut like a clam.
Sir,
is there something
you want to say to me?
She should have said so
if she was suffering.
She was hurting so much,
yet I didn't hear a peep from her.
In the last three years,
that was the hardest part of all.
Not knowing...
why my sister died.
I was right beside her.
We even shared a room.
Why didn't she tell me?
I wish she had just said...
something.
I must tell her...
so that the tragedy
doesn't repeat itself.
- Put pressure on it.
- Okay.
All done.
Thank you.
Excuse me,
where is patient Kim Gyo Ri?
Over here.
Mr. Eun?
Am I hearing things now?
Ms. Kim.
It's me, Eun Hwan Gi.
Just listen as you are.
Actually,
I...
I have a small problem.
Well...
I have a disorder
that prevents me from interacting...
I mean,
I have extreme difficulty
interacting with people.
If people find out,
I might get in trouble.
Please keep it to yourself.
Well...
What I'm saying is...
I'm...
really sorry...
for giving you a hard time.
I'll give you paid leave,
so take a rest.
Make sure you get treated.
I'll of course pay the medical fees.
Also, if you'd like,
I'll introduce you
to a psychotherapist as well.
I can't guarantee
her competence, though.
She...
failed to fix me.
I'm...
so sorry...
for giving you a hard time.
- The bike has started.
- What are you talking about?
I got rid of my constipation.
What I mean is...
Mr. Eun.
Relax. Breathe.
There you go. Start talking again.
I finally...
I finally told her.
I told her.
Mr. Eun. Mr. Eun?
Nice shot!
The CEO of Brain is the most
searched name on the web right now.
What?
Really? Let me see.
- What is this?
- What is all that?
Let me see.
(Under the Veil Was a Cruel Boss)
- Good shot.
He's great.
This article is about Mr. Eun's son.
- It is.
- My goodness.
- He abused his power?
- Are you talking about my son?
(Congressman's Son Abuses His Power)
(The CEO of Brain has been
treating his secretary cruelly.)
(His secretary has ended up
getting hospitalized.)
That brat.
We can't reach him at the moment.
Please wait.
- Here.
- We're preparing a statement.
We cannot tell you anything yet.
My goodness.
Here. Gosh.
- Where's Mr. Kang?
- Yes? Hello?
- He's not picking up.
- He's been out of reach.
- Hello?
We're preparing a statement.
- That's not true.
- We'll reveal everything.
We're not really sure.
Where is he at a time like this?
- He must be here.
- Where is he?
Please say something.
I told you. The CEO is not here.
Please go back.
That's him.
Did you treat your
secretary cruelly?
- Did you not feed her?
- Is it true?
- How much of it is true?
- Please say something.
- Is she hospitalized?
- Mr. Eun.
- Please say something.
Please explain.
Is she hospitalized?
Move.
Did Mr. Eun treat
his secretary cruelly?
She's hospitalized. Did he hit her?
Are there any other victims?
Did he really not feed her?
Has he visited her at the hospital?
Has he apologized?
Why did he treat her cruelly?
Did he abuse his power?
I'm the co-CEO, Kang Woo Il.
You've come all the way here,
but I'm afraid I can't
tell you anything for now.
We'll prepare an official statement
as soon as possible.
Please come back then.
- He's such a good speaker.
- My goodness.
- He's the best.
- He's amazing.
Please explain what happened.
Do you admit it?
Where is Mr. Eun now?
Did he hit her?
Did he treat her cruelly?
Is Mr. Eun's father aware of this?
What will happen to
Mr. Eun's father?
What's going to happen?
Please say something.
- Will he run for the election?
- Will he remain as a candidate?
- Please say something.
- Will he run for the election?
- Will it get in his way?
- Please say something.
Please tell us the truth.
Brain never hides or
avoids anything.
We won't make
any superficial apology.
That's why we need time.
If we did anything wrong,
we'll admit it...
and come up with a plan to improve.
I beg you to give us some time.
So many of you came
despite the cold.
Wasn't it cold on the way here?
- It was really cold.
- We waited so long.
- I apologize.
- Look at him.
He's so handsome.
We'll look into what happened and
come up with an official statement.
Please wait.
Mr. Eun.
- Why is she here?
- Don't you recognize me?
We've met before.
Well technically,
I didn't see your face,
so I guess I can't say that
we've properly met.
Still, I saw a lot of you
apart from your face.
She followed me
all the way to my office.
Did it all start from there?
You're Mr. Eun Hwan Gi, aren't you?
Let go of me.
Are you crazy?
Ms. Kim couldn't have done this
all by herself.
You seem perplexed.
Could she be involved in this?
Are you okay?
Wait.
I'm sorry, but could you
use another elevator?
Wait.
I'm sorry.
You should keep low.
I'll take care of...
- Do you know her?
- Who do you mean?
Do you mean Ms. Chae?
She works here.
She's our new employee.
A new employee?
Why? Did she say something to you?
No, it's nothing.
Did she quit musicals
all of a sudden...
to get a job at my company?
What is she trying...
to do here?
What about the article?
Did you read it?
(Brain's Co-CEO
Ill-treated His Secretary)
(Is His Father a Congressman?)
(Brain's CEO, Mr. Eun Hwan Gi,
treated his secretary cruelly.)
I still can't get a hold of Ms. Kim.
She disappeared
after she got discharged.
The hospital staff told me that a
man came to see her before she left.
Ms. Kim.
It's me, Eun Hwan Gi.
It must be because of money. She
has to support her entire family.
She's not that kind of person.
You don't even know her well.
I know her better than you do.
It's okay.
I'll sort everything out so that
there's no problem, so don't worry.
I shouldn't have given her money
when she's so hungry for it.
Anyway,
she'll get in touch with us soon.
If she wants more money, that is.
Hey. See?
Kang Woo Il speaking.
Ms. Kim?
No, it's totally fine.
Thank you for calling.
Where are you now?
I'll pick you up.
Stay right there.
I'll be there shortly.
She's in front of our building now.
- I'll go with you, then.
- No, Hwan Gi.
You don't need to get involved.
Reporters might swarm in again,
so you should lay low.
I'll be back soon.
What if Chae Ro Woon has something
to do with this incident?
It's only a matter of time before
Ms. Kim talks about Chae Ro Woon.
She's in danger.
Ji Hye.
I'll make him...
fall all the way down to the bottom.
I'll show you.
- Hello, Sir.
- Where is Hwan Gi?
Please calm down. Let me explain...
He must be shuddering in fear
in that penthouse of this.
You lead the way.
It's my fault. I should've
sorted out the situation sooner.
But the word didn't leak out
because of...
Where's that secretary?
I was just about
to try contacting her.
Go bring her right now!
That blabbing mouth of hers.
I'll cut it all up...
and thinly slice her tongue,
and store it in a jar with brine.
Gosh, what should I do?
The former CEO looks
like a scary man.
I bet he can fire me
without even blinking an eye.
I'm so dead.
Where did he go?
Please let me handle it.
You should just head home now, Sir.
"Eun Hwan Gi is apparently
Congressman Eun Bok Dong's son."
Reporters are excited
about their newly-found prey.
You should avoid
running into them at all costs.
Please don't worry.
I have a plan that can turn
this crisis into an opportunity.
That project you told me
about the other day?
Yes. The only challenge I'd have
is persuading Hwan Gi.
Let me handle him.
Sir... Sir.
Don't be surprised. Just listen.
It's not me. I didn't do it.
Please believe me.
Please lower your voice.
I swear I've never told any of my
family or friends about you.
I've let my guard down just once.
I told just one person.
I had no idea
that would explode like this.
Is it really her, then?
- Please forgive me, Sir.
- Lower your voice, please.
I'll tell you everything.
I'll tell you with whom
I chatted to.
Please let me live.
- It was...
- Shut it if you want to live.
Ms. Kim,
you didn't do anything wrong.
You didn't disclose
anything to anyone.
Pardon me?
You didn't say anything to anybody.
Do you understand?
That means... So you're saying...
No matter what anyone does to
persuade you, keep playing innocent.
Only then, you can get out of this.
Sir.
So you're worried about me.
Ms. Kim.
What took you so long?
I was really worried about you.
I'm saying it because I feel so bad
that you have to go through this.
I wish you reached out to me sooner.
It would've been great
if you hadn't signed...
the confidentiality agreement
when you joined the company.
If you leave like this, you'll be
known as a whistle-blower...
and won't be able to get
another job.
I... I never said...
anything to anyone.
I already know everything.
You can be open with me.
That man who came to see you
at the hospital. Who is he?
It was Mr. Eun.
Mr. Eun visited me at the hospital.
- You mean Hwan Gi?
- Yes.
You find it hard to believe, right?
I was so surprised, too.
He even brought me flowers.
Why would I do such a thing to him?
I really didn't do it.
Please believe me.
Goodness.
(Flower Boss,
Flower Delivery Service)
(Secretary Chae Ji Hye)
(3 years ago)
I'm sorry to interrupt, Sir.
If there's nothing else you'd like
me to take care of, I'll get...
Come in.
Excuse me, Sir.
Is there something
you want to say to me?
You seem to be in a bad mood today.
If you could tell me
what I did wrong, I'll...
I lost a cuff link.
Now I only have one.
Can you find me the same one?
- Right now?
- Right now.
You hardly wear dress shirts.
If you tell me
when you plan on wearing it...
I thought...
I said right now.
Yes. Right now.
Right away, Sir.
Yes. I'm sorry, Ro Woon.
I don't think I can make it tonight.
I hope you do well
even if I'm not there.
I know. I do.
You work for the best PR company
in Korea.
You serve the CEO
of the best company in the country.
Are you trying to make that obvious?
Mom and Dad only care about you,
and they don't care about my shows.
I don't need flowers.
I want you to come.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
(Flower Boss,
Flower Delivery Service)
Yes. Is this the florist?
(Flower Boss,
Flower Delivery Service)
I'm sorry.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I'm...
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry!
- What are you so sorry for?
Are you all right?
That was dangerous.
What were you doing?
Don't tell me
you were thinking of jumping.
Don't ever do that again, okay?
Are you hurt?
My arm...
My arm.
My goodness.
You dropped this.
"Flower delivery service"?
Let's do as she wants.
Then things will go back
to the way it was.
Regardless of my intention,
I ended up...
hurting someone.
I admit it is something
I cannot deny.
I'm reflecting upon it.
I apologize.
- Hello, Ms. Park.
- Hello.
- Are you well?
- Yes.
How are you?
Will he come?
- No way.
- Who?
The penthouse ghost.
The hidden monster
that's hiding behind a veil.
Of course he should be here.
The person responsible
should apologize himself.
Otherwise, it's not sincere.
To be an heir of the owner...
allows you never to be sorry.
It's always the weak
that have to be sorry.
Thanks to the mess a higher-up made,
look at how many staff
have to pick up afterwards.
These days, it's a trend
for the CEO to be apologetic...
even when a small problem arises.
He's old-fashioned.
He doesn't know what trend is.
No way.
He'll show up if he's human.
Hey.
- He's not human.
- He's a zombie.
Regardless...
Regardless of my intention,
I ended up...
hurting someone.
I admit it is something
I cannot deny...
I can do it. I have to.
I can do it.
Why did you come down here?
I'll apologize to everyone myself.
What?
Come with me.
I said I'll take care of it.
You can just hide behind me.
I know you cover for me a lot.
So this time, I'll do it myself.
In that condition?
What are you thinking?
I'll admit my fault honestly.
It might bring what happened
three years ago to light.
Will you be honest about that, too?
Is that what you're scared of?
Have you ever been
in my office before?
Compared to your penthouse,
it looks like a doghouse.
- Woo Il.
- But I don't care.
People tell me...
that I struggle to benefit from
my rich friend...
and that I shouldn't
work too hard...
because the money will
never be mine.
The money will go to the ghost CEO.
No matter what they say,
I've always tried to...
make things easier for you...
and cover up your weaknesses.
Just like you covered up my secret.
Don't worry.
What happened three years ago...
will remain hidden.
So please let me talk to the people.
This is not like you.
- Are you really Hwan Gi?
- I have to do it for it to end.
Nothing will end.
I'll make sure nothing ends.
Just trust me.
- This time, I...
- Can you...
really stand before
all those people?
Can you really express your opinions
correctly in front of everyone?
If you're confident that you won't
make a fool of yourself, do it.
Hey.
Hwan Gi, I'm sorry for being harsh.
I'm getting impatient
because the reporters are waiting.
I'll keep it short.
Will you step down from
your position for the time being?
It's just a formality, you know.
All right. I should. I was going to.
Instead,
take charge of a new project.
Your father will tell you
the details.
He's waiting for you.
You two decided on what I should do?
He must have calmed down by now.
I had a hard time calming him down.
I have to go now.
Can you really stand before
all those people?
We're sorry for making you wait.
We have someone here who can
clear up all the misunderstanding.
Please sit there.
See?
I'm...
Mr. Eun Hwan Gi's secretary.
The article is...
completely false.
What?
I was hospitalized...
because of my chronic disease.
Mr. Eun even visited me
at the hospital with flowers...
and cheered me up.
I'm very perplexed...
that false things about me
have been published against my will.
Mr. Eun and my colleagues,
I'm really sorry for the trouble
I caused the company.
- I have a question.
You seem to be in a bad condition.
Did you come here voluntarily?
As you just said,
was there no cruel treatment?
Have you met Mr. Eun?
Were you put under coercion?
Please explain.
Hold on.
I'm the CEO of Brain, Kang Woo Il.
I'll answer your questions,
considering my employee's condition.
Where's Mr. Eun?
He couldn't adjust his plans abroad,
so he's still outside of Korea.
That's all a lie.
You're stuck in your room every day.
Do you call yourself a man?
Can't you do any better?
I thought you said you're quite good
when you play against a wall.
Golf and tennis.
Real sports let you
mingle with other people.
Why do you make a fool of yourself
whenever people look at you?
Why do you always get so timid
in front of people?
Gosh.
Why does Mr. Eun never
show up in front of people?
We just divided
our work efficiently.
Mr. Eun takes care of the internal
matters of the company,
and I undertake
all the external businesses.
Three years ago, Mr. Eun's secretary
jumped from the office rooftop.
- Is that...
- That's not related to this at all.
There's a rumor that Mr. Eun
is impossible to communicate with.
That's exaggerated.
But I humbly admit that
there was not enough communication.
To prevent
any further misunderstandings,
we've come up with
an improvement plan.
Mr. Eun...
will be resigning...
from his position.
I can't believe this.
What?
You didn't win that position
because you deserved it.
We're starting a venture
in the company.
And you'll take charge of the team.
- Sorry?
- Break out of the egg.
Be reborn.
I can't.
This is your last chance.
If you don't pull yourself together,
I'll give the company to Woo Il.
I'm not interested in
taking over the company.
What? How dare you say that?
My goodness.
Gosh.
I'd rather start something alone.
Alone? What nonsense!
You can't do anything alone
from now on.
Come in.
Stay seated.
You should learn to mingle
with people.
An in-house venture doesn't have
the customary corporate structure.
Neither does it have
rigid hierarchy...
nor unnecessary formalities that can
hinder the organization's growth.
In that new horizontal structure,
Mr. Eun Hwan Gi will become...
a leader with communicative
leadership who can have...
flourishing relationships
with our employees.
In-house venture? What is going on?
My gosh, that's so clever.
They'll avoid the blame...
and pretend that he's giving up his
CEO position when he's actually not.
My goodness.
I have a question.
This decision will shock many people
considering that Mr. Eun...
is the heir of the company.
Has the founder of the company,
Congressman Eun, agreed to it?
Of course.
Many second-generation conglomerates
have been involved in scandals.
Even though the article is false,
he is deeply distressed because it
may have hurt some people.
He asked us to fundamentally
revamp our corporate system.
I promise that we will change.
I sincerely apologize...
for causing you concern.
Mr. Kang never disappoints me.
He's so good at everything,
but his crisis management skills
are truly outstanding.
From planning to execution, he gets
everything done like a thunderbolt.
I can't believe this.
What about Eun Hwan Gi?
He didn't even show up here.
Why did you do that?
Look who's talking.
Why are you doing this to me?
Did Mr. Kang make you lie?
It's true that Mr. Eun
visited me at the hospital...
with flowers.
That psychopath didn't even step out
of his office when you were...
almost dying
right in front of his door.
The article came out
regardless of my intent.
Keep your lips sealed unless
you want both of us to be doomed.
We don't know each other.
We've never even seen
or talked to each other.
You got money from them, didn't you?
What do you...
How much did they give you?
It must've been quite a bit.
That must be why you
gave up on your conscience...
Yes, I sold my conscience.
What was I supposed to do?
Because of some
missionary of justice,
I lost my job. My conscience
was the only thing I could sell!
You can get another job.
I mean,
this isn't the only company...
Who'd want to hire a whistle-blower?
Well...
I just wanted to help you.
You couldn't even
raise your head up...
or look at him
when you were talking to him.
But in return
for putting up with all of that,
I was able to buy food for
my family and pay the utility bills.
I shouldn't have told you anything.
Ji Hye.
You must've been
this distressed, too.
You were in so much pain,
yet you couldn't even
let out a squeal.
Lie face down.
I said, face down.
Lie face down completely.
Lie on your stomach.
The scrubbing towel
feels so rough on my skin.
It looks like he pulled out a new
one for me, so I should be thankful.
There must be a reason
why it hurts so much.
He's a specialist. He must know the
most ideal scrubbing intensity...
for removing dead skin.
My gosh, look at how much
he's sweating.
He's trying to do his very best
to fulfill his given task.
I'll be letting him down if I
complain and ask him to be gentle.
I feel as if my skin is on fire.
He might actually be trying...
to relieve his own stress
by scrubbing me as hard as he can.
What kinds of things has he been
through in life? He's so aggressive.
Is one of his family members ill?
Is he desperate for
the hospital fee?
I'm sure that he's trying so hard
to forget pain.
I'm just lying down.
I can't... I cannot complain.
(Moaning in pain)
My goodness. You should've told me
if it hurt that much.
- You've been enduring it all?
- Sorry?
Lie down on your back again.
I want to scrub the parts I missed.
You little...
They completely got me this time.
Kang Woo Il was the dark horse.
He was prepared
for every single possible scenario.
I bet everyone in the company
was expecting a scandal like that.
Exactly.
They probably started working
on the plans three years ago.
People are calling it the most
ideal crisis management strategy...
and highly praising
Brain's competency.
We ended up benefiting them.
Eun Hwan Gi's dad,
Congressman Eun Bok Dong.
He founded Brain with nothing,
and he's now aiming to get
elected as the mayor of Seoul.
It won't be easy to take them down.
I'll take all of them down,
including that psychopath's dad who
put a silver spoon in his mouth.
Forget being a mayor. He'll be too
humiliated to even leave the house.
You should leave that company.
You've done enough.
What are you talking about?
They completely destroyed my family.
You might end up in danger...
Do you know what
infuriates me the most?
It's the fact that the psychopath
did not show up.
He put Kang Woo Il on the frontline
and made him apologize.
He hid behind him and didn't
even lift a finger.
(Call for Applications:
In-House Venture Project)
Hye Young, have a look at this.
(Call for Applications:
In-House Venture Project)
(Objectives, Criteria, Required
Qualifications, Procedure, Schedule)
It looks like it's really happening.
The ghost of the penthouse,
Eun Hwan Gi.
He does pique my curiosity.
Then go ahead and apply.
Do you think I'm crazy?
Shall I apply?
- You?
It'll be such an easy job.
I'll just have to make sure
not to get on his nerves...
and flatter him as much as possible.
Do you want to be unemployed
for the rest of your life or what?
I'm telling you.
It's all for a show.
The project itself
will be cancelled in no time.
No way. I mean,
he's the founder's son.
Kang Woo Il is obviously doing it
to demote Eun Hwan Gi.
Being cutthroat about it
will look bad,
so he's trying
to be a little polite.
I guess you're right.
Joining that team means death.
Who'd want to apply for it?
Me!
I think it'll be fun.
Kid, come here.
- Me?
- Come here.
Yes?
You keep getting distracted as you
have too much time on your hands.
Let's get some work done, okay?
Yes. You know what to do, right?
Everything here.
How dare you!
If you misplace any of them,
you'll receive a death sentence.
Send them to the photoshoot
locations via express courier,
but make sure all the handmade
decorations don't get damaged.
Handle them gently
as you'd treat babies.
You have to be very careful.
Also, you must be punctual
and meet all the deadlines.
Those in fashion
are known for their impatience.
Okay!
Because I'm fond of you,
I'm giving you a chance
to be the boss.
A chance to be the boss?
When you work at a PR agency,
you have to put up with the media
and clients without losing a smile.
The only people we can boss around
are those express couriers.
I'm sorry.
Keep them on a tight leash, okay?
Yes! Of course.
All right, let's do this.
Hey, I saw you on the rooftop.
Are you not the guy?
Am I mistaken?
Where are you going?
You're the guy.
Why are you trying to run away?
Why can't you look at me in the eye?
Are you...
a newbie?
You must be
a newbie express courier.
I'm not picking on you, so don't be
scared. Everyone starts somewhere.
I'm new, too.
Here's another weird guy.
He walks around with his head down
and can't even make eye contact.
Gosh, my eye...
What's wrong?
What happened to your eye?
I like that you're looking
at me in the eye now.
What scares you? Do you think I'll
shoot laser beams out of my eyes?
There's a photo shoot
taking place in Ilsan Lake Park.
You just have to get there
in one hour.
You have plenty of time, so please
ride your motorcycle safely.
- Pardon?
- We'll see each other often.
Wait...
Let's not run into each other again
on the rooftop, though.
I believe in you!
Why do I have to do this? It's her
fault for jumping to conclusions.
I never said that I work
for an express courier service.
If these things disappear
into thin air,
the photoshoot will be affected,
and she'll get in trouble.
It may be enough reason to fire her.
I do feel bad, but I have
to straighten things out.
Yes, I shouldn't go.
Get off the car now.
Pardon?
The courier didn't arrive yet?
That's strange. We sent them via
courier before we left the office.
- You sent them out, right?
- Yes. I sent them.
We're ready to roll.
- Call the courier guy.
- Okay.
I don't have his phone number.
- What?
- Who was it?
Which company?
He's new. He came to our office
to promote the company.
Well... He's not bad looking and...
Is that why you forgot
to ask him for his business card?
I got his business card
on the rooftop...
I can't really say I got it. I found
the one he dropped, but I...
Call the courier companies
and locate the order.
- Hurry up!
- Okay.
Right. I just...
I would've already
called the police.
It actually turned out for the best.
I mean, this is what I wanted.
I'll be late anyway.
The photoshoot will have to be
rescheduled, and they'll complain.
But it's none of my business since
I'm no longer the CEO of Brain.
Yes. I should turn my car around.
- What is going on?
- Gosh.
What should we do? What a disaster!
No one has received the order.
Are you sure he's a courier guy?
Yes, he is. I'm certain.
Why else do you think he took them?
It's obviously because they're
very expensive designer stuff.
We have no time to waste like this.
Call the police now.
Just a moment.
- Let's wait just a bit more.
- He obviously stole them.
- He'll never do such a thing.
- You've never even seen him before.
You said you don't know
his name or his phone number.
That's true, but...
Are you two a team? Is that it?
- Are you two splitting them?
- Pardon me?
- Gosh, no way.
- This is why.
This is precisely why you have to be
careful when hiring new employees.
All right. It's all my fault.
I actually...
asked Ro Woon to take care
of arranging the courier delivery.
Why? What were you doing? Tell me.
You don't even do that much.
There're so many people here. Don't
get so worked up. Go easy on me.
Can you talk politely to me since
there are so many people here?
We did go to the same school, but
I can't go easy on you all the time.
- Do you understand, Ms. Dang?
- Yes.
I'm sorry, Ms. Park.
Can you still not figure out
what's going on?
I'm sorry. I'm...
I'm... I'm sorry.
It's always the weak
that have to be sorry.
I beg you.
I implore you,
so please trust him.
Are you really going
to be this bull-headed?
I promise you that I'll find them.
So please don't call the police yet.
Please give me some time.
Just a little bit of time.
Please wait just a little bit.
Hey, get yourself back...
What is going on?
Even Mr. Kang is here now.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Kang.
The thing that I've been
worried about finally happened.
Where on earth is he?
Did he get into an accident?
Where is he?
Where is he now?
Where did he go?
I knew it!
Look at that.
I knew he would come.
He even gave up his motorbike...
and ran all the way here.
Here!
I've been waiting for you!
I shouldn't have come here.
Thank you for coming!
I shouldn't have gone near her
in the first place.
There we go.
Thank you so much
for all of your support.
I shouldn't have hovered around her.
I had faith in you!
What if she finds out who I am?
If I told her then...
I knew you'd come!
No, before that...
Is there something
you want to say to me?
If only I had told her...
If only I had said
anything to her...
If I tell her now,
will I be able to make things right?
Move!
What did you say?
- Move!
- I can't hear you.
I can't hear you.
Or is it...
too late now?
(My Shy Boss)
This is a new beginning
and a new challenge.
Did you hear?
The penthouse will be opened.
- That's unbelievable.
- Why here, of all places?
She might get hurt
if my cover gets blown.
- Did you eat?
- Yes.
Don't worry.
This is only the beginning
of my revenge.
I've picked out members
for the venture.
Forget it. I have a few on my mind.
There's one more.
- Trust me.
- Have you two already become close?
She's cheerful and energetic
just like I used to be.
I like her.
We'll soon find out...
who he really is.
Meet the leader of Silent Monster,
Eun Hwan Gi.