Well, then shall we...
start talking?
You two have been just
staring at each other.
Well...
Will you say I have a grudge again
now that I don't speak?
Did I upset you?
Did you hold grudges again?
I don't talk...
because I'm considerate.
Do you get it?
It's because I'm considerate.
Do you know
what being considerate means?
I try to understand others that they
might have...
their own reasons and
they might stop someday.
I endured and waited.
Then I went through a lot...
to start talking like this.
I want you to know that.
Hwan Gi!
Do you think I say
all I want to say?
- I think you do.
- No.
- No?
- No!
Gosh. I doubt it.
I talk more than you just because...
I have much to say.
I barely get to say
what I really want to say.
I hesitate too.
I also think carefully...
and hold back. Do you know that?
No, you don't.
You think and hold back?
I can understand both of you.
Shall we start talking about
what you really want to say?
- Let me start first.
- Hey.
Wait. How dare you start first?
Where is my alcohol?
My alcohol is gone. Where is it?
- We need more drinks now.
- I'll go get it.
- I'm okay.
- I'll bring some more.
You just stay here.
You better not run away.
There you go!
I won!
We are here.
We are almost there.
Please move a bit more.
- Shall we go?
- No.
I'm too tired.
There, there.
- Please untie this.
- Do you want to untie that?
Are you stuffy?
- Yes, I am.
- Okay.
It's done now.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
Gosh...
I have one more to carry.
Are you crying?
She's so ugly.
- Oh, my goodness.
- I do look so ugly.
That totally sobered me up.
I won.
I'm injured, but I still won.
Does it still hurt?
Your photo was...
so funny.
Go on. Laugh as you want!
You didn't laugh
when I wanted you to do so.
We're here.
Oh, boy.
Almost there.
She's so ugly.
I didn't know he could laugh
so much like this.
He looks beautiful.
(Episode 9, If You Listen)
Where did Ro Woon go?
She promised to go on
a tour together.
Ro Woon!
Ro Woon! Ro Woon!
Move your leg away.
I am sorry.
Move your head.
You're using my arm as pillow.
- I'm not.
- You are.
I said to move your leg. It's heavy.
I did it.
Whose leg is this then?
Get off me. Seriously.
What are you talking about?
- Put her head away.
- What?
Do it gently.
Hurry up!
Gosh.
Do you want some coffee?
She's so odd.
With her, we might be able to go
back to how things were before.
Thanks to her,
we fought, argued,
and laughed just like in the past.
I want things to be like that
in the future as well.
For that to happen,
I'd better not...
marry Yi Soo.
I say this to you honestly...
because I don't want to lose you.
It could be my greed,
but I hope you understand me.
You've never brought out...
what happened
three years ago, right?
How can someone like me...
How can I...
I think I made...
a terrible mistake that
I should've never made.
Please don't say that.
I feel too guilty for her
to stay with Yi Soo.
It's also not right...
to stay with her feeling like this.
I realized only after
sending her like that.
The biggest mistake I made was...
not choosing her.
I don't want to...
repeat the same mistake.
I'm not going to repeat
the same mistake either.
I'm not going to hesitate anymore.
What do you mean?
The one you're about to choose is...
Ms. Chae's little sister.
- What?
- Chae Ro Woon is...
Chae Ji Hye's little sister.
Do you understand?
What are you talking about?
Are you sure?
Why didn't you tell me?
I told you to fire her.
Were you aware of it
from the beginning?
Why didn't you...
Wait.
Why did Ro Woon enter
our company in the first place?
Leave her...
be.
What?
- Don't do anything to her.
- What are you...
I can't...
let her go now.
Why are you coming out of
Boss's room?
What?
It's not like that.
I just came to look for him.
That's not true. I saw you
coming out of there.
No.
It's not like that.
I'm just looking for him.
Why this early in the morning?
Breakfast.
He should have breakfast.
Just to say that
he should have breakfast,
you hurried here
as soon as you woke up?
You haven't even washed your face.
Your hair is a mess.
Stop it.
Gyo Ri, you're sharing a room
with Ro Woon, right?
Hey.
- I was wondering if you slept well.
- Gyo Ri.
- Where are you now?
- Okay, I'll be right there.
- Hey.
- Okay.
- Wait.
Hey, stop.
Wait.
I can't understand a word
of what you're saying.
She's here to take revenge.
She's the one who published
the article on my power abuse.
Is that true?
Why did you...
- keep it to yourself?
- I thought she could get hurt.
That's why I didn't tell you.
- If Father finds out...
- So let's keep it from him.
Don't say anything to Ro Woon.
She doesn't know
that I'm aware of it.
Se Jong, let me explain, okay?
- Come here.
- It hurts.
Se Jong.
I'm getting even more suspicious
because you're stopping me.
There's nothing to be suspicious of.
What are you talking about?
- Is that so?
- Wait.
Stop!
Why are you so fast? Hey!
Stop right there!
I want to...
protect her this time.
If you're feeling guilty
about what happened to Ms. Chae,
protect her by all means.
Very good. Let's do a cat pose now.
Come down. Breathe.
Breathe out.
And come back up.
That'd be it.
- Thank you.
Gyo Ri.
Ro Woon didn't come to the room
last night, did she?
I don't know.
- I went to bed early last night.
- You would have noticed her.
She snores so loud.
Gyo Ri.
- Hey.
- Tell me the truth.
Who did you sleep with last night?
Boss? Mr. Kang?
Or both?
You're amazing.
That's right. I slept with him.
I slept with Boss.
Are you happy now?
See?
You like Boss.
We just slept.
He got drunk,
so I took him to his room.
And then I fell asleep.
Do you expect me to believe that?
Fine, don't believe it.
That's great.
Now, you could finally stop
harassing me.
Do you think
I'm trying to harass you?
You keep crossing the line
making others uncomfortable.
You're just fooling around with me.
I'm fooling around with you?
I looked for you everywhere
all night.
I wanted to show you fireflies.
I stayed up all night
waiting for you.
Do you still think
I'm fooling around with you?
Se Jong.
Boss.
- Where's Mr. Kang?
- He went back.
Did something come up?
I'm sorry.
I fell asleep in your bed.
In addition, I got caught.
By Se Jong, the big mouth.
I should have kept my mouth shut,
but he was so persistent.
Also...
I'm not supposed to tell anyone,
but you're good at keeping secrets.
It's only between you and me.
The thing is,
Gyo Ri has a crush on Se Jong.
I thought it might help Se Jong
give up on me.
He says he likes me all the time.
I feel so sorry for Gyo Ri.
You laughed so much last night.
You turned into an adolescent boy
overnight.
I have no idea
what's going through your mind.
Speaking of which,
I've been thinking about
how to communicate with you.
What is this?
Stay still.
Ta-da.
There you go.
- It's a signal light.
- Sorry?
You communicate your mood
using different colors.
When you don't want to be
bothered by anyone,
turn on the red light.
When you're available for urgent
matters, turn on the yellow light.
When you're feeling ready for
all kinds of discussion,
turn on the green light.
This is too... I'm okay.
You might feel awkward at first,
but you'll get used to it
eventually.
Here.
Right now, it's the red light.
Isn't it?
I'll stop talking.
Just relax.
How can she say such a thing?
How dare she belittle me like that?
I'm not fooling around with her...
I wanted to look cool
in front of Ro Woon,
so I even got these limited-edition
sneakers yesterday.
Right. She might think
that I'm too stylish for her.
Yes, that must be it.
It's all because of my good looks.
That's why she can't see how sincere
I am and doesn't take me seriously.
I don't need these stupid sneakers!
That was the reason!
My good looks were to blame!
My sneakers! Oh, no. My sneakers...
What is he doing?
Is he being like that
because of Ro Woon?
Se Jong!
Oh, no. My sneakers...
- Se Jong!
- Let go.
Don't go. It's dangerous.
No, I can't let it go like that.
I really can't.
Please don't be like this.
Don't be so hung up.
Just let it go already.
No, I can't.
My limited-edition sneakers.
I went through hoops to get them.
Gosh, my shoes...
Oh, was it about...
I thought you hate me now
or something.
Why would I hate you?
You've been distant
ever since you found out...
who my grandfather is.
Well, that's...
It's okay. That's normal.
Everyone changes a little
when they find out about it.
They either treat me better
or start hating me.
Anyway, I guess things can't be
the same as before.
It's not like that.
But there's one person...
who hasn't changed at all around me.
Is it Ro Woon?
Right.
Her belittling attitude toward me
does annoy me a bit, though.
- Thanks for this.
- Don't mention it.
By the way, can I ask you something?
Why did Mr. Kang go back already?
Okay, fine. I'll keep my mouth shut.
- By any chance...
- The red light is on.
You're defeating the purpose
of the signal light.
Please let me ask you
just one question.
Did I...
snore by any chance?
I did, didn't I?
Are you extra sensitive today
because you couldn't get any sleep?
Was my snoring that bad?
Enough to make both of you
run out of the room?
Is that also why Mr. Kang
went back to Seoul early...
Come on.
That's not what happened, right?
It mustn't have been that bad.
By the way, that flower
really suits you. Do you know that?
I want to go back.
- Shall we go back?
- Really?
(Welcome, Yun Jung.)
(10 years ago)
Hwan Gi.
When did you start
wearing that hoodie?
Oh, this.
When I was in college.
Why? Did something happen?
Was it because of a girl?
A heartbreak from your first love?
Gosh, that must've been
what happened.
What was she like?
Any tear-invoking stories
you want to share?
Tell me.
It's none of your business.
I think it's him.
Hello.
(New York Barbershop)
It doesn't look
like his daughter is back yet.
She didn't even leave a note.
How many days has it been
since she just took off?
Goodness.
He must be so worried.
- There she is. She's back!
- What?
Yes, she's back.
I guess we'll get
to hear him yelling this time.
He's been too lenient with her.
He really should
teach her a lesson this time.
Absolutely.
Yes! Good. Way to go.
Be a man.
Show her how scary you can be!
Have you eaten yet?
Yes, I have.
What did he say?
He asked her if she's eaten.
I've eaten as well.
You remind me
of someone I used to know...
even though you two
aren't really similar.
Yes, Mr. Park.
(New Year Message
for the Brain Family)
(Mr. Kang Woo Il and my daughter
are getting married.)
He's getting married.
He wasn't going to be mine anyway.
But this is so sudden.
I can't believe it.
The founder of Brain wrote
this message himself...
for all of the employees.
It's obviously not some gibberish.
So he announced it like this.
I thought you were aware of it.
Mr. Kang.
Congratulations on your engagement.
Congratulations.
- Mr. Kang, congratulations.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
You're here.
You announced my engagement.
I went out of my way
to make you proud.
You didn't say anything to me.
And I was away.
- You can leave now.
- Okay.
I've been a little cold to you
lately.
It's not because I hate you.
It's because I trust you.
I feel comfortable around you.
I rely on you
more than I do to my own son.
My son achieved an okay result
this time,
but he still has a long way to go.
Please help him come to the front...
and lead the company.
You've been carrying
so much burden by yourself.
Am I wrong?
You want Hwan Gi to stand out...
more than I do, right?
I just slapped you in the face once.
Are you still holding a grudge?
I wish...
you were my son...
a dozen times a day.
I'm even giving my daughter to you.
- Father, I appreciate that, but...
- Still,
don't get too excited
about your wedding.
Don't neglect the election
or the company.
We still don't know who released the
article on Hwan Gi's power abuse.
Woo Il.
You were surprised, right?
Mom was worried you were not
interested in marrying me.
She was making a fuss
saying she has a bad feeling.
While trying to defend you,
things got out of hand.
- I'm sorry, but...
- That's what I want to say.
I can't postpone our wedding
any longer than this.
Yi Soo.
Stay with me.
That's the only thing...
I ask of you.
He caught me off guard.
I knew how controlling he can be,
but I didn't expect this.
Ro Woon is giving me
enough headaches.
Now, a wedding announcement?
Let's fire Ro Woon.
That'll be best for her too.
- Let's not take any action...
- We should have earlier.
If she's planning something
in addition to that article...
She won't do anything more.
Then why is she still here?
She must be trying to dig into
what happened three years ago.
If she finds out...
Is that what you're going for?
That's my biggest weakness.
Is that why you...
- Are you saying I'm...
- Then?
You said you want to protect her.
Why are you keeping her here?
It just doesn't make sense.
Give me some time.
Why?
What are you thinking about
all alone now?
It's me. You can talk to me.
Wasn't keeping her identity from me
all this time enough?
Only my secrets are found by you.
You see through me.
Why can't I see who you are?
Can't I know what's on your mind?
Yoo Hee wants Boss.
She's starting a meeting.
- It was a mistake.
- A mistake?
You know guys can make a mistake.
What's going on between...
Mr. Kang.
Boss, did something happen?
The war has begun.
What do you mean?
Mr. Kang's wedding
has been announced.
He's going to be
the founder's son-in-law.
The son and the son-in-law will
fight over the management rights.
This is the beginning
of that cruel battle.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
It's hot.
It tastes good.
I don't believe they argued
over such a thing.
You never know.
My mom fights with her sisters
all the time too.
- That's the way it is.
- Is this battle even possible?
Exactly.
Mr. Kang has shown so much so far.
Mr. Eun doesn't have resources.
- I feel sorry for him.
- So do I.
What could Mr. Eun do
without Mr. Kang?
Sun Bong, come over here, will you?
No. We better decide our positions
carefully now.
- Bye.
- Wait.
Sun Bong, where are you going?
We should help him.
This is an old, small theater.
They want to renovate this place
into a theater for movie lovers.
Mr. Kang's team is working on
a project related to theaters too.
This is our chance
to prove ourselves.
Are we going to set the theme
ourselves as well?
Do you think marketing
is all about...
sitting at the desk
writing a few articles?
You have to try the whole process...
from planning to marketing
yourself...
to get an idea of how PR works.
Ro Woon, go check the place
with Boss.
Can't I go?
I think Ro Woon should go.
Okay.
Can't I know what's on your mind?
You fell in love with someone
you shouldn't love, didn't you?
She's your employee,
and she's another employee's girl.
Do you see?
The red light means "stop".
The yellow light means he's
available only for urgent matters.
- The green light is...
- Does the green light ever turn on?
Gosh.
I'll leave for the theater first.
Let me go with you.
No. The red light is on.
Sort out your thoughts.
Come when the green light is on.
Go.
Take your time.
- Go.
- I'm going.
A red light.
I realized I should stop.
Still, I...
Gosh.
Is the green light on yet?
I'm sorry.
Hey, Hwan Gi.
Did you not see me?
Or are you just pretending?
You were all I could see
even from across the street.
Yun Jung.
Every time I see you,
I feel like it's been so long.
Please leave a message
after the tone.
I'd appreciate it
if he at least picks up.
Come to think of it, I've never
talked to him on the phone.
Oh, that's right.
He has telephone phobia.
I actually saw you at the airport
a little while ago.
That was you, wasn't it?
Oh, the airport? Right.
Even on that day, you walked away
as if you didn't see me.
Right, you probably didn't have
the guts to face me...
after standing me up
like that three years ago.
I've developed trauma
about Christmas.
- I'm sorry. Back then, I was...
- Forget it.
I actually wrote a ton
of mean comments...
on the articles about your being an
abusive boss, so let's call it even.
No, that's actually not enough.
How about you buy me
a cup of coffee?
Coffee?
I have to get going now, though.
You're in trouble.
You won't be able
to run away this time.
And here's a cup of coffee.
That's for someone else.
I'm sorry. I already had a sip.
I was going to give it to Ro Woon.
- I'll visit you at work soon.
- What?
I want to talk to you about doing
PR work for the new exhibition.
You won't stand me up if I'm
meeting you as your client, right?
About three years ago...
I had a bit of a situation.
I know. It was probably something
you couldn't tell me.
Otherwise, you would've told me
the reason three years ago.
But I'm serious about the work.
I was actually on the lookout
for a PR agency.
Help me out.
All right, then.
I'm going to boss you around.
Brace yourself.
Is it still the red light?
I wanted to be
by her side like this...
for just a little longer.
Would it be okay for me to stay
by her side if I keep this distance?
("Don't Forget Me")
You didn't meet him at the theater?
He said he was headed there
as he was leaving yesterday.
Did something else pop up?
I guess he met
another girl or something.
He's been smirking too.
He seems to be in a good mood today.
Then...
is it the green light today, Boss?
If that's the case, do you mind
taking a look at my proposal?
To get on with the trend,
I thought we could use "virtual
reality cinema" as our theme.
Yes, I've read your proposal.
But...
It'd be different for games,
but there isn't enough content.
The trend isn't there yet.
He's right.
Sun Bong,
you're being cynical again.
Also,
prolonged use of VR headsets...
can induce motion sickness or
headaches. How will you tackle that?
What will you do if people complain
about blurred vision or eye fatigue?
Do you have a plan for how you will
deal with such problems?
Those are issues
that we can't overlook.
Sun Bong, do you have an idea then?
Something unique that can appeal
to the target group.
- No, I don't.
- See?
What is wrong with you?
You have no clue either.
Boss, please let us know
what you think.
I need some time to think.
We need to act fast so that we can
become the first one in Korea.
Yes, I know that. But...
The best, the biggest,
and the first.
I must say Korean people
can be so lame.
The just love those superlatives.
They think that's what
PR work is all about.
How simple-minded.
That was blunt, but he's not wrong.
I'll take some time
to think about it.
He loves taking time.
I guess
the red light is on again today.
About the signal lights...
Don't you think the idea
is a bit too childish?
A full-fledged adult is walking
around with colorful stickers.
What is that seriously? Is he
a pervert or what? How embarrassing.
Plus, he's our leader,
yet he communicates with us
only when he wants to.
What kind of nonsense is that?
Stop ruining it.
I was going to stop.
Gyo Ri.
Why are you dolling up?
Do you have a date?
I'm sure you don't.
- Why don't we go for...
- Gyo Ri.
- Should we go on a date?
- Sorry?
- Are you asking me?
- Yes.
I'd like to treat you
to a nice dinner.
You look especially pretty today.
(VR Movies)
That's so random.
Just the two of you?
Yes. I have something to tell her
in person.
- Let's go, Gyo Ri.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
What do you want to eat?
Anything is fine.
What about steaks?
Yoo Hee, why don't we have
some spicy food and soju?
I need to go home and feed my kids.
Your sons will leave you
for other girls after all.
Live your life.
Stop observing
and laughing at others.
Live your life, okay?
My goodness. Do you still have
hope for the VR cinema?
I can give you some advice
if you buy me dinner.
I'm okay.
I have to do some more research
on VR theaters.
I'll get going.
- Wait.
- Sorry.
I'm leaving.
Why does it feel like
there's someone behind me?
He seems to need someone
to have dinner with.
Should I ask him
if he wants to eat with me?
But if it's just the two of us,
he'll feel uncomfortable.
As I'm his boss,
he won't be able to say no.
Should I turn on the green light?
It means I'm ready to go along
with him as long as he wants.
But Mr. Um said
the signal light thing is childish.
He has a point.
It's embarrassing for a grown-up
to put colorful stickers on himself.
(Embarrassed)
But sometimes,
childish gestures break the ice.
Ms. Chae made these for me.
I should pluck up the courage.
Mr. Um?
Mr. Um.
How can he never buy me any meal?
We had a shared destiny once.
Everything's pointless.
Gosh, it's hot.
What a waste.
VR movies surpass the boundary...
between imagination and the reality
and the limits of space.
VR movies will set a new paradigm...
in the 120-year-long history
of movies.
Oh, my.
We're taking the innovative step
into the new world...
before anyone else in the country.
I'm co-CEO of Brain, Kang Woo Il.
Thank you.
Oh, my.
I knew it.
We won't be the first ones anymore.
You said it was lame
to strive for superlatives.
The upper management needs to
make quick decisions...
for things to move forward.
We're spending forever
to just wait for the approval.
The power struggle between the son
and the son-in-law. Round one.
- Mr. Kang won.
- Yes.
Ro Woon, your idea was great.
You worked so hard.
You must be disappointed.
Thank you.
I'm sure Boss has an idea.
I'm sure he has another plan.
You have no idea?
You've been thinking all this time.
I thought you turned on the red
light because you were thinking.
Let's think together from now on.
It's creepy here.
I'm scared ghosts will appear.
It's very old-fashioned.
It smells funny.
My bottom and back will
start to ache.
The seats are too close
to each other.
I like it.
I can sit close to my baby.
This way. It's here.
Since when are they so close?
The rich boy is playing around,
and an innocent girl fell for it.
What happened?
Are you two really dating?
The thing is...
He wants us to pretend
to be together.
Sorry?
He wants you to feel jealous.
He wants to show you
how he can make a girl happy...
and how nice he can be to a girl.
Why don't you tell him how you feel?
Not everyone can be...
honest about their feelings
like you are.
Everyone says...
you should be confident so easily.
But that's only possible
when you have someone listening.
I have no one...
willing to listen to me.
Why do you say that?
Can't you just pretend not to know?
Se Jong is trying to make me happy.
Who else would be...
so nice to me?
Gyo Ri.
Without a theme
as unique as VR movies,
it'd be hard to attract customers.
Exactly. What a shame we missed it.
It would have attracted attention
as it's a new thing.
Among the cheesy superlatives,
we've lost the best, the first,
and the biggest.
But there's one perfect word left.
What is it?
The worst.
- What's wrong with you?
- My gosh.
It's not the biggest in Korea, and
the service isn't the best either,
so let's come up with something
buzzworthy to make it memorable.
There's no need to waste money
on renovations.
How about a horror movie theater?
"Visit the worst movie theater..."
"for an unforgettable night of
horror that gives you the chills."
- Horror movies?
- "Coming soon." Ta-da.
That sounds good.
- Pardon?
- Sorry?
I like that idea.
Let's go with Sun Bong's idea.
What idea?
You mean what I just said?
Gosh, I wasn't serious about it.
I was just being sarcastic.
It's a great idea that twists
conventional strategies.
- Goodness, I was just joking.
- He just said it to make us laugh.
We can't use that idea.
To make us laugh...
Yes, it was funny.
Mr. Um, you have great wits
and an outstanding sense of humor.
Me? I do?
Gosh, what was that about?
Does that mean...
he's taking what Sun Bong said
seriously?
My gosh.
I'm flustered.
Sun Bong, tell us again.
What did you say?
The green light is finally on.
I've come up with an idea
for the promotional slogan.
I thought that women...
would hate to have dates at a place
known as the worst theater.
How about we say the chairs will
help them test their boyfriends'...
back strength?
I see. Right.
We do need to appeal
to female consumers.
I like the idea.
Great. There's this one too.
You know those man-spreaders, right?
The chairs will teach them manners
by making them close their legs.
He smiled.
There's another one.
- There's another version.
- Is there?
As you know, we'll market it
as the worst theater...
Everyone says...
you should be confident so easily.
But that's only possible
when you have someone listening.
What has gotten into him?
What is wrong with him?
He hasn't even budged from his desk
for hours.
He looks so cool now.
You got this.
Boss was a good listener.
The worst movie theater
in the world.
It'll be sure to disappoint you
more than you can ever imagine.
You're welcome to kick
the seat in front of you.
You can certainly leave
your phone on the whole time.
You may drink and dance away
inside the theater.
If an ugly monster
shows up on the screen,
you can go ahead
and throw your popcorn at it.
- That's hilarious.
- You're doing a good job!
Ladies and gentlemen, until when...
do we have to live according
to the society's rigid standards?
Forget the biggest, the best,
and the first.
The worst day ever
can also be enjoyable.
- That's right.
- Good!
William Shakespeare said this.
"The worst is not so long as
we can say this is the worst."
The truly worst moment...
is when we don't even have
strength to say so.
We still have the energy to overcome
what we think is the worst.
You, you, and you!
Please get the most out
of the worst experience.
The worst horror movie theater
in the entire world.
The real horror starts now!
You did it!
- Amazing!
- That was awesome!
- You did it.
- You did such a good job.
The reason why
he has always been so quiet...
- Don't cry!
It wasn't because
he didn't want to talk.
He probably wanted to listen.
What was that about?
- Just a high five.
- High five?
- On my back?
- Give me five, then.
See?
This is why I did it on your back.
Help me organize this.
In 1, 2, and 3.
Look at the camera.
My goodness.
I hope you're not here
to steal our idea again.
- What are you talking about?
- The VR cinema.
We came up with that idea
a long time ago,
but Boss took his sweet time
and ended up not approving it!
There isn't much content
for VR cinemas yet,
so a single-screen theater like this
won't be able to maintain business.
Hwan Gi made the right decision.
Work probably isn't his priority now
because of Ro Woon.
- What did you just say?
- He's turned into a romantic.
I guess you didn't know
he's been flirting with Ro Woon.
Do you have anything to say to me?
Just finish it up quickly.
"My gosh, you're really good."
"Where did you learn
how to do this?"
"Thanks for helping us
reduce the expenses."
Just for your information, those are
what others said to me.
Don't put too much blood on me.
I don't want to scare people.
Your black hoodie is already
scaring everyone enough.
I want to see myself in the mirror.
You're making me anxious.
- Hand me a mirror.
- Please close your eyes.
I need to do the eye makeup now.
Goodness.
I'll use this color.
Oh, gosh...
Please close your eyes. I need
to put this over your eyelids.
What's up with you? I can't believe
you took that off yourself.
What is with you?
You're not avoiding eye contact.
I am avoiding it.
Are you...
not going to close your eyes?
I'm doing my very best...
to avoid it.
Is this...
a staring match or what?
Are we doing this because...
turning away or closing eyes first
means losing?
Close your eyes, please.
What will you do
if I poke your eyes?
(My Shy Boss)
- Boss.
- Don't stay by my side.
You thanked me...
- for being by your side.
- Just a second!
Did I do something wrong?
- One of my employees bothers me.
- One, two.
- Bring it back.
- Run, run.
- It's not Chae Ro Woon.
- She's gone.
- Boss?
Ms. Chae.
- Either bring her back,
- The red light?
- Ms. Chae?
- or don't show it.
- Yi Soo needs you now.
- What are you doing now?
- Get lost.
- Excuse me.
Will you really be able
to do the presentation?
- I will.
- Not the presentation.
- You won't be able to do it.
- What if I do it?
I want Ro Woon back.