=The Litchi Road=
(A Radish Peeling Knife: One)
There's a traitor in Security Bureau.
(Nine Years Ago)
(Lu Huan.)
(I order you)
(to hurry to Pingkang Ward
to catch them.)
(Make sure there's no mistake.)
(Yes.)
(Zuihong Pavilion)
(Young Yun Qing)
Hurry and wash it.
Don't dawdle.
What are you staring at?
If you keep staring,
I'll feed your eyes to the dogs.
Little one.
(Ding Tong'er)
I bought you.
After peeling the radishes,
mop the floor.
You hear me?
Deputy Director Zheng is here.
Please.
Lead the way.
This way.
(Tianbao)
These are two land deeds.
Both are fine residences
with good fengshui in Anren Ward.
You're
a core official in the court.
(Security Bureau, Deputy Director Zheng)
Left Chancellor favors you.
Let you be in charge of Security Bureau.
But why did you
go to great lengths
to gain Right Chancellor's favor?
A wise man
serves under the right leader.
I also have a list of people
who have colluded with Left Chancellor
to impeach Right Chancellor.
I'll give it to Right Chancellor
as well.
(Name List)
I'll accept this generous gift
on behalf of Right Chancellor.
Yes.
If you have any instructions,
I will do my best
to fulfill them.
You
have a bright future.
Don't forget me in the future.
Thanks for your generous favor.
Get up.
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Let go!
Let go of me!
Let go of me.
Do you think you could survive
by escaping?
Even if you escape,
outside isn't all that different
from here.
Dress up.
She needs to meet a distinguished guest.
Sir.
I won't disturb you.
I'll go to the lobby
and wait for your call.
Deputy Director Zheng, this way.
What's your name?
Dongxue.
Dongxue?
He called you.
Dongxue.
Come here.
This is Xinghua Pavilion's
gourd chicken.
The skin is crispy
and the meat is tender.
Come on.
Let go of me!
Get out of the way!
=Episode 20=
Amita.
Godfather, what brings you here?
I heard you found someone
at sea.
Didn't Lan Yu tell you?
He's just a fisherman.
There was a small misunderstanding
during a fish deal earlier.
How did such a small matter
alert Inspector's Office?
Is this man called Tu?
Why did you bring him
to the association?
Inspector's Office
is also looking for him.
Why are you looking for him?
We heard
that Li Shande is looking for him.
This man knows
a shortcut out of Lingnan.
We can't let
Li Shande have him.
Don't worry.
I won't hand him to Li Shande.
Amita.
You probably don't know
how cunning Li Shande is.
You're no match for him.
How about this?
I'll take him away.
It's safer to keep him
in Inspector's Office.
Godfather.
I can't let you have Tu yet.
I heard he used to be
in charge of Sea Sail Fund.
Before the Qijing Pavilion fire,
a mysterious person dumped
2,000 shares of Sea Sail Fund
through him.
It's as if he predicted this fire.
I must find out
who this mysterious person is.
Qijing Pavilion's fire
and Sea Sail Fund's collapse
were major events
that shook Lingnan.
There are rumors all over the place.
Everyone told different versions.
We can't believe
in hearsay.
You don't know how chaotic it was.
Sea Sail Fund had large transactions
every day.
If you insist
it's related to Qijing Pavilion's fire,
isn't that nonsense?
In that case,
I can let you
take Tu away.
Alright.
I just want to ask
who this mysterious person is first.
It'll put me feel at ease.
Inspector He, we found Tu.
Let go of me.
Go.
- Save me, and I'll tell you the truth.
- No one can leave!
He's the one who dumped 2,000...
Shut up.
Speak.
He's the one who sold 2,000 shares.
I watched him
bring fire oil into Qijing Pavilion.
He burned Haihu to death!
This lunatic
is talking nonsense.
Do you believe him?
If he's talking nonsense,
why did you draw your sword?
He Youguang.
I have evidence against you.
If you kill me,
the evidence
will be made public.
Made public?
I won't kill him.
You have evidence.
That's a good thing.
Hurry and make it public!
He Youguang!
What are you trying to do?
Amita.
You've been by my side
since you came of age.
I raised you for ten years.
You should know
how I treated you all this while.
The days I spent with you
are more than your own father.
Today,
do you believe him
or me?
You decide.
I had a glimmer of hope
that Tu wouldn't say
it was you,
but you killed him right away.
My hopes were all shattered.
Since that dagger,
you've been lying to me.
You've been lying to me all along!
My father was your sworn brother.
Why did you kill him?
If I really killed your father,
why didn't I kill you too?
Why did I raise you?
For you to grow up
and settle old scores with me?
Think about it. Use your brain.
Who
taught you
everything you know about life?
Who patiently taught you
how to do business?
And who made you
the chief of Hu Merchants' Association?
I raised you in luxury
for ten years.
Are you not satisfied?
What else do you want?
I would rather you kill me!
I know the truth now.
I want you to atone
for the sin with death!
What did you say?
How dare you
say that to me?
Atone for the sin with death?
Are you going to kill me?
You want to kill me?
Who do you think you are?
I'll warn you for the last time.
I can love you
and also ruin you.
Go.
He Youguang!
He Youguang.
Today, either you die
or I die.
You'll die then.
Kill her.
Bow and arrow!
Shoot her to death!
Shoot them all!
Someone, come.
Zhao.
Inspector He!
You're injured.
You're not injured, are you?
I'm fine.
I killed everyone outside.
Inspector He, I'll take you outside.
Listen well.
Find out
who rescued Amita.
Tell Captain Yang
to kill everyone
who was in the association today.
Leave no one alive.
Put the entire city under lockdown.
Find Amita.
Yes.
An order from Inspector He.
Put the entire city under lockdown.
A secret manhunt
for Amita,
chief of Hu Merchants' Association.
- Yes!
Master.
Is the injury serious?
She'll live.
Who are you?
They call me Master Konglang.
We have never met before.
Why did you help me?
I want to make a deal with you.
He Youguang killed your father.
You can't beat him alone.
The whole city is looking for you.
You have nowhere to go except here.
I can help you,
but in exchange,
I want He Youguang's
evidence of corruption.
Miss.
It's alright now.
Stop crying.
You can stay in the litchi garden
or follow me back to Dayu Ridge.
You won't be homeless.
Miss.
I promised to send you
to the embroidery house.
I'll keep my word.
It's all my fault.
Tu wouldn't have died
if it weren't for me.
Uncle Tu once told me
this day would come sooner or later.
He said he could escape for a while,
but not forever.
Tu not only knew
Dayu Ridge's shortcut
but also some secrets
that led to his death.
This
was a catastrophe he was meant to face.
It's just
that I
never even got to see him
before he died.
So all this effort
was for nothing.
Despite all our efforts,
we still can't find
Dayu Ridge's path.
Mr. Li.
How about I ride a horse
to Dayu Ridge to find it?
Dayu Ridge is enclosed
by cliffs on three sides,
blocking three directions.
Only a narrow water basin
stretches to the east,
leading to Qianzhou.
The courier road is narrow.
Green mountains
stand opposite each other,
covering most of the sky.
It's hard to see anything in this place,
much less find the path.
We can only hurry up
and try our very best
to shorten the two days.
The more anxious we are,
the more we have to slow down
in a place like this.
If we make a mistake,
we'll lose everything.
If that's the case,
there's nothing we can do.
Be careful.
(Yi'an Embroidery)
Let me see.
Pay attention to this color.
Madam.
Lan...
Lan already told me.
Yes.
This girl
looks quite cute.
Does she have a name?
No.
You don't even have a name?
You're clever.
How about calling you Hui?
Sure.
Alright, Hui.
Don't be afraid.
It's alright if you can't see.
Embroidery is a craft
that relies on the heart.
Come here.
(Yi'an Embroidery)
Let me see your hands.
They're quite soft.
Have you learned embroidery before?
I learned it myself.
What have you embroidered?
This is what I embroidered myself.
Let me see.
This needlework is really good.
You embroidered this?
She has a good foundation.
Alright, I'll take her in.
Kowtow to Madam.
Thank you, Madam.
Alright, darling.
Get up.
Thank your savior.
No need to thank me.
From now on,
live here
and work on the craft.
Alright.
I'll give this back to you.
Mr. Li.
You can have this handkerchief.
Uncle Tu
carved the pattern for me.
He said this pattern
means hope.
Really?
Alright.
Hope.
What is this?
This is Dong people's custom.
They draw the direction
of the hometown's mountains
on the ground
during the memorial ceremony
to make it easier
for the soul to find its way home.
Tu.
Great Shaman.
Look.
Is this
the shape of Dayu Ridge?
Yes, it is.
(Dayu Ridge)
This should be a shortcut.
Tu
had been thinking about going home.
If there's no problem with this path,
it can make up
for two days of travel.
We can
start experimenting!
Good.
We can start experimenting!
Yan.
Mr. Li.
Mr. Li, time waits for no one.
We found
Dayu Ridge's path,
but only through taking that path
can we know
if it's passable.
Yes.
So I thought I'd scout it
right away.
Once I get through,
I'll immediately send a pigeon
to inform you.
I'll then head north
to gather all my comrades
before you start your journey.
Good idea.
That's what I came here to tell you.
After I hear from you,
I'll set out immediately to find you.
Remember.
After passing through Dayu Ridge,
head toward Chang'an from Mei Pass
and meet up
with the litchi transport team.
Mr. Li, don't worry.
My peers will wait
for the litchi transport team
at the corresponding post station.
I'll ride my horse to the post station
closest to Chang'an
to run the last leg.
I'll make sure you return
with fresh litchis.
Thank you.
We must make sure
this relay race is flawless.
If you need any fees,
I'll ask Mr. Su to set out in advance
to distribute money
to various money posts along the route.
You can just go and collect it.
I'll issue the certificate right away.
I'll leave right away.
Be safe!
Everyone.
Listen to me.
Stay calm.
How can we be calm?
There's no trace of Ms. Amita
these days.
She dispatched my fleet
to Sasan to transport glass
and asked me
to load a ship with urgent goods,
but now there's no news.
The goods on my ship are all going bad!
Yes!
She reassigned my fleet too.
Who's supposed to take over now?
Amita asked me to procure goods.
The price has been set,
but the goods haven't arrived.
If this isn't resolved,
my reputation will be ruined!
Yes.
She was the one who mediated
Hu Merchants' Association's dispute.
She should also mediate
with Maritime Trade Office
and Inspector's Office.
There's no one in charge.
What should we do with this mess?
Yes!
- Yes!
Where do you put us by doing this?
Listen to me!
I've recorded all your affairs.
I'll give you
an explanation in the next few days.
How many days?
Chief Scribe Zhao.
Hu Merchants' Association
is in turmoil.
Everyone knows Amita
had a falling out with Inspector He.
There's no one in charge.
We have several ships of goods
stuck at the border,
waiting for her to go
to Maritime Trade Office for inspection.
Am I going to lose
the funds I invested earlier?
Why are you so impatient?
Amita isn't here,
but Inspector's Office is still there,
right?
Besides, Amita's absence
may not be a bad thing for you.
Please make it clear.
The vacancy of a chief
has caused panic among people
and makes things difficult.
The priority now
is to get the association back on track.
We need to appoint
an acting chief.
I think
you have the potential to be the chief.
Thanks for the support.
Thanks for giving me the opportunity.
I didn't give you an opportunity,
You're lucky, young and promising.
You're also grateful
and know how to repay kindness.
I know this best.
Chief Scribe Zhao, this is the deed
for the caravan's 30% net profit share.
I hope you'll keep it for me.
Chief Scribe Zhao.
Allow me to ask one more question.
A new chief will be elected
in a few days.
Will I, the acting chief,
be replaced by someone else
within a few days?
Anything is possible,
but Inspector's Office has the final say
on who the new chief will be.
Thanks for the tip.
If things do turn out as you predict,
I'll look to you for guidance
and follow your lead!
Search here.
Yes.
And here.
Go out and stand still.
Inspector He.
You must rest.
Don't get angry.
Zhao.
Inspector He.
Did you find Amita?
We're still searching for her.
Since when
did it become so difficult
to catch someone in Lingnan?
Inspector He, calm down.
The city is under lockdown.
Amita can't get away.
Her capture
is just a matter of time.
Get out.
Keep searching for her.
Inspector He.
Something
is troubling me.
Amita isn't here.
Hu merchants
are causing chaos
in Hu Merchants' Association.
I don't care.
I don't have time to deal with them.
Inspector He, Lingnan...
No.
Most of Lingnan's taxes
come from the seaport.
Hu Merchants' Association
can't go a day without a chief.
If there's any rumor in the market,
the merchants won't come,
which will be bad for us.
Go on.
I have a solution
that gives us the best of both worlds.
Didn't those Hu merchants say
they have no chief?
We'll give them an acting chief.
At the same time,
it'll send a signal
that Amita
may be unable to be re-elected.
Anyone
could be the next chief.
This way,
it can downplay
Amita's disappearance
and keep those Hu merchants
on our side.
Merchants value profit.
Everyone wants to be a chief.
Who will care
about Li Shande's transport by then?
Are you saying
that the acting chief put forward
is just a bait?
These Hu merchants
will take the bait.
When the time comes,
not even nine bulls
can drag
Su Liang and Li Shande back.
You're wise.
Who do you want to appoint?
The appointment of this acting chief
is very particular.
First,
they must have no alliances.
With alliances comes confidence.
They can still survive without us.
Second, no prestige.
With prestige, the acting chief
can easily become the real chief.
As time goes by,
they'll repeat Amita's mistakes.
We have to choose the kind
with no alliances and prestige.
Someone
who only obeys us.
Just say
you want to appoint a loser.
Out of all of them,
Xiao Yunchuan is
the biggest loser.
Zhao.
Let me ask you a question.
Why do you think so highly
of Xiao Yunchuan?
Inspector He, you...
I'm only thinking
of what's best for you.
As long as the above requirements
are met,
anyone can do it.
He's nothing more
than a puppet
you set up in the association.
I'll go to the city gate
to continue the search.
Stop.
Let's do as you say.
Yes.
Ms. Amita.
You don't have to serve me anymore.
You betrayed me
and blocked an attack for me.
We have nothing to do with each other
from now on.
Ms. Amita.
I'm just afraid
Inspector He will discover
your secret meeting with Tu,
and you'll have a falling out
with Inspector He.
After all, he's your protector...
He killed my father.
Ms. Amita.
I didn't know
your father's death
was related to Inspector He.
Back then,
I was helpless
and had to sell myself on the street
to bury my mother.
Inspector He bought me
and buried my mother.
Later, he sent me
to your side
to take care of you.
He asked me
to report
your every move to him.
I dare not disobey Inspector He,
much less hide anything from him.
I was blind
to treat you as a sister.
=The Litchi Road=
It works.
The last piece
of the strategy for litchi transport
is complete.
- Good!
Help me take someone away.
There's no need for this.
He's one of us.
Who do you want me to take away?
Amita.
Amita?
I want to go to Chang'an
and meet Left Chancellor.
Are you going back to Chang'an?
This
will decide
whether I live or die.
♪As the moon rises and the sun sets♪
♪This love still lingers♪
♪Hard to part♪
♪Thousands of miles between us,
looking both ways♪
♪We meet and part, right or wrong♪
♪Lost in the wind and rain♪
♪Time can't weigh against the heart♪
♪The past will stretch into the future♪
♪Today's smiles have already faded♪
♪But I still think of those old scenes♪
♪The seas turn into starlight♪
♪As we rush through
partings and reunions♪
♪The wind sings, and the leaves respond♪
♪Merit and fault are but illusions♪
♪Before I knew it, the journey was long♪
♪And so♪
♪Amid blooming florals, weariness grows♪
♪All that vanity♪
♪Carved into timeworn years♪
♪Ordinary days
can outlast the long road♪
♪In joy and sorrow,
you remain a stranger♪
♪The world's noise never ends♪
♪But I'd rather stay alone
with the osmanthus♪
♪Hoping the one I knew
blooms again in spring♪
♪I'll admire the flowers alone♪
♪Untouched by cold or heat♪
♪Chang'an♪
♪Is it on the way to Lingnan♪