=The Litchi Road=
(A Big Black Carp)
(Ten Years Ago)
- Hello.
- I can walk. Let go!
- You two...
- Ask Chief to be the judge.
Chief is here.
Chief, look.
- Chief, look.
- How insolent.
Stop.
Who are you?
He's new.
The academic division's Li...
The mathematics division's Li Shande.
Instead of being on duty
at Leyou Garden,
why are you back at Shanglin Office?
- He put poison.
- Nonsense.
- Poison? Don't talk nonsense.
- You put poison.
Chief.
Today,
we went to Leyou Garden to release fish.
I just got the basin
off the cart.
When I turned around,
I saw scattered leaves
floating in the water.
They're Chinese toon shoots!
It's harmless to humans
but deadly to fish.
Carps
are different from other fish.
When carps
see something moving on the water,
they'll jump up and take a bite.
People don't understand.
That's why there's the saying
"a carp leaping over the dragon gate".
Alright.
Chief.
Uphold justice for me, Chief.
Uphold justice for me too.
It must be your fault.
You want to poison these carps
and
ask Shanglin Office to buy new carps.
You'll then benefit from it.
I ask for your wise judgment.
This is slander.
Alright.
If it's true,
you'll be punished severely.
If you accused Supervisor Song wrongly,
you'll be fined one month's pay.
One month?
One...
One month is...
You two.
Why get upset
over a carp?
This guy
just joined Shanglin Office.
He doesn't know the rules yet.
He's young and impulsive.
I can understand that.
How about you both meet halfway?
Forget it.
Liangyuan.
Calm down.
I
shouldn't have
hit you today.
Here.
These two Songjiang perches
are my apology.
No, Songjiang perch
is a specialty of Huating County.
None on the market
is supplied to Eastern Palace.
Is this
from Shanglin Office's ice storage?
It is said
that Shanglin Office's ice storage
is all fruits and vegetables
from various prefectures.
They're all very precious,
especially...
I'm of low ranking.
I dare not eat.
I ask for your wise judgment.
If I falsely accuse him,
I'm willing to be fined
one month's salary.
Chief.
If it is found that I did it,
I will also accept the punishment.
Chief, you can't drink.
You just ate a golden peach.
Golden peach is warm in nature.
If you mix both,
it'll be heaty.
Chief Liu.
Chief.
Just now,
we took the fish out
and found that it was alive.
It's not dead.
No way.
It's absolutely true.
Look.
Liangyuan.
Maybe you really saw it wrong.
I don't blame you.
But
I'm afraid you can't escape
the one-month salary fine
set by Chief Liu.
This isn't the fish.
- This is the fish.
=Episode 26=
I bought some hubings
for you and Xiu'er.
I didn't expect you to be at home.
Did the approval process
not go smoothly?
Those in intellectual work rule others.
Those in labor work are ruled by others.
I now understand
how did those in intellectual work
do their work?
Officialdom is like the sea.
Bad swimmers like me
will either drown
or be killed by fish.
If I had known this,
I should have lined my pockets.
Why transport litchis?
You didn't do that
because you're different
from other officials.
You have a conscience.
I have a conscience?
What's the use of having a conscience?
I act with my conscience.
What did I get in return?
I keep running into obstacles.
I should be like
those officials.
Have no conscience.
I should do my best
to line my own pockets
and make money.
At least I can take good care
of my daughter.
Stop saying these discouraging words.
There are many people in Lingnan
who care about you.
You should do them right.
Who's going to do me right then?
Transporting litchis
is next to impossible.
Why
do you all
try to stop me?
He Youguang was willing to kill me.
Alright, we got to Chang'an.
We couldn't submit the petition.
The transport strategy
was tricked out of me.
Why?
Why are people
more vicious than wolves?
Am I the one who wants to eat litchis?
Am I who wants it?
It's His Majesty who wants to eat it.
It's Right Chancellor.
It's Right Chancellor's sister!
His sister wants to eat it!
I worked so hard
to put myself in this situation.
Why?
You don't need to persuade me.
No need to persuade me. I understand.
Are you not transporting litchis
anymore?
No.
No one will help me.
What can we transport?
What can we do?
I'm at my wit's end,
with no way out.
Forget it.
In the past few months,
it feels like there's a big rock
pressing on my chest,
making it hard to breathe.
I just took advantage
of my daughter's absence
to vent some steam.
Sorry to make a fool of myself.
How could I laugh at you?
When I lost my status as leader
and everyone around me
turned against me,
I didn't know
how I could fight against He Youguang
and avenge my father.
But you managed
to revive
a hopeless task.
I didn't give up because of you.
I met Deputy Director Lu a few days ago.
He didn't say it explicitly,
but I knew
I would be useless
before I got evidence,
even if I came to Chang'an.
But I won't give up.
I want to return to Lingnan
and personally get evidence.
I ask you not to give up either.
What brings you here?
I thought about it.
I decided to return to Lingnan
and help Yun Qing get evidence.
Lingnan?
Lingnan is He Youguang's territory.
If you go back, won't you
be walking straight
into the tiger's den?
I still have to protect you.
I thought of a foolproof plan.
If I return to Lingnan under the pretext
of running the litchi transport,
I will be working for His Majesty.
He Youguang won't kill me.
You want to be involved
in Litchi Envoy's transport?
I had fallen out with He Youguang
because of my father,
so I wanted to use this opportunity
to get an identity
that could avoid death.
But Litchi Envoy is being pushed back
and forth by all the government offices,
unable to get official approval.
This plan can't be carried out yet,
So I would like to ask
Deputy Director Lu
to help him out.
Right Chancellor
is holding a grand birthday banquet
for Noble Consort.
Its scale is unprecedented.
He prepared
rare treasures from overseas,
intending to impress everyone
at the birthday banquet.
Lingnan's litchis
just happens to be a rare commodity
that he was in charge of.
If you help Litchi Envoy
transport litchis into Chang'an,
we'll be helping Right Chancellor
steal the show.
The litchis' arrival
is nothing but icing on the cake
for Right Chancellor.
But if it can't be transported,
Litchi Envoy will die.
Litchi Envoy
was a minor official in Shanglin Office.
He's honest and loyal.
He took this doomed task
because he was tricked.
He never pocketed any money
when he was in Lingnan.
He only focused
on transporting litchis,
hoping to survive
and live his own life.
We want to overthrow Right Chancellor
so that
no more innocent people
will have to suffer like him.
If we stand by
and watch him die,
how are we different
from the rich and powerful people
who trample on human lives?
What are your chances of success
after your return to Lingnan?
I thought of someone.
He must have
evidence of He Youguang's corruption.
Master Konglang
can't make a move on this person,
but I'm very confident
in making him change sides.
Recently,
I went to Konglang Bookstore
to buy information
and ran into Ma Guiyun.
Was he also there to buy information?
It's not that simple.
He held
a pink round fan.
It's obvious
that it's a gift for a lady.
But the only female member
of Konglang Bookstore
is Master Konglang
who never showed herself.
So Ma Guiyun wants to pursue
Master Konglang?
Why are you so worked up
about love affairs?
Are you jealous?
Don't talk nonsense.
All you see is love affairs.
Have you ever thought
that if they had
this kind of relationship,
he would not only have known
all the information I bought,
but the information
Master Konglang replied to me
may also not be completely true?
This is complicated.
Unfathomable.
I doubt
he's not
Ma Guiyun,
the envoy sent by Right Chancellor.
Ping'an?
Yes.
I arrived at Lingnan smoothly.
Why are you here too?
How could it be such a coincidence
that Pan Bao, who met Ma Guiyun,
died in Chang'an?
26 days ago?
Pan Bao died?
How come I didn't receive any news?
The new envoy Right Chancellor sent
died before he could finish speaking.
You...
You're not...
It's not that I won't go back.
I really can't go back.
The only person
who can prove his identity
is Master Konglang.
But why did he
impersonate Ma Guiyun?
For money.
It's not a big deal if it's for money.
I suspect
he doesn't work for Right Chancellor
but Left Chancellor.
The only person
who can compete with Right Chancellor
in the court
is Left Chancellor.
Gosh.
You're clever.
You saw through Chang'an's affairs
so thoroughly.
But why did Left Chancellor
send him to Lingnan?
Maybe it was to bring down He Youguang,
thus implicating
the downfall of Right Chancellor.
This is...
A big deal.
Why don't you
report this to He Youguang right away?
I can't interfere.
Or we'd be in the same boat
as He Youguang.
I didn't know
he killed Haihu.
He was so cruel to his brother
who had been through everything
with him,
let alone me?
The innocent suffer
when others battle.
You're the chief scribe
at Inspector's Office.
When the reckoning starts,
you're bound to be involved.
Well...
What should we do?
Don't worry.
Have you hidden
all the evidence I asked you to collect?
Don't worry.
I did. They're safe and sound.
That's good.
It can save us
at the critical moment.
If...
If I'm not wrong
about Ma Guiyun's identity,
everything will fall apart.
He Youguang.
All these years, I worked so hard
managing Inspector's Office,
but he treated me like a slave
and humiliated me at will.
Now,
don't blame me
for trying to protect myself.
I was impulsive.
I negotiated with Zhao Xinmin.
I should be able to get away with it.
You've been exposed.
Zhao Xinmin
used to sell Sea Sail Fund in Lingnan.
He moves seamlessly
among people from all walks of life.
He's best at reading people.
The fact that he has been able
to become He Youguang's chief scribe
over the years
shows that he's more cunning
than others.
If he doesn't believe you,
you can just go back to Chang'an.
He doesn't believe me now.
Today,
if he wants Amita's whereabouts,
he won't believe me,
no matter what I tell him.
I was careless.
How should I make up for it?
Forget it.
I'll handle Zhao Xinmin.
Stop for a moment.
Before Tu died,
he said he had evidence
of He Youguang buying fire oil.
If we can get the evidence
as soon as possible,
we don't need to worry
about these trivial matters anymore.
Have you found
the whereabouts of the evidence?
Luotuo.
Let's go.
I checked it once.
Tu probably gave the evidence
to his childhood sweetheart, Chai.
Chai?
She's also a member of Dong people.
Tell your master
that I will
investigate this myself.
Who's discussing me behind my back?
Gou'er.
Get some water for the ladies.
Alright.
Since you're sincere,
I'll help you ask around.
Why is there no news from Li Shande
since he returned to Chang'an?
Is he still transporting litchis?
Of course he is.
He must be dealing with the transport
in Chang'an.
Don't worry. He's always thinking
about the litchi garden and you.
I wondered
why I sneezed.
Turns out that Li Shande is missing me.
Sir, how much is this?
Ten coins a piece.
How expensive.
I can buy a few hubings with that price.
Why don't you buy hubings?
Being able to open
a pastry shop in Pingkang Ward
means I'm pretty skilled.
The Suxiang biscuits you picked
are unique in Chang'an.
It's only available in my shop.
The crust is crispy and soft
with a meat filling inside.
It's sweet and salty.
Hubing is just maltose candy.
You can also taste this.
If you say so,
choose something else.
This one.
This one is more expensive
than Suxiang biscuits.
This one is ugly.
It's not suitable as a gift.
What about this one?
These are Yulu balls.
Yulu balls? What a good name.
This must be very expensive.
It's actually
the cheapest
among these pastries.
How much is it?
Five coins.
I like this.
If I buy five,
can you give me
the crumbled one for free?
How can you
give the crumbled one as a gift?
I'm keeping it for myself to taste.
Sure.
Supervisor Xu.
Litchi Envoy is here again.
Why are you here again?
Well,
I was just passing by
Pingkang Ward's pastry shop.
Yulu balls.
They're freshly made.
I brought this for you to try.
What are you doing?
Take it away.
Try it.
I'm unworthy
of your Yulu balls.
I really can't submit
your petition.
Last time,
I got anxious
and left in anger,
ending it in a bad mood.
Don't blame me.
I didn't see this
from your perspective. Don't blame me.
I didn't come here
to submit the petition today.
I'm just here to apologize.
Liangyuan.
Given your personality,
you're not cut out
to flatter others.
It's just a misunderstanding.
We were classmates for three years.
How could I blame you for this?
We should blame your task.
Whoever gets involved
won't have it easy.
It's my fault
for losing my original intention.
I've been an official for many years,
but I've become so cunning.
I'm really ashamed.
We both have difficulties.
I hope you'll forgive me.
It's human nature.
Yes, if you do this
for me,
everyone else will be asking
for favors too.
You'll be put on the spot.
I didn't come back
for favors.
I just want to inquire about something.
Just go ahead.
I heard Attendant Yu
was in charge of procuring items
for Noble Consort's birthday banquet.
Has he
been to Left Storage Office recently?
You must have heard it wrongly.
Attendant Yu
is in charge of purchasing,
but he didn't have
to personally handle
the trivial matters of storing.
The servants will handle it.
Liangyuan.
Why are you asking about Attendant Yu?
Hasn't he always been
good at transporting and purchasing?
He has experience.
I want to learn from him.
Do you know
where I can I him?
The items he's purchasing are so diverse
that he must have been traveling around
and had no permanent home.
I'm afraid it's difficult
to see him.
How about this?
I'll tell you
if I meet him.
If the opportunity is right,
I will definitely introduce you.
How about that?
Thank you.
Liangyuan.
Don't misunderstand me again this time.
I'll stop bothering you.
I...
You can take these Yulu balls back.
You can keep them for yourself.
No need to be so polite with me
from now on.
You're making our three years
as classmates seem like it was nothing.
Take it away.
Well...
Well, I'll do whatever you say.
How about this? I...
I'll take a piece
for my daughter.
Keep the rest.
Attendant Yu, you
have been working very hard
on the purchasing matters recently.
You worked hard.
Noble Consort's birthday banquet
is a task
assigned by His Majesty.
Right Chancellor has entrusted me
with this task.
How can I feel at ease
if I don't oversee it personally?
Yes.
You're dedicated to your duties
and are truly a role model
for our generation.
(Purchase List)
By the way,
a Litchi Envoy came by just now
to inquire about your whereabouts.
I don't know what he wants,
so I sent him away.
Supervisor Xu.
Tribute goods have been
coming and going frequently
in Left Storage Office recently.
You probably
haven't had a day off for a long time.
I hosted a dinner today
and invited
Ministry of War's Carriage Director
and Ministry of Revenue's
Bureau of General Accounts'
Chief Clerk of Affairs.
Do you
want to join us?
Thank you for the honor.
I will attend it.
Attendant Yu.
These are the Yulu balls
I bought from Pingkang Ward.
Try it.
Made any progress?
Deputy Director Lu sent me a message.
He said the litchi transport
is supervised by Right Chancellor.
Left Chancellor and Security Bureau
can't intervene, but he found
a way to meet Right Chancellor.
What?
The patron that Madam Shiqi mentioned
is Right Chancellor.
Madam Shiqi knows Right Chancellor?
Do you know if they're close?
But Madam Shiqi is just a common
moneylender.
She probably doesn't have
any direct ties with Right Chancellor.
But at least
she can pass on the message.
Right Chancellor
is in charge of the litchis.
It's also to celebrate
Noble Consort's birthday.
You've made some progress.
Right Chancellor
has no reason not to see you.
But that villain is a handful.
Madam Shiqi has been forcing me
to pay her.
If I go to her,
it means I can't get the approval.
It's mainly because I'm scared
she'll do something to my child.
There's a saying among pirates.
When facing interests,
your enemy
can become your friend in the end.
If she really wants you to pay her,
she'll consider helping you.
Asking her is indeed the worst option,
but you have no other choice.
After days of maneuvering,
we still have to pull teeth
from the tiger's mouth.
I invited all of you here today.
Firstly, I want to introduce you
to each other.
This way, you'll have support
in the court.
Secondly,
I want to trouble you
with a small matter.
Just go ahead.
I want to talk
about Litchi Envoy.
Attendant Yu, please rest assured.
This person was my classmate,
but
we're not friends.
He submitted a petition to me.
I immediately turned against him.
Litchi Envoy also came
to Bureau of General Accounts.
I said a few words to him
and sent him to Hall of State Affairs
to bother the officials.
It's not necessary
to go to such lengths.
Litchi Envoy didn't even make it
to Ministry of War.
Litchi Envoy
is
working for His Majesty.
I want to tell you
not to push it around.
This approval
should be given to him
as soon as possible.
It just so happens that I brought
the petition he wrote today.
Attendant Yu.
It's not that I don't want to do it.
It's because Bureau of General Accounts
is responsible for Imperial Treasury.
We need to be extra careful.
Attendant Yu.
He and I were classmates after all.
I never lied to him.
The litchis don't need to be stored
after entering Chang'an.
The storage he needs
is on the way.
It has nothing to do
with Left Storage Office.
Attendant Yu.
You're also an expert
in transporting items.
Set aside the expensive expenses
from Lingnan to Chang'an first.
Let's just talk about litchis.
No matter how fresh the litchi is,
it will have already rotted
and stank after more
than ten days of traveling.
Who would believe
that he could transport them?
I would.
If you think about it,
litchis don't need to be stored,
but they're contributed by all parties.
They're indeed under the jurisdiction
of Left Storage Office.
Attendant Yu.
Litchi Envoy...
He...
The money and food
he needs are all clear.
The money he needs
should be allocated first.
We should help him with this.
We should help him.
I thought you invited me today
to make friends.
I didn't expect it to be a trap.
Our principles differ,
we can't work together.
Farewell.
Zhou Sanlang.
What brought you here?
Director Ma.
I, a member of Baiwang people,
Zhou Sanlang, greet the master.
Chang'an's Baiwang people
are willing to do anything for you.
We're at your command.
Director Ma.
We have such a large-scale
smuggling business.
If it weren't for Attendant Yu,
who had been helping to cover up,
you and I
would have been locked up
by Ministry of Justice long ago.
Of course.
Attendant Yu.
The transportation of litchis
is under the jurisdiction
of Carriage Bureau.
It's my job.
I dare not reject.
Here.
Attendant Yu.
(Pingkang Ward)
It's not difficult
to get approval.
I just need your help.
What does it have to do with me?
If we follow the procedure,
it will take a long time
and the process will be lengthy.
You can't wait for this.
I can't wait either.
If we have
someone highly respected
help me get out of the procedures...
If they help me
get out of the procedures,
you and I will be pleased.
Don't beat around the bush with me.
Just tell me
how I can help you.
I heard
your patrons
include Right Chancellor, who oversees
the litchi transport.
If I could meet him,
our dilemma
would be solved.
Li Shande.
Have you lost your mind?
You want to see Right Chancellor?
I can't even see him.
Who gave you the audacity?
Just help me pass on a message.
I'm very sure
that Right Chancellor wants
to bring litchis to His Majesty.
He'll meet me.
Do you know that there are many people
in Pingkang Ward who want to see
Right Chancellor?
Several rooms in the ward
are all used to store gifts.
Even so,
not many people can get what they want.
Do you think
I can help you
by saying a few lies?
I know
it's abrupt of me to speak so rashly.
Look.
You and me...
The two of us
are linked together because of a loan.
Now, my...
My life is at stake.
If I die,
won't you business...
You really are a math major.
You refused to pay me back
and eloquently
pinned the blame on me.
I, Madam Shiqi,
grew up in Pingkang Ward.
I've seen everything.
I can handle your threats.
I now understand
that you can't get the approval.
Hurry back and raise money.
If you can't pay it back,
don't blame me for being cruel to you.
Madam Shiqi.
I brought the deed with me.
This is all I own
and my daughter's
future home.
I know
I will have a way to survive
if I can meet Right Chancellor,
but I don't know how.
If you can help me,
I'm willing to mortgage this deed
here.
I can't bear to see someone so pitiful.
I'll pass on the message for you.
If we get into this mess,
we might lose our jobs.
If we don't respond,
we'll lose our jobs immediately.
But I still don't understand
why Attendant Yu did this.
Could it be possible
that litchis
could be transported to Chang'an?
If there's no fish,
why will the turtle move?
There's a turtle on top
that will eat big fish again.
In that case, wait
at your office tomorrow.
Baiwang people, Feng Shiqi,
is here to meet the master.
=The Litchi Road=
Tomorrow at noon,
Right Chancellor
will pass through the palace corridor.
Whether you can make him stop for you
depends on your luck.
Shanglin Office's supervisor,
Litchi Envoy,
Li Shande
is here to meet Right Chancellor!
Many people don't want you
to make it happen.
What do you think?
The Han emperor
longed for a beauty to rival a nation
For years he ruled,
yet couldn't find one
A girl from the Yang family
came of age
Raised in her chamber,
unknown to the world
Born with stunning grace
she couldn't hide
One day,
she was chosen to serve by his side
She glanced back
with a smile of myriad charms
All the palace beauties
lost their glow
In the chilly spring,
she bathed at Huaqing Pond
The warm spring water
slid over her silky skin
Handmaids helped her
rise from the water
Thus began the time
she gained the emperor's favor
Flowing hair, a flower-bright face,
and a hairpin of glamour
In the warm lotus canopy,
they spent spring nights together
Those sweet nights were too short,
he rose until noon
From then on,
he skipped the morning court
Always at his side,
forever delighting and dining
They spent spring on spring outings,
night on night together
In the palace
lived three thousand beauties
Yet all three thousand favors
were hers alone