=The Litchi Road=
(Ju)
=Episode 12=
Ma Guiyun really said that?
Yes.
So are we giving him
the horses or not?
If we do, it makes us look guilty.
If we don't,
that lunatic might flip out
and drag us all down with him.
I doubt Li Shande
is that shrewd.
Ma Guiyun's words are not to be taken
at face value.
You just started
dealing with him.
You do not understand.
The first time I met him,
I also thought
he was just some foolish, dull bumpkin.
I later realized
he is unpredictable and very clever.
I think we should just give him the horses.
It is only a test anyway.
Let's see
what kind of trouble he can stir up.
I just can't accept it.
We spent so much effort
laying this trap, digging this pit,
and now he just breaks through it.
I can't accept that.
Zhao.
You always say that you two
are evenly matched,
worthy rivals.
Why are you so quiet now?
If he were a dog,
you feed him, tame him,
and maybe he becomes your pet.
But this man is like a taotie.
His greed knows no end.
I'm afraid if we give him the horses,
he will keep asking for more.
If we have to give them,
let's be smart about it.
Over there, sir.
Mr. Li.
Our leader, hearing of your troubles,
specially had two fine horses
brought from Lingnan,
and sent me to deliver them
to you as a gift.
No, I told your leader
I needed 100 fine horses.
Ms. Amita said,
although these horses are untamed,
they are full of spirit.
With skilled riders,
each could be worth 100 on their own.
With these two, you have 200.
That's not the same.
Can they really travel
1,000 li in one day?
Absolutely.
This is Rixing. The other is Qianli.
[*Rixing and Qianli means travel 1,000 li in one day]
Ms. Amita
wishes you triumph
and success in your trials.
We take our leave.
The women of Lingnan
are really something.
They are clever and tactful.
She delivered the horses, all right.
Willingly and respectfully.
I did not expect them
to be this cunning.
Using this method to brush us off.
Shande, listen.
You cannot seriously be mad at me.
Shande!
Can you find me the best riders
in Lingnan?
Are you crazy?
I have seen those two horses.
They belonged to He Youguang.
He gave them just to mess with us.
They are wild horses.
Horses that have broken a lot of ribs.
You cannot be serious.
I am serious.
We have no choice but to adapt.
Worst case,
if they really are good horses,
I will use them as the vanguard
in the first trial run.
We're splitting into four routes, right?
Two won't be enough.
Well, what else can we do?
You're Ma Guiyun.
You sort this out.
Figure out
how we're getting the rest of them!
This one looks tasty. Try it.
Li!
Litchi Envoy!
Li Shande!
Over here, Li!
Did you crawl out of the mud?
Did you fall off the horse or something?
Don't remind me.
They told me these were fine horses.
But their temper is terrible.
They would not let me get on.
I tied myself to them with a hemp rope,
and they threw me right off.
Look at me.
Slow down.
Careful!
Take it easy.
Don't push yourself.
I was just like that earlier.
Yan Yazhuang, don't bite off
more than you can chew!
Get out of the way!
Way to go, Yan Yazhuang!
Did not expect you
to have these skills.
I thought all you could ride
was a donkey.
This horse may be hot-tempered,
but it is a fine steed.
If an expert rider were to tame it,
it could travel a thousand li a day,
swift as the wind.
You're the expert
I've been searching for.
I hereby recruit you as a rider
for the litchi transport trial.
Once Su gets back,
he will pay you.
Rider?
Who said I wanted to be a rider?
Yan Yazhuang.
You are the only one
who can mount this horse.
This money should be yours.
That money is enough to feed
and clothe you for half a year.
I'm not doing it
no matter how much you pay me.
Yan Yazhuang.
Listen to me.
Li Shande's business
is the litchi garden's business.
And the litchi garden's business
is your business.
You're doing this
whether you like it or not.
I'm not
changing my mind.
End of discussion.
Yan Yazhuang!
Why will you not help with this?
Why should I help him?
That Li Shande is unreliable.
Always going on about
how he is the Litchi Envoy
appointed by His Majesty.
But if that were true,
why won't the Inspector's Office help him?
He walks around all day
with that plaque of his aimlessly.
He doesn't even have a proper office.
It's obvious he isn't a proper envoy.
Why should we follow his orders?
In the past,
most of the litchi garden's harvest
had to be turned in as taxes
to the local government.
He turned this place
into an imperial litchi garden.
With His Majesty's protection,
no one dares bully us anymore.
Once it's the sixth month
and the litchis are delivered
to Chang'an,
I'll able to hand out
this year's harvest to everyone.
He is helping us.
And what if he can't get them
to Chang'an?
Our livelihoods depend
on this litchi garden.
We worked the whole season.
What if we get nothing in the end?
This garden feeds a lot of people.
We have many mouths to feed.
What will we do if he fails?
Do you really think Li Shande cares?
Even if he does care,
he's barely making ends meet himself.
What can he do?
Why... Why are you so determined
to trust him?
The first time I met Li Shande was
at the market.
A few thugs came looking for trouble.
He stepped in and helped me out.
The second time was
at the litchi garden.
Officials from the Inspector's Office
sent a bunch of people to seize the garden.
He helped resolve the situation again.
He is an official,
but has none of that arrogance.
Not only does he work alongside us,
he also goes to great lengths
to come up with ideas
to preserve the litchis.
Would someone go through all that just
to cheat us out of one season's harvest?
Yan Yazhuang.
You were once an outsider
to the litchi garden too.
You know,
the Dong people may be simple-minded,
but we are not fools.
We can tell good from bad.
Li Shande helped us.
If we turn a blind eye now,
we are asking for divine punishment.
He may be your benefactor,
but he is not mine.
I do not want
to stick my neck out for this.
You are a fine steed indeed.
Fast as the wind.
But a temper to match the tempest.
Too much of a temper.
Still, you are luckier than me.
Much luckier.
I thought you were just a mad horse,
trapped in a stable.
But you found someone
who understands you.
And now,
you get to shine.
Li Shande.
I'm sorry. He can't be your rider.
Why not?
Is it because of the payment?
No.
You're one of us now.
I don't want to lie to you.
He is a deserter.
I have never asked why he ran,
but I know he is not a bad person.
My father who took him in.
When my father was ill,
someone tried to seize
the litchi garden.
He fought them off with all he had.
Got some nasty scars from that.
All these years,
I have treated him like my own brother.
So if he thinks riding
for you is too risky,
I won't force him.
You're right.
We shouldn't force people into things.
To be honest,
even having one rider
will not solve the urgent need
for a four-route trial.
I will think of something else.
Su, it really is unfortunate timing.
There is a horse plague going around.
Not the best time
for trading horses, you see.
It's the truth.
Hadi.
You are not being honest with me.
I'm telling the truth.
I know
you are just afraid of offending Amita.
Su.
If you already know that,
why are you putting me
in this difficult spot?
The Merchants' Association was supposed
to be a place for Hu merchants
to support each other.
Yet, everyone lives in fear
of its leader now.
How pathetic.
I heard that Amita secretly bought
a large batch of colored glaze
from Sasan,
and she wants to keep
all the profits for herself.
Yet, she demands
a share of your business.
How despicable.
Are you all willing to stay silent
and let yourselves be taken advantage of?
Amita has Inspector He behind her.
Who can do business in Lingnan
without going through him?
The tolls at checkpoints
are unavoidable.
If they can grease the wheels
at the Maritime Trade Office,
what is the harm in giving them a cut?
Today,
they take 10%.
Tomorrow,
they will find a way
to demand 50%.
You joined the Merchants' Association
the latest.
You're a small boat.
If a storm comes,
you will be the first to capsize.
I heard
you are trying to charm Amita?
Just my guess.
I doubt you have
genuine affections for her.
You are just trying
to board her ship with the full sails.
But you had better think carefully.
Once you get on her ship,
she will have you by the nose,
and you will be
forever trapped in Lingnan.
We are helping Mr. Li transport litchis
so we can one day free ourselves
from Amita's control.
I, Su Liang,
do not do losing business.
The route to Chang'an
will open up many,
many new business opportunities.
Just think about it.
Is that not the perfect chance for you?
Su.
Why are you here?
Mr. Li.
I went to the post station
looking for you.
They said you went to the litchi garden.
With the sun setting,
I figured you would be back by now,
so I waited here to welcome you.
What is it?
Here is the thing.
For transporting the litchis
across four routes all at once,
we need a lot of good horses.
If...
I mean, if.
If we can't procure enough fine steeds,
will inferior ones really not suffice?
It's 5,000 li to Chang'an.
Yes.
Even the best horses will be pushed
to their limits, let alone inferior ones.
I ran the numbers.
On the road to Chang'an,
there is a post station
roughly every 30 li.
Average horses will be exhausted
before even reaching one.
Those calculations would be pointless.
If we can have fine horses
relaying back and forth,
perhaps that would solve the problem.
Relaying back and forth?
Like mill donkeys.
Even if a donkey walks 1,000 li,
it is only going in circles
in a small space.
A relay...
Wait...
I think I might have an idea.
Let me go back and do some math.
I'll do the calculations again!
Should I still keep looking for horses?
Yes!
What about donkeys?
What is he tinkering with now?
He is making a "ju."
A "ju"?
What for?
A ju is a measuring tool.
It is made of two perpendicular arms.
The short arm is called the gou,
the long one is the gu.
Both arms have markings.
Its most direct use
is to measure right angles.
Back in the Western Zhou,
the mathematician Shang Gao
discovered the gou-gu numbers.
Using the ju,
you can calculate all sorts of things.
Use the level ju to straighten a rope.
Tilt the ju to measure height.
Flip it to gauge depth.
Lay it down flat to measure distance.
Circle it around
to form a perfect round.
Join them to create a square.
You're putting me to sleep.
Li Shande.
Explain what you are trying to do here.
Li, hand me a rope.
Higher.
If this ju's angle aligns
with that angle,
then we can tell
whether this rope is level.
This is "leveling the ju
to straighten the rope."
If we want to know how tall that tree is...
Move aside, Li.
First,
we measure the distance
from me to the tree.
Then, use the ju
to sight the tree top,
and mark the scale
where the line of sight aligns with the tip.
By the principle of proportionality,
we can calculate the tree's height.
This is "tilting the ju to measure height."
Same principle applies
to gauging depth and distance.
That's "flipping the ju to measure depth,"
and "laying it down to measure distance."
If we put two jus together,
we can form a circle.
In this world,
there are squares and circles.
With both, we can measure anything.
That's all there is to it.
Understand?
I still don't understand everything,
but it sounds impressive.
Sorry.
I was showing off.
So, what exactly
are you trying to measure?
Who here knows
the roads of Lingnan best?
Yan Yazhuang, of course.
He could find his way
with his eyes closed.
Yes.
- That's true.
- What road are you looking for?
Can you go with me
to Small East Gate tomorrow?
You will know when we get there.
You guide the way,
and I will do the calculations.
Yan Yazhuang, you can't turn down
this favor now, can you?
When do we leave?
Third quarter of the Mao hour.
I'll see you at Small East Gate.
Mr. Li.
What kind of road are you looking for?
Ideally, a loop.
About 20 li of flat road
and 10 li of mountain road,
so that we can circle back
to where we started.
(East Gate, Small East Gate)
(The idea of a loop trial run)
(was like carving out a sliver
of hope in a desperate situation.)
(All that was left
was to find a capable rider,)
(and the plan would be complete.)
(East Gate, Small East Gate, South Gate)
(Xiu'er,)
(I am staking everything on this.)
- 95!
- (I am now one step closer to Chang'an.)
All right.
Can you manage it, Li?
(Great North Gate,
Small North Gate, East Gate)
Stop.
(Great North Gate,
Small East Gate, South Gate, West Gate)
(Total distance: 30 li)
I brought some cheese for Amita.
Serve this drizzled with honey
I made myself.
She is sure to love it.
Go get her so she can try it.
Hadi, Ms. Amita is unwell today.
She is not receiving visitors.
Please leave.
Is she down with a cold?
I know a bit of medicine.
Let me in to take a look.
Hadi.
Ms. Amita's bedchamber is not
for someone like you to enter.
Ms. Hongyu.
I also came
to confirm a rumor.
I heard
she plans to import
a large shipment of colored glaze
from Sasan.
Is that true?
I'm just a maid.
I don't know anything about that.
Please ask Ms. Amita yourself
when she recovers.
- Maybe...
- Well, things sure are lively today.
Mr. Ma.
Ms. Amita is unwell.
She is not receiving visitors.
You should go too.
Unwell?
Is it a cold?
I know some medicine.
Let me check on her.
Stop right there!
You think you can just walk
into Ms. Amita's bedchamber?
Who are you?
That's my question.
I see you brought a token of affection.
What's the matter?
Amita did not accept it?
Better than showing up
empty-handed, no?
May I ask your name?
Hadi.
I also have a Tang name.
Xiao Yunchuan.
With a "Yun" in it too.
How about this?
Since Amita is not in a state
to receive guests,
why do you and I find a place
to get to know each other better?
Us?
All right.
Let's go. I am not afraid of you.
- Let's go.
- Do let Amita know I was here.
- Come on!
I'll be right back.
You and I should admire
each other as heroes.
But alas, we both have
good taste in women.
For this fated bond,
Yunchuan,
I drink to you.
How long have you been pursuing Amita?
Three years.
For the past three years,
I've tended to her every need and whim.
Now,
I am her trusted confidant.
I'm just a step away
from becoming her lover.
Just a step away?
Obviously,
you do not understand women.
Women are easy to move emotionally.
You have courted her for three years.
If she liked you even a little,
she would have forced herself
to accept your affections,
even if she found them nauseating.
You can be her trusted confidant.
A close friend.
But never a lover.
Yunchuan.
Give it up.
You never had a chance.
Me? Give up?
And you think you have a shot?
What do you even have?
Talent?
Looks?
You are being shallow.
I never try
to impress women with my appearance.
My strengths lie...
That is awfully rude of you.
Is my advantage not obvious?
I hail from Chang'an.
So what if you are from the capital?
Of course, it matters.
Because I am from Chang'an,
I do not conflict
with Amita's interests in Lingnan.
She tells me
all her local dealings,
but not you. Never with you.
She can't and she won't.
Isn't that right?
Like what?
If you can't name any,
then you're just lying to me.
Why would I lie?
She told me
that she used to be wary
of transporting expensive goods by sea,
but now she isn't,
because she has military protection.
Military?
No need to speak of it aloud,
lest disaster follows loose lips.
There were rumors of her purchasing
a large shipment of colored glaze
from Sasan.
I didn't believe them.
She used to avoid
the Sasan trade routes entirely.
Did she change her mind
because she found a backer?
She told me not to share this
with another soul.
Said to wait
until the time is right.
At the very least,
not until after the leadership change
in the Hu Merchants' Association.
But today, I felt a connection with you,
so I let a little more slip.
We are both entangled by love.
- Heed my advice...
- Thank you for your honesty, Mr. Ma.
I dare not compete with you.
Please, do as you wish.
I won't disturb you further.
Thanks for the hospitality.
Farewell.
Mr. Hadi,
you have a heavy heart
after drinking with that man.
In the past...
When our cargo ships arrived in port,
to keep the shipping route open,
we only needed to give Amita
10% of our profits, yes?
Yes.
But if what he said is true,
and even the sea routes
are now under Inspector He's control,
then once our ships leave the port,
we will be exploited
by them both at every turn.
That means soon
they'll have absolute power,
and we will have to play by their rules.
Su is right.
As long as we are trapped in Lingnan,
we will always be at their mercy.
We will be led around
by the nose forever.
It is time we find another path.
You.
Choose the finest horses
and take them to Su.
What price should I ask?
Do not charge him.
Tell them it's a loan from me.
A token of goodwill.
Your foot is in this condition
and you didn't tell me?
You're not fine. Let me take a look.
Come here. Let me have a look at it.
Show me that foot.
Let me see it.
That wound could be infected,
and you're worried about your shoes?
Good thing I brought herbs.
This is hairy agrimony.
Anti-inflammatory and pain-relieving.
Grind it up
and apply it.
Here.
You know how to use it, right?
It's a mess.
We will have
to camp here overnight.
This calls for some litchi brew.
Give Li a cup too.
Li.
Just drink it.
Do it.
Thank you
for helping me
map the route today.
And to Li,
for all your services.
Let me toast you both.
Mr. Li.
Mr. Li,
you treat Li very well.
And he works hard for me.
He's not a slave.
He's a friend.
Mr. Li.
I know you're a good man.
It's not that I don't want to help you.
I simply can't risk
exposing my identity.
I've been in hiding all these years.
I haven't even returned home once.
I understand.
Tong told me
about your past.
I understand.
Everyone has their own secrets
and burdens.
You must have had your reasons
for becoming a deserter.
Mr. Li.
I'm not a deserter.
I was framed.
Back then,
we were on naval patrol
when we spotted a group of pirates
hijacking a ship transporting herbs.
I shot an arrow
and hit the pirate captain,
forcing him to the stern.
But their reinforcements arrived.
We were outnumbered,
and had no choice but to jump ship.
I was rescued by fishermen.
By the time I recovered
and returned to Lingnan,
we had all been listed
as military deserters.
Is it possible
that it was just a misunderstanding
because you had been gone too long?
That's what
we thought at first too.
But when one of our men
tried to explain to the authorities,
he was executed under military law.
After that, the rest of us knew
going back meant certain death.
Mr. Li.
You are new to Lingnan.
You don't know the rules here.
Here, the officials and bandits
are often in collusion.
When trouble happens,
it's always us little people
who take the fall.
It's a pity, given all your skills.
My skills are not worth mentioning.
You should have seen
my fellow soldiers.
They were the real experts.
Really?
Archery, horseback, sailing,
they could do it all.
They charged into battle without fear.
All they wanted was to return home
in glory one day.
But now?
We're all separated,
scattered, hiding.
Freedom may never come again.
Don't be so pessimistic.
We make our own destiny.
You're still better off than me.
I'm the one clinging to life
in a hopeless situation.
You will
find your way again.
Mr. Li.
Have a seat.
These past few days,
I've been thinking about what you said.
You need adept riders for your trial.
My fellow soldiers
are the experts you need.
So,
could use your status as the Litchi Envoy
to help clear our names
and obtain a pardon for us?
If...
I mean, if.
If you manage to pull it off,
we will help you with all we have.
Even if it means risking our lives
and everything we have.
Really?
Yes.
Mr. Li...
I...
Please get up, Mr. Li.
I can't accept this.
Thank you.
But...
I can certainly try to apply for a pardon
on your behalf.
If it succeeds, that would be wonderful.
But if it fails,
you might not even be able
to stay in this garden.
Mr. Li.
I have been on the run for years.
I know how slim the chances are.
No matter the outcome,
I'm ready to accept it.
Your willingness to try
is already more than I could ask for.
Mr. Li.
I have a piece of evidence.
I seized this from
the pirate captain that day.
Keep it with you for now.
I will give it a try.
You really are something.
You want to appeal to Inspector He?
Do you even know
that he used to be a pirate?
What if he is in league with those pirates,
and ends up arresting those people?
Was your little overnight disappearance
just you digging your own grave?
I just thought I'd do what I can to help.
Yan really is a skilled rider.
And more importantly,
he came to me willingly.
The man is trusting me with his life,
so I figured I should at least give it a try.
You figured you'd try?
Of all the paths in this world,
you had to pick the hardest one.
Is it easier to pardon a deserter,
or to find a good rider?
It's not just one rider.
It's a whole team of riders.
Yan said
he has several brothers-in-arms.
All of them are expert horsemen.
Well, I'm warning you now.
When you see Inspector He,
do not mention that you've seen this man,
and do not bring up that dagger.
We'll test the waters first.
See what kind of attitude he has
toward this matter before we decide what to do.
You're right.
I can't expose Yan just yet.
We'll give it a test first.
Take it step by step.
Since we are already talking about this,
I will help you one more time.
I'll give you a little extra push.
You?
Was it not me
who gave the horse situation a push?
Good news!
- Good news!
- Su.
Good evening.
Sit down and tell us.
What is this great news?
Guess what?
With my silver tongue,
I managed to talk Hu merchant Hadi
into giving us some fine horses.
Really?
Absolutely.
Told you my "little push" would work,
didn't I?
This man has done it!
Six horses?
Six horses.
Six.
You only needed six,
and now you got exactly what you wanted?
I only need six for now.
We have six horses.
That is wonderful!
Please help me choose
the six best ones.
Of course.
Also,
Su,
can you help me find
some experienced riders?
How many "horses" do you need?
How many people.
Riders.
Right. How many riders?
The more, the better.
Finding good riders
in Lingnan may not be easy.
True. Here's what we'll do.
I will look on my end as well.
We will prepare on both sides.
Excellent.
Rest assured, Envoy Li.
I will give it everything I have.
Like a baby sucking milk.
I await good news.
Thank you, Su.
Gou'er, bring a basin.
Soak your feet too.
Bring a clean one.
You are being too kind.
Not at all.
It relieves fatigue.
Indeed.
Where I come from,
we just strip down and soak in the sea.
We don't have to do that in Chang'an.
That's true.
=The Litchi Road=
What is it that you actually want?
Let's make a deal.
So,
you two already talked this over?
I must ask him in person
who betrayed my father.
You are a professional rider?
I run a cockfighting arena.
That's crossing into another field.
This is great!
Yes!
Although I cling to a branch
in Lingnan
I'm popular
My immortal aura drifted to Chang'an
Driving people mad
Who wore out their shoes for me
Running around all day without rest
Just to earn a sweet fruit to eat?
Everyone
wants a taste of something new
I stumble through mountains, rivers,
lakes, and seas
In my dreams
Endless deceit
Absurd negotiation
I also want to see
red tiles and golden bricks
A prosperous world
But all I see
Is a man crying all night
A little bit every day
A little bit crazier
I was once carefree in Lingnan,
only sharing the moonlight
With heaven and earth
I'm popular but with nowhere to rest
I saw the greed of the world
I was once carefree in Lingnan,
only wishing
To return to the forest and dream
Enjoy the breeze
and the crescent moon again
Carefree and humble from then on
A little bit every day
A little bit crazier
A day of insanity after another
I was once carefree in Lingnan,
swinging on green hills
And leafy branches
One day we'll meet in Chang'an
Embark on this crazy destiny