=The Litchi Road=
(A Lone Path Up Mount Hua)
(Fifteen Years Ago)
Liangyuan?
Liangyuan!
Guess who I just ran into.
Who?
The new student of
the Crown Prince's Bureau, Mr. Cui.
Why the blank stare?
Come with me.
Go where?
To meet Mr. Cui.
You know, Mr. Cui Shiyi.
He's new to the Imperial College.
You haven't met him yet.
From the Cui clan of Qinghe.
His father is the Vice Minister
at the Crown Prince's Bureau.
Young lords of the Wang family
of Taiyuan will be there.
Come on.
I'm just a commoner.
I'd better not.
You go.
Liangyuan.
If you insist,
I'll go then.
This mountain is really tall.
Jinniang?
Young Lady Zheng.
She's from the Zheng clan of Xingyang,
once betrothed to the Shiyi.
What happened?
It's nothing.
I sprained my ankle.
It's been half a year.
Is your family well?
Thanks to you,
all is well.
She is a noblewoman.
The matchmakers
kept knocking on her door.
Even sons of high officials
could hardly win her hand.
Why was the engagement broken?
Half a year ago,
Jinniang's father's branch
was expelled from the Zheng clan.
So...
You still keep this token...
Ranks must stay apart.
Nobles can't wed commoners.
Mr. Cui's decision
is quite reasonable.
Let me help you.
I could fall for you.
So, you know everything.
Parents gave the order
and matchmakers arranged.
Please leave, Mr. Cui.
We wouldn't want gossip.
How about
we carry her down in turns?
No.
I mean,
if we risk our lives to carry her down
and someone sees it,
they will talk.
True.
Besides,
carrying a girl
expelled by the Zheng clan
would disgrace our own families.
Not to mention
if she clings to us,
we may never shake her off.
Please go, Mr. Cui.
Do not keep me
from enjoying the view.
Let's go.
Please.
This way.
It's swollen.
It's sprained.
I'll help you up.
Give me the sachet.
No, that's not what I meant.
Lecher!
How could you ask for a girl's sachet?
I...
I don't want it.
I just want a sniff.
Here, take it.
It isn't worth much anyway.
Borneol.
Musk.
Smells good.
Here.
Here it comes.
Lecher!
Save the tantrum
for after we're off the mountain.
You are too injured to move.
I'll carry you.
We only just met.
Why take the risk?
It's no risk.
It's getting dark.
We're both stuck here.
That way.
Where?
Put me down.
This is too dangerous.
We can't see the road ahead.
That doesn't mean there's no road.
We will follow the path under our feet.
Step by step.
We'll get out eventually.
I promised to carry you.
I won't leave you halfway.
Sir.
What is your surname?
How should I address you?
If we had fallen and died just now,
I would not even know who I had
died with.
My surname is Li,
and my courtesy name is Liangyuan.
I'm from Huayin County.
What a relief. I thought
you were from the Five Great Families.
I am not.
How old are you?
I...
I am twenty.
Twenty?
You look much older.
Yes.
I look like this now,
and at forty
I will look the same.
What is your name?
I will tell you once we are down.
I can't go on. I need a rest.
Don't fall.
Liangyuan,
when you passed by the spindle tree,
were you afraid?
Yes.
Why?
Two lives were at stake.
But I still had to carry you down.
At night...
At night,
if the bugs did not bite you to death,
the cold would.
Right?
Come.
Hold tight. Let's go.
What's so funny?
Nothing.
Still laughing?
I just remembered something.
When I was little,
I went to Chang'an to sell sheep.
Just two of them.
One of the sheep was
dumb as a post.
It fell into a ditch.
It twisted its leg.
So then I
carried one sheep
and led the other to Chang'an.
Why do I feel
like you're making fun of me?
I am.
So what's your name?
I'll tell you once we're down.
We're almost there.
Tell me.
We're not there yet.
We're basically there.
=Episode 17=
Solid.
Ms. Amita.
The litchi transport project
is approved.
- Good.
- Great!
Let's not celebrate just yet.
Let me be blunt.
The Hu Merchants' Association
has a rule.
If the project shows no progress
within 30 days,
the funds will be withdrawn.
So you'd better make up
for the lost two days.
Of course.
I'll get right to it.
You have my thanks.
Hurry up, Li.
Get up!
(Inspector's Office)
Today, Li Shande's place
was swarming with merchants.
I sent someone over
to give him Eight Linglong cups,
five glazed goblets,
and two gold-inlaid teapots.
Such fine gifts
were all wasted.
He is the Litchi Envoy
on an imperial assignment.
We ought to
show some respect too.
Don't worry.
If he falls one day,
I'll take it all back.
This Inspector's Office
isn't short on gifts.
Indeed.
(Lingnan, Fang's Coconuts)
It was my mistake.
What on earth were you thinking?
I embarrassed the Inspector's Office.
Such a great opportunity,
and Li Shande
stole the attention!
What is the Inspector's Office for?
Are we just here to applaud?
The big fish swam away,
and now you think of casting a net?
What good does that do?
It's too late!
Yes, Sir.
Godfather.
Amita.
Why are you still standing here?
Get going.
Yes.
Be useful for once!
Yes...
Amita.
Here you are.
It was my oversight.
I didn't expect Li Shande
to come up with such a plan.
How long have you been
by my side?
Ten years now.
I remember when you first came back,
you were only
this tall.
Back then, your father died.
I did everything I could
to help our brothers
live a stable life.
I did right by your father.
I raised you with great effort,
and I helped you
become the leader of the Association.
And me?
Aside from pretending to be mad,
fighting birds and playing the fool,
I've done nothing else.
And why did I do all that?
Because I hoped
we could work well together
and quietly maintain
the good life we've built.
Now that we have the military tally,
Right Chancellor is waiting eagerly
for us
to control trade on the route.
But what have we done?
We've made no progress.
Then, Li Shande stirred things up.
All the Hu merchants
flocked over to his side.
If this keeps up,
our good days
will soon come to an end.
You are right, Godfather.
I understand.
I made a deal with Li Shande.
If he fails to produce
a viable transport plan for the litchis,
we withdraw the funds.
And if he delivers one?
Don't worry, Godfather.
Fresh litchis only last eleven days.
Transport alone takes thirteen.
Unless he sprouts wings and flies,
it's simply impossible.
Absolutely impossible?
Completely impossible?
Every time we say
it's impossible,
he somehow
pulls something off.
Ever since he came to Lingnan,
he has been constantly
thwarting our plans!
I'll keep an eye on Li Shande.
I won't let Su Liang take the seat.
Amita.
I'm tired of hearing that line.
What I want is a solution.
What I need is a result.
Amita.
Don't fault Inspector He for being mad.
You're the leader
of the Hu Merchants' Association.
You represent his reputation.
Now that you've been made a fool of...
Shut up.
I just want to ask
what the plan is.
I'll figure that out myself.
You need not worry.
Inspector He still trusts you.
If you fail,
you get scolded.
But if I fail,
it won't end with a scolding.
Your punishment
has nothing to do with me.
If Li Shande isn't removed,
the next Association leader will be Su.
And whether I lead or not,
that's none of your concern either.
Inspector He scolded me first, then you.
Do you think that means
we each solve our own problems?
Your business and mine
all serve Inspector He.
I got all set up.
Ms. Amita.
Alright, carry on.
Mr. Li.
Let me introduce you.
This is Mr. Wei,
Mr. Zhao and Mr. Zhou.
All three of them
are top clients of the Association.
They heard about your plan
to deliver litchis to Chang'an.
They are very intrigued.
- Mr. Li.
Gentlemen.
Mr. Li.
It's an honor.
We came here
at Ms. Amita's request,
hoping to see the project firsthand.
We're looking forward
to working with you.
We'd appreciate it
if you could walk us through
the plan.
Well, I already explained everything
at the Association the other day.
I'm not much of a speaker.
I'd hate to disrespect anyone.
In business,
customers always come first.
If our clients have requests,
we must do our best to meet them.
This venture
is fully funded by the Association.
Mr. Li, you should cooperate.
Su and Lan Yu are already
supervising the litchi garden.
What more do you expect from me?
Mr. Li,
we're here
to help you carry out
this groundbreaking project.
That's all.
By the way, see this outfit?
It's a Hu-style robe,
redesigned by none other than
Dafu Company.
Bright colors,
with a touch of Tang flair.
If you could help spread the word
and recommend it to others,
our sales will be...
Wait, I just transport litchis.
Why am I the one doing promotions
for your clothing?
I don't want the attention.
I don't need that.
Ms. Amita, it seems Mr. Li
may have misunderstood
our partnership a little.
Could you help explain it to him?
These three patrons' orders
make up nearly a third
of our Association.
If Mr. Li refuses to cooperate,
any future funding issues
will be out of my hands.
Gentlemen,
what you saw earlier
was the growing zone.
Now,
we're looking at the village...
Come to the center.
The villages of Dong people
who are experts in growing litchis.
Is this a litchi tree too?
You have a sharp eye.
This one here
is the thousand-year-old tree.
It has a remarkable history.
The entire garden
thrives under its protection.
You really do have a keen eye.
Look at them.
These mountain folk are so delighted
after tasting litchis.
Now imagine
how honored you'd be if Noble Consort
got to enjoy these herself.
Gentlemen, do you know
what these double-layer jars
are used for?
Well...
You're absolutely right.
They're for transporting spices.
The Hu Merchants' Association
paid a hefty price for these.
It was all thanks to Mr. Li...
Li...
Mr. Li!
Right.
It's all thanks to Mr. Li
for this water-seal preservation method.
Mr. Li, you've really worked hard.
Not at all.
Mr. Li is a true professional.
Tong?
Come on.
Tong, get up.
This young lady is Miss Tong.
She may be young,
but she is the head
of the entire litchi garden.
She's in charge of everything.
This girl
is a bit headstrong,
but she really
loves this job.
Just look at
how well she manages everything.
Come on, greet the bosses.
Wonderful.
- Come.
- She's got quite the attitude!
Let's keep going.
Mr. Li,
what's the story
with those bamboo baskets over there?
Those are freshly delivered backups,
meant specifically for carrying litchis.
That seems like a bit of a waste.
They look like the ones we use
at the docks for shipping goods.
There are no brandings
or custom designs on them.
They just won't do.
Mr. Li,
you pick a style.
Rest assured,
we'll provide all the baskets for free.
Exactly.
(Dafu Fruit Store)
The most important thing is,
Mr. Zhao's store name
must be clearly visible.
So, the jars for storing the litchis,
the horses,
the riders' uniforms,
and the litchi packaging...
All of these have to be in your design?
Mr. Li,
we'll take care of it.
And the cost is on us.
It's not about the cost.
It's about efficiency.
These litchis aren't sweet enough.
We can cure them
with sugar.
And still call them fresh litchis?
Can we change the name?
Let's just call them "Fortune Fruit."
It's a lucky name.
That'll definitely boost sales.
Get some trending poets
to write
verses about "Fortune Fruit."
They're sure to become famous.
How about this?
What if we paint all the jars
red?
That too has
a great symbolic meaning.
Festive. Very festive.
And the horses.
What about the horses? What horses?
Is there no end to this?
If you keep messing with things,
am I transporting litchis,
or is this turning into a joke?
Do you want to
see me make a fool of myself?
- No, that's not what we meant.
- No.
Mr. Li,
you've misunderstood.
We're just making suggestions,
and suggestions can be discussed,
right?
When it comes to transporting litchis,
we're all laymen here.
In the end, it's up to you to decide.
If we want to make it widely known,
and if we want this business
to really grab
everyday folks' attention,
we're the experts in that.
Exactly.
Of course.
Mr. Li, you're from the Shanglin Office.
You're a trained professional.
You probably look down
on our cheap tricks.
We get it. We understand.
But without these tricks,
we wouldn't be making any money, right?
Exactly.
Mr. Wei...
I'm not good with words,
but I meant no offense.
I know that you all are major clients
of the Hu Merchants' Association.
I'm just
someone doing a job.
As for what you brought up today,
this partnership,
I'm afraid I can't go along with it.
Mr. Li has integrity and dedication.
You truly do the work.
I admire that.
You're too kind.
Mr. Li,
isn't your daughter attending school
at an embroidery workshop
on Willow Lane in Anren Ward?
That workshop is run
by an old eunuch named Wang.
You know him?
Yes, that's right.
Funny how that works out.
The place he's renting
belongs to me.
Back when he first opened,
he was struggling financially,
and I gave him some help.
Now, if I were to
take back that storefront
and reclaim the land,
wouldn't that old eunuch
end up out on the street?
Mr. Li,
out of courtesy and reason,
please consider
becoming our
business partners.
Go back and tell Zhao Xinmin,
that I won't play his game.
Ms. Amita!
That slap is going to cost you.
Li Shande,
are you still going to eat?
Let's eat somewhere else.
The smell is off-putting.
Coming!
Move faster!
Move them inside.
Remember them.
Come on.
Since these match
their technical specs,
once you've
painted them properly,
we'll come back to inspect them.
Move them inside!
Don't break them!
Get that fool out of here.
He's in the way.
Out of here!
Leave here!
That's my brother.
Stop yapping!
You just can't stop, can you?
You messed up
everything we sorted out!
Miss Tong,
these are key points
the bosses mentioned.
I was only sorting
and checking inventory.
Keep your dog on a leash.
This is my turf.
You're not the one in charge here.
Li Shande
is in charge of the litchi transport.
Anything you want to move,
you have to ask him first.
I'm from the Association,
and was sent here to oversee all of you.
Besides, everything here
was paid for
by our Association.
But the Litchi Envoy
hasn't approved yet!
But Ms. Amita already has.
If she approves it,
then I'll make it happen. Got that?
Fine.
I'll go tell Li Shande.
Be my guest.
And while you're at it, ask Li Shande
how long it'll take to repaint
and refit these.
Time's ticking.
I'll be back to inspect.
Fine, I'll go.
Your wine.
Buy Inspector He some sugarcane.
Ms. Amita.
Ms. Amita!
It's been a while.
Try the tripe I saved for you.
Great.
The usual?
Two cups of wine.
Sure.
The food will take a while.
Have some litchis first.
Zhao Xinmin sent
Wei Yizhou for the deal.
You hit him.
How do we explain that to him?
Your wine.
Zhao Xinmin is just
He Youguang's lapdog.
No need to worry about me.
Worry about yourself.
Even though I don't know
why you helped me,
thank you anyway.
Me hitting him
has nothing to do with you.
I have my own reasons.
Tell me,
have you caught up on
the two lost days?
Not yet.
I'm still working on it.
They will taste better
when they are in season.
A Chang'an man
has become a litchi expert.
Times are tough.
I had to do my homework.
Do you think His Majesty
knows it's basically impossible
to get litchis from Lingnan
all the way to Chang'an?
Of course he knows.
People said Noble Consort
wanted litchis,
but I doubt it.
Sounds more like some man's promise
to please a woman.
Someone made a big and empty promise.
So, he gave the order.
We can't make such speculations.
Look how scared you are.
Clearly, you're timid by nature,
yet you risk
your neck for this suicide mission.
I've seen hardworking folks
and honest folks.
But a hardworking and honest man?
You're the first.
What kind of person are you, really?
A guy from Chang'an.
A low-ranking clerk,
gritting his teeth to survive.
That's all.
But you sure made some waves.
I don't even know how I got
into this mess.
Like these litchis.
They taste sweet to you,
but they're bitter to me.
Then why eat them
if they're bitter?
That's life.
Simple as that.
Even if you were a deity,
you wouldn't get everything you want.
Even Taibai Jinxing
might have his woes, right?
In this world,
the heart is never quite at peace.
But the work must be done.
At least your conscience is clear.
One day when you die,
and face King Yama in the underworld,
you get to tell him
you did your best.
That's all.
Why are you so willing
to risk your life?
Ms. Amita, how much money do you have?
Why are you asking that?
I have three hundred guan.
One hundred and fifty guan
came from a loan in Chang'an.
With that money,
I bought a house in Chang'an.
Taking out a loan to buy a house?
That's normal.
Sure, that's normal for you.
You can throw money around.
In Lingnan, you could buy as many homes
as you like,
anywhere you want.
But it's different for me.
That house of mine
is for my daughter.
It's my only
hope and goal.
That hope
got interrupted by this litchi mission.
So if I want to go back,
I must
pull this off.
No matter how He Youguang intervenes,
I won't give up.
You asked why I helped you earlier.
Because when I look at you,
I see my father,
who risked everything
just to protect me.
Li Shande, where did you go?
You were gone so long.
I had a meal with Amita.
What scheme is she up to now?
It was just a meal.
That Association lady
rummaged around.
She said she'd come to inspect again.
They've never shown
this much interest.
What are they after?
Now even the troublemakers
have shown up at our doorstep.
You'd better be careful.
What?
Amita hit a merchant?
That's right.
Amita's behavior
has become more unruly.
Back then, her father died in a fire.
If you hadn't stepped in
and taken her in,
and gone against all objections
to clear her father's fleet's name
and handed it to her,
would she be the Leader?
Yet now,
she doesn't even think of that.
Ma Guiyun has been
wooing Amita lately.
And what is Ma Guiyun capable of?
At best, he's just a messenger
of the Right Chancellor.
He wants Amita?
He's clearly out of his league.
That may be true,
but Ma Guiyun is
the definition of a schemer.
I just worry he might stir up
some real trouble.
What kind of trouble?
Don't worry, Inspector He.
I actually have a plan.
Go on.
Lately, Ma Guiyun has been
strutting around like a peacock.
He is relentlessly wooing Amita.
But Amita?
She won't even look at him.
I bet the guy must be boiling over
with frustration.
I just so happen to have an idea.
Send in a young beautiful woman
to play to his tastes.
It may be hard for a guy
to win a lady's heart,
but it's easy for a woman
to earn a guy's favor.
This is the perfect chance
to reel Ma Guiyun in.
But that Ma Guiyun
has eyes for Amita.
So, he's not one
to settle for just anyone.
Got anyone in mind?
Actually, I do.
Mr. Ma.
Miss Lan Yu.
I'm not Ms. Amita,
so are you disappointed?
Not at all.
Miss Lan Yu
heard we were hosting a banquet for you,
so she made a special effort
to dress up.
She will be dancing with you,
just like two birds soaring together
in perfect harmony.
Miss Lan Yu,
you came here alone.
Does Ms. Amita know?
I've admired you
for a long time, Mr. Ma.
But unfortunately,
you've never paid anyone else any mind.
In your eyes and in your heart,
there's only our Leader.
Before I came here,
I told her about my feelings for you.
I have her blessing.
Now, you'd stop
bothering her.
That is plain heartless.
I couldn't tell just now.
But look at you two right now...
You make such a lovely pair.
A match that will make anyone jealous.
Guiyun,
next time you travel the lands,
you'll have a beauty by your side.
Now that's a whole
different kind of pleasure.
We should toast to that!
Bottoms up!
Chief Scribe Zhao.
Please.
Chief Scribe Zhao,
you've gone to such lengths
for my sake.
So, is tonight's banquet
really just
to celebrate the bond
between me and Miss Lan Yu?
We haven't seen each other in a while.
Just catching up.
That's all?
Of course! Tonight is all about
you enjoying the food
and drink to your heart's content.
It's pure joy and merriment.
Lan Yu,
start the dance.
Let's see you dance!
Come now, Chief Scribe Zhao.
Having a good time?
Seems like it.
Easy there, Chief Scribe Zhao.
Mr. Ma.
Miss Lan Yu?
Even without the makeup,
you're truly radiant.
And you are quite the gallant gentleman.
If I didn't know better,
I'd think you were
the host of tonight's feast.
With friends, we drink
to our hearts' content.
You've all treated me so warmly,
I feel right at home.
We are all the same here.
Mr. Ma, I heard,
that just outside
the city lies Mount Pingyun.
It's scenic and lush.
It's worth a visit.
Why don't I accompany you there tomorrow
for a little excursion?
I'm just a lowly girl
with a frail body.
I overestimated myself.
Don't cry, Lan Yu.
Put those tears away.
I can't stand it when women cry.
Mount Pingyun, right?
Alright.
Put away the tears.
Mount Pingyun.
Take care, Mr. Ma.
Qilang,
how could you be so easily
charmed?
That Lan Yu
is just a pretty face.
Don't tell me you're that weak-willed?
You still have a mission.
Are you really off gallivanting?
With tricks as obvious as hers,
she can't fool me.
I'm going along with the flow.
Chief Scribe Zhao must have
invited me for a reason.
I don't know what he wants,
so I can't act rashly,
or burn bridges either.
I must play along for now.
Let's see
what he is really up to.
Qilang, you're brilliant.
We are all trying
to sound each other out.
We get the responses,
but nothing concrete.
Everyone also left
some room
for maneuvering in their words.
Gou'er, you're still
too young to get it.
You can't take things at face value.
We must plan ahead.
You'll need to trade moves
before the outcome is clear.
I just worry your act
might become a real thing.
You clearly enjoy this whole act.
I bet you like
being courted.
After all,
it's much easier than wooing her.
Romance is profound and deep.
Fake affection can't be real.
Only what's truly felt is real.
You're just a kid.
What do you even know?
I may be young,
but I'm not dumb.
Since we've come to Lingnan,
there've been women around you.
Master Konglang is
a teacher and a friend.
She is elegant and wise.
Amita is sharp and fearless,
a match for any man.
And today, the girl is
sweet and charming,
a delicate beauty anyone would cherish.
You really are quite the lucky man.
Gou'er, you're getting sharper.
Starting tomorrow,
stop brushing your teeth.
Today,
I'll knock out
all of them.
You spill nothing but nonsense.
Where did you learn those phrases?
Have some decency. Get lost.
What are you doing?
My aunt just arrived.
She's Chai, a powerful shaman
from the mountains.
Maybe she can
help us with the delivery.
Wait.
We don't resort to the occult.
We can't pin our hopes
on that kind of thing.
My aunt is the real deal.
She was born with a gift.
For major events of the Dong people,
whether weddings or funerals,
she's the one we turn to.
Whatever matter she handles,
it will go smoothly.
Can she tell me
how to preserve litchis?
Probably not.
The deities don't deal
with such tiny details.
It's over! Go on! Get out!
Show's over! Time to go!
Li Shande, what are you doing?
What else? I'm saving you all!
What are you doing?
You!
You dare interrupt my ritual?
The deities are watching!
They are angry!
They will punish you for this!
And when have they ever spared me?
This stuff is poisonous.
These are
(Chai)
thorn apple flowers and leaves.
When they are dried and burned,
the fumes cause hallucinations.
It's poisonous!
You serious?
Dead serious!
I have
seen it many times.
When we're sick,
we sniff it and feel better.
That doesn't mean you're cured.
It just numbs the pain.
It only masks
your symptoms for a while!
Stop inhaling it!
All of you!
Will you believe me,
or do you believe this city folk?
=The Litchi Road=
I'm not sure what to say.
Maybe something about poetry or music.
Or maybe
a pleasant moonlit stroll.
Moonlit...
Gou'er.
Get out.
Qilang, I didn't even go in.
At Dayu Ridge,
there's a shortcut.
A shortcut?
A shortcut!
It'll save us two days on the road.
That's terrific news!
I need you to find someone in Lingnan.
A man named Tu from Dayu Ridge.
He was burned to death ten years ago.
Your intel is outdated.
Although I cling to a branch in Lingnan
I'm popular
My immortal aura drifted to Chang'an
Driving people mad
Who wore out their shoes for me
Running around all day without rest
Just to earn a sweet fruit to eat?
Everyone wants
a taste of something new
I stumble through mountains, rivers,
lakes, and seas
In my dreams
Endless deceit
Absurd negotiation
I also want to see
red tiles and golden bricks
A prosperous world
But all I see
Is a man crying all night
A little bit every day
A little bit crazier
I was once carefree in Lingnan,
only sharing the moonlight
With heaven and earth
I'm popular but with nowhere to rest
I saw the greed of the world
I was once carefree in Lingnan
Only wishing to return
to the forest and dream
Enjoy the breeze
and the crescent moon again
Carefree and humble from then on
A little bit every day
A little bit crazier
A day of insanity after another
I was once carefree in Lingnan
Swinging on green hills
and leafy branches
One day we'll meet in Chang'an
Embark on this crazy destiny