You need to release your feelings.
Be open,
open yourself up,
and let everything flow out.
Let your feelings, thoughts, and emotions
splash out like paint.
Lyrical writing
is about expressing your inner emotions
and resonating with others.
How could you make it so rigid
like practical writing,
huh?
I'm giving you this
Guide to Lyrical Writing.
With it,
(Guide to Lyrical Writing)
you'll ace your Mandarin essays.
(Teachers' Office)
Sheng Wang.
Any issues these past few days?
Not really, no issues.
You know what?
I'll take you to a place.
That place is...
Just follow me.
Hey, tell me where it is.
I'll just take you there.
There's a lot of cool stuff.
Okay.
What kind of cool stuff?
♪Our encounter♪
♪Like the Milky Way's trajectory♪
♪Cannot be avoided♪
♪Like this heavy rain♪
♪Our youth♪
♪Like the frozen time♪
♪This moment is eternity♪
♪I run towards you♪
♪In the dark valley♪
♪You will catch my heart♪
=The On1y One =
=Getting close is just four lips touching=
=Episode 2=
Hello?
Hey, are you sleeping?
I was, until you woke me up.
So, did you finish that question?
Wow, you're amazing.
You know what? All my seniors
are still working on it.
I didn't.
You didn't?
So, what were you doing?
Watching a family drama.
A family drama?
What's going on?
It's nothing special.
Someone just moved in next door.
Out of courtesy,
I have to call him "big brother".
"Big brother"?
So, you actually called him that?
No.
I've always been quite impolite.
That's right.
Then you can let the dog out to bite him.
Right, you have a dog.
Lend me your dog.
No way.
My puppy's teeth are precious.
They shouldn't bite others.
Well...
Never mind.
As long as he doesn't bother me
or disturb my studies,
I'll be fine with it.
I'll work on the question.
Wait, hold on.
You said
you should call
the next-door guy "big brother",
so he must be older than you.
Why not let him try the question?
If he can solve it, great.
If not, it'll knock him
down a peg and scare him a bit.
Not bad, huh?
I think this is a good idea.
Then that's it.
Problem solved, now stop bothering me.
Alright, I'm going to sleep.
Bye.
Hey, Crab...
Come on.
Give me the answer you promised.
You really want me to lose sleep over this?
I'll definitely figure it out.
(The ratio of the centripetal force Fa
for object A to Fb for object B.)
Is he sure to solve it?
(Jiang Tian)
Mom.
It's not that I can't do it.
It's just beyond what I've learned so far.
And
I'm being magnanimous.
Since we are living together,
we can't stay at odds forever.
Your dear Wang
will use this question
to break the ice.
What am I doing?
What am I doing now?
Whatever, just forget it.
Many students won't solve it either.
I won't be the only one.
No. I'll go ask him.
What are you doing at my door?
I'm waiting.
What am I doing?
What am I doing now?
You're waiting? For what?
What do you want?
I should be asking you that.
You were pacing around my door,
and your footsteps were loud.
It's none of your business.
What do you want?
Well...
Actually...
Return my pen.
You took it today.
Give it back.
Anything else?
No.
Why did I do this?
He didn't see my test paper, did he?
I hope not.
Morning.
Sit. Have some breakfast.
Ms. Sun isn't here today.
I made some plain porridge.
Is plain porridge okay for you?
Okay.
Wang,
your dad's got an early flight today.
He went to Thailand for gift authorization
and asked me to let you know.
Here.
Tian moved in yesterday.
You two should chat more when you have time
and get to know each other better.
Tian.
Where are you going?
Aren't you going with Wang?
I've got stuff to do at school.
It's okay.
I'm not very good with people.
Because of Dad's job,
I move a lot.
People always see me as an outsider.
It's okay.
Ji Huanyu transferred the money to me.
I'll transfer it to you later.
Oh, okay.
Ji Huanyu?
See you.
Ji Huanyu is Tian's father.
Have your breakfast.
I'll go get another dish.
Oh, I just remembered.
I haven't finished
my science test paper.
I have to go.
But you haven't had your breakfast...
What do you want?
You're welcome.
But the key is the last line.
Mind your own business.
What do you mean?
Are you talking about me
stopping you yesterday?
If I hadn't intervened and stopped you,
where would you have gone that late?
Mind my own business?
I don't need your stupid answer.
Hey, Tian.
Tian!
Can we see your answer
to the last question?
We've got three different answers,
and we're not sure about any of them.
Can we see yours?
Oh, my.
A fourth answer.
Should we correct ours?
Of course.
Tian's answers are always right.
And...
The seventh question?
- No, the ninth question.
- I got an E too.
Let's see the ninth question.
Did you get it right?
Did I...
I got it wrong.
If it's wrong, it's wrong.
Why do you keep
correcting it?
Then go away. Do it yourself.
That's right.
You're amazing.
Alright, done.
I only correct the last one.
Sheng Wang!
Sorry.
By the way,
we'll have Miss Fortune's class next.
You haven't had her class before, right?
Miss Fortune?
Yes, our Mandarin teacher.
She's plump and does this when she talks,
like a fortune cat.
So we call her Miss Fortune.
What's her real name?
I forgot.
But how should I address her?
Just call her Miss Fortune.
Everyone does it. She doesn't mind.
Also, if you have any problems,
come to me. I've got your back.
Great.
Have you all received your test papers?
Yes.
I know, this exam was a bit tough.
The writing was easy to go off-topic,
and the average score
for the second reading
comprehension was low.
As for the poetry appreciation...
Never mind.
I never had much hope
for you to score well in this part,
but it can't be this bad.
Not even ten of you got it right
in the whole class.
But speaking of which,
I must commend
the new transfer student.
Where is he?
Look at Sheng Wang, guys.
He just transferred here
and hasn't even learned this so far,
but he's got a strong grasp of the basics.
He scored full marks in poetry appreciation
and reading comprehension.
His writing was excellent too.
Let's give him a round of applause.
But,
I do have a suggestion for you.
You need to improve your handwriting.
It doesn't have to be pretty,
but each character should stand upright,
not slouching.
It looks bad.
Sheng,
keep it up.
Chicken scratches, huh?
Keep it up.
Hey,
what's so funny?
At least he knows
how to answer the questions.
Unlike some of you,
whose lyrical essays
are as rigid as formulas.
Can you be a bit more expressive?
I won't say who that is.
Jiang Tian.
Now, let's look at the first
reading comprehension question.
I'm telling you.
Miss Fortune picks the one
who got it wrong.
What does that mean?
Jiang Tian.
Stand up.
What's the correct answer
to this question?
A.
Are you sure it's A?
Do you want to think it over?
D.
Alright, everyone,
what's the correct answer?
C.
The correct answer is C.
You need to understand the meaning
behind the words.
Be sensitive, okay?
Sit down.
Alright.
Let's look at the last
reading comprehension question.
It's on the second page.
Wang Youjun Pretends to Sleep.
Clearly, we know that Wang Youjun
is Wang Xizhi.
But why is he called Youjun?
Youjun isn't Wang Xizhi's given name
or pseudonym.
A friendly reminder.
Miss Fortune dismisses classes on time.
What does that mean?
We can get to the cafeteria on time.
As soon as the bell rings,
you should run.
Life is so tough for us.
- High school freshmen...
- Gao Tianyang.
Yes.
What did you say?
Nothing.
If so, why don't you share it with us?
I just said that
high school freshmen...
Louder. Repeat it three times.
I'll dismiss the class once you're done.
Come on. Say it.
I just said that
high school freshmen run faster than dogs.
High school freshmen run faster than dogs.
They run so fast.
Alright, sit down.
Copy the three classical texts
we covered today three times
and hand them to me
before the end of the day.
Class dismissed.
Thank you, ma'am.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Why didn't you two join them?
Huh?
W-We two?
Jiang is such a good student,
still working on his Mandarin test
after class.
Do you have any questions I can help with?
No.
It's okay.
I can help you out.
Ma'am, I'm going to have lunch.
Ma'am, I'm leaving too.
Correcting your English test
during my class?
See me in my office after school!
(Students' Cafeteria)
It's all Sheng Wang's fault.
He blocked my way.
Now I don't have a seat.
You ran slowly. Don't blame others.
Why don't you have a seat either?
Oh, right.
Your legs are short
and you can't run fast.
What's wrong with you?
Can't I tell the truth?
- Careful.
- You're annoying.
Gao Tianyang, you're being so unkind
to your classmates.
Exactly.
So my short legs are a joke now?
And you blamed Sheng Wang
for not knowing the cafeteria rules.
Is this how you look after
the new student?
Are you up to something?
That's nonsense.
Caring about a transfer student is normal.
Alright.
Then why don't you care about Qi Jiahao?
He's also a transfer student.
Qi Jiahao?
You mean the first-year student
who joined us because of good grades?
That doesn't count.
Why not? He's also a transfer.
Fine. That counts.
But they're still different, okay?
Yesterday, only three students got
the second-to-last question
on the practice test right.
Qi Jiahao,
Sheng Wang, and Jiang Tian,
please stand up.
I should've copied Tian's answers
like you did.
I'm wondering
how the three of you ended
up with the exact same answer?
Did you really know it,
or did you just copy each other?
You three, come up one by one, solve it,
and explain it to the class.
Qi Jiahao, you go first.
Get up here.
Can't you do it?
Did you forget?
You can't even remember your own work?
Sheng Wang.
Jiang Tian.
Isn't Sheng Wang amazing?
He also copied it,
but he understood it soon after.
But Qi Jiahao didn't.
They're clearly not on the same level.
The reality is harsh, huh?
Yeah, the reality is harsh.
Eat more. Maybe you'll grow taller.
What? I can still eat.
You're eating so much.
Why are you eating my girlfriend's food?
I'm not your girlfriend.
You're disgusting.
You have your own food.
Eat your own food.
Your tofu looks tasty.
Wait, no.
He's the one who was caught doing
English during Mandarin class, not me.
Why am I following him?
Come on, the transfer student is
as handsome as Jiang Tian.
He's your type.
- Hey!
- I'm in love. What should I do?
That's not right.
The cafeteria's that way.
Where are you going?
You'll only get leftovers at this time.
Go ahead.
Hey.
Where are you going?
I'm talking to you. Can you hear me?
Jiang Tian. Jiang Tian.
Stop getting in the way.
Uncle Mute and I can handle it here.
I told you to close the shop,
but you won't.
You just had heart surgery.
At least let me help you.
My small setup can't handle
someone as grand as you.
You've been abroad for so long
without a girlfriend.
You turned down Miss Yang, and Western girls.
Who'll be your partner?
Western food?
How will you get married?
Marriage is just a promise on a certificate.
It's just a choice.
You are also single now.
I have Uncle Mute with me.
But what about you?
Who will be with you
and take care of you when you're old?
Stop quarreling.
I found a place nearby
and want to open a coffee shop.
It'll open in a few days.
If you're free, you can come.
I'm just an old man.
I'll embarrass you.
Your place is too fancy for me.
I didn't expect there to be
a convenience store on campus.
But it's too far from the classroom.
Do people come here often?
What kind of question is that?
Of course, people come.
Students who live on campus all come.
Oh.
You're bringing a classmate to eat?
He'll eat.
I won't.
- Is it your first time here?
- Yeah.
What do you want to eat?
What do you have?
Fish ball soup with A-gei?
[*A-gei: a local delicacy]
Okay.
A new classmate?
He's tall.
Yes, yes.
Kids these days
are growing up like giants
with good nutrition.
This new student is quite handsome.
Hey, boy, do you have a girlfriend?
Or are you like Jiang Tian,
always acting aloof
and scaring the girls away?
Are you close with the owner,
or do you come here often?
You eat over here.
Where are you going?
He's not eating here.
He eats off-campus.
Off-campus?
At the Little White House.
Do you know Little White House?
It used to be the school's staff dormitory.
A lot of old employees still live there.
Some kids from far away
also rent rooms there.
Oh, I see.
I used to live in Tamsui.
I'm starving.
What's wrong?
Can't you eat alone,
or is the food not good?
No, it's just...
I can't eat it.
You can't eat it?
Why? You have a spoon and chopsticks.
I... I don't eat cilantro.
Then you can just pick it out.
No, I can't stand
this sauce either.
But the sauce goes with the dish.
Try it.
But...
Do you have any hot sauce?
What a picky eater.
If you want hot sauce,
go to a Sichuan restaurant.
Why did you come here?
This is a specialty.
It's sour and sweet. Give it a try.
But it's weird...
What a spoiled young man.
I have to pick out the cilantro for you.
What do you think?
Does my fish ball soup with A-gei
taste as good as the other places?
You know what?
My convenience store
is a real old shop.
I've been running it for decades.
Yes. And it's not crowded here.
Right? Glad you like the food.
Okay. Money?
Oh, right.
Sir.
I think I forgot to bring the money.
You want to get a free meal?
No, no.
How much is it? I'll pay you tomorrow.
No.
Then I'll go back to
the classroom and get it.
Trying to run away?
No way.
What should I do?
What should you do?
I have to solve this for you, huh?
Mr. Zhao, what's going on?
Well,
bring some money over
and bail out your classmate
who's dining and dashing.
Or I won't let him go.
I'm sorry...
What? He...
Sir, you'd better just kill me.
No.
My small business
can't afford that.
Why do I keep running into trouble
with everyone named Jiang?
Do I have a grudge against them?
What are you mumbling about?
Why not do something useful?
Here.
Take down his phone number.
So next time you can't pay for your food,
I won't have to call him
to bail you out.
But...
What's wrong?
Even brothers
settle their accounts clearly.
You owe me for this phone call.
Yes.
Done.
Great.
The person to bail you out is here.
Good for you.
I left in a hurry
and forgot to take the money.
I didn't expect that I'd have
to escort you and pay for your food.
Mr. Zhao, how much is it?
Anything else you need?
Me?
Who else would it be, a ghost?
I want these. Thank you.
(Notification: You have a new contact ".".)
Who is this? A period?
What does that mean? Speechless?
Or do you know others
have nothing to say to you?
If you do this again, I'll kill you.
Oh.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I won't make you angry again.
And I'll definitely keep my...
Distance.
You.
Yes?
I don't believe you.
A female instructor?
Is the photo genuine?
What if she's a middle-aged woman?
- What are you doing here...
- Hey, wait.
Close the door!
Sorry. Have some water and cool down.
Well...
I'll keep my distance.
You give it to him.
We need to change
for the P.E. class in the afternoon.
Changing is a hassle for the girls,
so our class has a fixed time at noon
for them to change in the classroom.
What other rules do you have?
No more rules.
If there are any,
I'll let you know afterward.
Keep moving.
Do it precisely.
Don't mess around.
Warm up properly,
or you might get injured.
During the school sports event,
each class must send representatives.
Everyone has a chance to participate.
Faster.
Are you alone?
Okay. I'll pair up with you.
Faster. Faster.
- I'm so tired.
- Move! Faster!
Excuse me, Mr. Wang.
The sports dean said
there's a meeting about
the sports event later.
Please come over.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Thanks.
Everyone, I'll go handle something.
You guys can have free time now.
Yay! Free time!
Free time!
But don't go too far.
Stay around here.
I'm exhausted. Lucky me, I don't have
to run in the mixed relay.
It's free time now.
What do you want to play?
Shouldn't we practice
for the mixed relay?
Forget about it.
Don't mess around.
What do you think?
Let's play basketball.
Or volleyball?
No, let's just disband here.
That's a good idea.
But, no.
What if Mr. Wang comes back?
We should have something prepared.
What should we play then?
Truth or dare.
Truth or dare?
Who said that?
Sounds good.
We haven't played it in a while.
And now we have a new student.
Sheng Wang.
Come join us.
Come on.
Let's play together.
What are we playing?
Truth or dare.
Do you want to play?
Or do you have some deep secrets?
I...
I don't have any.
So, you're in, right?
Game on.
Little Pepper. Lend me your hair tie.
Here.
Whoever the hair tie points to
will have to choose truth or dare.
Just like this.
- What's the color of your underwear?
- Red...
Hey, you have to spin it first.
Red! His underwear is red!
Alright, just kidding.
You go first, okay?
Okay.
The game begins.
Truth or dare?
Alright.
I'll go with Truth.
Well...
You're new. I'll ask him something cool.
Okay.
Does Big Mouth Xu kiss your mom at home?
Have you seen it?
Why would Big Mouth Xu kiss his mom?
Big Mouth Xu is his dad.
That's why he's called Little Mouth Xu.
Answer the question.
How could I have seen that?
Have you seen your parents kiss?
Not seeing it means you haven't seen it.
So, they do kiss!
Impossible.
Big Mouth Xu is so open-minded.
Hey, do you want to be like your dad
and kiss in front of us?
- What are you doing?
- Kiss who?
I've answered a question.
It's my turn.
- Dare, please.
- Truth!
Let me kiss her.
Why? It's not my punishment.
Don't think about weird stuff.
Fine, I'll grant your wish.
- Dare it is.
- No!
Go tell Mr. Wang "I love you".
If you can't do it, then you'll be...
No need. It's just three words.
Check it out.
We need to confirm it again.
Mr. Wang.
I love you!
- Poor Mr. Wang.
- Is it okay?
Okay.
Wow, okay.
Alright, my turn.
That isn't spinning.
Truth or dare?
Truth.
Truth?
Little Pepper.
What's the record
of your longest constipation?
Gao Tianyang!
Say it. Say it.
- Gao Tianyang.
- She can skip, okay?
Because she's my girlfriend.
Nonsense. I'm not your girlfriend.
Spin it.
- Song Sirui.
- Truth...
- Step on his head.
- or dare.
- Step on him.
- That's a piece of cake.
What's going on?
What are you doing? Watch out.
Take the chance to hit him.
Go away.
Alright, consider it your punishment.
Just spin it.
Truth or dare?
Dare.
Dare. Okay.
Kiss the next person who walks towards us
for ten seconds.
Kiss again?
If you don't,
you have to bark, crawl for three laps,
and pee like a dog.
Do you dare to do it?
Whoa! You're taking it too far.
Dare to kiss the person?
Do you dare?
Okay.
No problem, I can do it.
Good.
You're a real man.
That's okay, huh?
- Cool!
- Who is it? Who's that?
It's Tian!
That doesn't count, right?
We didn't specify
if it had to be a guy or a girl.
Yes.
Kiss him. Kiss him.
Scared? Then you have to bark.
If you don't kiss,
you have to crawl like a dog.
I'm not scared.
I can do it.
Oh, no.
For ten seconds?
Yes.
Do it.
♪It's alright.
I'll hide my vulnerability♪
♪So you won't see that side of me♪
♪In those few minutes
of so-called destiny♪
♪It gives me severe pain each time♪
♪Right after saying goodbye♪
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four, three,
two, and one.
Is that okay?
You really did it.
Okay. Good.
Tian will kill him.
Good for you.
♪We'll meet again at a crossroads♪
♪Let go of all regrets♪
♪Maybe we'll fall in love again♪
♪And everything will be different♪
Jiang Tian.
Hey, come on.
Jiang Tian, let me explain.
Jiang Tian.
Actually, I just wanted to...
You.
Don't follow me.
Hey, come on.
Actually, I mean. It was just...
It was just a game.
I admit
that kiss today
was a bit too much.
But in that situation,
I had no choice.
No,
I need to explain this to him.
Jiang Tian?
If you don't answer me, I'll come in.
Jiang Tian.
I apologize
for what happened today.
I'm sorry.
But...
But it was nothing.
Nothing?
Yeah.
It was just four lips touching. That's all.
Don't be so petty.
You really have a temper.
I'm petty
and have a temper?
(He is like a tree,)
(without happiness and sadness.)
It's nothing, right?
(A part of his body will be sleeping
in the earth peacefully;)
(a part will be dancing
with the wind joyfully;)
(a part will be providing
green shade willingly;)
(and a part will be bathing
in the sunshine warmly.)
(So quiet)
(and so proud will he be)
(that he won't have to depend on anyone,)
(or search for anything.)
(Jiang Tian's very moment)
Are you alone?
Okay. I'll pair up with you.
Faster. Faster.
I'm not very good with people.
Because of Dad's job,
I move a lot.
People always see me as an outsider.
It's okay.
- Hey, come here.
- I don't have to run in the mixed relay.
- I'm exhausted.
- It's free time now.
- What do you want to play?
- Play what?
Shouldn't you practice for the mixed relay?
Seriously? You want to practice?
What do you think?
Let's play basketball.
Or volleyball?
Let's just disband here.
That's a good idea.
Great.
But, no. What if Mr. Wang comes back?
We should have something prepared.
What should we play then?
Truth or dare.
Truth or dare?
Who said that?
Sounds good.
Sounds good. We haven't played it in a while.
And now we have a new student.
I promise I'll uncover big secrets.
Sheng Wang.
Come join us.
Come on.
Let's play together.
What are we playing?
Truth or dare.
What's the record
of your longest constipation?
Say it.
Gao Tianyang!
She can skip, okay?
Because she's my girlfriend.
Nonsense.
(Lyrical essays set the mood)
(without being explicit,)
(like placing an arm
around his shoulder)
(to subtly show)
(I've already got him on my side.)
I want these. Thank you.
Truth or dare?
Dare.
- Dare.
- Give him a hard one.
(Indirect lyricism:
some lyrical essays set the mood)
(without being explicit, like placing
an arm around one's shoulder...)
♪Hidden in your mysterious smile♪
♪Is a secret place
that can never be reached♪
♪With a weak resistance to mind waves♪
♪I want to know all your secrets♪
♪Until I find out the gap between us♪
♪And don't want to let you get hurt♪
♪I silently promised myself♪
♪That I would let you go with a smile♪
♪This is the most beautiful
interlude of youth♪
♪A line crafted in solitude
just for you♪
♪It's okay. I'll be with you♪
♪Until the last note
of the final melody♪
♪It's alright.
I'll hide my vulnerability♪
♪So you won't see that side of me♪
♪In those few minutes
of so-called destiny♪
♪It gives me severe pain each time♪
♪Right after saying goodbye♪
♪This is the most beautiful
interlude of youth♪
♪A line crafted in solitude
just for you♪
♪It's okay. I'll be with you♪
♪Until the last note
of the final melody♪
♪Hoping one day
we'll meet at a crossroads ♪
♪Let go of all regrets,
maybe we'll fall in love again♪
♪And everything will be different♪
♪This is the most beautiful
interlude of youth♪
♪A line crafted in solitude
just for you♪
♪It's okay. I'll be with you♪
♪Until the last note
of the final melody♪
♪This is our most beautiful finale♪
♪A line crafted in solitude
just for you♪
♪It's okay. I'll be with you♪
♪Until the last note
of the final melody♪