Fell asleep.
Who is this?
Who is it?
The sun is out.
No wonder I woke up.
Do you know why?
Why?
Because I'm a sunshine boy.
Getting some sun is really good.
Sunshine boy.
Isn't that a song?
Yeah.
I want to eat peanuts, bro.
Buy them.
Buy whatever she wants to eat. Go get it for her.
May wealth come from all directions.
No money.
I want this one.
Actually, both are tasty.
Then you eat this one.
But I can tell it's delicious, so...
That's fine.
Turn around and give a wave with the fan.
Okay.
Yeah, I...
White.
Feed it a little.
Then it'll be friendlier to you.
Okay.
So detailed.
Is it that detailed?
Don't shout, don't shout.
Teachers.
I'm really afraid of shouting.
It's not a Hengdian horse.
If you shout at a Hengdian horse, it starts running.
Three, two, one, as soon as you start, it runs.
How much do you weigh?
None of your business.
You definitely don't even weigh 140.
Come, let's take a group photo.
A big group photo of the "culprits."
Just sit down, that's fine.
It's okay, whatever works.
Come on.
Whatever.
Two against one.
Just do whatever.
Others want to sit, but you insist on standing.
I don't want to, I want to squat.
You lie down here.
It's fine, no need, just like this.
Come on.
Just stand here, that's fine.
I'll sit.
No need to sit, just stand.
Don't, just pose properly.
Do it properly.
Okay.
This feels like being forced.
I'm stuck here between these two gangs.
It's like wearing prison clothes.
That's exactly what it looks like.
Come on, hold him like this.
Just like this.
Our gang has arrived.
Your gang has arrived.
Hello, everyone.
Come on, let's take a photo.
Stop messing around over there.
Come on, group photo.
We're on the same team.
Those two bullied me just now.
They held me here.
Serves you right.
Okay.
Why is he wearing handcuffs?
This is the prop I won.
Today I have to be tied to him.
Why do you get to tie me up just because you won?
I get to pick someone to punish.
But I didn't lose.
Why are you punishing me?
I don't care if you lost or not, I just didn't win.
Ba.
Hello.
Ba, you brought a small bag again.
There's food inside.
What's your name?
My name is Bartfulai.
Bartfulai.
What's wrong?
What do you mean?
So it was you.
Don't talk.
What's up?
Comrades.
Comrades, her name is
Bartfulai.
What's up?
Aren't we going to talk over there in a bit?
Don't worry.
Let's talk over there.
Mysterious woman.
You need to hide for a while.
They asked me.
You're so well-behaved.
If they ask you, just answer.
They're a bit crazy today.
Let's go.
We'll catch up later.
Come.
Come quickly, Di.
Come from the back.
Puppy
She wants to bring
You want to bring
Okay
My fashion accessory
Puppy
Give me an explanation
Why did he die here
Fell asleep
Who is this
Who is it
It's putting all its weight on my leg now
It's sitting
Use a bit of strength yourself
Go inside and investigate
Go inside
Should we check his body
To see if there's anything
I'll hold the umbrella for you
Something fell
The flower fell
Hairpin
Sorry
I gave it a gentle pat
No licking
Good boy.
Just leave it here.
Let it stay with this.
Let it stay with him.
Such a good boy.
Protect him for us.
Don't bring him back to life.
It's so well-behaved, it's sleeping.
Take the dog and the snacks away.
As soon as she touches these two things,
So good.
Your paw is still on me.
Your paw is still on my hand.
Puppy.
It's very good, it kept sighing just now.
Let's go.
Can't we take the puppy with us?
It'll stay here.
After you finish work tonight,
you can rent it back to the hotel.
Rent it back to the hotel.
Rent it for one night.
Let's go, puppy.
Go.
It's obedient.
Come here.
Puppy.
Let's go.
How about it?
Wait, it says you can buy tokens.
One token per play.
Look, that's fifty yuan.
Fifty plays, that's too many.
Then you could play a hundred times.
Fifty yuan for a hundred tokens.
Just buy twenty tokens.
Let's get twenty.
Buy twenty, that's twenty yuan.
Right, just buy twenty yuan worth.
Here's the money.
Come on, you two.
Come on.
But I can't catch the dolls.
Give it a try.
You try to grab one.
Just play.
I can do it.
You can do it, can you help me catch one?
I'm a bit better at it.
Then each person gets two.
Each person gets two or three.
I'm a bit better at it.
You go.
Then you...
Yeah, you go.
I'll hold it first.
Look, the claw is too soft.
It's based on probability.
Maybe once every ten tries, it'll grip tightly.
Okay.
Go ahead.
So close.
Nice, very accurate.
It's okay.
There's more, try again.
It's accurate, but this one won't work.
Last three tries.
Almost.
It's almost done.
Push Sweet Candy Factory.
This is the arcade.
Don't overthink it.
Do you believe I can get it in one try?
I can catch a doll.
I don't believe it.
I really don't believe it.
Why not grab this one?
You try.
That's one way.
I've seen this before.
Can't get in.
Really?
Almost.
So close.
Come on, keep going.
Try again.
I think this one will work.
This one, let's go.
He's going to help me catch it.
Get it!
Could this really work this time?
It's really possible.
Give it another try.
Let's meow together.
Acting cute in front of you.
Oh, meow meow meow meow meow.
What is this for?
This seems to be for catching small ones.
This one works too.
We can try this one.
Catching this one is a bit...
I don't want to catch this one.
You should catch that kind.
The ones lying sideways.
This won't work, not the left, not the right.
This is even worse, this won't do.
Let's go.
Alright, let's go.
We got nothing.
We wasted twenty yuan.
Are we out of tokens?
It's okay.
Then we have to wait for him to come save us.
Yeah, the card can't be in the cell, right?
Then let's sit for a while.
Go ahead and sit down.
Take a break.
No.
There's something.
There's something there.
We should be able to reach something.
Try picking it up with chopsticks.
That should work.
I don't have any here.
Check if there's anything in that pile of grass.
Nothing.
You should be able to reach the ones on your side.
Those two.
I have to throw it to you.
I don't want it.
What do you think it means that we're locked in here together?
It means we are...
One of us must be the culprit.
You're right.
I knew it all along.
One of us has a problem.
Like that.
What are you doing?
I'm giving it to you.
I'm throwing it over.
I can't pick it up with the tongs.
Just put it on the ground.
The light flashed.
Look, it's time to test my aim.
Can you reach it?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Why aren't you behaving?
You dropped everything on the floor.
Bro.
We're on the same side.
Behave yourself.
Okay.
Restrain him.
I'm behaving now.
Let's try first and see if we can—
—find a way to keep it from falling on the ground.
Just lift the box directly.
Not really working.
It's heavy.
It's really hard to push this box.
I can move it, but...
But it's a bit difficult.
Look.
No, it's too heavy.
If it's a bit hard...
Is this a piece of cloth or a bag?
This should be a piece of cloth.
You just...
Let me see.
Yeah, cover it and drag it over.
You mean I take the cloth...
Cover it with the cloth, right?
Yes, cover it with the cloth.
Then, together with the cloth...
Bring it over together with this green thing.
Right.
Oh no.
It's fine.
It's right next to you.
Oh no, mine...
This thing is actually pretty useful.
Don't rush.
I can push it in a bit more for you.
Is that okay?
It's fine.
What are you doing?
Why are you moving around again?
Why is it always you who moves?
I didn't move. I can't even move my hands.
I can't move anymore.
Restrain him.
No need.
Stick it out.
Hand over the item.
What item?
I don't have anything.
Look.
There's nothing.
What's this?
What is it?
Give it to me.
I don't have it.
Hand it over.
I don't have anything. That's my hand.
I'll restrain you again.
I...
Give it to me.
I'll give it to you.
Can you take this off too?
Hurry up.
Can everyone behave, please?
Okay.
Behaving.
Got it.
Don't drop things on the floor.
Use two chopsticks to pick it up.
Use your two chopsticks to bring it over.
Right.
Okay, take your hand out.
Let me try first.
Say it again.
Don't put things on the floor.
On the floor, right.
I'll set this up first.
I still need to follow your lead.
That's right.
Don't rush, let me adjust the position first.
I need to make it easier for you to grab too.
I can't be the only one picking it up.
The length is enough.
The length is fine.
Like this, I'll bring it over to you.
Can you grab it from above and below?
Sure, I have no problem.
But you need to hold it steady.
It's a bit hard.
You...
It's a bit difficult.
Like this.
But how are you grabbing it?
Hold it steady.
Don't let go yet.
Don't knock it off.
You guys are being too dishonest.
Give him another measure.
Yes.
What's going on with you guys?
I already said it.
Don't drop my things on the floor.
Okay, big brother.
I just fell asleep, what's going on?
It fell by itself.
Say hello to sister-in-law.
Behave yourself.
Okay.
Hello, big brother, hello, sister-in-law.
Big brother, you look really cool.
Big brother.
I think we're about to succeed.
We still have to clamp it.
I can't put it on top.
Because putting it on top is too unstable.
What are you arguing about?
Time to eat.
They're eating.
What is going on with you all?
I told you, you can't drop things on the ground.
It's too hard.
How did the mask fall off?
It didn't fall, I put it on.
I put it on.
It's too hard.
Bro, aren't you going to eat?
Bro, go eat.
It's too hard.
You'll get too skinny if you don't eat.
Bro.
Sister-in-law is calling you home for dinner.
Dinner's not ready yet.
Okay.
Everyone, behave yourselves.
Keep watch.
Yes.
The sun is out.
No wonder I woke up.
The sun is out, really.
Do you know why?
Why?
Because I'm a sunny boy.
It feels so nice to sit in the sun for a while.
It's really good to get some sun.
Sunbathing is great.
Yeah, I like sunbathing too.
It's really nice.
After sunbathing, I feel like
I've become awesome.
Yeah.
I've turned into a sunny boy.
Right.
Sunny boy.
Isn't that a song?
Yeah.
Mushrooms.
Little mushrooms.
Will eating these make you sick?
Yes.
Probably.
If you eat them, you'll turn into Ba.
Hurry up and get it for me.
Are we going back to prison now?
No.
Go back.
Go back to that big mansion.
You go back to prison.
I want to eat this.
I want to eat peanuts.
No money.
I want to eat peanuts, bro.
Buy it.
Buy whatever you want to eat.
Let's buy it for her.
Do we still have money?
Buy it.
No money.
May wealth come from all directions.
I just want this, that's enough.
I want this.
I gave you bread but you wouldn't eat it.
You like eating this kind of stuff.
This one is the fattiest.
What's it got to do with you?
Hit him.
I've already been beaten up by her like this.
Green Tea Appraisal Bureau.
It's about becoming sworn brothers with someone.
Then the playboy turns himself in.
Calling each other brothers.
Secretly flirting.
I only feel sorry for my brother.
Puppy
Don't tease it.
Why shouldn't we tease it?
It's probably not a stray, right?
It's a big dog, you don't even know its temperament.
There are snakes here.
I have a big dog at home.
I have a dog too.
It's that one.
Schnauzer
Yeah.
The one that looks like it has a little mustache.
Didn't you film before?
When you were filming "An Le Zhuan,"
Didn't you bring it with you?
Yeah.
It seemed pretty young back then.
Still young.
It's grown up now, right?
It's pretty big now.
You only have that one dog, right?
Yeah, just that one.
It's still at home now.
Yeah.
When I go out, I leave it with my...
I leave it at my manager's parents' house.
Boarding.
Why is he walking so fast?
Murderer.
Hold this for me.
You bought that food yourself.
And you still want me to hold it for you?
I can't carry it.
Yeah.
Why do you look like such a fool?
What a bad man.
I just went to learn it.
What?
That thing Manba does.
What does Baby learn every day?
She learns all sorts of weird things every day.
There's no meme she doesn't know.
Let me tell you.
Alright, let's start.
Start.
"Let's Start Reasoning" Season 3.
Let's begin.
I brought you some snacks.
Yeah, we can have a little snack first.
Thank you.
Do you want to eat?
Sweet fried dough twist.
This one is tasty.
Actually, both are delicious.
I want to eat this one.
Then you have this one.
Tasty, right?
It's really good.
I want some too.
Did you buy this?
We bought it here.
No, we brought it over.
We brought it.
You're not dieting, right?
It's super sweet.
Not dieting.
But I can tell it's delicious, so...
Sure.
Today, compared to yesterday, I really
feel much sleepier than yesterday.
Today, I went back in the middle
and fell asleep on the sofa.
What did you do last night?
Nothing.
And I didn't go to bed late either.
Did you get enough rest?
Yes, I did.
So you're well-rested today.
Yeah.
Yesterday, I wasn't well-rested.
Yesterday, it was like I was on stimulants.
Really? You seemed in great shape yesterday.
Yesterday, I wasn't well-rested.
I hope you never sleep well.
If I don't sleep well, then I...
Alright.
Show your best form.
My best form?
I don't need to use my best form.
Because I've already got you locked down.
If I show my best form again,
what would you do then?
Got it.
I advise you not to play like this.
Whatever you say today
won't work on me anymore.
Then I won't say anything.
Okay.
Thanks.
Do you want to take something to eat?
I have one, it's in my hand.
Take this one.
It's fine, this is enough for me.
Ba, didn't you already eat?
Who?
You.
Didn't we eat in prison?
But that doesn't stop me from eating bread.
Mainly, after we got out of prison,
and entered that room,
she ate another pack of something.
She really likes to eat.
I really want to eat my bread.
Aren't you eating?
I'm not eating.
I really can't eat anymore.
It's delicious.
Do you want to try this?
What is this?
Just break off a piece.
Really not eating.
Not eating.
You have great self-control.
I just ate that biscuit, the crispy one.
And sweet potato.
Tasty, right?
Where did you get all this bread?
Where did you buy it?
Shenzhen.
Quick, look at the old lady's room.
It's so creepy.
Sis, you go in by yourself.
No, the old lady's room—
There are photos of Zhang Linghe everywhere.
Yeah.
Because this was yesterday—
Yue and his room.
Look closely at this photo of Zhang Linghe.
Look.
Did you see it?
He blinked.
If the moon hasn't come yet,
the streetlight can still shine on the windowsill.
This was at one of his New Year's Eve parties.
Do you want to be the boss?
I don't want to.
Why would I want to be the boss?
He wants to be the boss.
For many years.
Because the She pattern has started to appear.
Yeah.
Who gave him this stick again?
Who was it? I told you before.
He's holding my stick, right?
You already took the one from yesterday home.
This is mine. I didn't take it home.
Let's go.
Pull.
Okay.
We're leaving.
Let's go, Jiawei.
Let's go, we're heading out.
How strong is the taste of black coffee?
I only want soda.
Is this straightened?
Pull.
No, let me fix it in place first.
Let's keep going.
No, I'm about to turn a corner here.
No, your corner doesn't count.
You have to look at this one.
There's another corner here, right?
Yeah.
I'm really tired.
So tired, really so tired.
It's tough.
It's okay.
No, you have to take care of five kids.
Yeah, I have to manage a lot of things.
So,
I'm exhausted.
I'm a bit tired, guys.
Even someone like me, who doesn't handle anything, is tired.
Next, Ning is going to speak.
Everyone, listen to his instructions.
Especially...
No, just kidding.
Because I'm really grateful to you all.
You've always supported me.
Some of the childish things I suggested,
you were all willing to join me.
You never killed my vibe.
Being on this show has made me really happy.
It's painful but joyful at the same time.
For example, look,
when I say something to someone,
they listen right away.
Put the stick down.
Really.
Let's go.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
Go, look at the camera.
Where are you going?
What kind of walk is that?
Just walk in place.
Just pretend to walk, that's enough.
You're really going?
Just one step is enough.
Pretend to walk, okay.
Come on.
Haven't you seen that fake walking photo trend on Douyin?
What are you doing? What's this?
Pretending to leave.
Pretending to leave for a photo.
Three
Two
One
Go
Right, just one movement is enough.
One, two, three, then go.
Okay
No
I'm telling you, if you do it like this—
You're not solid.
What are you doing?
It's fine to film one person.
Why are you making that jingling noise up front?
Jingling
That's your phone.
You can look for the good-looking one.
He can't do it, it's all too weak.
Should we add some variation?
Is that okay?
Variation
A bit of that arms-around-shoulders look.
And someone squatting, like that.
Night Parade of One Hundred Demons
Yes, Night Parade of One Hundred Demons.
Like the vibe from "Bu Liang Ren."
Bu Liang Ren
My husband made that animation.
"Painting Rivers and Lakes: Bu Liang Ren"
I've seen it.
Black and White Impermanence
Zhou Keyu, a little higher.
Don't lean down too much.
Yes, good.
Okay, then I'll squat.
Then I'll squat down.
Yes, good.
Come on, look over here.
Three, two, one.
Okay, that's fine.
Thank you all for your hard work.
Thank you.
There's one more short video, please wait a moment.
Keep the same positions as before.
Just like before.
Alright.
Finally, it's higher.
I'll come up in a bit too.
Go down.
Let's take a group shot first.
Everyone, just keep it simple.
With the props in your hands.
Just interact with them a little.
Is this vertical or horizontal?
Horizontal.
Very happy.
Everyone, just interact simply with your props.
Okay.
Strike a cooler pose.
Then let's act like ghosts.
How do you act like a ghost, sis?
Like this.
Alright.
That works.
Right?
Yes.
How do we do it?
Just like that.
I'm going to blow on it.
Maybe after I blow, someone will die.
Something like that.
That's so creepy.
Ghost Blows Out the Light.
You look so cool doing that.
Who said "Ghost Blows Out the Light"?
It's flashing, the battery's dead.
It turned off.
The ghost blew it out.
No, it's electric.
Yeah.
Teachers, could you please crouch down a bit over here?
That's so scary.
There's a light control trick.
I got it.
I'll come out from behind you.
Right.
You saw that one, right?
What?
There's a video like that.
Like this, coming out like this.
Then it looks like one person with two heads.
Do you know that feeling?
Like one grows out from behind her.
I did something like that in a role.
It came out like this from the male lead.
Yeah, that's it.
Because it's a ghost.
We need this, it's really cool.
Gives me goosebumps.
At first, it feels like something's on your back.
Then it suddenly comes out.
That's pretty awesome.
This works.
Is it blocking your eyes?
No.
It's blocking my mouth.
Come on, teachers.
Teachers.
Three, two, one.
Why is there no sound?
Why is there still someone here?
Isn't this a video?
It's so quiet.
No, she laughed out loud.
I thought it was like a ghostly laugh.
What do you mean?
I'm the one laughing, and you call it a ghost laugh?
No.
I think we can make our movements bigger.
This movement is good.
Yeah, everyone move a bit.
Then you take a step forward.
Turn around.
Then I'll take a step.
Then I'll get up from below.
Okay.
Someone spins around.
Your fan.
Stop squatting all the time.
Hit.
You were squatting just now too.
Turn around.
Maybe you can add something.
Like making it fly or something.
Make the movement bigger.
Yeah, turn around and swing the fan.
Okay.
Right.
I do it like this.
Don't block her.
Just do your own thing.
Turn around for them, go.
What can my bird do?
Let your bird fly a bit.
You fly.
Use the wire rig.
Which shot?
Three, two, one.
Okay.
Shall we take a look?
Take a look.
Show us.
Let's watch the playback.
Watch the playback.
I laughed out loud again.
Looks great.
That's fine.
Next, we have two more shots.
Then the group in red.
Then the group in white.
Fight.
Showdown.
Dance.
Red team goes first.
Okay, red team goes first.
You look beautiful too.
Then...
The three teachers can...
Interact with the props in your hands.
And this side's movements...
Can be a bit bigger.
Diabolo.
Mage.
After I count down three, two, one...
Teacher Reba, reach out and swing the camera this way.
It really is the one who dances.
Jump, jump, jump, turn around.
Right.
Yours is so tiny.
On you.
Come on, get ready.
Three, two, one.
Teachers, interact.
Interact.
Move with the prop. Okay.
Ready, three, two, one.
Ready.
Three, two, one, go.
Perfect.
Okay.
It's the white team's turn.
Okay, start interacting.
Three, two, one, go.
Perfect.
Alright.
Okay.
Okay, let's officially begin.
Three, two, one, start.
I didn't even make a sound.
That was really loud.
Where do we go in?
Go up on stage.
Yes.
Which way in?
Come.
Be careful.
You two help each other.
No need to go up.
Come back.
Sorry.
This isn't our home field.
Then mine.
Where are the dots?
That's not right.
Is it this one?
There are six here.
This one has a number.
Go further.
There's a number.
Why are you tagging along with our red team?
We're splitting into teams for this?
Alright then.
What's this? Why?
Why?
Feeding the horse? Yes.
Carrots from Ning.
White.
You feed it.
It'll be friendlier to you.
That's so detailed.
Is it really that detailed?
Didn't expect that.
We can ride horses after the group?
Which horse is mine?
This one.
Ning.
Which one do you want?
I'm fine with any.
The light one or the brown one?
I'll take the brown one. The brown one.
Then I'll take the light one.
Are we riding side by side? Right?
One in front, one behind.
Feed it a carrot.
Come.
Good horse.
It can't chew anymore.
Alright, that's enough.
Is this horse well-behaved?
This horse is pretty well-behaved.
Very well-behaved.
Okay.
It's scared.
A little nervous.
It's okay.
I don't bite.
Alright.
It's hard for it to eat with this mouth, right?
You give it. Go ahead.
You can just give it.
Alright.
We'll go one in front, one behind.
Right.
Will this horse rear up?
It won't.
It seems pretty obedient, not bad.
This one might be a bit timid.
This one is a bit timid.
Alright, it's fine.
This horse feels really skinny.
It started shaking as soon as I got on.
Did you ever consider
that maybe you've gained weight recently?
Come on, I don't even weigh 140 jin.
Right.
No.
How much do you weigh?
None of your business.
You definitely don't weigh 140 jin either.
I weigh 150 jin.
Seventy-five kilos? No way.
Alright, everyone, let's get started.
Come on.
Come on, hurry, give it to me.
Don't shout, everyone.
I'm really afraid of shouting.
This isn't a Hengdian horse.
The Hengdian horses start running as soon as you shout.
As soon as you say "three, two, one, go," they run.
As soon as someone says "action," it knows.
You even have to ignite it.
Oh no, I'm not light.
It's fine.
Let its rear drop a bit.
Its rear is crooked.
Horse.
Three, two, one.
Go.
Thank you for your hard work, everyone.
Let's do it again.
I'll get off first.
It's too heavy.
Where do I go from?
It really is a white horse.
Are you coming down?
You can come down first and let them carry it back.
You all look so cool riding horses.
Then let's switch.
They all have white horses.
You look great on horseback.
What color is this horse?
Thank you, everyone, for your hard work.
Thanks for your hard work.
Thank you, little horse.
Be careful.
Watch out for the horse's rear.
Why do you still have a fan?
You're not taking the role anymore?
You didn't have a fan when you went over there just now.
I just put it here.
No.
Okay.
No, I just had it.
I want to ride a horse too.
I've never ridden one.
You've never ridden a horse?
I rode the kind in the park once.
But you've never ridden this kind of horse.
No, I've never ridden one while filming.
They look so cool riding horses.
Have you ridden before?
Yes, I have.
Everyone, this fire here—
needs a few minutes to cool down.
So let's go back and wait a few minutes.
They look so cool riding horses.
Are you scared?
I'm not afraid of horses.
But they look so good riding them.
She can get on and try riding now.
No, I think you look the coolest riding this horse.
You look the coolest on this one.
Really? Why?
You suit horseback riding so well.
Do you want to ride?
Now, you mean?
Yes, they have someone in charge.
Haven't you never ridden before?
I'm not brave enough.
Give it a carrot.
Whenever there's fire, this horse gets really scared.
It's okay, I've got it.
That white horse is a bit restless too, a little bit.
That little white one in front.
It'll take about ten minutes.
Then we'll wait a bit.
This time we'll shoot close-ups.
It's a bit tricky when turning in circles, right?
Because when we turn, all four of us have to turn in circles.
We can take pictures here.
Let's sit at different heights.
You sit a bit higher.
Who's going to take the photo for us?
Um...
Come on.
Coming.
Right, we need to take a photo.
Let's take a group shot.
Not this close.
From the back, see how nice it looks.
Edit it later to make me look just like her.
Okay.
Does it look good?
It definitely looks good.
I'm not worried about you or me.
Let's take a close-up.
One, two...
Okay.
So beautiful.
Thank you.
Let those four ride horses behind us.
The two of us will stand in front.
Hurry.
Alright, come on.
Can we take a photo?
Come on.
The horses can be ridden behind the two of us.
I'll kick you again if you do that.
Take a big group photo.
Actually riding horses.
The horses are behind us.
Behind the two girls.
Come on, let's go.
It's okay.
You really want to.
You want to be the leading lady for once, right?
Yes.
Its ears are wearing headphones too.
Let me do it, bro.
Bro, let's handle the reins.
Take a photo.
Sure, no problem.
You're much better behaved than the horses in Hengdian.
I want to twirl my skirt.
Okay.
If you twirl your skirt, you'll scare it.
Don't twirl, don't twirl, Jin Jing.
Really?
It'll get scared.
It will be frightened.
It's pretty timid.
This horse is a bit stubborn.
Let's hold hands.
Okay, come on.
Alright, look ahead.
Okay, three, two, one.
Look ahead.
Done.
Beautiful.
Thank you.
Thanks for your hard work.
Zhang Linghe.
What?
So handsome.
Handsome.
White Dragon Horse, hooves facing west.
You're about to kick me, aren't you?
White Dragon Horse, hooves heading west
A love
exercise
An unfinished
to be continued
Come
Alright, light it up, teachers
It's okay
Don't worry, it's fine
Pull-up
Season three is finished recording
Lao Bai, do you feel a bit reluctant to leave?
Reluctant, I'm very reluctant
You've already started your break
Found a nursing home
Staying there for a while
Thank you to all the staff and teachers
All the dear teachers
Looks great
Over two hundred expressions
My voice is hoarse today
You cried here yesterday
Down-and-out after returning from studying abroad
The aloof young lady
I don't believe you all can pass this round
Show us the replay
Pick up your own child
Jiawei was just
pulled up into the air, right?
He was lifted up.
His belly button was showing.
Don't catch a cold, keep your stomach warm.
Slim waist.
When we air this episode,
we'll clip this part out.
If you don't help,
we'll send this clip to the group.
It's the most expensive meal treat.
Send us a big red envelope first.
Can you help me turn off the light?
The light inside.