As last year's
six outstanding graduates,
I sincerely invite all of you
to join our intensive training camp.
The deduction is dead.
Someone used the "Killer Ghost" entry
and replaced it with "Infatuated Ghost."
The person killed by the Infatuated Ghost
Right.
This is a case of using someone else to kill.
Does she (Ba Mian Linglong) have a reason
to instigate me?
But it's absolutely impossible.
Because I don't want this matter
to be known by anyone.
Instigating murder
how is that not murder?
This is a legal issue and a moral issue.
Double culprits.
He instigated me, and I am the infatuated one.
I only made him have the intent to kill.
He carried out the act himself.
Nothing can affect
the progress of our company project.
Yes.
So our midnight intensive training camp
will still proceed as scheduled.
Then I'll wait for you at midnight.
Okay.
It's already midnight.
So next,
let's all go to the boot camp together.
Open an umbrella.
It's raining outside.
Use an umbrella.
Like this.
Can we walk out with that
heir-like style?
Can we?
How do we walk?
You set the rules first.
Let's do it like this.
Each of us opens the umbrella like this when we go out.
Then lift it up.
And walk forward slowly.
Then go back.
Then turn around and chat and laugh.
Where's the camera?
I get what you mean.
Director Ning is giving instructions, Director Ning.
Come on.
Alright.
Let's go.
Three, two, one.
No.
The main entrance is closed right now, right?
Aren't you the heir?
You look like a security guard now.
Ning, the security guard, right now.
The back door is closed too.
This is the main entrance.
Press it.
It's all sealed off.
So the door is broken, right?
Back door.
Then let's check the back door.
What about this one?
This one won't open.
It says "Do not touch" up there.
There's a bulldozer.
What's on this bulldozer?
There's surveillance. There's a camera in here.
Someone is watching us, right?
Yes.
He's watching us right now.
All the places we were just at?
This person is the observer.
Observer.
Should we get on the bulldozer?
Yeah, let's go up and take a look.
Go up and take a look.
Careful.
Come on.
This is the heir.
So it's from the family.
Inherited the family's bulldozer.
There's something inside.
Wait a moment.
Just take the thing out.
It's a cloak.
A cloak.
Here, take it.
That cloak.
There's a photo, and also...
Is there anything else, He?
No, that's all.
Okay.
Alright, come down first.
Be careful.
Come down first.
Watch out, it's slippery.
Your legs are really long, all of you...
Alright, let's go in and take a look.
Okay.
Let's go.
There's nothing scary, right?
Just a tattered curtain.
What's going on here?
It exploded.
This place is abandoned.
Did this place explode?
This door is closed too.
So what should we do?
Wait, let's check our stuff first.
Let's look at what we have in our hands.
Right.
The things in our hands.
This is Pirate Mansion.
Push Billion Film Company.
Push Sweet Food Factory.
Look.
Whose clothes are these?
But there's a photo.
So handsome, who is this?
Isn't this my idol?
You like him too?
Seriously?
So cute.
That's Barbie.
This is so girly.
Yeah.
Wait, these are all taken secretly.
Secret shots.
Someone's been watching all along.
So now we...
How do we get to the training camp?
Alright, if we can't get in this way...
We'll have to break in.
Let's do it.
This is so cool.
Yeah, cut it.
Cut it, cut it open.
Use more force.
Impressive, you even know how to use pliers.
Is there anything we can't do?
Of course not.
What?
Why is it so creepy here?
Don't forget, someone died here.
There was an explosion there.
The factory director died.
There's a burnt corpse smell, right?
Bai Dapao, go quickly.
Lead the way.
Alright.
Wait a second.
There's a dead body here.
They're all dead.
What? I want to—
Someone died.
I need to protect my heart.
Who is it?
The leg was sawed off.
What is that?
He's practicing martial arts.
Wait, is this person alive?
Yes, they're alive.
You're so flexible.
You're amazing. He's so flexible.
There's another one.
What?
Where?
Over there, there's another one in the back.
There's another one over there.
It's okay.
It's fine.
No problem.
All right.
Okay.
Wait a moment.
There's one more.
Hold on.
There's another one.
Stop.
They're from the Devil Training Camp.
Devil, right?
They're acting.
We have to act with them. Wait a second.
Should I do it like this?
Is this how I should do it?
Wait, what are you doing?
I'm acting.
Wait.
If we stick our photos on their faces,
will it freeze them?
Yeah.
I've been looking for it.
Stop.
It's fine.
Don't touch me.
All right.
Okay, that's good.
All right, you guys.
Bai, what are you doing?
If you can't beat them, join them.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Which way do we go?
Come.
Come on.
Go.
Cover the rear.
Watch the back.
Okay.
Thanks for your hard work.
That's enough.
Be careful.
We can't get through.
Hurry, there are more behind us.
Move quickly.
Hurry up.
It's fine, get inside quickly.
Get inside.
Get inside and close the door.
Okay, the door is closed.
Alright, it's done.
Wait a moment.
Stop.
It's actually a chase.
A deadly pursuit.
It's okay, we're safe now.
Safe.
This is our...
...training?
Yes.
A deadly pursuit.
Boot camp.
The first round tests our courage.
Right?
No, the first round tests...
...our brotherhood.
Just now, when we were walking,
He suddenly pulled me to the back.
To cover the rear.
I'll go first.
I'm telling you, adversity reveals true character.
How can this help us avoid danger?
No, it's making me even more nervous. No.
So what should we do?
What are we supposed to do now?
We need to find a way into the office.
Because inside the office is...
We should be going into the office.
They're back here again.
Hurry, go to the office.
Hurry.
Kick it, quick!
Should I kick it?
Kick the door.
Quick, kick it!
Should I kick it?
Kick it!
Three.
Two.
One.
Go, now!
Click.
You scared me to death.
We're filming.
Why did you barge in?
You're filming here?
I'm filming here.
That was terrifying.
I was scared to death.
I really...
...was scared to death.
I don't have time to mess around with you.
Why did you come here?
Cut.
Okay, cut.
Where's the director?
Director.
Director, how was my acting?
Come on, cut.
Come on, stand over there.
Cover the rear.
Bro.
You startled me.
We're in the middle of filming.
What's wrong with you guys?
You started acting without even seeing who it was.
No, what does this have to do with us?
Come on, let's stand over here.
Let's squat in the front.
Let's squat.
Squat here.
Are we actors or criminals?
No need, you don't have to squat.
Why are you guys here?
Didn't you say
to let us come find you?
Aren't we supposed to be training?
Isn't this a boot camp?
Boot camp training.
It's already twelve o'clock.
Yeah.
Director, what should we do?
Just give us a number.
I...
Yeah, we've been at this for so long.
It took me so much effort to create this art.
I got too into it.
Sorry.
You guys can disperse now.
Go reset the scene.
Then we'll have to reshoot in a bit.
We have to reshoot?
No.
The last take is invalid.
Why is it invalid?
Because they barged in.
Seriously,
this is just unprofessional.
You guys are so unprofessional, seriously.
You guys,
You, get out.
You don't even know they're filming.
Honestly.
Come on, don't leave.
Come back.
Okay.
Alright, you guys can go.
Hurry up and set things up.
Set things up.
Alright, let's go.
Sorry.
Thanks for your hard work.
Excuse me.
Thanks for your effort.
Our crew's rules—
Everyone, please—
Sorry.
Come on.
So, our boot camp here—
Why do we call it a boot camp?
Why is that?
Because the theme of our show
is set at the end of the world.
This script was adapted by a director whose films have grossed billions.
He personally adapted it.
This story is about
a terrifying infection that breaks out at the end of the world.
Those who are infected turn into monsters.
The lower-level monsters
are like what you just saw.
They have no consciousness.
The higher-level ones still retain some awareness.
Now,
let's go visit the second floor.
There's also a training room on the second floor.
It's also a very important place.
Follow me.
Okay.
This way.
Great.
Over here.
What that girl was doing just now was
aerial yoga.
Yes, aerial yoga.
That's impressive.
This design is pretty good, right?
That really startled me.
That just now also startled me.
Because as soon as I turned around,
she jumped down right then, you know?
I even turned to look at you guys.
Can we get up there?
Really?
It can't hold us up. It would take two guys to support it.
I think it can hold.
Really? It actually works?
You're amazing.
That's dangerous.
Don't mess around.
That girl just now—
Did she put her foot there?
Yeah.
Come on.
Let's go this way.
Then let's go from here.
What's going on here?
Didn't you guys do this?
Why did this collapse?
It was like this when we got here.
I even reinforced these stairs.
I think you should get a new construction crew.
Everything you've reinforced seems to have problems.
I just didn't coordinate with them properly.
You're not going to make us—
—clear this passage, are you?
Go ahead and clear it.
Alright, let's clear it.
How can we let the director do it?
Right? See, you're so considerate.
Come on, you go first.
Come on.
You go first.
Strongman.
You want the girls to do it?
Why are you making me go?
I don't know. None of us know.
I hate you.
What is this thing?
Someone's dead again.
What do you mean?
How did this happen?
Who is this?
Wait a second.
What's wrong?
Do you know him?
I don't know him.
What's on his head?
A knife.
Let's go over this.
Go ahead.
Because when we were filming,
everyone had an alibi for each other.
Right.
So,
the company staff also
all got off work at ten.
So only you guys were left.
No.
I'm not the same as you five.
I have a real alibi.
Me too.
Because I'm a livestream king on Weibo.
Alright.
I'm not the old Mr. Liu anymore.
You're the new livestream king.
Yes.
I have people from all over the world as my witnesses.
Alright, how about this.
No matter what,
you still need to discreetly find out
who the culprit is.
How can we be discreet about this?
The project
still needs to continue.
The path above
definitely shouldn't be taken any further.
Okay.
Alright.
I'll give this to you.
Puzzle-solving and reasoning test.
Tongcheng is fully online.
This is something Tongcheng Travel prepared for everyone.
It's a tool to help with evidence collection.
I hope it can help everyone organize the clues.
Clarify the logic and explore the truth.
Let's set off together with Tongcheng.
Thank you.
Here.
Give it to her.
I can't carry it.
Then let my little assistant help carry it.
I'm not your assistant.
You lost your infatuation with me so quickly?
Yes.
Okay.
No.
Then investigate discreetly.
Remember, you must be careful.
Don't let any information leak.
The project must continue.
Alright.
No problem.
I'll go handle the aftermath.
I'm going to settle the score with that shoddy construction project.
Okay.
"Let's Start Reasoning" Season 3
Case Six officially begins.
It is now 2025.
April 23rd, 12:30 AM.
The identity of the victim in this case is unknown.
After a preliminary investigation,
the suspect has been narrowed down to
Ba Mian Linglong,
Prince Charming,
the famous one,
from the Koban background,
prefers quality over quantity,
among these five people.
A golden reputation.
Because they were streaming live during the break,
they can be ruled out as a suspect.
You are the detective for this case.
Now, please question the suspects
and begin your investigation.
Come on, everyone speak up.
It's finally my turn today.
No one should expect to get off easy.
Don't laugh.
I just find her funny.
Alright, let's go one by one.
What is your relationship with the victim?
I don't know them.
If you don't know them, why would you kill them?
Okay, the stress test is complete.
You, come here.
This one of mine...
Lock the suspect.
Alright, so I don't know him.
You don't know him either.
That's right.
Come on, you say it.
Don't tell me you don't know him.
If anyone else says they don't know him,
I'll send you straight to the small room.
I don't know him.
I don't know him either.
Why did you flirt with her?
No, I didn't.
Because she said
no one is allowed to say they don't know.
So I said I don't know either.
You really took my words to heart.
I get it.
You do the same to him.
I want to see his reaction.
Now you say it.
Can you not be like this?
Your whole body is trying to avoid it.
Always like this.
That's just how he is.
He's scared.
Scared of me.
He's afraid of me now.
He's afraid of you now.
None of us know each other.
Really, we don't know each other.
Let's search.
Okay.
Like this, just take a look around.
What's up with this door?
Move it out first.
What's this?
A hammer.
There's colored paint here.
Colored paint.
Where would you hit to get colored paint on the hammer?
Isn't there color on that stone slab?
Yeah, look.
Pink, blue, green.
It's the same colors as on here.
So if he stood outside and hit it,
everything would fall down.
Then the rebar would stab into him.
Maybe he was
coming down from the second floor.
For example, if there was a support here.
After hitting it,
after he was crushed to death,
I hid this thing there.
Then I ran away.
That's possible.
You're getting the hang of it, bro.
No, I'm just identifying the culprit.
It's not your turn to identify the culprit.
I'm the real detective.
Another murder.
About to kill again.
Come on.
We need to search carefully.
Let's move the stones first.
Take it inside.
Three, two, one
Don't come over here
How did this happen?
Go in
Let's go with this
This is it
Like this
Okay
I want to check the rebar in his head
Did it go all the way through?
It went through
His clothes
These should be extras' clothes, right?
Looks like it
And he's also one of the people playing a "zombie"
Why do you say that?
Because look at the makeup on his hands and stuff
Is this makeup?
Not sure, right now
We can't confirm it right now
Whether it's zombie makeup
Or if he's actually injured
Rhymed
Did you check all the pockets?
This sleeve has been torn off.
Did you see it?
It's very even here.
So, he wanted to play
a trendy West Coast "zombie".
He's going for that West Coast vibe.
So he's a monster from the West.
That's why his hair is this color.
Right? Makes sense, doesn't it?
That's right.
He has this injury on his hand.
This injury might have been caused by someone hitting him.
For example, if someone swung a stick at him,
he could have blocked it with his hand.
That's possible.
Take a look at that hand.
This one is injured too.
This one was clearly burned by a cigar.
A cigar.
This is a burn.
Really, this is definitely a burn.
A burn.
Yes.
Since he's an extra, we need to ask around.
Let's go and ask those colleagues from earlier.
Boss lady, lead the way.
Come on, follow me.
Famous sign ahead, there's a ghost up front.
Sorry.
Sorry to disturb your rest.
Sorry to interrupt your break.
Because we're looking for
We're urgently looking for someone with red hair.
One of your extras—have you seen them?
No, we haven't.
Our group leader is over there.
You can ask them.
Group leader.
Let's go.
Sorry.
You guys go ahead and play, okay.
Where's the group leader?
Group leader, teacher, group leader.
Teacher.
The one inside just now.
Group leader.
Sorry.
Was that the boy inside just now, next to the director?
What does this mean?
The lounge is locked.
What does that mean?
Pull it out and see what it is.
Wait a second.
No.
Tug of war.
Tug of war, hurry!
What does that mean?
Pull.
Why?
There's a key on it, so we have to pull.
Pull.
Don't pull.
One, two, three.
Wait a second.
Wait, okay.
Okay, pause for a moment.
Pause for a moment.
Watch your hands.
You two aren't wearing gloves.
Someone on our side isn't wearing gloves.
I feel like I'm about to attend a wedding or something.
The groom is about to barge in.
Why is this so hard?
Should we stand crisscrossed?
I'll stand on this side.
Cross your hands, like this.
Like this.
I'm a pro at tug-of-war.
When I was a kid, they called me
the Prince of Tug-of-War.
Pull sneakily, quick!
Three!
Stop counting, hurry, pull sneakily!
Pull back quietly, quick!
Pull back quickly, stop talking!
That's not playing fair.
You started tug-of-war without even telling me.
Don't rush.
We're just resting here, what are you guys doing?
Who cares what they're doing, let's go!
Since someone dares to challenge us,
we, He Li Mo and Jin Yu, can't lose!
We are He Li, Mo, and Jin Yu.
Are you ready?
Okay, let's go. Come on.
Come on.
Come on, three.
Two.
One.
Go!
Three, two, one, go!
One, two, three.
Go!
Pull!
One, two, three.
Relax.
Hurry.
It's fine.
Let me ask, what exactly did you guys do?
Kicking the door and taking my keys—
You stop talking for now.
Wait a moment.
Let me rest for a bit.
Wait a second.
What are you doing?
In the middle of the night like this—
How about this—
You guys go to the back and rest for now.
There will probably be more filming later.
Alright?
Okay.
Rest for now.
Thank you, leader.
Unlocking the door
Then why were you playing tug-of-war with me?
That's my key.
How could I not grab it?
Alright.
Okay, come on.
Let's not talk about anything else, let's fight first.
Hit me.
You just kicked my door open.
Okay.
Let's talk about something serious.
What serious thing?
Do you know a guy with red hair?
Wait, why are you looking for him? What happened to him?
He's dead.
I'm so happy I could die.
No, we just want to find him.
We, um...
Yeah, we have something to discuss with him.
We have something to discuss with him.
You're looking for him?
No one could possibly die here.
We're all just filming here.
Yeah.
Yes.
Okay.
I roughly know everyone here.
An exact number.
But I can't
match each person exactly.
That list
Are you trying to become a rap star?
Where is your accent from?
I see.
Are there any other distinguishing features?
You're looking for someone, right?
Red hair.
Someone with red hair.
And one sleeve on their clothes is there,
and the other sleeve is missing.
Pretty muscular, has some muscles.
That's impossible.
All my actors here have sleeves.
All the sleeves are intact.
Then it must have been torn off, right.
All our actors' files
are on my assistant director's computer.
Come with me.
He's not here anymore.
Okay.
Keep your voice down.
This is my assistant director's office.
This is my assistant director's computer.
And the mouse.
All the actors' files
are on our assistant director's computer.
Alright.
Also, among our actors, there are five
who are top extras.
They are quite experienced.
All the information
all the information about the actors
they should all know.
I think if you can find those five
it will be a big help to you.
Alright?
Alright.
But,
I've never opened
our assistant director's computer.
If you want to open the assistant director's computer,
you have to become the assistant director.
But what's the most important thing to become the assistant director?
What?
Having good judgment.
Each time you complete an extra training wall,
you get thirty seconds of viewing access.
Each time you complete the background actor training wall
All the actor profiles
are on our assistant director's computer.
The top background actors know all the extras.
After we finish this training,
we'll see who the five top background actors are.
Then, based on those five,
we'll go find those five top background actors.
Ask them who the red-haired person is.
Right, among those people just now.
That's correct.
Okay.
Very clear.
I can tell you what this is.
Have you ever used a talking pen?
What is that?
A talking pen.
Wherever it lights up, you tap there.
Let me show you.
Start.
Training begins.
It's starting now.
If you don't capture it,
it's a failure.
That fast?
Yes.
Otherwise, I've never used his computer before.
I'll head out first.
Alright.
Hope you find the person.
No problem.
Alright.
I guess it will
be soon.
All six of us will be jumping for joy.
I don't know.
It's all so hectic.
What kind of game is this?
Is it about pressing the lights?
One question is, why?
Why did he set it so high?
Why make it so high?
Because we have three people who are 1.9 meters tall.
Right.
So cool.
Seriously, I'll leave this to you.
This whole row is mine, okay?
No, you two should each take one of the high ones.
Right.
I think you two can't reach the lower ones.
I'll help you two with the lower ones.
So the two of us can just rest, right?
Alright, let's do it.
Then us girls will take care of the three small ones at the bottom.
Is that okay?
Sure.
Alright, I'll take these few.
These two high ones, you two.
There's a high one here.
These few are just right for me.
Yeah, these four.
Then bring a chair over.
Bring a chair over.
Bring a chair, right.
Will this work?
That works too, this is fine too.
Start.
Okay, three—
Three.
Training failed.
Which one?
This one.
It's this one. Pressed too late.
It's okay, try again.
How about we take a look at this?
Press it again.
Let's check the rhythm first.
Okay, go ahead.
Training starts.
All lights on.
This one.
Press.
Training failed.
When it lights up, you have to press it immediately, right?
Right.
Try again.
Okay.
Then I'll focus.
Just watch your own.
Go ahead.
Alright?
Go.
I'm starting.
Three, two, one, start.
Training starts.
Getting ready to turn on the computer in the next second.
Not yet.
Impressive.
Alright, keep it up.
Go for it.
Nice.
Passed.
Look.
How do you see it?
Wait a moment.
Gold medal.
Full set, there's a full set.
Including a card.
Gold medal.
No, not a full gold.
This one.
Look at another one.
Alright, got it.
Just in case.
This girl.
The one in the white sweater.
She has an earring on the left.
They were just there.
She was just at the table.
Remember, there's one more.
Full, discard, extra.
Alright, let's go again. Come on.
Were you able to remember what they looked like just now?
I really can't remember faces.
There was a girl.
She was wearing a white sweater.
Her sweater—are you sure she was actually wearing a sweater?
That was their own sweater.
There was one with a middle part.
And a girl with straight bangs.
Right.
Okay.
Very clear.
No.
So we don't have to look for just those three?
Or do we still have to?
Remember them first.
We need to remember five.
We have to find all five. Let's go.
Come on, let's do it again.
Come on, one more time.
Nice, keep it up!
Three, two, one.
Training starts now.
You can do it!
Keep going!
Beautiful.
Continue.
This time, look from above.
Because you just looked down like this.
Start from the top, the first one.
This one.
The one with the middle part.
Right.
This one.
Thick lips.
Big eyes, thick lips.
This one.
This one is handsome.
So handsome.
This one.
He has a mole at the corner of his mouth.
That's all, right? We're done?
Just these few.
One, two, three, four, five. Right.
Let's look for him. Let's look.
Let's go.
Go.
Extras.
Gather up.
Hurry up.
Meal time.
Come quickly.
Is it the one with his head down?
Hello everyone, look over here.
This boy, right?
We need to go over there, right?
We need to go over there.
We can go in.
Is it this one?
Is it him? Is he the one?
But he doesn't really look like it.
Yes, it's him. He's one of them.
Really?
Look.
Yes, it's him. He's one of them.
Top extra.
We want to ask you something.
Do you know
in your team,
is there a young guy with red hair?
A young guy with red hair.
I'm not really sure about that.
There are so many extras, how could I know all of them?
I only remember
a few hours ago
I saw a strange person.
He seemed to go up to the second floor from the back door.
Went up to the second floor from the back door.
He was probably called up there, I think.
I don't know anything else.
Okay.
Got it. Okay.
Are you a top extra?
I am.
He isn't.
But he has more than a top extra.
I'm a "sacrifice" extra. I'm willing to get splashed with water.
There's even this kind of thing?
There's a punishment for making a mistake.
You scared me.
How about we go take another look over there?
Okay.
There weren't any top extras among those people just now?
No, there weren't.
So what about that person just now?
Does he know him?
He said last night—
Well, just a few hours ago—
He saw him go up to the second floor from the back door.
He was asked to go by someone.
He didn't say he was asked to go.
He just said he went up.
I inferred that he was asked to go.
What makes you think that?
Because I'm smart.
Do you accept that?
Take a look.
Wake up.
No, that's not it.
The guy with the middle part.
Aren't you annoying?
You splashed your classmate.
He's so innocent.
Why?
One of those two.
What are you doing here?
Still investigating here.
Do you know someone with red hair?
I knew it.
The one lying over there.
The girl in the corner should be the one.
Is that girl really the one?
It has to be one of these two girls.
I think it's her.
I think she looks like it too.
Stop arguing.
Not this one, the one inside.
Who's going to check?
Who dares to check?
She might throw water.
Hello, he has a question for you.
What is it? Can't you let people sleep?
It seems to be her.
Are you a top extra?
Are you?
So pretty, you must be, right?
Yes.
Definitely the kind who
gets invited to stand in the front row.
Have you seen a
red-haired
man?
Among your extras,
we don't have any extras with red hair.
Right, but he dyed his hair red.
It was really eye-catching.
I didn't notice.
But I think I
on the night of the 22nd
probably before 8:30
I saw someone
very strange.
How strange?
Because at that time,
he suddenly bit
his own right elbow.
Was he trying to bite it, or actually biting it?
He actually bit his right elbow.
Right here?
Yes.
And on his elbow
there were very noticeable red marks.
That's him—the red marks.
I remember now.
This person isn't one of our extras.
So who is he to you?
We don't know him.
We've never seen him before.
He just showed up that day
near our factory.
The 22nd—that was last night.
Yes, before 8:30 last night.
That's all.
Yes, I can't remember anything else.
Alright.
There's... there's one more person.
There's someone here who's a bit disturbed.
You go.
I don't dare.
Alright, no need to ask.
This is definitely it.
Yes.
This is...
Definitely.
It's definitely him.
Yes.
What's wrong with you?
This is definitely a top extra.
Because he's still acting even after the cameras stopped.
Didn't you see me here?
He is...
You're a top extra, right?
What do you all call me?
Top extra.
What?
I understand.
Are you the directors?
Yes.
Hello, teachers.
My front, side, and back.
Side, front, and a smile.
How is it?
Is there any work you need me for?
That's not important. None of that matters.
What's important is whether you know
someone with red hair.
An extra.
Your colleague.
You just joined, right?
Yes.
Our crew isn't allowed to dye their hair.
But I do know
we lost a piece of clothing.
Was it a plaid shirt?
I'm not sure about that.
I just remembered.
I was
on the morning of the 22nd
and I think I saw a strange person.
At that time,
he was in the corner of the tent area,
squatting there for a while, and then...
No way.
Seriously?
Could he be like me,
an introvert?
On the morning of the 22nd,
I did see a very strange person.
At that time,
he was in the corner of the tent area.
He squatted there for a while.
Then he put something
into a storage locker.
Tonight,
out of kindness,
I saw that the locker was open,
so I closed it.
And then, you can
try it yourselves.
Scan the code to open the locker.
Okay.
Then I'll go practice.
Alright.
Alright, thanks for your hard work.
Alright, let's go.
Let's go to the tent first.
Then head to the locker area.
They said
there's also a wardrobe.
Okay.
You really seem like an assistant director.
Where's the tent?
It's huge.
This really is a nice place.
There are still a few we haven't found.
There are two left.
Two more.
Still two.
Just look for the handsome ones.
Look for the super handsome type.
That one's handsome.
This one's handsome.
The really handsome kind.
This one is very handsome.
Just sitting here gives off a great vibe, this one.
This one.
It has to be him, he's so handsome.
Hey man.
I want to ask you something.
Have you seen a
sneaky-looking person?
Someone with red hair.
Haven't seen him.
But yesterday,
I did see someone strange.
Yeah, he said something to me.
What did he say?
He asked me about this place.
He asked me where this is.
I told him this is at the foot of Tiebu Mountain.
It's a film set converted from an abandoned factory.
And that was it, he just left.
Just
acting all mysterious.
There's a handsome guy here.
This one is really handsome too.
Someone this handsome must be—
This one is also so handsome.
He's about to laugh.
He's already laughing.
He can't hold it in anymore.
The corners of his mouth look like an AK.
Are you a top extra?
Yes.
I just became a top extra.
I'm so happy.
Happy? We're happy for you too.
We can tell.
Are you guys celebrities?
Why are you all so good-looking?
We're not as good-looking as you.
So, have you seen anyone suspicious around this factory?
Have you seen a suspicious person?
On the morning of the 22nd,
around eight or nine o'clock,
Eight or nine o'clock.
I saw someone
sneaking around here.
What was he doing?
Stealing clothes.
We lost a piece of clothing.
Do you remember what the clothing looked like?
He was wearing a hospital gown.
He stole a piece of clothing.
After that, I also saw him at the factory
and at the entrance of the film company.
I saw him there.
He was wandering around aimlessly.
Then I wanted
to go ask him for the clothing back.
But I couldn't go.
Why not?
Because our group leader told me the director was calling me.
I thought I was getting more scenes.
Did you get them?
Did it work out?
No, I didn't get them.
Alright, keep working hard.
Let's work hard together.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Good luck to you all.
Good luck.
We'll try our best to get that clothing back.
So you can wear it.
How about we search that cabinet first?
Check the cabinet. (Check.)
Box nine, the door is open.
Patient gown.
Take it out.
He even knew to put this thing inside.
No.
There's a possibility it happened like this.
I think this person
might have been locked up somewhere.
For example, treating him
like a mental patient and imprisoning him.
And he has signs of being tortured
and chased or beaten.
That's right.
So he might have wanted to escape from here.
And he didn't know where this place was.
Then he asked, "Where is this?"
Where is this?
So pitiful.
And in the end, he died so tragically.
That's possible.
Because he was wearing a patient gown,
it means
he was treated as a patient.
But everyone thought he was just acting.
So there's this here.
There's a note.
It says, "Tell me what... I, I want to..."
This is just... two scraps of paper.
Not sure if there's anything else.
Shake out that pocket.
Is there anything else inside?
No, that's it.
That's all there is.
Here.
So this person tore these things up.
And threw them in this trash can.
Alright, hold onto it for now.
There's another one here.
A barcode? Why?
Can it still be used? Let me try.
No, it's gone.
It's expired.
It's gone.
Let's go back to that office building.
Come on, let's go back.
This place was already a dangerous building.
They must have renovated it before.
They turned it into a training camp.
Right?
There was an explosion, so...
No, it was written on the wall just now.
The wall says it's not load-bearing.
Do not lean on it.
So even just leaning on it might...
...make the wall collapse.
Yeah.
So just a light hit could...
Let's go back to that office building.
Come on, let's go back.
Sorry.
I bumped into something.
Your rope
is all dirty.
It's fine, it doesn't matter.
Who still remembers when we first came here,
how confident and impressive we were?
Yeah.
Now going back,
we're all messy and disheveled.
So much for being like "The Heirs."
Right.
No,
you guys were stepping on me for ages just now.
When those people were chasing us,
you two kept stepping on me.
I was like this the whole time.
Constantly being pulled.
It's okay.
Come on.
Come.
Welcome.
Come on, say something.
Friends,
and all suspects,
Alright, how about this:
let's take a look at this first.
Let's see what this thing is.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Hot water.
A little, yeah.
It's boiling water.
It's too hot, babe.
Art Academy.
Come here.
Here's the thing.
Like this.
This person wants to go to school now.
This is Tuizhen Art Academy.
It's written at the top.
I was harmed back then.
Yeah.
Fell off the cliff at Tiebu Mountain.
Now life is worse than death.
I treated you as a friend, but you hurt me.
I want revenge.
Tiebu Mountain cliff.
Isn't that the friend I hit with my car?
Yeah.
My friend was also at Tiebu Mountain.
So I used this draft, Lidi.
I tricked my friend into going there.
He from that mountain
accidentally rolled down.
He fell to his death.
I took my friend Jin up the mountain.
I said let's go for a drive, have some fun.
Bang, hit him.
Then he fell down.
Pushed down the mountain.
It was my friend and that
Ning friend.
Both of them fell down.
No.
Are you two okay?
Something happened.
It hasn't happened yet.
Not yet.
So who is he?
He used to be a good friend of one of us.
That's right.
He didn't die.
Maybe he rolled down the mountain and someone found him.
He was saved.
Then he was locked up somewhere.
That's right.
So he's not mentally ill.
He's really just a
seriously injured patient.
He escaped from the ICU.
Why would someone want to kill him?
It must be one of us.
Who knows that my friend is still alive.
After I saw this note,
I must have wanted to kill him.
What do you mean?
If this friend comes back,
he'll reveal the truth from back then.
For example, you were driving.
Your statement was that you jumped out of the car.
He was on the verge of falling.
Or maybe you pushed him out of the car yourself.
You pushed him out.
Or you caused the accident on purpose.
That's right.
So if he comes back and tells the truth,
you'll be guilty.
He wants revenge.
It's all about fear.
So, he...
Who actually knows him is really important.
It's very important.
So everyone says
they don't know him.
I don't know him.
I'm not acquainted with him.
I don't know him either.
I don't know him.
Who's lying?
I'm giving him a chance now.
If he admits it now,
we can vote in secret.
He and I will each get a golden key.
But if you insist on continuing the game,
How do we vote in secret?
And still each get a golden key?
Because I made the rules.
If you admit it now,
Your rules are the rules.
I'll protect you.
And then we each get a golden key.
But if you want to keep playing,
then it won't be easy to handle.
I admit it.
You admit it?
I said to admit it secretly.
Sorry, I take it back.
Next, we'll enter the X confirmation phase.
Go straight to X.
It's X already?
Going straight to X.
I think you must be X.
No, she must be X.
Because I believe, in the eyes of the culprit,
if they don't choose her as X,
she's a threat.
Makes sense.
Because she's very sharp.
Are you X?
I'm not.
Impossible.
I really am not.
It doesn't matter whether you are or not right now.
We'll just assume you are.
Understood.
Alright.
Let's rest up and try again.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
Goodbye.
Assistant director.
How's the investigation going?
Still investigating.
Thanks for your hard work.
Thank you for your effort.
Looking forward to your results.
I'll head out first.
Alright.
A master of logic and eloquence.
A lucky charm who can find clues anywhere.
It's like you were born for detective work.
I need to hurry.
Share this with my detective partners.
Multiple character personalities are now available.
Enjoy the "Coca-Cola" sharing bottles.
Let's have fun together and enjoy solving mysteries.
Hello, everyone.
Let's go to yesterday's break room.
Come on.
Did everyone sleep well?
Not bad.
Alright, let's review.
The movements of the person with red hair.
This person
around eight or nine yesterday morning
arrived at this place
On the morning of the 22nd, around eight or nine
I saw someone
sneaking around here
We lost a piece of clothing
After that, he took his hospital gown
and hid it in that cabinet
He went out and started asking for directions
He asked me about this place
Wait, let me add a detail here
He also tore up that flyer
and threw it in the trash can
When evening came
he bit his own right elbow
It should have been around eight thirty
He bit his right elbow
In the end, there was someone
He seemed to have gone up to the second floor from the back door
That was when he went up last night
Then, when he was about to come down
he died, right?
That, I don't know
Was it
that he died while being lured upstairs
or after he came up
and died when he was coming down
I think
he died when he went up
Why?
He went upstairs
He rushed upstairs
Either he was lying in front
or lying in the back
Let me give you an example.
If the ceiling collapses at this moment,
how would you react?
For example, if I’m going downstairs,
I would definitely
It’s possible, anything could happen.
You get it, right? You understand this logic?
That makes sense.
Okay.
Yesterday, we
later used this flyer to cover it.
Then we discovered something:
He’s very likely
one of our friends.
Three steel rods
head, chest, and stomach
were brutally stabbed into his body.
Brutally stabbed into his body.
I’m giving you one last chance now.
Step forward right now.
I’m still willing to share the golden key with you.
If you keep playing,
it’ll be too late.
Look at her expression.
I hate that petty, self-important look the most.
It’ll be too late.
It’s too late.
Why do you always talk like that?
The pacing of this performance is amazing.
I have nothing more to say.
Perfect.
You have to keep up this state all day today.
You’ll be exhausted.
Constantly.
Your blood pressure will go up.
Yeah, your forehead will be flushed soon.
Is the person in your car a boy or a girl?
You don't have the right to ask me. I'm the detective.
Okay.
In TV dramas like this,
you'd be the first to die.
The first one to get killed.
Let's continue sorting things out.
At that time, on his body,
what did we find?
Who wants to answer?
Come on, who wants to raise their hand?
Come on.
You.
Go ahead.
What was found on the body?
Burns. Burns on the hand.
Right.
Burns on the hand.
The sleeve was half torn off.
It might be related to this.
Is it related?
He bit it off himself.
I don't know.
It's possible.
Wait, I'm really curious about something.
Can a person bite their own elbow?
Try it.
You can.
This is the forearm.
Elbow.
How long would that tongue have to be? Like a lizard.
It's like when people say you can lick your own elbow with your tongue.
That's a special ability.
So I think he's a remarkable person.
Maybe his body has mutated.
Someone with acrobatic abilities.
If it's a mutation,
is it related to that assistant director from yesterday
and the movie he was filming?
Because the theme of our play
is set at the end of the world.
A terrible infection breaks out.
Those infected turn into monsters.
Right, monsters and such.
Because he mentioned something about mutation.
Yeah.
There's another piece of evidence.
We found it yesterday.
It's that hammer.
There was a lot of paint on it.
Paint.
That's also an important clue.
This hammer was used to smash
and collapse that building, right?
Yes.
The receipt for opening the door.
There was a hospital gown stored in the locker, right?
The red-haired guy put it there.
Normally, this is
a one-time use.
He probably scanned locker number nine.
After opening it,
he checked what was inside.
After taking it out,
he changed clothes, stuffed them in, and closed it.
The receipt was left there.
No.
Do you remember that extra from yesterday?
When that extra gave us the paper,
he said he was the one who closed the locker, right?
He said it was open, and then he closed it.
Tonight,
out of kindness,
he saw the locker was open,
so I closed it.
So there's a question.
It's possible the killer
put it inside.
Put it inside.
Put his hospital gown
and the paper in there.
It's possible.
Because that's also possible.
The killer could have torn it up.
It's possible.
Tiebu Mountain is also an important clue.
Right, because all of our friends
jumped off the cliff at Tiebu Mountain.
Jumped off the cliff.
Their story hasn't come out yet.
We need to go take a look.
Famous and Bai.
Pick one from among them.
The best among the Bai.
What's his name?
Prince Charming.
The best among the Bai.
Do you think he's not worthy?
Go search for Prince Charming and Famous.
Let's go.
Break room.
This is locked.
Let's see, it's an acting challenge card.
Place the corresponding "Coca-Cola"
into the slot.
It can help you open the box.
Okay.
Acting challenge.
Come on.
Four characters.
Okay.
Eat.
Eat melon.
Right.
Crowd.
You're so smart.
Let me see this one.
This one is hard too.
The third character is this one.
The third character is this—"butt."
The second-to-last character.
What kind of "stock" are you?
I'm a potential stock.
Right.
Complete it into a full sentence yourself.
The onlookers saw a stock called
"Zhou Keyu" with great potential.
That's good.
Place the corresponding "Coca-Cola"
into the slot.
Take a sip of "Coca-Cola" and feel refreshed and happy.
Various personalities are now available.
Have fun with the "Coca-Cola" sharing bottle.
Let's enjoy together.
Take a look.
Whose phone is this?
It's yours, right?
Very famous.
Or did someone else send it to you?
He friend.
Is this your girlfriend?
Take another look.
Why is this girl's midface so long?
Is she good-looking?
She's quite pretty.
This should be his younger sister.
Because she looks just like him.
Then he said, "What do you mean?"
Like, why are you dressed as a girl?
Then he said, "None of your business."
You're a cross-dressing pro.
You guys have uncovered a shocking secret.
For real?
The talent show star has turned into a comedy star.
Why is the popular contestant acting like this?
If it really is you,
I won't let you go, even if I become a ghost.
You framed him.
Where did you go?
I took the wrong phone.
He thought he was me.
Your good friend found out about this.
I will definitely become famous in the future.
But you're afraid.
You're timid, you're afraid of being blacklisted.
Is he questioning you?
He treats you like a brother.
No.
I only found out the next day that my friend fell off the cliff.
What did your good friend say afterwards?
What's with the fierce look?
That was just an accident.
Behind-the-scenes manipulation.
So his friend was completely innocent.
You let your friend take the blame for you.
Being friends with someone like that...
Are we locked in?
Neither the stairs nor the elevator can be accessed.
Who locked us in?
Then you’re on your own.
Go.
Let's move.
This elevator can't come down.
The elevator is here.
This is the real them.
There's someone here.
Keep your voice down.
Someone's coming up.
Go to the rooftop.
Is there any emergency escape equipment in here?
We're doomed.
I don't dare.
Vertical descent.
Wait a second.
If this really happens,
I think I'd still be a little scared.
Aba.
A Jin.
No, I already feel like crying, what should I do?