The truth behind Old Master Gu De's disappearance has finally come to light.
It’s you.
The mysterious person watching everyone from the shadows
has finally slipped up.
After investigation,
it was found that this person will act during the folk parade.
They infiltrated the parade to investigate.
They also encountered a mysterious woman.
However, when everyone returned to the old mansion,
they witnessed a man in a black robe
take his own life in front of everyone.
The villagers insisted
that he could not have committed suicide.
Another bizarre murder occurred at the Gu De mansion.
How is all of this connected to the mysterious person’s plot
and what is the link?
Where exactly is the mysterious person hiding?
New suspicions arise.
The truth remains unclear.
After an initial screening,
the people involved in this case have been identified.
The two of us have always been together.
We’ve always been together.
Alright.
You two investigate this matter thoroughly.
Why are you acting like this?
Boss
Okay
Boss, you're awesome
Thank you
I just remembered something
What is it?
Yeah
Controlled another person
If the inhaler's head is hit by an external force
Right
Got it, I understand
So after you two fell yesterday
With a bang
Yeah
It was just you two
People with vital signs can't go in
So we have to
Have fun
What's their relationship?
We're father and son.
I'm his dad.
You're turning things upside down.
Then you guys watch.
I'll just go and play it.
Okay.
You're not going with him?
This is my younger son.
Who asked?
He's always liked taking on things since he was little.
This is...
She's the purple mamba.
What's that, Herba?
How do you do it?
Wait a second.
Right, you've seen it, haven't you?
It came out at the end.
Is it as good as yesterday's?
If it involves...
...restoring this body,
the technology already existed in 1925.
Yes.
To bring him back to life.
Then why still...
If what I use is the original person,
if it's really the person himself,
Right.
But yesterday he said...
That's right, because he succeeded in replacing.
So actually, we...
Yes, that's actually what I meant.
So you all would feel
that you were unaware
and became...
Do you get it?
What's wrong?
Bai Yu
Duck feet, duck wings, chicken feet
No money, let's go
A man like you
Your girlfriend goes shopping with you
And then you
No money, let's go
I want to eat this
Don't save us
Lock him in
Big bro, lock it in
That's too cruel
Then you guys watch
I'll just go release it
Three
Two, one
Open
Almost, okay, good
If that's the case
Instead, I think his
suspicion isn't that strong
Why?
Let me give a simple example
Brothers cursing and fighting each other
It's all out in the open
Because I think all his conflicts
are out in the open
Me too
No, you two are really hard to find
No, there's a possibility that
Why are you joining this parade?
I'm just bored
I came to the human world to have fun
Okay
You also have a little hat
I'm telling you, it's scarier if you stand inside
Cobra
Is that okay?
It can be opened.
If you turn this, you can open it.
Do you want to open it?
There's a box.
You're really strong.
Isn't this just a window?
Really.
This.
Let me kick it.
Move your head away a bit.
Okay.
I am.
Golden Hook Breaking Lotus Root
Is it because there's a photo of me up there?
Yes.
The one under my eye.
That's the one.
So I am.
Isn't that just it?
That's why I just said
I would definitely go look for it right away.
Doesn't that mean you already...
I just looked over it again.
That chat log.
I think the person who most urgently wants to find this
is
Give me an explanation.
Why did he die here?
We went to attend at 5:40.
Don't say anything.
He came from over there.
After he slowly walked over,
He seemed really down.
That's acceptable too.
He just edited some of his...
Never mind.
Don't laugh, I actually trust you too.
Why do you trust him?
What about me?
You don't care.
I don't care either.
Her carpet is red.
Even if there's blood, you wouldn't see it.
If you want to pin the crime on me,
there's no need to rush.
This room doesn't have a carpet.
Go and help me lift up all the carpets.
See if there's any crucial evidence.
No.
I can't stand being falsely accused like this.
I'm going to check
the real culprit's room.
Wait a second.
Weren't we analyzing
him making and receiving calls?
Yes.
Right, we made a mistake.
I get it now.
We all started from
Yes.
Let's start from the end point.
If he goes towards
Yes.
I'm just saying, if we want to
All three of us have this motive.
But the one who can best connect with that
I think it's actually what you said.
This sense of justice.
I'm done talking.
Darling, why is there blood on your face?
Darling.
We are husband and wife.
Really?
Don't listen to her nonsense.
After encountering an obstacle,
it will activate the video recording function.
So your voice is its obstacle.
No, look, it's like this.
We need to go from here to here.
Okay, got it.
Then let's go.
This thing indicates a point.
The killer.
He has it on his cloak.
He must have passed through here.
That's right.
First point, I just said I...
can only rely on...
At this time, I still let...
Killed—do you think that's reasonable?
Yes, that's right.
Welcome to the Tui City Welfare Club.
We've prepared several benefits.
Waiting for you to claim them.
Bro, did you understand the rules?
I understood—failed.
This...
And then?
Isn't this game a bit boring?
What else do I need to do?
What else needs to be done?
You won.
That's what it means.
Then I only need two, right?
None of these three can fall to the ground.
No way, I don't believe anyone can do it.
Did I sing this?
I sang it.
Where is everyone?
I don't want it anymore.
I'm not eating anymore.
Whoever wants to eat can have it.
Peanuts, sunflower seeds.
What the heck?
This won't work.
How do you play this? This can't be played.
Not a single one can succeed, right?
I feel half paralyzed, sorry.
Are we there?
Congratulations.
Challenge completed.
This game isn't for just anyone.
Failed.
It already fell on the ground, right?
Restart the count, it doesn't count as a failure.
Wait a second.
Hold on.
Wait.
My hand.
It's too sticky.
Do we prepare just one of these?
Or does everyone get one?
Just one.
So just prepare one.
What do you want to eat?
It's not about what I want to eat.
Then I'll order this specialty rice noodles.
Shouldn't you get each of us a bowl?
Then three bowls.
Alright.
Okay, three bowls of "Bai Sanwan."
Alright, okay.
Someone will definitely pick food, right?
Forget it, I'll pick the Old Town dessert.
Cafeteria, let's go with the cafeteria.
Pick one.
Then let's go with iron spoon rice cake.
Right.
Because I'm worried someone can't eat spicy food.
This one is fine, this one.
Okay.
What is this prop?
This should be a special skill.
Right?
Forget it, food is still better.
Let's get a big energy nut platter.