We have to keep tracking this person.
But this person is dead.
Don't you find that strange?
You need to scan Mr. She's iris.
Mission archive completed.
No match.
So She is still alive.
So, yes.
She’s consciousness exists among you.
You need to uncover the story behind She.
Find the vessel She used to transfer consciousness.
Real-time monitoring.
We are now in the same time and space.
So, we are from the future.
It must be the Special Immigration Bureau.
They sent us here.
To accomplish a certain task.
There’s a possibility like this.
People from the future, through
the dead on this side, come back.
People from the future
are reborn into present-day corpses.
Rebirth Project.
Future Human Rebirth Project.
Correct.
This is how they immigrate.
They transfer their consciousness
over here.
Yes.
The year 2120.
Year 2120
The Special Immigration Bureau launches the Rebirth Project.
This is the Rebirth Project.
A person's consciousness can follow their genes.
He is a She-person.
Traveling back a hundred years.
Inside the body that died in Tui City.
Everyone's iris is unique.
The iris of a reborn individual
will change along with their genes and consciousness
and transform.
The Special Immigration Bureau selected
the most outstanding and gifted children.
They hope these children can go to
Tui City a hundred years ago
to change the world's path toward doomsday.
From the moment the first reborn arrived in Tui City,
the history and future here
have already been subtly altered.
But we all know
the Special Immigration Bureau's plan
is absurd
and doomed to fail.
If the people of Tui City could change,
our world wouldn't become a wasteland.
We have an even more perfect
new Rebirth Project.
This is our ultimate goal to achieve.
Yes, I understand everything.
It's just that the Snake Clan has a different plan.
That's right.
So what She said yesterday,
about us living in
dark and damp caves before,
was actually talking about the future.
She was actually referring to the world of the future.
That's right.
The world of the future
is actually caused by humans today.
Exactly.
So they want to seize
the place where humans live now.
Once the Snake Clan takes over,
they will
rebuild it properly.
There's a code over there.
Our ultimate goal to achieve
is the New Rebirth Project.
Immortality.
No illness or disaster.
The New Rebirth Project.
It's open.
Bring it over.
What's inside?
What did you find?
This model
is the one from the Billion Push Film Company
There are
two lines of text behind it
This building is called
"We Will Meet Again"
Dad
Although we will never have the chance to meet again
I will do my best in this world
to leave my mark
It will represent my reunion with you in the future
Little She
Then Dad left her a message, saying, "Daughter,
In the year 2122,
you were chosen by the Special Transfer Bureau at the age of eight
but died in 2023
I was reborn in Push City too late
I couldn't be reborn at an earlier time
to save you
Your idea
was ultimately a naive wish
Your departure made me realize
that people today
cannot rely on their own strength
to solve their own problems
nor can they suppress selfishness and cruelty
We should directly replace them
We would cherish the blue seas and skies of today even more
On the ruins of your soul
I will build a brand new world
That actually sounds pretty impressive.
This is little She.
He's trying to save his daughter.
Did little She do this?
It's dedicated to her father.
It's the official immigration bureau.
His plan is
Someone died on this side.
Then the people on this side
just use this body as an opportunity
to come over.
For example, in 2025,
an eight-year-old girl dies.
So in this world,
we find an eight-year-old girl.
Didn't he say you were chosen by the special immigration bureau?
So, okay.
Now they need an eight-year-old girl over there.
They just grab any suitable one.
And send you over.
Then they tell you
you're going back to 2025
to change the world
and make this world better.
To benefit us.
Right.
This is the special immigration bureau's plan.
But now She says
this kind of thing is too absurd.
We have a more perfect plan
that can change this world.
Right.
So, a hundred years later, there are two groups of people.
One group is the Snake Clan.
The other is the Special Immigration Bureau.
Yes.
We are the ones chosen by the Immigration Bureau.
We have to go back to 2025
to stop She’s plan.
But we are being
constantly stopped by the Snake Clan.
Right, because they make us lose our memories.
Do you know why?
The real turning point
between the Snake Clan and humans
is very simple.
The Special Immigration Bureau’s plan for humans is
to select outstanding children to replace them here
and work hard to save the future.
The Snake Clan wants to
replace the entire world.
Why did you say you want to replace everyone?
Because this is the plan of the Snake Clan.
The Snake Clan's goal is the highest priority.
It says on it,
I was reborn too late.
I couldn't be reborn earlier to save you.
But your departure made me realize
that people nowadays
can't rely on their own strength
to solve their own problems.
Nor can they suppress their selfishness and cruelty.
We should just come and replace them directly.
We would cherish the blue seas and skies more.
Then what you said is right.
Makes sense.
Yes.
The Special Relocation Bureau will let some people come over.
To change this world.
She is the one who changes my world.
I brought my entire Snake Clan back.
To live here.
Adults and children, men and women, young and old.
Replace all the people of the future.
Yes.
There's blood on this doll.
There's a button below that says "press me."
Let's listen to what it says.
Okay.
Why are you crying?
We came to Kaitui Farm to play.
You keep running around everywhere.
You're so annoying.
She's already stopped breathing.
Why did you hit her so hard?
You hit her plenty yourself.
And now you blame me?
Last time, you were the one who pushed her down the stairs.
She didn't even die from the fall.
Why couldn't she take it this time?
Enough talking.
Think about what to do.
Throw her in the river.
Once she's washed away, no one will trace it back to us.
I get it now.
This six-year-old girl didn't fall for no reason.
Her parents have been beating her all along.
It's the child in the water.
Suitcase.
I've got goosebumps.
This is a person.
Are those human bones?
Isn't that a human head?
It's been dismembered.
This is a doll.
So that's the little girl.
Yes.
This person is so evil.
These parents...
She died.
In a few days,
we won't be able to deliver to Yun Island.
We'll lose a lot of money.
Let's find an orphan girl to pretend.
Little girls all look pretty similar.
Just get similar clothes and a doll.
A relative from Tuitu Village told me
there's a homeless orphan girl on the street over there.
She's about the same age as our daughter.
Okay.
Just lure the little girl over with a doll.
This teddy bear is dirty.
We can't use it.
Where's our daughter's doll?
Did we pack it in the suitcase?
Forget it.
Don't open it.
It's bad luck.
That doll was a buy-one-get-one-free.
There's another one just like it.
Use that one.
The suitcase.
I've got goosebumps.
What is this talking about?
It's this.
The girl who accidentally fell.
Yesterday, there was an eight-year-old girl.
She was playing on the balcony.
She accidentally fell.
I think they want to find another girl.
To replace their own daughter.
Then who are they sending her to?
Yun Island.
Ren Weishan.
That swapped child.
The child's DNA.
This person sent a message.
Mr. Ren, we still have
two nautical miles to go.
We'll be at Yun Island soon.
Is everything ready?
Yes.
So this child
was being transported to Yun Island at that time.
They wanted to send the child there, but
their own died.
So they wanted to find a new child as a replacement.
For a deal.
This just proves that the parents
treated her
with child abuse.
Cold-blooded.
And that was their own child.
Falling downstairs didn't kill her.
Actually, she died at that time.
But little She came back again.
So they killed little She again.
Killed her.
So little She's father
got angry and said
We traveled back with hope and love
to let you change the world.
But you were still killed by these cruel parents,
humans.
So the She people turned dark.
Yes.
So in that special immigration bureau
among the smart kids they sent,
was his daughter among them?
Yes.
So this little She is his daughter.
This person is also from the future.
Yes.
Right.
He thought they came to do good things.
Then he came up with an idea.
He blew up that place.
To get his daughter...
Maybe to save her.
But his daughter probably couldn't be saved.
No.
At first, the She people might have been good.
He thought his child came to change the world.
But he didn't expect that after his child came,
she would still be killed.
Because She's daughter
traveled to the past,
but was still
mercilessly killed by humans.
Correct.
Angry.
I want revenge.
You want revenge.
Yes, me.
It's She’s father.
Is that true?
So that's the plan.
There's also a phone.
There's also a notebook inside.
It's been taken out.
There's also a key.
Preliminary preparations.
From 2023 to 2025.
Collect and create more vessels in the city.
But act discreetly.
Don't attract attention.
From 2123 to 2125.
Gather members with the same beliefs in the city.
Let them be reborn in batches.
Let's look at the first plan.
From 2023 to 2025, he
wants to collect and create more vessels.
Vessels mean making
corpses.
Make more corpses.
But act discreetly.
Don't attract attention.
So what's his method?
Invest in Ning Lightbulb in advance.
The live-streamed killings were just my idea.
He found me.
He invested five million in me.
He also helped me accomplish something.
And what was that?
That every live-streamed killing would result in a death.
The final corpse
would be taken care of for you.
That's right.
Let Ning Dengpao start a live-streamed killing.
Then create a corpse as a vessel.
February 26, 2025.
Ning Dengpao was exposed.
Explain this.
What's going on here?
Actually, I
am the real owner of this streaming base.
So you're the big boss.
That's right.
I didn't do it for long.
Yeah, not for long.
Then you guys caught me.
Then monitor everyone at the Tuitian Food Factory.
If there's a risk of exposure, blow up the food factory.
Destroy the evidence.
Pirate Mansion.
Big Sister's daughter.
Who is Big Sister's daughter?
My daughter.
Good Baby, do you remember?
That green one—
The one who knocked on the door with the green glass.
She's mine.
She is the daughter of Ba Snake and Heshe Snake.
Her name is Heniba.
She was sold to
Ren Weishan's Yun Island.
She became a consumable for the rich in their pursuit of immortality.
We must find the location of Yun Island.
Rescue my niece.
These people with wealth and status
are the best vessels.
He said, President Ren,
that mysterious person bought
our list of wealthy clients,
and forty percent of the rich
stopped doing business with us.
Ren Weishan seems to be investigating me.
On the night of March 14, 2025,
he will take his men to Pirate Mansion.
Monitor everyone inside Pirate Mansion.
Look for an opportunity
to blow them all up.
We need to find the bombs.
Hurry, look for them.
There are three here in total.
Yes, hurry and find them.
We're doomed, we're going to be blown up.
Let's hug each other quickly.
Let's hug together, everyone.
Hug together.
Tui Baiyi Film Company.
Finally, we've found out
that the Tui Baiyi Film Company's
"All staff" and "Yuan Gong"
are the couple who caused my daughter's death.
Yuan Gong? What does "all staff Yuan Gong" mean?
Come, who's this?
Engineer Yuan.
That boy just now, the wedding photo.
Those two who turned into zombies just now.
Those two people, right?
This abuse.
The one in the recording.
The two people in the recording.
April 23, 2025.
Caused an explosion at the Tui Baiyi company.
So every time there's a bomb,
it kills the people here.
All the staff.
Let them become vessels for rebirth.
And then Engineer Yuan
actually put his daughter's model
on his workstation.
I need to go get the stuff back.
Why didn't it explode?
A virus appeared there.
Everyone, including Engineer Yuan, is already infected.
They died from the poison.
The daughter got her revenge, in a way.
It's all connected now.
Tuitu Village.
So they were hiding here.
Let Tui Taiye handle it
Collect more bodies
Rebirth vessel storage
Goodhouse private ice cellar
May 9, 2025
5:44
Using the Tuitu Village event as cover
to conduct the rebirth ritual
so that the core members of the organization
can be reborn into the best bodies
That was yesterday morning
when we performed that ritual
It was a rebirth ritual
We attended it
Those people seemed like something was implanted in them
Then they hugged each other
as if they remembered something
Yeah
They were very happy
And for a while, they were lying on the ground
unconscious
Suddenly, they stood up
Suddenly, they stood up and reunited
Rebirth
When we reunited, it felt like we succeeded.
That feeling
is like
finally
coming back to life.
Alive again.
That person is actually a core member of the organization.
Then so are we.
We’re imitating them.
We’re six fools.
Imitating them.
The most important day has come.
May 10th, the most important day.
That’s today.
The members head to Tui City.
Planting bombs everywhere.
To cause a massive explosion.
What?
After everyone in Tui City enters the shelters,
the shelters will release poison gas.
After they die,
all the organization members
will be reborn and return to Tui City.
Three bomb remote controls are hidden in Tuitu Village.
The map showing where the remotes are hidden is split into two parts.
Each part is hidden in a different place at headquarters.
What does that mean, bro?
He means
they’re going to release poison gas
in all the shelters.
This could kill
everyone in the city.
So no matter what today,
we have to stop this explosion.
Yes, we must stop the explosion.
Let’s check the notes first.
Rebirth research notes.
It says on it
Every time someone is reborn, fog appears
Targeted rebirth
To solve the "pushing eyes" issue
the drawbacks of random rebirth
I discovered targeted rebirth through my research
Encoding the genes
onto the bronze bell device
Bronze bell
Above your head
This one
That's the one
With this, targeted rebirth is possible, actually
By using this technology
our family members from 2125
can precisely be reborn into
bodies from 2025
That's right
This is the one you all
Yesterday, we learned about that plan
Yes, the one with the talisman
February 26, 2025
Organization member
successfully reborn from An Wenzhe's body
Test successful
That day, we found a notebook.
It mentioned an explosion at the Tuitian Food Factory.
Only
seven bodies were found.
Explosion witness record from the neighboring factory area.
On the night of February 26, 2025,
an explosion occurred at the neighboring Tuitian Food Factory.
According to the boss's instructions,
we went next door to patrol and investigate.
Seven bodies were carried out from the factory.
After identification, it was confirmed that
the owner of Tuitian Food Factory, Tan Qian,
and six employees
were among them. The site was cleaned up.
The staff worked until the early hours of the next day.
It was confirmed that there were no other people at the scene.
No one survived.
An Wenzhe.
We suspect he didn't die.
Right.
But here it says
he actually died at that time.
It just says that a member of the organization
successfully used An Wenzhe's body to be reborn.
Yes, it was taken.
And the person who came to see us yesterday
do you remember?
It was An Wenzhe.
Take him inside. Go.
Possession of a body.
So is An Wenzhe
actually a core member of the organization?
Then, on April 1, 2025,
five family members were brought back to life.
Five family members.
Yue, you, him, four, five.
Yes.
That's right.
Family, we've been reborn again.
Family.
May 9, 2025
Yueshe regained her memory
She wanted to stop me
I decided to send her consciousness
back to the year 2125 first
She told you I had something to do and needed to go out
But actually, she had regained her memory
He sent her back
After the big plan succeeds
she will be allowed to return and be reborn
Because earlier, there was a customer
in our shop
Then she added me on WeChat
And yesterday, she sent me a message
at around two in the morning
Later, she asked me to come here
Her name is Yue Liang
She said she had something to tell me
But it might be hard to explain over the phone
So she wanted to tell me in person
She said, "Sister, I am your biological younger sister"
Our family was in danger.
We got separated.
She wouldn't let me leave here.
She said it's dangerous outside.
I see, she wanted you to stay here, right?
She had to go deal with some problems.
Consciousness transfer.
To make up for my mistake.
To switch Ba Snake and Golden Snake back.
It's because you two switched incorrectly.
Right.
If the original form is a snake,
Actually, I entered the wrong body.
I should have entered this body.
Right.
Because my original form is a snake, right?
I kept trying consciousness transfer techniques.
You even killed the eldest brother.
Look how good he was.
He kept trying.
He kept helping you try.
It was accidental.
While talking, I ended up grabbing a knife.
The conversation got heated.
She did this to help you two switch back.
She discovered something.
That is,
consciousness can be transferred to a human body
or to a humanoid object.
It's not just corpses anymore.
Now it can be people too.
Like that paper figure.
Even the paper figure works now.
A mannequin.
Right.
It says below,
if the consciousness
is transferred into a human body,
meaning into a living person,
the original consciousness
will enter
a sleep
or dormant state.
If it transfers to a living person,
Right, for example,
if this person transfers into your body,
your personality, Bai Yu, would disappear.
It would go to sleep.
Bai Yu.
Bai Yu, wake up.
Don't let him take over you, Bai Yu.
No, he took over first.
Then I was automatically replaced.
Blocked.
Yes, blocked.
There's one more thing.
A breakthrough discovery.
It's possible to split one consciousness into
two.
What does that mean?
Splitting one consciousness into two.
That means there could be two people.
So there could be two She.
Qing She and Bai She.
So now it means
Da She’s body has been taken over.
In this case,
there might not be just one
Da She present.
It could be two.
Yes.
A temporary resurrection method for the investigators.
The Special Immigration Bureau found out about my plan.
They plan to send six investigators.
From the year 2125.
Our purpose for coming
is to investigate She.
To investigate She.
Yes.
The Special Immigration Bureau found out about my plan.
So they plan to send six.
Brave, handsome,
beautiful, and alluring.
Are there really those kinds?
He would write it like that.
When you first said six,
I was very unclear.
But when you added those descriptions,
I think
the image became vivid.
It’s clear now, yes.
The Special Transfer Bureau modified my reincarnation technology.
It allows six investigators
to repeatedly reincarnate briefly into living people.
For the first forty hours after reincarnation,
they will be in a state of amnesia.
They receive the original body's memories
and believe they are the original person.
It's as if our original selves never died.
That's how it is.
Every time we arrive at a new scene,
for the first forty hours,
we can't remember anything.
Right.
Once forty hours pass,
we suddenly remember everything.
But just as we remember,
we get blown up.
Every time,
we're blown up just as we're about to regain our memories.
We're really strong, beautiful, and tragic.
The Special Transfer Bureau wants them to reincarnate into
May 10, 2025,
their own bodies,
and then come to stop me.
Their own bodies.
That one.
Investigator Lu Ying.
Why is this phone moving by itself, bro?
What does this mean?
You have deviated from the route.
Okay, there's a call.
This desktop shows a cow and a horse.
That means he's called Niu Ma.
That's probably his subordinate.
Niu Ma's WeChat.
Early yesterday morning
at exactly 5:44
She said
That was close, I almost died
I was stabbed
In order to help Jin She and Ba She
switch bodies
I researched consciousness transfer techniques
and it actually saved me at a critical moment
Right before I died
I transferred my consciousness into the paper figure in the ancestral hall
which led to what happened today
That's great, boss
Who was the attacker?
I'll take him out and avenge you
She said, "Avenge what?"
I didn't die, did I?
The younger ones just lost their heads for a moment
They'll understand my intentions one day
Alright, alright
But for now
we really can't let them
keep causing trouble outside
and ruin my plans
What are you crying for?
Such fake crying
Pretending to feel guilty
Crocodile tears
You are Jin Jing now
Jin Jing, 118 years old
Then he asked, what should we do?
Should we lock them up?
She said,
It's been a long time since I played games with my younger siblings.
Let's have a family game.
Pervert.
I will split my consciousness in two.
And transfer them separately
into the two paper dolls in the ancestral hall.
I deliberately left clues on the phone.
After they see them, they'll enter the ancestral hall.
Each person will take a paper doll.
And enter the meditation room.
The ones who get the two special paper dolls
when they touch the heart of the paper doll,
my consciousness
can take the opportunity to transfer into their bodies.
After controlling these two people,
I can blend in among them.
On one hand, I can stop them from ruining my plan,
and on the other, look for a chance to lock them up again.
Now you know everything, right?
Okay.
Got it.
One thing is certain.
Among us,
there are two bad guys today.
These two people,
I don't know if you had time
to recognize each other.
How about this:
Let's all close our eyes.
Let these two people
do it this way, that's how it is today.
I'm a fair person.
You all close your eyes.
Congratulations.
You've successfully uncovered She's story.
Next, you still need to find
the one hiding among you
with She's consciousness.
And you found a key.
Come on.
Open it, isn't there a lock?
Use it to open that.
I think that one's scary.
But once you open it,
won't the countdown start?
Yes.
The countdown is about to start.
Wait a second.
This is remote bomb one.
The countdown has started.
The countdown is already underway.
Really.
Here, this bomb.
Friends,
Be careful, don't let it explode.
Let me read it to you.
If you want to deactivate this bomb,
we need to, right now,
guess correctly who "She" is.
And it has to be two people.
If we guess wrong,
it'll explode right now.
It'll go off immediately.
Let it explode.
Let it explode, right now.
I'll just cut these two wires.
No, it's about guessing both people correctly at the same time.
How is that possible?
If that's the case,
then this bomb will definitely go off.
Just let go, okay?
Also, go down.
Look down.
Verification method.
Both people put on the iris verification glasses.
Stand on the snake pattern on the floor.
It's outside.
No.
It's here.
This.
Right.
Stand here.
Face the eyeball, the one in front.
This one, let's go with this.
Wait for the laser scan.
Don't put it on yet.
Wait a moment.
We'll verify in a moment, just wait.
Don't, don't rush.
I'm not rushing, no one's rushing.
Don't rush.
You're getting anxious.
Why do you care if I'm anxious?
It's you, actually.
There's one more.
You can turn on the consciousness monitoring remote.
Turn it on.
Pressed it.
It's on.
That one's on.
That one's on. That one.
Consciousness monitoring.
Three people need to be tested at the same time.
There are only two chances to test.
Testers must press both hands firmly on the spherical buttons.
If She’s consciousness is detected inside,
an electric current will be triggered as a warning.
Okay.
Combinations.
This is a bit hard.
This is fun.
Should we just take the risk?
I think I’m pretty clean.
I think he’s clean too.
I think you’re clean too.
Let’s have the three of us go.
I’m clean, but—
Alright, let’s have the three of us try.
Wait a second.
Should we have a round of debate first,
and then try?
That works too.
Let’s do a round first.
I don’t think we need to rush.
Let’s debate first.
Right now, I think you’re very clean.
Why do you think I’m so clean?
Why are you giving me
the label of being clean?
Because I need to pick three people right now.
I think your state is really good right now.
Because if you pick a bad person,
but what if you’re the bad one?
Exactly, that's why I think you're even more innocent.
Wait.
Why is she so eager to take the test?
I think it's fine to take the test.
Listen to me, I know what you mean.
If the test shows that one of the three of us is it,
it's the same.
No, the reason she's eager to test
is because she wants to quickly put herself
in the group with the two innocent people.
Because she knows you two are innocent.
It's fine.
Her eagerness to test
is definitely not the behavior of a bad person.
Why?
Because the four of us good people are
a relatively large group.
Let me tell you,
when there are truly four good people,
they argue very intensely.
It's possible that the two bad people don't say a word.
Who isn't talking?
They could also be the bad guys.
During intense arguments,
everyone is thinking like a good person.
That's how we can all see it.
Do you get it? That's the logic.
Okay, sure.
It's possible, that's possible.
No, let's do this:
Don't rush to test yet.
Let's have a round of debate first.
Okay.
This is the most correct.
That's exactly what I mean.
Sit.
Everyone, calm down first.
We have a strategy now.
Go ahead.
Can we
put the two most suspicious people
in the same group?
That would narrow things down.
Yes.
If we get it wrong this round,
we'll have two out of six to choose from.
If we get it right this round,
we'll have at least two out of three to choose from.
Right.
Only then can we
That's right.
do this with a better chance of winning.
Exactly.
I think
did I just pick the right three clean people?
Three clean people.
Then the two bad guys found out.
So they urgently tried to stop us.
Are you saying I stopped you?
I think there's no need to rush.
Let's discuss it first.
Are you saying I stopped you?
No, you didn't stop me.
She was talking about him.
Me?
Why is she so eager to try?
But the problem is, do the two of them know about each other?
Did they attach themselves to each other?
If they know about each other,
not necessarily.
But the problem is, just now when we finished, we didn't
necessarily know.
Because he split off alone.
Okay.
You finish first, I'll listen to you.
Go ahead.
Look,
if she's the killer,
she actively let me and him join.
If all three of us joined,
then the two killers couldn't be together.
What do you mean?
Between the two of us, there must be
at least one good person, right?
Yes, that's what I meant just now.
So,
if she's the killer,
she just pulled me and him in.
That's right.
He agreed too.
Yes.
If those two are
they can't be together.
Right.
Isn't that right?
Who would be afraid to try?
Only a good person would hesitate to speak up.
Wait a minute.
I'm not sure.
But why would a bad person dare to try?
Maybe he thinks
he can blend in and hide among us.
Right.
That's why he would agree right away.
I agree with you.
You agreed right away, just now.
I didn't.
I even argued with her just now.
The two of us were arguing with her.
Right.
Okay.
Then how about the three of us try?
No.
What do you think?
You
Alright, I got it.
I have a ticket now.
What do you think?
You see your teammate here.
I know, I have a ticket now.
Don't.
I have a ticket now.
Let them speak first.
Don't rush.
Let me finish.
You go first.
Listen to him.
What I need right now is
Let's vote first, then talk.
Okay?
Alright, let's start voting.
I think it's you two.
Pair up.
Okay.
Great!
We have to win today.
We're really pairing up today, sis.
We're really pairing up today.
I think it's you two, one big and one small.
Which two? Us two?
How do you want to split into groups to test?
It's the three of us—how should we group?
Then arrange this.
Just the three of us.
And the three of you.
Alright.
Got it.
Based on what just happened,
I think the more aggressive people
seem more likely to be good in my view.
I’d prefer if the three of us try.
Because I think the bad guys
now seem to be Ning and Ba.
I think it might be two "She".
Because just now, Ning was in the cell
and kept not going up.
To me, it looked like stalling for time.
If all six of us go up,
we can’t raise our hands that high.
The six of us can’t make it up there.
Okay, got it, I understand.
Alright.
If
let me follow your logic.
Okay.
Maybe one of Ning or Ba
The two of them can be together,
and then add one more at random.
So, if you analyze it this way,
you think one of them is "She".
Put them in one group first.
Then the remaining three are us.
Who do you think is most "She" among us?
Then just assign that person over there.
The three of us:
You and me,
No, except for yourself.
You know you’re a good person.
Right.
It’s He, Jin, and Ke.
Which one of us three is "She"?
You’re not really "She".
I’ll rule you out for now, okay?
I’ll trust you for the time being.
Alright.
Then it’s between those two.
It’s a one out of two between us.
You’ll definitely pick me. Who else would you choose?
Can I think about it before giving my answer?
Okay.
Let me think about it before I answer.
Alright, but I already have my answer.
Based on the test you just did,
and their reactions,
I’m also more certain about my answer.
I think it’s those two.
The two of us?
Yes.
We’re together again.
Yeah.
Alright.
So here’s how it is now.
I’ve already prepared for two people.
One is him, the other is her.
I’m definitely ready.
If you want to take him to try,
I agree with that.
Then the three of us will be together.
But now I’m a bit suspicious of his identity.
I don’t care.
You don’t have to suspect him.
Because when he was pulled down in the first round,
I called for his help.
He didn’t help.
I think that’s suspicious.
You pulled, but I was already down.
You were already down.
You could have helped me.
How about the three of us give it a try?
Or maybe you three can try it.
This is my answer.
Okay.
Sure.
Then actually, the three of us are more likely.
Then it’s just the three of us.
Now it’s those three.
There doesn’t seem to be that much suspicion.
Just everyone.
The three of us will try, okay?
I think you really seem like a good person.
Okay.
Let’s try one round first and then talk.
Hurry up and go.
I don’t care.
Go quickly.
Which three of us?
Hurry up.
The three of us.
Yeah, do you agree?
Why?
Go.
I just changed my vote.
Okay, go ahead, you say it.
Alright, then you go ahead.
So what combination do you want to go with?
I think...
As for Ning, my opinion of him has changed.
I’m considering who the other good person is.
Which of the four is more certain?
Who do you think it is? Who’s the third good person?
I would think it's you.
So you want the three of us to try?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Okay.
I'm fine with anything. The two of us.
It's just that my vote changed just now.
I said my opinion of Ning has changed.
Alright, I think so too.
The four of us seem like good people.
So the four of us
can probably do anything and it'll be fine.
No, if you put it that way,
that means those two are definitely the bad guys.
We can't say for sure who's definitely bad right now.
We can only eliminate possibilities.
And say who we personally trust as good.
Then take the good people to try.
The chances of winning are higher that way.
Is it really like that?
Then let's go.
Wait a moment.
You guys.
You two.
Time.
There's still...
There's still ten minutes, ten minutes.
Hurry up, get up quickly.
You... you all.
Isn't it the three of you?
In the end, you two.
Can you talk a bit more?
Say anything, whatever.
I just think the three of us should go try.
That's what I think.
I think the three of us are fine.
The three of us
I have a question
For example, let's suppose, just in case
if the three of us go out
and one of us is "She"
can you be sure among the three of us
who is "She"?
That's the question
Come on
So you have to
Let me say something
Don't overthink this
Don't overthink this round
Let's just do our best
Because we've already analyzed it
We've already gained something
Even if you three figure it out
we'll figure it out too
We can still choose
So go ahead and try boldly
Go with your first instinct, bro
Come on, let's go
The three of us
Don't say anything
Let's just go with our gut feeling
Go
Cast a vote
Come on
Three
Two
There's power.
It's done.
Already done.
Let's go.
So one of you is She.
We have She among us.
There's She.
Bro.
It's you.
Then let's try again with Zhang Linghe.
Is that okay?
Okay.
No, why?
Let's try again with Zhang Linghe.
If both rounds are the same,
I'm willing.
We pick two out of four.
No.
You guys now...
We'll take He.
We pick two out of four.
That's still better than picking two out of six.
Right?
Right.
Isn't it?
Let's go.
Okay, sure.
You're not She, are you?
I'm not.
There's power.
Okay.
That was me.
Then I'm She.
Jin and He.
Jin and the two of us.
Doesn't this make it harder?
Wait, I probably...
Let me ask you this.
If you're not the bad guy,
which one of us would you choose?
I'm a bit unsure.
You're playing so well.
Now you're not sure about me.
I just had one...
Because if I'm being honest,
If it's between you two, I think it's you.
But how could I...
Why have you been with me the whole time?
And there's always been power?
Because of the three people in the first round
I said
if the three of us went to try
and it turned out there was She
I'm very sure She is him
That was my thought at the time
because I was already conflicted
You replaced him
Yes, I replaced him
because I thought you were definitely a good person
Your state was really good
So I thought if the three of us went
it would definitely be clean
But among the three of us
there was still She
And just now, he
like this
she went
in the rotation group
you went
Yes
to test the iris
Go try the iris scan.
The other She.
It's between you two.
I don't dare let you lead me anymore.
Go try it.
It's really not me.
Don't waste this opportunity.
I really can't let you lead me again.
Bro.
There was power in the first round, and there was She.
I really can't let you lead me.
Is he She?
I'm not sure anymore.
Because I'm a good person.
You don't seem like a good person.
Because...
I'm scared of you now.
Come, listen to me.
You don't seem like a good person.
Wait a second, everyone.
Three minutes left.
Hurry up.
In my heart, Ba is always that something.
Ba is always one of them.
Because Ba was there at the time.
When putting together that puzzle piece.
You kept getting it wrong.
Where is this?
I'm turning it clockwise, clockwise.
Left side, it's on the left.
No, clockwise, baby.
How much time is left?
Time's up.
I didn't get it wrong.
It will stick.
I think Bai and Ba should go try now.
Bai, Ba.
I agree with Bai and Ba too.
Bai and Ba.
Why not you?
Who am I with?
Don't rush.
Vote, stop arguing.
Stop arguing.
Guys, vote.
You just ended up with Ba, right?
No.
Vote.
Let's vote, okay?
Stop arguing.
Hurry.
It's about to explode.
You two are voting for us now.
Yes.
Jin and Ning, go.
I vote for you two, you go try.
You have the most votes.
Jin and Ning, go.
Jin and Ning, go try.
I've finished voting.
I have Ning.
I don't know who the other one is.
You two have to comply.
Minority obeys the majority now.
Hurry up.
It's about to explode.
Let's go.
Okay.
Jin and Ning, go.
Okay, come on.
Go quickly.
Come on, try it.
Hurry up.
Forty seconds.
Today, you...
If you really lied to me,
I'll really hate you for the rest of my life.
I'm telling you,
It's Bai Yu, I'm telling you.
I've already figured it out.
I need to move over a bit.
It might explode in a moment.
I think it's you.
You're laughing so happily.
It's not me.
It's you two.
No way.
Failed to identify the culprit.
Verification failed.
Unbelievable.
Iris verification failed.
Bomb number one activated.
A random location will be detonated.
It's you.
You two.
You kept putting me in front the whole time.
Sorry.
Let's go try it.
Really.
Sorry.
Okay, the two of us will go try.
I was apologizing to you two.
I was saying sorry to both of you.
I heard it, because you're She.
You're definitely She.
Why?
Dear.
Because you can't help but laugh right now.
Your mouth is all curled up.
Really?
Because you played it so well.
Then let's keep guessing, okay?
Okay.
Let's see how smart we are.
I really can't take it anymore.
We haven't tried yet.
About She, I think...
I'm begging you.
Please, let me try.
I really need to know who She is.
This is very important to me.
Boss.
You guys are amazing.
Leave the remaining four to us.
Take them out.
Lock them in the office.
Yes.
Take out those four.
Take them out.
Mr. She's consciousness is split in two.
You have another companion.
It's the person who chose the orange paper figure.
Mr. She's plan left two clues.
As long as you manage to
have the clue destroyed once,
and keep it hidden until the end, you can get the golden key.
Stop or delay the others' actions.
While others are completing their tasks,
secretly sabotage them.
I've already come down.
You're down now, you can help me.
Go stop them.
We can help them.
Help me.
Don't rush.
The two of us are...
The two of us are carrying it.
Where is it?
Two.
Who should take it? Should I?
Who is (turning) doing what?
Bai
Me? Is it me?
The two of us were dragged along by you.
It wasn't me.
Wait a moment.
Just now She was causing trouble.
Who is causing trouble?
Who did you just think was causing trouble?
Zhang Linghe
I had no idea where you all were going the whole time.
I am She.
You are S(he).
You are Cow.
Let us go.
I'm angry.
I want revenge.
You want revenge.
Yes, me.
That's She’s father.
Really?
If
Let me go along with what you said.
Okay.
Only good people would be afraid to say it.
Wait a second.
I'm not sure.
Yes.
Except for yourself.
You know you’re a good person.
Yes.
First impression, bro.
Come on, let's go.
The three of us.
So one of you is She.
We have She among us.
There is She.
Bro.
It's you.
Choosing two out of four is better than two out of six.
Right?
Right.
Isn't it?
Let's go.
The three of us.
Yeah.
Why
I just changed my vote
It's been two minutes, vote
Vote
Just vote, stop arguing
Stop arguing
Guys, vote
She goes
In the rotation group
Jin and Ning go
I vote for you two, you two go try
You have the most votes
Boss
We're here
Very good
Right across from headquarters
We've prepared a celebration banquet for you
Okay
We can go eat first
Alright
Boss
Please
You four
Goodbye
Let me bow to you
Why bow
We're both the boss
Feels good
Lock them in the office
I think he's clean too
The three of us will try, okay
I think you seem like a good person
You're not She, are you
I'm not
This is really too hard.
He just wouldn't get up earlier.
Because at first, I thought the three of you would go over.
When the three of us went over,
he just kept sitting there.
He said, "Wait, I don't get it."
Wait, I don't get it.
He just sat there on the bench.
I told him, "Go on!"
He still said, "Wait."
Hurry up and go.
Get up already.
Aren't you three supposed to go?
Just you, go ahead.
Why?
I just changed my vote.
Wait, I don't get it.
Just sitting there on the bench.
Poor good people.
Let's comfort each other now.
Let's not hurt each other anymore.
Let's comfort each other.
Oh no, oh no.
How did you guys get locked up?
Why did the magic stop working?
It's okay.
I found a way to drive She away.
Flick hard the person controlled by Mr. She
on the forehead.
That will drive away She's consciousness.
You guys hurry up and go.
Forehead? Whose forehead?
She's forehead.
These two people.
These two.
We have to find those two first.
Come on, let's go.
We should be able to get out through this window.
It's this window.
What is this supposed to be?
Okay.
It can be opened.
It can be pulled open.
Come on, let's go.
Come on, boss, after you.
Alright, boss.
Take your time eating.
I'll take the guys and head out first.
Alright.
Goodbye, boss.
Go get the whip and hit them.
Alright, let's go.
Hello.
Hi.
Please have a seat first.
Okay.
Eat first.
Have a few bites.
Let me know if you need anything.
Alright.
Should we go back?
See what they're doing.
Xiao Ba, you saw how foolish I was.
And you didn't stop me.
Because everyone was already suspicious of me.
So I said the three of us should go first.
Couldn't you use a true love's kiss
to wake me up?
If this happens again,
run.
Go beat them up for me.
Hit them for me.
Hit.
Put it on me.
I'm ready to fight.
No, it's okay.
Zhang Linghe.
Ning, have a seat.
Can I flick the arm?
What do you mean by flicking the arm?
They want to flick the forehead.
I think flicking the forehead isn't painful enough.
What's this task for?
Flick him.
We need you.
Flick the "She" out of your bodies.
Don't flick.
Then we'll keep it.
No, I want my real brother back.
This bad brother isn't mine.
Who will hit him?
Come on, let me flick you.
Go ahead.
You're not even using any force.
I don't feel anything.
Really?
No feeling.
I don't feel anything.
Come.
Give me your hand.
I'm on your side now.
No.
Hit hard.
Use force.
Use extra force.
It's okay, come here.
They've already been punished.
She's lost consciousness.
Then how do we know where the bomb is?
What is this?
Describe and act it out in Cantonese.
Let the restaurant owner guess the answer.
That counts as a successful challenge.
Restaurant owner.
What's the matter?
Can we play a game with you?
Sure.
There are a total of
eleven characters.
The first character is
another meaning of "tong".
And.
That's right.
Okay.
The second character.
Archery
Shoot
Yes
The third character
Cow
Yes
The fourth character
One
The fifth character
Sit down and stand up
Get up
Yes
The two of us are here
Playing
The last five characters
Come play
Nothing
What kind of person is he
Introverts and extroverts
But
Come
Play with the social butterfly
Introverts become extroverts
So smart
That means we are too
"Potential stock"
Then I'm just an "attention seeker"
Coca-Cola sharing bottle
Multiple personalities launched
Have fun with the Coca-Cola sharing bottle
Let's have fun together and happily recommend
Come on, cheers
Thank you.
This is the secret recipe.
You just need to dab a little on your forehead.
You'll recover in an hour.
She still has some lingering memories.
You guys try it out.
I'll go prepare the food.
Okay.
You put it on me.
Wait, don't.
You don't need to use it, right?
Okay, it's done.
The two of them already did it themselves.
Let's eat first.
Wait for their memories to come back.
Alright.
Wait, just now you...
Didn't you already eat?
I wasn't full.
Or maybe take real action, right.
Like this.
In a bit, you two sinners
will carry the two ladies forward.
For all the next steps, you have to carry them.
They're not allowed to walk a single step.
Work a little harder.
Alright?
You can atone for your sins.
It's fine.
Bro, you said carrying you is fine.
I carried for a while.
I won't be polite with you.
I feel like I ate something.
Some of She's memories are still lingering.
I just remembered something.
Before She left,
he said he would hide this
bomb remote control
in the city gate archway
and the location on the map.
After you expelled She's consciousness just now,
he transferred to someone else.
You need to find him as soon as possible.
First, send him back to the 22nd century.
So he can't update
the bomb remote control's timer in real time.
Then go find and disable
the bomb remote control.
Only then can you resolve the current crisis in Tui City.
She's consciousness has already been transferred.
So it's not among us.
Not among us.
That's right.
I'll give you two tools.
One can help you locate him.
This is a route.
Another one can send his consciousness
back to the 22nd century
It can only be used once
to send a person back to the 22nd century
Let's go
Let's go to Haoju Haosan Shop
So beautiful
Wait a second
What is this
Is this for that ritual
What do these mean
Let's go, hurry up
Quick, look for it, go
Hurry
Faster
You hit him in a bit
No
I'm afraid I won't hit him
You can do it
You hit him
I believe in you
Haoju Haosan
Haoju Haosan Shop
These people are very suspicious.
One of these people should be the one.
She.
The one fanning herself.
Who are you?
Is there something you need?
These are all your employees, right?
Yes, I'm moving my shop today.
These are all workers I hired.
Is there anyone
who suddenly started acting strange just now?
That's right.
All these people are workers I hired.
I gathered them.
I don't know all of them.
They just came here to make some money.
So what are their names?
You don't know?
I don't know them.
Then how do you communicate with them?
I just...
Yeah.
That boy
That's him
An Wenzhe
Where
Th-this
An Wenzhe
What are you doing
You can't leave
Boss
We'll buy all the umbrellas you have
Take off his mask
Okay, we'll give it to him
An Wenzhe
Are you sure it's him
We just passed a path full of flowers
She passed by too
Look at his feet
There is
Then he has it too.
This one has it as well.
They all have it.
How about this, then?
You all investigate thoroughly.
I don't want to use anyone with an unclear background either.
Alright.
Okay.
Come on, brothers.
Come, line up in two rows first.
Let's take a look first.
Brother, please lift your foot so we can check the sole.
This one has it too.
Alright.
Come on, lift your left foot.
Nothing.
Right foot up.
Alright, go back to work.
Brother, nothing else here.
Get some good rest.
What are you doing?
Come on, left foot up.
Come on, right foot up.
Alright, you two go have some tea.
Come on, go take a seat.
Find a place to rest.
You don't need to check anymore.
Come on, brother.
Left foot up.
Come on, right foot up.
Alright, you three go rest over there.
This way.
Her expression.
Come on, left foot up.
Come on, right foot up.
Teacher, this way.
Come on, left foot up.
There's something wrong with this person.
Lift your right foot.
Yes.
Stay here for me.
Come on, lift your left foot.
No.
Come on, lift your right foot.
Come on, lift your left foot.
Come on, right foot.
Go ahead.
Okay, come on.
You three, go stand over there.
One She can only be used on two people.
Now there are three.
That's right.
Thank you for your hard work, teachers.
Take off that mask.
Okay?
Let's take a look at their faces to see who it is.
Beard
We've met.
I am the director with ten billion in box office sales.
Nominate the ten-billion director.
We should have met him too, right?
He is the Great-Grandfather of the Good family.
I am the Great-Grandfather of the Good family.
Great-Grandfather Good
Nominate Great-Grandfather.
Yes.
So all three of them were resurrected by She.
Alright, come on.
I'll give you one last chance.
Who was just suddenly possessed by She?
That's so scary.
You look more like you were possessed by She.
The way you are now.
Me.
I'm a good person who was tricked by She.
She
You already embarrassed me just now.
I'll give you another chance.
Come out on your own, obediently.
Like this.
See, as soon as I make a fuss,
my brother will come out.
What time did you get here?
The umbrella shop owner called me over.
Then we said we were coming to move some things.
What were you doing at two o'clock?
I usually like a bit of
artistic hobbies.
So I write calligraphy and paint.
Where are your calligraphy and paintings?
Speaking of that,
I wrote a piece of calligraphy today.
But I didn't have time to mount it.
Let's take a look, come on.
Write the exact same thing again.
If you can't reproduce it now,
then you're a liar.
I'll shoot.
There's still music coming from Liuxing Street,
is it the sound of a bayan accordion?
Alexander's bakery,
has the rye bread come out of the oven?
Is this a song?
Alexander's bakery,
this is the right flavor.
We sang it on the first day.
I want to send you my endless longing.
Alright, what about you?
What were you doing at two o'clock?
Cooking.
Bring out your food, let me have a bite.
No, I mean, what were you cooking?
Chopping dumplings.
Chopping dumplings?
Those are two very amateurish things to say.
Making dumplings, chopping dumplings.
He seems like his consciousness just arrived
in a new host.
Yeah.
His mouth isn't fully under control yet, right?
That's right.
What were you doing at two o'clock?
I was carving jade.
If you're a jade carver,
your hands would have a lot of calluses.
Take off their gloves.
I think they should take them off.
Do your hands look like a jade carver's, man?
Which hand?
So smooth.
Which hand do you usually use to carve jade?
I use my right hand.
Which hand do you usually use to cook?
My left hand.
Which hand do you usually use to write?
My right hand.
It's him.
It's the left-handed person.
Why?
Because that guy, She,
is used to using his left hand.
Who said that?
In that office.
Yes.
You didn't mishear.
Who cooks with their left hand?
I cook with my right hand.
You just said left hand.
You said left hand just now.
You think we're fools.
Come on, play it back.
Which hand do you usually use to cook?
Left hand.
Alright, it's you.
I'll shoot you.
Don't move.
You think only you have guns?
You all better think carefully.
Why do you think I'm doing all this?
To help humanity, right?
Then don't you think
they should die?
If you think so too,
then why are you stopping me?
We just want to find you.
And give you a big hug.
Hold you tight.
Do you know what kind of life we live in 2125?
It's dark and cold there.
We never see the sun.
There are catastrophic famines everywhere.
But who caused all this?
Wasn't it all their doing?
We even sent our last hope,
our children,
back here.
We hoped to change them,
to change the future.
And what happened?
Your child was still killed.
That's right.
My daughter died.
She was just an ordinary
and very cute little girl.
My daughter was beaten to death.
What did she do wrong?
We have ways to deal with natural disasters.
We can unite together
to resist them.
But what about man-made disasters?
What should we do then?
But those two people were punished by you as well,
weren't they?
Was that punishment enough?
You can punish those two
who caused your daughter's death,
but taking everyone's lives
is not your right.
Well said.
Let me tell you all,
nothing here will end.
Even if you stop me this time,
this world
will still get worse little by little.
Everything will still happen again.
Everything will keep repeating.
Stop him.
Why are you treating him like this?
Is he a bad person?
He is a bad person.
Then let's carry him out first.
Let's go.
Here, give him to me.
He's too evil.
Sent him two hundred years further.
Gave him two more shots.
That's true.
He went to the year 2325.
Someone who definitely knows when to fire extra shots.
So at this moment,
we need to go back and find something.
Right?
Find the bomb.
That's right.
But there's a problem.
Come here, quickly.
What's wrong?
Hurry up.
Everyone, spread out a bit.
Look up there.
What are you looking at?
Look at the camera.
It stopped.
Come on.
I thought it was something else.
Come here.
Turn around, okay?
Everyone suddenly looks up like this.
It's that feeling of sudden realization.
Just as an example, I get it.
Like, you're over there, that kind of thing.
So, let's talk about a topic.
Do you know where to look?
Three, two, one.
Right.
That's what it looks like, right?
Yeah.
Come on.
So where should we look now?
We've been searching all day.
I'm so tired.
Where exactly are we going?
Okay.
Let's go.
Look for the bomb.
Hurry.
The bomb's remote is hidden in
the city gate passage.
Yes.
Now She has already
been sent back by us.
Next, we need to hurry to
the south gate tower to find the bomb.
Will it be there?
It's possible.
Yes.
One of the remotes is at
Haoju Hao Umbrella Shop.
Found it.
Where is it?
Bomb
Five-minute countdown
After the countdown ends
The bomb will explode immediately
Cut the wires in a specific order
to stop the bomb from detonating
Take this, then
Come on, strong guy
Let me carry it
I need to atone
You should take it
Atonement
Let's go to the south city gate tower now
to find another bomb
Okay
There's not much time left
We have to do it this way
Hurry
Go
Hurry, a little faster
Hurry
So it's right here
Outside, go out
Isn't this the city gate tower?
This
Look for the remote here
How do we find it?
It's such a large area
He said he would hide the remote for the bomb
in the city gate passage.
The passage under the city tower.
He said
He meant the passage under the city tower.
The passage, right.
The passage.
Then it should be here.
There's a hole in the door here.
Behind the door, check behind the door.
Here.
Thirty-six seconds left.
Hurry.
Quick.
We have to cut it.
This one needs to be cut.
Here.
Hurry, cut it.
What about the order?
This one.
Look at the words.
If you cut the wires in the correct order,
the bomb can be stopped from exploding.
What color is Room 1?
Paper figure.
Right.
Room 1 is purple.
Room 2 is red.
Here.
This one.
Room 3 is green.
Room 4 is yellow.
Blue.
Okay.
This one is done.
So what I said about the paper figure earlier was wrong?
This one?
Is this some kind of map?
It's the city tower.
It's the lights on the city tower.
Four, five, and there's six on top.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
What color is number one?
There's no number one here.
Mine starts from four.
At the back.
There are more at the back.
Number one is over there.
Number one is over there, it's purple.
I see it.
Number two, the tall one, look at number two.
Number two is blue.
Okay, cut it.
Number one is purple.
Number two is blue.
Blue.
Number three is green.
Number four is red.
Number five is white.
Number six is yellow.
It didn't explode, right?
It didn't explode.
Then that's right.
Right?
At least we saved a group of people.
So beautiful.
So pretty.
Okay.
Is this one an explosive?
This one isn't an explosive.
This is...
A celebratory firework.
A victory celebration firework.
Yes.
So beautiful.
Eyes, the eyes are bright now.
That's great.
You finally managed to perfectly
resolve this crisis.
With the Special Immigration Bureau
beginning to operate the Rebirth Immigration Project,
the reborn citizens of Tui City
have caused some
butterfly effect changes to Tui City.
The car is gone.
The names of these animals have all changed.
My surname is Lin.
You can just call me Old Lin.
Among these reborn individuals,
Mr. She also slipped in
as a conspirator.
To find him
and stop his plan,
the Special Immigration Bureau recruited you.
Your first rebirth
was on May 10, 2025.
You were reborn into
your own bodies during a team-building event.
But at that time,
you were still discovered by She.
He not only caused an explosion
that killed your bodies,
but also used the "Memory Eraser Bullet"
to make your consciousness lose its memory as well.
Do you still remember your mission?
No, we don't.
You almost completely forgot
that you were detectives from the year 2125.
I can only rely on
The times and places where She appeared
let you be reborn again to
February 25, 2025
at the Tui Sweet Food Factory
It was discovered that a mysterious person
was funding Ning Dengpao to carry out live-streamed killings
at the Pirate Mansion on March 14
a mysterious person was found
who kidnapped Ren Weishan
forty percent of the wealthy clients
on April 22
at Tui Billion Film Company
She was seen escaping with a box
at Goodhouse Private on May 8
Starting at the end of this month
I will transport to you every month
six corpses
The contact person is
Ning Dengpao from Tui Sweet Food Factory
It was found that the mysterious person was She
Tui Taiye helped him store the corpses
You were at Tui Sweet Food Factory
and caused an explosion at Pirate Mansion
killing so many people
The explosion was made to obtain corpses
Yes
And it was discovered
that the previous explosion
was also caused by She
Next
She was going to complete his new rebirth plan
Now, he has finally been stopped
Not only did you save your 2025
selves
but also saved the entire Tui City
We did it.
That's great.
Alright.
So we can say we've saved this city.
Really?
We saved one place, at least.
At least we saved some people.
Yeah.
Maintaining world peace.
And we sent She back.
Right.
But I think
the Special Immigration Bureau
and She both acted wrongly.
They don't believe
that people today can save themselves.
But we believe they can.
Yes.
Actually, this is a very, very
thought-provoking concept.
It's about protecting the environment.
In recent years,
we've also seen a lot of extreme environmental events around us.
Glaciers keep melting.
Some species are slowly becoming endangered.
Let's cherish our resources even more.
Every small action in our daily lives
Maybe it will all become part of the butterfly effect.
Environmental protection is not just an issue for the future.
Nor is it someone else's responsibility.
It's closely connected to each and every one of us.
I think in our daily lives, we can
do our best to protect nature,
experience nature,
and cherish our own home.
At the same time, we're also protecting ourselves.
As long as each of us starts with what's around us,
and cares for the environment we live in,
I believe we can have
a better future.
Yes.
We have to say goodbye to Tui City in 2025.
Say goodbye.
We're going back to 2125.
Are we going back to the future?
Yes.
This matter has come to an end for now.
It's temporarily concluded.
He said he would come back.
He said all of this is a cycle.
So something else might happen in the future.
Our responsibilities in Tui City in 2025
have been fulfilled.
Yes.
That's right.
We are He Li Mo and Jin Yu
This is a livestream factory
But they're a bit sinister
They don't let them leave
Looking into each little cubicle
Everyone is livestreaming
It feels like what you see isn't
real, living people
but rather one by one, they're
puppets controlled by traffic
I'll just give you
the latest flight number of the nine-letter actress
and send it to you
That's actually illegal
Don't think that just because you didn't press that button
it has nothing to do with you
If you stand by
watching
egging others on
or participating
Even if you weren't the one who pressed the button in the end
you're still responsible
Don't ignore small good deeds
Don't do something just because the evil seems small
Don't think what you did was just a small thing
It could affect many more lives
Pushing others forward just to gain immortality
creates a deadly trap
His desires only grow
Greed is like a dagger
At first, it might just
nick the edge of morality
But if left unchecked
it will cut deeper and deeper
The true value of life
isn't about how many days we've lived
but about, in those days
how many moments we were truly alive
Ren Weishan
He acts under the guise of kindness
and runs these companies.
But in reality,
behind the scenes, he controls a very
large and illegal
and extremely vicious interest group.
It's extremely cruel.
He turns many young, innocent women
into childbearing machines.
They are checked for no previous medical history,
no bad habits,
and excellent genes.
They are able to give birth.
They have already given birth for Ren Weishan,
having two sons and one daughter.
They even specially created
a system
to evaluate the quality of their genes.
This is extremely sick,
perverse,
and utterly vile.
I hope all women
when faced with any
situation that makes them uncomfortable,
can bravely say no.
May all women
truly have
control over their own bodies.
May every child
grow up safely and happily in the sunlight.
We all played the role of scapegoat friends.
When they have problems themselves,
they vent to you,
dumping all their negative emotions onto you.
I happened to think he was me,
so I beat him up.
My friend Bai and I were in the same scene.
He also had this script.
You falsely accused him.
Being friends with someone like this
really
If you ever meet a friend like this,
I hope you learn to cut your losses in time.
Have the courage to walk away.
Feudal superstitions
definitely lack a lot
of scientific basis.
They lead to blind worship.
In fact, it allows many people
to take advantage of you for their own gain.
Don't be the one to lead in superstition.
Believe in the power of science.
Let reason light the path ahead for us.
Every little thing humans do
affects their future.
Once lived in cold and damp
caves.
Everyone fell asleep in the cold.
It was all caused by the ignorance of people here.
As for the future world,
it is actually created by people today.
That's right.
These earth resources slipping through our fingers
are not just simple numbers.
They are bills our descendants will have to pay.
I hope everyone will take action.
Cherish every resource.
Because every step we take
truly affects the future of the Earth.
He Li Mo Jin Yu
See you in the market in 2025.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, friends.
Goodbye, friends. Goodbye. Say (goodbye).
We interrupt with breaking news.
Following the incident at Apartment 11,
Tui Town,
Tui Sweets Factory,
Classic Eternal Pirate Mansion,
Tui Billion Film Company,
and Tui Soil Village, where strange cases have occurred,
Tui City is once again facing an unknown crisis.
Location: Tui City.
The finale dinner of "Let's Start Reasoning" Season 3.
I'm going to finish this bowl.
Changsha's food is still the best.
What's wrong?
He ate a yogurt curd.
Summer Four-Fruit Soup.
They even specially made a goldfish.
That's He Li touching Jin Yu.
We should do a food travel variety show.
Rice wine Hakka Hetian chicken.
It has a wine aroma.
Its logic should be...
No.
It's all logic again, amazing.
The trophy just doesn't have any words on it.
I'm called "Crying and Laughing."
I'm both crying and laughing.
But I can't get the golden key.
You can't help but laugh.
You can't help but be bad.
He can't help but love.
May I ask Zhou Keyu,
if you return to the real world,
what do the older brothers and sisters mean to you
in terms of their roles?
Can't help but love.
I hope everyone doesn't do this.
Remember these iconic moments.
It will make them excited.
In the third season of "Start Reasoning",
what memorable scenes do you all remember?
It's public embarrassment again.
I was riding on Keyu's back.
It was also that swimming pool.
I'm the same as Brother Ning.
You can tell at a glance
he's a science and engineering guy who's great at math, physics, and chemistry.
What are the five of us?
Jellyfish?
I didn't draw people.
You didn't draw people, so you don't have anyone in your heart.
We're not in your heart.
What impressed you was the pool, not us.
Let me tell you, he didn't say a word.
Anyone could be in there.
He's 12 years younger than you.
Sorry, little brother.
I think this drawing is really good.
Next up is
the awarding of the "Star of Reasoning City".
Thank you for letting me win.
I think it's me.
Congratulations.
Split my consciousness into two
After controlling these two people
I can blend in among them
After seeing the eye gesture
I immediately realized
The six detectives were reincarnated into
the bodies of my family members
I can't get rid of the detectives by killing the bodies
to eliminate the detectives
Otherwise, my family would die too
So I can only blend in with them for now
and closely monitor their movements
Jingou Baiou
That's mine
You said it was delicious yesterday
This one is super tasty
There's still one unopened here
Noodles, do you want some?
I'll mix it for you
What do you want to eat?
I can skip eating
Oh no, my voice is even hoarser
It wasn't hoarse at all during the debate just now
I was just about to ask how you suddenly got better
Those two
The down-and-out returnee from abroad
The aloof young lady
I don't believe you all can pass this round
Show us the replay
Jiawei just now was
lifted off the ground, right?
He was airborne
His belly button was showing
Don't catch a cold, keep your stomach warm
Slim waist