(Crazy Handsome Rich)
(Episode 2)
Warning.
This series is created from imagination.
It is suitable for everyone.
Is that right?
Anyway, our content isn't realistic.
We focus on assumptions.
The previous episode
of Crazy Handsome Rich.
This is Sin, your family's new butler.
Are you Sin?
Yes.
Do you know
that we don't allow women here?
Yes.
I'm a man.
How can I be sure
that you're not in disguise?
By the way,
you don't look like your brother.
What should we do, Thod?
Take off your clothes.
Huh?
Why should a butler strip naked?
Hey.
I don't want to be a butler anymore.
But it's the rule here.
It's a crazy rule!
It's so embarrassing!
I'm so sorry that I didn't tell you first.
But he's very strict.
I'm out.
I'm going home.
Hey.
This is my special item!
You're rethinking now, aren't you?
Hey.
This necklace.
This is the necklace
that will lead you to your soulmate.
After this day, your destiny
will change.
Be prepared to handle it well.
Oh.
This?
This is Mr. Thod's necklace.
I'm going to put it away.
What is it?
Nothing.
Are you sure about that?
So will you go back inside?
So?
Come on. You're overthinking.
I haven't found my soulmate,
how can I leave?
Mr. Butler.
The way he called me
shows that he wants to stay longer.
Where is my room?
Why?
He probably wants to stay.
Follow me.
A love song.
It's amazing.
I'll keep playing then.
Huh?
Haven't you put your things away?
I'm sorry.
Please excuse us.
- Mister.
- What?
Should I put this necklace away?
Necklace? I thought it was a chain
for the door lock.
Okay.
Butler Sin.
Yes?
So let's keep playing.
I'll keep playing.
Where is he taking me?
We've arrived at the bridal house.
I mean his room.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Stop being surprised.
So this is my room.
Wow, it's so nice!
Here. This is the butler's dormitory.
You should get some rest inside.
We must prepare snacks
for the misters at 13:15.
Okay.
Good luck.
Okay, let's go.
He'll become rich.
Is this the bedroom?
It's so beautiful.
I'll stay as long as I want.
It's so luxurious.
This necklace?
Was the fortune teller saying the truth?
Mister.
Should I put this necklace away?
Necklace?
Huh?
Okay.
Why are you smiling?
Or you want to compete
and see whose teeth are whiter?
No.
You forgot this.
Oh, thank you, sir.
Never mind, I'll put it there.
Mister.
My name is Thep.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, Mr. Thep.
Are you really Butler Sorn's brother?
Yes, I am.
It's weird.
I never knew...
Knew...
Knew what, sir?
I never knew you were this handsome.
Oh, I was handsome since birth.
Thank you so much, Mr. Thep.
You are so handsome too.
Thanks. Everyone says so.
When you're with me,
don't be tensed.
You can talk to me.
- I don't have many friends.
- I see.
Yes, sir.
Because I've always stayed home,
I don't go out much.
That's the lock-shaped necklace.
Can my key unlock it?
What are you staring at? Hey.
Yes?
Never mind.
Do you like building things?
Come to my room when you're free.
I have something to show you.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
Okay, I won't bother you any longer.
You should get some rest.
Yes, sir.
Hello, Mamuang. What's up!?
Did Butler Sorn not tell you
that before you enter my room,
you must knock the door three times?
Please leave.
Yes, sir.
He didn't tell me.
Did Butler Sorn not tell you
that before you enter my room,
you must knock the door three times?
So I'll know that you're entering.
You must wait
for my permission to enter.
Yes, sir.
Wait.
Please understand
that while you are here,
you must strictly follow
the house rules.
Yes, Mr. Thod.
Here, sir.
I think the tea is cold now.
I'll replace it.
Never mind. You should go do your work.
Yes, sir.
Not good.
Who's that?
So cute.
Mr. Butler.
Yes?
Come here.
Yes, sir.
Get me some water.
Wait.
I want cold water and no glass.
I like to drink
from the bottle.
Yes, sir.
(Next Break)
Wait a minute.
Here.
Why?
It's your job, right?
Mister.
Your water, sir.
That was fast.
Let me take my gloves off.
So I can drink easily.
Why are you still standing?
Put it on the table.
Yes, sir.
Take this.
Yes.
Come on. Give it to me.
Mister?
Thad.
Thad like a bomb?
My name is Thad.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Thad.
Give it to me. I'm thirsty.
He's handsome
even when he's drinking water.
Very handsome.
He's easy on the eyes.
What's wrong?
Nothing, sir. I'm sorry.
Please excuse me, sir.
Who's calling me?
Is that a phone? He can't use it.
Hello?
Yo! What's up?
Wait a minute. I'm working.
What? Working?
I'll call you back.
Okay.
I'm hanging up.
I have to teach him a lesson.
This is very close.
There's one more rule.
Do not use your phone
in this house.
Huh?
- What are you wondering about?
- Oh.
I am sorry.
He's looking at me.
Does he have a problem?
Does he want to fight
or fall in love?
Let me tell you. I'm brutal.
How awesome.
Here
and there. Yes.
Over here. Yes.
Put it right here too.
Okay, well done.
Good work.
All right. Good.
Good job.
This looks good.
Yes.
You learn the job very quickly.
Ring, ring.
Oh, we must ring a bell in this house.
Put it down and wait for them.
This is a really cool door, see?
Hello, sir.
Please.
Take a seat.
Let's drink tea.
The tea is very fragrant.
Butler Sorn.
Yes, sir?
When are you going?
Is he chasing me away?
Well, the day after tomorrow.
Okay, the day after tomorrow.
Butler Sin.
Butler Sin!
Yes, sir?
Take care of the house
as Butler Sorn has been doing.
Yes, Mr. Thod.
If you don't know how,
I can teach you.
Ahem.
Do you want a lozenge?
He's always saying that.
Ouch, the tea is too hot.
Oh, no.
Who's calling again?
- You're not going to stop?
- It's not me.
I told you not to use your phone, right?
Sorry, Thod.
It's mine.
I've told you many times
that bringing in a phone
is strictly prohibited.
Damn it.
Calm down, Thod.
See?
I'm sorry.
You caused this problem.
Well...
Don't talk to me.
I'm mad.
Well...
Will I get in trouble?
I shouldn't have brought the phone in.
I will find Thot.
I don't feel like eating with a frown.
Troublemaker.
I'm sorry, Mr. Thad.
You don't know me well.
Go there.
Oh, he's getting rid of me.
I'm going, troublemaker.
What are they doing?
He should get back to work.
Talking verbally? I'm confused.
Didn't I tell you to put it away?
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
I'll put it away now.
I won't let you.
I am sulking.
He won't let me?
I want to put it away,
but he won't let me.
I'll give it to you.
Is he gone? Yes.
So cute.
He smells good too.
Damn it, Mamuang.
Now you won't call me, huh?
Hello.
How are you doing there?
I want to visit you.
No.
The rules here are very strict.
If Mister finds out, he will kill me.
Why?
Why don't you answer
my calls these days?
It's against the rules here.
- We cannot use mobile phones.
- Huh?
Okay then.
Let's talk later.
Okay.
I have to get back to work.
I forgot.
Did anyone see that?
Probably not.
Wow, the room is so clean.
It's so clean, what am I supposed to do?
Let's walk around.
There might be something to do.
This is the Mister's necklace.
- Hey.
- Yes?
Please understand
that while you are here,
you must strictly follow
the house rules.
Yes, Mr. Thod.
What are you doing?
Oh.
I'm cleaning the room.
Also...
I've come to get your used clothes.
- Yes?
- It's suspicious.
- That's it, sir.
- He snuck into my room.
- Hey.
- Hold on.
Hey.
Yes?
If you're going to do laundry,
take this as well.
Oh, wow.
His muscles are tight.
Mr. Thad.
I'll leave it to you.
- Please excuse me.
- Hey.
Hold on.
That's not it.
Take this too.
He not only took off his top.
But he also took off his pants.
See?
Here.
Why?
Isn't it your duty?
Yes, sir.
Please excuse me.
Can I go now?
I'll get going.
How awesome.
I'm so fit and firm.
I was almost blinded.
This smells like fabric softener.
Ouch.
I'm sorry, Mr. Thep.
Are you okay, sir?
I'm fine.
I'm okay, I guess.
What are you doing
at the butler's dormitory?
Well... I have a favor to ask.
A favor to ask me?
May I borrow your phone?
Huh?
- Huh?
- You heard correctly.
But your family is wealthy.
My phone is pretty old.
I'm rich, but I don't have a phone.
Having a phone
is against the rules here.
That's why I want to borrow yours.
He's so rich, but doesn't have a phone.
Please.
Please let me borrow yours.
Please. I'm begging you.
- Please.
- Fine.
Yes!
Thank you so much.
It's time for Mr. Thod's coffee.
Please excuse me.
Sure, don't let Thod wait.
Yes, sir.
Okay, all right.
Now...
- This is very important, Butler Sorn.
- Yes, sir.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Your coffee, sir.
Put it on the side.
Okay, I'll move it to the left.
Oh, dear.
The handle.
- The handle.
- Okay, I'll move it.
Move a bit to the right.
Make it straight.
Okay, that's enough.
- Is this okay?
- Leave.
Okay.
I'll leave it to you tomorrow.
Of course, sir.
Okay, good.
We must keep him here.
Yes, sir.
(Next break)
What is this ringing sound?
Which room?
Damn it.
Why do the three masters
all have the lock necklaces?
What should I do?
How can I unlock one of them?
Wait.
Or... should I steal it?
Yes.
I must steal it.
I should go to bed.
I must get up early tomorrow.
Keep fighting.
Let's start the plan.
Damn it. What's this ringing sound?
Where is this sound coming from?
Where is it coming from?
It's so late. I was about to go to bed.
From which room?
Mr. Thod?
Mr. Thad?
Or Mr. Thep?
Damn it.
Yes! A future invention is almost done.
Yes!
I will get a Nobel prize for this.
Hey. Why are you still up?
Didn't you call for me, Mr. Thep?
No. Look at this.
- No, it wasn't me.
- Wrong room.
I don't know why I would call you.
Then... I'm sorry.
Huh? Okay.
Let's put it back.
It's coming from this room.
Let's have a look.
It stopped ringing.
Huh?
Maybe it wasn't from here.
Hey.
He's in my room again.
Don't think it will be easy to leave.
I... I'm sorry, sir.
He's so close to me again.
How dare you enter my room at night.
Well...
I thought you were calling for me.
Really?
Yes, sir.
Then...
Oh, dear. I'm slipping.
All right.
- Mr. Butler.
- Yes, sir?
Go to sleep. It's late.
Yes, sir.
Oh, the ringing is coming from
Thod's room.
I see.
The ringing is from Mr. Thod's room.
It has a lower and deeper tone.
Thod's ringing.
I see.
- I can recognize it now.
- Okay.
- Hold on.
- He won't let me go easily.
I'll teach you.
Why?
How can you not remember
our different ringing tone?
- Didn't Butler Sorn teach you?
- Oh, dear.
- Are you not going to answer?
- What should I say?
I can't remember it.
What am I supposed to do?
- Do you remember?
- He's getting too close.
You should go now.
- So Thod won't be mad at you.
- I almost had a heart attack.
Yes, sir.
He was here and here.
- Was that okay?
- Do it again.
He's still not here.
We've been calling him for awhile now.
Wait.
There's another rule.
If I hear the bell at night,
I must enter immediately.
You were very late.
I've told you before that if you hear
the bell from Mr. Thod's room,
you must come in one minute.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Look at how you're dressed.
I'll tell you about one more rule.
You must wear your uniform until
the lights in Mr. Thod's room are off.
Yes.
Mr. Thod.
Before I leave tomorrow,
I'll train him more.
Up to you. I trust you, Butler Sorn.
You both should get some rest.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Hey.
Please be patient.
I'll get my naughty brother back
as soon as possible.
Okay.
Okay. Don't forget
what I told you earlier.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
- I'll get going.
If that's the case, I won't have time
to steal the necklace.
What should I do?
Maybe...
I might need some help.
What am I going to do?
Mamuang.
There are so many rules here.
Mr. Butler.
Yes, Mr. Thad?
Are you tired?
Well... a little bit.
You will need some time to adjust.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Hey.
Keep fighting,
my butler.
That made me feel so much better.
Thank you,
Mr. Thad.
(Next episode)
How was your first day at work?
He told me to take off my clothes
on the first day.
Did he really ask you to do that?
What? Why does he hate women that much?
How can we help you?
The new gardener here, sir.
- Hold on, Mr. Thep.
- Butler Love.
What are you doing here?
You also brought someone else here.
Please listen to me. I can explain.
Get out!