♪Through dust and storms,
I press on alone♪
♪Winds arise,
sands stretch far and wide♪
♪Trials of the world test my resolve♪
♪Forged in fire,
I chase the light beyond♪
♪Facing challenges, fate ever shifts♪
♪A journey
through the wilderness of time♪
♪Fearless like armor,
through thorns I grow♪
♪Breaking through darkness,
my name will shine♪
♪Never in vain♪
♪Guarding my fleeting light,
tempered to shine bright♪
♪Cherished past♪
♪A lifetime treasured,
through a thousand waves we ride♪
♪To fight with fury,
to love with passion♪
♪True to my faith♪
♪I greet the frost
and the prize with pride♪
=Love and Sword=
(Adapted from Shen Cangmei's novel
Sleeping Beside Yan Shao)
=Episode 23=
(Hanyu Pavilion)
Come here!
- I'm still grinding it.
- Get over here.
Why are you holding that?
Stand still.
What now?
Hold still.
And then,
crouch.
Raise your hands.
Raise your chest and lift your chin.
What are you up to this time?
I can't take my wedding photos now.
Can't I at least get a portrait?
A portrait of me?
That pose just now wasn't nice.
What if...
Your hand...
I told you to crouch.
Fine.
Raise your hand.
Hand at your waist.
Hold still.
Good.
Crouch.
Fine.
Are you doing what Jin Buyao does?
After I die,
will you carry the portrait with you?
Nonsense.
Don't jinx yourself.
Having a place in each other's hearts
and no secrets
is the true meaning of happiness.
I just want
to record every second
and every wonderful moment
we've had.
Alright, stop dillydallying.
Go on.
Alright.
Stand here.
- Fine.
- Stand still.
This should do it.
The usual pose.
You look cool this way.
Do not move.
I'll start drawing now.
Stay still.
(Shuxin Pavilion)
Brother Shaoci,
Sister Rong is not back yet.
I'll ask Chu Tianyao.
I'll go too.
Young Master Lin and Miss Tang.
Yesterday
was the wedding
of our Leader and Madam.
As of now,
the ceremony has been completed.
Young Master Lin and Miss Tang,
you need not worry.
A wedding with no guests?
Not bad, Sister Rong!
A secret wedding?
This is rushed and inadequate.
You misunderstood.
The ceremony was done
according to Miss Rong's requirements.
What's wrong with Shukuang?
Sister Rong and Leader Chu are married.
They didn't tell us
or invite any guests.
Just the two of them.
Impossible.
This is unorthodox.
According to Miss Rong,
the wedding was a matter
between her and Leader Chu.
The others shouldn't be concerned.
Besides,
Leader Chu has a message for all of you.
When the Six Great Sects gather
at the Moye Manor,
he will hold another
grander and more formal wedding.
Therefore,
there is nothing to worry about,
Young Lady Lin.
I've delivered the message.
I take my leave now.
Brother Shaoci, are you alright?
Yes.
I wish I could give them my best wishes
in person.
But...
(Why would she marry Chu Tianyao?)
(Is it a plot to get the key?)
Stay still!
How long is this going to take?
You're a great hero.
It's going to take some time.
Just hang in there.
Wait! Stop right there!
- I'm not done yet!
- Let me see it.
Don't come any closer.
- Come on, show it to me.
- I'm not done yet!
Let me see it.
No!
You can see it later!
Stop running.
Settle down.
I'll show it to you in a moment!
Let me see it now!
Darling!
Show it to me.
It took you an entire day
just to draw this?
It looks remarkable.
It's special.
You don't like my drawing.
It's fine.
If anyone ever asks you
what your husband looks like,
show them this drawing.
I bet they will say,
"This guy?
"This guy married the daughter
of the Yuchi Manor?"
"He must be very capable."
Then, I'll say,
"What would you know?"
"My husband is a young hero in red
with an honorable poise."
"He's saved me from perils
and shown me so much joy."
A dream in the martial arts world.
You drew this?
This is when we first met
in the desert.
I kept asking you to strike
different poses.
Are you mad at me?
Actually, I've finished
all of these images
in my mind.
Father, this way.
Shukuang.
Are you...
I brought you here
to explain something to you.
Is there a problem
with the Mount Moye?
This is Leader Chu's room.
We've already married.
When did you get married?
Why wasn't I told?
Just yesterday.
Tianyao and I are meant for each other.
We feel connected.
I didn't want to wait any longer.
We secretly got married yesterday.
There is another matter
I must tell you.
Yan Shao?
Leader Chu, you're Yan Shao all along?
Over the years,
no one knew Chu Tianyao
because I roamed the martial arts world
as Yan Shao.
I'm surprised.
You...
You did this for Shukuang.
Indeed.
Su Shiyu is my master.
Shukuang and I grew up together
in Misty Moon Village.
After my master passed away,
I promised her
I'd keep Shukuang safe
as long as I live and breathe.
My martial brother's adopted son
was Shiyu's disciple all along.
When Ghost Valley Sect
slaughtered the village,
Master gave me and Shukuang
the keys to the treasure.
The keys are now combined.
Shukuang agreed with me.
We will destroy the key
with everyone witnessing it.
I never asked for any conflicts
or disputes.
I agreed with my husband.
This is the only way
to completely
cut off the people's source of greed.
It should make the evildoers give up
on finding it.
Very well.
Did you learn anything?
Mount Moye is crawling with guards.
It's best to tread carefully.
The alliance formation gathering
is in two days.
We can't afford more mistakes.
Dismissed.
Why did you tie my servant up?
Did he do anything
to upset you?
He is no servant.
He is the Wailing Phantom
of the Ruthless Parlor.
He lost his home
after what happened to Ruthless Parlor.
He asked me to take him in.
So, I made him my sidekick.
I had no idea
who he was before this.
I had Father's permission.
What did you mean
there could be no more
mistakes at the alliance formation
gathering?
I asked him to learn more
about the gathering
because if I fall sick again
and can't attend it,
I still need to know
what happens at the gathering.
And why do you ask?
Shaoci.
I am still a member of the Yuchi Manor.
You and Shukuang always got to attend
important events like this.
But I could only wait in my room.
When I wake up in the morning,
I stare at the pagoda tree
outside my window.
You can leave the manor
and even the city.
You're free to roam the world.
You are free to witness
the wonders of the world.
You meet all kinds of people.
But all I have is a tree.
Wanci.
It can't be helped
that your body is frail.
The same excuse again.
I grow up hearing the same excuse.
I'm tired of it.
I told myself
to never get disheartened.
I can contribute to the manor too.
Wanci.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Shaoci.
You still have no idea
what I yearn for.
You are homesick.
I'll inform Father tomorrow
to send you home as soon as possible.
I'm not going back.
I want to stay with you and Father.
I'm safer with you.
How would you like me
to handle this person?
He is just a man without a home.
If you don't trust him,
you can send him away.
Sir, thanks for taking care of me.
I'm feeling better now.
I should be able
to attend the gathering.
They want to destroy the keys.
Do you serve Wanci
because you're plotting something?
I'm a homeless person.
Young Lady Lin took me in.
Why would I harm my benefactor?
I am the Wailing Phantom.
But I am not an ingrate.
Shaoci, don't worry.
With my health,
what could I possibly do?
The gathering
of the Six Great Sects is coming soon.
I don't want Father to be
bothered by trivial matters.
Once the gathering is over,
I'll return to the Yuchi Manor.
Head Yu.
The people from
the Yuchi Manor are here?
Yes.
This way, please.
Greetings, Madam Xing and Head Tang.
Welcome to Tiangang.
Please proceed.
My concern is
that Madam Xing is cunning.
Can you really convince her?
There must be a way.
Well, as the First Young Lady
of Tang Clan,
you certainly have your own plans.
It's not what you think.
You're not using poison?
The one thing
more powerful than poison
is taking advantage of others' fears.
You're one step ahead.
I came
because I need some Heart Devourer.
Make sure everything is foolproof.
This poison is unusual.
Prolonged consumption
might actually endanger
your uncle's life.
When you become the alliance leader,
and when we have the treasure,
can we forsake him?
Eldest Brother,
who will you nominate
as the alliance leader tomorrow?
Master Lin has always
favored the Spirit Fox Sect.
But he is advanced in his years.
The Tang Clan could be
a potential candidate.
Eldest Brother,
this concerns a lot of people.
We should...
Go and get some rest.
Why did you
come to see me in person?
Where is Wailing Phantom?
He's been caught by Shaoci.
He can't just leave now.
The gathering is tomorrow.
What is the plan, Leader Shen?
When the Six Great Sects gather,
I will infiltrate Tiangang
and launch a pincer attack.
We can take them all out.
You must not.
The sects' elite warriors
will attend the gathering.
Besides, Chu Tianyao will be there.
Brute force isn't going to work.
Chu Tianyao resides on Mount Moye
because of Yan Shao.
But Crimson Lotus Heart
had caused Yan Shao great damage.
A dead man walking is no threat.
What? Do you feel sorry for him?
You seem rather devoted to Yan Shao.
What a shame.
You still lost him
after you risked your life for him.
There's more to the Six Great Sects
than meets the eye.
Leader Shen, we must change our plan.
Rong Shukuang and Chu Tianyao
are going to destroy the keys.
(Shuxin Pavilion)
Shukuang.
Your wedding gown looks gorgeous.
After just one glance,
I couldn't help but try it on.
Can I help you with anything?
Unfortunately for me,
I might not live
to see my own wedding.
Rong Shukuang.
In what aspect are you better than me?
I am the Young Lady Lin
of the Yuchi Manor.
But why do people like you instead?
Ever since you came to the Yuchi Manor,
my father, brother,
and everyone only care about
the girl named Rong Shukuang.
They don't care about me.
It's you.
You took everything
that was rightfully mine.
Do you remember that fortune teller
at Blossom's Smile?
Remember what he said?
I'm destined to live without
a home or family.
I was to cast my past aside
and marry a man from far away.
Is that the life you long for?
You only see your own suffering.
You always overlook
how much I've lost.
Loss?
Who are you to talk about losses?
When you were the hero
in everyone's eyes,
I could only be in the company
of plants in my room.
Everyone I've ever cared about
only cares about you.
Even Yan Shao
ingratiated himself with me
just to deceive me.
He tricked me into telling the truth.
He never cared about me.
Even if I were gone,
you'd never have his love.
Why?
Your family name was Fang!
Why do you get to use
my mother's family name?
I could risk my life for Yan Shao,
but he wouldn't bat me an eye.
He loves you so much
that he would transfer
Crimson Lotus Heart
to his own body.
Tell me.
Should I kill you
for a chance to have his love?
Killing me won't cure him
of the poison.
Why you...
Spare me the false kindness!
Why did you come here?
I'm here to offer a deal.
I can help you unlock
the Fuxian treasure.
I've made up my mind.
I won't open it.
What if Yan Shao needs you to unlock it?
He won't.
You claim to love him,
but you don't seem to
understand him at all.
He won't risk unlocking the treasure
for another age of conflict.
He will never
let someone like you have the treasure.
Yan Shao won't do it,
but you will.
You will unlock the treasure
for Yan Shao's sake.
I am the wife of Tiangang's Leader.
Yan Shao means nothing to me now.
Please leave.
Chief Jiang
of the Seven-Star Hall arrives.
What is this about?
Uncle!
He fell terribly sick all of a sudden.
Young Master Ruhai is the only
candidate from the Seven-Star Hall.
I only followed
my uncle's instructions.
I infiltrated the Ghost Valley Sect
to earn their trust.
But I've been serving
the Six Great Sects all along.
How touching.
You're quite a filial son.
Uncle!
The Leader of Tiangang is here.
Everyone,
this is Chu Tianyao,
the Leader of Tiangang.
All Six Great Sects gather
on Mount Moye.
I am honored by your presence.
I apologize for the lack
of a proper welcome.
So, the rumors are true after all.
You are a mysterious figure.
Just some baseless rumors.
I hope you don't mind.
Leader Chu and I invited all of you
to use the wedding as an opportunity
to quell the evils lurking on our land
and uphold justice.
The Six Great Sects are here.
The Six Great Sects?
Master Lin, you can't be serious.
The Six Great Sects are gone.
I'm still here.
What?
The Junshan Sect is here.
Him...?
As long as I live,
the Junshan Sect lives.
As long as I breathe,
the Junshan Sect stands.
I am my own sect.
I thought the sect was wiped out.
This is the traitor who is wanted
by the Junshan Sect
for killing their chief,
Shangguan Tong.
Shangguan Tong didn't kill their chief.
Indeed.
The Ghost Valley Sect killed my master.
The Ghost Valley Sect bribed our people
to poison my master
and kill him.
Why do you wait until now
to tell us the truth?
He didn't tell anyone
because he thought his master
became deranged from an accident
during cultivation.
He hid the truth to preserve
his master's reputation.
He sought Tiangang's help to uncover
the truth of his master's death.
And he learned the truth.
The Ghost Valley Sect
bribed our disciples
to put poison in my master's tea,
causing him to hallucinate
and become deranged.
I even brought
the letters they exchanged.
These secret letters
were found by the disciples of Tiangang
after the Junshan Sect was wiped out.
Tiangang can guarantee
that these letters
are all authentic.
Shangguan Tong,
if your master could see
how much you've done,
he'd gladly entrust the sect to you
so you could rebuild it.
My sect was slaughtered
by the Ghost Valley Sect.
Unless you learn from this tragedy,
and see who the enemy is,
you will be massacred
just like the Junshan Sect.
The Ghost Valley Sect incites chaos.
Only by forming an alliance
and fighting as one
to quell the Ghost Valley Sect
can we ensure peace.
We need an alliance leader
to lead us.
The Yuchi Manor has always
led the Six Great Sects.
In terms of experience and reputation,
Master Lin is the best candidate.
I beg to differ.
Head Tang is meticulous
and excels in martial arts.
She is a better leader.
Is that your sister's goal?
My sister wouldn't be so reckless.
Given the circumstances,
I can't be too sure.
We'll wait and see.
Jiang Ruhai.
Do you think we will
take your word for it
because you claim to be a spy?
I explain the matter about
the Yu family to your eldest brother.
It's not your place to speak here.
Why you...
Linglong.
There must be a misunderstanding.
I was poisoned by the Ghost Valley Sect.
I must take an antidote regularly.
Mr. Jiang stole it from
the Ghost Valley Sect
and sent it to me.
Otherwise, I'd be dead already.
I never told you
because I knew you'd be worried.
You never mentioned that to me.
I agree
to let the Tang Clan lead the alliance.
If you think so,
you must have considered
all the pros and cons.
Indeed.
Very well.
As of now,
the Junshan Sect nominates Master Lin,
while the Seven-Star Hall
and the Pure Sword Sect
nominate Head Tang.
And the Spirit Fox Sect?
What is your decision?
The Spirit Fox Sect...
We are willing to follow
Head Tang's leadership.
Very well.
You've all made your decision.
Congratulations, Head Tang.
You are the alliance leader
of the Six Great Sects.
Congratulations, Head Tang.
You shall lead us on a conquest
to eliminate the Ghost Valley Sect.
As you know,
I, Tang Chanyi,
have always steered clear
of conflicts and disputes.
However,
upholding the peace
of our martial arts world
is the duty of all my predecessors.
Since I am elected
as the alliance leader,
I won't fail you.
Let's make use of this opportunity.
With you as our alliance leader,
we can discuss
how to unlock the Fuxian treasure.
Alliance Leader Tang,
the alliance has formed.
What will you do with the treasure?
Any propositions?
Ambition and greed
will only bring endless
bloodshed and sorrow.
Master Lin, Shukuang, and I
discussed the matter.
We plan to destroy the keys
with everyone here as our witnesses
to avoid more bloodshed.
You can't be serious!
You can't destroy the keys!
Could we speak with Young Lady Lin?
Wanci is unwell.
If we send for her now...
Very well.
Bring Young Lady Lin here.
Yes.
The treasure key was
the cause of discord
among the Six Great Sects.
I've decided.
We'll do as Leader Chu proposed.
We'll destroy the keys
to avoid more bloodshed.
Chanyi, you can't...
As you all know,
I've always hated defeat.
I took an oath
to become the Head of the Tang Clan.
I swore to never get married
or have children.
And today, you've made me
your alliance leader.
I'm truly honored.
Ruhai.
Someone once told me
as long as
you have your legs,
you'd never rest.
What?
- What happened?
- He just collapsed!
Everyone,
Jiang Ruhai's legs have been crippled.
This is justice for the Six Great Sects.
Eldest Brother.
The antidote!
Take this.
Chief Jiang became sick
because of Jiang Ruhai.
The medicine I gave him
only caused temporary damage.
Take it regularly.
He will get well.
Chanyi!
How could you lie to me?
You are prudent,
and you work in the dark
for the sake of the Six Great Sects.
On behalf of Tiangang,
I thank you.
Each sect has its own goals.
We loathe each other
while worrying about
getting overshadowed
by the other sects.
But when a common enemy rises,
we band together as an iron wall.
I have never
considered the other sects my equals.
But I do understand that our fates
are tied together.
Jiang Ruhai thinks his lies
could instigate the Tang Clan
to fight the other sects.
He overestimates himself.
After years of fighting,
I've grown sick and tired.
Leader Chu, you know me well.
I will agree to assist you,
but on one condition.
All right.
I agree with your condition.
You have my thanks, Leader Chu.
♪Spinning through my heart,
my dreams, the endless Jianghu♪
♪A fateful turn,
where love and hearts collide♪
♪Ah, such a blissful tide♪
♪A journey long,
yet life is but one ride♪
♪Blades in chaos,
the world in turmoil, tangled ties♪
♪A fleeting warmth
to shield me from the ice♪
♪Ah, as spring awakens love's delight♪
♪One single glance,
my heart takes flight♪
♪I've heard tales of love and vengeance,
left forgotten in the tide♪
♪And whispers of desert stars and rain,
where love at first sight fades to cries♪
♪But I don't know, I don't know,
how long this moment will abide♪
♪Yet here and now,
for this one soul, I stand beside♪
♪I understand, love and longing,
how much truth, how many lies♪
♪Yet my swift blade cannot sever,
cannot sever these endless ties♪
♪I have known, the lonely journeys,
wandering years without goodbyes♪
♪Yet this moment stirs the ache inside♪
♪One turn through this dream of Jianghu,
one heartbeat lost in time♪
♪No dream compares
to a fateful meeting so divine♪
♪Love needs no hero,
only a foolish mind♪
♪Trapped in Jianghu's ruthless tides,
once, let me defy♪
♪A single touch, a fleeting smile,
is enough to shake the sky♪
♪Stirring the stillness,
where the winds rise high♪
♪Though fate may part our paths,
we walk the same road♪
♪A crescent moon,
a crimson glow, a love untold♪
♪Like passing winds, like aching souls,
never to meet once more♪
♪Then what is fate even for♪
♪Just once, to fall into your arms,
not lost, nor torn, nor bound to strife♪
♪Amidst the storm of masters' might,
hidden deep, a love so bright♪
♪Standing apart from all the fight,
only one embrace so right♪
♪A dream of Jianghu's light♪
♪One turn through this dream of Jianghu,
one heartbeat lost in time♪
♪No dream compares
to a fateful meeting so divine♪
♪Love needs no hero,
only a foolish mind♪
♪Trapped in Jianghu's ruthless tides,
once, let me defy♪
♪A single touch, a fleeting smile,
is enough to shake the sky♪
♪Stirring the stillness,
where the winds rise high♪