♪Through dust and storms,
I press on alone♪
♪Winds arise,
sands stretch far and wide♪
♪Trials of the world test my resolve♪
♪Forged in fire,
I chase the light beyond♪
♪Facing challenges, fate ever shifts♪
♪A journey
through the wilderness of time♪
♪Fearless like armor,
through thorns I grow♪
♪Breaking through darkness,
my name will shine♪
♪Never in vain♪
♪Guarding my fleeting light,
tempered to shine bright♪
♪Cherished past♪
♪A lifetime treasured,
through a thousand waves we ride♪
♪To fight with fury,
to love with passion♪
♪True to my faith♪
♪I greet the frost
and the prize with pride♪
=Love and Sword=
(Adapted from Shen Cangmei's novel
Sleeping Beside Yan Shao)
=Episode 10=
(Since you both have your own plans,)
(I can't just sit around
and do nothing.)
(If I want answers,)
(I need to make enough money)
(to buy back the album.)
Sister Rong,
what are you up to now?
I'm making a weapon
that'll help me make money.
How's that going to earn you money?
A crossbow.
One that can ignite
and explode on impact.
That sounds
even deadlier
than our Tang Clan's hidden weapons.
They're not even on the same level.
This is the difference
between projectile weapons and firearms.
Then what do you call this weapon?
I'll call it Inferno Crossbow.
It's fine.
Scientific experiments
always have setbacks.
We'll get it right.
Let's go again.
Come on, please work.
We'll try again.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let me tell you a strange tale
from the martial world.
The master of Xingfeng Cave
has suddenly died,
leaving behind a legendary weapon
known as the Inferno Crossbow!
What is an Inferno Crossbow?
Never heard of it.
This weapon has driven
his two top disciples to turn
against each other,
fighting to the death.
They've agreed to a final duel
on the lake tomorrow!
Mister, may I ask
who these two are?
Ah, you want to know?
One is swift as a bat in the night,
known as the Lone Swallow.
The other one
fights like a beast,
wielding a great blade,
the Merciless Blade.
It's a battle between Merciless Blade
and Lone Swallow.
That's a true clash of masters.
We have to watch this.
We must not miss it tomorrow.
Hurry! Let us through!
Hurry! They're going to start!
Don't push.
The fight hasn't started.
Excuse me, excuse me!
Excuse me,
that man in black on Huxin Pavilion,
is he the hero, Lone Swallow?
That's him.
They say his sword strikes
as fast as a ghost's shadow.
He's one of the finest swordsmen
in the martial world.
Wow, that's amazing.
But where's the other one?
There he is. Over there!
There he is!
Look! It's the Merciless Blade!
Merciless Blade. That's Merciless Blade.
Martial Brother,
this duel between us...
It's not what I wanted.
Are you really going to kill me
over the Inferno Crossbow?
In the martial world,
grudges are endless.
I'm tired of this life
that I wish only for death.
But my skills are so great,
even dying is difficult for me.
So in the end,
you refuse to hand over
our master's weapon?
I've lived for decades.
Today,
I finally get to witness the peak battle
of Xingfeng Cave's
two greatest disciples.
I can die with no regrets!
But it would be a shame
if both of them perish from this duel.
Then this legendary weapon
will disappear forever.
What does the weapon even look like?
A legendary weapon?
It must be priceless.
In that case...
They're starting.
Make your move!
In that case,
we shall start this duel!
They're making their move!
Look!
That's impressive!
That power is insane!
Martial Junior,
this weapon has turned us
against each other.
It's nothing but a curse.
I'll destroy it right now!
I only hope this can bring peace
to the martial world.
Wait, hero!
If you're going to destroy it,
why not just gift it to me instead?
That's right!
What? No way!
Such a treasure
can't be given away for free!
I'll give you five taels for it!
Five taels is too little.
I am willing
to pay 10 taels.
I'll pay 20 taels.
Thirty taels!
Forty taels!
Fifty!
- Sixty taels!
- Eighty taels!
One and fifty taels!
Three hundred taels!
Five hundred taels!
Six hundred taels!
Seven hundred taels!
Eight hundred taels!
Nine hundred taels!
I'll pay 1,000 taels!
Following Young Lady Rong is amazing!
Young Lady Rong.
It didn't take long
to sell all 100 Inferno Crossbows.
I must be a marketing genius.
That's right.
Young Lady Rong is truly brilliant.
It's time to split the money!
Come on.
Everyone.
Here's your money.
This is yours.
Let me say this in advance.
You must keep quiet about this.
When we get back to the manor,
don't say a word about this.
Understood?
Yes, we won't say a word!
(Heshun Restaurant)
You'll get paid what you asked for.
Money on delivery, goods in return.
Rong Shukuang has always been
proud and aloof,
never involving herself with money
or wealth at the manor.
Where did you get this money?
A woman can't earn a single cent
without relying on a man?
That's the biggest joke of this era.
But even if I explain it to you,
you won't understand.
Come on, give it back.
If you've decided
to sell the paintings,
that means you've completely moved on
from Young Master Lin.
So why spend so much to buy them back?
Are you still holding onto him?
Rong Shukuang,
what exactly are you up to?
Yu,
that will cost you a fee.
Everyone says Rong Shukuang
is a meticulous person.
She marked the same symbol
in multiple places.
There must be a deeper meaning.
Could she have been
secretly recording clues?
They've really cut ties.
After this,
we'll have one less obstacle in our way.
But Young Master's men
are still guarding the Hidden Pavilion.
I can't make a move yet.
The more they tighten security,
the more likely something is inside.
No matter what, you have to go.
As for the guards,
I'll give you their shift change times.
So getting in will be easy.
Young Lady Lin,
you're always so thorough.
(Rivaling Tycoons in History)
Finally, you're here.
You really enjoy sneaky business,
don't you?
If you surrender now,
you might still have a way out.
You...
If we didn't stage all this,
do you think we can lure you in?
There's a traitor in the manor.
And that person is someone close to me.
Yuchi Manor has indeed been
unsettled lately.
But the only outsider is Yan Shao.
It can't be him.
These illustrations were drawn
before Shen Zuitian captured me.
The markings
were added later on purpose.
I believe that even back then,
I suspected
there was a Ghost Valley Sect spy
inside the manor.
So I secretly investigated
while leaving these marks.
Each marked location
is where I suspected
the spy had appeared.
At that time...
Yan Shao hadn't even arrived
at the manor yet.
You're smart, Young Master Lin.
My father told me
Yan Shao is trustworthy.
Since Master Lin believes in me,
I'm willing to play along
with your setup
to dig out the real traitor hiding
in the shadows.
At the same time, I'll help you see
the true nature of those
in Yuchi Manor.
Then I'll be counting on you, Yan Shao.
(Thank you for visiting)
Well?
How's my writing?
Surprised?
Take him down!
Liu An?
Liu An, huh?
I've suspected you for a long time.
Who ordered you
to betray Yuchi Manor?
Just kill me already.
No need for all this nonsense.
Well, at least you've got some backbone.
You want to die?
I won't give you that chance.
Take her away
and interrogate her properly.
What happened here?
What did she do?
Don't hurt her!
Young Lady Lin treats you well.
You bear to hurt her?
Don't come any closer!
Don't hurt her.
Young Lady Lin, don't worry.
We will save you.
Let her go!
Wanci!
After her!
Are you hurt?
Are you all right?
I'm all right.
Get some rest early.
What?
Are you still thinking about it?
About what?
Young Lady Lin in your arms,
soft and warm.
You must have enjoyed that, right?
No, I wasn't.
Of course, you did!
You were obviously overjoyed.
So stop pretending to be all serious.
Keep your voice down.
I'm not lying to you about this.
But what if one day I do lie to you?
And what if I lie to you first?
Forget it.
Everyone has their own secrets.
What a shame.
Liu An got away this time.
The person behind her
is probably back in hiding.
Ghost Valley Sect
won't give up that easily.
So they'll be back.
We might as well take our time
and play along.
So no rush.
Uh... Your face...
This side.
Not there.
(Oh, no.)
(Why is my heart racing again?)
(Rong Shukuang, pull yourself together.)
(Stop being so obsessed.)
You used red flower juice
to fake bloodstains
and trick Liu An.
Who taught you that?
Do I need to be taught?
That's how it's done in storybooks.
As for this contract,
I only made it up to mess with you.
It doesn't mean anything.
So why bother returning it to me?
Keep it.
So, what are we now?
Young Lady and a guard,
or Master and disciple?
Up to you.
Gu Long once said
that life has two purposes.
One is to burn,
and the other is to watch others burn.
Which do you choose?
I'll burn
so you don't have to.
Shaoci?
Have you not slept
or did you wake up early?
We wake up at the Yin hour
to train since childhood.
It has been a habit for years
and never changed.
That early?
No wonder martial artists
have such strong willpower
and endure what ordinary people cannot.
But every time I wake up,
I see you practicing sword techniques
in the courtyard.
I've always wanted to ask.
What time do you actually wake up?
Nowadays, I often sleep
until the sun is high in the sky.
I guess you'll never
have the chance to know the answer.
When we were kids,
I always hoped you'd be a little lazier.
Then I wouldn't have
to push myself so hard
to get stronger.
Why?
I'm the Young Master of Yuchi Manor.
If my martial arts weren't
as good as my sister's,
wouldn't that be embarrassing?
Seems like no matter the era,
strong women
always make men feel pressured.
I think back then,
I just wanted to impress you.
But working so hard
backfired.
I must've left a bad impression instead.
If you hadn't been so strong back then,
maybe
I would've seen you as a girl sooner.
I'm going to check
if my master is awake.
Otherwise,
he'll scold me for being lazy again.
Wait. I know you trust Yan Shao.
Capturing the traitor proves
that he is upright
and honorable,
always standing up for justice.
But that doesn't mean
you truly understand him.
I understand.
After losing your family
when you were a child,
you came to Yuchi Manor knowing nothing
except your own name.
Back then, I secretly vowed
to treat you like my own sister.
Because of our years together,
I assure you
that I have no grudge against Yan Shao.
I just don't want his presence
to bring trouble to you.
I understand.
Then, I'll go practice now.
Go.
Cosmic Shift.
Is that what I taught you?
Isn't this the move?
Not enough power.
Again.
Can't you at least give me a hint?
Don't hit me!
I just pointed...
I mean, what is this?
Gathering internal energy
at your fingertips
to release sword energy from a distance.
It's Flowing Cloud Finger,
able to injure foes from a distance.
That powerful?
Sounds like that Six-Meridian Sword.
The whatever Finger move...
Uh...
Why can't I do it now?
Does it only work
in life-or-death situations?
What if you can't pull it off
in a real crisis?
Maybe you should give me some pressure?
Like ambushing me at night or something.
What do you mean?
What were you thinking?
I meant a real sneak attack.
Flowing Cloud Finger...
See? It still didn't work.
Again.
Who exactly are you?
I really hope you're the last person
to ask me that.
Knowing my identity
won't do you any good.
But you want to know
who I really am too.
We're the same in that way.
No.
You and I are nothing alike.
I don't risk my life for others,
especially
not for the man who killed my father.
Misty Moon Village.
Your real name is Liu Yue.
(Misty Moon Village)
My precious treasure!
Ah! You lost!
All right. You can all go and hide now.
I'll come find you later.
Hurry.
One, two, three, four,
five,
six...
Someone's attacking the village! Run!
Nine,
ten,
eleven...
Run.
Run for your lives!
Here.
Let's escape into the forest
behind the village.
No matter what happens,
remember not to look back.
Don't you remember
the ones
who massacred Misty Moon Village
were those from the Ghost Valley Sect?
Father!
That can't be.
That's impossible.
Ghost Valley Sect murdered your family.
Yet you still want to acknowledge
your enemy as your father
and help them wipe out Yuchi Manor?
That can't be. It can't be!
You're lying to me.
I won't believe you.
It was all the Fang Family's fault.
Because of them,
the Misty Moon Village was massacred.
(Young Liu An)
Do you know
everything happened because of her?
I'm taking you back to Yuchi Manor.
From now on,
forget Misty Moon Village.
Your name
is no longer Fang Yi.
Then what should my name be?
From now on,
you are Rong Shukuang.
Rong Shukuang.
Remember that.
Let's go.
The people of Misty Moon Village
had sworn
to protect the Fang Family.
It was their duty.
I don't know what duty or purpose means.
All of them were dead!
But why is the Fang Family's
daughter still alive?
This silver locket belonged
to your sister.
Your father held onto it tightly
even as he died.
You and she are both victims.
Deep down, you know exactly
who killed your family.
Enough talking! Just stop it!
Yue...
You are...
If you weren't blinded by hatred,
wouldn't you already know who I am?
If everyone in Misty Moon Village
was dead,
who else could possibly know
your real name?
Palm or back of the hand,
they're all part of the same body.
You lost!
Two,
three!
You are Yan Wuying,
the one Su Shiyu took in.
You're here for Rong Shukuang,
aren't you?
What poison
did you use on her?
Where did you get it?
Where's the antidote?
There is no cure.
Rong Shukuang will die
from it sooner or later.
Yan Shao.
Even if you give everything you've got,
you still won't be able to save her.
Tell me.
What poison did you use on her?
It's the Crimson Lotus Heart.
The Crimson Lotus Heart
was Su Shiyu's own creation.
And now, it's been used on her daughter.
She was dead.
No one in this world can cure
the Crimson Lotus Heart.
As long as I'm here,
she won't die.
♪Spinning through my heart,
my dreams, the endless Jianghu♪
♪A fateful turn,
where love and hearts collide♪
♪Ah, such a blissful tide♪
♪A journey long,
yet life is but one ride♪
♪Blades in chaos,
the world in turmoil, tangled ties♪
♪A fleeting warmth
to shield me from the ice♪
♪Ah, as spring awakens love's delight♪
♪One single glance,
my heart takes flight♪
♪I've heard tales of love and vengeance,
left forgotten in the tide♪
♪And whispers of desert stars and rain,
where love at first sight fades to cries♪
♪But I don't know, I don't know,
how long this moment will abide♪
♪Yet here and now,
for this one soul, I stand beside♪
♪I understand, love and longing,
how much truth, how many lies♪
♪Yet my swift blade cannot sever,
cannot sever these endless ties♪
♪I have known, the lonely journeys,
wandering years without goodbyes♪
♪Yet this moment stirs the ache inside♪
♪One turn through this dream of Jianghu,
one heartbeat lost in time♪
♪No dream compares
to a fateful meeting so divine♪
♪Love needs no hero,
only a foolish mind♪
♪Trapped in Jianghu's ruthless tides,
once, let me defy♪
♪A single touch, a fleeting smile,
is enough to shake the sky♪
♪Stirring the stillness,
where the winds rise high♪
♪Though fate may part our paths,
we walk the same road♪
♪A crescent moon,
a crimson glow, a love untold♪
♪Like passing winds, like aching souls,
never to meet once more♪
♪Then what is fate even for♪
♪Just once, to fall into your arms,
not lost, nor torn, nor bound to strife♪
♪Amidst the storm of masters' might,
hidden deep, a love so bright♪
♪Standing apart from all the fight,
only one embrace so right♪
♪A dream of Jianghu's light♪
♪One turn through this dream of Jianghu,
one heartbeat lost in time♪
♪No dream compares
to a fateful meeting so divine♪
♪Love needs no hero,
only a foolish mind♪
♪Trapped in Jianghu's ruthless tides,
once, let me defy♪
♪A single touch, a fleeting smile,
is enough to shake the sky♪
♪Stirring the stillness,
where the winds rise high♪