♪Through dust and storms,
I press on alone♪
♪Winds arise,
sands stretch far and wide♪
♪Trials of the world test my resolve♪
♪Forged in fire,
I chase the light beyond♪
♪Facing challenges, fate ever shifts♪
♪A journey
through the wilderness of time♪
♪Fearless like armor,
through thorns I grow♪
♪Breaking through darkness,
my name will shine♪
♪Never in vain♪
♪Guarding my fleeting light,
tempered to shine bright♪
♪Cherished past♪
♪A lifetime treasured,
through a thousand waves we ride♪
♪To fight with fury,
to love with passion♪
♪True to my faith♪
♪I greet the frost
and the prize with pride♪
=Love and Sword=
(Adapted from Shen Cangmei's novel
Sleeping Beside Yan Shao)
=Episode 6=
Isn't it March now?
Why is it so hot?
Yan Shao.
What is it?
What's wrong?
It's so hot.
Hot?
Is the poison acting up again?
Do you feel uncomfortable?
It seems like
you've been poisoned again.
You smell really nice.
Are you back to your senses now?
I am sorry.
Sorry?
About what?
Everything. I was wrong from the start.
I never should have come here.
If you hadn't saved me,
I would've gone back a long time ago.
Here and there?
Where exactly are you talking about?
I don't even know
if this world is a dream
or some time warp.
Anyway, I never should have come here.
If I hadn't,
none of this trouble
would have happened,
and I never would have met you.
Yan Shao,
am I just trouble to you?
Do you want me
to just disappear from your sight?
No.
Liar.
I'm not lying.
I am willing
from the bottom of my heart.
If I never get my memories back,
doesn't that mean
I am going to be useless?
Then
I'll take you away from Yuchi Manor,
and we'll disappear together.
Your heart?
Where is your heart?
I can't even see you through clearly.
How am I supposed to see your heart?
♪The night turns cold♪
♪The starlit river dims♪
♪By the lakeside, shadows flicker♪
♪Silhouettes linger♪
♪A tattered robe♪
♪In this fleeting world,
yearning remains♪
♪Maple leaves rise with the wind,
sorrows stretch for miles♪
♪Yet a soft call lingers♪
♪Drunk under the moonlight
as rain gently falls in the courtyard♪
What are you doing?
Why am I here?
You were poisoned.
Again?
Seriously, who keeps poisoning me?
Am I some kind of test subject?
I... I feel fine now.
Sure?
So can I get out now?
Yan Shao.
I'm here.
I feel safe
when I call your name.
Maybe your name
is my lucky charm.
Don't be scared.
I'm here.
Have you been here this whole time?
Yes, always.
Yan Shao,
come and have some tea.
Yan Shao, you look pale.
Did you not sleep well last night?
I...
There was a stray cat last night.
Shukuang, why don't you join us?
Shukuang, come and join us.
Come on.
It looks like
you didn't get much rest either.
A stray cat kept me up all night.
Since you had a hard time sleeping,
how did you pass the time?
Young Lady Lin, you're so concerned.
Were you woken up by the cat too?
There was no cat.
Two frogs croaking by the water
all night.
All right then.
I'll go catch the cat and the frogs
after lunch.
So that everyone can finally sleep
in peace.
Young Master Lin,
what woke you up?
I'll catch that too.
I didn't hear a thing,
so I slept just fine.
You all continue chatting.
I'm going for a walk.
I can't believe this.
Rong Shukuang,
what on earth did you do last night?
Are you just hormonal deficient
or what?
That was so awkward and so embarrassing.
What are you doing?
I feel ashamed.
You don't need to avoid me.
Last night,
I didn't take advantage of you.
You didn't?
Why not?
Why the hell not?
What's wrong with you?
I...
have manners.
I won't take advantage
of someone else's misfortune.
I'm young and beautiful.
In the middle of the night,
we were under the moonlight
with the perfect romantic atmosphere.
Even the cats were calling out to mate,
and the mood was right!
You still have manners?
You don't take me seriously at all.
I'm so disappointed in you.
Disappointed?
Are you saying you wanted me
to take advantage of you?
What are you trying to do?
Act like a beast?
That's why I didn't do anything.
You're even less than a beast.
So whether I did anything or not,
I'm still wrong.
What do you even want?
Forget about what happened last night.
Anyway,
it wasn't entirely your fault.
Let's just say it was an effect
of the poison.
But speaking of that,
what kind of poison is it this time?
This is...
Something from the Tang Family.
Tang Yingluo?
(Forgive me, Sister Rong.)
(I don't know if fighting poison
with poison will work.)
(But I have to try.)
This lady...
Does she want to save me or kill me?
This won't do. I need an explanation.
Tang Yingluo, come here.
I have a score to settle with you.
Come here.
Oh, caught you.
What on earth are all these?
Don't tell me
you used all these poisons on me!
Well, these poisons are meant for you.
But I was helping you!
(Since I promised
Yan Shao not to tell anyone)
(about the second poison,)
(I'll just have to make up something.)
Helping me?
It's also helping Brother Shaoci.
Sister Rong, think about it.
Ghost Valley Sect
is against Yuchi Manor,
and even the Six Great Sects
are at odds with each other.
Shaoci has too much on his plate.
To deal with...
Don't touch me.
When you still have your martial arts,
you can fight alongside him
and share the burden.
But ever since you lost your abilities
after Shen Zuitian injured you,
you couldn't help out.
He's left to deal with everything alone.
He's really struggling,
and I sympathize with him.
But what does that have to do
with you poisoning me?
I was trying to fight poison
with poison!
Tang Yingluo,
I'm warning you anyway.
If you do this again,
our friendship is over.
I won't talk to you anymore.
How is that funny?
No, it's just...
Sister Rong, you used to be so cold
and fierce.
But just now,
you said
we're friends.
I never dared to think of you
as a friend before.
But I like this version of you better.
Was I really
that scary before?
Actually, Shaoci used
to be a little scared of you, too.
He was scared of me?
He thought his martial arts
weren't as good as yours.
Even the hall masters
respected you more than him.
He admired you,
but he was afraid of you.
He cared about you,
but didn't dare to get too close.
(No wonder he rejected
Rong Shukuang's proposal.)
(What kind of man would want)
(a terrifying woman?)
Fine.
No more next time.
I'm leaving.
But you seem different
after you return.
If you regain your abilities
and help Shaoci manage the manor,
that would be even better.
I'd like to.
You're right to trust her.
I know.
Her poor poisoning skills,
out of not wanting to harm you,
just took half your life.
I'm sorry. I didn't do it on purpose.
But your body is strong enough.
So you will be fine.
(Of course, she's going to be fine.)
(I was the one who ended up taking)
(on all the poison
while trying to draw it out of her.)
Rong. Yan Shao.
You're all here.
Yingluo, we should go now.
I almost forgot.
Today, I'm supposed to inspect
the arrangement
of Zhonghe Festival with Brother Shaoci.
What's there to inspect?
I thought you enjoyed
Zhonghe Festival,
especially the Red Banner Flower Fair.
It's the only time
I've ever seen you smile so happily.
Am I right?
Yes.
The Zhonghe Festival
is a long-standing tradition
held in the city every year.
The highlight for Yuchi Manor
is the Red Banner Flower Fair.
You have always taken the top prize
at the fair,
and been admired
by heroes across the world.
(Yuchi Manor)
You don't usually go out much.
It's windy today.
Maybe you should stay home.
It's fine.
I've been frail since childhood.
I'm used to it.
With the treats going on,
I can't just sit back and do nothing.
Besides, the Red Banner Flower Fair
is my responsibility.
I'll only feel at ease
if I inspect it myself.
I'm just worried
you'll overexert yourself.
Shukuang!
Every year, the Zhonghe Festival
is the one day she's happiest.
Let her go this time.
Sister Rong wants to come with us too.
I was just telling Shaoci
that we shouldn't keep you cooped up
in the manor forever.
You were ambushed
the last time you went out.
I just can't rest easy.
We've got so many people this time.
Besides, Yan Shao's with us.
So nothing will happen.
Just let her go.
The city is packed
with martial artists
from all sects today.
It's a mixed crowd, so stay on guard.
Got it. Let's go.
Let's go!
This shop just opened recently.
Their crystal goose is famous.
Let's eat here.
That sounds great.
Let's order the stuffed crab too.
Yan Shao seems
especially protective of you
and always looking out for you.
Well, I did pay him.
It's his job to protect me.
But Yan Shao possesses
an extraordinary demeanor,
not like an average swordsman.
He doesn't seem like someone
who'd be driven by money alone.
Wanci, listen to yourself.
I'm the fifth-ranked martial artist
in the martial arts world,
the legendary swordswoman,
and Yuchi Manor's Young Lady Rong.
With all these impressive titles,
are you telling me
none of them are enough to impress him?
Have you ever been here before,
Yan Shao?
Zhonghe Festival is the busiest time
of the year in this city.
Yuchi Manor's Red Banner Flower Fair
is the highlight.
Shukuang used to win the competition
every single year.
She was an unstoppable force
whom people admired.
It's a pity you can't compete this year.
If Yan Shao enters,
the winner's prize will be
my personally brewed Baihua Brew.
Yan Shao, do you dare to compete?
Sure.
Then let's hope
you come out on top tomorrow night.
All right. Enough talking.
Don't catch a cold.
Close it.
Let's go.
Hey, come here.
Young Master Lin.
Are those
Hall Master Feng and Hall Master Lu?
It's to prevent anyone
from sneaking into the Fair
with bad intentions.
With such strict precautions,
everything should go smoothly.
I hope so.
But why is there a checkpoint
between the East and West Markets?
I never arranged it.
Father personally ordered it.
He's worried someone might slip in
and cause trouble
at the Red Banner Flower Fair.
But
won't some people say
we're overreacting
for being too cautious
and afraid of conflict?
Father must have his reasons.
Come on, Feng.
What a grand setup!
Look over there.
Even in ancient times,
their festivals
were like grand opening ceremonies.
Everything is ready.
Everything is already in place.
Let's go.
As you've mentioned,
most of the defenses are concentrated
in the inner city.
There are fewer crowds
in the outer city,
so there's no need
for extra precautions.
Let's go.
The festival is a time for honoring
the harvest god, praying for prosperity,
brewing Yichun Wine,
and holding poetry contests
or martial arts tournaments
for entertainment.
Yuchi Manor hosts
Red Banner Flower Fair every year,
attracting countless martial artists
from the martial world.
But this year, the elders
of Six Great Sects gathered here
are likely due to the conflict between
Yuchi Manor and Ghost Valley Sect.
Are all Six Great Sects
on Yuchi Manor's side?
Hard to say.
Because of Shen Zuitian,
the entire martial world suspects
that Yuchi Manor holds the key
to the Fuxian Treasure.
Freshly-made roujiamo!
I came up with it in the desert.
Now, it's already spread here.
Hold it.
Merchants are after profits.
So it'll spread quickly.
I should have charged a franchise fee!
But don't worry.
You'll always be the first person
in this world
to have tasted roujiamo
made by me, a genius!
I was the one
who funded the ingredients.
I talk about friendship,
and you bring up money?
It goes both ways.
No rush. There's enough for everyone.
- There you go.
- Here's the money.
It can be used during the tournament?
What are they selling?
- A gourd as a weapon? It's unheard of.
- Sister Rong.
How does one use a gourd
in a tournament?
Just chant some spells
and trap them inside.
Wanci.
Thank you, Yan Shao.
No problem.
Wanci, are you all right?
I am a little tired
from all the walking.
There's a tavern in the West Market.
How about we stop there and rest?
The West Market is too far.
Let's go to Blossom's Smile instead.
All right.
Let's go.
Feng, come on.
Flirting all you can, huh?
(Blossom's Smile)
This place looks familiar.
Is it the place
where you sobered up last time?
What? You don't like it?
Yes, I do.
(Secrets of Fate Revealed)
(Blossom's Smile)
My last visit here was exciting.
The inner city is heavily guarded.
Are you saying Yan Shao...
Guards are stationed at the corners
of the loft and the outer city
with a flexible defense strategy.
If anything happens in one area,
nearby guards can quickly
move in to help.
You planned it out well.
One jar of Hundred-Year Brew
and three side dishes.
(Fragrance Miles Away)
Hundred-Year Brew?
Why is the wine called that?
This wine was crafted
by both the owner and his wife.
They share a deep love.
Since their ages combined
are nearly a hundred years,
the wine is called Hundred-Year Brew.
Shaoci said
we shouldn't drink
while handling business.
Let's guess
how old the owner is.
Do you know?
This wine carries the depth of time.
A sip feels like gaining insight
into life itself,
and like watching the clouds drift by
without worry.
So, I'd say the owner is over sixty.
Then his wife is probably
in her thirties.
Feng, you're the smart one.
Smell that.
There's a faint, fruity fragrance.
Adding fresh fruit notes to the wine
means the owner's wife
must be young and full of life.
Not necessarily.
Mister, Madam.
Your wine is truly excellent today.
As long as you enjoy it, sir.
A younger husband
with a much older wife?
Were ancient folks this open-minded
about age gaps?
The owner's wife, Lihua Bai,
is a master brewer.
She dedicated her life to making wine
and refused to marry.
Until she met Qianjin Xiao
who is also her only apprentice.
The two fell in love,
and no one objected.
You knew that and didn't tell me?
Dear guests,
how are you enjoying the wine?
I am Qianjin Xiao,
and this is my wife, Lihua Bai.
You're my idol.
You two are perfect together.
It's rare to find a guest
who appreciates our wine so much.
I'll treat you to a jar
from my century-old collection.
Oh, that is so generous of you.
- Thank you.
- Please enjoy.
I'm not drinking.
(Fortune Telling)
Welcome, mister.
May your business prosper.
Please come inside.
Thank you.
(Fortune Telling)
Mister,
shall I bring you a fresh batch
of our latest brew?
That's exactly what I was hoping for.
And add two small dishes, please.
Coming right away.
- Here, Wanci.
- Thank you.
Look, there's a fortune teller there.
I've heard blind fortune tellers
are the most accurate.
Not necessarily.
Seems like you don't know.
Actually, not all fortune tellers
are blind.
See? I can see.
Mister, what kind of reading do you do?
I may not be the best.
But I understand the mysteries of fate.
I can foresee both fortune
and misfortune in life.
With the sun and moon in my palm
and the universe hidden within,
nothing escapes my sight.
Go on, take a seat.
Then foretell
what I want to ask.
How about this?
Whether it's love, wealth,
blessings, or spirits,
I can answer anything
honestly and fairly.
What do you think?
That impressive?
Then tell me about my wealth.
Your finances?
Yes.
Easy.
Then please
draw a fortune slip.
Please draw one.
Give me a good draw.
Give me
a good draw.
Drifting like falling petals,
carried by the wind?
Let me take a look.
Drifting like falling petals,
carried by the wind.
Sweet at first but
with a subtle bitterness.
Blown away by the wind.
It means a life of wandering
with no place to call home.
You probably grew up
without many family members,
without inheritance or land,
and without elders to take care of.
So
it means leaving the past behind
and marrying far from home.
So, I have no home, no elders,
and I'll be sent far away in marriage?
That's a terrible fortune.
Well, a bad draw could be a lucky draw.
Haven't you heard
that a bad fortune
can be a blessing in disguise?
Wanci, let's go and check it out too.
Come on. It looks interesting.
Marrying far from home
isn't necessarily a bad thing.
If someone never finds their true love,
what's the point
of having acres of land?
So it's a good draw.
You have a point.
Yingluo. Wanci.
Why don't you try as well?
Feel free to draw one.
Wanci, here.
(Spring crabapple blossoms
under the moon.)
(A person gazing at flowers
by the water.)
How about letting me read it?
Here, mister.
Spring crabapple blossoms
under the moon.
The book says it clearly.
Unrequited love brings nothing
but heartbreak.
Looking back, the person you long
for is already far away.
Miss, if you hold onto this love
too tightly,
you won't just hurt yourself
but others as well.
It could even take a toll
on your health.
It's like poison.
Bitter yet willingly swallowed.
Good.
Well said.
Wanci, come.
Take a seat.
Have a seat.
Let's see what your fortune says.
All right.
Good.
Gazing at flowers by the water.
Gazing at flowers by the water,
slender willows swaying in the wind.
This means you were born
with a weak constitution.
But you come from a wealthy family.
So, in this lifetime,
you'll always be well provided for,
and your wishes will likely come true.
It's a good draw.
Thank you, mister.
No need to pay me yet.
What's on your mind right now
is like a mirage.
It's beautiful but out of reach.
Just a piece of advice.
If you become too fixated on it,
it might not end well.
It's just a few words.
So don't take it too seriously.
Yes, exactly.
The food is getting cold.
Let's go back and eat.
Reality is what you choose to accept.
That's right. Let's go.
Wanci, let's go. Don't dwell on it.
(Tiangang members have gathered.
Waiting for the next step.)
(Meet up with Feng Ming.)
How was the reading?
Not bad.
Waiter!
Go get your fortune read.
Sir, what can I do for you?
A pot of fine tea.
Coming right up.
The inner city gates now
have additional checkpoints.
It's being handled
by Hall Master Feng and Hall Master Lu.
The wind is picking up.
♪Spinning through my heart,
my dreams, the endless Jianghu♪
♪A fateful turn,
where love and hearts collide♪
♪Ah, such a blissful tide♪
♪A journey long,
yet life is but one ride♪
♪Blades in chaos,
the world in turmoil, tangled ties♪
♪A fleeting warmth
to shield me from the ice♪
♪Ah, as spring awakens love's delight♪
♪One single glance,
my heart takes flight♪
♪I've heard tales of love and vengeance,
left forgotten in the tide♪
♪And whispers of desert stars and rain,
where love at first sight fades to cries♪
♪But I don't know, I don't know,
how long this moment will abide♪
♪Yet here and now,
for this one soul, I stand beside♪
♪I understand, love and longing,
how much truth, how many lies♪
♪Yet my swift blade cannot sever,
cannot sever these endless ties♪
♪I have known, the lonely journeys,
wandering years without goodbyes♪
♪Yet this moment stirs the ache inside♪
♪One turn through this dream of Jianghu,
one heartbeat lost in time♪
♪No dream compares
to a fateful meeting so divine♪
♪Love needs no hero,
only a foolish mind♪
♪Trapped in Jianghu's ruthless tides,
once, let me defy♪
♪A single touch, a fleeting smile,
is enough to shake the sky♪
♪Stirring the stillness,
where the winds rise high♪
♪Though fate may part our paths,
we walk the same road♪
♪A crescent moon,
a crimson glow, a love untold♪
♪Like passing winds, like aching souls,
never to meet once more♪
♪Then what is fate even for♪
♪Just once, to fall into your arms,
not lost, nor torn, nor bound to strife♪
♪Amidst the storm of masters' might,
hidden deep, a love so bright♪
♪Standing apart from all the fight,
only one embrace so right♪
♪A dream of Jianghu's light♪
♪One turn through this dream of Jianghu,
one heartbeat lost in time♪
♪No dream compares
to a fateful meeting so divine♪
♪Love needs no hero,
only a foolish mind♪
♪Trapped in Jianghu's ruthless tides,
once, let me defy♪
♪A single touch, a fleeting smile,
is enough to shake the sky♪
♪Stirring the stillness,
where the winds rise high♪