Winter Begonia
Episode 28
Mr. Cheng has photos of me?
Are you blind?
This is my mother.
She looked great.
She used to sing operas as well.
She also performed the best as
Lady Yang.
I’ve been looking for her for more than a decade.
I hadn’t been able to find anything.
I finally found something.
But then it was burnt.
Letters…
If there’s one letter,
there must be more.
If she was able to
find your address,
she will come to you one day.
Just be patient.
What’s your plan now?
One step at a time.
I’m all on my own now.
I’ve got nothing to lose.
What do you mean nothing?
You’ve got me.
Shuiyun Theatre will take care of you.
I am very high-maintenance.
I only use
the best imported goods.
There’s also
a baby to feed.
How are you going to take care of us?
Taking care of you two is not a problem.
Shuiyun Theatre is a cash cow.
When the time comes,
all you need to do,
is to stand next to the cow,
and I will bring you all the money.
Terrific.
I chose the right person.
Now,
take the water out.
Go to bed.
Wait! The towel!
♬ The moon ♬
♬ Gently rises over the island ♬
Mom, why did you stop?
You father is coming back soon.
He doesn’t like me singing at home.
But I like it.
Well then,
I will secretly sing it for you.
Great!
Harder.
I can’t go any more, leader.
More! Higher!
You’re very stiff.
I can’t anymore, leader.
Leader…
I can’t… Leader…
Leader I’m going to die.
Stand up straight, all of you.
Leader!
I can’t.
Can’t do this, boss.
Higher up.
I can’t…
You’re very stiff…
Leader… Dying…
I’m not dying.
I’m quite alright.
Leader, I can’t do this.
Try harder.
From the waist.
Higher.
Higher. Try harder.
No I can’t!
Morning, Mr. Cheng.
I can’t…
Are you trying to train these people,
or kill them?
Yes…
No, no killing.
Harder.
Go easy on them.
If they want to make it,
you’ll have to cut them open,
crush their bones,
and mold a new person
with their flesh.
Everyone has to do it.
No exception.
Do you want to make it?
Yes!
Does everyone want to make it?
Then suck it up!
After you make it, you’ll make that cash.
Hold it.
Hold it. Higher up.
-Here you are.
-From your waist!
-More strength!
-Thank you.
Mr. Cheng,
are you not having breakfast with me?
No slacking!
From the waist, up!
Manager Fan is here.
What happened to your head?
Mr. Fan.
Brother…
When did you come back?
This noon.
Did you sister do that to you?
Who else dares to hurt me
other than her?
Brother,
you saved me from such a big trouble,
I can’t be a coward, right?
You deserved to be hit.
In fact, you need to be hit harder.
You should be hit to death.
Look at the mess you made.
What did you sister say?
She didn’t say anything.
She thought
we did it together.
You know her.
How stubborn she can be…
The more you talk about these things,
the more she suspects.
Just let her figure out on her own.
What do we do?
What if she never figures out?
Are you going to stay here forever?
You also don’t like staying at home, do you?
I finally get to stay out of the house.
Let me be for a few days.
Three of us going through all this,
for one child.
Whom else should this be for?
For me!
For me…
Brother,
you did the most of it.
do they have a spare room here for you?
Why don’t you
crush at my place?
Your place?
All those people. Such a mess.
Not even as quiet as Shuiyun Theatre.
I’m not going anywhere.
I’ll stay here at the theatre.
Right,
Zeng Aiyu is leaving Peking tonight.
You need to see her off.
I’m worried that she won’t see me.
Such a coward.
Leader is coming.
Where’s his kettle?
Anyone saw it?
I’ll deal with you later.
I’ll have to go out a for a bit.
Don’t forget
to get some rest.
You have another show tonight.
Mr. Cheng.
You’re here.
I apologize.
I didn’t see anything.
Just to let her have a little from her own mom.
She won’t get any
after this.
All done.
You can turn around.
Are you really leaving Peking?
Tell me what happened with your family.
I can help.
Help me?
You help me
and I can stay.
Then what?
Are you going to marry me?
If you really want to be with the baby…
It’s better for her
if she stays with you.
Fine.
Give her to me.
I’ll treat her as my own daughter.
Don’t you worry.
Mr. Cheng.
The luggage has been loaded.
Got it.
Just to hold her a little longer.
From now on,
I can only think about her
for the rest of my life.
It’s not too late to change your mind.
There there…
This jade pedant
looks like a feather.
It’s a phoenix tail.
Mommy wanted to leave it to you
as something to hold on to.
But I need this jade
for something else.
I can’t leave it to you.
Child,
don’t blame me.
Since this is
a phenix tail.
I’ll just call the baby
Fengwei (phenix tail).
Something to hold on to.
Fengwei…
Fengwei.
I think she likes it.
There there baby.
Fengwei.
Thank you, Mr. Cheng.
Where is Fan Lian anyway?
That’s it.
No more waiting.
Or I’ll miss my train.
Mr. Ge,
thank you.
Get her on the train safe.
And go home.
Don’t worry, Mr. Cheng.
Hurry.
Hurry up!
Faster!
(Peking Station)
(Exit)
What took you so long?
I went to the train station.
Did you see her?
I know you’re not really married.
But since she was pregnant,
you’ve been very upset and indecisive.
You don’t want to lose the baby nor the money.
No wonder she can’t respect you.
Arms out.
What?
Take her.
Okay…
Higher up.
Hold her bottom.
I’ll tidy up.
Brother,
why… why is she crying?
She’s probably hungry.
-There’s a bottle on the table.
-There there…
Feed her some milk.
Check the temperature with the back of your hand.
Don’t burn her.
A few drops are enough.
This?
Yes.
There there. It’s okay…
It’s okay baby.
There there.
It’s okay honey.
Where is the nanny?
Where did she go?
I let her go.
Why?
Who is going to take care of the baby?
She got trachoma.
I don’t want her to give it to the baby.
So I let her go.
It’s okay. It’s okay.
Don’t cry, baby.
Brother,
what were you thinking?
It’s okay baby.
Just have some milk.
Brother, brother…
She’s still crying.
She won’t stop.
It’s okay…
It’s fine. Don’t cry, baby.
Oh… It’s wet.
You need to change the diapers.
What…
I can’t do that.
You’re her father.
Where’s your responsibility?
Where is it?
It takes time to build a relationship with her.
You should do it…
Brother, please.
Here, give her to me.
There, there.
It’s okay.
It’s okay baby.
There you go.
Good girl.
I’ll change your diapers right away.
Bring me the baby powders.
This is baby formula.
The other one.
This.
Oh that’s a lot!
Well done. Good girl.
There. Some baby powders.
Now you’ll feel all better.
Good girl.
All done.
Brother,
I’m not even half as good as you are at this.
I feel that
you’re her father.
Get out.
Brother,
let me ask you.
Are you really leaving my sister?
That’s not up to me.
What… What are you going to do?
Who… Who is going to take care of this baby?
Don’t look at me like that.
It’s not that I don’t want her.
It’s just that all the uncles
will be mad at me if I take her back.
She’s better off without you.
I’ll take her back to the theatre.
Shuiyun Theatre?
Why don’t you just stay here?
I don’t want to.
Since I rented this place,
so many bad things have happened.
The fengshui is probably wrong.
Are you also superstitious?
I didn’t believe in these things.
But recently I feel like
things are just a bit too odd to explain.
Wait,
her hat is a bit off.
I’ll fix it.
Baby girl…
Sister,
do you know where my brother went
after moving out of here?
Shuiyun Theatre!
He’s living in a theatre!
Let her be.
He likes hanging out
with those show people.
I can’t control him anyways, right?
You would’ve been furious
if this happened in the past.
How are you so calm now?
Are you really thinking about
leaving my brother?
This time,
we both made mistakes.
We’re both guilty.
Neither of us will give in.
Aren’t you afraid that
my brother will betray you?
Then divorce you and marry someone else?
Sister,
do you really think
I’m just sitting at home, doing nothing?
I’ve done my homework
on that Zeng Aiyu.
A young and pretty social butterfly.
Had Mr. Cheng and Fan Lian fooled.
I have both Mr. Cheng’s check book
and his stamp.
He doesn’t have much cash with him.
Will she still hang around
after he runs out of money?
As long as I have the control over the money,
he can’t go anywhere.
All I need to do
is to take care of this business.
When Cheng Fengtai gets a taste of being poor,
when he finally sees what she really is,
he will be back.
Hope he’ll find her mother back
by then.
I had indeed
underestimated you.
You didn’t underestimate me.
You only underestimated where I came from.
You…
You’re indeed
very clever with your words!
Whose baby is this?
So cute!
My little daughter.
Isn’t she adorable?
-So adorable.
-So pretty.
She really looks like you, Mr. Cheng!
So pretty.
Adorable.
Indeed…
What are you all doing here!
So noisy.
-I’m trying to prepare for the show there.
-Leader.
I…
What on earth is this?
This is my little girl.
Didn’t I tell you last time already?
But you didn’t say you’d bring her here.
Where else will I take her?
Should I sleep on the street with her?
I didn’t mean that.
Mr. Cheng,
don’t you know?
Our leader
is afraid of children.
He finds them scary.
What’s wrong with you this time?
Don’t you think it’s very scary when they cry?
It sounds like when you’re walking alone
in the middle of the night
and you walk by the graveyard,
and you hear the cats screaming…
What are you talking about?
What kind of metaphor is this?
You’re just not familiar with them.
All you need to do is hold them.
Here, give it a go.
No, no, no.
-Here. Come!
-Nope. No need.
Mr. Cheng.
-Come here.
-No! No way!
-Help me!
-Just one second.
-One second.
-Leader!
-Help!
-Just one second.
-Mr. Cheng.
-Help me!
Here. Don’t tease him.
He really can’t stand babies.
Come here.
Our leader doesn’t like you.
I like you.
Sister will sing for you, little girl.
Sister?
Aren’t you even too old to be her aunt?
Shut up.
Dasheng!
What are you going to do
when you have your own?
I don’t want any.
I don’t want kids.
Then who will inherit
your legacy and skills
from Shuiyun Theatre?
I have Zhouzi.
Zhouzi? Zhouzi?
Are you trying to take advantage of him?
He’s not your child.
I’m not my father’s biological child either.
My brother was his biological son.
But he couldn’t sing as well.
He was a waste of food for my father.
Get this,
biological or not, it doesn’t matter.
Sometimes your kids just don’t look like you.
What kind of argument is this?
If everyone thinks like this,
we’d be going extinct already.
There are people like me running away from babies.
There are those like you who can’t stop holding them.
We keep it balanced.
Human beings won’t be extinct.
You simply
don’t like children.
You simply like children too much.
You like them even when they’re not yours.
You’d even pay for them.
I should’ve just taken one home for you.
It’ll save you a lot of money.
Baby girl.
-Well…
-She’s so cute.
Does she have a name?
Fengwei.
Phenix tail.
Tail is not “Wei”
Mr. Cheng,
follow me,
it’s “Yi”.
Tail is pronounced as “Yi”.
Fengyi… Yi…
Yi…
Fengyi…
That’s actually not bad.
Sounds quite nice.
Yes.
We’ll call her Fengyi then.
Fengyi!
Fengyi girl.
What do you say?
Fengyi?
Cheng Fengtai.
Cheng Fengyi.
Same character.
What a name.
Fengyi. Fengyi. Fengyi.
Stop thinking about it.
Eat.
Why do you think he left?
Did I do something wrong?
Should we go talk to him?
You did make a mistake
by not talking to me earlier.
Cheng Fengtai is a smart man.
He wouldn’t take the baby to your cousin.
He’s most likely just having a woman for fun.
It’s already happened.
Too late to talk to him now.
For fun?
This…
Having an affair is not just for fun.
I can’t believe you just said that.
If you’re helping her hide this today,
is he going to hide for your one day?
This is his family matters.
Why are you mad at me?
♬ If I get to be selfish once ♬
♬ I’d like to shoulder your sins ♬
♬ So that you can smile ♬
♬ So that we can cherish our time ♬
♬ If I get to only cry once ♬
♬ I wouldn’t be able to help ♬
♬ Pretending nothing happened ♬
♬ The flowers blossom from the dust ♬
♬ I’m not afraid of our time together ♬
♬ Let’s finish this drink and this show ♬
♬ You understand my regrets without being told ♬
♬ You told me life was wonderful in my dream ♬
♬ Life is precious ♬
♬ We have to leave the sorrows behind ♬
There there.
It’s okay.
It’s okay. Don’t cry.
Are you hungry?
♬ Look at the mountain ♬
♬ Look at the dust on the satin ♬
It’s okay.
There, there.
Don’t you cry.
It’s okay.
Cheng Fengtai,
tell her to stop!
We’re trying to sleep here!
Will she listen to me?!
It’s okay.
♬ I pretend to muddle along as if nothing matters ♬
♬ A bud blossoms from the dust ♬
You’re killing me.
My son
didn’t even worry me as much.
♬ Let’s finish this drink and this show ♬
♬ You understand my regrets without being told ♬
♬ You told me life was wonderful in my dream ♬
Stop.
I’m busy taking care of the baby.
I can’t take care of you as well.
I found a girl to take care of you.
What did I do wrong?
If you don’t like Chunxing,
then find a “clean” one for yourself.
Why do you have to be so upset?
You won’t understand.
♬ Look at the dust on the satin ♬
When do you think
I get to go back
and get you a little sister?
What’s happening here?
What’s wrong with you?
We didn’t do anything wrong.
Wait,
you’re making all this dust.
We can’t practice in dust.
Move along then.
Practice there.
Can’t you see I’m airing the quilt
for our money man?
He is the priority.
More important than all of you.
Wait a second.
What’s the matter with you?
Did Mr. Cheng do anything wrong?
He is such a nice person.
He is nice.
But that wife of him
is basically blind.
She’s so stupid.
A word of advice,
stay away from him.
If she shows up here tomorrow,
she will kill anyone
who has talked to Mr. Cheng.
All of you,
will… will suffer.
Wait. What does that mean?
Whom are you talking about?
Wait.
Come here.
Who?
Whom?
Talking about you.
Shut up.
I wasn’t talking about you.
Whom?
Tell me now.
Leader.
Leader! Leader! Leader.
♬ Cheng Fengtai, show yourself ♬
♬ Here I come ♬
♬ What can I do for you ♬
Today
I’m going to get us
something really big, really fancy.
What is it?
Yes, what is it?
What thing?
What are we getting?
Something big?
Fancy?
Listen up,
listen.
-Spill it.
-What is it?
It’s got walls around it.
Inch away from the ground.
Can you guess?
-No idea.
-What is it?
What?
I got it!
A litter!
That’s silly.
Nonsense.
I’m getting a car!
A car? Car?
A car for a theatre.
That’s new.
Right!
Are we going to drive
to our shows?
I know!
Don’t be silly.
This car is for Mr. Cheng.
For Mr. Cheng?
Me?
Did you say?
You wanted a car.
Those imported cars are not comfortable for you.
I didn’t mean it.
But I meant it.
It’s just nonsense.
I’m not taking the car.
I’ve made a deal with them.
You can buy me a meal.
Cancel the car.
This is too much.
I’m want you to be happy.
I’m happy.
Very happy.
I’ll order. You’ll pay.
Right, Xiaolai,
could you take care of Fengyi for me?
The formula is in the room.
On the table.
Let’s go.
That’s enough. Walk along.
Let’s go. Let’s go.
Back to practice.
It’s about to rain.
Mr. Cheng,
take an umbrella with you!
I’ll bring him the umbrella.
He…
A money man indeed.
All these privileges.
Being served all the time.
Having people do things for him
wherever he goes.
Mr. Cheng,
are you really not taking the car?
I don’t need it.
I’ll tell you what I want
when I figure out.
You really would spend that money for me?
What are you saying?
As long as I have a coin in my pocket,
I’ll spend it for you.
Don’t push! Don’t push!
I have enough papers here.
Here you go.
Don’t push!
Take this one.
Are people going mad in Peking?
They’re fighting for newspapers?
They’re electing a leader at Opera Association.
Peking Times is the sponsor.
One paper means one vote.
Whoever has more followers and money wins.
Xue Qianshan knows how to make his money.
-Mr. Shang.
-Don’t push.
I always hear about this leader of the Association.
What’s the big deal?
Latest news!
It’s got everyone in Peking
so excited.
The election of the leader
happens once every 5 years.
I haven’t been here long enough
to see one before.
I heard that
those who made it in the first round
will have to go through a second round.
And then
they will announce the result here at the Association.
(The Opera Association)
Winning the election
is the biggest thing.
The person gets to march the street.
It’s really something.
It does sound quite fun.
Did your father win?
My father.
The first ever election he was the runner-up.
Same with the second election.
And then he left Peking.
After that,
he couldn’t stop thinking about
this election.
He kept talking about it
all the time.
I can recite his words now.
Well then,
this is you representing your father.
Too bad.
I don’t have much money with me.
Or you’ll definitely win.
Shut up.
I don’t need you to cheat for me.
True.
Mr. Shang is one famous performer.
You’re already very capable.
(The 5th Election of Peking)
(Shang Xirui winning first place)
Be careful.
(The 5th Election of Peking)
(Shang Xirui winning first place)
Don’t rush. Be careful.
(The 5th Election of Peking)
(Shang Xirui winning first place)
-Okay.
-Slowly.
Sir,
welcome.
Mr. Niu,
the set up for this election
is really fancy.
Thanks to the sponsorship
from Peking Times.
Take a look.
How do you like the stage setup?
Quite nice.
It’ll look very good in the picture.
You guys,
take photos of this stage and the setup.
-Yes.
-Yes, sir.
Sir,
look,
this is
all I can do for you.
Not it’s your turn
to show your magic.
8 writers
and 60 articles.
Is that enough?
Sure. Certainly.
Shang Xirui is here this year.
You just wait.
The money will go to you.
How is that so?
Think about it.
Here at Peking,
so many dramas have happened since Shang Xirui came.
This election will be extra eventful.
You just wait and see.
At the end of the day,
operas are about songs and music.
All we need is audience and some popularity.
Don’t you agree?
(Jiang’s Mansion)
Fried dough twist! Pancake!
Sir,
are you serious?
What’s wrong with your ears.
I know my worth.
A few decades ago,
I might be elected.
But now…
Look at me.
I haven’t performed for years.
Chen Renxiang left for Shanghai.
Dengbao is not ambitious enough.
I don’t think we have a successor
here at Longchun Troupe.
We have known each other for long enough.
Supporting you is better than anyone else.
I’ll give you a leak.
Ning Jiulang is also participating this year.
How many years has it been?
Don’t you want to compete with him again?
Ning Jiulang…