Winter Begonia
Episode 9
You took me here
but hide it from me.
Gosh!
Good.
In some days,
the painter will be a master.
Can you do me a favor?
I can repair the cave.
What I need to do is making it firm.
It can be maintained for 60 years.
Is it enough?
60 years?
That’s enough.
But,
it’s unfair to me
if everyone can go through the cave
after it’s repaired.
What else do you want?
I want
a lock in the cave.
When
I want it to collapse,
it will collapse.
You’d rather ruin your house
than let others live in it?
You look like a socialite,
but you are not generous like them.
This is an arduous work.
You ask me to do it
because you trust me.
So,
I’ll ask something more for the payment.
Write a number that you want.
Mr. Cheng, don’t misunderstand.
This is not what I want.
I heard
that you are the brother-in-law of Commander Cao.
Sir, do you want a position in the government ?
I’ll talk with him about this.
Before the Emperor left the Palace,
he asked me to repair the Hall of Supreme Harmony.
But before I started,
the Empress, Concubine Shu and he
were driven out of the Palace.
I wrote several letters to those senators and
ministers.
I told them
if it couldn’t be repaired immediately,
the Hall of Supreme Harmony would collapse.
But they
didn’t believe it.
Tomorrow,
no,
tonight,
I’ll talk with my brother-in-law about this.
I’ll pay
for the restoration.
Dasheng, stop.
What’s the matter, leader?
Go through the eastern road.
It’s not convenient to
go through that narrow and dark road.
Spring troupe will finish their show.
Don’t let them laugh at us.
Mr. Shang.
Mr. Cheng.
Where are you going?
I’ll take my troupe back to Pingyang.
Go back to Pingyang?
Why?
Won’t you build a new theatre?
How do we build a new one?
These senior peers
stole the money that we have earned for years.
We have no choice.
Shijiu.
Mr. Cheng.
Peking is the origin of Peking opera.
We go back and perform in Pingyang.
When we save enough money
and this thing is solved,
I’ll come back
to continue my career.
I’ll give you tickets then.
Mr. Shang,
can we talk alone?
I make friends with you sincerely.
But you didn’t tell me
about such an important thing.
And you’re leaving in such a hurry.
Don’t you believe that I can help you?
That you help me is what I’m afraid of.
Our friendship is pure like that in operas.
I don't want it to be involved in other things.
It will be vulgar when it’s related to money.
In operas, people
spend thousands of money to get a soul mate.
Now, my soul mate is in trouble.
How can I ignore this?
I won’t forgive myself.
Mr. Cheng, please don’t say that.
Mr. Shang.
Mr. Cheng.
If you were Fan Juqing,
there must be Zhang Yuanbo.
When you are alone,
the opera won’t be complete.
So you
will be my stage?
Yes.
What?
What are they talking about?
I’m so cold.
The leader comes back.
Everyone!
We don’t leave today!
We don’t leave?
We don’t leave today,
and we won’t leave ever.
We must be successful
in Peking.
Let me introduce him again.
Cheng Fengtai, Mr. Cheng,
the shareholder of our Shuiyun Theater.
I watched your opera.
You are all talented performers.
Pingyang can’t give you a stage to show yourself.
You are driven into a corner
because you offended Commander Cao,
and you are short of money.
I am Commander Cao’s brother-in-law.
I’m not afraid of him
even though others are.
And when it comes to money,
I have no shortage of that.
If you trust me,
I, Cheng Fengtai,
will be the backer of Shuiyun Theater.
I protect your performance,
so please make your stage bright for me.
We don’t need to go!
We’ll have a stage again.
Great!
♫ Concubine ♫
♫Wait for me to walk with you later ♫
Bravo! Bravo!
Mr. Tian takes office,
and exposes Minister Tong’s trick,
which draws much attention.
Ministers Tong is discharged from his position.
- Liu Zu’ning sees Mr. Tian...
- Be concentrated!
...as a thorn in his side.
He colludes with the newspaper offices
and spreads the rumor that Mr. Tian
offends the Commander Zhang.
It sounds like a story
of our leader.
Yes.
Mr. Tian is our leader,
and Liu Zuning is Jiang Rongshou.
Who wrote this?
Interesting.
Let me have a look.
Don’t rob it.
Give me back.
What are you doing?
You look furtive.
You must be a thief.
No. No.
Don’t misunderstand.
I am a journalist.
A journalist from a newspaper office.
Mr. Qiu?
What brings you by?
I heard that Mr. Shang will leave Peking.
I am his die-hard fan.
So I come to take a picture for memory.
Who told you that we are leaving?
Now
Shuiyun Theater’s attendance rate is the highest in Peking.
Why do we leave?
Isn’t Mr. Shang afraid
that Commander Cao will execute him?
What are you talking about?
If Commander Cao wants to execute our leader,
he has to discuss it with his brother-in-law
in case that
what his brother-in-law paid
will be in vain.
What do you mean?
Cheng Fengtai, Mr. Cheng,
is our shareholder now.
He’ll build a theater for us.
Shijiu!
Mind your words.
Cheng Fengtai?
Mr. Jiang.
Come to the point.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to stop Shang Xirui building a theatre.
You are the chairman.
So you must know how to do.
Yes, I do.
But I
like watching Mr. Shang’s performance.
Why do we bring trouble to him?
You must not know
that Shang Xirui
has a backer, Cheng Fengtai.
Cheng Fengtai
bought him the land.
If you stop him,
you’ll help me and also,
this is a warning to Cheng Fengtai
that money is not the license
of everything in Peking.
OK.
I’ll take this bottle.
I lost that lucky place.
I promised to build a theater there
when I have enough money,
but it was sold to another one immediately.
Don’t believe their bragging.
If Bodhi court is really a lucky place,
how come it’s taken by eunuchs?
Don’t worry.
Let’s find a new place.
None is better than there.
Other places are too remote
or too bleak.
Good places are all taken.
Then buy a theater directly.
I’ll ask Fan Lian to do it.
But it costs time.
Don’t be hurried.
I have a theatre to perform anyway.
So don’t hurry to find a new one.
Also,
how will you deal with
those who steal money from your troupe?
You don’t always keep
your eyes on them,
so they have chances to do things stealthily.
They may sell you one day
when you don’t notice.
Mean people
don’t have friends.
It’s always like this.
If you are
like them,
that’s fine.
But you are not.
You focus
on friendship.
You are a good friend,
but you are not a good boss.
Who isn’t a good boss?
Don’t I lead them well on opera?
I don’t mean on opera.
I mean on business.
What does a good management need?
It doesn’t need loyalty
or temper.
It needs disciplines
and rules.
Look at other troupes.
They are all under strict rules.
That’s what a good boss should do.
I can’t learn it well.
My time is
for studying opera.
Yes.
It’s not your style if you
teach them rules strictly.
Forget it.
Let me do it.
I am the shareholder.
So my words
will work for them.
Money talks after all.
Leading a troupe is even harder
than leading a troop.
Artists never obey your rules.
Mr. Cheng, can you make it?
Don’t underestimate me.
Let’s wait and see.
Listen.
Paris in France
is very beautiful.
People are tall and strong.
They have cheek kissing when they meet.
That’s an amazing city.
Do you understand?
Leader.
Finally you are back!
Leader! Leader!
Look who is here.
Rui!
Mr. Du.
Take care.
Rui!
I’m back, Rui!
Superstar,
did you miss me ?
When did you come back?
You ask me?
I wanted to give you a surprise.
So I came to you after I arrived in Peking last night.
But
no one was here.
I heard
that Jiang Rongshou brought you troubles.
He drove you out.
How arrogant he is!
So
I wrote a story a whole night for revenge.
Have a look.
A story about me?
Look at me...
Sorry that I forgot to introduce you.
Mr. Du.
This is the shareholder of Shuiyun Theater,
Cheng Fengtai, Mr. Cheng.
Mr. Cheng,
He
is Du Luocheng
from the Imperial Academy.
He writes librettos for me.
Mr. Du.
Nice to meet you.
Screw you!
What’s wrong?
What happened?
Heartbreaker!
Heartbreaker?
You must make a mistake.
I find you finally!
Mr. Du.
Mr. Du! Mr. Du!
Stop it! Go down!
What?
Mr. Du!
Stop it!
Fight in Shuiyun Theater?
Is this approved by our pioneer?
You pushed me?
I am your God of Literature!
I am his God of Wealth!
How dare you talk back?
Alright. Alright.
Stop fighting.
That’s enough.
You both studied abroad.
How can well-educated people fight?
Also, none of you is good at fighting.
Don’t you feel embarrassed to fight
without any practical skill?
I feel embarrassed?
He abandoned his lover.
It’s he who’s embarrassed!
I must teach you a lesson today!
Stop! Stop!
It’s weird.
Who is heartbroken for me?
Stop it!
-No...
-Stop!
Mr. Du.
Tell us
how he makes you heartbroken?
Yes.
Yeah.
Not me.
Cheng Fengtai,
listen carefully!
Su Shanna.
Who?
You mean her?
Her?
You think of her?
Don’t deny it.
Su Shanna loved you so much.
Go away!
She loved him so much.
She said that she would only marry him.
She also took his photo with her
and looked at it every day.
She was almost crazy.
But he?
He went back without telling Su Shanna.
Cheng Fengtai.
Tell me,
are you wronged
to be called “heartbreaker”?
If you must say so,
I’m really wronged.
Are you provoking?
How dare you?
Mr. Du!
Take it down.
When I studied in Britain,
a girl named Su Shanna was my classmate
and my friend.
Su Shanna
told me
that an Asian student wooed her.
And he climbed up to her window at night
to give her roses.
It was creepy.
So she
asked me to give her my photo,
and let me disguise as her boyfriend
-to make that boy give up.
-I see.
But it surprised me that
the Asian boy was Mr. Du.
Gosh.
You did so?
Mr. Du.
Look at your thin limbs.
How could you climb up to her window?
Do you know Romeo and Juliet?
No.
It’s because of love.
Love.
Mr. Du.
If you climbs up to my window,
I’ll say yes to you.
Look at you.
What a pity.
Su Shanna never loved you.
Of course,
she never loved me as well.
She loved Vikings
and thought Asian men are not strong enough.
You don’t believe?
Look.
Why must she play the mermaid
instead of the princess?
Just to be held by that Dane.
I should have exercised my muscles.
Alright. Alright.
Mr. Shang.
I need to go back to pack things up.
Goodbye.
Take care, Mr. Cheng.
Mr. Du.
Let’s chat another day.
By the way.
Next time...
No, this time
when you leave,
go through the gate
instead of the wall.
Bye, Mr. Cheng.
-Bye, Mr. Cheng.
Mr. Cheng.
Come to have dinner tonight.
We’ll have the first shareholder’s meeting.
Rui.
When did you make friends with him?
Be careful.
Businessmen are more cunning
than monkeys if they have tails.
How can you play games with him?
I don’t play games with him.
We’ll do great things.
Do great things?
I brought some goods from France for you.
Come. Western goodies.
Did you have chocolates?
So sweet. Trust me.
Finally, we overcame
all the barriers.
We couldn’t stay in Peking
without Mr. Cheng’s help.
Now, toast Mr. Cheng.
I said it before.
I am your backer,
and you make your stage bright for me.
Everyone,
this is our promise.
Toast Mr. Cheng!
Mr. Cheng.
Enjoy.
Help yourself.
Taste this.
Mr. Cheng. Taste this.
Thanks.
Give me one.
Come.
Eat.
Don’t be hurried.
Contract.
One more thing.
Now that Mr. Cheng is our shareholder,
he’ll take care of our finance.
Behave yourselves in the future.
You won’t have room for stealing.
Don’t be nervous.
From now on,
we do things based on the contract.
Contract?
What’s the contract, Mr. Cheng?
-What’s that?
-What is it?
What’s the contract?
(Contract)
This is the new rule of Shuiyun Theatre.
Everyone should sign your name on it.
Once you sign your name,
you’ll be arrested or accused
if you break the rules.
Be accused?
Such serious?
Is... Is this a contract?
It’s still an indenture to sell ourselves.
Nonsense.
The indenture is valid for your life.
But the validity of this contract is five years.
Five years later,
no one forces you to stay.
Leader.
What if we leave within the five years?
You can go
as long as you pay the liquidated damages.
It’s much less
than that for your previous indenture.
It’s not a long time.
Not bad.
Xiaolai, give me one
in case I’ll forget later.
Give me one.
Everyone has one.
Give me.
Give me. Give me.
Here.
Everyone has one.
One by one.
Here.
It’s only five years.
Time flies by.
Yes.
Where should I sign?
Everyone who was there
signed it.
This is nice.
Anyone can go when they want.
They don’t think I’m a good boss,
and I don’t think they are good staff.
We just had dinner.
Have extra meal?
I’m not full without wheaten food.
Mr. Cheng.
How’s going with the account?
This gives me a headache.
Your account
is more messy than your backstage.
Who took care of the account for you?
No one.
When they needed money,
they drew a line on it.
Mr. Shang.
Your money would never be enough
even if you had a gold mountain.
Many things are not matched
on this account book.
What’s more,
they always used money on what we can’t see.
You won’t know how much you lost.
My mind is as messy as the account.
It’s time to stop.
Mr. Cheng. Have you regretted?
What are you talking about?
I said
“have you regretted”?
Crazy guy.
Give me the shoes.
No.
Once you step on my boat,
don’t try to leave me alone.
I shouldn’t have stepped on your boat.
That’s nonsense.
You entered my room
and had my food,
so you must stay.
This is a troupe,
not a bandits' lair.
Are you kidnapping me?
So what?
OK. OK.
Mr. Shang.
It was just a joke.
Let me smoke outside.
Will you manage my account?
Yes!
Yes! Yes!
I stepped on your boat.
How can I step down?
Give me a ticket.
Can I have a box now?
Hurry.
Don’t crowd.
Don’t crowd. Queue up!
Everyone.
Can you see that?
They all come for us.
Our Spring Theater’s golden days
will come.
Let’s go.
Give me one!
One by one. Don’t crowd!
Why do they come?
Aren’t you from Shuiyun Theater?
Who are you?
The backstage is only for staff.
Didn’t your master teach you?
We Spring Theater will perform tonight.
What are you doing here?
Go. Go.
Ask the manager.
Why should I answer you?
Manager!
Leader.
Yes, Mr. Jiang.
I’m sorry, Mr. Jiang.
My staff will go to inform you.
Inform me what?
Well,
from now on,
Shuiyun Theater will perform here
at night.
How about us?
How about our Spring Theater?
I’m sorry but you have to perform in the morning.
If you want,
you can perform on Monday.
Why?
You promised me.
But why you broke your words?
How dare you ignore Chairman Jiang?
Well...
The chairman
can’t fill the auditoriums.
Money is the motivation of business.
Putting me in dilemma?
Remember this.
Wait me.
I’ll tell my dad.
None of you can get away from it.
Shang Xirui.
I’ll see you cry soon.
Go.
Go back!
Yes.
-Are you waiting for our show?
-Go back!
-Go back for your dad.
-What are you waiting for?
Will you watch our performance?
-Catch up with them.
-Go back to your dad.
-Go.
-Go back.
Hurry to go.
What are you looking at?
Leader.
We just drove Spring Theater away.
Jiang Dengbao will incite his dad
to frame you.
They’ve
been hating me for long.
This is not a big deal.
How can you laugh?
(Yahong Theater)
♫ Ices rise ♫
♫ From the island ♫
Nice!
Good voice!
♫ Jade Rabbit appears ♫
Bravo!
Morning, Mr. Cheng.
What happened?
You asked me here in the morning.
What new goods will you show me?
Come in.
Close the door.
I ask you here for something serious.
No.
I’m nervous to death
for your serious thing.
I would like to listen
to the story about beauties, gambling
or opera.
Here is a story about opera.
I’ve made a deal with Shang Xirui.
I’ll bought a theater for him
and invest for Shuiyun Theater.
Is my hearing okay?
You are in league with Shang Xirui?
What do you mean “in league with”?
We hit it off
and appreciate each other.
Do you understand?
Yes.
I understand.
But a theatre costs a fortune.
Dose my sister know it?
I asked you out
to avoid your sister.
You know, she dislikes
those entertainers most.
I won’t succeed
if she knows.
So keep this secret for me.
Don’t speak a word out.
I want you
to be
the manager of the theater.
You always behave like a social butterfly.
You are a suitable person
to receive the guests.
Fengtai.
As the manager,
I won’t get enough profits.
How about this?
I have money now.
Let me buy some shares.
Both of us are shareholders.
Don’t let my sister know.
You are always on a tight budget.
Don’t make a fool of yourself.
Fengtai,
I will buy a share
even if I only have a penny.
Only in this way,
can I be the boss and have my business.
Now
Shang Xirui earns
more than a cinema.
He’s really your cash cow.
Please let me join you.
Fengtai.
Fine.
Buy the shares
as many as you can.
This will be our own business.
If you are still careless,
you are really a loser.
OK.
My God of Wealth.
I’ll strut my stuff.
This is a good thing.
Yes.
How did you think of it?
I’m spying Cheng Fengtai these days.
He avoids as possible as he can
and never responds directly.
Seems that he’ll play dumb with us.
So,
let’s take action as what we planned.
Yes, sir.
Before you go,
remove the bullets in the gun.
Remember,
don’t kill him.
Got it.
He’s a relative of Commander Cao after all.
Bullets can only be used on the battlefield.
Others don’t deserve dying in this way.
Yes.
Hello?
OK.
Mrs. Cheng.
Mr. Ma from the freight agent calls Mr. Cheng.
Tell him Mr. Cheng is not at home.
Sorry, Mr. Cheng is not at home.
He said the thing is urgent.
Only Mr. Cheng can deal with it.
It’s me.
What’s the matter?
It’s the same to tell me.
Mr. Han.
Mrs. Cheng.
Something serious.
Cao Guixiu’s men
detained Mr. Cheng’s goods at the train station.
Childe Cao?
I didn’t know that they have a conflict.
This happened out of the blue.
Find Mr. Cheng back.
OK.
Mrs. Cheng.
Is Mrs. Cao at home?
She went to play mahjong.
Call her back.
OK.
Hurry up.
Mr. Cheng.
Please wait at the box.
Our leader just finished a pork leg.
He’s practicing the opera inside.
So he won’t see anyone.
Including me?
You are our God of Wealth.
You are not included.
What happened?
Why did you call me back in a hurry?
Sis.
Is everything well with Childe Cao?
Why did you ask about him?
Does a girl of Fan family
want to marry him?
Mr. Cheng always told me that he is capable
and generous,
and he will achieve something in the future.
Childe Cao is out of our girls’ league.
Don’t flatter me.
Fengtai only says
that Cao Guixiu is cunning.
He may add something like
“he’s as cunning as my sister”.
Am I right?
No.
You care your family,
but Childe Cao doesn’t.
What did Cao Guixiu do?
He detained some goods of Mr. Cheng
at the train station today.
Sis,
what does he want to do?
Is there a misunderstanding?
Mr. Ma called me at the train station.
So there’s no misunderstanding.
Also...
What?
He said
he must let Mr. Cheng know that he did so.
Sis,
Mr. Cheng works for Commander Cao.
I never ask him about this.
But I know he’s honest
and does everything under rules.
Please don’t get the innocent involved
if Mr. Cao and his son have a conflict.
Rest assured.
I will protect Fengtai.
But he’s not easy to do things between them.
Fengtai.
Have a seat.
Sit.
Sweet heart.
Sit here.
OK.
I can’t see the stage.
I want black tea.
Miss,
sorry.
We don’t have that,
but our Dahongpao is also good.
I’m not happy.
Go.
Put it aside if you dislike.
I’ll take you to drink coffee later.
Be happy.
You are right my best.
Cheer up.
What are you thinking about Fengtai?
I’m thinking about Shang Xirui.
What happened?
He brought troubles again?