Jung Il-woo
Kwon Yu-ri
Shin Hyun-soo
Bossam - Steal the Fate
This is really the place, right?
It must be that widow in the mourning clothes.
Who are you?
We must inform His Majesty.
That won't do.
My father is really helpless.
You didn't know? This ahjumma is her highness the princess.
You must find her at all costs. Our family's fate depends on this matter.
And please tell Hwa In to come to the palace tomorrow.
Only the dead will keep their lips sealed.
Who are you saying has died?
The daughter-in-law of this noble household, her highness the princess, hung herself.
When my daughter-in-law is found, wherever it may be, and whoever sees, make sure to kill her.
- Let's go.
- How can I run away by myself?
Please go first. I'll follow close behind!
Please spare my sister-in-law.
That's impossible. We cannot endanger our family just for your sister-in-law's sake.
Please die, Your Highness.
Find Hwa In.
Secretly keep a close eye on the Left State Councillor.
If he kills Princess Hwa In, bring that evidence to me.
The fact that Your Highness is alive will be trouble to his majesty, the king.
Perhaps ... a true revolt will happen.
I'm telling you to start living for yourself!
I have no reason to live.
We all just live like this!
It would have been better, even for your sake, if I had died.
Like you, I'm already a dead person.
From now on, I'm not "Your Highness,"
I'm going to live as a commoner.
Why do you try to push me to an even more perilous cliff edge?
If it brings death, I will be the one to die in your place.
And if that's impossible, I will die with you.
If you don't give up on me to the end, I will disappear.
Let's do a job together. It's the only way to save my sister-in-law.
This Myeon Sa Cheol Gwon grants you a pardon from any crime,
as long as it isn't treason.
Haven't you seen Dae Yeop?
Behead the ringleader of the treason, Kim Je Nam!
If we are caught now, everyone you know will not be safe.
You were my enemy too! You were that bastard's son.
Princess Hwa In is alive.
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
We're going to leave this place so start packing our things.
- Why exactly are you doing this?
- I don't want to be entangled with you even for a moment.
If I told you to leave, I thought you'd make all kinds of excuses and not leave! That's why we are going to leave.
We captured the women as you requested,
at the latest they should arrive by tonight.
Without your orders, no one will even see the shadow of the princess.
Are you that worried?
Even if it's by myself, I must go in.
Answer me. Do you want to live?
Yes, I want to live.
Suicide, you say?
So you aren't a princess any longer. You are just a woman.
The one whom I want to protect with my life.
I heard your sister-in-law's drawing skill is extra-ordinary.
Hey, this will bring money, I tell you! Erotica!
What has the police bureau been doing, allowing such vile books to circulate?
I think I've seen the drawings somewhere. Please trust and leave this to me, Hyeong-nim.
It's that man. He's the man who made the drawings.
Just forget everything and live as you've been doing.
I intended to live my life as Ba Wu, forgetting both my enemy and about vengeance.
But your family has made me into Lord Kim Je Nam's grandson Kim Dae Seok.
All of that resentment, and your family... you gave all of that up for my sake?
No matter the cost... I'll make sure to return to your side in one piece.
The left police division conducted the investigation, so surely the ledger will be in the hands of the left police chief.
Kim Je Nam's eldest grandson is alive.
The criminal locked in the royal investigation bureau is Kim Je Nam's grandson, Kim Dae Seok.
I understand there is a second ledger.
Why do you think you are here?
It must be because I am of use. Please restore my name.
Pass the military service exam.
Find a way to kill that rascal.
If you truly support Hwa In and me, prove it.
Be my sword and shield at my side.
You are to report every little thing your father does to me.
Restore the status of everyone involved in Kim Je Nam's case during the ousting of Prince Yeongchang!
It seems that he is definitely hiding something.
That man is a bait. A bait to lure in Yi I Cheom.
You have until the incense burns completely to fire three shots.
During the rifle shooting test,
disguise it as an accidental firing and shoot Kim Dae Seok.
You have until the incense burns completely to fire three shots.
Fire the shot!
Look here, are you all right?
You can't get up.
Stand aside.
I have one shot left.
You're low. Aim a little higher.
Shoot.
Episode 13
Minister of Defense, you must question the culprit.
Make sure to find out if it is something he did by himself,
or if there's someone behind him.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Look here. Are you awake?
- Where is...?
- It's the physician's quarters of the training hall.
I guess you don't remember?
I remember up until being hit by the rifle shot.
It was really a close call.
See me for a moment.
-  Accept this.
- What is this?
Wear this underneath. It will be helpful.
I am alive because of you.
I won't forget this kindness.
Thank His Majesty. I only followed his orders.
How are you feeling?
It's bearable.
More importantly, what happened to my military service exam?
You've passed, so don't worry.
It hasn't been announced yet so just know for yourself.
- Yes.
- Don't overexert yourself for the time being.
Are you all right?
Your father started it first.
Why is Cha Dol's father so late?
You go and take a look outside.
He's coming now.
Father.
Did your test go well?
(using casual speech)
Cha Dol, you should use honorific speech with your father.
He'll get better as we go.
- Did your test go well?
- Yes.
You look very tired. Go on and rest.
Yes.
The fate of the family name rests on his shoulders, so it won't be easy for him.
So make sure he is well taken care of. Do you understand?
Yes.
You were shot by a rifle?
- Let me take a look.
- It's fine. I'm all right.
This is a real problem. You could die if you keep this up.
Man, you can't even escape, as you used to before.
We might end up as sitting ducks here. What shall we do now?
What else can we do? We have to return the favor.
If they mess with either me or my family, they must at least expect death in return.
At least then, they will think twice about it in the future.
We should have used this opportunity to kill him.
He is quite resilient.
Still, it probably served as plenty of warning.
You look ... are you all right?
Is it that obvious?
Don't worry. It's nothing serious.
I understand you're covering this because you don't want to worry your family.
But occasionally lean on your family, when you're going through a difficult time.
It's in their best interest too.
Please rest. I will bring you your dinner table.
You pretended to not notice?
It's so obvious that he's hiding his injuries to not worry his family.
I just couldn't bring myself to ask him about it.
But he injured his ribs.
Who is going to care for his injuries?
I'll leave that in your hands.
Yes, I understand.
The left state councillor will likely continue to harass Cha Dol's father.
What should we do?
Good work.
I will call you when the time is right. I want you to lie low until things calm down.
Yes, my lord.
Are you just letting him go?
What are you doing here?
Aren't you overstepping your bounds?
His majesty will not stand still for this.
What if he doesn't? What can he do?
Under whose authority did you let him free?
Your Majesty, we merely dealt with the problem according to the law.
According to the Gyeongguk code of laws, someone who accidentally injured another person
is to receive floggings, and to pay for the funeral expenses for the victim.
Accident? Accident?!
Yes, Your Majesty.
The man dropped his bullets, and in his panic he accidentally—
I will interrogate him personally,
so go, arrest, and bring him back again at once!
You must not do this, Your Majesty!
Without definitive evidence, we cannot handle this with personal feelings.
Please hear our pleas, Your Majesty!
- Please hear our pleas!
Whose subjects are you anyway?!
How could you say such harsh things?
Please spare us from your wrath, Your Majesty.
- Please spare us from your wrath!
Get out of my sight.
I said leave!
Jung Yeong, are you outside?
My head feels as if it's splitting open.
Hurry... hurry and get me my medicine.
His majesty's madness is getting more and more severe.
I'm concerned about the future of Joseon.
I'm worried if it'll get worse...
I don't know if we should consider having the crown prince start a regency on his behalf.
- Already?
- Proxy ruling
Now, now. This isn't the place for this.
Whether it's about making the crown prince a regent or the abdication of the throne, let's discuss this in the meeting chamber.
Have Kim Dae Seok and Yi Dae Yeop come see me immediately.
Yes, Your Majesty!
Please be wary of my father.
Don't worry.
- I'm off, Mother.
- Please be careful.
Don't worry.
I'll be back soon.
Please return safely.
Have a safe trip.
Your Majesty, it's time to leave for your Confucian lessons.
Your Majesty...
Lift your heads.
You worthless fools.
I was certain I told you to report to me every little thing your father did.
What were you doing when your father planned to kill him?
And you, will you continue to be a victim your whole life?
Now that your title is restored and Hwa In is hidden away safely...
It seems you two have grown lazy and slothful.
Shall I call Hwa In in immediately and reveal everything that's happened?
If that were to happen, Hwa In will probably become a Buddhist nun,
and spend the rest of her days in a temple.
Shall I make her that way for you?
The choice is in the hands of you two.
What will you do?
Allow me to leave the palace at the end of my shift.
I will come up with a plan.
And you?
Allow Kim Dae Seok to return home at the end of his shift.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I will give you two weeks. Have a solution ready by then.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
- You may leave now.
Yes.
Why haven't you answered yet?
Have you given up on Hwa In?
What? Are you afraid that I will use your information to kill your father?
Don't worry. What I desire...
is for your father to willingly retire, just as his predecessor Jeong In Hong did before him.
Things may have gotten messy because of Hwa In...
But your father was someone who helped me ascend the throne and has supported me since then.
Therefore, it is no small burden for me to decide to kill him instead.
It's not as if your father would quietly die either.
It would only spark a war that would result in chaos and confusion in the royal court.
Rather than going that route, if I could have your father's weakness,
I think having him quietly resign would be the best method.
What will you do?
I will follow Your Majesty's orders.
Good. You've made a difficult choice.
I will remember that you and Hwa In had an affection for each other since childhood.
You may leave now.
What's wrong? Does it seem he doesn't believe me?
It's not that, Your Majesty.
I was merely concerned.
People will believe in what they want to believe.
This is the only way he can win Hwa In.
He will have to trust me, even if he doesn't want to.
What did he say?
Don't delude yourself.
Do you think we're friends?
To you, I'm the son of your enemy, and to me,
you're the foe who is trying to destroy my household.
If it were not for the princess
I would have personally killed you.
Princess.
Did you look for me?
Sit down.
When you used to take part in the smuggling trade,
to your knowledge, where was the silk sold?
I heard that it was sold to merchants in the marketplace...
It's not as if there are only one or two fabric stores.
That—
Back when we used to live at the left state councillor's house,
do you know which fabric store they used to frequent to buy silk and clothing?
Yes, it was in the marketplace at—
W-wait-
the left state councillor's house?
Why do you want to know about the shop they used to buy from?
There's something I want to look into.
Your Highness, surely you don't plan to go there in person?
It's too dangerous to step outside now. I will go in your place.
Wouldn't the shop owner recognize your face?
Well that may be true, but still...
Aigoo! Welcome! Take your pick.
Your wares are lackluster. Let's go, Sister-in-law.
Excuse me. Are you not able to find what you were looking for?
Nothing like this.
Do you have anything from overseas?
I do.
This way!
Over here, miladies.
- Wow!
- Now, please come in.
Now!
How much do you need?
For starters, I'd like five rolls of each color.
If my in-laws are pleased, I will come back again.
Oh my, it seems you're preparing for a wedding.
Then you will need to prepare a wedding gift* to the groom's family. On top of that, new blankets and clothes...
(typically silk)
Oh dear, I think five rolls will be too few for that.
Are the fabrics in this room all you can offer?
No, this isn't everything. We only need your order,
and I will have everything ready.
Mother!
What did you buy so many things for?
This isn't a lot at all.
Since it's spring, I should make new clothes for the family.
And I thought we could use some spring blankets, so I got them in advance.
You're right. Good, I understand.
- Bring them inside.
- Wow!
It's all thanks to your brother.
I got it already! It's all because of my brother.
Of course, of course. It's all thanks to your impressive son. Ow!
Stop, before I break your wrists.
- Move aside!
- There you go again!
Please try to have some dignity.
How could you say you'll break my wrists?
What will you do if your daughter-in-law overhears you?
You... just put away the silk.
That's weird. I was sure I put it here...
What did you do with it?
- What?
- The land deed for the property in Icheon.
There's nobody in this house who would think to touch this chest besides you.
Am I wrong?
- You're right.
- I'm right?
You crazy... are you in your right mind?
- Have you lost your mind?
- Then what was I supposed to do?
I've already had my wedding. Do you want me to live as a widow?
I need to do whatever I can to emancipate Orabeoni Chil Seong and bring him here, right?
- Even so, how could you take the land deed?
- Then what should I have done?
Neither you nor Brother would do anything to help me.
Should I also forget about him too?
Fine. When your brother returns, I'll consult with him.
So give me the land deed now.
I don't have it.
I've already sent it to Cheonan.
What? When?
It's been some time. By now I should've gotten at least a message or someone with news.
What are we supposed to do? If your brother found out about this...!
It's not as if his name is written on this silk.
How can we prove that these rolls of silk were the same ones that the left state councillor smuggled in from Ming?
Because of the northern barbarians, all of the land routes to Ming have been blocked off.
How else could they import these fabrics?
It must've gotten here through smuggling.
Furthermore, the left state counsillor couldn't have received any bribery from elsewhere.
How else would he procure the funds to commit treason?
You may bow to each other now!
I hope you live happily Chil Seong!
Wait...
Why is that scoundrel coming from here?
Why are you doing this to me? Who are you?
Your bride, Yeon Ok's brother.
What?
Not me.
Why were you coming out from there?
Her family had their titles restored and became nobles...
but I am a peasant, am I not?
I was emancipated thanks to her. I couldn't just return empty-handed...
I don't want to hear it. Go back immediately, and tell them you're quitting.
I don't want to.
- What?
- I don't have any money, but if there's anything I can do,
I'd like to do it for Yeon Ok and her family's sake.
- Please, just let me do this.
- I can't. It's too dangerous.
If I find out anything, I'll pull out of the place immediately.
I told you, I won't allow it! Quit that place immediately.
- Let's go home.
- Hey, wait just a second.
Doesn't he look so earnest? Let's at least hear him out.
By chance, do you know where the silk comes from?
I'm still a new hire so I don't know that much yet, but I will look into it!
Then... tell me something about the owner.
I don't know much, but I heard he can't control himself when it comes to gambling.
Gambling?
Then... me too!
Let me borrow some urgent money.
- How much?
- Just give me five nyang.
Five nyang, you say?
Let's take care of the promissory note first.
Now, let's see them.
- Sorry to see your loss.
- Ah, seriously!
Ah, sorry to do this.
Excuse me, let me borrow some money in advance.
Do you have any collateral to offer?
I'll offer my fabric store's wares for it.
Your fabric store, you say...
For two hundred rolls of cotton, I'll give you a hundred nyang.
Hund—A hundred nyang?
Isn't that a little too much?
You can just win and pay it back. Don't be so stingy!
I got it. Give it to me.
Now... first the promissory note.
Now, here you go.
- Here you go.
- Thanks. And here you go.
Ah, I lost again!
Excuse me.
Let me sign another note.
How much will you give me for a hundred rolls of silk?
Hund—a hundred rolls?!
Come now, don't do that.
- You should stop here.
- Yes, you should stop.
No, no, no! I've decided. So... how much will it be?
I really shouldn't do this...
Wow, what a man!
Now... you should pay up on your debt, right?
Gambling debt isn't real debt.
What?
- What are you doing?
- I have another!
- Boys!
- Yes!
What's this?
One, two... move for a second. Three, four...
- Hey, boys!
- Yes!
Move! Move!
Move, I say!
You'd better move!
Hey, load up!
I'll make good use of the silk.
And...
I'm telling you this out of pity.
Don't gamble anymore.
And worry about selling your silk instead.
Careful, careful! And take everything!
I hope we can continue working together, Hyeong-nim!
Here!
Yes...
What are your next plans?
I've emptied his storehouse.
So now I have to make him fill it up again.
Oh, you're here.
I'd like to see the silk from overseas.
Si-silk?
How much do you need?
As I mentioned before, my sister-in-law will have a wedding soon.
And my mother-in-law will have her 61st birthday feast soon, so I need quite a lot of it.
Can you have them ready right away?
Well the thing is... I've come across a situation.
It's hard to provide them at this moment,  do you need them that urgently?
What a predicament you put me in!
I've trusted your word alone and already informed all of my in-laws.
I suppose it's not too late to find a different store.
Wa-wait! Please wait just a moment.
No matter what it takes, I'll prepare what you need, my lady.
Cost is not an issue, so make sure to have them ready for me.
Yes, of course! Don't you worry!
He's taken the bait.
The silk storage chest is empty, so they will have no alternative but to bring in new supplies to fill it.
Thank you and I'm sorry.
Please leave the work to me in the future.
No. Just as you have taken care of me,
I will do anything to take care of you.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Truly, you are beautiful.
Did you just realize that?
Now that I'm looking at you...
Your forehead is smooth and beautiful and the line of your nose is high.
The lips too ...
There is no one more beautiful than you in all of the eight provinces of Joseon.
At least, not in my eyes.
Mother is waiting.
Wait, let's go together!
♫  The hand which hugged me  ♫
♫  is gently caught in my collar  ♫
♫  it hurts.  ♫
- Go right in.
- All right.
- You're back.
- I'm sorry. Am I very late?
Not at all.
Let's do it together.
You!  What have you been doing since early this morning?
Doesn't it bother you even a little that your mother-in-law is starving?
Mother, be dignified!
You stay out of it.
They say that if you don't bring in a good daughter-in-law, the family will be ruined.
I suppose I will be the first to starve.
I'm sorry.  I will do it so that it will be ready soon.
Mother, let's go in.
Why are you sitting like this again?
This is what life as a new bride is like. So don't be too upset over it.
There was still so much time left before supper!
Hey.  Eat this. It will make you feel better.
Instead of doing that, try tasting this.
I don't have the appetite.
Try it once, even if you don't feel like it.  I ran around for a half hour to buy this.
What did you spend a half hour getting?
What ... dried persimmon?
Court lady ... no ... Yeo Ju Daek, you like dried persimmons.
This is a Sangju dried persimmon. It's really delicious.
When I'm feeling down, if I eat something delicious, it makes me feel better.
Flower.   Dried persimmon.
Her highness the consort loved this.
Follow me.
Is it today? Isn't the day too bright?
Her highness the consort?  Who is she?
Would you cry at a funeral without knowing who died!
(idiom for "Why are you so clueless?")
She is the princess' mother.
- Ah, Ba Wu's mother-in-law.
- Do you have a death wish?
Why? When the princess acquired a mother-in-law and  sister-in-law,
Ba Wu would have made some in-laws as well.
Then is the king "father-in-law?"
Oh, is that that how that works?
How can you do that?  How can you? How dare you speak of the king that way?
All right. All right.
- So, which highness?
- Her highness, the Rank 2 Noble Royal Consort.
So you want the princess and that royal consort to meet?
Yes. Isn't there a way?
She's a noblewoman who lives in the palace. What can we do about that?
It would be faster to talk to Ba Wu instead.
If I wanted to talk to Ba Wu, I would've just done that instead. Why would I be wasting time with you?
As to that, well, I am trustworthy
and we also have some things we need to work out.
Forget it. It's fine so be that trustworthy brute and chop us some firewood.
Oh, oh, oh.  You'll be in big trouble if you go near the palace.
We're done talking.  Here ...
Court Lady Jo!
- Have you been well?
- Yes, ma'am.  There is a rumor—
Don't be concerned. I am not a ghost.
Is her highness the consort well and in peace?
How could she be?
After the princess died, she has constantly been in her sickbed.
Please eat.
How bad is she?
Although every day she takes the special tonic
mixed by the king's personal physician per his Majesty's order,
it doesn't seem she is getting any better.
When it's her spirit and not her body that is hurt,
what's the use of any drug?
Do you miss her highness the consort a lot?
It's not too late to at least send her a letter.
I didn't hide this whole time...
because I didn't realize how great her devastation would be, right?
If I were to make a mistake, even my mother could be endangered.
The king knows everything now.
What could possibly go wrong?
Royal Mother
Greetings from an unworthy daughter.
You must be so heartbroken because of this undeserving girl.
I don't know what I can do about all of my impiety.
I don't know how to seek forgiveness.
I am in a safe place, so I pray you will not worry.
If you will stay strong,
I will survive to see you again.
Except for her highness the consort, no one must know of the existence of this letter.
In the event the whereabouts of this letter becomes a problem,
you won't be safe either. Do you understand what I am saying?
Yes, ma'am.  I will bear that in mind.
What are you saying? Court Lady Jo met you?
Yes.  I was told to deliver this letter secretly to her highness the consort.
- Is Court Lady Choi outside?
- Yes, ma'am.
Find the deputy administration officer, Kim Ja Jeom, and tell him to see me immediately.
Yes, ma'am.
Deliver it to her highness the consort.
What did you just say?
Did you say Court Lady Jo?
Yes, Your Highness.
All right. You may leave.
Hwa In.
Your Highness, please compose yourself.
You could collapse.
I told you, I saw the letter that Princess Hwa In wrote myself.
It was a letter written to her own mother, and it clearly said,
that she is somewhere safe now, so her mother shouldn't worry.
So where could Princess Hwa In be safe inside the capital?
Someone who has the connections to hide Princess Hwa In,
it can only Kim Dae Seok, isn't that true?
So what has happened?
Didn't you say that you met with Kim Dae Seok before?
Did you actually meet that man?
How could I dare to lie to you?
When I last met with him, he said he parted with the princess the very day he left my home.
And he clearly told me that he doesn't know what happened to her after that.
You are truly frustrating.
Are you really unable to distinguish whether he spoke the truth or a lie?
I apologize.
Please go meet with him again at his home immediately.
She is definitely hiding in his home
and if not, at the very least
he will know where she is staying.
So please find out properly this time. Properly.
Yes, my lady.
I'm Kim Ja Jeom, the deputy administration officer of the ministry of defense.
You look like the Royal Guard.
On whose command are you guarding this home?
Do you reside in this home?
Ah, yes. May I ask who... ?
Tell him that Kim Ja Jeom, the deputy administration officer of the minister of defense, wants to see him.
Yes.
Oh, oh, big disaster.
That guy is here.
That guy? Which one?
That guy who used slave hunters to capture the princess and Court Lady Jo.
You two stay here, and do not budge. You must never come out! Never!
What brings you all the way here?
I was just passing by.
A pretty nice place for a home that you've prepared rather quickly.
Yes, well... let's go inside.
Who is that man?
He's a friend who looks after the household. This way, please.
And who is living over there?
That's the ladies' quarters, where my mother and my sister are living.
- I should greet your mother since I am here.
- Right now—
She is out right now.
Yes? And your sister, too?
Yes, they went out together.
Let us go inside.
What happened?
Ba Wu took him to his room.
Imagine if I wasn't the one who happened to meet him at the door.
Hold on. Isn't it about time for Cha Dol's grandmother and aunt to return?
It doesn't matter if those two meet that man, does it?
It's not that.
What if they say something useless?
What brings you all the way to my home?
I was just passing by, and wondered how you were doing.
And I was worried about your gunshot wound, and whether it was healing well.
Gosh, you are worried about me.
I am so grateful I don't know what to do with myself.
Your words are making me sad.
If you want to discuss origins, you and your family are all Westerners like me, aren't you?
Ah, yes. Well.
After all, if not for us Westerners, would it have been possible for your identity to be restored to you?
And, in order to free your aunt* from confinement ...
(Queen Inmok)
It was we, the Westerners who made unceasing effort, isn't that true?
Yes.
And now that you've passed the examination and become installed in your office,
time has come for you to do your part as a Westerner.
I am grateful for your words, but I am still lacking in many ways.
Untrue.
You have already gained the favor of His Majesty, haven't you?
That is enough to confirm your abilities.
So begin working with us to push out Yi I Cheom.
Getting rid of Yi I Cheom fulfills your personal objective of taking revenge of your family's mortal enemy.
In addition, isn't it our duty as noblemen to do this for the sake of Joseon's future?
Yes, your words are correct.
So about that,
Princess Hwa In.
There is no better weapon than Princess Hwa In to get rid of Yi I Cheom, is there?
What do you mean
by that, all of a sudden?
Where is Princess Hwa In? You know, don't you?
No.
How can I know that?
As I told you earlier, I do not know anything more about Princess Hwa In.
Is that true?
Why would I lie?
If I knew where Princess Hwa In was,
I would be seeking revenge against Yi I Cheom. Why would I be sitting here?
I even got shot by a rifle because of him.
So you just came right back here after hearing Kim Dae Seok tell you that he really doesn't know?
About that...
I did suspect that Kim Dae Seok was hiding something.
But it's not as if I can search his home. So there wasn't anything I could do.
It's not that you couldn't do anything, it's that you have no skills.
I will check it again.
But, aside from that,
the fact that that home is being guarded by the Royal Guard
is what bothers me even more.
Perhaps His Majesty is the one who hid Princess Hwa In in that home?
You are really too much.
How could you hide this even from me?
Since that child died, every single day has been hell for me.
My heart was already broken that she was a young widow.
And her having died so futilely made me pity her so much.
I felt that everything was my fault,
so my only thought was to follow her in death...
And after seeing me like this every day, you still didn't tell me?
You cannot be this cold-hearted.
You cannot be this cruel.
I was in a situation in which I had no choice but to do this.
Of course you were.
I'm sure that you would not
have made a living child into a dead child without reason.
But I am that child's mother.
And that was all the more reason I could not tell you.
A mother dives into water or fire for the sake of her child.
So if you had known that Hwa In was alive,
you would have immediately set out to find her.
And that would have put Hwa In's life into further danger.
In that case,
even while knowing that she is alive, must I pretend to not know...
in order for Hwa In to be safe?
It was the left state councillor who said that Hwa In committed suicide.
He deceived me and the entire council.
If he finds out she is still alive,
I'm sure you can guess what he will try to do.
I did hide her in a safe place.
But I have not yet devised a way to completely stop the left state councillor.
I cannot tell you more, so please understand.
You must miss her highness, the Royal Consort Yun very much, don't you?
I am sorry that I couldn't tell you, even while knowing how deep your sorrow was.
But please understand that it was the last resort in order to ensure Hwa In's safety.
And please believe that I am still doing my best to continue to ensure her safety.
You don't have to say that.
If I don't trust you, whom could I trust, Your Majesty?
When I think of Hwa In,
my heart also feels heavy, as if a boulder is tied to it.
I know... how precious Hwa In was to you.
I know that better than anyone.
How you used to let Hwa In ride on your back
during horse play,
I can still remember that image vividly.
I will trust that you will protect Hwa In no matter what.
And I won't ask you any questions anymore.
But I do have one request, so please hear it.
Tell me.
Hwa In...
Just once...
Please allow me to meet her, just once.
I miss her so much.
I cannot hold myself back now that I know she is alive.
Please pity me
and let me at least see just her face.
Please show me your grace.
You know that Royal Consort Yun is Hwa In's mother, don't you?
Yes.
Please find a way for her and Hwa In to meet.
Mother!
Mother.
What's the fuss? You can't behave prudently?
Prudent, or whatever.
- Orabeoni Chil Seong appeared in my dream.
- What?
He told me to wait as he will return home soon.
Aigoo, how nice for you.
I no longer have to see you sigh as if the floor is collapsing.
When he comes, I should surprise him.
What should I wear?
Oh, my head hurts.
What will people think?
I can't let her keep behaving that way.
I wish there were lessons for conduct.
I wish I could send her there.
Mother.
What?
If you leave it to me, I will give it a try.
You?
How regretful, when you almost made it.
Please try it again.
How many more times?
Ah, ah, my neck and legs hurt so much.
Quickly, focus my gaze at a point far away,
one, two...
I think I'm doing it. I think it's working.
Shall we use chopsticks?
When we chew food, we shouldn't make any noise.
You should chew with your mouth closed.
You are making noise too, Mother!
I am not.
It doesn't look good when you open your mouth with food inside.
You should not talk while eating.
I'm done eating!
T-That.. That girl!
What's up with her?
Sister-in-law...
Are you all right?
Yes?
Please sit down.
It's hard, isn't it?
To live as a noblewoman isn't always great.
Because there are a lot of things you have to give up for reputation and dignity.
To be honest, reputation and dignity don't feed you.
I want to act like a lady too, you know.
But I lived as a peasant since I was very young
I don't even remember being a noble.
I know it's hard, but you shouldn't be scorned
because of the past that you and your mother had to endure, should you?
Moreover... You need to consider the man
you are going to get married to.
It will be hard, but at least for his sake,
try your best.
The silk will arrive soon.
Thanks for your help.
Don't mention it. It's for our family after all.
Is Yeon Ok doing well?
She's well. Take care of yourself.
If it gets risky, get yourself out of there first. All right?
Don't worry, Hyeong-nim!
Long time no see!
You  are... ? Hey, hurry and block him.
Get them!
He has a no-in*.
(A permit issued by government offices for travel and selling)
Merchant's permit
- Is that it?
- Yeah.
The Chief of Left Police's seal is on it.
All right.
I will take care of things here. Hurry and take this to the king.
Exclusive right to trade in cotton at Jemulpo Port, Hanyang,
1620, 1st lunar month, 14th day
signed: Chief of Left Police Yi Won Yeop
Imagine that the one backing the smugglers was the chief of the left police bureau.
Yi I Cheom was acting so high and mighty about how upright he was.
But it seems he had a hidden back pocket.
Hypocritical old man.
So how should I settle this situation?
Keep it and use it when I'm driving out Yi I Cheom,
or immediately dismiss the chief of left police bureau from his office?
I will do what you want.
I heard that to capture a commander, you must first shoot his horse.
Since we cannot know what the left state councillor will do when given more time,
I think it will be correct to settle this situation immediately, Your Majesty.
For violating our country's laws
and giving protection to criminal smugglers,
the Chief of Left  Police will be removed from his office!
It appears that the left state councillor isn't quite as powerful as he used to be.
After all, he couldn't protect his eldest son.
The evidence is so clear, and as with the banned book from last time,
the left chief of police's mistake is just too great, isn't it?
Even so, before, he would have found some way to avoid this.
His excellency the left state councillor is not one to just allow something like this to happen.
So is this your work?
Let me ask you something, too.
Did you get me shot by a rifle?
It's a dog-eat-dog world anyway, isn't it?
You're trying to kill me even while I'm doing nothing. So I should at least try struggling against it.
What?
You thought I was a mouse you could easily handle,
but now that I've bitten you on the nose, did it surprise you?
Don't expect His Majesty to
protect you indefinitely.
And you, too,
should not expect your power and authority to last forever.
Didn't I tell you to forbid the smuggling for the time being?
I meant to do it just once more, because there was a situation with my in-laws, and then...
I told you many times to not be weak before wealth.
Show self-restraint.
I am sorry, Father.
Bring me liquor!
Do they know who I am?
Bring me liquor immediately!
My lord, you should return home.
What are you doing, not bringing the liquor!
You've worked hard, Hyeong-nim.
Imagine that I am benefitting from you people.
- You worked hard. Accept this drink.
- Yes.
Look at this man, he is flipping out now that he sees liquor.
Once you get married, it won't be easy to drink like this.
So pour it down now.
- Yes.
- Cheers.
How dare he. Does he know who I am?
Is he someone you know?
It's nothing. Let's go.
Are you looking down on me too, because I was removed from my position?
I asked you who that man is.
He is the brother-in-law of Kim Dae Seok, who is said to have been the mole at the fabric store.
- Capture him right now.
- My lord.
I told you to capture him right now, didn't I?
Please spare me.
Please spare me!
Spare me...
You insect! Because of you people ... I was....!
Please spare me, my lord, please spare me.
This dirty scum, how dare you!?
My lord, please stop.
Out of my way!
My lord!
How dare you? Who do you think you are?
Chil Seong is dead, they said.
What is going on?
W-well...
Chil Seong is...
He died, they said.
Chil Seong?
Hyeong-nim! Hyeong-nim! Hyeong-nim!
- Ba Wu.
Where is Chil Seong?
I asked you, where is Chil Seong?
Over there...
Is he your family member?
My brother-in-law.
The chief of police said he saw an unidentified assailant running away holding a sword.
It appears to be that man's doing.
That is a lie!
He did it. That man,
someone saw him holding a sword with blood on it.
He said the blood is from his battle with the unidentified assailant.
We will tell you the results of the investigation later, so please leave.
Please return home, my lord.
Let's go, Hyeong-nim.
He was your brother-in-law?
An insect happened to bother me,
so I stepped on it.
Out of my way.
That is enough. Back off now.
Are you serious, damn it?
If someone is of a lower class, do they look like insects to you, too?
I told you to back off!
He is my hyeong.
Yes.
We are mortal enemies after all, just as you said.
One of us will have to die
for this sickening ill-fated relationship to finally end.
There is no one more beautiful in all eight provinces of Joseon.
♫  They say this is how the world is  ♫
♫  But it's not only today that things don't go my way  ♫
There is one less than when they entered the palace?
Who dares to hide in the palace after entering among the band of entertainers?
I must find out.
What is it that you want?
Please give up on Kim Dae Seok.
You look like you would actually commit treason if it comes to it.
When will we see its effects?
It won't be long.
Now that His Majesty has collapsed, the world immediately belongs to them.
You must not go. It is the left state councillor's plot to kill you.
This is the last chance that I am giving you.
You must return alive.
Trust in me and wait for me.
♫  The stone rolls on  ♫