=Ancient Workplace, Love Handbook=
=Episode 9=
(Why is he here?)
(Did he stay here all night
to watch over me?)
Are you feeling unwell?
I feel refreshed.
Wait for me.
I was worried you'd be hungry.
I've prepared food for you.
Just this?
You had a fever last night.
You need to eat something light.
But...
I want hotpot.
Snail noodles.
Stinky tofu.
Spicy gluten is fine.
I'll do it myself.
Take it slow.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the office.
The physician said
though you didn't hurt
your muscles or bones,
you still needed to rest for a few days.
I don't feel unwell though.
Could it be
that I've suffered the legendary
internal injury?
Lie back down.
(Arrangement Office)
Miss Xu,
Mr. Yan asked you to rest at home.
I'm fine.
He's making a big deal out of it.
If Mr. Yan hadn't arrived in time,
who knows how badly Wei Yingying
would have hurt you?
Forget it. It's a blessing in disguise.
There's a vacancy,
and Yunxin got promoted.
But Miss Yunxin
doesn't seem happy about it.
She looks like
she's got a lot on her mind.
I bought flowers for you.
I said I didn't want them.
- Take them.
- Why is it always flowers?
Finally caught you.
- They're hard to buy.
- Miss Xu.
It took me ages to find them.
Please accept them.
Let go of her!
Miss Xu!
Take them.
Are these your favorite flowers?
Miss, he's...
He's the one
who's been bullying Yunxin.
Why aren't you resting at home?
What are you doing here?
Looks like someone else
will need to rest now.
Brother?
Bro...
Well.
Mr. Jun, I'm sorry.
So,
you're the pervert.
No.
The one giving gifts to Yunxin.
(Yuwen Jun, first son of the City Lord)
He said it was fine.
You've got quite a kick.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You should leave.
I'm not leaving.
There's no chance for us anymore.
Don't worry.
I don't need your help.
What are they talking about?
It's a long story.
Ten years.
Childhood sweethearts.
Then why has Yunxin
been avoiding him?
Are Mr. Jun's feelings one-sided?
But Mr. Jun
can't even speak properly,
yet Yunxin understands him.
They're quite the match.
Very sweet.
What?
Nothing.
Then
should we help them?
How?
Who just refused them?
Now, you're quite happy.
Are you free tomorrow?
Yes.
Ever since Wei Yingying was dismissed,
there has been
so much work
in and around the office.
I'm so busy I can hardly keep up.
You should take care of yourself.
What I mean is
you're now part
of the management team at the office.
You should share my burden.
There's a big event tomorrow.
You must be there.
Do I need to prepare anything?
Just show up.
(Junling Pavilion)
Jun, you know Miss Zhong
has her reasons.
I'm definitely going to help Yunxin
all the way.
Jun, let's go somewhere tomorrow.
Is Yunxin asking me out?
Xinglan accidentally hurt you.
Tomorrow, she'll apologize to you.
Yan.
Miss Xu has a hot temper.
How will you live your life
in the future?
(Arrangement Office)
What's going on?
Is the big event you mentioned
playing mahjong?
- Yunxin.
We...
We need one more player.
Right, right.
- One of Characters.
This should be what you want.
Nine of Bamboo.
I can't afford your tile.
I won.
So fast?
Yunxin, you're amazing.
Because I can do math.
I was careless.
Continue.
Seven of Characters.
I won.
Three of Characters.
How is it possible to win so fast?
Self-draw.
All of one suit.
I won again.
You took a tile,
but you discarded it to help me.
You could've won,
but you gave your tiles to me.
When I was surely a winner,
you still helped me.
I...
Young Master, you don't need
to be so kind to me.
I...
Yunxin.
Then I'll head back first.
I planned to defeat Yunxin,
make her cry for help,
and then have Mr. Jun save her.
Unexpectedly...
We were outmatched.
It's okay; there will be other ways.
(Niu Dazhuang Solves a Cold Case)
(The plan failed.)
(I need to come up with another plan.)
Something's off with her.
(Supplement to Valuable Prescriptions)
What's wrong with her?
(Niu Dazhuang Solves a Cold Case)
Miss Zhong.
This month's supplies have arrived.
Please check them, Miss Zhong.
This makes it easier.
Likes me.
Doesn't like me.
Jun.
What are you doing?
Yunxin
probably really doesn't like me.
Impossible.
If she didn't like you,
why would she keep
the little tiger from you?
Really?
She's still keeping our love token.
I can only help you this far.
After all, pursuing a girl
requires strategy.
You know it.
I...
Brother.
Speaking of strategy,
I can offer you some pointers.
Yan, please teach me.
♪Memories pass away like water♪
♪Time flows through the years♪
♪Deep feelings in the heart
are unspeakable♪
♪Endless love reveals in the snow♪
♪A soft sigh through reincarnations,
a love lasting a thousand years♪
♪Amid the myriad beings,
separations come♪
♪Awaking from dreams,
only longing remains♪
♪Life is but a fleeting dream,
like clouds and smoke♪
♪A thousand-year promise♪
♪Through the changes of time,
love remains unchanged♪
♪The red thread of fate ties us♪
♪Tightly together♪
♪May my live be exchanged
for your peaceful years♪
♪In memories♪
♪It's not just a thousand-year dream♪
♪Turning into eternity♪
♪The starry sky of longing♪
♪Beauty and white snow
reflects the parting♪
♪Moonlight scatters among the stars♪
♪The vow echoes in the heartstrings♪
♪Awakening from dreams,
waiting feels like eternal sleep♪
♪The burning vow,
difficult to meet again♪
♪Together, the bond deepens♪
♪Amid the myriad beings,
separations wound♪
♪Dreaming of the past
brings joy to the heart♪
♪A thousand-year promise♪
♪Through the changes of time,
love remains unchanged♪
♪The red thread of fate ties us♪
♪Tightly together♪
♪May my life be exchanged
for your peaceful years♪
♪In memories♪
♪It's not just a thousand-year dream♪
♪Turning into eternity♪
♪The starry sky of longing♪
♪A thousand-year promise♪
♪Through the changes of time,
love remains unchanged♪
♪The red thread of fate ties us♪
♪Tightly together♪
♪May my life be exchanged
for your peaceful years♪
♪In memories♪
♪It's not just a thousand-year dream♪
♪Turning into eternity♪
♪The starry sky of longing♪