=Ancient Workplace, Love Handbook=
=Episode 5=
(I can't ask him for it.)
(Peace and Eternity)
(But what if I accidentally
wander into his room)
(and the ledger
fell into my hands?)
(That'd be fine, right?)
(He didn't even lock the door.)
(He's so fair-skinned.)
Song Heng?
Leave everything for tomorrow.
I want to rest early tonight.
(I need to find the ledger quickly.)
(I can't let him find out.)
Where is it?
(Tao Te Ching)
Why isn't it here?
Not here either.
(Ledger)
Are you looking for this?
Yes, that's it.
How did you...
(Running into my room
in the middle of the night.)
(What exactly does she want?)
Good night, Mr. Yan. Rest early.
Stop.
This is my room,
not somewhere you can just
come and go as you please.
Let me tell you.
I'm the supervisor
appointed by the City Lord.
If anything happens to me...
Who's your superior?
What superior?
I don't even have a bottom line.
Who can be my superior?
What nonsense are you saying?
Sneaking into my room,
peeping while I bathe,
and now trying to steal the ledger,
what are you really up to?
Should I call everyone over
to see what your intentions are?
If you could speak to me properly,
would I need
to steal the ledger so late?
Madam promised me
that if I solve the issues
at the office,
you can...
What will I do?
Forget it.
You're intentionally
targeting me everywhere.
Xu Xinglan,
you could've kissed him just now.
Why didn't you?
Such a coward.
(I didn't get the ledger
and was humiliated by him.)
(Forget it.)
(I have plenty of methods.)
(Arrangement Office)
Eight of Characters.
Five of Characters.
Wait.
I won again.
Pay up, pay up.
Gambling in groups.
This is absurd.
Go, go, go.
Go.
Come catch me. Catch me.
- Don't run.
- Can't catch me.
Over here.
- If this goes on,
- Here.
the Arrangement Office
will be a mess.
- Gotcha.
- Oh my.
Miss, you're amazing.
Young Master,
I think Miss Xu is quite lively.
It's been a long time
since the office was this lively.
Miss, this duck is so cute.
This way, come on.
- Here.
- Catch me.
Over here. Over here.
- Here.
Still trying to run?
This doesn't feel right.
What are you doing?
Didn't you see? We're playing.
This is ridiculous.
It's fine. Let's continue.
Mother.
Yan, why are you here?
Where's Xinglan?
This concerns our mansion.
I have to speak up.
Five, six, seven, eight.
What are you doing?
(Arrangement Office)
Tell me. What's going on?
What do you mean?
Xinglan.
The City Lord and I brought you
to the Arrangement Office...
To let me organize internal affairs.
I know.
Then why haven't you done anything?
I haven't done anything?
Pay up, pay up.
Come on, come on.
You lost all your living expenses to me.
What are you going to do this month?
It's okay; we still have some.
Are there other ways to earn money?
We're family now,
and when I
start making money,
I won't forget you.
We're playing mahjong together,
so I'll tell you this.
At the end of the month,
we can add a few more items
to the masters' purchase reports.
Then the money for playing
will come in.
(Falsifying accounts
and embezzling public funds.)
It's fine. Let's continue.
By the way,
why is the actual number of people here
fewer than the names on the list?
The registers are all our family.
Adding a name is easy.
(Management loopholes.)
(No wonder there is
a severe labor shortage.)
Let's go. Come on, let's continue.
Here we go. I won.
Come on, stick it on yourself.
We play mahjong like this every day.
If Miss Wei finds out,
will she report us?
Don't worry; Miss Wei is off duty.
We won't see her for at least
ten days or half a month.
She's off for that long?
Every position has
at least ten people.
If everyone takes turns once,
that's about ten days to half a month.
(It's severely overstaffed.)
(So, the payroll expenses are high.)
So,
you've done all this to understand
the situation at the Arrangement Office?
Yes, but not entirely,
because it's really fun.
Mother,
I told you.
She's still stubborn.
This is absurd.
Xinglan,
this is so fun.
You should invite me earlier next time.
Of course, no problem.
Mother, she...
What's wrong with her?
Do you have any prejudice
against her?
But I still need to tell you.
Xinglan.
If you want to investigate,
just investigate openly.
What's with going around in circles?
Some people accused me
of having ulterior motives
and sneaking around for secrets.
I'm afraid that'd be improper.
Who dares to say that?
I'll tear their mouths out.
If you need anything, just ask Yan.
I want the ledger for work purposes.
The ledger?
(Arrangement Office Ledger)
Madam.
Give me.
Here, Xinglan.
Thank you, Madam.
(Arrangement Office)
I believe you
will certainly handle the matters
I entrust to you well.
Madam,
why do you trust me so much?
I don't know why.
Maybe it is
because when I first saw you,
I felt that you needed
someone to help you.
I don't know what brought you
to my mansion initially,
but I can sense that
you carry a certain burden.
Xinglan,
if you feel wronged here in the future,
just come to me.
Thank you, Madam.
(Arrangement Office)
First-rank maids are paid
one tael monthly.
Second-rank maids
are paid 800 qian monthly.
Third-rank maids
are paid 500 qian monthly.
Currently, the office
has 10 first-rank maids,
20 second-rank maids,
and 30 third-rank maids.
So the monthly salary expenses are...
Fourty-one taels.
Zhong Yunxin.
What's wrong, Miss Xu?
My math can't be wrong.
Yunxin, you're so good at math.
(Account Details)
Can you help me?
I can't look at the ledger
due to my status.
If you keep saying that,
I'll really get angry.
As my friend, you can call me Xinglan.
Okay, Miss Xu.
Xinglan.
(Account Details)
It's done.
Based on this number,
you missed some earlier.
Young Master.
(Serenity and Fragrance)
Miss Xu's ways of doing things
are truly unprecedented.
No wonder Madam likes her so much.
She knows everything clearly
and even has the ledger.
Miss Xu is doing this to complete
the tasks assigned by the City Lord
to reorganize the Arrangement Office.
I want to see
how she reorganizes
the internal affairs.
Young Master,
I do have a way.
What?
I will never do such a thing.
♪Memories pass away like water♪
♪Time flows through the years♪
♪Deep feelings in the heart
are unspeakable♪
♪Endless love reveals in the snow♪
♪A soft sigh through reincarnations,
a love lasting a thousand years♪
♪Amid the myriad beings,
separations come♪
♪Awaking from dreams,
only longing remains♪
♪Life is but a fleeting dream,
like clouds and smoke♪
♪A thousand-year promise♪
♪Through the changes of time,
love remains unchanged♪
♪The red thread of fate ties us♪
♪Tightly together♪
♪May my live be exchanged
for your peaceful years♪
♪In memories♪
♪It's not just a thousand-year dream♪
♪Turning into eternity♪
♪The starry sky of longing♪
♪Beauty and white snow
reflects the parting♪
♪Moonlight scatters among the stars♪
♪The vow echoes in the heartstrings♪
♪Awakening from dreams,
waiting feels like eternal sleep♪
♪The burning vow,
difficult to meet again♪
♪Together, the bond deepens♪
♪Amid the myriad beings,
separations wound♪
♪Dreaming of the past
brings joy to the heart♪
♪A thousand-year promise♪
♪Through the changes of time,
love remains unchanged♪
♪The red thread of fate ties us♪
♪Tightly together♪
♪May my life be exchanged
for your peaceful years♪
♪In memories♪
♪It's not just a thousand-year dream♪
♪Turning into eternity♪
♪The starry sky of longing♪
♪A thousand-year promise♪
♪Through the changes of time,
love remains unchanged♪
♪The red thread of fate ties us♪
♪Tightly together♪
♪May my life be exchanged
for your peaceful years♪
♪In memories♪
♪It's not just a thousand-year dream♪
♪Turning into eternity♪
♪The starry sky of longing♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)