=Ancient Workplace, Love Handbook=
=Episode 18=
(Arrangement Office)
Mr. Yan.
I personally bought it for you.
I didn't do anything.
Princess Zhenzhen,
haven't you heard
a melon forced
off its vine isn't sweet?
You can't force a cow
to drink water
by holding its head down.
I like forcing things.
I will make the cow drink water.
So, did you succeed in forcing things
or making the cow drink?
None of your business.
I bear the responsibility of uniting
the two cities through marriage.
Why is she pestering Mr. Yan now?
Princess.
Did Mr. Yan accept your pastries?
It's because of that Xu Xinglan.
If she hadn't messed it up,
he wouldn't have refused.
Princess,
haven't you noticed?
After Mr. Yan came back
after being away for a while,
he seemed closer to Miss Xu.
You noticed it too?
Do you think your marriage
with Mr. Yan might fall through?
You said it in front
of the madam and Miss Xu...
If you hadn't said
he cared for me so much,
how could I have thought
this marriage was almost a done deal?
What should we do now?
I'll have to think of another plan.
Are you awake?
Yuwen Yan.
What were you just doing?
Reading.
No.
You were hugging Zhenzhen.
I don't care.
In my dream, you were hugging her.
Madam.
You didn't see how arrogant she was.
The mansion
is in chaos because of her.
Mother,
I wasn't this scared
even on my first battlefield.
She even took
my wedding handkerchief.
Madam.
She's clearly disrespecting you.
She's disrespecting me.
She's ruining our reputation.
If this goes on,
I'm afraid my marriage to Mr. Jun...
Yunxin.
I didn't expect this princess
to be such a troublemaker.
This concerns the alliance
between Xiliang
and Anjin.
We cannot let peace be disrupted.
Madam,
what should we do?
Don't worry.
I have another plan.
(Yuwen Qi, third son of the City Lord)
- Qi.
- Qi?
So, that is
what happened.
So, Mother,
you urgently called me back
just to marry that Xiliang princess?
Mother,
am I really your biological son?
What nonsense are you saying?
Look, your eldest and second brothers
both have wives now.
You're the only one
still single.
So, tell me.
Who else can I turn to for help?
But I...
What?
What do you want to say?
Let me ask you.
Do you have a girl you love?
The scope of "the girl I love"
is too narrow.
My dream is
to give every girl in the world a home.
(Scumbag.)
Where are you going?
I'm going to see that Xiliang princess.
Don't worry, everyone.
For your happiness,
I'll take this on without hesitation.
But Qi,
her methods
are hard to predict.
From my experience...
Experience?
Do I look like I don't have any?
So, how do you plan to act?
The wise have their strategies.
Mr. Qi
seems very confident.
Maybe
he really can solve this.
Princess Qinqin.
(Isn't this the girl I love?)
Who are you?
I'm the one you're going
to fall in love with.
(Zhen)
Do you know which three people
in this world are the most beautiful?
That'd be me in the morning,
me at noon,
and me at night.
If you're uneducated,
go read more books.
My name is Zhenzhen.
Everyone else calls you Zhenzhen,
but you're different to me.
Uneducated rogue.
Report!
In the first clash,
Mr. Qi was defeated.
Defeated?
Wasn't Qi very confident?
Military texts say
that arrogance leads to defeat.
Scout again and report.
Yes.
No worries.
Seems it is
an unprecedented clash of masters.
Qi will fly his battle flag up front.
We'll hold firm
in the rear.
Let's all pray for Qi.
(Did I enchant her
without even making a move?)
What's that smell?
Even the most beautiful flowers
can't outshine...
That's my manure flower.
Why did you bring them here?
Report!
In the second clash,
Mr. Qi was defeated.
Defeated again?
Scout again
and report.
Yes.
I brewed some
brown sugar ginger tea for you.
Drink it while it's hot.
How did you know?
Don't ask me why I knew.
I just can't control my feelings.
Did this go bad?
Report!
In the third clash,
Mr. Qi first won
but then was defeated.
What does that mean?
It means he was defeated.
Scout again
and report.
Yes.
Report!
Report.
Stop reporting.
We surrender.
♪Memories pass away like water♪
♪Time flows through the years♪
♪Deep feelings in the heart
are unspeakable♪
♪Endless love reveals in the snow♪
♪A soft sigh through reincarnations,
a love lasting a thousand years♪
♪Amid the myriad beings,
separations come♪
♪Awaking from dreams,
only longing remains♪
♪Life is but a fleeting dream,
like clouds and smoke♪
♪A thousand-year promise♪
♪Through the changes of time,
love remains unchanged♪
♪The red thread of fate ties us♪
♪Tightly together♪
♪May my live be exchanged
for your peaceful years♪
♪In memories♪
♪It's not just a thousand-year dream♪
♪Turning into eternity♪
♪The starry sky of longing♪
♪Beauty and white snow
reflects the parting♪
♪Moonlight scatters among the stars♪
♪The vow echoes in the heartstrings♪
♪Awakening from dreams,
waiting feels like eternal sleep♪
♪The burning vow,
difficult to meet again♪
♪Together, the bond deepens♪
♪Amid the myriad beings,
separations wound♪
♪Dreaming of the past
brings joy to the heart♪
♪A thousand-year promise♪
♪Through the changes of time,
love remains unchanged♪
♪The red thread of fate ties us♪
♪Tightly together♪
♪May my life be exchanged
for your peaceful years♪
♪In memories♪
♪It's not just a thousand-year dream♪
♪Turning into eternity♪
♪The starry sky of longing♪
♪A thousand-year promise♪
♪Through the changes of time,
love remains unchanged♪
♪The red thread of fate ties us♪
♪Tightly together♪
♪May my life be exchanged
for your peaceful years♪
♪In memories♪
♪It's not just a thousand-year dream♪
♪Turning into eternity♪
♪The starry sky of longing♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)