=Ancient Workplace, Love Handbook=
=Episode 20=
(Arrangement Office)
Although you won the bet,
I still think those two are strange.
You didn't dress up today,
but you're still very handsome.
Yan.
Qi.
What a sweet couple of newlyweds.
So inseparable.
I have no choice.
She's too clingy.
Right, right.
It's me who's clingy.
Let's go.
What a sweet couple.
How could there be a problem?
Not right.
What's not right?
When Zhenzhen approached him,
her feet stood outward,
and she kept her distance,
maintaining a safe space.
She was on guard.
When they smiled at each other,
Zhenzhen's lips went up
about 150 degrees,
her facial muscles were stiff,
and her gaze wandered.
So, she was pretending.
She looked like leaning on Qi,
but in fact, she wasn't.
So, something's wrong
with these two.
What should we do?
It's too high.
Honey,
why not help them?
Mr. Qi, Princess.
It's so high. I...
Come on.
Great. Mr. Qi can help.
Just a little more.
Yes, just a little more.
Mr. Qi!
Are you okay?
- Honey!
- Mr. Qi!
Get up.
Good for me.
Thank you, Mr. Qi.
- Thank you.
- You're amazing.
- It broke my heart.
- Let's go.
Clean up yourself.
As expected.
Yuwen Yan.
I've discovered something.
What did you discover?
I've discovered
the major secret
between Mr. Qi and Zhenzhen.
When others are around, they're close,
but when alone, they ignore each other.
Something's fishy.
Are you overthinking it?
Who's always glued together?
We are.
Come on.
Really?
If you don't believe me,
see for yourself.
I'm not going.
Shall we just go back?
- I want you to know
- Stop it.
my judgment is correct.
Be gentler.
I'm already being very gentle.
You're hurting me.
Forget it.
(The sage said)
(love wasn't about obvious actions)
(but careful ones.)
Honey, you've worked hard.
I'll give you a massage too.
Stop looking.
It's broad daylight; being that intimate
indicates a problem.
Your shoulders are really wide.
Is this pressure suitable?
I'll pour you some tea.
Please, dear.
Come with me.
Let's go.
Princess, I feel
that you've been different
towards Mr. Qi recently.
Last night...
Yes, Princess.
I thought you were only interested
in the marriage alliance,
but I didn't expect you
to have feelings for Mr. Qi as well.
I just want to marry
a young master of Anjin asap.
I have no other intentions.
That's true.
Those few books Mr. Qi sent
have been left untouched.
You didn't read any of them.
Why did you marry me?
- Because I like you.
- Because of my status?
Of course not.
- It's because...
- I heard it.
I didn't expect you
to be this kind of person.
How can you judge me?
Do you think you're a good person?
You spouted nonsense when we first met.
It seems we're evenly matched.
We're the same.
You're a vain liar.
You're a sly scoundrel.
Well, in that case,
let's get a divorce.
Divorce then.
(A familiar scent.)
Are you saying
this flower is poisonous?
Infusing this flower into wine
is deadly.
How do you know that?
Go check who brought in this flower
and where to get more.
Remember.
Don't alert anyone.
Yes.
Young Master.
So soon?
No, I forgot to tell you
they want a divorce.
A divorce?
Yes.
Let's go.
Let's go take a look.
What's going on?
You just got married
and now want a divorce?
How can you do this?
Qi, I don't want to lecture you.
You've always been mischievous.
You'd cause trouble if undisciplined...
The contract?
First, regularly display affection.
The princess must help Mr. Qi
maintain a doting image in public.
He wants me to set up a persona for him.
Isn't that excessive?
Second,
when the two parties aren't pretending,
no physical contact is allowed.
This clause applies to Mr. Qi.
What does that mean?
It means
only the princess can touch Qi,
but Qi can't touch her.
The princess cannot interfere
with Mr. Qi's career plans.
If necessary,
the princess should firmly express
unconditional support
for Mr. Qi's career
in all public settings.
He doesn't necessarily have a career.
Actually, he...
Mr. Qi must acknowledge
his status as a matrilocal husband
in Xiliang.
Both parties must live in Xiliang
annually for several months.
A matrilocal husband?
Maybe Mother doesn't even know
her son has become a matrilocal husband.
Sorry for the suffering, Qi.
What about you?
Why are you doing this?
With Xiliang in turmoil,
I can only rely on the power of Anjin
and marry into Anjin City
to help my father stabilize his rule.
I'm the only princess of Xiliang,
so I must fulfill this mission.
So,
it doesn't matter who it is,
as long as it's a young master
of Anjin City.
No wonder you were wavering
between Mr. Jun
and Mr. Yan.
I don't like either of them.
Mr. Jun is so boring,
and Mr. Yan...
What did you eat for dinner?
The food here suits my taste.
Thank you for your hospitality.
You're too kind.
So, about our marriage...
You traveled a long way.
I'll take good care of you
on behalf of Mother.
Although he seems to care about me,
he always keeps his distance.
Maybe ghosts and monsters
wouldn't dare to approach him.
I'm not talking about you.
Since you don't like them,
what about Mr. Qi?
Him?
I don't like him at all.
♪Memories pass away like water♪
♪Time flows through the years♪
♪Deep feelings in the heart
are unspeakable♪
♪Endless love reveals in the snow♪
♪A soft sigh through reincarnations,
a love lasting a thousand years♪
♪Amid the myriad beings,
separations come♪
♪Awaking from dreams,
only longing remains♪
♪Life is but a fleeting dream,
like clouds and smoke♪
♪A thousand-year promise♪
♪Through the changes of time,
love remains unchanged♪
♪The red thread of fate ties us♪
♪Tightly together♪
♪May my live be exchanged
for your peaceful years♪
♪In memories♪
♪It's not just a thousand-year dream♪
♪Turning into eternity♪
♪The starry sky of longing♪
♪Beauty and white snow
reflects the parting♪
♪Moonlight scatters among the stars♪
♪The vow echoes in the heartstrings♪
♪Awakening from dreams,
waiting feels like eternal sleep♪
♪The burning vow,
difficult to meet again♪
♪Together, the bond deepens♪
♪Amid the myriad beings,
separations wound♪
♪Dreaming of the past
brings joy to the heart♪
♪A thousand-year promise♪
♪Through the changes of time,
love remains unchanged♪
♪The red thread of fate ties us♪
♪Tightly together♪
♪May my life be exchanged
for your peaceful years♪
♪In memories♪
♪It's not just a thousand-year dream♪
♪Turning into eternity♪
♪The starry sky of longing♪
♪A thousand-year promise♪
♪Through the changes of time,
love remains unchanged♪
♪The red thread of fate ties us♪
♪Tightly together♪
♪May my life be exchanged
for your peaceful years♪
♪In memories♪
♪It's not just a thousand-year dream♪
♪Turning into eternity♪
♪The starry sky of longing♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)