I have feelings for you.
I know I treated you
badly in middle school.
But it's because I didn't know
what it was called
and whether it's wrong.
But I know now.
Come on, Ryu. Stop messing with me.
Do you know
how what you just said
made me feel?
I do.
You're not the only one.
I feel it too.
It's hard for me too.
I don't know what to do.
Are you for real?
Will you try going out with me?
I'm serious.
Ryu, I...
I know.
You already have Atom, don't you?
I'm okay.
He's a good guy.
Well,
it has nothing to do with him.
So why didn't you agree
to go out with me?
You have to give me some time.
I'm about to say yes to
my very first boyfriend.
You've never had a boyfriend?
No.
I'm glad
I got to be your first.
Hang on. I haven't said yes.
Then say it.
I'm waiting to hear it.
So?
Do you want to be my boyfriend?
But when it comes to the team,
I'm your captain,
and you're my teammate.
Do you want to be my boyfriend?
Ryu, if someone asks,
don't tell anyone
until I say
you can tell other people.
Do you want to be my boyfriend?
Mm.
Huh? What did you say?
Do you want to be my boyfriend?
Are you deaf?
I already said "mm".
Huh? What did you say?
Do you want to be my boyfriend?
Okay.
- What?
- Okay!
Well then.
I have to prove it.
What now?
(The Rebound)
(Directed by Tanwarin Sukkhapisit)
(Ryu: What are you up to?)
(Working at the pool, of course.)
(Ryu: Don't let anyone get close
unless necessary, understand?)
(You're getting out of control.)
(Ryu: Whatever. I'm saying no.
You're mine.)
Zen, what are you smiling about?
Zen,
I quit Interhigh's team.
Atom,
I wanted you
to sort things out with Pipo.
But I didn't want you
to quit school.
Weren't you on scholarship?
Just forget it.
I can't play with a team
that can't accept losing.
Won't you
get in trouble with your family?
I did.
But I've made my decision.
Atom!
It's okay. My dad's fine.
He'll be able to find a school
that can give me a scholarship.
Zen, I'm sorry.
Why would you apologize?
I didn't get hurt or anything.
But I feel really bad about this.
I understand.
But I think
if you really want to apologize
so you can feel relieved,
you should apologize
to someone else.
So why are you here?
You said you wanted to talk.
Well...
I...
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
You didn't do it.
On behalf of my team.
Basketball is a team sport.
The whole team must take
responsibility for any wrongdoings.
He quit Interhigh's team.
Oh?
Why did you do that?
You're good at basketball.
I didn't quit just because
of what happened to you.
Don't take it the wrong way.
I just don't want to play
with them anymore.
Do you think doing that
makes you look cool?
I can't help it, can't I?
I'm just that cool.
Hang on.
How did we get here?
Boys, it's time to eat.
- Yes, Grandma!
All right. Eat up.
Okay.
- Here, Zen.
- Oh.
- There.
- Hey.
Eat up. Have you lost weight?
Thanks so much, Atom.
But I can serve myself.
It's okay. I'm happy to help.
Here. That's yours.
Thanks, but I didn't ask.
Eat so your arm can recover quickly,
and you can finally go home.
Ah, you've made amends, Ryu? Atom?
- Yes.
The credit goes to me, Grandma.
It took me ages to
get them on good terms.
Okay. I believe you.
Life is short.
Be nice to each other, okay?
- Yes, Grandma.
I will.
Zen.
What?
Come here.
What's with you?
Who told you to serve Atom?
What?
He served me. I didn't serve him.
Whatever. I've got
a bone to pick with you.
For what?
For smiling back at him.
Hold up.
Didn't I smile at you too?
I also smiled at Grandma.
But not at Atom.
You're mine.
Come here.
What's up with you?
A hug as a punishment.
No, I haven't even showered.
Ryu!
It's okay. I don't think you stink.
Ryu, ugh!
That's enough!
Ugh! Ryu!
You're going to hurt your arm.
Zen! Ryu!
Keep the noise down.
The neighbors might complain!
Sorry, Grandma.
What's wrong with you?
Ryu!
Hey!
That's enough.
Stop it, Ryu!
Hey!
Have you eaten anything?
Yes.
What did you eat?
Did you eat anything healthy?
Don't forget.
Even though you've quit
from Interhigh's team,
you still have
to keep yourself physically fit.
Okay.
Wait.
I've talked to the people in Phuket.
We'll move there together
after this tournament.
That's all?
Yes.
(Dad talked to me about
the scholarship when I got home.)
(Zen: And are you okay?)
(Mm. Thanks for worrying
about me. Goodnight.)
(Zen: Goodnight.)
Grandma,
I'll stop to buy you ingredients
after Ryu gets his cast removed.
- Just get what's on the list.
- Okay.
Ryu, I hope your life gets better
after they remove the cast.
Thank you, Grandma.
- Bye, Grandma.
- Bye. Ride safely.
I will.
- Oh? Atom?
- Hi, Grandma.
Mm!
You missed him by minutes.
Zen took Ryu to get
his cast removed.
It's okay, Grandma.
Atom,
you've visited me
many times already.
But we've never had
a serious conversation.
What's the matter?
Nothing, really.
I'm just curious
about why you wanted
to be a basketball player.
Like Zen, his father taught him
since he was little.
I had no idea he'd be this serious
when he grew up.
It's okay if you can't tell.
I understand.
Actually, it's not
something I can't tell, Grandma.
I just don't know where to start.
My dad taught me to play
when I was little too.
Just like Zen.
But the difference
is that Zen seems
to love basketball.
And you don't?
I just...
followed my dad's orders.
Grandma,
is it strange
that I still don't know
what my dream is,
even at this age?
Do you know
why I started my dessert business?
No, is it because you like it?
Not at all.
It's the only thing I can do
at an acceptable level.
No way, Grandma.
Your desserts are the best.
Aw, you really have
a way with words.
It's true.
When I was little,
my family didn't have much.
I'd follow my mother to help her
with work at various places.
She was quite good
at finding jobs too.
And she'd take me along everywhere.
Good thing child labor laws
didn't exist back then.
Back then, I was happy enough
to see the next day come.
I grew up
without having any dreams as well.
I see.
What you see here is
everything my mother taught me.
I don't know
how much you like basketball.
But as far as I know,
you're very good at it, aren't you?
Perhaps
people can be successful
at things that aren't their dreams.
Wow,
that's very pretty.
You're very talented.
Really, Grandma?
The board didn't approve the budget.
What is this?
I requested it so the kids could
compete. How can they do this?
The thing is, our school
only allocated a budget
for two games.
No one expected our team
to get to the finals.
So? We got to the finals.
Shouldn't they keep supporting us?
It's not that I don't want to help.
But it's not my decision to make.
Of course.
It's not a science activity.
That's why they don't care.
They even want to demolish
the sporting club's building
to construct
a science building instead.
This sucks.
- Hey!
- Shoot!
- Darn it!
- Well done!
Here.
Pass the ball!
Come on.
What are you guys doing?
- Ryu?
Ryu!
How are you feeling?
You got your cast removed.
Can you use your arm as usual?
I don't think there's
going to be a problem.
Says who?
The doctor said you shouldn't
use your arm too much just yet.
No practice for you today.
Just sit and watch.
Oh? I don't want to do that.
I'm with Zen on this one though.
Oh?
Ryu, can I ask you something?
When you had the cast on,
how did you...
do it?
- What's "it"?
- Well...
It!
- Jerk.
- This!
- You pervy moron, Jed!
- What?
- That.
- Hey!
Jed, do you see me standing here?
- I'm a woman.
- That's right.
Well, I'm just curious.
They said the budget is exhausted.
How is that possible?
We made it to the semifinals.
I know.
I said all I could,
but that's what they said.
What else do you want me to do?
In any case, I'm going
to get you to compete.
Are you guys in this with me?
I'm in!
Me too!
Us too!
We'll give it all.
What do you want?
The gamblers requested Ryu
for the next game, Boss.
They threatened to go somewhere
else if he doesn't play.
What should we do, Boss?
If we don't do anything,
you're going to lose millions.
That brat.
Go and find Q.
- Yes, Boss.
Your guy had his cast removed.
I think he should be up for it now.
- Boss, well...
- Well what?
Well, he just had it removed.
I don't think he's up
for a game just yet.
I didn't ask you for your opinion.
I told you to go and get Ryu!
Can you stop disappointing me
again and again?
You probably know
what the consequences would be
if I had to take matters into
my own hands.
(M)
Who's this "M"?
You always reject the call
whenever it's them.
A loanshark?
No.
Why didn't you answer
your mom's phone?
I'm not going.
I've made
all the preparations for you.
And I have an errand
to run over there.
But I'm playing in the finals.
I can't abandon Zen and the guys.
How can a school
basketball game be so important?
Your future is more important.
I'm not going.
You have to.
I've let you have your way
for far too long.
If Dad was still here,
he'd never force me to do anything.
And is he with us?
Is he here with us?
Ryu?
Huh? What?
What's wrong?
I was speaking to you,
but you ignored me.
I'm fine.
I spaced out. That's all.
I have to go to class now.
Oh. Study hard,
10th grader.
Get to class. See you.
Q?
Can I have a word?
Tos told me to get you
so you could compete.
This still isn't over?
I told you. That was the last time.
You should go.
That time,
the cops interrupted the game.
It doesn't count.
This really is the last time?
Mm.
Tomorrow night? I'll catch up
with you after practice.
You'll catch up?
And you're going to flake out on me
like last time, aren't you?
I'm not going to fall
for your tricks anymore.
- Come with me now.
- No.
I have to go to class.
I'll go if I'm going.
Ryu!
Huh? What are you doing?
- Hey!
- Easy.
- Hey, get in the van.
- Move.
(How are you feeling?
What are you doing?)
Jedi!
Have you seen Ryu?
No, I don't think
he came to school today.
I was about to ask you.
There's homework to hand in.
Give me your phone.
Here.
I set up "Find my Mobile" for you.
I'll be able to find you now
wherever you are.
Did something happen?
- Boss!
- Get it up!
Hey!
What are you doing over there?
Boss, Stop!
Boss, don't you want him to play?
Hey, stop.
Get him up.
Boss!
Oh? Zen?
What's up?
Do you think you're cool
for bailing on me?
- Let me go!
- Boss!
Do you know how much money
and connections I've lost?
But I made you a lot of money,
didn't I?
Shut your mouth.
- Hey!
- Boss!
I'm giving you
another chance to play for me.
Name your price.
I'm not playing.
"I'm not playing"?
- Ugh!
- Ryu!
Stay put!
Boss,
you should stop. He might die.
I've talked to him.
He's going to play for us tonight.
Not just tonight.
I want him to play forever
until I tell him when he can quit!
Your school's team is good.
They've gotten in quite far.
These guys are the reason you don't
want to play for me, aren't they?
- Leave my friends alone!
- Hey!
I'm going to give you
some time to reconsider
whether you're going to play for me
or you want me to go after them.
- Stay still!
- Ugh!
What are you going to do to me, Q?
Don't do this, Boss!
You really love him, don't you?
- Your beloved brother...
- Yes!
I do!
- Darn it!
- Q!
Q!
You have until
the end of the day to decide.
Tie him up.
- Yes, Boss.
(Atom)
Ryu.
Q?
Ryu,
how are you feeling?
- What's going on inside?
- Boss tied them both up.
He's giving Ryu a chance
to reconsider.
Let's go and check the back.
Do you think this is the park?
Is that why you're wandering around?
So it's you.
Where is Ryu?
Ryu? Everyone's willing
to risk their lives for him.
Oh? Atom?
- Hi, Golf.
- Hi.
Hasn't Zen arrived yet?
Not yet. But he'll probably
be here soon.
Oh. Well then.
I'll have the usual, please.
Orange americano.
Sure, orange americano.
- Yes.
- Have a seat. I'll get it for you.
Okay.
- Golf.
- Hm?
- What?
- Actually,
I feel sorry for him.
You do? Why?
It's an experience to add
some flavor to his life.
But unrequited love is tiresome.
Hold it. How do you know
Zen isn't into Atom?
It's obvious who Zen's into.
Stop. The clock's still running.
This game isn't over yet.
Hang in there, Atom.
- I'm Team Atom.
- But I'm Team Ryu.
Okay. Go and make the coffee.
No slacking off.
And stop gossiping.
Zen!
- Zen!
- Ryu!
Ryu!
Tos, you punk!
Why did you capture my friend?
Why do you see me
in such a negative light?
I haven't even done anything.
He's the one that barged in.
So I lent him a hand
and escorted him here.
Hey, stop that!
Hey!
What?
Have you decided
you're going to come back
and play for me forever?
Gambling street basketball?
Ryu, don't do it!
Shut your mouth!
So, Ryu?
Are you going to come back
and play for me?
Or do you want me to stomp
your friend to death?
Choose.
No, Ryu! Don't worry about me!
You really love your friend.
I like that.
Hey, beat him up.
Hey, stop!
Hey!
Stay still.
Do you think you're so tough?
Come here!
- Ryu!
- Boss, stop!
- Ugh
- Ryu!
Ryu!
Are you hurt?
- Zen...
- Ryu.
I'm sorry you...
you got hurt.
Don't apologize.
It's worse for you.
You really love him, don't you?
There you go, the guy you love.
Boss,
I'm begging you.
Please let him go.
Shouldn't Ryu play for you?
I'm at your mercy now.
You can do anything to me.
I'm begging you.
Just let him go.
You're begging me?
Do you think my basketball
gambling den needs him that much?
Huh? Q?
I...
I don't need him anymore.
Boss, no!
Ryu!
Boss, don't!
Is this really okay, Q?
Shut your face,
and stay out of my business.
I can handle things myself.
But you saved us.
You have to come with us.
I'm a murderer now.
I don't think I can come with you.
No, Q.
You have to.
We promised each other,
as brothers,
that we will never
abandon one another.
I think you should
return to where you should be.
My time is up.
But you saved me.
Come with us, Q.
Please...
Listen to me.
Go.
And from now on,
live the life you want to live.
And you have to enjoy every moment.
Do you understand?
Eat three proper meals a day.
You have to eat until you're full,
understand?
Q.
Thank you for everything.
I love you.
He's in your hands now.
Q.
Hello, Grandma.
Atom, dear.
Has Zen come home?
He has. I'm calling
so you won't be worried.
Did he tell you where he was?
Why did he disappear
all of a sudden?
I didn't ask him.
Elderly people
are happy enough to see
their grandkids come home.
He'll probably tell me
if he wants to.
Okay, Grandma.
Thank you for calling me,
keeping me company,
and for always worrying about Zen.
It's my pleasure, Grandma.
It's time to go to bed.
Don't forget to keep yourself warm,
or you might catch a cold.
Thank you, Grandma.
Goodnight.
I'm sorry
for getting you hurt again.
It's not a problem at all.
I'm happy to help.
You risked yourself to save me
loads of times too.
Next time,
don't risk yourself
like that for me again.
Do you know
how scared I was seeing you
get beaten up?
What if you got really hurt?
I'd probably...
I know.
I know you're worried about me.
Zen,
I don't want to wait anymore.
I don't know what's
going to happen in the future.
Let's...
take our relationship
to the next level.
I don't want to wait any longer.
If something else
happens in the future,
let's get through it together.
Mm.
We'll get through it together.
Thanks.
You have to tell me
if there's anything,
understand?
Mm.
They said there's no budget.
We're in the semifinals,
so there are two more games.
- How much money do we need?
- Sixty-thousand?
Holy moly!
We have to hurry up
and earn some money,
or we won't get to compete.
What can people like us do?
- Dunk tanks?
- Bingo!
Let's go!
Aren't you going
into the dunk tanks, Ryu? Zen?
We want to dunk you.