=Revenge of Royal Princess=
=Episode 24=
Shu.
I am fine, sister.
I will be
your Shu
in my next life.
Sister, don't cry.
Sister.
Come over.
I guarantee you endless glory and wealth.
Okay?
Sister.
Do you still remember the rebellion
of the Han family?
We put down countless painstaking efforts
to quell the rebellion
and restore the stability of the country.
Now
how could you be overwhelmed by love?
Do you know that
all your years of hard work
will be in vain?
Don't you know
who ruined my hard work?
Sister.
Your sister died three years ago.
I don't know what Shu is to you
and what I am to you.
I don't even know which of the times
you called me sister
is true from your heart.
Sister.
If you call me sister,
you have to be worthy of it.
Sister.
(When I was Li Yanchu,)
(I exerted my utmost effort for Li Xie.)
(After I became Xie Yugui,)
(I only wanted revenge.)
(Looking back at the past,)
(my biggest regret in these two lives)
(is that I didn't take a good look
back at Han Shu,)
(even if it was only for a moment.)
(The right of communication through network)
(exclusively belongs to Tencent.)