=Revenge of Royal Princess=
=Episode 18=
Everyone says that
a couple should treat each other
with courtesy,
and there should be mutual help and relief
in time of poverty.
Is it true that only if you marry me
can I have you forever?
Han Shu.
Do you know what you are doing?
Sister.
I got you.
Untie me.
You are the prettiest person
I have ever seen in red.
Especially today's set
is the most gorgeous.
Sister.
Since you rescued me
from the execution ground,
I can never leave you again.
Let's get married today.
How dare you!
Don't cry.
(One month later)
Sister.
Don't ignore me.
You stepped on my dress.
- Let me go.
- Sister.
Let me go.
Sister, I won't cry now.
Sister.
Sister, try it.
Take a try.
Sister.
Sister, what are you reading?
Let me choose for you.
I am combing my hair.
Why are you giving me this?
Hairpin.
Punish me, sister.
The whip...
Are you here to apologize?
I haven't used it for a long time.
I wonder if I would...
Kill me, sister.
Why should I listen to you?
Don't call me sister again.
Others would think it horrifying.
Yan?
Your Majesty.
Now King Regent died in the tomb
with the witch.
How to deal with the military power
of King Regent?
Your Majesty.
Now that His Royal Highness is gone,
what should I do next?
Your Majesty, I am begging you.
I am willing to marry King Regent.
King Regent died for love with that witch.
What does it have to do with you?
It's not your turn to attempt suicide.
Get up.
Now that Princess Yong'an is dead,
why can't I?
Miss Guo, why are you saying
that I am dead?
(The right of communication through network)
(exclusively belongs to Tencent.)