[English subtitles are available]
[Gank Your Heart]
[Episode 16]
Tong Wu. Buy me my meal.
Hurry up!
It seems like
you'll be having a tough fight.
Sister Wen. Didn't you sign me to fight?
Besides, these players
have competed
many times with me in the games.
It's fine. I'm confident.
Well, you'll stay in room number two.
After Pei Xi left,
the room has been empty.
Sister Wen, is there any sharing room?
Lu Sheng's room has an empty bed.
But, he is a little reclusive.
That's okay. I will live with him.
We can even communicate sometimes.
I'll bring you in then.
There's no need. I'll go on my own.
Hello, Lu Sheng. I am Xiang Kong.
We will be roommates from now on.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Why are you here?
I am Legends' new captain.
From now onwards, this is my room.
I don't allow you to live here.
Do you hear me?
Why are you holding
my Brother Kong's notebook?
Didn't he leave this in the room
because he wanted to show me?
Come on. You are so tall.
Can't you be a bit shameful?
Give it to me.
You think it's fun, right?
Give it to me!
You are so tall. You.
What are you doing, Lin Yi Xuan?
What's going on?
He is stealing.
He stole Brother Kong's notebook.
Give that back to me.
All right. Stop that!
Why don't we have a match?
Okay. I'm not afraid of you.
What do you want to compete in?
You decide.
All of you heard that.
I decide what to compete. I decide.
This is a small room.
I will wait for you at the training hall.
Everyone is here.
Nothing important,
I just want you guys
to be the witnesses.
In case someone
is reluctant to admit his defeat.
After all, he is the captain.
Don't use some underhanded tricks.
No.
I decide what to compete.
This was what Captain Pei Xi said.
I just want to give a brilliant idea.
I want you
to have fun and be happy.
It doesn't matter.
Let's begin.
Okay. All the competitions
encourage friendship first,
competition second.
Let's have a
friendly smiling competition.
Within a minute,
whoever makes the other person laugh,
will be the winner. What do you think?
Not too much, right?
Let's begin.
Do you have facial paralysis, Pei Xi?
Do you think it's funny?
It's my turn.
I win.
Where is Li Gan?
Master says that he has a stomachache.
He is not coming.
Okay. Let's start first.
Let me announce.
From today onwards,
Ji Xiang Kong will officially join VNG.
Let's welcome him.
I'm new to the team.
Please take care of me.
Ji Xiang Kong is not only a member of VNG.
He will also be your new team captain.
Sister Wen.
Shouldn't you discuss
such an important issue
with my master first?
I am your coach.
My decision
is VNG's decision.
Sister Wen.
It's a good thing to have doubts.
This means that
everyone cares about the team.
It's also a good time to encourage me,
the captain that appears suddenly.
Don't talk nice words.
I am more qualified than you
to be VNG's captain.
Qi Yue!
Do you dare to play a game with me?
Okay. All of you will be in a team.
I'll lead the reserve players.
You said it.
Don't embarrass yourself later.
If I lose,
I will call you captain.
What if you lose?
I'll quit.
Sister Wen. He said that himself.
I'm sure you guys
won't have any disagreement, right?
Okay. Do whatever you want.
Brothers. Let's go.
Let's do some preparation.
Let me show him what is a captain.
Don't worry.
We'll do the same.
Four people will protect the Carry.
The jungle's money in Mid is all mine.
All of you just have to follow me.
Do you understand?
Brother Qi. Don't worry.
We will do whatever we can to support you.
A clumsy hand with four reserves.
Why is he being arrogant?
How are we playing?
We can't fight against Qi Yue.
We can't win.
Qi Yue will use
four people to protect the Carry.
Then, we will use the Dual-Core strategy.
Dual-Core?
In short, it's to let our
Top and Carry farm quickly.
Forming a dual-core
that can compete with their ace.
Qi Yue will definitely
put pressure in Mid.
Then, we have to destroy his flanks.
No matter how powerful he is,
he won't be able to do anything.
Come on. Take it easy.
Listen to my command.
Aren't you feeling sick?
It's better now.
Good to know.
This is…
Qi Yue and Ji Xiang Kong
are playing against each other?
Qi Yue refuses to accept it.
Ji Xiang Kong called four reserves
to join him for this round.
Ji Xiang Kong is
sacrificing the Mid towers.
It's very dangerous.
I don't think so.
Ji Xiang Kong and his teammates
are splitting into two groups.
A tower in exchange for three.
It's worth it.
But Qi Yue's Bug Queen
only relies on the team.
Unlike Ji Xiang Kong's four-one split
that has the advantage.
He can avoid teamfights
and push lanes as well.
We have a strong line-up in this game.
Let's end it in the early game.
I am at Mid. Middle.
Mid lane is farming fast.
I'm coming to support you.
Top lane, be careful.
Jungler is heading there.
Support. Aid the river.
I'm telling you.
Whoever touches my jungle
will taste my wrath.
All right.
Seems like the result
is no longer in doubt.
Qi Yue hasn't farmed yet,
but the equipment
of Ji Xiang Kong's two cores
have already been formed.
His tactic
totally crushes
Qi Yue's "four-guarantee-one".
Seems like you are right.
I hope you understand
that all I did is for VNG.
Take a look.
Ji Xiang Kong's contract.
One yuan?
He said he will fight
side by side with VNG.
Li Gan.
I trust Ji Xiang Kong won't let us down.
Okay.
I will submit the transfer application
on the official website later on.
Thank you.
ADC and Carry, keep hitting.
Push them back to base.
Destroy the nexus quickly.
Minions. Minions. Minions.
What is this?
What are you doing?
Who got you in here?
What are you thinking? Qi Yue!
Master.
Let me have another around with him.
I am not convinced.
Are you done?
-Master.
-Shut up!
A nice win.
All right.
The result of one game
can't represent anything.
But I hope all of you
can see the importance of tactics.
The tactics are more important,
especially in a game.
Qi Yue.
Right now, you should know
why you lost.
Anyone else who is not happy?
Okay.
Then, from now onwards,
Ji Xiang Kong will be your captain.
You need to listen to his commands.
Train according to his tactics.
Understand?
Xiang Kong.
All of you did really well.
But in terms of tactics…
Let me talk to him first.
Qi Yue! Stop right there!
Master, I don't want to play anymore.
I am not convinced.
When Pei Xi was here,
he let me play "four-guarantee-one".
I am willing to do that.
But right now,
you want me to call Ji Xiang Kong captain?
Impossible!
Can he defeat me in a solo match?
That match already proved that
Ji Xiang Kong is more suitable as captain
despite your strong capabilities.
iConquer is about teamwork.
Master. Why are you
speaking for that clumsy guy too?
Shut up.
Admit your defeat.
Your pride and arrogance
need to have a limit.
You are my apprentice
and also the founding member of VNG.
You need to be more broad-minded,
and responsible.
I hope you can put down
your distracting thoughts.
Play well in the competition.
Don't destroy your future
because of a moment of success.
There's still a long way to go.
If you want to prove that you're better
than Ji Xiang Kong, prove it in the game.
Understand?
Why are you here?
What's going on?
Who bullied our Young Master Qi?
Who else could it be?
Ji Xiang Kong. I'll kick him out someday.
I heard he replaced you as captain.
He's just a nobody
without Sister Wen protecting him.
What kind of background
do you think he has?
He came so suddenly.
Who knows.
Ji Xiang Kong.
I will make him suffer
for taking my captaincy away.
It's so annoying. Forget it.
Would you like to go on a ride with me?
You are messing up my hair.
What's wrong?
Are you going to meet Pei Xi again?
You have such a handsome boyfriend here
yet you are looking for other men.
What are you talking about?
Why do you believe the words of netizens?
Besides,
You should know
what happened during the duo queue.
The thing about duo queue?
The thing about duo queue is that
I used his account
to duo play with you
to teach Qiu Ying a lesson.
What's the result?
My girlfriend ended up
as Pei Xi's rumoured girlfriend.
All right.
My Young Master Qi is the best. Okay?
How about this? Tomorrow.
My time tomorrow only belongs to you.
How about that?
Today, I am really not available.
I have to meet
the organizer of Rising Star.
You are going to the competition?
I have an acquaintance at GDV.
I'll make a call for you.
There's no need.
I've already found a way.
It's late. Time to go.
Bye.
Looks good.
You look the part.
Okay. Let me introduce
our working procedure here.
Anyway, there are
morning and evening shifts.
The morning shift starts at ten
and the evening shift starts at two.
There is an hour of break in between.
It's shift work.
That's all, basically.
Okay. I know.
All right. Let me find someone
to give you a tour.
Okay.
Pei Xi.
Come here.
Come quickly.
Show the newbie around.
I am busy.
You're busy? What are you doing?
I am really busy.
I am creating an opportunity for you.
What opportunity?
I already asked.
Ji Xiang Kong and Qiu Ying
are not a couple.
How do you know that?
Ji Xiang Kong told me in person.
I get it.
What do you mean by opportunity?
Is there water inside your head?
Just listen to me.
Let's go.
Well. Sorry to trouble you.
Go.
No.
Why do I have to do this?
Because I am the boss and you work for me.
You have to listen to me.
Go quickly. Go with him.
-Thanks, Boss!
-You are welcome. Bye.
Let's go.
Just forget it.
-I can do it by myself.
-This is the procedure.
I have another interview tomorrow.
Then, when you go home later,
send me the information
and email me. Is that all right?
-Okay.
-Thanks!
Yi Yi, I am leaving first.
-Bye.
-Okay. Bye. See you tomorrow. Careful.
-Lu Yi Yi!
-I...
What's wrong with you?
Did I scare you?
I need to buy you dinner then.
Let's go.
I know a very good Sichuan restaurant.
-Trying to bribe me?
-No.
Tell me. Why are you here?
Did I invite you to dinner
because I want something from you?
Am I that kind of person?
No.
Actually, there's something.
I want you
to investigate Zhao Yang for me.
Investigate him?
He is indeed not a good person.
But am I that close to you?
Why should I help you?
-I am leaving.
-Wait. Come back.
Aren't you a great reporter?
Punish evil,
promote good and deliver justice.
Aren't these
the responsibility of reporters?
Besides,
Exposing Zhao Yang's underhanded business
will shock the whole industry.
This is a nice chance
to make a name for yourself.
I won't give it to others but you.
Stop. I can't accept it.
You've already seen.
I am just an editor
of a small magazine company.
I don't have such a noble responsibility.
-Bye.
-No.
Grandpa Lu.
Grandma Lu. Beauty Lu.
Beauty Lu, all right?
Are you looking for a fight?
I am telling you.
I'll call the police
if you follow me again.
There is no use to call the police.
After I come out, I will still follow you.
You...
Okay.
I give up. All right?
I'll help you.
How chivalrous of you!
Let's talk while we eat.
That Sichuan restaurant is wonderful.
There is a long line for it.
Right.
Are you close with Shu Wen in VNG?
Shu Wen? Of course.
She is my former sister-in-law.
Former sister-in-law?
Right.
Ji Xiang Kong. This scumbag!
Wait.
How's that related to my Brother Kong?
What happened?
Wait. Why did you hit me?
Are you eating or not, Lu Yi Yi?
Here she is.
Leave it to me.
Hello. These are your coffees.
Here you go. Be careful. It's hot.
Isn't this Qiu Ying?
That's weird.
Why are you here being a waitress?
We are really curious about
the news about you and Ji Xiang Kong.
Is that true?
It's none of your business.
-Wait. Don't go.
-Don't touch me.
Ji Xiang Kong has Shu Wen now.
Are you being left out?
-You even brought a little notebook.
-Give it back.
What are you doing?
You are not welcomed here.
Get out.
Isn't this Pei Xi?
-What are you being proud of?
-I ask you to leave.
-Let's go. They are driving us out.
-Let's go. Don't play anymore.
Ji Xiang Kong's.
Thank you.
If you have any trouble in the future,
you can ask me directly.
As long as I am here,
no one will bully you.
Former sister-in-law!
Lin Yi Xuan told me personally
that Shu Wen is his former sister-in-law.
Ji Xiang Kong is his Brother Kong.
Do you know
the relationship between all these?
I'm sure he joined VNG
to reunite with Shu Wen.
This liar.
Yi Yi.
Can you stop asking Lin Yi Xuan
about these things in the future?
I asked these things from Lin Yi Xuan
because I am afraid you've been cheated.
You are so silly.
Before you got trapped in this,
I have to…
You think too much.
I don't have time
to think about these things right now.
I sold my house to pay my loan,
preparing for Rising Star,
becoming a waitress at Dream Traveler.
I am very clear about
what I am doing every day.
This might be the only chance
to become a professional commentator.
I have to try my best.
I can't waste a single minute.
Okay. Let's not talk about this now.
But you have to promise me
not to see him again.
The most important thing for you now
is to prepare well for this competition.
Don't worry.
You were busy the whole day.
Take a shower and go to sleep.
All right.
You should sleep early too.
You are back?
Do you play basketball?
Not anymore.
It has been here for a while.
Let me help you pump it up.
No need.
I want to throw this anyway.
Okay.
Right. I have a problem
and I want to speak with you.
Sure. Say it.
I looked up your data recently.
I discovered that you've played
every role and played well in all of them.
Do you think your current role suits you?
What do you mean?
Are you saying that I can't do well
in my current role with my standard?
Are you saying that
I'm holding the team back?
Please check the data carefully.
Which game of mine has a problem?
No. That's not what I meant.
Perhaps I didn't make it clear.
My point is that…
I want to say. Every role
and every performance is very stable.
It's even like a straight line.
From another point of view,
does it mean that
you can achieve more with your potential?
You just came to VNG as the captain.
I understand that
you want to open the situation up.
But I am this kind of person,
I'm straightforward.
I don't like beating around the bush.
So I advise you
not to spend your energy on me.
Take care of yourself.
I was just checking the data
and want to have a chat with you.
I think you have
great room for development.
Of course, how you tell others…
It's our rest time now.
Can I go to sleep?
Okay. Sorry.
Good night.
Tong Wu.
Can you eat all of these?
It's also for
Brother Qi and Brother Shen.
Good morning.
Morning.
It's these three types of food again?
Can you be more creative?
Buy buns next time.
I want meat buns.
Okay.
Good morning, Captain.
Morning.
How can you find the energy to fight me
without eating anything?
Anyway, you will be beaten by me.
Do you know
what will be trending tomorrow?
Prince of E-sports
defeats clumsy-handed Ji Xiang Kong.
Sister Wen. Good morning.
-Sister Wen. Good morning.
-Good morning.
Your breakfast looks good.
Sister Wen.
Let's go out for a talk.
Okay.
Take your time.
Go out for a talk?
What will they talk about in the morning?
I am not eating.
You just came to the team.
You need to give them some time to adapt.
But Qi Yue is rash.
Sometimes, he is too blunt.
Qi Yue is a founding member.
He is proud and arrogant.
I guess he doesn't listen to him
when Pei Xi was here.
Shen Yue is a cunning guy.
He is siding with Qi Yue right now
but he is not really convinced by him.
What about others?
Lu Sheng's skill is well-rounded,
But he seems to be
disillusioned with the mortal world.
He only asks for stability
instead of improvements.
Tong Wu is the youngest.
He is also the one with the least courage.
But they have strong ability overall.
Good job. It just took you a few days
to figure out
these people's characteristics and temper.
The autumn season is coming soon.
Time is limited.
But I already analysed all their data.
Next,
I'll have to make a proper training plan
according to their characteristics.
Then, you might need to try harder.
Otherwise, it's hard
to employ your training plan.
Don't worry. If you have any problem,
I will fix it for you in the first place.
Thanks, Sister Wen.
I know what to do.
It might be a little risky
but don't worry, Sister Wen.
No matter what I do,
please let me go through it.
Since I got you here,
I will give you my full support.
Master.
This Ji Xiang Kong is a lovers boy.
Sister Wen trusts him so much.
I think he must've enchanted Sister Wen.
It's all made up by the media.
You actually believe that?
Master. Don't you worry that
Sister Wen and Ji Xiang Kong…
Enough!
I know Shu Wen's personality
better than anyone else.
Master.
Why are you bearing this?
Qi Yue.
My thing is none of your business.
Just work hard on training
and take the competition seriously.
Showing your true capabilities
is more important than anything else.
Don't forget what I've said to you before.
Okay. I know, Master.
I will go to training now.
Go.
[Luo Tian's Review]
Pei Xi?
Pei Xi. Why didn't you
reply to my text messages?
I don't have time.
Pei Xi. I know you are busy.
So, I come to see you in advance.
Why don't we have a chat?
Have you eaten yet?
Don't disturb my work.
I come here to study this time.
I am here for
Teacher Luo Tian's review.
Aren't you a hostess?
Why is a game review related to you?
How is it not related?
It's related to me for sure.
I am participating in Rising Star.
I've decided to change from
hostess to professional commentator.
In that way, we will be able
to meet very often at the game.
You want to be a commentator too?
Right.
Is there someone else too?
Who else besides me?
Waitress. Waitress.
What's wrong with this computer?
It's powered off.
Qiu Ying?
Waitress.
Coming.
Okay. I'll bring it to you in a moment.
Hello.
What do you want?
I am a little thirsty.
What do you have for drinks?
Please introduce me.
Right. Take a look yourself.
The text on the menu is too small.
Why don't you read it to me?
We have flower tea, juice,
Nongfu Spring, and Scream.
What do you want?
Just these few things?
Do you have coffee?
Yes. Cappuccino.
Okay.
Give me a cup of Cappuccino.
Wait a second.
I need to do commentary recently.
So, don't make it too hot.
My throat can't stand that.
Also, I have a bad stomach.
It can't be too cold.
One more thing.
Recently,
I'm on a diet.
So, I don't want milk or sugar.
Do you remember that?
If you don't want milk,
it can only be Americano.
But I ordered Cappuccino.
Sorry about that.
We don't know how to make
a cup of Cappuccino without milk.
What's your attitude?
Be careful. I will complain about this.
Pei Xi. Did you see that?
That was too much.
We only have one kind of coffee today.
Latte. It's free.
Pei Xi.
Thanks for helping me out.
You think too much.
I am not helping you.
We have limited staff here.
There are many customers waiting.
Remember.
Just do your job well.
I know.
Waiter. Where is the review section?
Here. This way, please.
Let's go.
Waitress!
Coming.
Come and see
what's wrong with my computer?
Okay.
Is it hard to choose?
I don't know what you mean.
You have to choose one
so I can help you.
I don't need your help.
I think you are too bored.
Do you want both of them?
All right. Bad boy.
You have my grace before.
Do you want any advice?
I've told you. I don't need it.
Good boy. You finally grow up.
You've learnt to think by yourself.
Do you want me to advise you
as someone who's experienced?
Are you very free now?
The bar is short of people.
Do you want to help?
Do I look free to you?
I am busy
worrying about your relationship.
Teacher Luo.
Teacher Luo is here.
He is running faster than anyone else.
What did you do to Pei Xi?
He's shy and going through puberty.
You are gossiping
about his personal life again, right?
How is that gossiping?
I am his brother. I am responsible
as an elder member of the family.
What time is it?
It's time. Go in there.
You're making it into a big occasion.
I put a lot of thought into this.
Let's go. Many people are waiting for you.
Here.
-Teacher Luo!
-Teacher Luo is here!
You are so famous. Teacher Luo.
Summoners, good afternoon.
This is
the famous commentator in the
e-sports industry, Teacher Luo Tian.
I believe everyone knows him.
Yes.
This is his first time being here
at Dream Traveler.
From now on,
Teacher Luo Tian
will come to Dream Traveler
to do reviews on past games every week.
Let's welcome him.
Teacher Luo.
I'm Qiao Xin, a hostess of
You Xing Video's iConquer edition.
I admire you a lot.
Thanks!
I also admire you.
Go there. Talk nicely.
I'll leave it to you.
Hello everyone, I am Luo Tian.
Welcome to attend
my offline review on past games.
Today, I will review
the final game of the Beta test.
This game was won against Legends by VNG
with an overwhelming score of two to zero.
Since this is a Beta test match,
every team must choose
at least a new Champion of this version.
But in this game,
Legends chose two new Champions,
while they were losing a game.
See.
From the line-up, it seems like
Legends actually have the advantage
in this game.
By supporting
the fixed-point control
of Deep Sea Prisoner,
Lu Feng's balance…
It's useless.
What?
Writing notes so crazily
is useless.
Then, what is useful?
Ask Luo Tian directly.
A professional is just in front of you.
Asking him directly
is ten times better than writing notes.
It makes some sense.
Are you trying to be a commentator
with this brain of yours?
Of course, the key is this team fight.
What can you see from this?
Teacher Luo Tian. I have a question.
Very active.
Yes.
I want to be a commentator like you
in the future.
So I will definitely
study hard and learn from you.
Sure. So, what can you see from this?
I think Ji Xiang Kong entered first,
he is not able to initiate.
After his death,
he can't cooperate with his teammates.
That's the reason for the loss.
Anyone else has a different opinion?
Teacher Luo.
I think the key to this loss
is on this team fight.
I think it's not Ji Xiang Kong's fault,
but his teammates
who didn't back him up well.
This caused the bad control on VNG's ADC
and the counter killing.
That's right.
The real reason is Huo Yao's mistake.
At a key moment, he missed his skill.
The Support of Legends fought Pei Xi's
Hell Emissary every time aggressively.
It was not just a simple mistake.
Very negative position.
This led to the later failure of Legends.
Today's review is over.
In the future, I will be doing
more reviews at Dream Traveler.
I hope everyone will
continue to support iConquer.
Thank you!
Thank you, Teacher Luo.
Can I take a photo with you?
I want one too.
-Thanks!
-It's my turn.
Teacher Luo Tian.
-Thank you, Teacher Luo Tian.
-Thanks, Teacher. Do your best!
You stepped on me!
Teacher Luo, nice to meet you.
Brother Summer said
he will wait for you at the bar.
Okay.
Teacher. Let me take
you to the resting area.
He will be here soon.
-Here.
-I'll just sit here then.
Teacher Luo. Do you want a drink?
We have everything here.
There's no need. You can leave me alone.
Just find me
whenever he is done with his business.
Teacher Luo.
Do you want an autograph?
You are my idol.
I don't just want your autograph.
I also have many questions
about commentating for you.
This is my notebook.
Have we met before?
Luo Tian. What do you think?
A trainee's practice is so casual now?
I remember you.
GDV's commentary room.
Teacher Luo, I...
I am so sorry.
I didn't mean it that day.
Someone who can't even lift her head.
How can you convince me that you will
be confident at the commentary table?
Okay.
I know.
Not a problem.
Just do whatever I said.
All right.
Fine.
I'm hanging up. Someone is here.
Okay. I know that. All right. Bye.
Teacher Luo Tian.
Your waitress at Dream Traveler
has quite the dream.
You've discovered that.
I admit.
I arranged that on purpose.
I don't want you to think that
I'm getting her in through the backdoor.
This is not called
getting through the backdoor?
But, if she can convince you
to give an opportunity for her
to get closer to me,
she is quite a sly one.
She didn't use any method.
She worked really hard. You know?
To study at my place,
she became the regional server's
top player in a month.
She comes in early
and leaves late every day.
That's rare.
That was all it takes to convince you?
I met too many amateur hostesses like her.
They seem to work really hard
on the surface,
but they still need to attract fans
with beauty and talent after all.
She tries whatever she can
to take advantage of other's popularity.
A girl with nothing but a suit
is not needed in our commentary circle.
I understand your worries.
I'm just giving her a chance.
Whether it works or not
depends on her hard work.
But I can promise you
that she is definitely not
the kind of person you just said.
How can you be so sure?
Summer.
I haven't seen you being keen
on someone for so many years.
I really appreciate her.
This little girl looks pretty too.
She can rely on her beauty
but she wants to rely on her talent.
This kind of girl is very rare now.
Weren't you the one
who said you lack people?
Tell me the truth.
It's Pei Xi.
Do you know? Pei Xi likes her.
Why didn't you say it earlier?
It's your future sister-in-law.
That's not a guarantee yet.
What's more important
is that I appreciate her too.
But you know I have a high standard.
-I don't simply appreciate anyone.
-I know.
That's why you are the expert.
An expert is different.
You can guide anyone.
-Fine.
-Come.
-I'll toast you with tea instead of wine.
-Sure.
Let's pretend it to be true.
Hello, Yi Yi.
If I rush in there and find Teacher Luo,
Do you think I'm will be seen
as too eager for success?
I am telling you,
you can only be successful
by being shameless.
-Okay.
-Go.
They are coming out.
I'll tell you later at home. Bye!
-When will you come again?
-I'll call you.
Teacher Luo.
I am sorry.
I know I might've given you
a bad impression just now.
But, I really want to
become a professional commentator.
Maybe, you think I am reckless right now.
But I insist on doing this.
So...
So…
So, what?
So,
I want to be your student.
Everyone can say something beautiful.
Everyone can have a resolve.
Tell me.
What is so special about you?
It's fine. Nothing else.
I am leaving first.
You...
Drive slowly on your way home.
All right. It's fine.
He has always been strict with others.
But,
he never accepts any students.
You are so brave!
Then,
does it mean
I don't have a chance anymore?
That's not necessary.
I think he means
you shouldn't just say something out loud.
Make something happen
and show your speciality.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
I've known him for many years.
He has always been like this.
Then, it means I still have a chance?
Yes, you do. But you have to
earn that chance by yourself.
I'll tell you a secret.
Rising Star.
Teacher Luo Tian
will be the main examiner.
Didn't you sign up for it?
Prove your efforts in front of him.
Then, will he be there?
Don't tell others I said this.
Thanks, Boss! I will try my best.
Okay. Don't call me Boss anymore.
Call me Brother Summer.
Thanks, Brother Summer!