[English subtitles are available]
[Gank Your Heart]
[Episode 25]
Sorry.
I sprained my ankle by accident yesterday.
It's fine.
Take a seat.
Hello.
Your strawberry milk tea.
Actually, regarding the rumours
about you and Xiang Kong,
I knew about it even before
you joined Rising Star.
When I saw your pictures online,
I have a feeling that
you and he are more than just rumours.
That's why I asked you
to come to my fan meeting.
I wanted to talk to you.
He never told me anything
between you and him.
That's why
we're in this awkward position.
You like him?
I do.
I like him.
But so far,
we are just friends.
I know.
Some things...
Even he doesn't say it, I know.
That's because we grew up together.
No one knows us better than each other.
Is your relationship with him
really like what you wrote
in Beyond the Sky?
Beyond the Sky is a song for him.
This song
records the hardest moments
yet also the sweetest days we've had.
When I became a trainee,
he applied to become an exchange student.
He rented an apartment
[beside my company,]
[only 12 square metres big.]
[After coming back from campus
every day, he would cook for me.]
[During the weekends,]
[he accompanied me to the theatre]
[for rehearsals and performances.]
I feel so tired.
I can't hold on anymore.
Even we might fail and get teased at,
yes, it does feel bad.
But we still have each other.
At that time,
we have nothing
but each other.
Xiang Kong said that
he would always be by my side.
Forever.
Later on, I started to become popular.
My company forbade me from dating.
Xiang Kong chose to leave
for my career development.
Till now, we've never met again.
But, he came to every concert I had.
You see.
Now, I've finally succeeded.
I can support him
and help him realize his dream.
We accompanied each other
throughout our entire youth.
Qiu Ying.
Can you understand
this relationship we have?
Sorry, Ms. Fu.
I need to go to work now.
But don't worry.
I won't interfere in
your relationship again.
Thanks for your coffee.
Bye.
This version of Holy Princess
seems to have improved.
You did your research.
Qiu Ying.
What's wrong? Your confession failed?
Qiu Ying refused you?
Handsome Ji.
Coach.
Is it because of Pei Xi?
Say something.
This is the line-up of
Polaris in three games.
They often use these two group control
heroes, the Bug Queen and Gorgon.
But there is also one weakness.
Their long cooldown period
after using their ultimate skill.
That means we need to fight back
when they're still cooling down.
No problem.
Qi Yue.
Tell us what you think.
It's already very clear.
You are the captain.
You decide the tactics.
We'll just listen.
The captain has clearly
explained the strategy.
The captain and I will lure them
to use their ultimate skill.
Then, Brother Qi will sneak from the back.
During the training session later,
pay attention to your entrance timing.
The match tomorrow is extremely important.
If we lose, we will proceed
into the losers bracket.
Qi Yue.
Do you understand?
Clear.
Are you done?
My mom is at the hotel. Can I visit her?
Mr. Can.
Have you seen the latest shift schedule?
Qiu Ying suddenly got promoted
from assistant to commentator.
Who would believe
she's not pulling strings?
Look at it this way.
Even if Qiu Ying did pull some strings,
it was Mr. Luo who appointed her.
Who can say no?
Even…
Even Mr. Guo needs
to show respect for Luo Tian.
For these few months,
I've learned so much from you
at the commentator's table.
We can't just sit by and watch someone
get promoted using dirty tricks.
I'm your protege.
Can you help me find a way?
Qiao Xin, don't worry.
See, I will definitely help you.
But the playoffs have begun.
We can only let it be right now.
Don't worry, later on,
I will definitely find
a way for you, okay?
I have to use the washroom.
Go ahead.
Follow me.
Wait. Where are you going?
Let go of me!
Why are you with Can again?
Explain it to me.
What's with you?
What's with me?
Then, what's with you?
Why didn't you reply to my messages?
If I didn't bump into you,
I can't even meet you, right?
Can't you see? I'm at work.
Enjoying coffee with some
other guy, is that work too?
Look at yourself.
Don't you feel embarrassed
for yelling like that?
If you're really capable,
do I need to keep some other man company?
I've already told you.
My career development
in You Xing is limited.
I need to secure a spot at GDV.
Right now, Qiu Ying
already has Luo Tian's support.
If I don't find a way to save myself,
would you help me?
You're finally telling the truth.
To you, I am just a loser.
What else?
All these years,
have you done anything for me?
Right now, everyone is staying here.
Don't come to me now.
-Qiao Xin.
-Let go of me.
Qiao Xin!
All these years, I've been
caring for you, and you?
Who do you think I am?
I can't stand it anymore.
Then, let's break up.
I didn't beg you to stay with me.
-Done?
-Mr. Li.
We are going to train first.
Where is Qi Yue?
Mr. Li, there's something
I need to talk to you.
Qi Yue is your apprentice.
He only listens to you at VNG.
Xiang Kong.
Just speak your mind.
If he is really with his mother,
it's fine for him to take leave.
But, if he's just dating,
which influences his performance,
that's a different story.
Xiang Kong.
This moment can make or break VNG.
Qi Yue and you are both indispensable.
I don't want any conflicts
between you two now.
Mr. Li, if I did misunderstand him,
I will apologize to Qi Yue.
But if it's not,
I hope you can talk to him.
Okay. I understand.
I'm going to train now.
Polaris is a relatively aggressive team.
They love boosting.
On average, three players can deal more
than 1000 points of damage in one match.
Nice analysis.
But not comprehensive enough.
Well, let's eat first.
Then, I'll help you organize the data.
Okay.
Xiang Kong?
You're here for Qiu Ying?
Qiu Ying. Can I talk to you privately?
Sorry. I am busy right now.
Mr. Luo.
I still have some unsolved problems.
I'm going back.
I'm going back to work too, then.
Brother Qi, you're finally back.
Mr. Li.
Is Qi Yue back?
Don't know.
He is probably with his mom.
What is he doing?
He doesn't answer my calls
or reply to my messages.
He probably forgot to bring his phone.
-Then, tell me when he comes back.
-Okay.
-Rest early.
-Bye, Mr. Li.
Why won't you answer my call, Brother Qi?
Just came back?
I went to Qi Yue's room.
I heard Qi Yue left early today again.
Yes.
His mom doesn't know her way around here,
so she needs his company.
Isn't it
because of something else?
Do you distrust Qi Yue so much?
-I'm going to sleep.
-Li Gan.
I'm concerned about Qi Yue.
Can we talk?
It's late. There's a game tomorrow.
Go to sleep early.
Qi Yue!
What's wrong?
-Why are you so drunk?
-Buzz off!
Qi Yue, tomorrow is the competition.
What's wrong with you? Wake up.
Sister Wen.
Am I a loser?
Why did Qiao Xin treat me like this?
Qi Yue, you are drunk.
Let me take you to your room.
Tell her this.
Someday, I will let the whole world
know that she is my woman!
Look at him.
Qi Yue, go back.
Shut up!
Why did Qiao Xin treat me like this?
I gave her everything she wanted.
Go away!
Li Gan.
Did you hear that?
Tomorrow is the game.
He's utterly drunk.
You'd better not cause any trouble.
Brother Qi!
Get up!
Master, did you see that?
Mr. Luo.
At my first live commentary,
I also stared from here for a long time.
Only by looking down from this angle
can you can feel more responsible.
The competition is about to start.
Let's get prepared.
Okay.
I know that you must be nervous
during your first commentary.
Later, during the commentary,
try to calm down.
Don't rush.
Make sure you report your data accurately.
If you are not confident
with your memory skills,
review your notes first.
Mr. Luo, Director An is looking for you.
Okay.
I need to go. Get prepared.
Let's go.
♫ The most brilliant ♫
♫ And most beautiful vista I've seen ♫
♫ Is in your eyes ♫
♫ From then on ♫
♫ I've never anticipated like so ♫
♫ If it weren't for ♫
♫ that hurried encounter ♫
Qiu Ying. Let's talk.
♫ that appeared in this life ♫
♫ I would have been fearless ♫
Let's talk outside.
♫ Unafraid of losing anything ♫
♫ Love is cautious ♫
♫ Wary of being expressed ♫
♫ A restless emotion ♫
♫ Love doesn't come easily ♫
♫ It's too pretty ♫
Qiu Ying, do your best.
This is your first time
in the commentator's podium.
You've waited so long for this day.
Don't be nervous.
Unleash your skills.
Thanks.
Good luck on your competition too.
♫ I just want us ♫
♫ To stare into each others' eyes ♫
Right.
I love the bike model you gave me.
Thank you.
That's just a gift to thank you
for supporting me all along.
I don't mean anything else.
Okay, I need to go.
You should head to the lounge too.
Qiu Ying.
♫ Love is cautious ♫
♫ Wary of being expressed ♫
♫ A restless emotion ♫
♫ Love doesn't come easily ♫
♫ It's too pretty ♫
♫ Always the subject of obsession ♫
I know
I shouldn't bother you now.
But,
after the game, can we talk?
Sure.
Let's invite Yi Yi and Lin Yi Xuan too.
We haven't gathered for a while.
I mean…
Just the two of us.
♫ I just want us ♫
♫ To stare into each others' eyes ♫
♫ Because it's you ♫
♫ I'll hug tightly no matter
how much it hurts ♫
Can we?
Let's talk about this after the game.
What are you looking for, Qiu Ying?
Zheng. My notebook is missing.
All my scripts and competition
analyses are in there.
You lost such an important thing?
I just went out for a while.
I remember I just put it on the desk.
Let's see how you'll show off.
Qiao Xin?
The game is about to start.
What are you doing here?
Mr. Luo, nothing important.
I was just throwing something.
I'm going up to prepare.
Zheng. The game is about to start.
Aren't you supposed to
prepare at the analysis table?
I will go now.
What happened? What are you looking for?
No…Nothing.
Can's partner just took ill.
They couldn't find someone to substitute.
So later on, we need to
follow Can's live hosting.
Live hosting?
Right, these emergencies
happen a lot during live games.
But, it's fine. just follow my pace later.
Here's the script, take a look.
Okay.
Brother Qi. Are you alright?
Drink some water.
Why did you drink so much?
What should I do?
Sister Wen saw everything.
I don't know the details.
But, your relationship with Qiao Xin...
Mr. Li should know by now.
I think Sister Wen is okay with it.
This will influence my performance.
Of course not.
You are so important in our team.
How would this influence the game?
You're right.
I am indispensable at VNG now.
The game is about to start. Let's go.
Where is Qi Yue?
He is in the washroom.
Sister Wen.
Master.
Play well in the game.
Don't worry.
Trust me.
Turn on your best mode
during today's game.
I have confidence in you.
Don't worry, Sister Wen.
We met Polaris before
during the regular season.
We all know them well.
Okay, keep it up.
Welcome to the live games of
the 2018 Fall Championship!
I am your old friend, Luo Tian.
Hello everyone.
I am your new friend, Qiu Ying.
[After two months of battling it out,]
[the top four teams
are now in the playoffs.]
[This is a double-elimination tournament.]
[Two consecutive defeats
result in elimination.]
Today is the first match
of iConquer's 2018 playoffs.
Here, we have VNG,
who wrote a new record
of 11 consecutive wins
in the regular season
[versus the dark horse team, Polaris.]
Mia?
Sister Wen.
Why are you here today?
I am here to support Xiang Kong.
Thanks for your support.
Mia?
Mia, the superstar singer,
is with us today!
[Mia!]
Excuse me. Thanks everyone.
Don't take photos.
Please respect her privacy.
Thank you, please sit and watch the game.
Please watch the game first, okay?
Thanks everyone.
Qiu Ying, for your first
commentary, you sure are lucky!
It seems like Qiu Ying is overwhelmed
by the audience's enthusiasm.
This is really a surprise
in today's playoffs.
Can, since we have a surprise,
[we'll leave the interview to you.]
Why would a celebrity
join a fare like this?
[Let's welcome the superstar singer, Mia!]
Welcome!
Actually, I'm here as an ordinary
member of the audience
[to experience the atmosphere here.]
I didn't expect everyone
to be so enthusiastic.
[Now that you're here today,]
[I can't miss this opportunity]
for some juicy gossip.
Which team today do you support?
I am a fan of VNG.
[That's because I heard that]
[during the regular season,]
[they set a record
of 11 consecutive wins.]
I really admire a team
with such passion and drive.
[Which player do you
support the most in VNG?]
VNG's captain, Ji Xiang Kong.
[Can't believe that Mia
is also a fan of VNG]
[and a fan of Ji Xiang Kong.]
What's wrong with you? Are you ill?
Sorry, Mr. Luo.
I was in a daze just now.
The game is about to start.
Pull yourself together.
Relax. Don't be too nervous.
Thanks.
[Let's give a round of
applause to our teams!]
[Welcome, everyone.]
[Both teams may
occupy their positions now.]
Based on the points
accumulated in the regular season,
Polaris is ranked 4th.
Also, during the regular season,
both teams have competed once.
VNG defeated Polaris by 2 to 0.
Yes, it's a new beginning in the playoffs.
[For all four teams,]
[every game is a life-and-death fight.]
[I believe Polaris today
will not give up easily.]
[Ladies and gentlemen,
show your enthusiasm.]
[Cheer for your favourite team!]
Xiang Kong, go!
-I'm coming!
-Follow!
-Go!
-Fire!
Go farm while I protect you.
I can't farm.
Qi Yue, what are you doing?
Why can't you farm after so long?
Mind your own business.
Sorry, my bad.
[Qi Yue is in trouble this round.]
[He's forced to farm in the jungle now.]
[Polaris seems to be hot on his heels.]
[Two supports are
heading into the jungle!]
[Two Level 6 supports!]
What is the jungler doing?
Why isn't he ganking now?
Calm down.
I'm caught. Help.
[Qi Yue has been caught.]
[He has been caught by two
heroes from the other side.]
[It seems like Qi Yue
is going to be killed.]
[Yes, he's utterly suppressed now.]
[He can't farm at all.]
[Actually, at around the 10th minute,]
VNG's Double Yue
would usually start to gank.
But, it's obvious that they're
all after Qi Yue this time.
He hasn't even reached
Level 6 in the 8th minute.
The numbers are against him.
According to previous data,
Qi Yue takes seven minutes
on average to reach Level 6.
Six to seven minutes.
Double Yue would start ganking
around the 10th minute mark.
They should have already farmed enough.
Their team participation rate is 75%,
while Polaris's rate is
75%.
But compared to Double Yue's 93%,
there is still a marked difference.
But this round, Double Yue's
participation rate will decrease.
[Now, Polaris's midlaners
is earning 484 gold per minute.]
[They've already surpassed Qi Yue.]
[Usually, he would be earning
around 580 gold per minute,]
[but right now, it's only 465.]
The lack of skills and equipment
may limit Qi Yue's strength.
Initiation will be harder.
Polaris is splitting
Double Yue intentionally.
VNG will be at a disadvantage
in the next team fight.
What? Now that I'm the MVP,
everyone's targeting me now?
Next time, when I call you,
come quickly, okay?
-No, it's you...
-What?
Look at Qi Yue's performance.
The opponent is targeting him, right?
Is this his first time being targeted?
Double Yue has never been a
long-term strategy anyway.
As long as he doesn't mess up,
Double Yue has absolute
advantage in this game.
Shu Wen.
In this world, nothing is absolute.
-We can attack here.
-I got it.
Brother Qi, I'm right below you.
Brother Qi, mind yourself.
Go back.
Move, move!
Back, back!
Fight them, fight!
Push!
Go!
Congratulation to Polaris
for winning this round.
Next, will VNG catch up
and start a third round?
Let's take a 15-minute break.
Looking forward to the next round.
Explain yourself.
You messed up the stats twice.
What's wrong with you?
Sorry, Mr. Luo.
I didn't prepare my notes well.
Where are your notes?
They're missing.
Missing?
Sorry, Mr. Luo.
I didn't keep them well.
Lift your head up.
Without your notes,
can't you comment anymore?
No. I don't feel confident without data.
To be a good commentator,
the most important skill is adaptability,
not relying on data.
You don't need to stress too much.
Later on, leave the data to me.
We are partners.
Next time, if there is
another emergency like this,
you need to tell me right away.
Since Double Yue is being targeted,
then we'll change tactics
in the next round.
Sister Wen.
Next round, let's fake Double Yue up.
What do you mean?
Since Qi Yue is being targeted,
then we'll pretend to be targeted.
Let Lu Sheng play carry.
I don't care if it's real or fake.
Next round, I will let them know
that I, Qi Yue, am not to be trifled with.
Qi Yue.
Next round is Polaris' game point.
I hope you can pull yourself together
and cooperate with us.
Do you understand?
Qi Yue, help me here.
Stop farming in the jungle, help me here.
We can attack at midlane, Qi Yue.
Protect Lu Sheng.
Shen Yue, you protect him.
Brother Qi, come to me.
-I'm coming.
-Qi Yue, where are you going?
Brother Qi is initiating at midlane.
I am going to kill the dragon.
Why kill the dragon now?
How to play bottom lane without gold?
There's someone at bottom.
We can push at mid.
-I'm caught.
-Help.
-Got it.
-This is a mess.
Shen Yue, come back!
You'll die if you go there.
-We can't take this wave.
-Brother Qi, go back.
[Qi Yue has been killed.]
[Three down at VNG's side.]
VNG is getting wrecked this round!
Qi Yue seems to be driven
by impulse in this team fight.
But, Qi Yue is totally suppressed.
He can't gank, so he's trying
his luck by killing the dragon.
It did seem like Qi Yue
was going for broke.
[But, have you noticed that]
[VNG is not using Double Yue
this round anymore?]
[Yes, Ji Xiang Kong seems to be
using Qi Yue to lure his opponent.]
Let's see Lu Sheng's stats.
His stats are the highest in his team now.
Actually, it was probably better
for them to not fight the dragpn.
Yes, but Ji Xiang Kong, Tong Wu and
Lu Sheng are all at the bottom lane.
While Polaris is killing the dragon,
they could use this chance
[to destroy the outer turret.]
Qiu Ying's commentary
is getting better and better.
[Qiu Ying sabotages Mia Fu
and Ji Xiang Kong's relationship.]
[Now, she gets to be a commentator
all because of Ji Xiang Kong?]
Why are these people always up to no good?
Even if they're digging up dirt
between Ji Xiang Kong and Mia,
what does it have to do with Qiu Ying?
But,
how are Ji Xiang Kong and Mia related?
-Go!
-Attack!
Gather here, quick.
The other side is open.
Qi Yue, help us here.
Shen Yue, follow me.
-I know. I am following you.
[Another team fight at midlane.]
What does Qi Yue want to do?
He's diving, but
the carry can't follow him.
Replace Qi Yue next round.
Who'd replace him?
No. I've been caught.
Who can help me?
I'm coming.
-I'm holding him.
-Help, help.
Shen Yue. Where are you, Shen Yue?
Coming. Coming.
Polaris captures Qi Yue again.
What? Are you nervous because
there's a superstar down there?
Polaris's net worth is
much higher than VNG now.
If VNG is aced, there's no
chance for them to come back.
Coach. I need to answer this call.
Go.
Hey. What's wrong?
Lin Yi Xuan, I'm asking you this.
Do you know that Mia is
Ji Xiang Kong's first love?
Brother Kong and Mia? Really?
It's all over the Internet now!
No. Is it a joke?
Brother Kong is Mia's first love?
I might as well say I'm
Mia's long-lost brother.
Jerk, don't play dumb with me.
Why would I play dumb
with you, Reporter Lu?
Brother Kong is Mia's fan.
The whole team knows that.
So, Mia's watching the game live,
and then rumours of them
broke out on the Internet.
[This can't be a baseless rumour.]
Then, isn't it possible that
Mia's just a fan of VNG?
It can't be that simple.
Look at that photo of Mia hugging someone.
It's obviously Ji Xiang Kong!
There's even a photo?
Right now, there's also news
about Qiu Ying and Ji Xiang Kong.
All the netizens are accusing
Qiu Ying for being a third wheel.
[Listen, Lin Yi Xuan.]
If Qiu Ying gets bullied again,
you and Ji Xiang Kong will be so dead!
Wait. How is this related to me?
[Why are you angry with…]
Hello. Hello?
What's happening?
Seriously?
[Let's congratulate Polaris...]
Brother Kong lost?
[Congratulations to Polaris for
entering the winners bracket.]
Qi Yue made too many mistakes today.
That's how he is.
Once things spin out of control,
he can't control himself.
In the losers bracket, they have
to go back if they lose another game.
No, something's not right in this game.
I think there's something
wrong with Double Yue.
I've already alerted him.
If a person becomes too arrogant,
losing is a matter of time.
Pei Xi. What do you mean?
Don't forget that Brother Kong
has defeated you before.
Look who is saying
that he is too arrogant.
Yi Xuan.
Pei Xi is talking about Qi Yue.
He was the MVP every round.
He's consumed by arrogance and pride.
If he continues like this,
the future is bleak for Double Yue.
Then, if Double Yue is over,
what about Brother Kong?
I also want to see
how Ji Xiang Kong will handle this.
Thanks for watching today's competition.
-I am your commentator, Luo Tian.
-I am your commentator, Qiu Ying.
Summoners, see you in the next game.
Even without your notes,
it's not as hard as you think, right?
Thank you, Mr. Luo.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have held on till now.
Commentating takes two.
One person can't do this.
Your performance today was excellent.
Xiang Kong, wait.
Please follow me down the stage.
Just a while, let's go.
Just a while.
[Xiang Kong is with us now.]
[We have a fan today
who's related to you.]
So, is there anything
you want to tell her?