Hello.
I'm Yoo Byungjae, a quiet man
hosting The Quiet Interview.
Today's guest has a smile
that feels like a warm spring day.
It's the kind of smile that could melt
the frozen Hangang River.
But when that smile fades,
it can make the air turn icy,
letting a chill settle in.
Will a spring breeze
fill the studio today,
or will the chill of winter take over?
Let's quietly welcome our guest.
Hello.
Where is it?
Could you please take a look
at the audience members?
They came all this way just for you, Chuu.
Some of them look familiar.
Hello, I'm Chuu.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you so much for coming.
YUCHAN CAN PROTECT CHUU
PROTECT MY HEART, CHUU
This is amazing.
Chuu actually joined us
on No-Laughing Birthday Party before.
I did.
The Quiet Interview is a bit different.
-So let me go over the rules with you.
-Yes, please.
It's simple. You can't laugh.
These cameras in front of us
aren't just any cameras.
They're equipped with
a cutting-edge AI detection system.
What?
They detect in real-time
whether you're smiling or laughing.
If you let out a giggle,
you'll hear a warning sound.
A warning sound?
-I see.
-You'll hear that sound.
And if it's clear to everyone
that you've burst out laughing,
a much louder siren will go off.
We have our "siren guy" here on set,
assisting with that.
Okay.
Once the siren goes off,
you'll be sent to the Quiet Room
for five minutes,
where you'll spend
a lonely and isolated time.
-Me?
-Yes.
-I see.
-And if I happen to laugh,
you'll be able to come back and join us.
So your strategy could be
to make me laugh.
Got it.
As I've mentioned before,
I'm a huge fan of yours.
And I've been watching
Chuu Can Do It for ages.
I remember almost every little moment.
What I love most is
how the show inspires people
to protect the environment
and care for the planet.
Thank you so much.
Have you been practicing
what you learned on the show?
Yes, I have.
My parents and friends
put a lot of it into practice as well.
-Some friends keep it up to this day.
-Really?
We were so inspired by your channel
that we've made
The Quiet Interview eco-friendly too.
-Do you see the person on the bicycle?
-Yes.
-The lighting and the cameras on set…
-I see.
…are currently being powered
by that bicycle generator.
-Really?
-Yes.
It's something we felt strongly about.
The Earth and every living creature on it
-are truly precious.
-Right.
That's why… Hey, you!
Hey!
I'm sorry.
Good.
I'm so sad.
I was actually crying.
Hey.
-Hey!
-Yo!
-Yes?
-The Earth is hurting.
It's hurting.
-So push through the pain.
-Push.
Keep pedaling.
Faster.
Faster!
So it was true.
Welcome to the eco-friendly talk show,
The Quiet Interview.
Chuu is our guest for today.
The warning sound went off earlier.
I know you laugh a lot
and always have a smile on your face.
So, for the first time ever,
we've prepared a special segment for you.
What kind…
-What did you just say?
-What kind of rule?
You see, I…
No! What do I do?
-You're okay for now.
-Really?
It's okay to laugh now.
We've prepared a special segment
where you can laugh as much as you want.
So for this segment,
we've invited a comedian
whose jokes land perfectly every time.
We'll give you some time
to just sit back and laugh at his jokes.
-Okay.
-Where is he?
I'm right here. Hello.
-Hello.
-All right.
-Should I start?
-Yes, go ahead.
What's the opposite of a stand-up cop?
A dirty cop?
A sit-down cop.
-I see.
-Okay.
What happens if Chuu gets electrocuted?
Pikachuu!
-You knew that one.
-Yes!
That was just a joke.
We don't want you to get electrocuted.
-I'm thinking of going to Japan.
-Okay.
I'm planning to go to Fukuoka.
Just going to Fuku-soak in the culture.
That was Choi Useon.
Goodbye, everyone.
That wraps up this segment.
Now the no-laugh rule is in full effect.
Let's talk about what's new with you.
From music to variety shows to dramas,
you've truly been active
across the board this year.
You even took on
a serious acting role this time.
-Is that right?
-Yes.
-My Girlfriend Is The Man!
-Yes, it aired on KBS.
Thanks to your performance,
the show recorded
a remarkable 13.1% viewership,
-an impressive feat in this OTT era.
-What?
-Wait.
-I don't think it was 13.1%.
-My apologies.
-Yes.
Sorry, one second.
What? "Add it up"?
What do you mean?
-How many episodes were there?
-Twelve episodes.
"Add it up"?
You can't say it like that.
What were you thinking?
Seriously.
Just because the ratings weren't great…
No show gets 13% these days.
Yeah, that's crazy.
So you added up
all 12 episodes to get 13.1%?
Okay.
She's laughing!
Are you laughing?
Let's talk about your variety shows.
You're a regular on so many.
You've got your channel, Chuu Can Do It,
and you were also on Steel Troops.
They received so much love,
and I enjoyed watching them too.
-Really?
-Yes. You were also on The Devil's Plan…
One second.
Why did you write this?
What's wrong with you?
Did you do the research?
She wasn't on The Devil's Plan.
-I was on it briefly.
-Hey.
I watched that show twice,
from beginning to end.
-I was on it.
-I watched it twice.
I only went to pee once.
This is ridiculous.
I must have appeared
when you went to the bathroom.
I apologize,
it seems there was a slight error.
But rules are rules,
so please head to the Quiet Room.
-Me?
-Yes.
I just want to make it clear
that I did appear on the show.
You must've peed for a long time.
I was on the first and second episodes.
Unfortunately, our guest has been confined
to the Quiet Room.
But our show must go on.
We anticipated this situation
and invited a substitute in advance.
This person is bright, bubbly,
and has puppy-like features,
just like Chuu.
Really? Who is it?
They asked to be introduced
as the "Second Chuu."
Who is it?
Let's welcome them.
No way!
Hello, I'm Chuu.
What? No!
Thanks for coming today.
Good to see you, Chuu.
That's not Chuu.
I feel like I'd get in trouble
if I don't ask you to do this.
Could you show the viewers
your iconic "biting heart"?
That's great.
-No.
-Let's keep it going.
Could you show us
the viral "Frozen Cat Challenge"?
Oh, my goodness.
A cat walks across
the frozen Hangang River.
Final question.
You just had a smoke, didn't you?
-I'm Chuu, so--
-No.
You just smoked a cigarette, right?
Well…
-I'm just--
-I'm asking because I can smell it.
Yes, I did.
Sorry, but we can't have smokers here.
Please go back to your seat.
Thank you.
It's been five minutes,
so you can come back.
I'm the real Chuu.
-Yes, please come back.
-Okay.
Thank you.
We weren't trying to collect
heartwarming stories about you,
but someone on our crew said
they worked with you before
-and had a good story to share.
-Really?
Do you recognize anyone here?
Yes.
-I see.
-I know him.
He worked as a producer on Chuu Can Do It…
-I know.
-…and now works with us.
-Do you remember him?
-Of course.
I recognized him right away.
Please start by introducing yourself
and then share your story.
-He wrote a letter.
-Really?
Hi, I'm Park Sanghyeok,
a former producer on Chuu Can Do It.
Park Sanghyeok! Sorry.
Chuu is the most professional celebrity
I have ever met.
Really?
When I would nap during breaks on set,
she'd personally go and buy me hot coffee.
-What?
-You're very kind.
Looking after the crew
during shoots isn't easy.
I've read a lot of comments
that talk about how nice you are.
She poured the hot coffee on my thigh.
When I screamed,
she kicked me in the shin a few times
to remind me we were on set.
CHUU WOULD NEVER DO THAT!
-Chuu always carried a magnifying glass.
-How cute.
She would use it to burn ants
when shoots ran long.
Then one day, she said we had to film
a sequel to the "Frozen Cat Challenge,"
but with a dog this time.
She told me to fetch a golden retriever
and freeze the Hangang River.
I see.
It was August.
I managed to find a dog,
but since it was a labrador retriever
and not a golden retriever,
she hit me with brass knuckles,
leaving me with short-term memory loss.
Oh, dear.
Despite his short-term memory loss,
he came here to share this story.
So let's give him a hand.
How is this a heartwarming story?
Also, that was all a lie.
Was it a lie?
-Yes, it was.
-Which part?
The only true thing he said was
that he was a producer on Chuu Can Do It.
But he said you were the most
professional celebrity he's ever met.
I'm not a professional.
I'm still an ama-Chuu-r.
All right, thank you for clearing that up.
Yes?
Do you have more to say?
Hi, I'm Park Sanghyeok,
a former producer on Chuu Can Do It.
Chuu is the most professional celebrity
I have ever met.
-When I would nap during breaks on set…
-What?
…she'd personally--
-We…
-What's going on?
Maybe you should try again later.
Sorry about that.
Let's continue with the questions.
One of the reasons I became
such a big fan of yours
is because of your bright,
positive energy.
What do you think your real charm is?
My real charm?
I want to be everyone's sunshine.
-Everyone's…
-Sunshine.
-Do you want to be the sun?
-No.
Sunshine.
-Like spring sunshine?
-Yes.
But what does that even mean?
Some celebrities get called
the girl next door or sweetheart.
-The heart-stealer.
-That's right.
They get a lot of nicknames like that.
But I don't want to be labeled like that.
I just want to be someone
who feels warm and approachable,
-like sunshine.
-Someone who feels like sunshine.
Now that I think about it,
I don't think anyone has been called
-"everyone's sunshine."
-Right?
I want to be the first.
That's great. This is something
I always ask everyone.
What's a N*tflix show
you've enjoyed recently?
I enjoyed You and Everything Else.
-It's the best.
-It's so good.
It's a bit difficult to get into at first
because it's not sensational,
but everyone who's watched it
recommends it.
-It's serene, and the acting was great.
-It's the best.
-Anything else you've watched?
-On N*tflix?
The Devil's Plan.
That was also a huge hit.
-There are hardcore fans of that genre.
-Yes.
Could you recommend a N*tflix show
to our viewers on Disney+?
I almost forgot.
You asked,
so I just said what came to mind.
You and Everything Else…
Disney+ has the best shows.
-Don't do this to me.
-What are you watching?
-On Disney+?
-Yes.
Right! I saw Big Bet.
That's unexpected.
And also this show.
Sorry, that took me a minute.
I saw The Quiet Interview!
Our show hasn't aired yet.
Exactly! Oh, right.
It just felt like…
-We have a liar with us today.
-Help me, Sanghyeok.
-Let's move on.
-Okay.
You're making strides
as both a singer and an actor.
How are they different?
On stage, I can go wherever my heart
and my fans lead me.
There's a sense of freedom in being able
to connect with my fans directly.
With acting, when I memorize my lines…
I'm still learning, of course.
Talking to the director
and trying out different ways
to deliver a line is really fun.
And when I watch it later,
I feel this sense of pride and joy.
That's wonderful.
Let's move on to the next question.
-Hi, I'm Park Sanghyeok.
-Hold on. There he goes again.
Chuu is the most professional celebrity
I have ever met.
-You said that…
-When I would nap…
-You said that already.
-Sorry.
Sanghyeok.
I apologize. Let's keep going.
You're known for your bright
and lovable personality.
But after watching
a lot of your videos and content,
I felt like you have
a bit of a tough side too.
So I thought it'd be fun to bring that out
with a short acting scene.
-Can we act out a scene together?
-I love doing improv.
-I really do.
-Great.
Instead of doing improv, we have a script.
I'll play Sukwoo.
-You can play Cha Moosik.
-Okay.
"Moosik, can you lend me
just 100 million won? Please?"
"Are you done already?"
Sorry, I wasn't happy with my acting.
Let's do that again.
I need to act more pathetic.
"Moosik, can you lend me
just 100 million won? Please?"
"Are you done already?"
"Yeah. I have absolutely nothing
right now. I'm penniless."
"Is that so?"
"Is that…"
"Is that all you had?"
CAUGHT UP IN THEIR ACTING,
THEY FORGOT THE NO-LAUGH RULE
I'm so sorry, I'll go again.
So…
"Is that so? Is that all you had?"
Applause, everyone.
Seriously, this is a tough role.
I said I was a fan first,
-but I think the feeling's mutual.
-You're right.
We love each other's content.
So I've prepared a quiz about me.
You should be able to get these right.
"Which of the following messages
was written in Yoo Byungjae's yearbook?"
-Okay.
-"Who are you?"
Oh, no.
"Thanks for switching seats with me.
Take care."
Oh, my gosh.
"Thanks for a great year, Changseop.
Let's hang out again."
Changseop?
-"No one wrote anything."
-No way.
I feel like you were popular, though.
You're a bit shy,
but everyone likes you
because you're funny.
I bet they wanted to carry you around
like a little Pocket Girl.
Sorry, you're not a girl.
I meant, P*k*mon.
No, wait. Sorry, I meant Pocket Man.
I can't believe I said P*k*mon.
Sorry, I meant Pocket Man.
I'm sorry, I used to be a Pocket Girl.
I was always the shortest
or second shortest in class.
I heard you were too, so I figured
you might've been a Pocket Man.
You said "P*k*mon."
I'm so sorry.
The siren went off,
but since I laughed while we were acting,
-I'll let it slide.
-I'm sorry.
You're so expressive that
some people call you the human emoji.
That's why we've prepared
a little emoji interview.
I'll ask you a question,
but instead of answering out loud,
-you'll reply with an emoji.
-Okay.
What would you like to say to our viewers
watching The Quiet Interview?
Hello, viewers of The Quiet Interview!
This is Chuu.
Nice to meet you!
-That was very cheerful.
-Yes.
-I'll take this since you've used it.
-Wait, but earlier…
Which emoji best represents Kim Jiwoo?
Please hold up an emoji.
Oh, my gosh.
I can't use any of these. Maybe this one?
Why that one?
-I use this emoji all the time.
-Really?
When I ask my friends where they are,
I always send this emoji.
So when they saw it was my most used one,
they said they weren't surprised.
-This and--
-That emoji is so you.
I'll probably think of you
when I see that now.
Please give that to me.
-But…
-Please let go. We have to move on.
I heard you had a very special reason
for appearing on our show today.
The Quiet Interview?
How many questions are left?
-Three.
-Three?
The Quiet Interview?
-Pick one.
-I guess this one.
What does that mean?
I actually don't know.
I don't even know
if I'm getting paid to be here.
Then, is it okay if we don't pay you?
Before we move on,
let's get a quick thumbnail
and a few still photos.
-You're taking it from there?
-Yes.
-Let's look at that camera.
-Okay.
-Are you ready?
-Yes.
Wait, you're not in the frame, Byungjae.
-Please move closer to Chuu.
-Okay.
-You stay. I'll move.
-Okay, here we go.
-Sure.
Sorry, Byungjae, but your face
looks three times bigger than hers.
-Could you step back just a bit?
-Okay.
-Farther.
-We can edit it later.
-A little more.
-Really?
-Go way back.
-His face isn't that big.
-Keep going.
-How's this?
Keep going until I tell you to stop.
You'll have to step down.
Keep going.
He's going to fall off the stage.
No, it's not enough.
How about you just go home?
-Can you go farther back?
-This is as far as I can go.
We'll shoot it later.
Okay. I guess there's nothing we can do.
You can send a picture of yourself later.
They can edit it in.
It's easy to do these days.
It's already time for the final segment
of The Quiet Interview.
We've prepared…
-Hey!
-I can't do this anymore.
The Earth is hurting!
My butt hurts so much.
I said the Earth is hurting.
I'm sorry.
Keep pedaling.
-Keep going! Faster!
-He's quite muscular.
You're watching The Quiet Interview,
an eco-friendly talk show.
To be perfectly honest,
we've let you off the hook
more than any other guest.
You just couldn't stop laughing.
-I'm sorry.
-So, we…
-Could I ask for a personal favor?
-Sure.
Can we act out Big Bet one more time?
Really? How's that a personal favor?
I personally loved the show.
-Really?
-I just want to act it out one more time.
-Did I do a good job before?
-Of course.
-Really?
-Yes, just add your own flair to it.
-"Moosik."
-"Are you…" Sorry.
THE QUIET INTERVIEW
"Moosik, can you lend me
just 100 million won? Please?"
"Are you done already?"
"Yeah. I have absolutely nothing
right now. I'm penniless."
"Is that so? Is that all you had?"
"I lost 20 billion won."
"So you only started with 20 billion won?"
"From the way you were gambling,
I thought you were a chaebol CEO."
"I guess…"
"I guess you've really got--"
"I guess you've really got
to snap out of it now."
The siren went off.
"Hold on. Ten days? Write me an IOU."
"Hey, bring me paper and a pen."
"Hey! Bring me paper…"
You can say your final goodbye
from the Quiet Room.
-Okay.
-I wanted to try this one more time.
-Can I try this scene from the room?
-Sure.
I can do better.
I really enjoy acting, you know?
-It's fun.
-It really is.
All right, so that wraps up
my personal request.
-We were supposed to…
-This is hilarious.
We were supposed to hear
Chuu's closing thoughts
-or a quick promotional message.
-But…
But instead, we'll give that chance
to someone in the audience.
Would anyone like to say a few words?
-I would.
-No, wait a minute!
Then why did I do all this?
Hi, I'm Park Sanghyeok,
a former producer on Chuu Can Do It.
Chuu was the most professional celebrity
I have ever met.
-When I would nap during breaks on set…
-What the heck?
…she'd personally go
-and buy me hot coffee.
-…buy me hot coffee.
-She poured the hot coffee on my thigh.
-…hot coffee on my thigh.
When I screamed,
she kicked me in the shin a few times
-to remind me we were on set.
-To remind me we were on set.
-Chuu always carried a magnifying glass.
-A magnifying glass.
She would use it
-to burn ants when shoots ran long.
-To burn ants.
-What the heck?
-She said we had to film
a sequel to the "Frozen Cat Challenge,"
but with a dog this time.
That wraps up this episode
of The Quiet Interview with Chuu.
-Thank you.
-What? Thank you.
Thank you.
Hi, I'm Park Sanghyeok,
a former producer on Chuu Can Do It.
Chuu was the most professional…
THE QUIET INTERVIEW
HOST: YOO BYUNGJAE
GUEST: CHUU
Translated by Jane Oh