Please keep a close watch
over His Royal Highness.
Yes.
Your Royal Highness!
Your Royal Highness…
His Royal Highness is now safe.
Fortunately, Mr. Charan intervened
and raised concerns
about the poison in time.
Thank you, Charan.
Mr. Charan has been reinstated
as your coach, Your Royal Highness.
Chakri didn't lie:
you did stay by my side.
I vow…
to protect you with my life.
Ran.
What?
Still find it strange?
Are you still thinking about…
last night?
Will you give me a bite of that macaron?
Please.
Give me a bite.
I want to be spoiled.
Would you really deny my plea?
Oh…
Prince Calvin!
I'm here to see Prince Khanin.
Oh…
Please proceed this way,
Your Royal Highness.
Have you recovered from your illness?
You sure have a sharp eye.
I'm feeling much better now,
both physically…
and emotionally.
Would you like some macarons?
I shall not disturb you.
Please feel free to carry on.
You just came to ask that?
Knowing that you've recovered,
I feel at ease.
I shall take my leave.
But I don't think he'll tell anyone.
I believe there is nothing
to worry about.
But from now on, let's be more cautious
when we're close, Your Royal Highness.
We don't need to.
Your Royal Highness…
I want to be this close to you.
What's wrong with that?
Let's do what I said.
Come on.
Let's go to my room.
Please get some rest.
Chakri,
I want something.
Can you order it for me?
You're talking about…
Lolane Intense Care Water Treatment?
We still have them, Your Royal Highness.
Yeah, that's good.
Make sure we're not running out of them.
But what I was talking about…
is…
What is it, Your Royal Highness?
What's the emblem
of the Davichmetha clan?
Uh…
A bird.
That's correct.
What kind of bird?
I need to know that, too?
Yes.
Who would know that?
A flamingo, I guess.
Nin, if you fail to be attentive,
you may face unexpected problems
during the Competition.
I just don't know the answer.
If you do, tell me.
How about this?
If I get it wrong one more time,
I'm willing to be punished by you.
Come on, I'll let you punish me.
What kind of punishment do you want?
Well…
One wrong answer,
and I'll give you a kiss.
One kiss for one wrong answer.
Right here.
How exactly is that a punishment?
Of course it is!
It's all on me.
You won't kiss me,
but I'll kiss you.
What?
You were literally…
Anyway,
it's just a kiss.
Let's focus on our lesson.
What is the former capital of Emmaly?
♫When looking at the sky,♫
Higher.
Again.
♫Yet I don't think it's much of a climb♫
You need to be faster.
♫If our love feels out of sight,♫
♫Just hold each other's hand tight♫
♫I believe that love conquers all,♫
♫Nothing can make it fall♫
Faster!
♫As long as you're with me,
right by my side,♫
♫I am not afraid♫
Your Royal Highness!
♫No matter how endless
the sky may seem,♫
♫And how treacherous
this journey might be,♫
♫If I must cross the heavens,
I'll set out willingly,♫
♫As long as you're there,
waiting for me♫
♫We'll build a bridge
of a million stars,♫
♫Let love guide us, no matter how far♫
♫All I ask
is to trust in love and in me,♫
♫Take my hand and you will see,♫
♫Above the sky, we're meant to be♫
You beat me again.
It's no fun at all.
Your shoulder twitches
before lunging again.
I didn't mean to.
What do you want me to do?
You need to stay more focused.
When all you care about is winning,
it tends to backfire.
Let me ask you something.
Does being adopted by His Majesty
mean you have to be a fencing expert?
I was born into the Phithakthewa family,
so I've been learning fencing
since I was little.
Why, though?
My family serves as royal guards,
protecting the Assavadevathins.
But why would they have to do that?
My ancestors swore
an oath to His Majesty
the moment he was crowned king.
So it's inherited?
Even if I hadn't said anything
to Grandfather,
you still would've become my guard.
Whether I become a royal guard or not
is solely up to His Majesty.
Do you protect me this well
just because of some oath
your ancestors made?
If it's my duty,
I need to do it
to the best of my ability.
How about…
this thing?
About that,
I'm sure you can tell
from everything I've done.
A reward for being so sweet.
It's been such a long day.
I don't wanna fence anymore.
Let's do something else.
How about we go have some fun?
Wanna touch him?
Is this how we're gonna have fun?
It sure will be fun.
Your turn.
Don't worry.
Dyrane never harms anyone.
Dyrane?
That's his name.
Come on, touch him.
Let's get to know each other,
so you'll feel more comfortable.
You and him seem so close.
I've trained him myself.
It's only natural we're close.
Seriously, being close to a horse?
Have you introduced yourself to him?
What?
I need to do that with a horse?
Yeah, so you'll get closer quickly.
Fine, here we go.
Dyrane…
I'm Nin,
Khanin.
Please don't kick me, okay?
I want to be friends.
Let's be friends, alright?
Is this a joke?
It was your plan, wasn't it?
That's for tricking me.
I won't do it again.
Come here.
Hold the saddle right here firmly.
Put your left foot in the stirrup
and push yourself up.
Go on, try it.
Here, hold this.
Don't tense up.
I'm not.
Let me know if it scares you.
It won't as long as you're here.
Ran…
Should we call it a day? We might fall.
He's not moving.
We'll never fall.
You should've told me you wanted a hug.
You should've done it if you knew.
It feels nice,
just being together like this.
Then, let's be together for eternity.
We've got tough training ahead.
I don't want you to worry too much.
I will be fine
as long as you're with me.
I've always been with you.
If there's anything
I can do for you, I will.
And I'll do my best
to always be there for you.
It's gonna be okay.
I'm right here.
I had Chakri order it a while ago,
but I couldn't find the right moment
to give it to you.
Wait…
You should close your eyes.
Wear these when it rains,
so nothing will scare you now.
I just want to help you
through tough times,
the way you helped me survive mine
when I had no one but you.
Thank you.
You don't have to worry
about anything now.
I'll be right here for you, always.
Have you had enough
of Emmaly yet, Prince Calvin?
I would never have, Your Majesty.
I've enjoyed it here,
and with some friends at the university,
it's even more enjoyable.
I'm grateful
you hold our country in high regard.
And how is your father doing?
He is pleased and in excellent health.
Should you need any help,
do not hesitate to ask.
I am glad to help.
I appreciate your kindness.
You did mention your university.
How is everything going?
Is Charan attending to you properly?
He has been looking after me well.
During this long holiday,
my friend has invited me
to visit his hometown in Meenanagarin.
I see.
Oh, you're here.
Join us for a meal.
Let me know if you need anything.
Prince Calvin just told me
he's visiting Meenanagarin.
Did you say Meenanagarin, Grandfather?
You want to come, too?
Yes.
I've just learned
about the dark champagne pearls,
so I want to see them
in their natural setting.
I see.
So,
would you like to join my trip?
May I accompany Prince Calvin
on the trip?
Alright, then.
I'm coming as well.
It's been a long time
since I last visited there.
Alright?
Let me give you a hand.
Why are you not joining me
for a bike ride?
Forgive me, Your Royal Highness.
But…
today,
my muscles are sore.
A bike ride after a while feels so nice.
I've had enough of the fencing training.
But…
if Prince Rachata finds out
that you skipped your training…
My father will never know about it.
Trust me.
Companions
must endure
and take the blame for one another.
Father!
- Prince Ramil…
- Stop it!
Stop!
Just let go of me.
Stop it, Father.
Please, Father.
- Let go!
- Please stop.
Leave me alone!
- Prince Ramil!
- Father!
- Prince Ramil…
- It's not his fault at all!
Prince Ramil, you should stop.
Father, it's not his fault!
- Prince Ramil…
- What the hell?
- Take him out now.
- Your Royal Highness…
- Prince Ramil…
- Please stop!
Prince Ramil!
You should stop.
- Have you gone nuts?
- Please, Prince Ramil.
- Why?
- Guards!
- Paytai!
- Get him out of here.
- Prince Ramil…
- Please stop, Father!
Please!
Paytai!
Who said you could stop?
I…
I'd like…
a break, please.
Are you really going to
defy Prince Rachata's command?
Stop!
Stay away from him.
That's a command from me,
Prince Ramil Bhuchongpisut.
Get rid of those.
Your Royal Highness,
please don't get involved.
If Prince Rachata finds out,
I'll surely face
even harsher punishment.
No!
Now!
No more punishment.
I deserved it, Your Royal Highness.
Being your companion comes with a duty
to take the blame for you.
Come with me.
I trust that
you will keep me safe.
What are you going to do to me?
So…
is everything going well?
Both of you,
place this bag
and those two
at the door.
There's so much stuff.
Come on.
As you're aware,
formal attire is needed
when visiting other cities.
Right,
did you bring
my Lolane Intense Care, too?
Oh…
Yes.
That has been prepared,
Your Royal Highness.
Forgive me, Your Royal Highness.
Please make haste
to His Majesty's presence immediately.
Wirun!
I wish to talk to His Majesty
about the mining matter.
I apologize, Your Royal Highness.
It'd be better to wait
until His Majesty is fully recovered.
I came to discuss a matter with you,
only to find out you had an accident.
Come on,
it's nothing serious.
No need to make a fuss.
Alright.
Are you okay, Grandfather?
I just had a little fall.
Do not be concerned.
He injured his wrist
and has caught a cold,
so the doctors advise
against any travel.
Sickness
is simply a part of nature
and can happen to all.
That said, the trip to Meenanagarin
must proceed as scheduled.
Otherwise, we'd be failing
Prince Calvin's trust.
I could use some rest, too.
Wishing you a speedy recovery,
Your Majesty.
I entrust Khanin and Prince Calvin
to your care.
They are on their way to Meenanagarin.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I shall take good care of
them and the entourage.
Please recover quickly, Your Majesty.
I am truly honored
by your visit to Meenanagarin.
The honor's all mine,
Your Royal Highness.
The royal attendants
shall take you to rest.
Please feel at ease, Prince Calvin.
Should you need anything, let us know.
I will.
I'm really glad
you came to visit us, Khanin.
I wish to learn about your culture
and see the dark champagne pearls
with my own eyes.
I humbly ask for your permission, Uncle.
You don't need my permission at all.
I'd like to stroll around the city
like an ordinary person.
Could you please treat me like one?
I'm more than happy to do as you ask.
However, as you are the important heir
of the Assavadevathins,
and Prince Calvin
will also be accompanying you,
I can't take any risks.
Therefore,
I will have my guards
discreetly protect you from a distance.
I hope you do not mind.
I don't, Uncle.
If my child were still alive,
he would be about your age.
I'm going to bed now.
Oh…
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
Should you need anything,
please don't hesitate to let me know.
Ran,
stay with me.
Not here.
Not there
and not here.
Looks like I'm the only one
wanting to stay with you.
I want to stay with you, too,
but I don't think
it's proper to do it here.
Why not?
No one would doubt it.
A guard's duty is
to be by the prince's side.
Trust me on this.
Listen to me, okay?
Rest well.
We're having a trip tomorrow.
What a nice car to ride in.
It seems perfect for everyday use.
Do you recall that…
we've also ridden in
another model of this car?
Are there two models?
Yes.
You sure are good at this.
You know exactly
what fits each situation.
Oh…
Have you been here long?
Yeah.
Let's go for a walk, then.
Calvin!
Is everything okay?
Yeah, everything's fine.
I was just texting my friend.
You've got a friend here?
He's a friend from Morpheus,
and he's from around here.
It's a semester break, so he's home.
I see.
So…
wanna go see him for a bit?
We can plan to meet up again later
to return to the palace.
Sounds nice?
Prince Wasin firmly instructed that…
Just send someone
to follow him at a distance.
A distance, you know?
Come on,
we're on a trip here.
Just relax.
I understand his concerns, though.
You can send someone,
but make sure they keep their distance.
Thank you.
Ran,
why are there only male vendors?
None of them are female.
In Meenanagarin,
it's believed that the husband
should provide for the family
while the wife is responsible
for the housework.
What?
Seriously?
Why do they still believe
in things like that?
What if a man doesn't want
to be the provider?
What if a woman doesn't want
to stay home?
Why can't we do things we love?
They should stop imposing
these roles on people.
Not saying anything?
You also believe in it?
I just think beliefs…
are the hardest thing to change.
But that doesn't mean
change is impossible,
right?
Yes.
It just takes time.
Yeah.
Let's check it out.
Feel free to look around.
Let me know if you like anything.
Feel free.
Let's go further.
Okay.
Feel free to check them out.
- Hello.
Oh, you're the prince!
Do you have any dark champagne pearls?
Oh!
I just happen to have the last one!
Finally, a real one!
It's beautiful.
What do people usually make
with pearls this size?
They're usually made
into necklaces, Your Royal Highness.
A single pearl can enhance the elegance
of both the piece and the wearer.
So now we have to look for
a necklace maker?
About that,
please leave it to me.
Thanks.
Isn't it pretty?
It is.
- We'll take this, please.
- Yes, sir.
June!
June…
This is June, my sister.
My name is Calvin.
Are you okay?
You alright?
He came to travel.
You should show him around.
But Mom isn't home yet.
I can't leave you.
I'll be fine.
It's nothing.
I can wait.
You can stay with her.
Jay, just take him on a walk.
I'll be fine.
It's nothing.
Coming back this time,
her condition's gotten so much worse.
It's hard to believe
someone so young
could be that ill.
Now…
I understand
why you're part of the protesters.
This was never just about her illness.
The truth is,
my dad passed away
from a severe lung disease.
After that,
we left Assavadevathin and moved here.
I originally joined the movement
just to get justice for my dad…
and June.
But once I got involved,
I realized something.
If we don't fight for change,
how many more lives
will end up like my dad and my sister?
If we all stay quiet
and don't speak up,
how will anyone in charge
even know this problem exists?
But I think…
those in power
also want to help the people.
If they really do,
why is there no sign of progress?
If they do care,
shouldn't there be
some solutions by now?
Do you want to join me tomorrow?
Sure.
I appreciate your understanding.
We're friends after all.
Friends…
share both the good and the bad, right?
I never thought I'd like you this much.
The super strict…
and meticulous one…
Yet when you give me what I want,
you'll become the sweetest!
I can't give you everything you want.
- I have my duties to…
- Come on.
I know, I know.
That word again.
So being strict
is part of your duties,
but falling for me
is beyond them, right?
You understand me, right?
Yeah.
I'll try to.
Will you stay with me tonight?
I can't.
Again?
Jeez.
At least…
join me for dinner,
please!
Come on, we'll just have dinner.
It's not a big deal.
Will you say yes?
Take a seat.
How was everything?
Did you have a good time, dear?
Your city is truly beautiful, Uncle.
And the air feels so fresh.
Make sure you come back often, then.
You're always welcome here.
Uncle,
actually,
there is something I wish to request.
What is it?
I came across this flyer.
And I hope to join the campaign
and sing with the people.
Sure.
The younger generation
holds you in great admiration.
To them,
you represent change for our country.
Meeting you in person,
they'll grow even more fond of you
and offer greater support.
Thank you, Uncle.
But I will have my guards
discreetly protect you from a distance.
I hope you do not mind.
I'd like you to stay by my side today.
I don't want you too far from me.
Why?
Afraid I'll disappear on you?
We have to stay alert all the time.
I don't want to risk you getting hurt.
Public places can be unpredictable.
What happened in Davichmetha
might happen again.
I know,
but I also want to stand
with the people.
You understand me, right?
I want to use my title
to truly make a difference.
[Your prosperity comes
at the cost of our suffering]
[We need cleaner air]
[We deserve air to breathe,
not dust in our lungs]
It's turned off?
Thank you.
Let me know if you need help.
[Say no to lung cancer]
Thank you.
- Hey, Jay.
- What?
Prince Khanin's joining us.
He is?
Yeah.
He has…
visited our university.
Oh…
- Oh, right.
Wait, this is gonna be fun.
Come with me.
Come on, Jay.
Hurry.
Quick!
Prince Khanin…
May I join you, too?
But…
I wanted to help.
Thank you, Your Royal Highness.
Then…
Please proceed this way.
This way.
Dear everyone who loves Emmaly,
let us sing with all our voices,
so those in power hear us
loud and strong.
Okay?
Okay!
- Yay!
- Okay?
Let those in power
recognize the hardships we endure.
Let this song turn Emmaly's fate
toward a brighter tomorrow.
Exactly!
♫Hard to see the road ahead♫
♫Through the quiet dread♫
♫The mist is thick,♫
♫The sky is dead♫
♫With our fading breath♫
♫Keep your eyes open wide♫
♫Every soul deserves to breathe♫
♫Don't walk away from silent cries♫
♫Each heart longs to live♫
♫Whispers in the mist♫
♫Always echo, never quit♫
♫We rise inside the mist♫
♫They don't see, but we persist♫
- ♫Whispers in the mist♫
- Louder!
- Sing it clearly!
- ♫Always echo, never quit♫
♫Even shadows can resist♫
♫Hear whispers in the mist♫
The Assavadevathins
are knowingly taking innocent lives.
Ran,
stop it.
I want to talk to him.
Your Royal Highness…
Your Royal Highness!
What did you mean by that?
The mine in Assavadevathin…
It killed my parents.
That mine has blood on its hands.
The King is killing more people!
You're all so damn selfish.
Your mine does nothing
but spread toxic dust.
We're dying out here.
Do you even care?
If it weren't for your greed,
my parents would still be here.
- Hey…
- Hey!
Just take it easy!
Stop!
Come on, calm down.
Hey, you're going too far.
Think you can do anything to me, huh?
You're hurting us!
You're harming your people!
You're harming us!
Things are starting to go wrong.
We need to go.
Hey, don't be violent!
Don't hurt them!
Stop!
- Calm down!
- Take it easy.
Just calm down.
Don't be violent.
Hey!
Stop!
Don't hurt them.
Calm down! Stop!
He didn't harm me, Uncle.
We were the ones who went too far.
He nearly lost his life
from suffocation.
You can't really tell
who's on which side.
Your Royal Highness!
Trust no one
but yourself, Nin.
Not even me.
Your Royal Highness…
- Please…
- Sorry to bother your personal time.
I can't even trust
my own family.
Come closer.
I'll let you have a bite.
I enjoyed our stroll today.
Can you take me here often?
If nothing's in my way,
I will.
Next time, let's bring this along
as a snack,
so we can eat it anywhere.
♫The only love I've longed for,♫
♫Just the word "love" from you,
and that's all♫
♫Let me hear it, I won't ask for more♫
♫I need your love♫
♫The only one I adore,♫
♫My heart's been waiting
just for you, my all♫
♫Oh, I need your love♫