FICTIONAL EVENTS,
VIEWER DISCRETION ADVISED.
I am taking part in the Royal Competition.
The Assavadevathins will also participate.
I will participate
in the Royal Competition.
No rule forbids women from competing.
With you both competing,
it'll be exciting.
Train hard, Brother.
Nothing is beyond my control.
This is my grandson,
Khanin Assavadevathin.
Through the tears, I stared out the window
I couldn't see anything even a shadow
Every second's moving too slow
All I could do is hold
Hanging here in the longest, darkest night
At least the clock hand is moving wise
Sitting, taking longer deep sighs
Here comes another try
Light of a new dawn
It's time to move on
Waiting for a new day
Better days are on the way
And the sun will rise again
Waiting for a new day
It's gonna be okay
I'm Lady Aon.
I'm from Thailand.
and so fabulous!
Thank you for joining us today, Lady Aon.
Please excuse me.
Thank you.
Thank you for joining us,
Emperor of Da Caihong.
Your presence
at this momentous celebration
is the greatest honor
I could ever receive.
To be part of your magnificent celebration
is a tremendous honor for me as well.
The Emperor of Da Caihong,
who has long been
one of Emmaly's key trade partners.
It's an honor to meet you, Your Majesty.
My name is Khanin.
Nice to meet you, too.
Your piano performance today…
was truly enchanting and beautiful.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I hope today's celebration brings you joy.
Indeed, it does.
On behalf of our nation, Bhujar,
we humbly offer congratulations
to Your Majesty.
There's no need to be so formal.
We're close neighbors,
just like one big family.
Nice to meet you, Prince Khanin.
I'm Prince Calvin.
Nice to meet you, too, Prince Calvin.
Before long, I might need to ask a favor
from both of you.
My son, Calvin, is interested in studying
at the University of the Arts here.
It is a great honor for our country.
Today,
I'm truly honored
to be part of this celebration.
You are exceptionally gifted
in music, Your Royal Highness.
Thank you for your kind words.
It's because I've had a passion for music
since I was younger.
Hello.
On behalf of Bon Dre Cher, it is a great
honor to be part of this celebration.
Congratulations, Prince Khanin.
I'm honored by your presence as well.
Apart from your musical talent,
your fencing abilities
are equally impressive.
We've heard of your achievements
while you were still in the UK.
Thank you.
Fencing has always been a part of my life.
I grew up with it.
Ande Emmaly is known
for having the finest fencers.
Your Royal Highness,
it's time to get ready
for tonight's dance.
Thank you.
The pleasure is mine.
Khanin, the celebration is magnificent.
Come, Ava. Will you dance with me?
Sure.
Where the time has gone
I just know you're my world, my dawn
You've taken my heart, my soul, my way
In this night, it's us who'll stay
Moonlight shines so bright
Thousands of stars join us tonight
Every step we take, stars align
This moment feels like it's truly mine
The world's a fairy tale
In your arms tonight
I wish to stop this time
And call you my endless light
Dancing in the moonlight with you
Under the stars, just us two
With every beat, my heart's complete
You, you made my dream come true
Now and forever with you
Hold me so tight
All through the night
Thanks.
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
Let's take a break, Your Royal Highness.
Come on.
Please go on. Have fun.
Your Royal Highness?
Please listen carefully.
Stick to the script.
Any unexpected questions…
particularly those concerning Mr. Charan…
Must not be addressed.
I understand, Chakri.
Mr. Charan, well…
I'll wait here.
This way, please, Your Royal Highness.
I still find this odd.
On behalf of the people of Emmaly,
I would like to offer my congratulations
and welcome Your Royal Highness back.
May I respectfully ask
about how your life was
before you returned to Emmaly?
I grew up in London.
To be honest, I never imagined
that I would ever experience
something like this in my life.
Living in such a grand palace
and living a life so different
from what I was used to.
Adapting to this new reality
is incredibly challenging for me.
I'm not quite used to it.
During the dance,
Your Royal Highness seemed close
with Mr. Charan.
Could you share more
about that connection?
Please excuse us.
We're past the allotted time,
and Prince Khanin needs to proceed
with his next appointment.
Are you tired, Your Royal Highness?
May I offer you some treats or snacks?
Sounds nice.
Thanks, Chakri.
You've been a great help to me today.
Are you tired?
It's my duty, Your Royal Highness.
Aren't you tired of standing? Have a seat.
Right here.
What are your duties?
To protect and take care of Prince Khanin,
and to protect and remain loyal
to the Assavadevathins.
Those are my duties.
When it's just the two of us,
you don't need to speak so formally.
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
Okay.
Why weren't you with me
in the interview room?
Answer me.
At the dance,
a lot of people
were keeping an eye on us.
And?
Nothing matters more
than your public image.
"I care about you."
That's how you say it.
You don't know how to say it?
I care about you.
You do?
As what?
All right.
Yeah, I know. I'll be there.
Gosh, this will blow up the Internet.
They're flirting!
Your Royal Highness!
Your Royal Highness…
Chakri?
You…
He forgot to take off the mic,
and we could hear
their intimate conversation.
Guys, this is like a drama.
So we got this news.
Prince Khanin and Mr. Charan
are a perfect match!
Gosh!
What are your thoughts on this?
I don't think it's possible
that they're a couple.
Charan is wise
and well aware of his status.
So you believe…
it's all just to draw attention?
Dating rumors that spark curiosity
can really stir up attention,
but it's unclear if this one
was intentional or just an accident.
How are you still smiling, Ava?
Do you think popularity
is just a trivial thing?
It may not directly affect the Competition
according to the old rules,
but I don't think
things will go that smoothly.
His Majesty…
will likely make some adjustments.
That's why
you should start looking for a coach
to train you from now on.
Mira is already the perfect fit.
I shall take my leave.
"I care about you." That's how you say it.
PRINCE KHANIN AND HIS GUARD TALKING!
You don't know how to say it?
I care about you.
You do?
As what?
Make sure Prince Ramil's bike
is in good condition.
Yes, sir.
Your Royal Highness…
How did this go viral?
ALL EYES ON PRINCE KHANIN AND HIS GUARD.
The Assavadevathins could have
intentionally stirred up this rumor.
Do you know why I called for you?
To ask us about the rumors?
Although today's world
embraces marriage equality…
you're my grandson…
and I've adopted Charan.
Any relationship
that goes beyond family ties…
would be inappropriate.
Grandfather, Charan and I are close
simply because he was the one
who brought me back.
We've been through
life-threatening situations together.
But care that goes beyond that closeness…
doesn't look good, Charan.
Rest assured, Your Majesty.
I'm merely taking care
of His Royal Highness
in my capacity as his royal guard.
I have no other feelings or intentions.
He's right, Grandfather.
I don't have
any feelings for him, either.
Given that this is Khanin's introduction,
you must exercise extra caution
from here on.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
The rumors.
What are you going to do about them?
I humbly request
your pardon, Your Majesty.
I have a suggestion to make.
At this time,
His Royal Highness is receiving
overwhelming support from the public.
Would it not be wise
to shape his public image
as someone warm and accessible?
I believe such an approach
would win him public affection.
If the Royal Palace
attempts to correct the rumors now,
it might raise doubts among the public,
suggesting a cover-up or fabrication.
Might this not affect
His Royal Highness' reputation adversely?
Smile a bit wider.
Ready? This way, please.
Please smile, Mr. Charan.
This day's finally over.
Your Royal Highness,
how about taking a shower first?
It could help you feel better.
Let's go.
Stop right there.
Stop.
I can do it myself.
It's been a long day. Go get some rest.
Were you talking to me, too?
Who said you could leave?
Your Royal Highness…
There's no one else here.
Okay.
When you spoke to Grandfather,
what did you mean…
when you said
you were merely being my royal guard?
That's what I have to do.
But we're friends, too, aren't we?
If there's nothing else…
please rest.
You have an early lesson
on Emmaly tomorrow.
In ancient times,
Emmaly was long ruled
by the Bhuchongpisut royal dynasty.
However, during the colonial era,
Emmaly fell in defeat.
Invading soldiers
oppressed the people for decades,
plunging them
into poverty and hardship.
Eventually, they rose up in unison,
and the heir of the Bhuchongpisuts
rose with them.
He challenged the enemy
to a fencing duel.
Whichever side prevailed
would lay rightful claim to Emmaly.
The Bhuchongpisut led the nation
to reclaim its independence.
Out of deep gratitude and reverence,
he named his father the King of Emmaly.
As the victory had been won
through the alliance of four clans,
Prince Thanes Bhuchongpisut announced
the Royal Fencing Competition
to determine the rightful heir
to the throne.
What's on your mind, Your Royal Highness?
Nothing.
Forget it.
Go on. I'm listening.
What awaits Your Royal Highness
after the current king
abdicates the throne
is the Royal Fencing Competition,
held to determine the next king.
Should the heir of any clan
emerge victorious,
their father shall ascend
as the next King of Emmaly.
So, now that
I'm finally becoming useful,
the Assavadevathins decided
to bring me back?
Your Royal Highness…
At the time,
they were simply trying to keep you safe.
So that I could compete one day.
I don't mind it, actually.
You both know
that I returned and agreed to compete
just to find out
what happened to my dad.
But even now, I still don't know a thing.
May I have your word…
that if I tell you this,
you will not put yourself in danger?
What have you got?
Please promise me first.
Okay.
I promise.
I had Vetith look into the evidence I got
from one of the attackers in the UK.
As you can see,
he really is a police officer
in Bhuchongpisut.
Look at this.
That's the photo the Royal Palace
released to the press.
Prince Rachata.
I looked into his background.
He climbed the ranks way too fast.
The attempt on Khanin's life
could be linked to the Bhuchongpisuts.
Maybe you're right, maybe not.
Have you told Grandfather?
You're the first to know.
- And I'll--
- Don't tell him yet.
I think…
we should investigate it ourselves first.
Also…
I want to go to Bhuchongpisut.
His DNA matches Tharin's 99%.
Prince Khanin has arrived.
Khanin, did your journey go smoothly?
We are delighted
that you came to visit our city.
My journey did go smoothly,
Uncle and Ramil.
Khanin,
I'm very glad
that you came to visit Bhuchongpisut.
How about this?
I'll get Ramil to show you around.
You're the same age.
Get to know each other.
So you won't feel uneasy around me.
Thank you for your concern, Uncle.
Once you've finished touring around,
I'll have Ramil take you to our museum.
It's full of historical facts
about Emmaly.
You'll have the chance to learn more.
Understood, Father.
If you have any questions at all,
I'm here to answer them.
After all, the Bhuchongpisut clan
remains the oldest royal family.
That sounds like a great idea.
I hope you don't mind, Ramil.
Follow me. This way.
Khanin,
I've taken you around the entire palace.
But there's one more important place
that I'd like you to see.
An important place?
Isn't that the Bhuchongpisut Palace?
There's another important place
outside the palace
that's closed to outsiders.
Only the Bhuchongpisuts have access.
If you don't mind,
would you go with me this evening?
I don't think Ramil had anything
to do with Prince Rachata's plans.
Or maybe the Bhuchongpisuts
aren't even responsible.
We can't be sure of that yet.
Either way, do not trust Prince Ramil.
I don't trust anyone but you.
Are you sure you don't need an escort?
I'll be fine.
He wouldn't act so brazenly.
Your Royal Highness, always remember
that Prince Ramil is your rival
in the Royal Competition.
Never underestimate him.
I won't.
I'll call you if anything happens.
This stunning place
is closed to outsiders, Ramil?
Certain places…
aren't meant for everyone.
You may not know this yet,
but your mother, Princess Khunita,
was from the Bhuchongpisut bloodline.
She was my father's cousin.
We're actually family.
Anyway…
please let me give you a gift, brother.
Thank you, Ramil.
When I was just a kid,
whenever I felt low…
I'd come here by myself.
The pressure from all the expectations…
made me feel so small.
Being part of the royal family
must have weighed heavily on that kid.
It was to help you stand
with the grace you possess today.
This is the Serpent King statue,
a revered figure that our family
has honored and worshiped for centuries.
You might find it familiar
since the emblem of the Bhuchongpisut clan
was inspired by this very statue.
You can compare it
with the bracelet I just gave you.
Khanin…
The bracelet…
Did you drop it around here?
You may not know this…
but in the Bhuchongpisut clan,
we value every gift we receive
and protect it with our lives.
But don't worry.
I'll go find it out there
where we came from.
Keep looking around here, okay?
Okay.
Prepare a meal for His Royal Highness.
- You may do it now.
- Understood.
Professor Charan.
Why are you all by yourself?
Where are Prince Ramil and Prince Khanin?
They went to the forest behind the palace.
When did they go?
Four hours ago.
They must be on their way back.
Khanin's gone missing,
and I can't reach his phone.
Hang on, Mr. Charan.
Why are you back already?
Weren't you supposed to return tomorrow?
This is not the time.
We need to find Prince Khanin.
- Prince Khanin!
- Khanin.
- Khanin!
- Prince Khanin!
Prince Khanin?
Prince Khanin!
We went this way.
I'll go this way.
Prince Khanin!
You three go that way.
The rest, come with me.
Yes, Your Highness.
Prince Khanin!
Prince Khanin.
Charan!
Is that you?
I'm right here.
Are you okay, Your Royal Highness?
Yeah.
I fell off my bike.
The tires are flat.
All I could do was wait.
Are you wounded?
Got this when I fell off.
I'm sorry to make you worry.
Please don't be.
It's my fault.
How is it your fault?
It was just an accident.
No, it wasn't.
It's still my fault.
If I fail to act when you're in danger,
then my oath to protect you with my life
means nothing at all.
- But…
- Your Royal Highness.
You mean more to me
than you could ever imagine.
Please get up slowly.
Well, you could've just helped me walk.
You've found Khanin?
Khanin.
I'm really sorry.
I actually went back to the cave,
but I didn't see you there.
We must have missed each other.
Right, the bracelet.
I found it.
I'd like to give it back to you.
This may hurt, Young Prince.
Hang in there.
Khanin.
Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
Please don't be, Uncle.
It's your fault,
letting Ramil take Khanin
into the forest unaccompanied.
Ramil, have you apologized to him?
I asked you if you've apologized to him.
Please don't do that, Uncle.
I'm not mad, and I don't blame him.
I just…
I don't think it's appropriate
for me to stay here tonight.
I'd like to take my leave, Uncle.
That was a stupid thing to do.
You are clearly dumb.
You think I don't know?
You chose to go into that forest
because there's no signal there.
And the missing bracelet…
That was you, wasn't it?
No, Father.
No?
Listen to me.
As long as the Assavadevathins
are still in power,
don't you dare pull stunts
with Khanin again.
And just to be clear…
your stupidity got Paytai into this!
I shall take my leave,
Your Royal Highness.
Hold on.
Well…
I shall take my leave.
It wasn't your fault.
I was being stupid.
You got caught up
in the royal families' games.
I'm glad, though…
that you found me before they did.
I'm glad to have found you, too.
Thanks.
I believe…
the Bhuchongpisuts do not mean well
toward the Assavadevathins.
Something feels wrong.
Anyway, don't tell Grandfather
about today's incident
and about the attacker being
a police officer.
Make sure that none of the guards…
ever speak of what happened today.
It's impossible to keep secrets
from His Majesty.
Have a seat.
What brings you back early?
His Royal Highness has journeyed
as he pleased.
I'm sure you know
there's nowhere safer than here.
Yes, Your Majesty.
What do you think of that picture?
The constellation of the twins…
glowing brilliantly in the sky.
It looks quite romantic, Your Majesty.
The two stand side by side,
yet it is no easy feat.
Legend has it
that Pollux is like a god,
bestowed with immortality.
Castor, on the other hand,
is like a mortal with a fleeting life.
The two cannot be together…
unless Pollux sacrifices his immortality.
And should this tale culminate in death,
would you still find it romantic, my dear?
My apologies, Your Majesty.
In my humble opinion,
even though they stand together
as stars in the sky…
their tale endures as one of love
and leaves a lasting impression.
I'm sure you'd make a great artist.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Right, I almost forgot.
Prince Calvin of Bhujar
is to come and further his studies
in the arts at your university.
For such an important guest,
I think you're the most suitable.
My only fear is that…
I won't have enough time
for Prince Khanin's training.
Forget that.
Go on and do what you truly love.
As for Khanin, you can leave him to me
so that he finds greater focus.
I hope you understand.
Yes, Your Majesty.
It is my belief that Prince Khanin
may have ordered Mr. Charan
not to speak of what happened
in Bhuchongpisut.
Forget it.
Nothing bad happened. That's enough.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Some distance
between Khanin and Charan
is probably for the best.
This is Calvin,
an exchange student from Bhujar.
Please keep an eye on him for me.
Sure.
Why are you here, Your Royal Highness?
Why aren't you at the palace with me?
I was just doing my duty.
What about your duty to protect me,
to take care of me,
and protect and remain loyal
to the Assavadevathins?
Charan, come sit with me.
I'm afraid that--
That's an order.
Check out the buzz we're getting.
This is a good sign, right?
How soft.
There something's even softer.