=In Love With Loving You=
(Based on Love by Erxi on Qimao)
=Episode 4=
(This Year's Autumn Semester
Aid Recipients)
(Ji Xuan, Female, Environmental Art Design
Aid Amount: 2,000 RMB)
Hello, Mr. Zhang?
Ji Xuan, I have some good news for you.
Someone saw your profile
and decided to sponsor your education.
Could you give me
his contact information?
I want to thank him in person.
It's anonymous.
He only left an email address.
He said you can communicate via email.
Okay, please send it to me later.
Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
If you're creatively drained, go home.
Don't waste my time.
Who is she?
- Why was she in Mr. Song's room?
- Yeah.
Then Xie Yao...
Go back.
Take the day off today
to clear your head.
Redo it when your mind is clear.
- Yes.
Quick, let's go.
Who was that woman just now?
What's it to you?
I'm your fiancée.
You owe me an explanation.
Listen to me, Xie Yao.
Marry whoever you want.
It has nothing to do with me.
Song Zhaoli! Song Zhaoli!
I checked. You're the one
involved in that scandal, right?
You are...
Did you often sleep your way up?
I'm Xie Yao, the marketing manager
of Song Corp.
Technically, I'm also your client.
So, Miss Xie,
what exactly do you want to say?
Sorry, I didn't mean to.
Sorry, I didn't mean to either.
Let me be honest with you.
I am Song Zhaoli's fiancée.
You better know your place.
I don't like Song Zhaoli.
I'm not interested in him.
You don't need to see me as your rival.
You're not interested in him?
Then why did you sleep with him?
I was just playing with him.
Mr. Song?
Was it fun?
Want to play some more?
Are you crazy?
You called me all the way here
just to walk me like a dog?
You're too weak. Practice abstinence.
So aggressive.
Not working out as the other man?
Let's talk.
Master Liao's emotional counseling.
I heal heartbreak.
Have you been in love?
Never.
But I'm a groom every night.
(Ji Xuan)
(Sorry, Mr. Song.)
(I want to explain it to you.)
(I absolutely did not mean
to badmouth you behind your back.)
(I hope you don't take it to heart.)
Are you pissed off, Mr. Song?
Mind your own business.
Does Ji Xuan know you were her sponsor?
She doesn't know.
Don't tell her.
Impressive. Pure love, huh?
You don't want Ji Xuan
to be with you out of gratitude.
You spent money and effort,
yet you're hiding your contributions.
You're truly a role model
for the other man.
She doesn't need to know that.
Song,
all these years,
I've actually wanted to ask you.
Why did you sponsor Ji Xuan then?
Do you remember
when my brother and I were kidnapped?
On my way back after being rescued...
(IOU)
(Debtor: Ji Jianye)
Ji Jianye borrowed money
to start a business
and ended up ruining himself.
But the debt remains.
Listen to me.
Today, whether you want to or not,
you two are paying it back.
Stop the car.
If you really have no money,
pay for it with your place.
- No.
- My dad left this place to us.
I won't sell it.
I'll pay back the money my dad owed you.
Do you think I'm stupid?
How can a little girl like you
pay it back?
Xuan!
Either kill me today,
or we sign the contract.
I will repay every cent
of the money my dad owed you.
Xuan.
You're tougher than me.
Fine, we'll do it your way.
Let's go.
Xuan?
Mom, I'm fine.
Xuan.
Let's go back.
My brother died back then.
I didn't want to live.
But that girl, burdened with debt,
fought so hard to live.
So you fell for her?
I didn't.
You didn't?
But I heard
that Ji Xuan came out of your room
this morning.
I'm just having some fun.
(Song Zhaoli)
(Mr. Qiu, I think
I said the wrong thing to Mr. Song.)
(Do you know where he is?)
(I want to apologize to him.)
You may go back.
I climbed over the rocks to get here.
Alright.
(Mr. Qiu)
(Mr. Song is at the beach.)
(Location)
(You can go find him and cheer him up.)
(Mr. Song isn't that petty.)
Mr. Song. Mr. Song.
What a coincidence.
You like running too, Miss Ji?
Why are you running in a suit?
I came specifically to apologize to you.
I misspoke this morning.
I'm sorry.
Please don't take it to heart.
Is this an apology to me
or to your client?
Is there a difference?
The difference is huge.
To me, there's no difference.
You are my client, after all.
How about this?
We run back to the hotel together.
If you're faster than me,
I'll forgive you.
Okay.
♪In the vast sea of stars♪
♪Flickering neon lights♪
♪Longing spreads
throughout the universe♪
♪Every star is♪
♪My heartbeat for you♪
♪Want to ride the evening breeze♪
♪And land in your arms♪
♪The starry sky is like your eyes♪
♪In the blue sky♪
♪Your smile still lingers♪
♪You are the brightest light
in my regrets♪
♪You are the painful greeting
in my despair♪
♪Can't find a cure♪
♪To love you after we've parted♪
♪You are the time I most want to keep♪
♪The future I strive toward
in the darkness♪
♪Slowly getting closer to you♪
♪How I wish
I could give you my sunshine♪
♪You are the brightest light
in my regrets♪
♪Can't find a cure♪
♪To love you after we've parted♪
♪You are the time I most want to keep♪
♪The future I strive toward
in the darkness♪
♪Slowly getting closer to you♪
♪How I wish
I could give you my sunshine♪