=In Love With Loving You=
(Based on Love by Erxi on Qimao)
=Episode 10=
Xuan.
Wu Shu told me everything.
The reason you joined Song Group
and your situation there.
Take this.
Put it on your desk.
Within half an hour,
everyone in the company will know
you have a knight in shining armor.
Seriously?
It's a passive skill
for Song Group employees, gossiping.
Here, let me hold it for you.
Thanks.
Mr. Song.
See you later, Xuan.
Mr. Wu.
Come to my office.
Ji Xuan.
This elevator's too crowded.
You should wait for the next one.
You and Ji Xuan...
Are you two dating?
Yes. My cousin is Ji Xuan's best friend.
I had the inside track.
Do you know
the company forbids office romances?
Mr. Song.
I don't recall that being
in the company rules.
Mr. Wu, you've been
working here for so long.
We have many written rules
and plenty of unwritten ones too.
Ask Qiu Lin.
Help me, help me.
Mr. Song.
The company really
doesn't have that rule.
I remembered wrong?
The person in charge
of the Xisha Resort is on leave.
We need someone to step in.
You mean to send me there?
Good pay, less work,
double the performance bonus.
Maxed-out travel budget.
I'll go. I'll go.
Goodbye, Mr. Wu.
Goodbye, Mr. Song.
Are you and Wu Rui very close?
No, we're just colleagues.
Mr. Song, everyone in the group knows
that Miss Xie is your fiancée.
If you say you are
banning office romances,
that justification is too flimsy.
It won't reflect well on you.
Oh, so you were just being thoughtful.
I thought you two had a deep friendship.
(I must not let him find out)
(we were both once members
of the boss complaint group.)
Anyone there?
Can anyone hear me?
(Wu Rui)
Sorry, the person you're calling
is currently unavailable.
Why isn't he answering?
(Mr. Qiu)
Xuan.
Mr. Song?
Miss Ji.
Mr. Qiu ran a red light while driving
and got pulled over by the police,
so I came.
Hello?
Turn all the lights in the company on.
We have a rule. No overtime after 9 PM.
The power automatically cuts off.
It's my fault that he ran the red light.
I should still send him a message.
- No need.
- It's all...
I still should send one.
It's no big deal.
Mr. Qiu and Wu Rui
are good friends privately.
I called Wu Rui, but he didn't answer,
so I contacted Mr. Qiu.
Wu Rui is on a business trip.
Didn't he tell you?
He did.
I... I was busy
looking up info on Mr. Yu.
I forgot.
Alright.
Let me drive you home.
I can go back myself.
Let me.
I'll go in.
Thank you, Mr. Song.
Go to sleep early.
Bye.
Good night.
(Ji Xuan.)
(When will I be able
to step into this yard legitimately?)
Delivery guy.
No insulated box.
Mr. Song!
Mr. Song, are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'll change your lock tomorrow.
To be safe, stay at my place tonight.
Okay.
You take the master bedroom.
I take the guest room.
No need, Mr. Song.
I sleep in the guest room.
It's fine.
If you stay here,
word will get out eventually.
Staying in the master bedroom
sounds much better.
You haven't eaten?
These seem to be dishes
from my hometown.
I'm more capable than you think.
Try it.
It's good.
If you ever get tired of being CEO,
maybe consider becoming a food blogger.
But I only want to cook for you.
Too cheesy.
I'll be your blotting paper.
Let me do it.
You like roses too?
Yes.
Do you have enemies?
No enemies, just creditors.
Have you ever dealt
with something like this before?
I've had paint thrown at me,
locks glued shut.
♪In the vast sea of stars♪
♪Flickering neon lights♪
♪Longing spreads
throughout the universe♪
♪Every star is♪
♪My heartbeat for you♪
♪Want to ride the evening breeze♪
♪And land in your arms♪
♪The starry sky is like your eyes♪
♪In the blue sky♪
♪Your smile still lingers♪
♪You are the brightest light
in my regrets♪
♪You are the painful greeting
in my despair♪
♪Can't find a cure♪
♪To love you after we've parted♪
♪You are the time I most want to keep♪
♪The future I strive toward
in the darkness♪
♪Slowly getting closer to you♪
♪How I wish
I could give you my sunshine♪
♪You are the brightest light
in my regrets♪
♪Can't find a cure♪
♪To love you after we've parted♪
♪You are the time I most want to keep♪
♪The future I strive toward
in the darkness♪
♪Slowly getting closer to you♪
♪How I wish
I could give you my sunshine♪