=In Love With Loving You=
(Based on Love by Erxi on Qimao)
=Episode 11=
Do you have enemies?
No enemies, just creditors.
Have you ever dealt
with something like this before?
I've had paint thrown at me,
locks glued shut.
How much debt is left?
Still 100,000 yuan in debt.
But Mr. Liao gave me 200,000 yuan
for my four years of college.
So altogether, that's 300,000 yuan.
You needn't repay Liao Bei.
I need to. I absolutely must.
I've owed this debt of gratitude
for too many years.
If I don't repay it, I
won't be able to live with myself.
Besides, Mr. Liao is the one
who actually sponsored me.
Isn't it improper for you
to be so generous with others' money?
True.
Mr. Song, you said before
that I'd get a commission if I secured
the Bisheng project.
Is that true?
If you complete it.
I'll work hard.
Why did you choose Wu Rui?
He's reliable.
Scarred by Xiao Jin,
you're now going for the safe type?
Wu Rui's at least
more straightforward than you.
How do you know I'm not straightforward?
Mr. Song, I'm done eating.
I'm going to bed first.
Just you wait.
Mr. Song, you go up first.
I'll come up ten minutes after you
to prevent misunderstandings.
So you're saying
you'll arrive later than your boss?
Then I'll go up first?
You want your boss to wait here for you?
Then what do you suggest?
We'll go up together.
What are you doing?
Mr. Liao?
Why are you two together?
Last night, did you two...
Mr. Song and I just ran into each other.
Let's go upstairs.
Mr. Liao, I made you a cup of coffee.
Mr. Liao doesn't like coffee.
Right. I don't like coffee.
I even forgot it myself.
Then I'll make you some tea.
Ji Xuan,
the company didn't hire you
to study beverages.
Sit down.
Have you found anything about Mr. Yu?
I asked a friend at the airline.
Mr. Yu lands in Qingcheng
next Wednesday.
But strangely,
starting that day, the beach campsite
is booked exclusively for a month.
Mei, this is where I proposed to you.
Revisiting this place,
but now I'm here all alone.
Over there.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
This area is booked exclusively.
Sir,
it's my girlfriend
and my anniversary today.
Mind if we share the area?
Let them in.
Yes.
Please, you two.
Is this cooked?
Not yet, I think.
It's good.
Are you okay?
I got burned.
I'm fine.
Sir, try my girlfriend's cooking.
Mr. Song, you've been acting all along.
Who exactly are you deceiving?
Her or me?
News about you travels far.
Though I'm old, my mind's still sharp.
I clearly remember
Miss Xie was your fiancée.
I've long heard you see and hear all.
Seems nothing escapes you.
I hate beating around the bush.
Get to the point. Why are you here?
She's a project manager at Song Group.
She wants the land you hold.
If that's why you're here,
save your breath.
My late wife bought that land.
I won't sell it under any circumstances.
Go back.
He refuses to sell.
It's okay.
We'll find another way.
They say if you know someone's past,
you see their future.
I had someone look into
Mr. Yu's overseas projects.
You may focus on your work.
Any findings?
Mr. Yu is very sentimental.
His whole life revolved around his wife.
They visited countless
art exhibitions together.
They crossed forests, deserts,
and the great rivers of many countries.
For such romantic free spirits
like them,
If they bought a plot of land,
what would they do with it?
It's been sitting idle for a long time.
Clearly, it's not for making money.
Mr. Yu met with a famous
overseas art district designer.
If I'm guessing correctly,
he seeks a land designer
but is unsatisfied with the results.
Any ideas?
I think
if we can come up
with a design plan that satisfies him,
we could use that as an opening
to get Mr. Yu to sell us the land.
Good idea.
Have some fruit.
What's with your hand?
I accidentally hurt it
while cutting fruit for you.
You can cook meals,
yet you got hurt cutting fruit?
♪In the vast sea of stars♪
♪Flickering neon lights♪
♪Longing spreads
throughout the universe♪
♪Every star is♪
♪My heartbeat for you♪
♪Want to ride the evening breeze♪
♪And land in your arms♪
♪The starry sky is like your eyes♪
♪In the blue sky♪
♪Your smile still lingers♪
♪You are the brightest light
in my regrets♪
♪You are the painful greeting
in my despair♪
♪Can't find a cure♪
♪To love you after we've parted♪
♪You are the time I most want to keep♪
♪The future I strive toward
in the darkness♪
♪Slowly getting closer to you♪
♪How I wish
I could give you my sunshine♪
♪You are the brightest light
in my regrets♪
♪Can't find a cure♪
♪To love you after we've parted♪
♪You are the time I most want to keep♪
♪The future I strive toward
in the darkness♪
♪Slowly getting closer to you♪
♪How I wish
I could give you my sunshine♪