Graceful Family
Episode 6
Approximatly 15 years earlier
Is it good?
Yes. It's tastier since we came here together.
Mom doesn't let me eat hamburgers.
Do whatever you want to do today.
- Really?
- Of course.
What do you want to do?
My friends went to see the football game with their dads.
Grandfather, it's dirty!
No. Your food is not dirty to me. It's fine.
Then should we go to the football stadium together?
- Really? Then let's go right away!
- Okay!
I'll take that.
I'll do it.
It's okay.
To a girl who couldn't live with her dad,
grandfather was more than a father.
You worked so hard raising Seok Hui without a father.
She's a very smart and a kind-hearted kid, Father.
You're the rightful lady of the house. It's time you moved in.
Chairman is coming.
Seok Hui's mother is a member of the Mo family.
Move into the house with Seok Hui.
I'll do that.
Hey. You move out.
Father!
Move into the house and study management.
Grandfather, I don't think that would be much fun.
Father, we have an eldest son. Why Seok Hui?
Do you know what times we're living in? What do you mean an eldest son?
Are those two good enough in your eyes?!
Seok Hui.
Being overly loving toward one brings out jealousy,
disenchantment, and rage to others.
You seem to have a lot of special affection for Seok Hui.
She's a special kid. The backbone of our family.
I'm going to raise Seok Hui as someone who will take over our company.
You're also a woman who's living like a great man!
MC Construction is in talks with a company in the Middle East about a huge project.
And?
Provided that Director Mo Cheol Hui becomes the group's CEO
they are going to approve.
Also, all the executives and staff members of the company believes the director to be the successor.
so if you choose Miss as the successor all of a sudden,
it would negatively hurt the company.
It's a useless worry.
Chairman.
I've already made up my mind.
From the Chairman's wish not to lose something precious to him
and Director Han's betrayal
could the tragedy of MC Group have started?
Graceful Family
Present
We're doing a DUI check.
You've been drinking.
Pardon? I...
Give me your license.
East Police Station
Hello, I'm her attorney.
She has a provisional driver's license right now?
Yes, that's right. So it's not driving without a license.
Because she drove under the influence,
she was waiting to get a license suspension, but she drove again under the influence.
You know that after two times, you're out, right?
I think there's a misunderstanding.
Call a doctor. I'll sign.
I have an illness.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm sorry. Could we talk privately?
I have a deja vu with a place like this.
Why aren't you angry? It's unlike you.
You should be upset that I've been drinking.
Did you really drink?
The article about my DUI is up already.
Like someone planned and waited for it.
Why did they do a DUI check this morning all of a sudden?
In front of my house at that.
How did the reporters know about my DUI quicker than you?
So... someone planned this so that you couldn't come to the shareholders' meeting?
Who would it have been?
TOP.
I... suffer from a condition called auto brewery syndrome.
- Auto brewery syndrome?
- Yes.
It's a condition where the carbohydrates turn into alcohol.
Um... that's a real thing?
You don't die or anything. It started last year.
I came to Korea suddenly while getting treated for it in the States, so I couldn't bring my medicine with me.
I hadn't gone to a hospital here since I was afraid TOP would find out and use it against me.
Then the DUI last time, too, that was because of this illness?
Yes.
"Auto Brewery Syndrome" (also gut fermentation disease) is a real medical condition
They must have put something in my juice that I drink every day. Like some carbohydrate powder or something...
So TOP found out about it after all...
What happened at the meeting?
Your appointment as CEO got cancelled.
In the end, did my father become the CEO?
The medical records from the treatments she received in the States and her medical diagnosis.
We'll submit a medical diagnosis from a national hospital after an examination, too.
The shareholders pushed for Chairman Mo Cheol Hui as the CEO at the meeting.
I apologize.
Then what happens to Miss?
Since the reasons for disqualification were revealed at an official appearance,
I think it'll be difficult to appoint her as the CEO.
Chairman! Chairman, are you okay?
Chairman! Chairman!
Doctor Hong, call 911!
How is he?
He's of advanced age and already has problems with his heart as well as blood vessels,
so it would be best for him to get stabilized at the hospital.
I did what I could urgently,
but he needs complete stabilization.
Doctor Hong was at the house.
- How is the media's reaction?
- Take a look.
MC Groups new rising star, caught for DUI on the day of stockholders' meeting, moral laxity of Chaebols,
A radical club maniac heiress who is pro same-sex marriage.
The media is having a field day.
She made her debut internationally. Not a positive one, of course.
What about articles on the fight for management rights?
There are none so far.
- Keep up the defense.
- Yes.
What do you predict Head Chairman's stance will be?
He'll probably drag out the fact that Chairman Mo has been  elected CEO.
Although Miss isn't the CEO, she is the largest shareholder.
They might sue us.
Yes, there is a good possibility.
They'll insist that the decision to appoint a CEO without the major shareholder is procedurally problematic.
You could be charged with coercion in obtaining the stockholders' proxies.
What's the alternative?
Even if they decide to file a suit, it'll take a while.
We have to obtain more shares as quickly as possible in the meantime.
Okay.
Director, what are you going to do with Lawyer Heo?
His internship has ended, so is there's a point of keeping him around at TOP?
I'll take care of that myself.
Yes.
Auto Brewery Syndrome
After proving her innocence for a year, she was released on the 8th. The guardian has stated that her body is like a distillery.
I think it'll take time.
They have to take more blood, too. People are interested since it's a rare condition.
Submit it to the police station as soon as the results come out.
Does the grandfather... know?
I talked to Lawyer Yoon and he was told.
I messed it all up.
Congratulations to  our CEO!!
This is a special alcohol that I  saved for a day like this. Love shot!
Hey, that's embarrassing.
From now on, take care of Soek-Hui too.
Of course, she is also my daughter.
But when will you do the personnel changes within the Group?
Executive Director Han will bring me a draft.
Director Han?
MC group is yours.
They say you put new alcohol into a new unit. (  Old Biblical  saying about not putting new wine into old bottles)
While you're at it, consider changing the head of TOP.
I find that woman really burdensome.
Terrible!!
My son? How have you been?
Oh, my baby... Did you miss me?
Of course!
Okay let's see... Have you eaten?
Yes.
But, why did you suddenly ask to to see me?
By any chance, is anybody in that house tormenting you?
No. It's okay.
My son.
Aigoo... Chae Na Ri, long time no see
Did you guys come together?
Yes.
Why? Is there some sign prohibiting our seeing each other?
I came here because I have something to say.
What do you need to say?
Invest in my movie.
Invest... out of nowhere?
I don't have money to do that.
Even if I did, I wouldn't.
You've recently done three CF (Commercial Shoots).
Oppa.....!
Anyway, I don't have money.
Then, can you ask Dad for it?
Seok Hui promised to invest but I think that offer is off the table now.
I'm desperate.
Please ask Dad.
Why do you live like this?
Let's age gracefully.
If you don't help me this time, I have another plan.
I will tell everyone about us dating.
Have you gone crazy?
Ah.... I'm hungry.
Thank you.
Seo Jin, you need to order.
My nephew ... is quite handsome, isn't he?
What do you want auntie to buy for you?
Bye.
By the way...
- look at this when you get in.
- What is it?
You will know when you see it.
Go in, I'll drop the car and leave.
I Took Your Name As Medicine by Park Joon
Sorry.
There is no need to be sorry.
This hasn't come to an end yet.
You don't know what it took to make this happen for you...
He said it's not the end yet.
But, is Grandfather seriously ill?
I have security measures in place as well...
so be strong and prepare for it.
Yes.
God seems to have granted you all the good fortune.
Since strong Seok Hui also has fallen,
now you are the only heir left.
Brother-in-law, don't you know he's very sensitive?
The dinner is late as it is,
so please stop.
Dinner isn't the issue right now.
When my movie is on the verge of failure.
So,
what is it you want?
Give me some money! Please!
We're going to lose all our staff from the shooting site!
You're okay overall, but I think you lack humanity.
A cold guy who doesn't bleed even when pricked...
That's completely out of style.
A next generation leader needs to be sensitive.
Younger brother, save your hyung's face.
Wan Joon, Wan Joon!!
Aren't you embarrassed?
- Why?
- Just...
accept the fact that you have no talent.
Owning up to that fact is enough to gauge your worth.
You heartless son of a bitch. Aren't you so great.
If you covet the company, then take it!
At least become that competent or just keep your mouth shut.
What did you just say?
- Just because I let it slide all the time--
- Why are you doing this?
"Why are you doing this??
This couple is heartless together, huh?
It's real marital harmony.
What a beautiful scene... amongst brothers.
Hey, Mo Seok Hui! You should have done your job properly!
I had all my faith in you! My movie is about to be ruined. What are you gonna do about it?
What are going to do about it?!
I know, right? I feel bad.
Try to hang in there by spending less on your drinking habits.
Oh My God!!
How can no one in this family understand art?
If I don't have a drink right now, I'm going to be committed to a mental institution.
Although Oppa Wan Soo may not be at your level to be competing with,
there's no need to be so rude, no? After all you're siblings.
You two are similar.
Why don't you give collaboration with him a try as half-siblings?
If you corner him, he could bite.
Really?
Wow, now that I think about it, it really scares me!
The internet is going crazy talking about the chaebol family's only daughter.
It's that girl from last time, right?
But she is nice and pretty and so smart.
Why did she drink and drive?
Drunk driving is no different than murder.
You definitely should't do it even if you are going to die.
Dad, you shouldn't believe in everything the news says.
If I don't believe the news then, who am I to believe?
These days, there are lots of fake news as well.
I heard she drank all night so she wasn't sober even by morning.
How much did she drink that in the morning she still couldn't pass the breathalyzer test?
Seriously... I said it's not true!!
I Took Your Name As Medicine by Park Joon
Thinking about your sorrow in a miserable world ...
Lawyer Heo is quite impressive.
I like this poem.
Hello?
Have you read the poem?
Do you know what time it is right now?
Did you call me to ask that?
It's daytime in New York.
So, you want to get revenge?
As if..
I was wondering if you read the poem.
- It's a poem I like.
- Really?
When we share common likes to this degree, aren't we almost like siblings who are blood related?
I'm thinking of your sorrow in this miserable world.
Thinking  about your sorrow in a miserable world  is as remote as
the land  losing its homes and the homes losing their occupants.
Can you sing one more time for me?
Never mind. f you go overboard one more time, I'm going to do a flying kick.
- That's a relief.
- What?
It is the Mo Seok Hui I know.
Sleep well.
Take a look.
I'll submit it.
A New Movement, The Prosecution Growing Together
What happened?
Miss Seok Hui just filed a lawsuit,
saying that we coerced the shareholders into signing the proxies. We are being sued for coercion.
There's also suspicion of violating the Capital Market Act.
The dates of when the proxies from shareholders were received are all different.
Article 153 of the capital market and stock market investment law.
Breach and disclosure violation of proxy and reference documents.
Seok Hui is a lot more thorough than she looks.
It's probably that her will to be the CEO is that strong.
It was expected.
Right now, the Head Chairman is meeting with the directors.
Choi Kyeong Oh, Sin Oh Cheol, Baek Jong Hn... just assembling  three would be enough to convene an emergency council.
Director Baek came over to our side. Did you get that info from the other side?
Yes.
Convene an emergency council...
Remove Chairman Mo by convincing the board of directors and then go for it again?
Should we send those three people overseas for the time being?
No, wait.
The fact that they made contact with Director Baek means that
even if that information is leaked, they're that confident.
Then that means the other two have already taken their side.
Find out exactly where and when the meeting will take place!
Yes.
No. Use Director Baek and steer the conference to take place at his place of residence.
Why is that?
If something bad happened outside, no good can come of it.
Emergency council...
Greed never gets old...
Tenacious...
Chairman...
Head Chairman is coming.
Leave.
Appoint Seok Hui... as the CEO.
Something that was decided at the shareholders' meeting...
how can I change it myself?
You will be severely punished for that greed of yours.
If you play any more tricks, I will not l leave you be.
This is still my home.
Let's go.
You should have been left as a judge.
My karma is great.
Now... it's not possible anymore.
I'm sick of it.
It's been a while, but there was a time I hit the jackpot.
It started as something fun with $100,
but quickly only a $1 coin was left.
There was a passing thought of walking away, but the coin was inserted without care...
and that gave me the jackpot.
A $1 coin changed my fate.
A gambler shouldn't be in possession of even a dollar.
Living a long time with an illness,
is an embarrassment to a family.
Sorry while you're resting.
It's good manners not to do something you'll be sorry for.
Do you think you can overturn the decision if you convene an emergency council?
I don't like playing games where there's no chance of winning either.
Where did that innocent Miss from years ago disappear to?
I wonder.
That Seok Hui probably died in New York when she was about 20 years old.
You should know very well...
Since you and MC Group killed her.
Miss, how long do you think Head Chairman will be by your side?
If you don't let go of your ambition, it might put him in an awkward position.
Are you threatening me?
If I can just get MC Group in my hands,
whether he dies or not doesn't matter to me.
He's already advanced in age.
Why are you surprised?
If I am to fight against you people, I have to think and act the same.
Since this is how you work.
How impressive.
I'll take that as a compliment.
Medical Records
It's a medical report on Mo Seok Hui's auto brewery syndrome.
My lacking son used Seok Hui's illness as a
reason for disqualification.
It's an embarrassment to my family. I can't apologize enough.
As written in the doctor's notes,
if I control my diet, it doesn't have any effect on my daily life.
Lawyer Heo, please pass out the proposal.
MC Group Management Strategy Plan
It's my thought on what direction MC Group needs to
go in the future.
Also, the file that's attached to the back is
her certificate from New York University Stern School of Business.
A news article came out today about how she graduated with excellent grades.
Now, now, let's eat
and take our time listening to her briefing.
She can't make another mistake again.
So, the menu is meat.
Please understand.
Please.
Head Director's condition is very serious.
Please be specific.
He's of advanced age and his spine isn't in good health,
so even if his sympathetic nerves is stimulated, it can result in neurological shock.
The sauce is very good.
It's tasty. What is it?
It's almond sauce.
Grandfather, eat a lot slowly.
Okay.
Put some more on.
That's good.
The dinner is coming to an end.
Yes.
Let me speak to Head Chairman.
Grandfather, Director Han has something to tell you.
What is it?
Grandfather...
Grandfather!
His heart wasn't great to begin with.
Recently it's become weaker,
so he has to be very careful with his diet.
Food that's okay for healthy people can become poison to him.
For example, nuts with a small amount of almond butter
can affect the heart,
so it's best to avoid it.
He received a great shock at the shareholders' meeting
so if there's another shocking incident,
he'll probably have difficulty recovering from it.
He has passed away.
Make the funeral
as elaborate as possible.
We can't.
If people find out that as soon as you became the CEO
the Head Chairman passed away, there could be an unwanted dispute.
Also, the stock fell 7.8% after the shareholders' meeting,
so the shareholders aren't in a good mindset. Please have a private funeral instead.
You're right.
I'll prepare it that way.
A moment of silence.
Mo Wang Pyo.
Director Han!
We developed the first ship that could hold 6200 containers
20 m tall in the world!
From now on,  MC  through its products will roam around all oceans of the world.
Congratulations.
This is all because you went to Kuwait and won a hundred million dollars in contracts.
So I'm glad I have you behind my back!
Mo Wang Pyo: September 3, 1932- September 9, 2019
He lies here to rest after a lifetime of tirelessly running forward
But, you know...
what did Director Han say to him before he died?
He received her call and was shocked.
She caused him to die from shock.
All the people I have loved are gone.
Now I am really alone.
The Head Chairman was buried at the arboretum.
You all worked hard.
It's surprising. I never expected that he would pass away like this.
He was hanging in there for his granddaughter. It seems like the shock at the shareholders' meeting was too great.
It's the end for Miss Seok Hui, right?
No, right now, she has the largest share.
That's why you have to be on your toes.
Until the Group stabilizes under Chairman Mo,
our work isn't done.
You two worked so hard for a long time for MC Group.
How could you hold a funeral like this on your own?
It should be enough for you to leave alone.
It's not enough that you're kicking me out... You are also planning to keep an eye on me forever.
Director Han, you!
You should've retired a long time ago. Please step aside for  your juniors.
What?
Please choose.
Embezzlement?  What do you think you are doing?
I didn't use that money but--
I heard the weather in Australia is great this days. You should take a break where your daughter is.
Right, housekeeper Jeong.
from now on, you cannot contact Miss Seok Hui in any way.
Here,
Sign here.
If you don't keep your promise, I won't be able to guarantee your safety.
Jeong Yoon Seok
Housekeeper Jeong
The number no longer exists,
please check and call again.
Lawyer Yoon.
The number no longer exists,
please check and call again.
The chairman of the cheobol group just died.
Did they not provide any food at the funeral?
You eat like you've been starving! Slow down or you'll get an upset stomach.
They're really ridiculous, though.
In what circumstance do you finish the funeral in one day when seven days wouldn't be enough?
It's not like he passed away at a young age. At 88, he lived a long life...
I have never seen a funeral end in one day.
I've never experienced this before in my whole life.
So Dad, there's no need to be jealous of the rich.
Who cares if you're a rich chairman when no one can visit him at the funeral?
You... when I die, do it for three days at the most.
Why not ask for seven days?
No, seven days is too long.
Three days is more than enough. Promise me.
But... I think that you are going to live longer than me.
This kid... Don't say something like that even if you are joking.
Thank you , Dad.
Why all of sudden?
Just thank you for everything.
Do you want some more food?
Enjoy.
MHan Je Gook
Yes, Director.
Director?
I want to make you TOP's member.
Now that Chairman is dead and Mo Cheol Hui is the CEO of MC Distribution,
now the new era of MC Distribution has begun.
TOP, also, to compliment that new era,
needs a new person.
The door to TOP is narrow.
How about you come in when the door is open?
Are you disappointed?
What do you mean by it?
You wanted Mo Seok Hui to be the CEO.
Do you think the Miss can lead millions of employees?
That's why, because Mo Seok Hui is not talented enough to lead the company,
because she got in the way of MC's new era you got her drunk?
Is the new way this violent?
Where is your final destination as a lawyer?
I don't think I'm close enough with you to talk about personal matters.
Those who save up nice words and say critical things eventually succeed.
Miss is talented and has good qualities but not for management.
To manage, the ideal and the reality have to come together in a concise manner,
But Miss lacks the sense of reality.
If you are a CEO, given  a reality that you don't like,
you have to be able to set yourself aside and compromise.
Do you think she will be able to do it?
If Miss were to manage, she might get complimented by the scholars,
but it's likely the company would suffer from deficit.
Our ways of thinking are really different.
I have watched her longer than you have.
If she gives up on the management rights, she could go back to the States.
Or live an affluent life as the only daughter of a wealth family.
Didn't you force her to give up her management rights?
Nevertheless, she still has the biggest shares.
I respect the facts.
Let's go.
This is where selective TOP members can enter.
At one time, the power of this country came from dominating the military,
But now, high-level information and the technology to deal with it,
and capital determines that power.
Search anyone you want.
Im...
Heo Yoon Do
Now, this time, search using TOP's exclusive ID.
Search results for Heo Yoon Do
I see there are nine Heo Yoon Do's that we manage.
Here, let's look you up.
You've worked part time at over 10 places before you passed the bar.
This is it. The file on the murder would also be somewhere here.
Shouldn't you learn how to work properly, too?
I want you to have and use this place to your heart's content.
Why me?
Because you are new and refreshing.
I'm supposed to be honored but I am Mo Seok Hui's lawyer.
Although Miss is the largest shareholder, there is little she can do.
Are you just going to be a butler lawyer to clean up after the family?
Is working at TOP that much better than working as a butler lawyer?
You know how ambitious you are.
Having a goal is also ambition.
I sense tenacity in you.   However I don't know what its goal is.
Are you curious?
No, but I know that working as a butler lawyer isn't your final goal.
I don't know what it is that you want, but if you become a member of TOP
you can achieve everything you want.
Only, as you have taken care of the young lady,
now, you must vigilantly watch her.
So, you want me to choose between TOP and Mo Seok Hue?
You know I don't have a hot temper, but I am impatient.
I won't wait long.
Go now.
TOP MC GROUP SECURITY AGENT.
MC TOWER.
Look at Seok Hui's class in eating steak even on a day like today.
As I expected, her survival power is go great!
Amazing, Mo Seok Hui.
Noona, stay strong.
I guess you really like her.
You even know how to console her.
I told you,
she is just my type.
What to do? I am now worried about your future.
Why?
Miss, the chairman wants to see you.
Miss Seok Hue is entering.
The spot occupied by your grandfather's arboreteum is a place I've been coveting for a long time.
Then why didn't you use it as your grave?
The chief monk will take care of everything, the 49th day of mourning as well.
Where did you send Housekeeper Jeong and Lawyer Yoon?
I like that you're bold.
You might be the CEO, but,
I hope you are aware that I am still the largest shareholder.
The equity structure changed today.
Current MC Distribution Shares Structure
I've bought all  the shares of Directors Choi and Sin.
Now I know why everyone keeps saying "Director Han, Director Han".
This is a waiver of management rights.
Why would I sign such a document?
I'm no longer the largest shareholder, so I don't have management rights anyway.
Even if you're not the biggest shareholder,  when you have the amount of shares that you do,
it could interfere with the Chairman's control.
Even if you don't interfere, the people around you won't let you just be.
Also, give up the assets you were given by Head Chairman, too.
What did you just say?
Director Han!
Miss, coming to Korea after 15 years
you had fun as if you were in a theme park.
It's now time for that theme park to close.
Let me ask you one thing.
Who killed my grandfather?
Mo Seok Hui!
Tell me the truth. Then I'll sign it.
I did it.
Director Han...
Now... sign it.
Waiver of MC Global Management Rights
What do you get if I sign?
Like you lived in the US--
While being watched--
Eat, wear and spend as much as you want.
- Only with a card--
- You can live freely.
Let me have Lawyer Heo Yoon Do.
- You can't.
- Why?
TOP will use him. He will make a decision soon.
I'll think about it.
Come in, Team Leader Gwon.
Sorry, Miss, can you give me your cell phone?
What are you doing?
Miss. You shouldn't ask sensitive questions.
I'm sorry.
Let go. Let go!
Who killed...grandfather?
Tell me the truth. Then I'll sign.
Then I'll sign the paper.
I did it.
You're the one who killed Head Chairman.
As long as I get the MC Group in my hands, I don't care whether the grandfather dies or not.
He's old anyway.
Sign the paper.
Fine.
I'll sign the paper.
Memorandum of Relinquishment of Management Rights
Mo Seok Hui
Young Master is coming.
Director Han...
Get ready for her.
Yes, I understand.
What happened?
It's an emergency situation.
Step aside.
What's going on?
Picasso.
What?
Informing all of the team, it's an emergency situation. Emergency situation.
TOP
What is it?
You can't do this to me.
If you have something good, share it with me.
What are you doing, not sleeping?
Wait till you get old. You wake up in the middle of the night.
Since I was already up, I came to see your face.
TOP
Where are you going this early?
Did somebody else die?
Picasso.
What? The artist?
That person was still alive?
Dad, I'll be back.
Drive safely.
Picasso?
The list of invitations.
What about the Director of the National Art Museum?
That is... she's abroad right now and the flight schedule isn't working out
so she said it'll be difficult.
Send her a private plane. She adored Picasso.
We have the public's attention.
You can take off the logo and send it.
How about the seat arrangement?
YBS CEO should sit next to MC Construction's President Joo.
And Director Mo should sit behind me and CEO, so that we can introduce him to the people.
Yes.
New Minister of Land and Transportation is coming too?
We sent a special invitation.
It turned out well. We should approach him naturally given this opportunity.
What about the food?
MC hotel's chef is going to prepare it.
Change it. It's Picasso's last. He deserves the best.
Use the chef's team we used for the American Embassy party.
Yes.
Make sure you guard well.
- Pay special attention to security.
- Yes.
Take good care of the funeral.
I understand.
15 years ago, Picasso,
after he became a member of MC family up until now
was the patron saint of MC family who has guarded the growth of the family.
The reason why MC group was able to overcome numerous hurdles
was because Picasso protected the family with loyalty.
Also, for some of us, Piccaso was a family member and a friend who spent a long time together.
In happiness, in sadness,  in loneliness or when in difficulty,
Picasso was always there during those times.
Even though he has left our side, his efforts and loyalty--
Are you confident you will be as successful as Picasso?
He will be with us forever.
I don't know.
I don't think the minister would come to my funeral.
Our family.
Picasso is great.
Honestly, it's too much.
Rest in peace.
It's culture shock.
By the way, is this the type of funeral for a Chabeol's pet?
I have seen a couple dogs' funerals,
but a fish's funeral, this is the first time with Picasso's.
But you have to see this as not funeral, but business.
Picasso is better off than grandfather.
And now, we'll have a one minute of silence for Picasso
who  lived for MC Group family and died.
Everyone, silent tribute.
Directly.
Next is a floral tribute for Picasso.
Everyone offers flowers.
Hey, give it to me. Give it to me.
Give it your best, why don't you try
Hey, give it to me.
But your best can't hold me back.
Adieu, Fish.
I'm on fire, I'm on fire
You're liar, you are liar
Black Diamond
You and I, to that place
The paradise of just the two of us
Graceful Family
Upgrade yourself, Lawyer Heo. If something comes ot it, that's even better.
You really gave up on the management rights?!
Dad you would be proud. You've got a hardworking Director Han.
Have Mo Wan Joon as successor?
Hurry up.
Chairman, are you that afraid of me?
Can you become a TOP member to the bone?
Let's open my mom's case again.
Let's say there are two secret agents behind this.
- Why 2 agents?
- Mo Seok Hui.
Heo Yoon Do died of a car accident?
Are you saying Lawyer Heo has been resurrected?
Heo Yoon Do, get disarmed now.