Yi Yang.
How can I be like Guard Lu,
always by your side?
If I tell him about the foreseen danger,
will he believe me then?
Black horse.
I never thought that at such a young age,
instead of dying on the battlefield,
I'd be defeated by a bowl of chicken soup.
General,
I'm leaving.
Look at you.
Put it down, put it down, put it down.
Alright.
Are you alright?
There are still a few detoxification pills left from the doctor's last prescription.
I'll go get them for you.
Where is she?
Who?
You mean Miss Bu Nian, right?
She built a wooden cabin in the backyard.
I don't know how she managed to build it.
But it's fine.
At least she won't come here to bother you.
Wooden cabin?
Tree house.
Take this empty bowl back to her.
Just say you drank from it.
Shouldn't empty bowls go back to the kitchen?
Why give it to her?
Just do as I say and take it to her.
Let me nap a bit longer.
How about you become the general then?
it's not impossible.
Off to deliver the bowl then.
Actually,
I didn't want to come here today.
You're all grown horses now.
you should know better.
Please don't make me worry anymore, okay?
All the food, clothes, and things you use,
are all earned through the general's hard work.
Isn't that right?
So,
I hope you can be more emotionally stable.
Don't get angry so easily,
and kick people out with your hind legs.
It's very dangerous, okay?
You're not happy about it, are you?
you're the type who
goes crazy when your temper flares up,
throwing people off like a wild horse, right?
You really can't be like this anymore.
Grow up a little, will you?
And you,
you look pretty docile,
but when you go crazy, you're fiercer than anyone.
Why are you staring at me with those big eyes?
You're not happy either.
Can't you do it even if I beg you?
I know it's tough for you.
going to the battlefield is also difficult.
but this can't be
a reason for you to throw people off, right?
It's you, isn't it?
You throw people off and still think you're right, huh?
What's this fool doing?
Turn around and look at me.
Be a little more mature.
How old are you now?
A Li, why are you here?
I'm going to report to the general.
Wait for me.
I'll go with you.
I'm going to tell the general you've gone mad.
I believe
if we work together,
Crazy person,
the general definitely won't be thrown off by the horse.
Is it Young Master Pei?
It's me.
Hello, sir.
Here are the lease agreement and keys.
Thank you for your trouble.
May I ask if you're alone or...
I'm here to pick up my bride-to-be.
That's wonderful!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Please, come in.
Have you finished looking?
You haven't agreed to my request yet.
Don't be ridiculous.
Am I supposed to never ride a horse again?
Should I take a carriage even when marching to battle?
Don't be angry.
Haven't I already told you?
I have the ability to foresee danger.
I really saw it.
You'll really have an accident if you ride a horse.
Then tell me.
when will it happen?
I can't say for sure when it will happen.
But if I'm there...
I won't let anything happen to you.
I've already arranged everything with Ma.
now it's just up to you.
Right, Ali?
How dare you!
Comparing me to livestock!
Let go!
No.
I heard you built a treehouse yourself.
How did you hear about that?
Yeah, I built it myself.
Pretty impressive, huh?
You're quite handy.
Of course I am.
Let me show you around.
Sure.
Is that it?
Which one?
Yes, that's the one.
That orange one is the one I covered.
How is it? Looks good, right?
Yi Yang.
Xue Yi Yang.
A Li, something happened to Yi Yang.
Young City Lord's Consort,
why don't we take a break?
The doctor said moxibustion can dispel dampness,
which is beneficial for the Young City Lord's Consort to conceive.
You'd better not interfere arbitrarily.
It's alright, let's persist a bit longer.
You.
Do you have to follow me everywhere I go?
Well, I'm going to take a bath now.
Come on.
Wait.
Are you really going to bathe with me?
Sure, why not?
You.
You're a woman.
How can you have no sense of shame?
What is a sense of shame?
In the future, when you're out,
if a man is naked in front of you,
you must not look at him for even a second longer.
Do you understand?
I'm going to take a bath.
Wait here.
Stand still.
Those who know,
we're going to suppress bandits.
Those who don't might think we're adulterers.
I'm just worried she might be a spy for the young lord.
Then knock her out.
Torture her.
What's going on?
Bu Nian was just worried you might fall off the horse.
You've been riding horses since you were five.
If something was going to happen, it would have happened already.
It's too late. Let's go.
The last report from our scout
said they followed the mountain bandits into this Eastern Mountain.
After that, there was no news at all.
They've been gone for at least three or four days.
Find someone to inquire along the way.
Ask if there are any villagers nearby
who have seen traces of horses and carriages.
There are quite a few of them.
It rained just a few days ago.
They couldn't have gone far.
Be careful.
General, are you alright?
It's just a minor wound, nothing serious.
A dart.
It seems Miss Bu Nian truly has the gift of foresight.
Let's return to the mansion.
Young Lord,
if you miss the Young Lady,
why don't you go see her?
Between husband and wife,
there's no grudge that can't be resolved.
Why should I think about her?
Who knows which man she's thinking about?
Xue Yiyang arrived at the location and was stabbed.
It seems the fish has taken the bait.
Then let him investigate the clues.
The more thoroughly he investigates, the better.
The woman I asked you to investigate, the one who spent the night with him,
how's that going?
This woman is very mysterious.
It's as if she appeared out of thin air.
There's no trace of her to be found.
Then find an opportunity to meet her.
Young Lord,
the Young Lady today underwent
a full hour of moxibustion treatment.
The doctor has also prescribed a new medicine.
Young Lord,
trying to conceive is not
something the Young Lady can accomplish alone.
You don't see her day after day.
How can there be offspring?
There's no rush.
If she wants children,
let her come and beg me herself.
Bu Nian, come down.
come down.
Why don't you come up?
How childish.
If you don't come down, I'm leaving.
Alright, I'll stop teasing you.
What's the matter?
Don't you have the ability to foresee?
Then tell me,
what did I ask Lu Li to bring?
Do I need to foresee such a trivial thing?
He'll be here soon.
You'll find out then, won't you?
Fine.
He'll be carrying a wooden box.
A brown one, unlocked.
Cast
Bu Nian: Zhang Chuhan
Xue Yiyang: Hu Bowen
Liu Ruofeng: Lu Xi
Xue Fu: Ye Yi
Lu Li: Zhang Ning
Chief Protector: Hou Junjie
City Lord
Captain Zhang
Grandpa
Middle-aged Man: Liu Yunlong
Maid A: Shen Yinzi
Maid B
Soldier A
Soldier B: Wei Bo
Soldier C: Yuan Hong
Also Starring
Mi Na, Zhang Yujie, Zhang Qiang, Lin Weibiao, Cao Tingting
Wang Qiyuan
Li Yixuan, Chen Yiliang, Ying Jiaming, Lin Yinuo, Shao Yangjian
Zhao Wenyu, Hong Junli, Zhang Shicheng, Ma Shuai, Yan Zheng
Chen Kaiqi, Lai Yuying, Wu Guanhong, Dou Dou, Xing Chen
Zeng Wenhua, Chen Xingyu, Xiang Bufan, Meng Xiang'an, Gao Xiaoya
Cao Yuqing, Sun Shijie, Wang Jiang, Cheng Feng, Luo Jinchuan
Crew
Producers: Shu Hua, Chen Xizhong, Cui Jingge
Co-producer: Zhu Lingzhong
Screenwriter: Yanran Ziwei
Executive Producer: Chen Meisong
Directing Department
Executive Director: Ma Xiaoyu
Script Supervisor: Pei Wenjing
Casting Director: Zheng Haoyu
Gao Xibing
Actors Coordinator: Zhuang Yinming
Production Department
Chief Producer: Chen Xizhong
Producers: Cui Jingge, Jiang Zhijun, Zheng Da
Production Managers: Wang Shuliang, Meng Xiaotian
Finance: Jin Baoqian
External Liaison: Sun Weigang
On-site Producer: Ju Zhibo
Vehicle Management: Wang Shuliang
Life Producer: Wang Shuliang
Photography Department
Cinematographer: Yuan Zhichao
Dolly Grip: Fan
Focus Puller: Yang Mingming
Assistant: Mu Liansong
Focus Puller: Wang Weijia
Lighting Department
Gaffer: Yang Lu'an
Lighting Assistants: Mu Yanhao, Yin Wenbin, Shi Wanlei
Art Department
Art Director: Chang Xu
Assistant Art Directors: Liu Baizhan, Lian Junlong
Props Department
Props Master: Wang Xinghui
Set Dressing
Set Props: Wu Yongjian
Cong Yindi, Song Zhan
On-set Props: Bai Zhengguang, Li Xiaowei
Props Tailor: Jin Limin
Set Decoration Department
Set Decoration Supervisor: Zhong Gencun
Set Carpenter
Lou Liangpeng
Styling Department
Stylist: Chen Mohan
Hair and Makeup Department
Hair and Makeup Supervisor: An Qingdong
Key Makeup Artist: Chen Xiaoxin
Makeup Artists: Wang Mingyang, Yin Zhihao
Costume Department
Costume Supervisor
Costume Supervisor: Liu Lei
Second Assistant Costume Designer: He Qiqi
Costume Assistants: Wang Xiaoning, Gong Panying, Wang Guohao
Sound Department
Sound Recordist: Chang Xiaolei
Sound Assistant: Xu Zhangui
Editing Department
Editors: Xu Weiwen, Hu Baihui
Special Effects Department
On-set Special Effects: Zhang Ting
Digital Imaging Technician: Li Jiawei
Production Assistants
Production Assistants: Zhang Chuang, Zhang Xiaotian, Zhang Xiaolei
Behind-the-Scenes Team
Still Photographer: Zhang Xing
Behind-the-Scenes Videographer: Wang Zhixiang
Post-production Video
Beijing Jingyu Xiansheng Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Video Supervisor: Chen Yipeng
Video Producer: Bai Zijun
Video Technicians: Hu Weiwei, Liu Yang
Subtitles: Wang Wei, Song Pan
Compositing: Hu Weiwei
Post-production Audio
Beijing Lecheng Yisheng Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Sound Supervisor: Ding Liang
Audio Manager: Huang Bin
Audio Producer: Wang Qinsi
Motion Graphics Artists: Liu Jianli, Teng Fan, Xiong Ming
Foley Artist: Shi Yaoqing
Motion Graphics Sound Recording: Li Chaoyang
Mixing Assistant: Zhang Changshuai
Audio Technicians: Zhang Haozhe, Yu Jiaxu
Music Supervisor
Music Designer: Li Yanmei
Post-production Visual Effects
Beijing Jingyu Xiansheng Culture Media Co., Ltd.
VFX Supervisor: Zhang Na
VFX Producer: Du Dandan
Compositing Artist
Digital Matte Painting: Hou Jiacheng
3D Production
Post-production Dubbing Team
Dubbing Director
Voice Actors: Shi Zekun, Tian Fengkai, Xia Haiqing
Marketing Materials Production Team
Beijing Lightning Film and Television Co., Ltd.
Creative Director: Huang Rongjun
Production Coordinator: Yang Hong
Color Grading: Nie Yaxiong, Chen Chong
Graphic Design: Yang Hong, Han Jinting, Xu Zhinuo
Packaging and Compositing: Han Jinting, Wang Zi
Music Copyright Company
Beijing Songba Culture Development Co., Ltd.
Production Company
Yihuo (Zhejiang) Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Beijing Lesheng Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Dongguan Lesheng Culture Media Co., Ltd.