=Soft-Hearted God=
=Episode 20=
(Let us merge our flesh and bone.)
(We will never to be parted again.)
(I was so foolish.)
(I couldn't tell whether you
were human or demon.)
(Nothing can separate us now.)
Xi.
Let us return home.
She is Xi?
Bring her back to me.
He is already
on the brink of exhaustion.
Today, we shall slay the god together!
Kill him!
Don't be afraid, Xi.
I'm here.
Do it!
Master.
- Master.
Immortal, run!
I will cover you.
So it is you.
You made Zhao suffer the pain
of being devoured.
Toying with pawns
is the power of those
who wield the pieces.
What can you do to me?
What can I do to you?
Continue.
Our souls have already merged as one.
As long as the demon root
is not eradicated,
you cannot kill me.
Even if you take your own life,
I will follow you
into reincarnation.
You and I shall be together
forever and ever.
Shut your mouth!
You shall never leave here.
Zhao almost
lost his life for you.
If you wish to stay longer with him,
stay away from those Flower Slaves.
Zhao.
(Lingyun Pavilion)
♪Once, the Nine Provinces shone
with brilliant lights♪
♪For you,
I brushed the snow from your robes♪
♪I crossed mountains and seas
just to see you once♪
♪Through countless nights
across rivers and mountains♪
♪Yet we couldnEmperort last through the years♪
♪This parting gathers all joy
and sorrow into silence♪
♪I too once lost myself for ages♪
♪Through love and life,
I roamed the mortal world♪
♪Only after a fleeting century
did I learn how shallow this love was♪
♪You are the snow
that rests on timeless hills♪
♪You fall into my gaze♪
♪Yet mistaken for the moon♪
♪I break through fateEmperors cocoon♪
♪Travel a thousand miles to you♪
Your Highness.
The Immortal has been
unconscious for a while.
No one can remove the swords.
All the physicians in the city
are at a loss.
We can only rely on a medicinal bath
to sustain his life.
You may leave now.
But...
Leave!
Yes, Your Highness.
Zhao, it's me.
The swords are poisoned.
They prevent your recovery.
Be good.
Let me remove them.
Zhao.
I'm here.
No one will ever separate us again.
Zhao.
You're finally awake.
What did you just call me?
Zhao.
I remember everything now.
That night...
That night must have been
despairing for you.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
It's my fault.
I couldn't tell...
when you have a demon heart.
Those cuts you took to save me
must have hurt.
It must have hurt.
It must have.
It hurt.
It really hurt.
Alright.
I'm here.
I'm also here.
Come.
It's cold outside.
I have something for you.
(Martial Hall)
General, your confidential letter.
(Helian Shu colluded
with the Flower Slaves.)
(He was stripped of his military power
and locked in the dungeon.)
(The court is becoming
more transparent.)
(I will bring Xihe
back to the palace soon.)
(Stop scratching me. It itches.)
Thank you, Miss Baobao,
for helping me find Her Highness.
Her Highness is fine now.
I will certainly
do my utmost to heal the Immortal.
I'm connected
with Master's divine power.
Now that I've transformed
into human form, he should be fine.
No need to be so formal.
This headband is for you.
I don't accept rewards without merit.
I...
Do you not like it?
I shall take it back, then.
I thought you didn't want it.
There is no reason to give a gift
and then ask for it back.
Give it back to me.
Ye Zhao.
Ye Zhao?
Why are you calling me by my full name?
The demon heart is called Hua Hui.
It contrasts greatly with your name.
Ye and Hua.
[*Leaf and flower]
Zhao and Hui.
[*Bright and dark]
Zhao.
Do you have any recollection
of this name?
I have no memory before becoming a god.
Perhaps this name
is just a coincidence.
A coincidence?
♪Too bad the rain will stop♪
♪The wind will fade,
tomorrow will clear♪
♪I'd rather this night never end♪
♪Let the long shadows♪
♪whisper what's in your heart♪
♪If in a dream♪
♪I can hear your voice♪
♪Then let it be our meeting♪
♪Let it be us♪
♪drawing endlessly close♪
♪Too bad the rain will stop♪
♪The wind will fade,
tomorrow will clear♪
♪I can't even hold you properly♪
♪Not even in time♪
♪to tell you how I feel♪
♪If the rain won't stop♪
♪If the wind won't fade,
if time stands still♪
♪Let love go on♪
♪Until forever♪
♪Until we slowly grow old♪