=Soft-Hearted God=
=Episode 15=
(You should give your all to me,)
(my love.)
What are they doing?
You little nerd.
All you ever do is
bury yourself in medical texts.
You'll know when you're older.
Let's go.
We're leaving?
You can't see this yet.
♪To meet is to overlap♪
Zhao.
Your lips are so soft.
♪Counting every moment,
unwilling to pause♪
♪As raindrops kiss the ground♪
♪Soaking these hazy, drowsy eyes♪
♪Even if reluctant, what can be done♪
♪Chasing something always out of reach♪
♪So I'm afraid of goodbye♪
♪Living the same day
over and over again♪
You're sober now?
Then, does what you said just now
still stand?
What I said just now?
It doesn't.
Okay, it does.
It's not meant for you.
It's my birthday.
Are you giving yourself a gift?
If I wear it,
hearing this sound,
you'll know I have arrived.
Every step a sound.
Every step a longing.
Such sweet words.
Who taught you to speak so?
It must be Bai
who reads far too many romance tales.
Was this bell
his idea as well?
I cannot betray a friend.
I wonder how many ladies
Bai will beguile in the future.
Zhao,
let's choose an auspicious day
to get married.
Okay.
We should also give our child
a name.
Zhao.
Let's name our child
Baobao.
Okay.
Baobao it shall be.
(My mind is made up.)
(What can you do to stop me?)
(One month later, Qingxin Pavilion)
(She's pregnant with a demigod.)
(This baby must not remain.)
Weren't you on the bed?
Xi.
Xi, are you alright?
I'm fine.
Help him up first.
I'll fetch some medicine for him.
Insolence!
How dare you sleep with a demon?
My mind is made up.
In this life,
I will grow old together with Xi.
Humans, gods, and demons
each have their ordained path to follow.
For you to cross races and join with her
is something Heaven cannot abide.
He Xi is now pregnant.
This matter will bring endless calamity.
Xi and I...
have a baby?
Since ancient times,
whenever a demigod is born,
it brings ruin upon the Three Realms.
This baby cannot be kept.
If you persist in your delusion,
I shall summon heavenly lightning
and strike it down.
But if you
get rid of this ill-fated baby yourself,
I will spare you and the demon.
Zhao,
why haven't you helped him up yet?
I am Chu Daqiang.
Thank you for saving my life.
May I ask your name?
My name is He Xi.
I will always
remember your name.
If I should have descendants,
I will name them after you.
You're overstating it.
It was but a small act of kindness.
The battle is intensifying.
I must return
to the battlefield at once.
Take this wound medicine with you.
And this blade as well.
It is of little use to me.
You can keep it.
Thank you, Lady He.
I shall take my leave.
Zhao.
What's the matter?
Why do you seem so troubled?
Has something happened?
Nothing at all.
Perhaps
you overexerted yourself last night?
What are you saying?
Come try again.
Look at this color.
Does it hurt?
It doesn't.
I'm really fine.
I'm used to it.
(Xi,)
(only by refining
our flesh and blood into an artifact)
(and sealing the baby's intelligence)
(can we deceive Heavenly Dao)
(and preserve Baobao.)
(Forgive me.)
Since ancient times,
whenever a demigod is born,
it brings ruin upon the Three Realms.
This baby cannot be kept.
If you persist in your delusion,
I shall summon heavenly lightning
and strike it down.
But if you get rid
of this ill-fated baby yourself,
I will spare you and the demon.
So this is all your love amounts to.
Today, Zhao
took your baby from you
out of fear of the Heavenly Dao.
Tomorrow, he will
destroy you
to save his own life.
Cutie,
let me help you.
♪Too bad the rain will stop♪
♪The wind will fade,
tomorrow will clear♪
♪I'd rather this night never end♪
♪Let the long shadows♪
♪whisper what's in your heart♪
♪If in a dream♪
♪I can hear your voice♪
♪Then let it be our meeting♪
♪Let it be us♪
♪drawing endlessly close♪
♪Too bad the rain will stop♪
♪The wind will fade,
tomorrow will clear♪
♪I can't even hold you properly♪
♪Not even in time♪
♪to tell you how I feel♪
♪If the rain won't stop♪
♪If the wind won't fade,
if time stands still♪
♪Let love go on♪
♪Until forever♪
♪Until we slowly grow old♪