=Soft-Hearted God=
=Episode 22=
(Fate turns in endless cycles)
(and won't rest till it's resolved.)
I want this.
No.
Baobao!
Stop right there!
Mother!
Baobao!
- I need some water.
- Mother, Mother!
Fine, I won't fight you for it.
I won't take it.
Open the door!
Physician! Physician!
Help, please save me!
Help! Help!
Please save us!
Save the child!
Sir, please save us!
Sir! Sir! Please!
Please save us!
Open the door, Physician!
I'm begging you!
I don't want to die!
Save me!
Open the door!
(Buns)
Zhao!
I'm here.
Mother, I'll help too.
Your Highness, I await your orders.
(Fate has given the same problem again.)
(This time, I will solve it.)
Your Highness! General!
Something terrible has happened!
All the Flower Slaves
have been released by Helian Shu!
My father and the people in the prison
have all been killed!
Helian Shu!
Xiao, stay calm.
Immediately bring the Pei Army
stationed outside into the city.
Move all infected civilians
to Baihua Hall outside the city.
Then await my orders.
Xiao, go to the palace.
Report this situation to the Emperor.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Highness, there's one more thing.
Helian Shu and his shadow guards
have a red flower growing on them.
It's very strange.
Could this Verdant Decay
be connected to Helian Shu?
Then, when did he get infected?
You wretch!
(It's been a hundred years.)
(I've finally awakened.)
(I really want a bite of meat.)
You...
Your eyes...
(I'll start with you.)
Your Majesty, run!
Helian Shu has gone mad!
I've obtained Stellar Dew.
The root-seeking worm
will be ready tonight.
Once it's done,
I'll go to Baihua Hall to find you.
Then, I'll protect Mother
from the Flower Slaves.
We'll meet at Baihua Hall.
Sir, please!
Quiet!
Please save us!
Everyone, listen to me.
Your Highness,
all infected civilians in the city
have been moved to the main hall.
The physicians are in the side hall.
Do not station troops in the main hall.
Don't frighten the patients.
Have the soldiers patrol nearby.
Yes.
We've never seen this disease before.
That's right.
What are we supposed to do?
It's a natural disaster!
Such a strange illness.
Everyone, I'll keep this brief.
This disease is called Verdant Decay.
The vile plant thrives
when it touches water
and feeds on human flesh and blood.
When the flower falls, the person dies.
If the pollen touches a human body,
it takes root and sprouts immediately,
repeating the cycle.
Such a strange disease...
I've practiced medicine for decades
and never heard of it.
I've heard of it before.
A hundred years ago, it appeared once.
But overnight,
all the patients disappeared.
May I ask, miss?
What happens if we forcibly
remove the plant?
The plant's roots
run through the blood vessels.
If forcibly removed,
the roots will invade
the organs instantly,
and the patient will die on the spot.
What should we do?
Is this truly a disaster?
- What do we do?
Yeah!
Quiet!
Everyone, I have a solution.
First,
keep the plant away from water.
Second,
those not infected
must wear masks and gloves.
Do not expose bare skin.
Cover the plant with gauze
to prevent spread.
Third, prepare tonics
that restore energy
to calm everyone.
Fourth...
Follow these three steps
to control the disease first.
Then, I'll explain step four.
Everyone,
General Pei has summoned
all the best physicians in the capital.
We will cure every single one of you.
Please rest assured.
During this time,
all food, clothing,
medical costs,
and even lost wages
will be covered by the General's Manor.
Please stay here with peace of mind.
That's great!
We trust the physicians!
Next,
we'll rely on all of you, gentlemen.
- Understood!
Your Highness, please come with me.
Where to?
The people are the priority right now.
Your Majesty, Her Highness has arrived.
I take my leave.
Greetings,
Your Majesty.
It's only been a few days,
yet you seem to have endured a lot.
All thanks to you, Your Majesty.
Come forward.
What's wrong with you?
The imperial physician has seen me.
The poison has reached my heart.
There's no cure.
Who poisoned you?
It's all because of Helian Shu.
Your mother had long
suffered from illness.
That was also his doing.
Helian Shu!
Xihe,
I don't have much time left.
Let me finish.
Lately,
I often dream of your mother.
In my dreams,
she always asks me
to see you one last time,
to say what must be said,
so I won't meet her
with regrets.
When you were born,
the nation had just stabilized,
and the court was in turmoil.
The farther I kept you,
the safer you were.
I'm not a bird in a cage!
I can wield blades,
study strategy,
and master the art of balance!
I've never been inferior to anyone.
I know.
I know all of it.
Xihe,
you've never been inferior to anyone.
It's my first time being a father.
I didn't do as well as your mother.
I don't expect your forgiveness.
I only hope
to ease the hatred in your heart.
The edict of succession
is already written.
Once I remove
all the corrupt officials...
I hold
no grudge.
Your poison
can still be cured.
I'll have Xiao deliver the prescription.
You just need to take it on time.
I still have to handle
the epidemic in Ning Capital.
I'll take my leave.
Xihe...
(Twenty years ago)
Your Majesty, you've just given birth.
Please take care of your health.
Burning the princess
is the Emperor's order.
I'm just following orders.
Quick!
Stop her!
Move!
Your Majesty, this is an evil infant!
If we don't burn her,
Ning State will fall!
Your Majesty!
Do not come any closer!
Or I'll throw
the princess off the tower!
You think I'd be
threatened by a eunuch like you?
My child!
Don't be afraid.
I am here.
Quick!
Surround her!
Don't let that evil infant escape!
Do not come any closer!
Empress!
It's windy outside.
Come back to the palace with me.
Your Majesty,
this is our only child.
Are you truly going to burn her?
Your Majesty,
the princess is stillborn.
Nonsense!
Can't you hear her crying?
Empress, look carefully.
My child...
Your Majesty,
she's not dead!
Your Majesty!
I stake my life on this!
This infant was born without a heart,
covered in blade marks.
Her eyes just flashed red.
It's an ominous sign!
If this evil infant is kept,
it will bring disaster to the nation!
Your Majesty, think of the greater good!
Burn the infant at once
to ensure the kingdom's peace!
Burn the infant!
Protect the kingdom!
I will
keep the child.
Issue the decree.
Name her Xihe.
Record her in the royal lineage.
Your Majesty!
I said
the child stays.
(Ning,)
(our daughter has grown up.)
Zhao.
Baobao, Xiao,
stand guard outside.
No one is to come in.
This worm will burrow
into every blood vessel in your body,
search through your organs
until it finds the demon root.
When that happens,
the pain will consume you.
It will feel like
your organs are being torn apart.
Have you thought this through?
If it saves the people and you,
then pain is nothing.
Xi...
Are you okay?
Don't worry about me.
Find where the demon root is!
Quick!
How is it?
Did you find it? Did you find it?
The demon root isn't in your body.
♪Too bad the rain will stop♪
♪The wind will fade,
tomorrow will clear♪
♪I'd rather this night never end♪
♪Let the long shadows♪
♪whisper what's in your heart♪
♪If in a dream♪
♪I can hear your voice♪
♪Then let it be our meeting♪
♪Let it be us♪
♪drawing endlessly close♪
♪Too bad the rain will stop♪
♪The wind will fade,
tomorrow will clear♪
♪I can't even hold you properly♪
♪Not even in time♪
♪to tell you how I feel♪
♪If the rain won't stop♪
♪If the wind won't fade,
if time stands still♪
♪Let love go on♪
♪Until forever♪
♪Until we slowly grow old♪