=Soft-Hearted God=
=Episode 24=
(You collapsed in the snowstorm.)
(My heart turned into a dark shrine.)
(Dexin Hall)
Darn you, heavenly lightning!
Heavenly lightning
doesn't strike mortals.
We can't just stand by.
Everyone,
let's shield Immortal together!
Let's go.
Yeah.
He's right.
We can't just watch him die.
Let's block the lightning!
They once ate immortal flesh to survive,
but now face heavenly lightning
to protect one.
Mortals are truly interesting.
Block the heavenly lightning!
Come at us!
We must protect our savior
even if we die!
We won't let go!
Don't you dare harm our savior!
We can take it!
Come on!
Zhao!
Where's your father?
He's with Xiao.
Come on!
Come at us!
We're not afraid.
We must protect our savior
even if we die!
Zhao!
Heavenly lightning, we're not scared.
Bring it on!
Come at us!
You think we're scared?
We're not afraid!
Come on!
Bring it on!
The lightning stopped!
We won!
♪To meet is to overlap♪
♪To see is to part again♪
♪To stay is to wish for forever♪
♪Counting every moment, unwilling to pause♪
(Qingxin Pavilion)
♪As raindrops kiss the ground♪
Zhao.
Father!
♪Soaking these hazy, drowsy eyes♪
♪Even if reluctant, what can be done♪
♪Chasing something always out of reach♪
♪So I'm afraid of goodbye♪
♪Living the same day
over and over again♪
♪Too bad the rain will stop,
The wind will fade, tomorrow will clear♪
♪I'd rather this night never end♪
What did he do?
Zhao.
What did he do!
He used his powers
to treat all patients
with Verdant Decay.
♪I can hear your voice♪
♪Then let it be our meeting♪
♪Let it be us♪
Zhao,
how could you be so foolish?
I am the princess of Ning.
Saving the people is my duty.
Not yours!
Don't cry.
Stop crying.
Protecting you
has always been my greatest wish.
I don't want your protection.
I don't want it!
I want you alive.
Do you hear me?
I want you alive and well.
I know.
I just want us to be us.
I only want us to be us.
It's useless.
It won't help.
It won't work.
My divine heart is damaged.
This body has lost its foundation.
Nothing can be restored.
They...
helped me block half
(Qingxin Pavilion)
of the heavenly lightning.
Otherwise,
I would've been destroyed.
It turns out mortals
aren't so bad after all.
Xi...
I'm here.
I'm tired.
I want to take a rest.
(Qingxin Pavilion)
Zhao!
Zhao.
(One Month Later)
♪Once, the Nine Provinces shone
with brilliant lights♪
♪For you,
I brushed the snow from your robes♪
♪I crossed mountains and seas
just to see you once♪
♪Through countless nights
across rivers and mountains♪
♪Yet we couldn't last through the years♪
♪This parting gathers all joy
and sorrow into silence♪
♪I too once lost myself for ages♪
♪Through love and life, I roamed the mortal world♪
♪Only after a fleeting century
did I learn how shallow this love was♪
♪You're the snow that rests on timeless hills♪
♪You fall into my gaze♪
♪Yet mistaken for the moon♪
♪I break through fate's cocoon♪
♪Travel a thousand miles to you♪
♪You are a night of falling petals♪
♪Gone in a blink,
you fade to the horizon♪
♪Telling me not to long for you♪
Your Highness, bad news.
Verdant Decay has reappeared.
What did you say?
(No way.)
(Zhao couldn't possibly
miss out any patient.)
Your Highness, General.
The capital's epidemic
is out of control.
We are in chaos.
Captain Li requests your presence.
Old man of the Heavenly Dao.
Come out!
Old man of the Heavenly Dao!
I hid my form,
yet you still grabbed me.
I want you
destroy that demon root right now!
I can't destroy it.
Only Ye Zhao can do it.
But Father's divine heart is damaged.
He can't destroy the demon root.
Demigod,
let go now,
or I'll get angry.
I'll get angry too if you don't tell me.
Everything in this world
has its reasons.
Arguing with me here
is pointless.
Old man,
you're the best.
Bend the rules a little.
Old man,
please.
I bought this umbrella.
It's yours now.
The snow is heavy.
Go home early.
A divine heart
can only be restored
by another divine heart.
What do you mean?
(Demigod,)
(I hope you'll never)
(have to use this bead.)
After him!
Quick. Over there!
Your Highness, General,
what brought you both here?
What made you ask for us
so urgently?
I never asked for your presence.
You asked for it.
Speak.
Who sent you?
I'm in a terrible mood now.
I have no patience for this.
I'll kill you if you don't talk.
It was Duke Rong!
Is the return of Verdant Decay
his doing?
That day,
the shadow guards were cured
of the Verdant Decay.
Still here.
It's still here.
As long as one Red Spider Lily
still exists,
this plague will never end.
But that flower slave chief
blocked the divine light
meant for His Grace.
Why would he do that?
His Grace heard the chief say
when one has Verdant Decay
and eats Ye Zhao's flesh,
they can turn
into an immortal flower slave.
His Grace wants an army of slower slaves
to rule the world.
Oh no. Zhao is in danger.
(Dexin Hall)
(Qingxin Pavilion)
Master, the immortal body
is as heavy as lead.
I can't lift him.
♪Even if reluctant, what can be done♪
♪Chasing something always out of reach♪
♪So I'm afraid of goodbye♪
♪Living the same day
over and over again♪
(Perhaps, if I reincarnate,)
(I can rid myself of this demon heart.)
(I will definitely
come back to find you.)
(You must wait for me.)
♪If in a dream♪
♪I can hear your voice♪
♪Then let it be our meeting♪
♪Let it be us♪
♪drawing endlessly close♪
♪Too bad the rain will stop♪
♪The wind will fade,
tomorrow will clear♪
♪I can't even hold you properly♪
♪Not even in time♪
♪to tell you how I feel♪
♪If the rain won't stop♪
♪If the wind won't fade,
if time stands still♪
♪Let love go on♪
♪Until forever♪