I shall anoint you.
Consider it me marrying you two, Rid.
Pudtarn.
I will begin preparations
for your wedding.
I will tell your father
to arrange the wedding within the year.
If I cannot go back on my word
and you have no intention of objecting
or officially challenging it,
then the other party
must withdraw willingly.
There is no way they would.
You must create a way then.
If we can procure enough rice
to sell to them,
up to three million buckets,
the Emperor will waive the taxes on it.
Keep your voice down.
Regarding the Emperor's tax exemption,
do not let anyone know.
Choi has yet to come to fetch you.
Why are you leaving now?
This plant, may I have it?
You may.
Give that plant to the viscount.
Yes, my lady.
Where will you plant it?
At your residence?
Well…
I shall give it to someone
who shares their name with this plant.
Name?
This is a pudtarn tree.
His Majesty has bestowed you upon him.
You will be superior to his other wives.
Remember this.
Hey, it's a pudtarn.
That's right.
I got it
from the Marquess Kosathibodi's residence
for you.
I just thought
it had the same name as you.
Did you really go there
just to ask for it?
Are you sure
you didn't visit your side chick?
Side chick?
Yes, side chick.
Someone who is more than a friend,
but not a lover.
A sister.
Someone who is more than a friend
but not a lover.
That's called a sister.
Fine, I believe you.
The flowers of the pudtarn tree
are strange.
They change color three times per day.
They are strange, just like you.
You know nothing.
It's teaching us a life lesson.
The changing colors of the pudtarn flowers
tell us that
everything in the world can change.
It's also saying that life is like this.
We come into existence, prevail,
and then perish.
My love…
came into existence,
is prevailing,
and…
will never perish.
The same goes for mine.
Even if I can't marry you
and be your wife,
I will love you…
forever.
I promise.
You cannot marry me?
Everything in this world can change.
Remember this.
What is the important matter
you wanted to talk to me about?
I'm grateful to you
for agreeing to see me.
Of course.
Just say it, Rid.
You are to be my son-in-law.
You shall take care of my daughter,
so of course I'll listen to you.
Also,
you are a decent and talented man.
I'd be glad to give Praejeen to you
without the king's command.
What I wish to speak about,
with respect, Marquess,
concerns what I have discovered
and observed.
Why do you speak of this?
You're acting as if you don't know
that this is our tradition.
It is how it has been done
for generations.
I know it's our tradition.
I also know that…
What?
Why hold your tongue? Just say it.
I also know…
that some people
wouldn't have to work so hard
and would have a better life
if officials were less corrupt
and were considerate of them.
But since this isn't the case,
then I'm afraid
I can no longer work with you.
I will ask His Majesty
to transfer me to my previous post.
He is a grave threat.
I cannot allow you to marry him.
A threat to whom?
I have never seen him harm anyone.
Who is he a threat to, Father?
Don't ask.
You do not need to know.
All you need to know is that
he is a threat.
Slowly, my lady.
I'm sorry, Rid.
Please forgive me.
Everything in this world…
can change.
Yes.
Change is inevitable.
My lady.
My lady, it's time for your medicine.
My lady, please get up
and take your medicine.
Grandmother.
Rid, Marquess Kosathibodi
has requested Praejeen back.
So the problem of your love triangle
has been solved, has it not?
Is there anything else I can do for you?
Your kindness knows no bounds,
Your Majesty.
I have no more requests.
All right.
Let's move on to In.
Rid.
What do you call it again?
Pudtarn calls it…
being crazy in love, Your Majesty.
Right.
I have never heard of this before.
Thongkam.
Were you ever crazy in love
with your wife?
I was for the first few days,
Your Majesty.
It has been a few years now,
so not any longer.
Who is your eldest son?
He is Thongdee, Your Majesty.
How old is he now?
He's 20 years old, Your Majesty.
I see.
He shall work with us.
He seems like a good man.
Yes, Your Majesty.
As for you, Rid.
You gained one and lost one.
You lost your grandmother,
but you got a wife.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I believe Pudtarn
will no longer object to marrying you.
Your eyes are all puffy from crying.
You should stop, my dear.
I was about to marry Rid.
Why did things turn out this way, Mother?
Let bygones be bygones, dear.
You won't get Rid back,
no matter how much you cry.
You know I love him.
Why didn't you object to Father?
I wasn't aware of it.
He informed me
after he had made the request to the king.
I want to die, Mother.
My poor child.
Rid is getting married today.
I should be his bride.
I'm supposed to be with him.
I'm supposed to be there.
This necklace represents my parents.
It represents the bond
between you and me, my lord,
-because--
-Khun Pi.
Yes, Khun Pi.
It represents the bond
between you and me, Khun Pi.
If you hadn't returned it to me,
it would have been lost
from my life forever.
You two may be
the parents of that girl named Pudtarn,
but the fact that
I have had the chance to live in this body
indicates that we were once bonded
in a past life.
That's why I feel that you two
are my real parents.
Do you know
how long I have been waiting for this day?
I have waited so long.
It has been terribly long.
Many lifetimes.
You told me once that…
you would cook something for me.
Did you mean something that is
spicy,
delectable,
and
requires some pounding?
My lord, you want to eat…
What?
Khun Pi.
From now on,
there will be no more Lord Rid.
There will only be Khun Pi.
This is the last time
I shall tell you this.
My lord.
Khun Pi.
Do you want to eat now?
We are about to spend
our first night together.
It's not the time to eat.
I'm going to eat
right now.
Into the mortar enters
The pestle
As it mixes and pounds
The ingredients…
Garlic, chilis
And shrimp paste combine
And fuses with the mango
As it pounds
Rid, I don't mind Pudtarn selling food,
as I see she loves making a living,
but she should do it moderately.
Yes, Mother.
What?
Hey, Choi.
Yes, my lady.
What is she selling today?
Boat noodles, my lady.
My gosh, boat noodles?
I want some.
Didn't you say
you don't want her to sell food?
Hey, it's boat noodles. She must sell it.
It's a specialty in Ayutthaya,
Pin and Yaem.
I want some. It's the bomb.
My gosh.
My dear customers,
please taste our delicious boat noodles.
Please wait a minute.
It will be worth the wait.
Here you go, ma'am.
Here you go.
Please come and try
our delicious boat noodles.
It's fresh, safe, and toxin-free.
Yes, my lord.
One bowl of noodles, please.
What noodles would you like?
Thin rice noodles, wide rice noodles,
vermicelli, or egg noodles?
Wide rice noodles.
I would like thin rice noodles.
Act normal.
If you don't,
you may not trade.
-Yes, my lord.
Please wait a minute, my lord.
What would you like, sir?
This guy is good-looking.
Whose son is he?
I don't know, my lord.
What are you selling, my lady?
Noodle soup.
What noodles do you want?
I don't like noodles.
Can I have a bowl without noodles, please?
That's called gao lao.
So fragrant
and appealing.
That's flirting.
He's flirting with Pudtarn.
He's quite bold.
If Rid were here, he wouldn't spare him.
Even I didn't get her.
Who do you think he is?
And who are you?
If you are going to fight,
then please go over there,
my dear customers.
I'm fine with her selling noodles,
but she must stop everything else.
If she spends all her time making food,
will she ever make any babies?
Aren't you pleased
that she is hardworking?
Well, I want grandchildren.
I see.
You will have to tell Lord Rid this then.
It's not Miss Pudtarn
you should be concerned about.
Tell Lord Rid that if he works too much,
he won't be able
-to raise the flag.
-To raise the flag.
No way.
My son has no problem in that department.
Just wait and see.
My goodness.
Yaem.
Sit still.
Why is she so quiet?
You're right.
Our lady was loud
when delivering our lords and ladies.
Yes.
Do you want to try being in labor?
They are just wondering
why Pudtarn is so quiet.
Prik, I hope she doesn't--
-Hey.
-Goodness!
-For god's sake.
-I haven't said a single word.
I know you were going to say
something inauspicious.
-I'm going to hit you.
-My goodness.
I'm sorry, my lord.
She's so quiet.
-Mother, why--
-Just wait a little longer.
But she should at least make some noise.
I shall wait no more.
Rid.
-It's a…
-Say it or we'll hit you.
It's a boy!
-My gosh!
-What? Eung, do I have a son?
Mother, it's a boy.
I heard it. I'm not deaf.
I have a name for him.
He shall be called Phat.
Phat.
Go and tell my husband
that his grandson has been born.
Hey, Rid, hurry and make another.
You can't have just one.
Pudtarn told me she would only have one.
Don't let that happen. Do you understand?
Yes, Mother.
It's a boy.
-It's a boy.
-A boy.
-What?
It's a boy, right?
Here is mine.
That's a lot.
A boy.
It's short.
Lord In.
It's a boy, my lord.
There's no need to be sad, Pong.
Look at our daughter.
Yes?
She's prettier than any other woman
in Ayutthaya.
A beautiful flower
shall be visited by a bee soon.
Greetings, my lord.
My lady.
This is Wake.
He took up a post at the treasury
just today.
Have a seat.
Praejeen.
Come here for a second, my dear.
What?
Praejeen.
Khun Pi.
Her heart is devoted to Rid.
Please be considerate.
I am being considerate.
That's why I brought him here.
Congratulations, Mali,
for having been granted the title
of Thao Thong Kip Ma.
Thank you so much, Karaked.
I was already fulfilled
through serving as a courtier
in the royal kitchen.
The title was beyond my expectations.
That's because you worked hard
and served His Majesty with honesty.
You started out as a royal kitchen hand
and have worked your way to the top,
overseeing hundreds of people.
His Majesty recognized your hard work
and decided to reward you.
I often think of their kindness.
Both of them,
King Phetracha,
who allowed me to become a civil servant,
and King Tai Sra,
who has granted me the title.
Now, let's wait and see
if the request you submitted
to King Louis XIV
requesting dividend payments
from the French companies
your husband invested in will be granted.
I think it will.
I don't think
the king of France will cheat you.
Be patient.
I have enough to live on.
I don't wish for great fortune.
Father.
Phin, what is it, dear?
Auntie Keaw and Auntie Prang are here.
Here they are.
Greet them, dear.
-Good boys.
-Hello.
How have you been?
Keaw.
Prang.
Yok, my dear.
Rid.
Mother, your baked goods are ready.
Shall we have them over there?
Go.
-Take them there.
-Go.
It's time for your medicine.
What is the matter?
I don't know.
I have a bad feeling.
I feel sad.
I feel very sad.
Malaria…
is difficult to treat.
Do not worry
that people will say
you didn't care for your husband well
and that you caused his death.
Take Ruang's ashes to Ayutthaya.
Hand them
to his father and mother yourself.
Yes.
Take Boonruang with you, dear.
Fai and two more servants
are ready to escort you.
Yes.
What's wrong?
Rid,
Ruang has passed away.
He died of malaria.
I didn't take care of him well.
Choi.
Lord Ruang.
I know.
It's not true, is it, Prik?
He has gone to heaven.
This isn't true, is it?
My dear lord.
Don't wallow in grief, my dear Karaked.
I feel like my heart has been torn apart,
Khun Pi.
Birth, old age, sickness, and death
are normal.
I never thought…
our son would die before us.
If Little Ruang weren't in Phitsanulok…
I would have been with him…
before he passed away.
Ten years ago…
when the Krishna Kali Manuscript
let out a golden light,
I read your fortune and found that…
you would retrieve something you loved,
but would lose something else you loved.
At first, I thought that…
you would have to part with me
and go back to the life you lived before.
I got back Pudtarn,
who must be the real Karaked, my sister.
But it is at the expense
of Little Ruang, is it not?
In a person's life,
there are things you gain
and things you lose.
This is inevitable, my dear.
Even though I know
that the departures
of Lady Champa and Little Ruang…
are not permanent,
as we will meet each other in the future,
I can't help but feel saddened.
That's normal.
If we are destined to be with each other,
our destiny will bring all of us
who have a shared bond
back together in no time.
Kids.
Grandmother.
No, I'm your great-great-grandmother.
I'm the great-great-grandmother
of you all.
-Great-great-Grandmother.
Take care
of my great-great-grandchildren well.
-Yes, my lady.
Grandma.
My dear Ket.
What about Mom? Didn't she come with you?
She is now living a peaceful life
practicing dharma.
I have something to say to Dech.
Ayutthaya was once
a prosperous and heavenly city,
but when the time
of its collapse approached,
even heaven
could not prevent such an occurrence.
Change is inevitable.
Be aware of and accept this truth.
Khun Pi.
Does Ayutthaya collapse, Karaked?
How do you know?
I…
had a dream.
You had a dream?
I dreamed that…
your grandmother told me this.
That's right, Khun Pi.
Ayutthaya collapses.
Everything my grandmother said was true.
Hey.
Look.
I can do it myself.
-My lord.
-Will this do, my lord?
We are moving to Pribpree.
All of us are moving there.
For those who do not wish to come,
I beg you to come.
Let's live there together.
We will live together
until we die.
That way, we won't be sad
when we die and leave each other.
That's because
no matter what life it may be,
destiny and fate
will bring all of us
back together once again.
And again.
My lord, my lady.
-Hey, my dear.
-Please be careful.
My lord, my lady.
-Miss.
-Eung.
Miss, please come over here.
-Father.
What is it, my dear?
Mother vomited
after smelling flowers, Father.
Where is your mother?
Goodness.
Please be careful, miss.
My gosh.
Please come this way.
Did you vomit after smelling flowers?
Are you pregnant?
-Yes, my lord.
This will be the last one.
I find flowers smelly now.
In the future,
I might find my children and--
Husband.
Goodness.
You're having your third child now,
but you haven't changed at all.
My mother wants many grandchildren.
If you believe that destiny and fate
will bring those who have left us
back to us again,
then the person in here
may be one of our family members
who has passed away.
My father and mother believe that
-this is Ruang.
-Ruang.
Can you stop reading me like a book?
Stop reading you like a book?
That's impossible.
VISCOUNT PIPATRACHASIN - RID
MARQUESS WISUT SAKORN
BARON NARONGRATCHARITTHA - RUANG
PUDTARN
KETSURANG
KARAKED
KING SANPHET IX (KING TAI SRA)
WAS THE 30TH AYUTTHAYAN KING.
HE ISSUED THE ROYAL ORDINANCE
TO PROHIBIT THE CATCHING OF SILVER BARB,
THE FIRST LAW
ON AQUATIC ANIMAL CONSERVATION.
HE ORDERED
THE REPAIR OF WAT MAHEYONG,
BUILT BEFORE AYUTTHAYA
WAS ESTABLISHED.
HE EXTENDED THE MAHACHAI CANAL,
LINKING THE CHAO PHRAYA
AND THA CHIN RIVERS,
AND DEVELOPED BOTH SIDES OF THE CANAL
INTO LARGE RICE-GROWING AREAS,
LEADING TO THE FIRST EXPORTS OF RICE.
HE HAD CLOSER DIPLOMATIC RELATIONS
WITH CHINA THAN ANY PREVIOUS KING.
HE MAINTAINED PEACE
THROUGHOUT HIS REIGN
AND BECAME A MODEL
FOR FUTURE LEADERS.
Subtitle translation by: Tanida Itthiwat