Haru.
Please break up with me.
This can be considered a threat.
- A threat?
- He may also send a letter or something to you.
I want to make Miku happy, for as long as I can.
What can you do?
This is the first time I'm taking the courage to face my life properly.
You're going back.
I don't think it's right to chase Miku back to his place.
I'm the only one who can make Miku happy!
Why can't you understand?
Souta? May I come in?
Yeah.
What is it?
That's good.
What's good?
I mean...
Thanks for your help earlier.
I'm glad that you're siding with me.
I'm not exactly siding with you, per se.
Still, I owe it all to your support.
So...
about Haruhisa.
Has he come to terms with calling off the engagement?
Why ask?
He came to our house.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime occasion, so I want to make Miku happy.
He said he was preparing for the wedding, as a surprise to you.
He was asking Mom for advice.
When you came back home the other day,
he demanded compensation from you, didn't he?
What's going on?
How did you know?
I was looking for something,
and happened to see the letter.
Sorry for making you worry.
But...
please keep this from Mom.
I'm fine with that.
But Haruhisa is a lawyer, right?
Will you be okay?
Yup.
I'll solve this problem on my own.
Good morning.
Morning. Breakfast is ready.
Sorry, I'm on the early shift today. I have to go.
Miku.
Why don't you talk it over once more with Haruhisa?
I've already said what I wanted to say to him.
There's no need for me to talk to him again.
- But you see ー
- Sorry,
I'm running late for the train.
[Make up with mud]
[Episode 8]
Yes.
I'll be working from home today.
Thank you.
Have a good one.
Miku.
[July 2nd, 2018: Anniversary of my relationship with Yuuki]
I'll definitely get you back...
Miku.
You may think you lead a carefree life, but don't be mistaken.
Your freedom rides on the protection from your parents.
I'm sure you know it.
Between you and me, who can realistically make Miku happy?
Takakura, did something happen?
You're sighing so much that it's obvious.
I'm still very much a kid, huh?
What happened to the confident Takakura?
It's hard to be that right now.
Hey there.
Hello, Mr. Kitake.
Kazumi, I need to speak with Takakura. Could I borrow him for a moment?
You can't enter the kitchen as you wish.
Sorry about that.
I'm officially representing Miku in her case against her ex-fiance.
She previously approached you for advice, right?
Well, I am a lawyer after all - though I may not look the part.
In any case, did you know that your name appeared in the written notice?
Yes, I heard.
To make sure the matter doesn't blow up, let me handle this from my end.
I hope you can just observe patiently.
In a lawsuit, the one who's correct doesn't necessarily win.
The one who holds the evidence does.
So when injustice happens,
the more socially vulnerable you are, the more likely you'll accept it without protest.
But in my opinion,
lawyers are meant to help those people fight on equal footing.
That's why I'll give it my all for Miku.
Mr. Kitake, can you understand how the socially vulnerable feel?
Trust me, I've got my circumstances.
Anyway, I hope you can leave this case to me.
Okay. I'm counting on you.
[...instances where he applied make up to several female college students, and was in contact with them...]
I see...
Hello? Yuuki speaking.
You're looking at it again?
Yeah.
Not again, Takakura.
- Hello.
- Hey, Yuzuhara.
Can I get you a drink?
I'll have a tomato juice, then.
Okay.
- One tomato.
- Got it.
If you're looking for Takakura, he's already left.
I'm actually glad he's not around.
Huh?
I mean, I don't want to make him worry unnecessarily.
Besides, today...
I came here specifically to thank you.
Thank me?
Mr. Kitake is a really good lawyer.
Thank you so much for introducing me to him.
You don't have to come all the way here to thank me.
So, is the case with your ex going smoothly?
Well, I'm not sure.
But...
I'll make sure not to drag you all into this.
I swear it.
Oh, drag us in all you want.
Especially if that helps your case.
Wrap us in or do whatever. Bring it on, I say!
Thank you so much.
That's very heartening.
Glad to hear it.
Is this... Eve?
That's right!
This sketch is drawn really well.
It's like Eve is right here, right now.
I know, right?
The artist has an excellent sense of style.
Go on, stare at it for as long as you like.
Thank you.
[Artist Name: Souta Yuzuhara]
Souta?
That's right! It's drawn by your brother.
He's been coming by often to draw Takakura's portrait.
I think this boy has great potential.
- Haruhisa.
- Welcome.
- An iced coffee please.
- Sure thing.
Did Miku do something wrong again?
No.
I'm the one who's at fault.
What do you mean by that?
I am very sorry.
My imperfections
have led to the annulment of our engagement.
No, don't say that.
Please raise your head.
I heard about the annulment from Miku.
Haruhisa, what is the real reason for your break up?
Please tell me.
The truth is...
What is this?
It was because of this person
that Miku had a change of heart.
No way... Miku wouldn't...
Miku is pure at heart.
I believe she has been deceived.
I can't talk sense into her.
- In that case, let me convince her.
- Please, don't.
Excuse me.
Here is your iced coffee.
I shouldn't cause you any more trouble.
Besides, I believe that Miku will surely come back to me.
But Haruhisa...
I will wait for her.
No matter what, my love for her will never change.
So could you watch over us for a little longer?
I am so sorry.
Don't be. We are the ones who should apologize.
Please, stop that.
Haruhisa,
I have a favor to ask of you.
Is it okay not to go after Yuzuhara?
I'll stay away from her for now.
If I get close to her,
I might leave evidence that could work against her case.
That may be true, but...
I'm still not financially, nor socially independent.
The only thing I can do for Miku now,
is to stay away from her.
That's the most I can do.
[Investigation Report]
I'm home.
Miku, come over here.
Mom, if this is about Haru ー
Just come over.
This is my own problem!
It's despicable of you to have an affair.
Don't you understand?
You have been deceived!
Mom, what are you talking about?
The man you're having an affair with dresses up as a woman,
and plays around with others before dumping them afterwards.
Who told you that?
Don't you get it?
This man can't even compare to Haruhisa.
You met up with Haru?
I'll go with you to apologize to him.
Go back to Haruhisa.
I'm sure he will forgive you.
He said he'll wait for you until you come around.
Mom, wait...
He gave me this as proof.
You don't know how much Haruhisa loves you.
[Name of Applicant: Haruhisa Yuuki]
[Name of Witness: Michiko Yuzuhara]
Mom, I ー
You can't find another man who's as generous as Haruhisa.
Get this in your head!
Miku, are you alright?
Yup.
Are you going back to him?
Miku.
That portrait you drew was really good.
- What?
- I happened to see it at the store.
I didn't know you were such an artist.
Ms. Mochizuki also said you have talent.
She said you'd go a long way.
Oh...
She said that?
You're amazing, Souta.
You've found...
your own way to shine.
Hello?
It's Souta.
Today,
Miku's ex met up with our mom,
and handed her what looked like a marriage registration form.
Miku started acting strange since then.
I'm worried that she may go back to him.
He also did a background check on you.
Are you okay with that?
I'm fine with it.
If you say so.
I don't know why Haruhisa is doing all this.
I think I can understand how he feels.
Huh?
I think he's frustrated.
He can't do anything about the situation.
All the more so, now that Miku is totally different from the old Miku.
He's trying to make Miku come back to him,
no matter the cost.
He's serious about this.
I guess so.
Thanks for informing me about the situation.
Please take care of Miku for me, okay?
Got it.
Bye.
I told you, didn't I?
This is what's considered an proper crush.
- This?
- Yes.
Does it hurt?
Yes.
Can we talk for a bit?
I'll be waiting at the traffic junction in front of the station.
I'll wait for you until you come.
She's not coming.
I'll speak with you on her behalf.
Big bro.