I like you. I like you the way you are, bright and dazzling.
I'm so sorry.
If you're willing to move back in with me,
I'll go along with whatever you want.
Nee-chan has moved back to live with her boyfriend.
If it was Miku-san's decision to return,
then that's probably what's best for her.
Miku, if you're going to change, then I'll try my best to make myself change for you.
So don't leave me.
Haru-kun is...
as vulnerable as I am.
Here. Take it.
I thought this lipstick color would suit you.
Miku, if you're going to change,
then I'll try my best to make myself change for you.
So...
don't leave me.
[Make Up with Mud: Episode 6]
I think I can come home early today.
That's great to hear.
To be honest, I've already prepped for dinner tonight.
Let me guess. Roast beef?
Bingo!
I figured you'd be craving it since it's been a while, Haru-kun.
No wonder you woke up so early.
Thanks.
Yuzuhara-san, I noticed you haven't been wearing that red lipstick.
It's like you're back to wearing your old make up.
I am. For a change, that's all.
I see.
I thought your boyfriend had stopped you from wearing it again.
No, not at all.
Lately, he's starting to accept the things I like.
I'm glad to hear that.
I was honestly scared for you when I first heard about the compensation and stuff.
Anyway, it's great that you both talked it out.
Thanks for your concern.
Sorry to make you worry.
Don't be.
Haru-kun hasn't objected to anything.
- See you.
See you. Bye.
It'll be okay.
Our relationship is on the mend.
The make up plays the supporting role.
You play the main role.
The one who's pretty is you, Onee-san.
Hold on a second.
Am I trying to sacrifice make up,
the very thing I'm passionate about,
so that I can patch things up with Haru-kun, again?
Hey, Takakura-kun!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
My lecture overran.
Where's everyone else?
Misaki caught a cold, Nana made plans with her boyfriend,
Goto got called into work,
and Madoka had to take care of her sick goldfish.
In other words, the rest can't come?
That's how it is.
Okay then. Let's go.
What shall we buy?
- Lipstick. Yup.
- Lipstick? Good idea.
What color should I get?
- Pink, maybe.
- Pink? Will it suit me?
The color is like this. It looks quite sheer.
[Cosmetic]
It also seems like...
Welcome.
May I help you?
I'm looking for lipstick.
What colors are you looking at?
I'm looking for something on the reddish side.
- Red?
- Yes.
Right this way then.
Thank you.
This is the sheer matte series.
It has a smooth and moist texture, and the color can last for a long time.
They're so pretty.
For this orange-red one, it's the only one that...
I didn't know there were so many kinds of red lipstick.
There's a deep red, a brownish-red, and even an orange-red.
They're all red, yet a little different from one another.
What kind of red do I like?
Well...
May I try on this one?
Of course.
- Let me put it on for you.
- Okay.
What do you do in your free time, Takakura-kun?
I'm kind of busy with my part-time job lately.
Oh? What kind of part-time job?
I'm a store assistant at a gallery cafe.
Can I visit you there some time?
Sure.
It's a really nice shop, so come and visit with the rest.
- With the rest? Thanks.
- Yes.
Takakura-kun?
Shall we take a look over there?
Thank you, Takakura-kun.
I managed to get some pretty cosmetics.
No problem. Glad that I could be of help.
You see... I had a lot of fun today.
Could we go out again sometime?
Sorry.
Thought so too. I'm a nuisance, aren't I?
No, you're not a nuisance.
It's just that...
there's someone that I like.
So I can't go out with you anymore.
Not someone you're interested in?
No. Someone I like.
Then I guess this won't work out, huh?
Good luck, Takakura-kun.
Thank you.
Yuuki Sensei, please give me your advice.
[Yuki Law Office]
All that man thinks about is work.
He barely takes care of our daughter,
and now he says he wants custody over her?
Ridiculous.
Sensei, please, I need your help.
I can give him anything, except my daughter.
I must confirm one thing before we proceed.
You have not engaged in any acts of infidelity, have you?
Excuse me?
We need to be informed in advance of any circumstances
that may be disadvantageous to your case in court.
About that...
No, I have not.
Haru!
Haru, your mom is a lawyer, right?
- Yes.
-  Haru, your mom is super cool.
Nah, that's normal.
Wow! Did you cook this by yourself, Haruhisa?
Yes. Because you said you'll be home late and I'm sick of takeout.
Thank you, sweetie!
Jeez, your lipstick got onto my cheek.
It's a sign of gratitude.
After all, red lipstick is a mighty weapon used to fight in a male-dominated world.
Hello, this is the Yuuki residence.
Dad!
A hotel? Today as well?
Got it.
Wanna speak to Mom?
No need?
Dad's staying over at a hotel. He'll be working late again today.
Is that so?
I would never cheat on my husband.
My child is my everything.
Takeout sushi? Do your job properly as a mother.
Then do you do your part as a father?
You use work as an excuse to avoid coming home!
Haruhisa and I would have been happier
if you had quit your job, and became a housewife.
How nice it must be, to know you can rely on the husband's income if things came down to it.
Wearing such flashy lipstick, and looking fashionable at work...
You must be enjoying it.
Mom...
Your lipstick is supposed to be a weapon against men, isn't it?
Are you going to take the loss like that?
Why did you reject that lady's request?
She lied about not cheating on her husband.
How did you know that she was lying?
Well...
One look at her face, and I could tell.
Please hold the elevator!
- Thank you.
- No problem.
- Which floor?
- First floor.
You look young. Maybe we're the same age.
I'm 27. And you?
- I'm 27.
- For real? Then we're peers.
When were you born?
- Excuse me?
- I was born in March. A Pisces.
January.
January, huh?
So that makes you the older brother.
The name's Kitake Touma from R&K Law Firm.
Surely you remember the family name of the man your mother remarried, right?
Haruhisa nii-san*.
(Term for an older brother in Japanese.)
Hey, wait up!
Don't avoid me on purpose, Haruhisa nii-san.
Stop it!
Don't talk to me ever again. It's disgusting.
I bought it.
It's so pretty.
If I use this lipstick,
I may want to wear heavier eye make up.
Guess I'll get some eye shadow next time.
I can't stop admiring it.
[Yuki Law Office]
Hello? What's up?
What were you up to just now?
I bought a new tube of lipstick.
It's my first time getting a high-end brand.
It looked pretty,
I couldn't help but stop to admire it.
Say, can you come over to my office now?
Why?
I feel like going out to eat today.
I found a nice restaurant.
Miku, if you can come over now, we can eat out together.
In that case, I'll have the roast beef for lunch tomorrow.
It's my day off anyway.
Sounds good. You do that.
Let me know when you arrive.
"You do that"?
Haru-kun...
This...
is the me now.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Shall we go?
Haru-kun? Are you listening?
Yeah, I am.
Tani-san is getting married, right?
No. The one getting married is my chief, Watanabe-san.
I heard the news from Tani-san.
Is that so? Sorry.
Say, Haru-kun...
Yes?
What do you think of my makeup today?
You're asking me?
You didn't look like that when I left this morning.
Did you wear it on purpose?
That's right.
Haru-kun, I wanted you...
to accept me.
To see me, the way I really am.
So I changed my make up on purpose.
Please excuse me.
Here is your vegetable salad.
What's with that tone of speech?
I am accepting you the way you are.
Don't make it sound like I object to it.
But...
you don't like it, do you?
Even if you don't say it out loud,
it hurts to see that look of disgust whenever you see my face.
It feels lonely,
even though we've been together all this time.
It makes me feel empty.
This doesn't feel like you've whole-heartedly accepted me at all.
I'm sorry, Haruhisa.
I feel so lonely with this kind of life.
I feel so empty.
I can't stand it anymore.
I hate it.
That red lipstick...
I don't want you to wear such a vile color, Miku.
Cosmetics are used to hide your unfavorable true nature, right?
Lipstick...
easily gets smeared everywhere.
It's a nuisance.
When you eat, it gets onto the tableware and dirties it.
It makes me uncomfortable.
You put a lot of makeup on...
It's only a plaster of lies, to make yourself pretty on the outside.
In other words...
Haru-kun, you've been feeling uncomfortable...
this whole dinner.
- That's not it.
- Haru-kun.
You're quite self-centered, you know that?
You didn't care if I felt hurt.
You were more concerned for your own comfort.
You're always putting yourself above others, after all.
- Like I said, it's not what I meant ー
- Forget it.
I'm leaving.
I don't want to make you any more uncomfortable than you already are.
Wait, Miku!
Miku!
Wait, Miku.
I'm sorry.
I didn't intend to hurt you, Miku.
Haru-kun...
You see,
today, when I bought the lipstick color that I liked,
I was really happy.
To be honest, I don't care whether it suits me or not.
It's just...
when I see myself in the mirror,
my mood lightens up.
I feel happy.
But then...
we met up for dinner.
And those feelings of happiness...
all disappeared.
♫ Unable to affirm myself ♫
It happens all the time.
Haru-kun, every time I'm with you,
my excitement...
my happiness...
They always get trampled on.
♫ Sorry that I never talk much ♫
♫ My frustration is proportional to my feelings for you ♫
Haru-kun.
Please break up with me.
♫ You might not understand if I stay silent ♫
Please...
don't smear my heart with mud any further.
♫ No matter how many times I try, I'll never make a mistake ♫