=Rainforest Passions=
=Episode 29=
Xiamo has been kidnapped
by Li Qingfeng.
Chaya is also in his hands.
He told you not to alert anyone
and to bring all your money
along with the Eye of Wucha to him.
Chaya.
I didn't expect
you and Bai Lan are still scheming!
You made me do this.
I'm bleeding.
I've done so much to find our secret place.
I said, I'm bleeding.
Why aren't you feeling sorry for me?
I no longer have any sympathy for you.
You only disgust me now.
Don't look at me like that!
That look in your eyes
only makes me want to gouge them out.
But you know
I can't bear to.
How about this?
I'll torture her instead.
Then beg me, okay?
Don't do it.
Li Qingfeng, no.
Please.
I'll do anything you ask.
Just don't harm the innocent.
Why do you care so much about others?
Yet, there's no place for someone
like me?
Do you know
nothing else matters
than you
in my heart?
Do you know
why I brought you here today?
Eighteen years of secret admiration,
I hid it all here.
But you broke your promise.
You once told me
that we'd always be family
and I'm the most important person to you.
I kept my word.
Did you?
You're like a ray of light.
Just one glance
at you fills me
with satisfaction.
I've cared for you
like a delicate flower.
I've done so much for you.
Why can't I enter your heart?
When we were five,
we moved into a new home together.
I always thought
becoming family with you
was the happiest moment of my life.
Do you remember
how happy we all were back then?
I wasn't the one
who destroyed this bond.
It was you.
For years, I've been trapped
by calling you sister.
Can't you feel it
when I look at you?
You've lost your mind.
Yes.
You're right!
I've lost my mind!
I've completely lost my mind!
Why won't you love me?
You're willing to give up everything
for Qi Chuan.
Why can't you do the same for me?
You will come back to Mangbei with me.
So long as Qi Chuan gives me
the Eye of Wucha,
I can make a comeback.
Stop dreaming.
He won't let you succeed.
That's not a nice thing to say.
Then I have to start the punishment.
Li Qingfeng.
Li Qingfeng!
See?
Don't.
I've unlocked the gates
but she couldn't even walk out.
I'll do whatever you want.
Please don't hurt her.
Li Qingfeng.
Li Qingfeng!
No!
I'll give you one last chance
to say something.
You're the reason
I'm in this state.
It's all my fault for trusting
the wrong person.
I thought you would change your ways.
Our special guest has finally arrived.
Xiamo.
Qi Chuan,
watch out for Bai Lan.
Ms. Bai is a smart woman.
Why would she choose
to work with Li Qingfeng for a second time?
Don't waste your breath.
One of you used me to pave
the way for your success.
The other one turned her efforts
in vain.
She can only trust me.
It's all because of you guys.
Li Qingfeng,
this money and treasure
are more than enough for you
to escape unscathed.
Release them.
What gives you the right
to order me around?
These things
were mine to begin with.
I am the one you hate.
Kidnapping two women
doesn't make you a man.
I'll give you a chance.
If you want something,
direct it to me instead.
Trying to be a hero, huh?
I'll give you that chance too.
Go inside
and I won't mistreat them.
Take that
and tie him up.
How do you plan to deal with them?
Burn it all down
and make it look like an accident.
Then we should leave now.
No rush.
Go and check the goods.
We'll need a scapegoat for this fire
and it can only be you.
Qi Chuan,
our game will begin now.
♪Listen to the black-and-white
chess pieces melt into tears♪
♪Who is the one♪
♪Who speaks the obscure lie?♪
♪Your answer is always better♪
♪Than feigned ignorance♪
♪Is it fate that refuses to let me go?♪
♪Is it something I can't let go?♪
♪Or is the past too complicated?♪
♪The scar etched♪
♪In my heart still hurts♪
♪Should I be bound♪
♪Or struggle free from your kiss?♪
♪The most hurtful words may not be lies♪
♪If fireflies are destined to burn out♪
♪And every meeting comes with parting♪
♪Can all the regrets be traded♪
♪For this one overlap of fate?♪
♪Is loving you an obsession♪
♪Or my self-deception?♪
♪Memories surface♪
♪When I look at your face again♪