=Rainforest Passions=
=Episode 23=
It looks like
the Wucha God
wants you to stay again.
Hey, kid.
What's is it, mister?
Can you lend me
your bubble machine for a while?
Sure.
Thanks.
I'll give it back to you later.
Can't I just be left alone for a while?
Do I no longer have the right
to walk on my own?
I don't like seeing you look gloomy.
I want my little plaything to be happy.
Can you just let me go?
It's also letting yourself go.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
How is that possible?
The world is filled
with too many distracting noises.
You only need to listen to one.
But now I regret it.
I can no longer return
to the safe haven I know.
Just forget about the safe haven
he created.
My black castle
will be completed soon.
Chaya.
Be careful.
I was planning to show off
my recovery.
Your shoelace is undone.
Be careful not to trip.
Xiamo!
Can you go
and buy me a bottle of water?
Okay.
It's been a while.
I finally get to see you.
Do you know how worried I was?
You were worried about me?
You've always been
under Li Qingfeng's control.
He's been blocking me
from contacting you.
It wasn't until I saw
the engagement news
between you two on the media
that I realized something was wrong.
Li Qingfeng
may be a little overprotective.
But he's really nice to me.
We have a great understanding.
But Qi Chuan doesn't think so.
No one can take your place
in his heart.
It's just a shame
I've become his burden
over the past year.
In his eyes,
I'm the indirect killer
of Zheng and his brother,
and the bad woman
who caused you to hurt your leg.
He forced me to stay by his side
only to torture me
so he could feel better.
Did you also lose your senses
since your memory loss?
Why would he want to torment you?
He's gathering evidence.
What evidence?
There was blood
from a fourth person at the scene.
My father passed away
in prison due to a stroke.
Li Qingfeng left with the Eye of Wucha
and disappeared with you without a word.
Have you ever considered
there might be other possibilities?
Are you okay?
I can't remember.
You've told my assistant too much.
She can't take it here.
I'll visit again in a couple of days.
Xiamo,
I hope you'll be able to see the truth
the next time we meet.
The company is saved.
Mr. Qi has sent over the proposal.
Do we really have no choice
but to cooperate with them?
What happened?
You look upset.
Xiamo wants to break off the engagement.
It's her own fault.
Xiamo has always been a burden to us.
With Mr. Qi's investment,
we can cash out and leave.
As for the shares Xiamo holds,
we should hold
a press conference immediately
and expose her
as a fraud pretending
to be a rich heiress.
Don't harm her.
Announcing it now
would do no good for the company.
I really don't want to wait any longer.
Once the funds are in,
we'll empty out this company
and leave together,
okay?
You wanted the scent of fir.
Bring it in.
This used to be your favorite smell.
But now,
I prefer the fragrance of flowers.
Li Qingfeng has sheltered
and turned you into someone weak.
What are you doing?
Relax.
I'm just letting you feel
the warmth of fire.
After the explosion,
Zheng and Chaya were trapped
in the car for a long time.
That fire
also burned for a long time.
Do you hear...
Do you hear that noise?
What noise?
I don't know.
With your superior hearing,
I'm sure you can distinguish it.
My hearing is very sharp.
There's no way I'd mishear it.
It's the sound of a countdown.
Get out!
There's a bomb!
I heard the sound of a countdown.
How did you get out alive
from that explosion?
I... I told him to save them.
Who is he?
Li Qingfeng.
You've finally remembered.
♪Listen to the black-and-white
chess pieces melt into tears♪
♪Who is the one♪
♪Who speaks the obscure lie?♪
♪Your answer is always better♪
♪Than feigned ignorance♪
♪Is it fate that refuses to let me go?♪
♪Is it something I can't let go?♪
♪Or is the past too complicated?♪
♪The scar etched♪
♪In my heart still hurts♪
♪Should I be bound♪
♪Or struggle free from your kiss?♪
♪The most hurtful words may not be lies♪
♪If fireflies are destined to burn out♪
♪And every meeting comes with parting♪
♪Can all the regrets be traded♪
♪For this one overlap of fate?♪
♪Is loving you an obsession♪
♪Or my self-deception?♪
♪Memories surface♪
♪When I look at your face again♪