Timing and Subtitles brought by The Spiritual Guardians @ Viki
Don't bother, child surnamed Cao.
You want to die first? That's fine too.
Guardian spirit!
How dare you try and bluff me!
Brother, you came back?
Enough! Let Cao Yan Bing return to burn some paper offerings for you both!
- Cao Yan Bing!   - Brother!
Rakshasa Street
Episode 4
Demolishing my wall. Entering my territory. Beating my younger brother. Scaring my girl.
Hey!
I must figure this debt properly with you.
I wondered who finally appeared. Cao Yan Bing.
Brother. He and the people 10 years ago are the same group.
I have a lot to ask you, but I know you won't talk.
You are really funny.
If you don't talk, I'll beat you until you're half dead!
You begging for forgiveness will be your answer.
Do you understand?
Cao Yan Bing. Do you know who I am?
Understood. Understood.
Your surname
Hei Er Kan Pu
- Occupation.  - Special knight of the kingdom.
Purpose
Capture Cao Xuan Liang's guardian spirit.
Brother. His target is also the spirit pagoda tree.
Also the spirit pagoda tree
10 years ago, did all of you come because of the spirit pagoda tree?!
Yes
But it wasn't me at that time. That task was executed by another person.
Who made you?
I do not know.
Speak!
The kingdom is a very large organization. I'm just a small bandit among them.
Higher up. I really do not know.
You're so weak, like a small bandit.
Brother. Don't be deceived by him. His guardian spirit is Dao Jin Yi Hong.
Dao Jin Yi Hong?
Kid, don't you know what delay tactics is?
If you come closer, I'll kill him!
If the spirit host dies, the guardian spirit also dies.
What? Turns out you're not his guardian spirit.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Spiritual Guardians @ Viki
Lord. Let me out.
Lord. You have proven yourself as a powerful spirit host.
Let me out.
I really proved it?
I believe Wen Ze did not blame you.
Xiao Liang
Cao Yan Bing
Although Wen Ze left, Hu Chi will be determined and courageous to advance.
Wake up quickly!
You and I have been waiting for this day for 10 years.
Hu Chi requests to fight.
Xu Chu!
What's wrong?
Thanks
Xiao Liang
We won.
God of Ninja, Hattori Hanzo?
Ling Ling likes to eat these.
Right.
What's wrong? There are so many people.
Here. I'll go out and see. You pay.
Ok. Don't run far.
Hurry. Take a picture.
The fire of Sacred Pagoda connected two worlds.
Apparently, Hattori Hanzo has accomplished the mission of destroying Sacred Pagoda tree.
Sacred Pagoda branch must be already in his hand too.
I never worried about the mission assigned to Hattori.
He is the first generation descendant of Hattori Hanzo.
His body is flowing the blood of God of Ninja.
That is...
The light's boundary.
Captain, it seems the place of occurrence of the light is at Rakshasa street.
Rakshasa street?
Where is that?
Mom.
Ling Ling. Are you at school? Did you take a look at the sky?
I am looking at it right now.
What is that in the sky?
It's huge! It looks like a city! And the inside is all fiery!
Uhh...
Mom, the signal is bad. I will call you later.
Hello?
It's you.
You're that guy from the video, called something like Gui Shu San Tong!
He's called Gui Fu San Tong
I am named Gui Fu San Tong. I am honored to meet you, Fire General.
Is that axe yours?
It's mine.
Pay for it! Hurry and pay for cutting the tree!
Brother, it looks he did it to put out the fire.
What's wrong? What's wrong? What's with all these people?
Just then there was... there was a big flame!
It was all fiery, super huge!
- Go, go. They're waiting for us.  - It was really scary!
Pay me back! Pay for burning the tree! Pay for cutting the tree! Hurry and pay up!
- Pay up! - Ok, ok! Please don't get so emotional, Fire General. I'll pay you.
I was in a rush to leave, so I only bought this much.
I was just joking with him. He actually thought I was being serious.
Okay. Let's forget about the tree.
- I am here - Speak.
What are you doing here?
Master, the mission is complete.
Now the light of worlds' opening has disappeared. The Sacred Pagoda should be burnt up already.
Who injured you?
By Cao Yan Bing's spirit guardian.
Cao Yan Bing's spirit guardian?
No way. Cao Yan Bing's spirit guardian died ten years ago in a battle.
It wasn't Yu Jin, but Xu Chu.
Xu Chu? Hu Chi?
What a surprising kid.
Why don't you let me go personally and
get rid of him instantly.
There will be someone else taking care of Fire General.
You don't need to bother it.
Hattori, bring Hale to treat his wounds.
Also, pay attention to Cao Yan Bing.
Yes.
Calling out your guardian spirit will create a burden on the spirit host,
especially for someone who suddenly awakened his guardian spirit, like you.
In the next moment, your eyes will fill with blood.
And then, you will have a nosebleed.
Finally, you will see darkness,
grow weak, and faint.
Brother.
- Cao Yan Bing.   - Brother.
Who is it?!
Yay! I won. Yay!
Give me five.
Bro, what are you doing with your weapon?
Where's that lady?
Are you talking about Xia Ling?
She said that her parents are coming over so she went to go eat with them.
Come with me for a bit
As far as I could remember,
this tree has always been in my backyard.
I've long gotten used to playing chess beneath this tree, have tea,
play on my phone, snatch red envelopes.
I would wash my clothes and hang them on the tree to dry.
But now, it has actually become a bunch used coals.
Seems like Fire General actually
cares so much about this Sacred Pagoda tree.
Sacred Pagoda tree was planted during Dong Jing dynasty.
Today, it has been almost 1,600 years.
About 1,600 years?
Fire General, do you know the relationship between Ghostdom and the human realm?
Ghostdom is one world. The human realm is another.
Yes, this is correct. However, how did the Ghostdom come about?
God created the universe in seven days.
Could it be, that Ghostdom was also created?
Bingo. You are right.
You this psychic!
You...
-This way. -Okay. Thank you.
-Hello. Here's the menu. -Thank you.
Sister Xia Ling and Uncle Ghost, I can't handle this anymore. I'm going to go sleep first.
There's plenty of rooms, you two better go to sleep soon. I won't bother with you two anymore.
- Goodnight.   - Goodnight.
I know that you have one hundred thousand, "whys" in your heart.
Number one. Who exactly are you?
This one here has already dressed up in this way,
clearly to avoid being recognized in my original appearance.
Second, you said someone wants to hurt me. How did you know?
Also you said I didn't die in the bus accident because it was just an accident.
You also said that I was originally a dead person.
Because Miss Xia is a spirit host.
At the bus accident, your guardian appeared,
and protected you, Miss Xia.
Or else it would've been hard for Miss Xia to live.
That bus accident... is it all related to this?
Then how come after the bus accident, I didn't remember anything?
The bus accident...
It's just an accident.
And why Miss Xia doesn't remember it, then I don't know how to explain.
Perhaps, a doctor's explanation will be more accurate.
Number three.
The one who wants to harm me, who can go invisible, is called what...
evil spirit, why do they want to harm me?
Because you are...
a spirit host.
I'm not sure if the Fire General has mentioned it to Miss Xia. I have sent out a warning message,
informing all spirit guardians to beware of an organization called the Kingdom organization.
They capture other spirit guardians,
and force them to join the organization.
It is similar to an evil cult.
So that evil spirit actually came to capture me?
That's right.
- Ling Ling!   - Dad, mom.
- Dad, mom! Take a seat..  - Ling Ling.
We bought so many things today that my legs were about to break.
Hurry and sit. Wah, so many things!
This is too fatty!
Hey! This is high in sugars!
I can't eat this. I can't eat that. Why did you order it?
It's for your father to eat.
Here. Eat.
Here. Eat more vegetables.
Women have to keep a nice body or they won't be able to get married.
How old am I? My life is just beginning! This beautiful flower is about to
blossom...
Newton devoted the later years of his life to God,
working diligently to prove the existence of God.
Do you think he's silly?
Theology is a science awaiting to be explained.
Ghostdom is indeed a place that was created.
But it wasn't by... God.
Fire General, do you know how the universe came about?
The Big Bang.
The Big Bang Theory of the universe states that
the universe came about from a big explosion.
And this universe that came out of the Big Bang is constantly expanding.
The ones who created the Ghostdom made use of this theory.
They also used a large explosion to create a new and small space.
Started out as a small space? So Ghostdom is included in it?
This space that started out small, was continually growing.
It kept growing until it became the huge Ghostdom that you know of now.
Furthermore, this ever expanding Ghostdom is constantly pushing on its borders.
Until one day... boom!
It collided with the human realm.
Collided with the human realm?
This is just like an increasingly expanding bubble meets another bubble.
If two bubbles crash into each other, what will happen?
If two bubbles collide they will just pressure each other.
But I would prefer to use the simile of connected spaces to describe this situation.
This situation has a name that is very familiar to you both, Men (door).
So it turns out the door connecting the two worlds is because of this!
The universe is constantly expanding. Ghostdom is also constantly expanding.
If these two bubbles continuously push against each other, then what will happen?
The smaller bubble will be pushed into the larger bubble, and then become a part of the larger bubble.
Bingo. You are right again.
This small bubble contains one world. The large bubble
contains an earth. When the section connecting the two places dissolves,
what will happen to these two worlds?
The air will flow freely between the two, the environments will combine, and will become a new world.
You are in me, I am in you
It will be a huge, splendid whirlpool.
It would be a word destroying vortex?
Yes, it is the a vortex that destroys worlds.
Bloody mixer...
Then... why is the world not destroyed yet?
Since, the universe is constantly expanding.
Alright, go back to the beginning of the topic.
Because of the existence of the Spirit pagoda tree, we are all still alive.
Here, let's make an example.
Ghostdom can be likened to a piece of plastic wrap that is constantly being stretched out.
If, on the border of this plastic wrap we hammer in a nail
and fix it to ground with this nail, this plastic wrap will not continue to get larger.
The Spirit pagoda tree is just like this nail.
But, just this one nail is not enough.
That's right. So, 632 years ago
the constables, in order to limit the expansion of Ghostdom,
planted 12 hundred thousand Spirit Pagoda trees.
- Twelve hundred thousand? - - Yes, twelve hundred thousand.
They are scattered across all the hundreds and thousands of requiem streets.
However, most of them don't have the ability to stabilize the space.
They are actually just a smokescreen. Only every one in every hundred thousand is a truly space stabilizing "nail".
These 12 trees are called the Spirit trees.
This Spirit pagoda tree is one of those.
So, as long as these 12 spirit trees are destroyed,
Ghostdom and the human realm will be doomed?
They don't all have to be destroyed.
Think about it. This plastic wrap is constantly being pulled apart.
If one of the nails stabilizing it is pulled out, then the remaining nails...
The remaining nails will automatically be weakened.
In other words, as long as one of the Spirit trees are destroyed,
The rest of the Spirit trees will be unable to hold on.
If you think back to the strange light that showed up yesterday,
you will know that I am telling you the true situation.
I'd like to know, who exactly destroyed my tree.
And you, how come you appeared at the critical moment to put out the fire?
Not sure if Fire General noticed,
yesterday, right before the Spirit pagoda tree was destroyed, a new sprout grew out.
This kind of appearance on the tree is known as a new start.
Each of the twelve trees harbor an immense amount of strength.
Only after a new start occurs can one of these trees be destroyed.
Sacred Pagoda was planted in 1632 years ago.
Yesterday was the first time this would happen. This is a secret that only a handful of people would know.
It is very normal for Fire General to not know about this.
So, you're saying for me to not know that this Spirit pagoda tree has been growing in my backyard for 1632 years is perfectly normal, and that for you to know this is normal?
Come on, Fire General. Look at how I am dressed, clearly I am in disguise.
Gui Fu San Tong, such a strange name, is also clearly an alias.
Without question, I am obviously an extremeeeemley awesome person.
Therefore, for me to know this information, is obviously very normal.
Fire General, are you starting to have a sense of powerlessness?
No matter. However, the next things I say to you, please remember well.
After Qi Ming, the new branch grown out from Sacred Pagoda tree is called Sacred Pagoda branch. As long as we get back the Sacred Pagoda branch, we may restore Sacred Pagoda tree.
I'm willing to help Fire General to get back the Sacred Pagoda branch.
I refuse.
I only care about ruling this street, it's not in my job description to save the world. If you please, Mr. Gui, pick up your drawing and take your leave.
Even if you don't care to pursue the ones who invaded your territory yesterday,
Do you not wish to pursue the ones who killed your friend and your guardian spirit ten years ago?
Does Fire General not wish to know the truth?
What exactly are you?
Timing and Subtitles brought by The Spiritual Guardians @ Viki
Bring Miss Xia Lin along with us on our trip.
I haven't even graduated college, and you already want me to meet with suitors, isn't that a bit crazy?
Why hasn't my guardian spirit shown up yet?
He was formerly in the service of the Muwen family
She's a beauty that can overthrow countries and cities.
Afterwards, we were attacted to each other, and fell in love.
Unfortunately, she contracted an incurable disease.
If I cannot save her, then I will join her in death!
Xuan Yuan!
♬  When earth and heaven become blurred, the beautiful becomes demonic,  ♬
♬  swallowing the maelstrom of the soul's desires  ♬
♬  You ask me why I still persist,  ♬
♬  why I don't surrender to the shining, golden shackles  ♬
♬  Even when everyone has been   ♬
♬   reduced to a powerless puppet,  ♬
♬  we cannot give up our world   ♬
♬   to those flashy, hypocritical scum  ♬
♬  Throw away your fears and prepare your strength  ♬
♬  Even if the heavens don't distinguish right from wrong,  ♬
♬  I vow to forever protect the fortress   ♬
♬   of our freedom, without giving in  ♬
♬   I will become a monument of a hero. Take all of our sins  ♬
♬   and burn them to ashes  ♬
♬  Too many people have already become puppets under their control  ♬
♬  Even when everyone has been   ♬
♬  reduced to a powerless puppet,  ♬
♬  we cannot give up our world   ♬
♬  to those flashy, hypocritical scum  ♬
♬  Take all of our sins  ♬
♬  Take all of our sins and burn them to ashes  ♬
Rakshasa Street