=Race to Romance=
Alright, this is our strategy
for the race.
Shen Nan, Gu Yichen,
do you have a problem?
- No.
No problem?
That's great.
No problem.
Mechanic, what about you?
You neither.
But you have a problem.
Gu Yichen,
we'll meet on the track again.
Please go easy on me this time.
Don't break my leg
again.
Zhang Yang, once drivers
are on the track,
they risk their lives.
If you're scared,
why don't you quit now?
You found a handsome boy
to back you up, huh?
Is that all?
- Get out!
- What are you doing?
Shut up, or I'll beat you!
Zhang Yang,
you're targeting me
instead of my teammates.
You're not welcomed here.
Please leave.
Gu Yichen,
I'm just trying to help.
Look,
they're all defending you.
But think about it.
What if you make a mistake
and cause his death on the track...
Oh, god! The thought makes me terrified!
Goodbye, guys.
Before every race,
I'd walk a few laps
on the track
to feel the changes
and ups and downs.
I'd keep these details
in my mind.
Gu Yichen,
are you okay?
Shen Nan,
if I told you I'm fine,
would you believe it?
Gu Yichen!
My idol!
You'll
be mine
sooner or later!
Gu Yichen!
My idol!
You'll
be mine
sooner or later!
I'll be yours sooner or later.
What about now?
You have to be mine every moment.
By the way...
Take this.
This is my favorite race car.
Do you like that?
No.
I don't like it.
Then why are you staring at it?
Can't I look around?
Enough, let's go back.
(Jiang)
There's a signature.
Gu Yichen likes this race car so much.
I suppose he also likes this driver.
And this is...
also my brother's and my dream.
So, this signature...
Where did you get this?
Well...
The signature...
Shen Nan,
did you write it yourself?
Just forget it.
I prepared this gift
to celebrate our first win.
But now...
I'm giving it to you in advance.
I want to tell you
this time,
I'm with you.
You're not fighting alone.
Trust me.
I like it.
I really like it.
This was my favorite
person when I was a child.
And this person
was my childhood idol.
I wanted this car so badly
that I begged my mom for a long time,
and she finally bought it.
Then one day,
my dad was furious
and returned the car.
(Fifteen Years Ago)
Dad.
Let's play the race car.
Dad!
Dad...
Why?
Maybe because
he's lived a conventional life.
He's never got
what he wanted.
So, when I could finally make decisions
for my life,
I chose to be a racing driver
without any hesitation
and won my first
championship.
I don't know
why I love racing so much.
Maybe it's thrilling.
Or maybe
I enjoy controlling the car.
So, I didn't think
racing was dangerous...
Until that accident.
I made a mistake.
I watched Zhang Yang
being pulled from the car
with blood all over his body.
But I couldn't do anything.
If someone lost their lives
because of my error...
How could I...
How could I compensate them?
I'll never forget
that moment.
And I can't forget it.
I must move forward
with this burden.
Shen Nan.
Maybe this is my choice.
I trust you, Gu Yichen.
We can make it.
Because...
you're not alone.
=Episode 9=
=To Fight=
(Shen Nan)
Every parameter,
every piece of data,
and even every component
are my work.
Nothing will go wrong.
Shen Nan.
Just do your best in the race.
I'll handle the rest.
You too.
Gu Yichen.
What's wrong?
Gu Yichen! Gu Yichen! Gu Yichen!
(Changgu Racing Team)
(Drive Non-stop, Win the Race)
Gu Yichen! Gu Yichen!
Dear audience,
the most exciting
qualifying race of City Grand Prix
has begun.
For all the drivers
and teams,
this race is crucial.
As we can see,
(City Championship)
All
the drivers and their teams
are ready to go.
Now, let's stay tuned.
The qualifying race
will be faster than you can
imagine!
(Marshal, 1 Min)
(Gu Yichen)
Zhang Yang is after Yichen.
He must break through.
Shen Nan,
help Gu Yichen get rid of Zhang Yang.
I can take the middle lane
to stop them from overtaking.
Shen Nan, it's too dangerous.
Trust me, I can do it!
Gu Yichen, seize the opportunity!
♪When the heavy rain falls♪
♪When the world collapses♪
- Great!
Shen Nan, Gu Yichen,
your single-lap speed is not enough.
You need to try harder.
- Keep going!
- Got it!
♪You must stay strong♪
♪Bravely fight for the light♪
♪When the heavy rain falls♪
♪When the world collapses♪
♪Don't be afraid, we're by your side♪
♪Look ahead♪
♪Light shines bright♪
♪You must stay strong♪
- Great!
- Awesome!
- We won!
- Gu Yichen 1st place, Shen Nan 2nd Place!
- Yes!
I'm so proud of them!
- Awesome!
- Gu Yichen
had a perfect performance
in the race.
He once again
set a new record
for single-lap speed.
He made it again,
reminding us of the past!
♪Bravely fight
for the light that's yours♪
Did you hire the new driver
for Dayuan Racing Team?
I haven't seen him before.
Yes.
His name is Zhang Yang.
He's full of spirit.
After he joined us,
we saw a catfish effect.
Everyone has improved.
I watched the race.
He's indeed full of spirit,
but it seems a bit too much.
He was targeting
Gu Yichen the whole time.
It feels like
they have
a blood feud.
Grandpa, don't worry.
My brother is working for our rival,
but
we're family after all.
No matter what,
I won't let anyone
hurt him.
♪Oh oh, alright♪
♪You try, baby, tell me, lovely girl♪
♪Love is like
a layer of burning mustard♪
♪Tears spill from the sting♪
♪Back to back, we whisper♪
♪Promises we swore♪
♪I want a reason to comfort you♪
♪You dodge my gaze, ice in your eyes♪
♪I don't want to let go,
should we both say goodbye♪
♪Or persist in staying this way♪
♪Hi, hi, hi, your helpless look♪
♪Me, me, me, with polite words♪
♪From start to end, you never cared♪
♪Too weak to bear♪
♪After leaving, go chase freely♪
♪Love, love, love, don't be like this♪
♪Me, me, me, no tears this time♪
♪We'll walk away more free♪
♪After leaving, go chase freely♪
♪No love won't mean lonely nights♪
♪You don't have to hold me back, okay♪
♪This clouded love's too blurry to see♪
♪The reason to let go grows clearer
in my mind♪
♪I'm not stubborn,
just slip away silent♪
♪Brave the split, make the cut clean♪
♪Just like this,
it might not be happy anymore♪
♪Love, love, love, don't be like this♪
♪Me, me, me, no tears this time♪
♪We'll walk away more free♪
♪After leaving, go chase freely♪