=Race to Romance=
Shen Nan,
how did you
get into racing?
Just because I like it.
The thrill of competition.
Just like it?
I thought you'd answer more sincerely.
What about you?
It's about choices.
Ever since I was a kid,
I've felt like
a lot of things
have been arranged for me.
And my will was always dictated
by others.
Sometimes
I really envy my brother.
Maybe Grandpa kept him away
from the family
so he could choose freely.
And sometimes
I feel like my father
is quite biased.
Privileged background.
But had no other choice.
Gu Yichen,
it sounds like
you're somewhat bragging.
But I respect
that you chose to do
what you like,
just like me.
Though
I sound pretentious too.
I just want to tell you,
don't worry about me.
Racing is my only choice.
I'll stand my ground.
On this track,
I won't back down.
I believe you, Gu Yichen.
I'm with you, too.
We'll surely win together.
But
there's only one champion.
We're teammates
and rivals, who know each other best.
Don't be jealous
if I win the championship.
It's not decided yet.
=Episode 6=
=He Must Be Very Upset=
You woke up so early.
You're awake.
You were exhausted yesterday.
I made you some congee.
Go wash up.
It's almost ready.
Shen Nan,
if you were a girl,
I'd marry you.
Really?
Yes.
What's up?
They're about to start the track training.
I came to check the data.
Come here.
You've been really tired lately, huh?
Yeah, a bit.
Let me give you a massage.
Not bad.
Did you take lessons?
Yeah, I tried to be versatile.
I can even read palms.
Let me check yours.
Seriously?
Yes.
Do you think I'm lying?
Let me.
Enough?
No.
No, I'm not...
I... I really know how to read palms.
I'll read it for you.
You're missing someone in your life.
Come on, keep going.
Born in 2000.
He's an Aries.
And then?
He's lively and cheerful,
and quite handsome.
You're not talking about yourself,
are you?
His name is Fu Chuan.
Alright, enough jokes.
Get out now.
The training's starting soon.
Fine.
Take care of yourself.
Alright.
And
make sure to rest well.
Got it. Now leave.
Alright, I'm off.
Straight-line speed
isn't maximizing the car's potential.
With today's data,
you'll be dead last
in the City Grand Prix.
Gu Yichen, take a look.
Your braking points are off,
and cornering speed's a joke.
This isn't you.
Fix whatever is messing
with your head,
or quit now
and spare the shame.
But our two-car pit strategy worked.
We can recover...
Li Su,
give them some more time.
Take it easy.
Take it easy?
Sure,
with the first race is just days away.
The City Grand Prix includes 12 races.
It's ranked by points.
Every race is crucial.
There is no time
for gradual teamwork,
got it?
Li Su,
I need to talk to you.
Stop training.
It's not a technical issue.
It's here.
Sorry,
the subscriber you dialed
can not be connected for the moment,
please redial later.
♪Oh oh, alright♪
♪You try, baby, tell me, lovely girl♪
♪Love is like
a layer of burning mustard♪
♪Tears spill from the sting♪
♪Back to back, we whisper♪
♪Promises we swore♪
♪I want a reason to comfort you♪
♪You dodge my gaze, ice in your eyes♪
♪I don't want to let go,
should we both say goodbye♪
♪Or persist in staying this way♪
♪Hi, hi, hi, your helpless look♪
♪Me, me, me, with polite words♪
♪From start to end, you never cared♪
♪Too weak to bear♪
♪After leaving, go chase freely♪
♪Love, love, love, don't be like this♪
♪Me, me, me, no tears this time♪
♪We'll walk away more free♪
♪After leaving, go chase freely♪
♪No love won't mean lonely nights♪
♪You don't have to hold me back, okay♪
♪This clouded love's too blurry to see♪
♪The reason to let go grows clearer
in my mind♪
♪I'm not stubborn,
just slip away silent♪
♪Brave the split, make the cut clean♪
♪Just like this,
it might not be happy anymore♪
♪Love, love, love, don't be like this♪
♪Me, me, me, no tears this time♪
♪We'll walk away more free♪
♪After leaving, go chase freely♪