=Race to Romance=
Shen Nan,
did you see the gap?
Okay, back to the team.
Next group.
You have good driving skills
and reaction speed.
But why is your body
so weak?
Shen Nan just said
he wanted to take another
physical test with me.
Really?
I...
Sure.
Keep it up.
Listen,
a racing driver's helmet weighs
about two kilograms.
Every acceleration,
brake,
and turn,
will create a strong centrifugal force.
Therefore,
you must have
strong neck strength
and stamina
to support you
and keep your mind clear.
Otherwise,
you and your car
might be broken
into pieces anytime.
Shen,
how many girls
have you been dealing with?
I mean,
how many girlfriends do you have?
I... I don't have a girlfriend.
You don't?
Then why do I feel
you're so exhausted?
I...
You what?
Listen,
you've been acting really soft lately.
Haven't you noticed it?
Keep going.
Are you okay, Shen Nan?
You go first.
Hey, can you run faster?
We've almost finished it.
Faster.
Shen Nan!
What's wrong?
Come on.
Let me check.
Okay.
Let's deal with the injury.
Don't move.
=Episode 4=
=What Have I Done?=
Look.
What's wrong?
Don't you think
they are a bit strange?
No, they're always...
They're indeed a bit strange.
Well, they do look a bit...
strange.
Who's strange?
You two are strange.
Get back to work.
Susu,
have some water.
You must be thirsty.
Susu, I heard about
a new instant-boiled mutton restaurant.
Let's try it together.
No.
Instant-boiled mutton is too bland.
Let's eat hotpot.
Hotpot sounds good.
It's great. Let's eat hotpot.
Susu, I really like eating...
Can you stop calling me Susu?
That's so cheesy.
Call me sister.
Then, Sister Susu.
Do you want me to beat you?
Even I want to beat you.
Beat you.
Ouch, ouch!
It's done.
I never expected
the physical training
to be so hard.
I never expected
you'd be like a weak girl.
Hey.
What do you mean?
Are you being sexist?
I'm not being sexist.
Listen,
Shirley Muldowney
is a female champion.
After a car accident,
she couldn't get sponsorship,
but she never gave up.
And there are
Janet Guthrie
and Lyn St. James.
They are all top female racing drivers
and champions.
You got me wrong.
I'm not biased against
female racing drivers.
It's just that race cars are so fast
that even a minor mistake can be fatal.
That's why we need to accept
all kinds of physical training.
The intense physical training
is more difficult
for women.
Am I wrong about that?
(Is he still training?)
♪Oh oh, alright♪
♪You try, baby, tell me, lovely girl♪
♪Love is like
a layer of burning mustard♪
♪Tears spill from the sting♪
♪Back to back, we whisper♪
♪Promises we swore♪
♪I want a reason to comfort you♪
♪You dodge my gaze, ice in your eyes♪
♪I don't want to let go,
should we both say goodbye♪
♪Or persist in staying this way♪
♪Hi, hi, hi, your helpless look♪
♪Me, me, me, with polite words♪
♪From start to end, you never cared♪
♪Too weak to bear♪
♪After leaving, go chase freely♪
♪Love, love, love, don't be like this♪
♪Me, me, me, no tears this time♪
♪We'll walk away more free♪
♪After leaving, go chase freely♪
♪No love won't mean lonely nights♪
♪You don't have to hold me back, okay♪
♪This clouded love's too blurry to see♪
♪The reason to let go grows clearer
in my mind♪
♪I'm not stubborn,
just slip away silent♪
♪Brave the split, make the cut clean♪
♪Just like this,
it might not be happy anymore♪
♪Love, love, love, don't be like this♪
♪Me, me, me, no tears this time♪
♪We'll walk away more free♪
♪After leaving, go chase freely♪