A wedding dress!
Are there 11 couples?
Standing before you
are 11 married couples.
Five of these couples
- have multiple children.
- Multiple children?
The other 6 couples
have no children.
What makes this so extreme
is that some here have no kids.
Completely childless.
This must be tough.
There are twice as many people to read.
That's way too many.
They have to read 22 people.
Read the couples' fates
and their child-related fortunes,
then find the couples
with multiple children.
How are we to guess who has kids
with a minor on our team?
Come on.
Mommy's got this.
I have a child of my own,
and most of my clients are moms.
I've met moms with many kids,
so I was confident.
I'm good at reading who's had an abortion
or who's had or will have a baby.
But…
the first match was tough
because we couldn't agree on things.
Honestly, I'd basically given up.
But I was still determined to survive.
I'm pretty confident.
Last week, my Granny spirit told me
to put seaweed on the altar in my shrine.
That means Grandma Samshin
is involved.
And today, we got a question
that needs Grandma Samshin's powers.
I'm sure we'll go through.
You will be given 100 minutes.
If you think you have the correct answer,
go to the Well of Truth,
ring the bell,
and you'll find out if you're right.
If your answer is correct,
the moon will appear in the well.
Fate Readers, please begin the reading.
Right away? Just like that?
Hmm?
Noh Seulbi is always quick to move.
Totally. She just charges straight in.
Do couples with many children
give off a different aura?
I'm sure they do.
With couples who have many children,
I can tell just from their faces.
I can tell if the mom
is a boy mom or a girl mom.
Grandma Samshin.
She's 1 of the deities I serve,
so I'm good at this kind of thing.
Oh, she must be here.
Grandma Samshin's taking over.
Grandma Samshin's here.
- His gaze has changed.
- Yes.
He must have a feeling.
My Granny spirit showed me images
of couples holding a baby,
not knowing what to do.
TEAM BLACK TORTOISE
Grandma Samshin…
My Guardian spirit
plays the role of Grandma Samshin too.
And the scissors I carry around
are the very ones
she uses to cut umbilical cords.
That's why I carry around those scissors.
So I took them with me.
- Young Master Plum Blossom.
- He's here.
I walked around the couples
with the Samshin scissors
and I could get a vague idea
of whether they have kids.
I then snapped the scissors
in front of some couples.
I did that to see
if I could hear babies crying.
After that…
I smell baby formula.
I opened up all my senses,
and suddenly I could smell baby formula.
But since there were so many people,
I couldn't tell
who the formula smell was coming from.
So I walked back and forth
between them for a while,
and I stopped in front of the couple
where I caught that formula smell again.
I was sure she has a child.
TEAM AZURE DRAGON
Shall we do a reading separately first?
-Yes. Let's discuss after.
-Let's do it separately first.
- Let's see if we have overlapping answers.
- All right.
Team Azure Dragon.
Lee Sobin's a bit quiet, isn't she?
Yeah, she wasn't going for it.
But she needs to prove herself
on this one.
This is her moment to deliver.
I wasn't much help in the first match
because my Granny spirit had gone home,
so I was determined to do well this time.
She is fated to be a boy mom.
During my initiation rite,
the first fortune I told was,
"There's a baby in your tummy."
ANOINTING TO RECEIVE
DEITIES AND BECOME A SHAMAN
They say I have strong ties
with Grandma Samshin.
That means I'm good
at reading fortunes related to babies.
Are they able to stay together
without children?
Or do they need children to stay together?
That was my approach to this question.
Jeong Gihwan, 45, Choi Bogyeong, 46.
Do they have more than 1 child?
Do you have your answers?
Shall we discuss?
Why don't we start with the first couple?
Number 1, Hwang Hyeonhwan and his wife.
What I'm getting from couple number 1
is that they're like friends.
But I got the sense that they fight.
My initial reading is
that they do have a child.
- Me too.
- They have a child?
The compatibility of this first couple is…
They're both incredibly stubborn.
- They clash.
- They clash hard when they do,
- but when it's good, they're great.
- Yes.
The husband's energy is stagnant,
but the wife's cards show fire,
so she gets pregnant easily.
For them, I got the Three of Cups,
which symbolizes the womb.
There's a card that symbolizes the womb?
I also got the Birds,
and birds flock, you know.
So their kids are like sparrows.
That's how I felt, so I marked number 1
as a couple with children.
Oh.
Sparrows hatch a lot of eggs.
She saw a womb in the cards for number 1.
-Ah.
-How about you?
To me, number 1 is…
a maybe.
This is when things get confusing.
When 2 people say "yes"
but 1 of them says "no."
Team Azure Dragon might argue a lot.
Why do I keep seeing the wife
with a pregnant belly?
Sobin, can you check
number 1 for me again?
A GREEN FLAG SIGNALS NEGATION
Uh-huh.
But honestly,
Sobin doesn't seem like herself today.
She's not her usual self.
I keep losing my flow today.
Even my obanggi
are not working.
This round just isn't going my way.
This is bad.
I'm totally off today.
What? No, Sobin…
Sobin's in bad form.
I can't see anything right now.
- Don't give in. Try again.
- I'm done for.
I'll draw your obanggi, then.
Let me try.
Here you go.
A BLUE FLAG SIGNALS NEGATION
This means no children.
My obanggi can't be trusted right now.
Why is my Granny spirit so angry?
I could feel something was off
with me today.
There are days
when you just can't read fortunes.
So I figured
something must've upset my Granny.
She'd basically gone on strike today.
I think my Granny spirit clocked out.
Her Granny spirit went home.
Oh, no.
Sobin is completely deflated.
No wonder she was so quiet.
- It must be a bad day for her.
- Oh, dear…
She's not getting any readings.
When I go to get my fortune told,
even the good shamans say,
"I can't see anything today."
Right, this is not her day. It can happen.
They say their Granny spirit's angry.
It must be really tough for shamans
when they can't see anything.
It must drive them crazy.
- They become helpless.
- Ah.
She must be devastated.
"Why won't you help me today,
Granny? Why won't you speak?"
I was upset with her,
and I guess slightly resentful.
They seem lost.
Goodness.
TEAM WHITE TIGER
We must discuss
the most likely candidates.
Number 1. They have children, right?
Number 1.
I think they have multiple kids.
Do you all agree?
Number 1.
We'd missed an answer
in the previous match
because I didn't listen to them,
so I decided to be more accepting
of my teammates' opinions.
A RED FLAG SIGNALS AFFIRMATION
I also think that number 1 has children.
Do we all agree?
No, I'm not sure.
- You're uncertain?
- I'm confused about 1 thing.
They're incredibly incompatible.
-Yet they're still together.
-Something makes it work.
-They could be staying for the kids.
-Yes.
-They'd split if they didn't have kids.
Why don't we confirm with the well?
Ask about couple number 1.
-Shall we?
-Yeah, let's ask.
- You're unsure about them, right?
- Yeah.
- Then go for it. I trust you.
- Okay.
- We must ask when we're not sure.
- Right.
-They're going already?
-What?
What's going on?
Team White Tiger's fast.
TEAM WHITE TIGER
COUPLE 1 HWANG HYEONHWAN,
YANG EUNYEONG
- The moon appeared.
- They got the moon.
- This is crazy.
- Wow.
They got it right away.
Okay, they got it right.
COUPLE 1 HAS MULTIPLE CHILDREN
They're staying for the kids.
- Right?
- Yes. We were right.
They have no choice.
Without the kids,
they can't stay together.
COUPLE 1
Team White Tiger's off to a good start.
TEAM BLACK TORTOISE
Should I try holding their hands?
Yeah, go for it.
Then I'll go and check their hands.
Plum Blossom's fired up, isn't he?
If you don't mind, may I feel your pulse?
Excuse me.
I checked their pulses
because women
who've given birth many times
have an extra pulse that signals life.
Most importantly, I feel a jigi in my stomach.
COUPLE 9 KIM HYEONGU,
YEO EUNGYEONG
When I felt her pulse, I felt
a tearing sensation in my lower stomach.
I physically felt she'd given birth.
Thank you.
Ouch, my back.
- Looks like he has back pain.
- He's gripping his waist.
He's sensing multiple pregnancies,
that's why.
Oh! Ah!
- Birthing pains.
- Is that it?
- He's got his cloth out.
- Mmm.
- He's tying it up.
- Yes.
Last time, I prepared
a goppae
for a deceased who died tragically.
I used a white goppae this time.
It's like the pure white cloth
used for baby diapers back in the day.
We do rites with pure white cloth
for the Chilseong deity,
who oversees babies.
I held pure white cloth
in front of the couples
to see if I could feel babies.
I closed my eyes
to see if I'd get any visions.
COUPLE 10 HAN GYEONGMIN,
PARK JIYEON
I hear crying.
I heard the heartbeat of a fetus
and also the loud cries of a newborn.
When I untangled the cloth,
I saw a vision of rice grains falling.
Rice means abundance,
so I figured it meant
this couple had many children.
Let's compare our answers.
Number 5 wasn't too bad.
- I've marked number 5 too.
- Me too.
I sensed the energy of Grandma Samshin
quite strongly from number 5.
- That's right.
- Plus,
my reading tells me
the wife really pulls the husband in.
But number 10 is just like that too.
What I'm sensing from number 10 is,
- the man has the birth chart of a butcher.
- I see.
It means there's a hole in the ceiling.
So, no roof over his head.
But for him,
his wife is a blessing.
The wife has the temperament of a general.
- That's right.
- So she embraces him
and props him up at the same time.
So when I untied my cloth
in front of the wife,
I saw rice grains fall.
They have Grandma Samshin's blessing.
I'm sure.
I just got the chills.
The man's a butcher,
and the wife's a general.
- Which couple?
- Number 10.
- Like Beauty and the Beast.
- Wow.
- Mmm.
- I also marked number 8.
I picked out number 8 too.
I thought they were
a good match as a couple.
COUPLE 8 JEONG HWANDO,
JEONG YOJEONG
I'm sure about 5, 8, and 10.
- Me too. We all picked the same couples.
- Yeah, same here.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
I want these 3 couples
to be included in our final answer.
- Okay. Numbers 5, 8, and 10.
- Yes.
COUPLE 5, COUPLE 8, COUPLE 10
I'm confused about this couple too.
TEAM WHITE TIGER
Don't you think? I'm confused about them.
- I'm sure about number 5.
- Mm-hmm.
- Number 5 is a definite yes.
- You think so?
AT THE START OF THE READING
As soon as I waved my fan and bells…
My Granny spirit told me
to write down this number.
"I must mention number 5."
I'm sure about number 5.
We missed out
on a correct answer in the last round.
I'll be more assertive this time.
Young Master Jiseon is…
Yes, speak up.
I'll go take a look.
COUPLE 5 JEONG GIHWAN,
CHOI BOGYEONG
May I see your hand?
When I hold their hand,
I hear either a "yes" or a "no."
"This is it."
- I checked out number 5's energy.
- Okay.
I checked on them just to be sure.
They say men are better cool
and women are better warm, right?
The husband's hand is cold,
and the wife's hand is hot.
In other words,
their yin and yang energy mixes well.
Mmm.
And also, I think
the woman has a more potent "field."
Mmm.
- "Seed" means man and "field" is woman.
- Yes.
Oh, really?
I'm quite certain about number 5.
Let's put them down as a "yes" then.
I'll trust my instinct.
We didn't listen to you last time.
Young Master Jiseon's answers
last time were all correct.
If he's that certain,
I figured I should trust him on this.
They were actually hearing me out.
I thought our teamwork
was finally coming together.
Numbers 1 and 5.
- We're sure about these.
- Yes.
TEAM AZURE DRAGON
Team Azure Dragon's a letdown.
It looks like they gave up, doesn't it?
Ah.
Team Azure Dragon needs to try harder.
They aren't even talking to each other.
It looks like
they've lost their morale.
- They've lost their power.
- It seems so.
It was pretty likely
Sobin was having a bit of a breakdown,
so I thought we might actually lose.
I decided I shouldn't let ourselves
sit still and do nothing.
So I went up to the couples.
Seolhwa's on the move.
I'm not the type to just sit still.
I'm actually quite competitive.
Because I was part of a team,
I felt a sense of responsibility.
I thought I should take the lead.
As soon as I stopped before the couple,
my Granny spirit spoke to me.
So I was confident that this couple
has multiple children.
I pick number 6.
COUPLE 6 LEE SEUNGHEON, KIM MIJEONG
Their birth charts tell me
the woman carries the man.
My reading is
that the husband is incapable…
…of having a monogamous marriage.
If they have children,
she'll be the one doing all the raising.
The woman must do everything.
Having kids would
make things difficult for Mijeong,
but my Granny spirit told me
that they do have kids.
Okay, so they do have kids.
But I didn't mark this couple
because the husband
has a serious fertility issue.
- Oh.
- That's what the cards say.
There's no movement.
Lee Seungheon, 40 years old.
And Kim Mijeong, 39 years old.
Do they have more than 1 child?
No sign of children?
I'm seeing no movement.
KING OF WANDS, PAGE OF PENTACLES,
THE EMPEROR, COFFIN, BEAR
Oh…
You can see that too?
Tarot can show if the sperm is dormant?
Can you also see azoospermia?
Is he an azoospermic man?
It looks like the sperm
can't reach the egg.
I should get a crane
if they're meant to get pregnant,
but I keep getting an eagle
snatching up a lizard to kill it.
Gosh, I've got goosebumps.
She can see such details too?
It depends on
how you ask your question, huh?
I'm sensing some kind of surgery.
- That surgery could be a vasectomy.
- Yes.
A RED FLAG SIGNALS AFFIRMATION
COUPLE 6 LEE SEUNGHEON HAD A VASECTOMY
Seolhwa's on fire.
Seolhwa's on a roll right now.
- I'm curious about number 6.
- Number 6?
- Yes.
- Number 6.
- Shall we ask about number 6?
- Yeah, let's.
Mmm.
TEAM AZURE DRAGON
COUPLE 6 LEE SEUNGHEON, KIM MIJEONG
The moon appeared.
Seolhwa's carrying this.
COUPLE 6 HAS MULTIPLE CHILDREN
Who are you most confused about?
He works under the blazing sun?
Why does number 6 bother me so much?
COUPLE 6 LEE SEUNGHEON, KIM MIJEONG
- I think they have kids.
- Right?
I also think number 6 has kids.
What about the couple at the end?
- Number 7.
- Right, number 7.
COUPLE 7 OH YEONGSU, LEE EUNCHAE
I think number 7 has kids.
- I think so too.
- Same.
We all have the same picks.
Write down the couples
that we all agree on.
- Number 7 is a yes.
- Yes.
Mmm.
- They're really good.
- Yes.
Team White Tiger's back in the game.
- They might actually go through.
- They're doing pretty well.
They're back in form.
- They must be good at couple readings.
- Yes, maybe.
- Reading on couples?
- That's right.
TEAM BLACK TORTOISE
Are there any couples you're sure about?
Number 2.
I marked number 2 as well.
I marked number 2 but crossed them off.
Oh, why?
Well, I had a look and…
COUPLE 2 JU SANGWON, PARK SEOHYEON
The husband agrees
with whatever his wife says,
and it looks like
she said having a child was a risk.
I took that to mean
she doesn't really want kids.
I do think you are right about that.
But I still sense the energy
of Grandma Samshin.
- Do you?
- The energy's still there.
Then shouldn't we check with the well?
Let's confirm number 2 later.
Okay, sounds good.
Number 2, on hold.
- Next, we have…
- Mmm.
Hmm…
Number 4.
I picked number 4 too.
Ugh… What now?
Oh, no.
Looks like Young Master Plum Blossom is
the only one with a different opinion.
You're undecided about number 4, right?
Yes.
You guys think couple number 4
is compatible, right?
COUPLE 4 KIM TAEWON, OH JIAE
Actually, the truth is…
- This means her birth chart is very dry.
- Okay.
When it's this dry…
"BIRTH DATES & PERPETUAL CALENDAR
WERE PROVIDED"
…just a nudge, and you get pregnant.
Oh, really?
Young Master Plum Blossom
must be flustered.
It's all because it's a team mission.
If he forces his opinion and he's wrong--
- He'll be responsible.
- Yes, that's right.
But there will be nothing to be
responsible for if they're out.
- So he has to go for it.
- Yes, he has to.
He should speak up a bit more.
Should we confirm number 4 at the well?
Okay, sounds good.
Pie's walking up.
TEAM BLACK TORTOISE
COUPLE 4 KIM TAEWON, OH JIAE
Well of Truth, please.
COUPLE 4 HAS NO CHILDREN
- No moon.
- No moon? I knew it.
We're narrowing it down well, though.
Yes. We are.
I'm glad we checked.
- And…
- That leaves us with number 2.
TEAM BLACK TORTOISE
COUPLE 2 JU SANGWON, PARK SEOHYEON
Goodness, no moon again.
COUPLE 2 HAS NO CHILDREN
- Team Tortoise is pretty lucky, though.
- How so?
All the couples they feel iffy about
have no children.
- They can just rule them out.
- Right.
- It's easier that way.
- Yes.
- Number 2's a no too.
- What?
- Number 2's a no.
- Really?
I got goosebumps.
The couples I said no to
are all childless.
You're the most accurate right now.
- Right.
- Thank goodness.
- We ruled out the wrong ones accurately.
- We did.
- That's a relief.
- It's a good thing.
Are there any couples
you're confused about?
As for me… Number 10.
This couple confused me as well.
But number 10…
One of them comes from a family
without children.
- Hmm.
- That's what my Granny spirit told me.
But I think that could be
Han Gyeongmin's family.
The husband has the birth chart
of someone who has itchy feet.
Looks like he's always out doing sports.
Right, I sense they are struggling
with something.
Ah, this is a tough one.
They're struggling.
They seem torn.
She's walking over.
Sobin's up.
I have a feeling she'll be
the troubleshooter for the team.
My teammates were very torn
about number 10.
I wanted to help my teammates,
so I pleaded with my Granny spirit.
"Help me, Granny."
"I know you're done for the day,
but can you just help me out here?"
TEAM WHITE TIGER
COUPLE 1, COUPLE 5, COUPLE 6, COUPLE 7
Numbers 1, 5, 6, 7.
We need to pick 1 more.
I think number 11 is correct.
Number 11.
COUPLE 11 HWANG SEONGYU, GWAK YUNJEONG
I'm pretty convinced about them.
They have a deep tie.
If they do have children,
I'm sure they have more than 1 child.
They can't stand watching their kid
grow up all alone and lonely.
I think she has a weak womb.
They don't have multiple children.
Number 11, Hwang Seongyu
and Gwak Yunjeong.
Do you think they're right?
I'll go take a look.
What? He just walked past number 11.
He stopped in front of number 10.
Before I even knew it,
I stopped in front of number 10.
I think it was a sign.
It's number 10.
I don't know why,
but my Granny made me stop right there.
Right.
Number 10.
No way.
I'm right.
Number 10 is right.
That's what I keep getting.
Number 10 feels like an obvious one to me.
I'm sure it's not number 10, though.
Give me a chance. Trust me on this.
I think number 10 is right.
No, I say number 11.
Seulbi kept saying number 11,
but I was dead set on number 10.
I still say number 10.
I'm getting the opposite.
Number 10 is blue, 11 is red.
NEGATION
Let's go with 11, then.
I'll feel really bad if I'm wrong.
Will you be okay?
Number 11 doesn't feel right to me.
Still, her Granny spirit said so.
Is this your Granny spirit's reading?
- That's what I felt.
- Is that so?
Then let's go with it.
- I'll write them down.
- Okay.
TEAM WHITE TIGER
COUPLES 1, 5, 6, 7, 11
The time is up.
Write down the names of the 5 couples
and leave the envelope by the well.
Show me the moon, please.
Good job. Well done.
I have no regrets.
Honestly, I think we got everything right.
Well, we did weed out the wrong ones.
We did.
My Granny says, "Well done."
1, 3, 6, 9, 10
1, 5, 6, 7, 11
3, 5, 8, 9, 10
The Battle of Synergy.
The second team match.
- Ah…
- Find the couples with multiple children.
Here comes the results.
Only 3 people will move on from here.
I have to go home if we lose here.
I was confident.
Team Azure Dragon and Team White Tiger.
You've both chosen the following couple.
Hwang Hyeonhwan and Yang Eunyeong.
- Ah, number 1.
- Number 1.
"It was hard work raising the kids."
That was the reading we got,
so we were convinced they had children.
When I looked at Hyeonhwan's fortune,
I saw money leaking.
He has many people to look after
and he's carrying a lot of a burden.
That's why we thought
they had more than 1 child.
From what I could tell,
their birth chartssay
they're destined to have kids.
Right.
Also, the husband is the kind of person
that burns hard and hot.
I saw something fiery in him.
What was hard and hot?
Well, I mean…
Fired up, how?
Right, right…
Hey, he's only 18 years old.
Yes, you know…
That's an awkward question.
Fire.
Fire…
Anyway, I saw something fiery.
I was walking around,
and my Granny spirit
made me stop before them.
So I concluded
it would be safe to bet on them.
I discussed with Seulbi and made the call.
Hwang Hyeonhwan and Yang Eunyeong.
Please reveal your family portrait.
SELECTED BY TEAM AZURE DRAGON
AND TEAM WHITE TIGER
- The photo holds the answer.
- The family portrait.
Hey, hey.
COUPLE 1 HAS MULTIPLE CHILDREN
They have multiple children.
They have 5 children.
MARRIED 11 YEARS WITH 5 CHILDREN
TEAM AZURE DRAGON, 1 POINT
TEAM WHITE TIGER, 1 POINT
TEAM BLACK TORTOISE, 0 POINTS
Number 1 was right.
They were right. What a pity.
My gosh.
We were torn to the very end
about number 1.
Yeah, we thought about picking number 1.
My goodness.
He's clearly a very energetic man.
My gosh. What a passionate couple.
They have this love-hate chemistry.
They drive each other mad,
wanting to smack each other sometimes.
But all that fighting builds affection.
That's why they get along as a couple.
What came to mind was,
"They're staying together for the kids."
I see.
We did fight a lot.
We had a lot of fights.
But once the kids came, we grew calmer,
and things got better between us.
We're happily married now.
Wow.
Children sure are important, huh?
They change your temperament
and turn your life around.
That's true.
They need kids to stop fighting.
Did you get your fortune read
before getting married?
Yes, they said
my husband would hold me back.
Oh, no…
-You married him despite that?
-Yes.
-That's how much you loved him.
I was sure
there's no way he'd get in my way.
I have a question.
If that's what the fortune-teller said,
what was it about him
that you fell for when you first met?
He was a bodyguard then.
Seeing him in a suit…
He was the most handsome guy
I'd laid my eyes on.
- A man really shines in a suit.
- Gosh.
You initially planned to have 6 children?
Ms. Yang,
are you willing to have more kids?
If we could have a girl,
I'll think about it.
Oh, that's amazing.
It's impressive.
Fate Readers,
do you think you can you sense
the sex of their next child?
- Young Master Jiseon?
- Oh, go on.
You're not destined to have a girl.
Oh!
-He put his foot down.
-He's so cold about it.
Then you're not interested, right?
That's right.
- Right.
- I see. Very well.
Now then, Teams Azure Dragon
and White Tiger are tied at 1 point each.
Team Black Tortoise still has 0 points.
DRAGON 1, TIGER 1, TORTOISE 0
Now we need them to get something wrong.
Team Black Tortoise and Team White Tiger
have chosen the following couple.
Jeong Gihwan and Choi Bogyeong.
- Number 5.
- Ah.
COUPLE 5 WAS SELECTED
We didn't choose them.
I feel good about this.
This is Team White Tiger's second pick,
but a first for Team Black Tortoise.
I went up to them to check.
The wife's birth chart
shows that she is like
- a fence that protects husband
-Oh, a fence.
while the husband
is destined to keep losing things.
So, he's destined to go through
the ups and downs
within the fence, the wife.
And what I sensed most strongly was
that the core of their compatibility
is their kids.
So I told that to my teammates
to convince them.
Do you yawn
when you feel something like that?
I saw you keep yawning.
It's called a "haam"
in the Jeolla Province.
When I feel or am possessed by a deity,
I yawn as I hear
what they have to tell me.
- I yawn a lot.
- I see.
He did yawn a lot.
What about you,
Team White Tiger?
I insisted on this answer.
I am certain.
You're certain about number 5?
I'm 100% sure they have multiple children.
Young Master Jiseon,
is this the couple you're most sure about?
Yes, that's right.
We need this to be wrong.
Ugh, what do I do?
Here is the answer.
SELECTED BY TEAM WHITE TIGER
AND TEAM BLACK TORTOISE
Jeong Gihwan and Choi Bogyeong
have multiple children.
MARRIED 22 YEARS WITH 8 CHILDREN
Whoa!
TEAM WHITE TIGER, 2 POINTS
This is the couple
Young Master Jiseon was most sure about.
That was a good choice.
We'll go through.
-We all chose number 5.
-We did.
Hello. We've been married for 22 years,
and we have 8 kids,
including 2 sets of twins.
- First, we had twin girls.
- Oh, my word.
Then we had 3 sons in a row.
- Then we had twin girls.
- Twins again?
And then our youngest boy.
Wow.
They have 8 children.
Well, they're full of energy.
Team Azure Dragon
didn't get that one,
so they're still on 1 point.
Team White Tiger, 2 points.
Team Black Tortoise, 1 point.
The current score is 1, 2, and 1.
Azure Dragon almost had it.
That team got it wrong once.
And White Tiger got 2 right so far.
We need them to get 1 wrong.
Team Azure Dragon.
TEAM AZURE DRAGON
And Team White Tiger.
White Tiger keeps trying.
TEAM WHITE TIGER
You have chosen the following couple.
Lee Seungheon and Kim Mijeong.
COUPLE 6 WAS SELECTED
Team White Tiger.
This is your third try in a row.
Why did you pick this couple?
I sensed he wouldn't work
- if he didn't have kids.
- Hmm.
- The husband? Oh.
- Yes.
The kids make him work
under the blazing sun.
That's what I saw, so I chose him.
I also thought things would be better now
because the kids are older now.
DRAGON 1, TIGER 2, TORTOISE 1
Please, I hope it's wrong.
If we get this right…
We advance if it's right.
Lee Seungheon and Kim Mijeong.
Please reveal your family portrait.
Oh, okay!
MARRIED 15 YEARS WITH 9 CHILDREN
Team White Tiger, you're incredible.
Whoa!
Yes!
TEAM WHITE TIGER, 3 POINTS
-Yay!
-Whoa, whoa, yeah!
Lee Seungheon and Kim Mijeong
have 4 boys and 5 girls.
They have a total of 9 children.
- Nine kids.
- That's amazing.
She said you worked under the blazing sun.
May I ask what you guys do for a living?
Right now,
- we're farmers.
- Oh!
So they do work out in the sun.
She was right.
I found something interesting
in the Book of Fate.
It says that the husband had a vasectomy
after the fifth child was born,
but you have 9 children.
Can you explain how this happened?
Oh, my.
The husband has a serious fertility issue.
- Oh.
- That's what the cards say.
There's no movement.
I'm sensing some kind of surgery.
- That surgery could be a vasectomy.
- Yes.
After our fifth child was born,
we decided to stop having more kids,
so I got a vasectomy.
About 8 months later,
- she got pregnant again.
- Oh, my.
Is that even possible?
I heard that can happen,
but at first, you must've suspected her
because you'd had a vasectomy.
Well, I was dumbfounded.
I thought she got pregnant without me.
I was so taken aback.
"She got pregnant without me."
It says here that sometimes
the sperm find another pathway.
Yes. Mine found a highway.
- That's some serious vitality.
- You could call that a blessing.
It must've been a tough decision.
-They're amazing.
-Impressive.
-We got 3 right?
-Yes.
How did they get that?
We have 1, 2, 3 points each, right?
One, two, three.
DRAGON 2, TIGER 3, TORTOISE 1
We must try to get 3 points.
Yeah, we must.
I can't believe I made a mistake.
Team Azure Dragon
and Team Black Tortoise
have chosen the following couple.
Kim Hyeongu and Yeo Eungyeong.
Azure Dragon and Black Tortoise.
White Tiger didn't pick them.
We ruled out this couple.
I hope it's wrong.
I got a Sparrow card and a Birds card,
so I assumed they'd have lots of kids,
like sparrows do.
BIRDS
I'd carefully say it could've been
a one-shot, one-kill scenario.
With that in mind,
we chose number 9.
One-shot, one-kill.
- Your cards told you that?
- Yes.
What exactly did you get?
The Seven of Wands card
has sticks in the ground facing upward.
That means his sperm…
Oh.
- I think we get the picture.
- Okay.
He's very active and his energy…
- He's got that stamina.
- Ah.
Insane stamina.
Yes, insane stamina.
So the card represented "insane stamina."
Let's see the result.
Every team but White Tiger chose them.
SELECTED BY TEAM AZURE DRAGON
AND TEAM BLACK TORTOISE
Kim Hyeongu and Yeo Eungyeong.
Please reveal your family portrait.
You got it right!
Oh, that's really impressive.
TEAM BLACK TORTOISE, 2 POINTS
-I'm welling up.
-Well done.
I knew it. One-shot, one-kill.
TEAM AZURE DRAGON, 3 POINTS
TEAM WHITE TIGER, 3 POINTS
We should've chosen them.
The scores are 3, 3, and 2.
Team Azure Dragon's in the lead now.
Kim Hyeongu and Yeo Eungyeong
have 1 boy and 6 girls.
They have a total of 7 children.
That's incredible.
So, were all 7 kids
conceived on the first try?
You got that in the cards?
The dad is impressive, for sure.
His sperm must be potent.
And you're willing to have more kids?
Yes, but only if
the eighth is a boy for sure.
We're willing to try again, then.
-You want a boy?
-Yes, so that our boy doesn't feel lonely.
- Ah.
- You mean your son?
I do sense a son.
I'm the youngest of 7 kids and a shaman.
-Are you?
-As the youngest of a big family,
I think…
- I see a chili pepper, a boy.
- Oh, yay!
I see a chili pepper, a boy.
You see a chili pepper?
Our ancestors used to hang ropes
with chili peppers when a boy was born.
I keep seeing that for you.
- I think a boy will come next.
- He's right.
We should ask Team Azure Dragon too.
A few words from you
- could change the fate of this family.
- Yes.
As soon as I heard her story,
I felt the energy of a son.
You'll have a boy.
What, really?
It looks like they're ready
to go for it tonight.
- Another one-shot, one-kill?
- Yes.
Yes, that's possible.
Congratulations.
Oh, gee.
-What kind of conversation is this?
-My gosh.
Oh, my goodness.
Very well.
Team White Tiger didn't get this one,
so the score currently stands
at 3, 3, and 2.
DRAGON 3, TIGER 3, TORTOISE 2
They caught up fast.
It's neck-and-neck.
WHICH FINAL COUPLE IS THE ONE
WITH MANY CHILDREN?
Let us reveal the last couple.
The last couple
that the Fate Readers chose
as a couple with multiple children.
Team Black Tortoise.
TEAM BLACK TORTOISE
And Team Azure Dragon.
TEAM AZURE DRAGON
These 2 teams chose
Han Gyeongmin and Park Jiyeon.
COUPLE 10 WAS SELECTED
Team White Tiger
chose the following couple.
Hwang Seongyu and Gwak Yunjeong.
COUPLE 11 WAS SELECTED
Only Team White Tiger chose
Hwang Seongyu and Gwak Yunjeong.
If this couple is the right answer,
Team White Tiger
advances to the next round.
If number 10 is the right answer,
Team Azure Dragon
advances to the next round.
This is the moment of truth.
Team White Tiger,
why did you pick this couple?
We talked about this for a long time.
Seulbi chose number 11,
and I chose number 10.
We almost went head-to-head,
but I wanted to trust her once more.
So I went with her answer.
Okay. Team Azure Dragon.
It's the only couple my Granny picked
before she clocked out.
- Gosh.
- What a relief.
I pleaded with my Granny spirit.
"I know you're done for the day,
but can you just help me out here?"
My desperation must've reached her.
She gave me a message.
Couple number 10.
My body trembled when I stood before them.
I felt a really intense energy
and I got a jigi too,
which was my body trembling.
We're in trouble.
I looked at the husband,
and I saw him happily wondering,
"Should I make a soccer team?"
"Should I make a girl band?"
That's what he thought as he had kids.
Then I looked at the wife,
and I saw a bunch of grapes.
So I figured they'd have a lot of kids.
They could be wrong.
Let's find out the result.
Han Gyeongmin and Park Jiyeon.
Hwang Seongyu and Gwak Yunjeong.
Please reveal your family portraits.
Let's see.
COUPLE 10, MULTIPLE CHILDREN
COUPLE 11, CHILDLESS
This is the couple with many children.
MARRIED 19 YEARS WITH 7 CHILDREN
CHOI HANNAH, SEOLHWA, LEE SOBIN SURVIVE
This is the couple with many children.
Thank you.
Han Gyeongmin and Park Jiyeon
have multiple children.
I'm sorry.
Han Gyeongmin and Park Jiyeon
have multiple children.
Young Master Jiseon must be so upset.
I'm so sorry.
Let's call it even.
-It's okay.
-Don't cry. I'm sorry.
We're from Gurye, Jeollanam-do.
We've been happily married for 19 years
with 3 boys and 4 girls.
-I'm Han Gyeongmin.
-I'm Park Jiyeon.
Oh. We've been filming
for almost 2 hours now.
They've been holding hands the whole time.
They're the only ones who did.
For 2 whole hours.
When my wife feels
uncomfortable or has indigestion,
she says it helps if I massage the spot
between her thumb and index finger.
I've been massaging that spot every day
since she had our first child.
How sweet.
And you've been married for 19 years?
He's so sweet.
The final score is 4, 3, and 3.
Team Azure Dragon advances.
Congratulations.
It really was a battle of synergy.
The teams that had good teamwork advanced.
-Yes.
-Right.
Good job.
I prayed damn hard before this.
She said, "Damn hard."
- I fell ill too.
- Oh, dear.
But my Granny spirit told me
to take the lead.
That's what I did.
She carried her team.
Before the first match,
we held hands to lift our spirits
and said, "Let's make it through
after the second round."
- Let's pray.
Let's give it our all in round 2.
The second one.
Yes. What they said
in the beginning was right.
Yeah, right.
I think fate brought us all together.
I survived
because I was with a great team.
It felt better than winning alone.
The survivors of the Battle of Synergy are
Yoon Daeman, Monad,
Manshin Kwon Sujin,
Seolhwa, Choi Hannah,
Lee Sobin.
Six people in total.
The top 6.
I'm so excited about this round.
Battle of Fates.
Let me introduce the 6 Fate Readers
that made it to the fourth round.
The first survivor.
The sharp-tongued, no-nonsense shaman.
Seolhwa.
She looks like a Heavenly Fairy.
She's straightforward.
She says what she sees and feels.
She speaks freely, no filter.
The schizophrenia's long gone.
Bring her to me. She'll listen to a woman.
I was so impressed.
She's eloquent, doesn't hesitate,
and is very confident.
Let's win this, no matter what.
The second survivor.
A shaman with 20 years of experience
who consoles your hearts
with profound readings.
Lee Sobin.
She looks extra charismatic today.
She's very charismatic
when she's reading fortunes.
Her aura is extraordinary, for sure.
I've come this far,
so let me win this thing.
She has this fierce energy.
The third survivor.
- Ooh.
- A staff?
A tarot master with unparalleled charisma.
Monad.
MONAD
8-YEAR TAROT MASTER
Her tarot reading skill is remarkable.
Tarot masters are no easy mark too.
Homeless people have no homes.
For number 4,
the card suggests they're without a home.
I came here to win.
I'll show you what East Asian tarot
is capable of today.
The fourth survivor.
Pansori
singer with spiritual powers.
Five-year singer-shaman.
Yoon Daeman.
YOON DAEMAN
5-YEAR SHAMAN
His readings are quite impactful.
There are thieves and rats
with big eyes and big feet.
All sorts of thieves and rats.
He tells fortunes as if he's singing,
and that itself is very intimidating.
I'll show you
the skills I've honed over the years.
The fifth survivor.
A Gen Z shaman with 26 years of experience
that was born to be a shaman.
Manshin Kwon Sujin.
She's warm and gentle,
but she has that firmness
that comes from experience.
This person had to live
away from home since he was young.
Cash rolling around in his palms.
Manshins have the skills
that befit their experience.
I've got this far,
so I'm determined to win.
The sixth survivor.
The tarot master
who reads fates with spiritual power.
Choi Hannah.
She's a spiritual tarot card master.
She's basically a shaman.
The wife's cards show fire,
so she gets pregnant easily.
A one-shot, one-kill situation.
I'm positive.
I'm sure I can beat everyone and move up.
I'm confident.
Today's competition
will be a fun one to watch.
Battle of Fates.
The fourth round is…
…the Battle of Gods.
With the power of the spirits and deities,
we hope to look into a person's fate.
In the Battle of Gods,
2 Fate Readers
will go head-to-head
to read 1 person's fortune.
- A 1-on-1 face-off?
- Whoa…
This is the most fun.
Two people reading together?
Reading 1 person at the same time
felt like good fun.
I'm pretty confident at reading fortunes.
I did think I'd survive,
regardless of who I go up against.
Three well-known public figures
joined Battle of Fates
to seek advice
on tricky questions
about their personal lives.
BORN ON SEPTEMBER 28, 1985, MALE
BORN ON MAY 11, 1965, FEMALE
BORN ON JULY 3, 1983, FEMALE
The 3 people have selected
2 Fate Readers they wish to seek
a fate reading from.
Oh…
Born in 1985.
May 11, 1965.
July 3, 1983.
After the Battle of Gods…
…only 3 people will survive.
Another half goes home.
All I want is to win.
I trust my Granny spirit.
I must trust my deities
and charge forward.
Let's just do my best.
I'll show you
what real spiritual tarot is.
I'm confident I won't lose.
The Battle of Gods.
Let the match begin.
I'm curious.
This is the first person for you to read.
Please enter.
A man born in 1985.
- A famous person born in 1985…
- Someone famous?
We must all know him.
Someone's here? Oh, he's coming out.
- Whoa.
- How cool.
- It's so bright.
- Where is he?
- Gosh.
- Someone's coming.
- Huh? Hang on.
- Who is it?
What?
- Huh? Hang on.
- Who is it?
It's you, Shindong?
- Huh? Huh?
- What's this?
What are you doing down there?
Hello. I'm Shindong.
LONG-RUNNING LEGENDS OF K-POP
SUPER JUNIOR,
THE ROLE MODEL OF K-POP IDOLS
THE FIRST FATE TO READ
SHINDONG
- No way.
- Is this for real?
What… Why is he coming out of there?
Why is he down here?
- Didn't he say he had a gig?
- You said you had…
You had personal business.
-Another gig.
-He said he'd be abroad.
It wouldn't be fun if you knew,
and I thought the Fate Readers
should be clueless
in order to give me a reading properly.
I'm sorry, but I lied.
You all know.
Anyone up there knows the feeling.
You want to be down here.
- We said that a hundred times.
- I'd love to.
Yes, I'm jealous.
I want those 2 people to read my fortune.
It must be fun. I want to be down there.
-I'm really curious.
-Same.
I really want to give it a go.
I want to look from up close.
I'd try to guess
if I didn't know the answer.
This is insane.
I wanted to have my fortune read,
so today, I came down here myself.
But that's not the only reason.
You have an actual question, right?
Yes. Being a celebrity
means you're bound to be
anxious about the future.
I know what happened in my past,
but I really want to know
what lies ahead of me.
I'm getting older now too,
- and I'm curious about marriage.
- Oh, dear.
I love children,
so I wonder how many I'll have.
I believe you chose
2 Fate Readers, Shindong.
-Is that true?
-Yes. I've chosen 2 Fate Readers.
The first fate for you to read
is Shindong's fate.
He chose the following Fate Readers.
Seolhwa.
SEOLHWA
4-YEAR SHAMAN
And
Choi Hannah.
CHOI HANNAH
3-YEAR TAROT MASTER
Oh…
Why Hannah?
Sobin, Hannah, and I
had become allies before we even knew it.
But now we've become opponents.
It didn't feel nice, to be honest.
Ah, I found it so cruel.
This is fate. We're fated.
We helped and rooted for
each other during the third round,
and now we must go head-to-head.
Ah, what twist of fate is this?
- Yesterday's comrades…
- Yes. It can't be helped.
We can have only 1 winner.
Seolhwa will give a reading first.
Seolhwa first.
To avoid being influenced
by Seolhwa's reading,
Hannah, please put on the headset.
They're making sure she doesn't hear
Seolhwa's reading.
Ah, so she can't hear the other reading.
THE FATE READER ON STANDBY
WEARS A HEADSET TO AVOID LISTENING IN
How interesting.
The final round is coming up.
I should win no matter what.
Let's not feel intimidated.
Seolhwa, please begin your reading.
Your real name, please.
My real name is Shin Donghee.
I feel nervous now.
Granny, Grandpa, this is Shindong.
His real name is Shin Donghee.
He was born in 1985, the Year of the Ox.
Help me relay the right message
without my human thoughts.
From 1 to 2, from 2 to 3.
You say you want to marry
and want to meet women,
but no one's up to your standards.
Hmm…
I think you're only saying
that you want to date and marry.
You don't trust women.
You need a younger woman who's mature.
Even a 12-year age gap is fine.
- Is that okay?
- Yes.
He said, "Is that okay?"
- He can't hide his joy.
- He seems so happy.
- He seems over the moon.
- So happy.
An age gap of 12 to 15 years is fine.
- Oh.
- But…
But you can't stand
younger girls that act like a baby.
And you can't stand a housewife
who doesn't work.
You're better off with someone active
that manages and maintains her own life
and brings in an income together.
I'm so surprised right now.
I thought she was talking about my ex.
She hit the nail on the head.
She got everything right,
from the age. Everything.
I don't know who your ex is,
but you almost married her, right?
You almost got married,
but it looks like the timing was off.
- She's right.
- Yes.
- That's true.
- She's right. For real.
You guys know about it.
You know.
-I know.
-I know too.
Oh…
You almost married her.
Your ancestors were in agreement.
- Yes.
- You could've had a baby too,
but you broke up
because something didn't go right.
You said your grandmother is a shaman.
-Which side of the family?
-My paternal grandmother.
When she passes away…
It might be dangerous for you.
What does that mean?
Someone's trying to make you hold bells.
Bells?
Someone wants you to become a shaman.
- Oh, no.
- Gosh.
- To become a shaman?
- He'll get the calling.
- I got goosebumps.
- Oh, dear…
You must be careful.
I'm not saying you'll become a shaman,
but it runs in your family.
You're bound to feel the pain.
You have powerful ancestors,
and there's a shaman in the family,
and you have shaman ancestors too.
And 1 of the shaman ancestors
will touch you.
He definitely has that shamanic gift.
I can't say who,
but he told a girl group member
to be careful as he felt something,
- and a scandal broke out.
- Yes.
He does have that spiritual power.
Because you have
the tendencies of a shaman,
you sing and dance in public
to stave some of it off
and it's true that it's helping somewhat.
But…
The way I see it,
it's nowhere near enough.
Your luck in business opens up this year.
2025, AGED 40, GOT AN OFFER
TO START A BUSINESS
Oh…
My gosh.
I sense a lot of money leaving your hands.
The door's open,
but you should hold back for now.
You're losing a lot of money this year.
You're not meant to be the cook.
-Right.
-You give orders as the owner
-and ask people to do the rest.
-That's right.
But you're blessed to have a lot of food.
Ah…
That's true.
You'd hit it big
if you start a food-related business.
I've considered it for a long time.
And I recently got a good offer
and might go for it.
2025, AGED 40, PREPARING
TO START A F&B BUSINESS
I'm supposed to be a host,
but I'm just sitting here watching.
Seolhwa…
You know I go to see a lot of shamans.
I like her style.
-She just gives it to you straight.
-Very straightforward.
Build a foundation and start in 2028.
You will see actual changes
in 2028 for sure.
- In 2028.
- Yes.
And then…
In your family…
Neurological problems, brain issues,
and dementia.
Who has that?
And dementia. Who has that?
- My grandfather.
- Your grandfather? Huh?
Oh? Whoa.
- That info's not in here.
- No.
She's mentioning
so many things that are not here.
I'm not saying that you have
all of the health problems he has,
but there is a chance you might.
You shouldn't overwork yourself,
but rest is not written in your stars.
- You're never satisfied.
- Yes. That's true.
Yes. I know how hard he works.
He's very ambitious,
so he's never satisfied.
Your mom's life is pretty comfortable now,
so why's she so obsessed with money?
2015, AGED 30,
HIS MOTHER LOST ALL THEIR SAVINGS
That is mentioned here.
Your mom is always worried about
how to keep the family afloat.
- And that demoralizes your dad.
- Yes.
And because he's demoralized,
your mom's likely to take over
as the boss of the family.
To tell you the truth,
I cut contact with both my parents.
Oh, really?
Oh, dear.
And the reason was financial issues.
We had problems because of money.
So my mom was… Well…
Whenever I give her money,
she'd ask me for a big sum
instead of a monthly allowance.
She said she'd do something
with that money
so that I wouldn't worry about her.
She always asked me
for a big amount of money.
But when I did give her a large sum,
she ended up getting scammed.
And she's even made a bad investment
and lost all of the money.
-That's why you want a family of your own.
-Yes.
Yes. I think I feel lonely
around my own family.
So I often said on TV
that I wanted to get married,
and I almost got married too.
That's because I've always wanted
to get married since I was young.
I guess I thought getting married
would bring me happiness.
He's said that a lot.
He wants children too.
- Let me see if there's anything else.
- Okay. You're so good.
This is so much fun, guys.
- I'm so jealous.
- Hey.
You'll have nothing to ask Hannah, though.
Right.
The last thing my Granny spirit said is…
I don't know why,
but I've been feeling emotional
from the start.
We're similar people, basically.
I also used to be a dancer,
and I'm estranged from my parents.
I am in touch with them, but…
We have a lot in common.
- I think you chose me for a reason.
- You're right.
My gosh.
Through this show,
you got to know all the Fate Readers.
Don't come as a client. Come for a chat.
Just call us up and say,
"Hey, this happened today."
Since you know my situation
and can relate to it,
so I think talking to you would
put me at ease.
What…
Here's my number.
Gee, that sly…
Now we see what your plan was.
Seolhwa's reading is over.
That was so much fun. Are you jealous?
So jealous.
Hmm. Let's not get swayed.
I'll just do my thing.
The role of a tarot master or shaman
is to objectively share
what they feel and see
without letting their emotions
get the better of them.
So I told myself to pull myself together.
"Don't waver."
I tried not to be swayed.
A tarot master with prayer beads…
I serve Buddha, so I always wear
a necklace with 108 prayer beads
whenever I give a reading.
Choi Hannah, please begin your reading.
Here we go. She's started.
Tarot reading. Let's go.
Here we go.
She's using a different deck.
There are many kinds of cards.
Sometimes, I keep getting the same card.
And using just 1 deck can really limit
the range of my interpretation.
- Uh… I'll be blunt. Is that okay?
- Of course, it's okay.
Off to a great start.
Great. Let's go!
When I picked out cards
for your acquired character,
I got The High Priestess card.
You've always had a good hunch
since you were a kid.
And your spiritual energy made me feel
that you and I might be similar people.
When you meet someone,
you can tell what that person is like,
but you also use
your spiritual sense to tell such things.
He can really see things accurately.
He can tell at a glance
if a K-Pop idol group will make it or not.
He can tell?
- When he sees the rookies.
- For real?
- But because you do that,
-Yes.
you end up overlooking people's faults.
- Mmm.
- Ah…
That's why you feel very lonely inside.
The blues or sentimental thoughts
can take over.
That's what I'm getting from the cards.
Oh…
How's your stomach?
Are you okay?
I have heartburn every day.
-It's killing me.
-Right?
I asked because I felt it all of a sudden.
Do you have acid burps?
- Yes.
- Acid burps.
I had a hard time with acid reflux.
Yes, it's possible
you suffer from acid burps.
Shamans call that "jigi."
I felt a sharp pain in my stomach
and I had acid burps.
I knew I was feeling his pain.
He has stomach issues.
You have serious acid reflux.
He'd complain about nausea too.
I also see so much sorrow in you.
But even if people try to console you,
it doesn't really help you feel better.
You're right.
It doesn't quite help you.
- It doesn't resonate with me at all.
- Mmm.
You believe that people don't change.
You think no one can change.
That's what I always say.
You strongly believe
that people don't change
and you can't fix people for the better.
That's spot-on.
You want to date and get married,
but you don't trust women.
- Seolhwa said the same thing.
- She said it too.
Both said he can't trust women.
You don't trust women.
Trust women first--
then talk about marriage.
He doesn't trust women.
It's because he's been hurt by people.
- Look at this card here.
- Okay.
The man's asleep
and the woman's up, doubting him.
- She can't go to sleep.
- Ah…
I'm having bad flashbacks.
But I do think
things will get better for you.
Let me see when that will be.
- When I'll get married?
- Yes.
Oh…
She's a love expert.
-A dating expert?
-Yes. She nailed it the other time too.
- She said that's her expertise.
- Right?
Hmm.
Your luck with marriage…
You will marry later in life.
When?
A woman will enter your life
when you're 43.
You'll consider marrying her.
Oh, you will have a serious relationship.
But I don't see this relationship
leading to a marriage.
No marriage?
Another breakup? Oh, dear.
- If you miss this opportunity…
- What if I do?
Then your next chance to marry
will be when you're 46 years old.
We got the peach tree branch,
so you'll be very compatible with her.
Sparks will fly, and things will
finally start to settle down.
Everything will come to an end,
and there will be a new beginning.
Can you tell the age and occupation
of the woman I'll meet when I'm 46?
- Of course I can. Let me see.
- For real?
- You can get the age and job?
- He wants to know her age.
It's so detailed. That's interesting.
-The cards tell you that too?
-Of course.
That's amazing.
Tarot's great.
She's a businesswoman.
- She runs a business?
- Yes.
- She's a businesswoman.
- Oh…
I got the King of Pentacles,
the king of money.
SIGNIFIES FINANCIAL STABILITY, BUSINESS
I sense this woman could even offer you
some sort of financial support to you.
-She's a bit younger than you.
-She's younger?
- My gosh.
- Wow…
Seolhwa said that too.
You need a younger woman who's mature.
Even a 12-year age gap is fine.
They're saying a lot of the same things.
Lastly, what kind of business should I do?
-Let me see.
-What field should I get into?
The time is up.
Oh, I still had a question.
It feels like time went by faster.
I know.
That was so much fun.
Seolhwa and Choi Hannah's
individual readings are over.
For the next 10 minutes,
the 2 Fate Readers
will read his fortune simultaneously.
THE FATE READERS READ SIMULTANEOUSLY
Huh?
They must read at the same time?
In front of all the other Fate Readers?
That's a bit ridiculous.
- It's a simultaneous reading.
- Oh.
- They're answering 1 question?
- Yes.
That's a bit cruel.
To be honest…
I was confident.
I'm bad at interrupting. What should I do?
I was afraid.
Shindong, please share your concern.
One of my biggest concerns is
something I've been thinking about
a lot recently.
I'm starting to wonder
if being a celebrity
is the right job for me long-term.
- It is.
- I'm unsure.
But as a member of SUPER JUNIOR,
now that I'm physically getting older,
- it's getting harder.
- Yes.
So I'm wondering how much longer
I could keep doing this.
Do it every now and then.
If there's a SUPER JUNIOR
10, 15, 20-year anniversary,
do that every now and then.
Even if I don't do it regularly,
- Yeah.
- I shouldn't drop it completely?
Yes. Your golden age is long over.
She's blunt.
Those times are long gone.
You will continue to be on TV.
But when it comes to singing and dancing,
you can do that on shows
for singers from back in the day,
every now and then.
-A trip down memory lane.
-Like Sugar Man.
It's fun to watch over a meal.
You're still business partners
and the SUPER JUNIOR members are around,
but you should cultivate
a career path of your own
- while continuing to be on TV.
- Right.
I can do just that,
but the problem is,
I want to continue what I've been doing.
You can keep going.
The energy that lets you continue
is currently a bit stagnant.
Hannah managed to interrupt me.
I was surprised, to be honest.
- She butted in pretty well.
- I know.
Just like that.
- She completely took over.
- Yes.
-You're meant to be in the public eye.
-Yes.
But you must do something else
to refresh your energy.
You must try getting into other fields
and you should learn to let go
when you have to.
You can't completely give up
your career as a singer.
If you do, when you watch TV,
you'll feel this helpless yearning,
and that could churn you up.
-You mentioned my members.
-Yes.
Out of the SUPER JUNIOR guys,
can you tell me who I can trust the most?
Oh! He can't even trust them?
He's seriously asking that to them?
- I just had a brief look.
- Okay.
As for your relationship with the members,
you seem to keep
a certain distance from them.
- Me?
- It's all business to you.
Wow, I just got the chills.
That's what I always tell the guys,
half joking, half serious.
"This is a business-based relationship."
"And that's how we'll last longer."
"We must have boundaries."
I say that often.
- That's true. You need boundaries.
- You do.
It's true. That's wise.
Hmm.
You see Heechul sometimes for work,
so you both stay in touch,
but once you think he
no longer has business ties with you,
you might distance yourself from him.
That's spot-on.
I might not have liked Heechul much
if he weren't popular.
You nailed it.
- My goodness.
- You nailed it.
- My gosh.
- Oh, dear.
This will cause quite a stir.
This is amazing.
Can I ask 1 last thing?
I was told I'd get divorced
if I got married before I turned 48.
Am I likely to get divorced?
Well, why am I getting this?
Forget this is for TV. I'll just say it.
The women you meet before you turn 48
all have insane temperaments.
Oh.
Your ex had the birth chart
of a celebrity, like us.
She is fated to sing and dance as well.
Your personalities were similar,
but that's also why you clashed.
So breaking up with her
was like a divorce of sorts.
- Ah. I see.
- Yeah.
That's true. That's very right.
But in your case, Shindong,
your acquired character
could make you consider divorce.
I got The Devil card
when I checked your love life.
Oh.
You must watch the timing
and act wisely, or you could get divorced.
If not divorce, it could be separation.
You have to focus on the person
who's with you in 2028.
Even if you meet someone before then,
she might not be the one.
If you were to marry the woman
you meet before 2028,
nothing will actually come of it.
It sounds like the woman
we talked about earlier.
-In 2028.
-Yes, the woman you'll meet in 2 years.
You said 2028? Yes, I felt someone
entering your life then.
-How are you both saying the same thing?
-Maybe that's when your Great Luck shifts.
The time is up.
- Ah!
- That was a taster.
Ugh, I wanted to hear more.
You got 2028 with the tarot cards?
- Yeah.
- That's interesting.
The Battle of Gods.
The first match is over.
Shindong and the Fate Reapers.
Between Seolhwa and Choi Hannah,
choose the survivor.
How am I supposed to choose?
This is hard.
They both did so well.
This is a real tough one.
They're quite similar yet very different.
- Yes, that's true. Totally.
- Totally.
Shindong, you need to consider
-whose reading resonated with you more.
-Yes.
-We have your Book of Fate,
and we heard the readings too,
so we'll make our decisions.
One was sharper, and one was more vague.
One touched on everything,
while the other focused
more on love and relationships.
We should pick the person
who mentioned more things we didn't know.
The person who said stuff
that wasn't in the Book of Fate.
-The one who mentioned more of those.
-Yes.
The person who said things
he never mentioned on TV.
- Who is that?
- I can't tell you that.
This is hard. What should I do?
The Battle of Gods.
Here comes the result
of the first match.
This is the last round before the finals.
I want to win, to be honest.
I'm confident.
I'll be the winner today.
Let us reveal Shindong's choice.
I'm curious.
Who is it?
CHOI HANNAH
"Oh, I guess I did a pretty good job."
I was so happy.
I lost.
I thought, "Oh, I lost."
And now, the Fate Reapers' choice.
SEOLHWA
Huh?
A tie?
That's unexpected.
The Battle of Gods.
The first survivor is…
For real?
Translated by Jennifer Jean Lim