The first survivor is…
Noh Seulbi.
NOH SEULBI SURVIVES
Congratulations.
- Whoa.
- Wow.
She's so Gen Z.
She's a real Gen Z.
The late Ko Miyeong
was a sports climber-turned-mountaineer.
On July 11, 2009,
on the way down
after successfully scaling Nanga Parbat
in the Himalayas,
she fell to her death off a cliff.
Mmm…
She lost
her footing and died.
I knew it. That's why I said
she fell to her death.
I know. I want to show them.
"Fell while mountain climbing."
FELL WHILE MOUNTAIN CLIMBING
I got everything right.
I wrote it all down.
"She fell off a mountain cliff."
I wrote
that she fell from a height.
My neck went stiff,
and I couldn't move it.
She probably broke her neck.
FELL AND INJURED HER HEAD
We unanimously chose Noh Seulbi.
This person passed away in the Himalayas.
From your very first words, you completely
captivated us Fate Reapers.
"It's cold and dark."
Then you said she went missing.
You also said she was away from home.
Everything you said made us think
you saw exactly what happened that day.
You got everything accurately.
Now, you asked,
"Are you sure that's when she died?"
Can I ask what you meant by that?
I didn't think that date was right.
Maybe they found her later on,
or that's just when they think she died.
Her body was recovered
after she died, with the help
of other climbers and a helicopter.
Ah…
The date is just an estimate.
Well, that's not when she died.
This is insane.
She's tough. Really tough.
When I first walked
into the hall and looked around,
she had the strongest aura.
She's really something else.
That shaman named Seulbi.
She's spiritually powerful and confident.
She doesn't seem to hesitate.
I thought she was impressive.
She was incredibly accurate.
As a fellow shaman,
I have to give her credit.
Getting all those details right
in such a short time
made me think she was the best there is.
Fate Reader Noh Seulbi survived.
Impressive.
She's so cool.
As soon as she got
the first one right, she got up and left.
It was so badass.
I thought her
intuition was so powerful,
and I wanted to be next.
She did get it first,
so I guess she's pretty good.
But it's not over until it's over.
We'll see at the end.
This is hard.
- It's not easy.
- It's hard.
I need to focus harder.
Here is the next question.
It's a man.
KIM CHEOLHONG
DIED ON MARCH 4, 2001
- Another deceased person.
- He's passed away.
Another dead person?
I specialize in reading through spirits,
so I'm confident
when it comes to reading the dead.
Calling and communicating with spirits
is something I'm pretty good at.
I decided to go with what I see and feel.
"This is my second chance."
The fate for you to read
is the deceased's cause of death.
Please begin your reading now.
SAGE CHEONMYEONG
10-MONTH SHAMAN
I'm sorry to ask this of you,
Granny, Grandpa.
The name is Kim Cheolhong.
Kim Cheolhong,
born in the lunar September of 1964.
Show me the cause of death.
He was born
in the Year of the Azure Dragon.
HONG YULJAE
6-YEAR SHAMAN
Show me what happened
at the time of his death,
as if I were there to witness it.
DOEYU
7-YEAR SHAMAN
Someone's whistling.
Whistling?
I don't ring bells.
I whistled to call on my deities
and ask them
to show me his cause of death.
I usually keep my shrine very quiet
when I do a reading.
I've never met this many shamans before,
but I've also never heard this many bells
ringing at the same time.
Everyone was ringing their bells,
and it was driving me crazy.
I had to focus on my whistling,
so I covered my ears while reading.
I hear whistles from all sides.
Ugh, it's giving me the chills.
Young Master Seo is whistling.
YOUNG MASTER SEO
5-YEAR SHAMAN
Young Master Seo
looks really confident.
Mmm.
I serve my deities in Osan,
Gyeonggi-do.
I go by Young Master Seo
of Cheonshin Shrine.
I used to teach children taekwondo…
…until I was told
I was destined to become a shaman.
So I accepted it
and began serving right away.
Actually, both my mom's and dad's
sides of the family have had shamans
for 3 generations.
So I was confident
about guessing the cause of death.
I got a jigi , and my deities showed me.
I'll never disgrace them.
LADY WISH
6-YEAR SHAMAN
I see visions,
so I see how they looked when they died
or what happened to them.
A vision is…
When shamans sense something
while trying to read fortune,
some of them see a vision with their eyes.
Some see it with their eyes closed,
while others see with their eyes open.
The images play before you like a film.
You see the situation.
-I think shamans are at an advantage here.
-Yes.
- Because they can see what happened.
- Yes.
Someone's yawning.
-That person keeps yawning.
-Oh, no.
Oh, goodness.
He looks really tired.
He must be tired.
YOUNG MASTER PLUM BLOSSOM
Whenever I channel
my Granny, Grandpa spirits
and other deities, I yawn a lot.
So, you'll see me yawning a lot.
Sometimes they give me a reading
or even a vision.
My Granny spirit
mostly works with scissors.
And hwatu cards.
She made me pick up the hwatu cards.
I use them to read people's love life,
do a spirit reading,
or read people's finances and life paths.
I looked at the man's photo
and picked out a few cards.
All cards had fire on them.
Then I asked my Granny spirit
if that was right,
and she said,
"That's for you to find out."
So I started tying the go.
It's called "go,"
but the exact name is "goppae."
We use a black one
to call upon the spirits
who died tragically, far from home.
On the fourth day of March in 2001,
he died while doing a good deed.
As I was tying the go into knots,
my Granny spirit said,
"You know what to do, right?"
I said, "I do."
To find out the cause of his death,
I tied the black go into knots
and put the scissors on it.
That's when I felt him.
Just imagine the spirit's lying on the go.
It'd be this big,
lying on top of the cloth.
I got a jigi, and I wanted to jump
into the water in front of me.
It was so hot.
It felt like my skin
was burning from the inside,
so I could do nothing but sit still.
KIM CHEOLHONG
DIED ON MARCH 4, 2001
What is his cause of death?
FIREFIGHTER WHO RESPONDED
TO THE HONGJE-DONG ARSON SCENE
ON MARCH 4, 2001, A FIRE BROKE OUT
IN A MULTIPLEX HOUSING UNIT IN HONGJE-DONG
THE CEILING AND WALLS CAVED IN,
BURYING KIM CHEOLHONG
DURING THE RESCUE EFFORTS
THEY TRIED TO RESCUE HIM,
BUT HE DIED UNDER THE RUBBLE
I think I'll have chills
if anyone mentions heat.
- "It's hot."
- "He didn't deserve it."
- "He was trapped."
Since the cause of death is clear,
it'll be easier to judge.
I'm wondering
if it was related to a crime.
I think it was an arson case.
He died in a way he didn't deserve.
The time is up.
Any Fate Reader who wants to have a go,
press your button now.
- Oh.
- Ah…
Twenty-nine Fate Readers
are up for the challenge.
The number went down a bit.
- That's how hard it is.
- Of course, it is.
Here are the Fate Readers
who will present their readings.
YOUNG MASTER PLUM BLOSSOM
YOUNG MASTER MINT
YOUNG MASTER BYEOLSANG
YOUNG MASTER SEO
- I think they're mostly shamans.
- Looks like it.
The first to press the button
was Young Master Plum Blossom.
Please present your reading.
When I gave my deity
the deceased's birth date and time,
I was told he was destined
to be close to fire.
I took that to mean
he dealt with fires as a firefighter.
…as a firefighter.
I'm losing my mind here.
I was also told that he was meant
to wear heavy clothes and a heavy hat.
…a heavy hat.
More importantly,
I sensed a strong smell of ash.
So did I.
Me too.
Based on his birth chart,
the last thing he saw
was a raging fire
and he probably died trapped in it.
What on earth?
Oh, my gosh.
It seems
he cared deeply for others in life,
and there was
the energy of death in his fate,
but he fought it by saving lives.
I think he was destined to live
as an honorable man.
It's game over.
Right from the start? What do we do?
How did he do that?
- What the heck? It's scary.
- And he's only the first one.
Next, Young Master Mint.
Please present your reading.
Hmm.
The master versus his disciple.
SPIRITUAL MASTER, SPIRITUAL DISCIPLE
Young Master Byeolsang is my mentor.
I think he has the strongest aura here.
Still, I think
I've gained some experience myself.
I want to beat him, to be honest.
I think I'll do better.
I just know I will.
I'll show the skills I've honed
for the last decade.
I also get the feeling
that he was a public servant.
"Died in the line of duty"
was what came to mind first.
- I believe he died a noble death.
- That's right.
What's important is,
when he died in the fire,
something hit him hard.
Maybe he was trapped.
…maybe he was trapped.
He was trapped.
It seems he suffered
a concussion or fractures.
I think that's what killed him,
rather than the fire itself.
I think so too. My joints hurt like crazy.
Next, Young Master Byeolsang.
They've mentioned
that he was a public servant
and that he fought fires and died in one.
I got a similar reading as well.
But it must've been an urgent situation
where he tried to escape but couldn't.
That's what it felt like.
He saved many lives
but lost his own.
He seems to have sacrificed himself.
That's what I got.
- Wow.
- Ah…
So many have said
that he was a firefighter.
Next, Young Master Seo.
When I tried to sense his spirit,
what I felt more strongly than flames
was pressure.
I believe something fell on him,
and he was crushed to death.
I felt that much more strongly.
Like he was crushed and couldn't breathe.
That was my reading.
That's the right answer, isn't it?
Before the smoke suffocated him…
-He'd already been crushed to death.
-Yeah.
The moment I felt this strong sensation,
my back hurt as if it were broken.
Gosh. So did I.
He could've been saved,
but he was stuck and couldn't move.
He died young, before his time.
So if you ask me what killed him,
I'd say he was crushed to death,
rather than killed in the fire itself.
I did feel a huge piece
of metal pressing down on me at the end.
I should've mentioned it.
Too bad I didn't.
What do we do in this situation?
Ah…
This is tough.
Fate Reapers,
please choose the person
who read the fate most accurately.
It's hard because so many got it right.
The second one.
Concussion and fractures.
But Young Master Seo was the one
who said he was crushed to death.
I got chills
when I heard the first reading.
- I also found him most impressive.
- I did too.
He said he smelled ash and…
Heavy clothes.
I was shocked
when he got it from the start.
Me too.
It's a tough one.
Let's find out
the Fate Reapers' choice.
I thought my answer
was the most accurate,
so I thought maybe they'd pick me.
I said he was crushed to death,
so I think I'm the one who got it right.
Young Master Seo
and Young Master Mint
gave very detailed readings,
so I was worried they might not pick me.
The survivor is…
Young Master Plum Blossom.
- Oh! Congratulations.
- Thank you.
YOUNG MASTER PLUM BLOSSOM SURVIVES
Congratulations.
Well done.
His reading was very impactful.
It really was.
It was tough for us to decide
the survivor for this one.
Many of you were pretty close.
The reason we chose
Young Master Plum Blossom
was because he gave his reading first,
which is important too.
He also mentioned
heavy equipment and the helmet,
which was impressive.
That's why we chose him.
Can you tell us
exactly what you saw in the vision?
Physically, the first thing I felt
was tightness in my chest
and a bad headache.
If he'd died of a head injury,
I would've felt pain on the outside,
but I felt dizzy.
I felt suffocated, like I'd inhaled smoke.
I saw him take off a heavy helmet.
Hmm.
I saw him take it off and wipe his sweat.
That's why I thought he was a firefighter.
The second vision I saw was
him covered in sweat
and him eating popsicles
with his coworkers
and tapping them together.
Oh. It's like a movie scene.
Wow.
Although we picked
Young Master Plum Blossom,
we were very torn
because Young Master Seo
also successfully figured out
that the deceased could've been saved.
Actually, to rescue Mr. Kim Cheolhong,
over 250 firefighters went to the scene,
but when they got to him,
he had already passed away.
That part really gave me the chills.
But you didn't pick me.
He said, "But you didn't pick me."
That's cute.
He's adorable.
Thank you, though.
I'll try harder.
Young Master Plum Blossom,
you may leave the hall now.
I have a favor to ask.
Before I leave,
can I untangle this go for the deceased?
- Yes.
- Yes, sure.
He came prepared.
- Maybe that's why the spirit came to him.
- Right.
- He must be grateful.
- Hmm.
There are the Siwang,
the 10 Kings of the Underworld.
You untie each knot in the goppae,
praying the 10 Kings show mercy
when they judge the deceased.
UNTYING THE KNOTS
TO HELP A SPIRIT CROSS OVER
I was half-possessed by his spirit
when I was untying them.
I could feel his grief
as the knots were being untied.
I prayed that he would rest in peace
as I was untying the knots.
May he be reborn in paradise.
When you untie the knots,
you can see the spirit leave.
You neatly fold the go afterward,
and if the ends line up perfectly,
it means the spirit is at peace.
Thank you. I'm done.
That was great.
- Congratulations.
- Good luck!
The reason why
I really hoped to get this one
was because I wanted
to untie the knots and send him off.
I'm so glad I got to do that.
Perhaps, he appreciated my intent
and helped me move forward in return.
- Shamans have an edge in this department.
- Definitely.
They're bound to be good.
-They can literally see what happened.
-Yes.
"Heavy clothes
and a heavy hat." That was it for me.
What would be the next question?
The next question
is the deceased's cause of death.
LEE JAEHYEON
DIED ON AUGUST 1, 2004
Please begin your reading now.
Granny, Grandpa. He was born
on the 29th of the lunar February, 1977.
Please grant me an accurate reading.
Many of them are using flags.
Flags.
I see a lot of them drawing
the obanggi this time.
Right.
They've started drawing obanggi.
Obanggi means flags of 5 colors.
The most simple and common use
is to see if something's good or bad.
Obanggi are
usually used to confirm the reading.
Even if our deities
tell us something,
we still have doubts sometimes
because we're only human.
And when we do,
we check to see if the reading is right.
Usually, white and red mean good fortune.
MEANING OF THE COLORS
WHITE, RED: POSITIVE
Tell me the answer.
Green implies scandal,
illness, or an accident.
MEANING OF THE COLORS
GREEN: NEGATIVE
HONG YULJAE
6-YEAR SHAMAN
FAIRY PEACH BLOSSOM
And that's how I knew
he died a tragic death.
SEOLHWA
4-YEAR SHAMAN
Tell me how this person passed,
Granny and Grandpa.
Help me out here.
I could tell
he died a tragic death.
Oh, dear. A broken leg.
YOUNG MASTER SEO
5-YEAR SHAMAN
It was sudden.
A sudden death.
I've got my eyes on Young Master Seo.
I think he'll get it again.
Yes.
I watched the shamans
doing their thing,
and honestly, I was impressed.
Talking to the spirits
and getting everything right.
But myungri
is an entirely different field.
I couldn't figure it out at all.
I used to be an IT engineer.
But I started studying myungri
and developed a formula
about the 24 solar terms.
Then I created my own theory
and launched my saju business.
My name is Pie.
We specialize in saju and myungri.
We can't let the shamans win.
We have to win.
I'm going to make it.
I always make sure to analyze
one's environment and disposition.
"What kind of path
have they taken so far and how?"
I keep trying to gain more insight.
PERPETUAL CALENDAR
AND BIRTH DETAILS WERE PROVIDED
The time is up.
Here are the Fate Readers
who will present their readings.
Young Master Seo
got another chance.
As expected.
PIE
12-YEAR SAJU EXPERT
You made it.
SEOLHWA
4-YEAR SHAMAN
SOHO
5-YEAR SHAMAN
Oh, I'm in.
The first to press the button
was Young Master Seo.
Please present your reading.
Young Master Seo.
I can't wait to hear it.
I'm curious.
I think it was a sudden death.
That's what we call this kind of death.
- He's right.
- That's true.
I feel he suffered from an illness,
and he was on a lot of medications.
I believe he died from a disease,
something that runs in the family.
I'm getting the image
where he feels something
and collapses all of a sudden.
That's how I think he passed away.
Next up, Pie.
In the case of Mr. Lee Jaehyeon,
he was born in late spring
under Yang Wood,
which symbolizes logic and learning.
But I also see Yin Fire, which implies
artistic or intellectual talent,
so it seems he worked out in the field.
And if I look at his annual fortune,
he was likely out in the field
either as a police officer or a soldier.
I see him trying
to save others from danger.
I noticed he was born on the month
and the day of gapjin.
And gapjin means the azure dragon.
It represents courage,
bravery, and leadership.
That's the impression I got.
Also, Yin Fire implies
the tendency to point out what's wrong.
He could've been someone who saved others
from a wrong or bad situation.
That's how I interpreted it,
so I concluded he was
either a police officer or a soldier.
That's the correct answer.
DECEASED
OCCUPATION: POLICE OFFICER
STABBED TO DEATH
WHILE APPREHENDING A SUSPECT
I wonder if he died in a fight
where a knife or a gun was used.
This is madness.
-Saju readers are impressive too.
-Saju readers are doing amazing today.
Saju can be more accurate
than spiritual divination, and I can win.
Next, Seolhwa.
- Seolhwa.
- She's the dancer-turned-shaman.
-She cried earlier.
-Right.
Why? Is she feeling something?
She must be sensing
the spirit's emotions.
I'm Seolhwa, a novice shaman
with 3 years of experience.
We're nervous
in our own way as novices,
and manshins are nervous in theirs.
I'm still a novice.
You're feeling nervous?
Then how would I feel?
- She's an utter novice.
- What about me?
We must do whatever we can.
I'm still a novice,
so I'm keeping my head down.
and I greet them with respect.
But I'm no pushover.
I trust my Granny and Grandpa spirits
when I read one's fortune.
I don't see or care about anyone else
when I'm doing that.
I don't want to bring disgrace to them.
The first thing I saw
on this person was a bandage.
A puncture, a stabbing with a knife.
I see he was stabbed.
Oh, my word.
I also saw that his leg was broken.
I saw a cast, and I also saw him
being taken away in an ambulance.
Oh! This is crazy.
He died in transit.
It's likely he was a man in uniform
and got stabbed.
He wore a cast and was bandaged,
so it's likely he was hurt.
My gosh.
"A man in uniform was stabbed."
That's spot-on.
Next up, Soho.
The person who sat next to me.
The person in yellow, Seolhwa.
I wanted to leave before her.
I wanted to prove my spiritual power.
In the vision, I sensed
a loud smack or bang.
I saw it was an unfortunate accident.
I also saw him being taken
to the hospital.
This person was a good and righteous man,
and he would sacrifice himself
to protect others.
In my vision,
he has something in his hand,
and he's fighting to protect something.
Either he died in the line of duty
or he was hurt
while trying to protect others
and died while being taken
to the hospital.
- Died on duty.
- Died in transit.
-While being transported.
-Yes.
I think this person…
All readings have been shared.
Fate Reapers,
please choose the person
who read the fate most accurately.
- Let's go with the concise, accurate one.
- Yes, of course.
Seolhwa wasn't bad either.
She mentioned
a uniform and stabbing.
It was spot-on.
But Soho actually said
he died on his way to the hospital.
- Did she?
- Yes.
-That was good.
-What I liked about his reading
was that he got the occupation
and the cause of death right.
- Pie? You're right.
- Yes.
To be honest, I was confident.
I trust my deity.
I believe in my Granny spirit.
Please. Please pick me.
The survivor is
Pie.
PIE SURVIVES
MANSHIN KWON SUJIN
26-YEAR SHAMAN
They're all surprised.
A saju reader beat the shamans.
BUSINESS SAGE KIM
8-YEAR SAJU EXPERT
Saju.
Saju readers have still got it.
Pie did a lot of research
and protected saju readers' pride.
I'm grateful to him.
I'm happy. So happy.
This wasn't even my area of expertise,
but I pulled it off,
so I felt proud and relieved.
The late Lee Jaehyeon
was a police officer.
On August 1, 2004,
while apprehending
a perpetrator on the run
after locking up
and assaulting his girlfriend,
he was stabbed
and killed in the line of duty.
STABBED 9 TIMES BY SUSPECT,
DIED EN ROUTE TO THE HOSPITAL
Oh, that's terrible.
Again,
it was a really tough call.
Pie was the first
-to say he was a police officer.
-That's right.
He also mentioned a knife
and said he must've died
while trying to save someone else.
That was very accurate.
He got both the job
and the cause of death right.
But how did you know
it involved a fight and a knife?
He seemed to be a brave person
and the type to rectify what's wrong.
That's why I thought
the incident might've involved a weapon.
-So it was his intuition.
-He interpreted it himself.
That's part of his skill set.
It was his intuition.
To be honest,
while listening to your reading,
I thought that well-trained intuition
is like the finger of a deity.
Well-polished knowledge
must have allowed him
to peer into things
like the eye of a deity.
I was very surprised.
All that from studying… That's impressive.
Like a deity
pointing to the answer.
Fate Reader Pie survived.
- I'll see you later.
- How cool.
That's so admirable.
- It's cool he pulled it off with saju.
- It is.
It's easier for shamans to do it, so…
So impressive.
Every time someone left,
I thought, "I've got to move on
to the next round too."
"Why am I still here?"
I got jealous and antsy
each time someone survived.
I pretended I was happy for them,
but I was actually boiling inside.
I kept telling myself, "Get it together."
That was awesome.
I only mentioned uniform
and forgot to say he was a police officer.
- You have to be even more accurate.
- I know.
This must be why we're novices.
- Gosh.
- This is why.
Ah…
I thought the shamans would beat everyone.
- I guess you never know.
- He's a saju reader.
- It's crazy he got the cause of death.
- I know.
Two shamans
and one saju reader so far.
Here is the next question.
- What's going on?
- It's opening.
What is this?
It's a different kind of question.
We've got actual people now.
- What's this?
- There are people.
What?
Five people in hanbok.
What's this?
Don't tell me we should pick out a shaman.
Looks like we need to guess who's shaman.
Good God.
Here is the next question.
Who's the shaman?
- Come on.
- This should be fun.
Who's the shaman?
Unbelievable.
How funny.
Come on, are you serious?
Asking shamans to find a shaman?
That's harsh.
Interesting.
Standing before you
are 5 shamans.
1. FLOWER HEAVENLY FAIRY
2. SHAMAN THUNDERBOLT
3. SHAMAN KANGSEON
4. SAGE BEOM
5. FAIRY WOLHWA
However, only 2 of them
are actual shamans
- who have their own shrines.
- Two of them?
The other 3 are not shamans.
Oh, they're fakes.
Read their fates
and find the 2 real shamans.
Not just 1 but 2 of them?
- This can be pretty tough.
- It's difficult.
Wouldn't this be easier
for shamans, though?
I'm a counselor, and I recognize
a counselor when I see one.
Yes, you can tell.
LEE SOBIN
20-YEAR SHAMAN
This is so much fun.
SEORIHWA
5-YEAR SHAMAN
It couldn't be easier.
I can tell just by looking at their eyes.
You can tell just by looking.
YOUNG MASTER BYEON
15-YEAR SHAMAN
We can tell just by looking.
You could line up 100 people
and tell me to find a shaman,
and I think I could.
I've seen so many of them.
YOUNG MASTER BYEOLSANG
11-YEAR SHAMAN
When you do a reading
on a shaman,
the bells often fall off the bunch.
Two, three bells… They keep falling off.
That's how you know they're a shaman.
Isn't this something
only shamans can tell?
Only shamans can tell.
Shamans recognize
their own kind.
HONG YULJAE
6-YEAR SHAMAN
Shamans have this unique gaze.
DOEYU
7-YEAR SHAMAN
When you look at another shaman,
they have another pupil in their eyes
that's invisible to ordinary people.
There's something
that looks like a deity's pupil.
I bet most shamans can feel it.
The shamans seem
to just keep staring, right?
They say they can see deities.
How can you see them?
A Granny's face.
LEE SOBIN
20-YEAR SHAMAN
I was looking at numbers 1 and 3,
and their faces turned really red,
and I saw some elderly spirits
that looked enraged.
As soon as I saw that, I knew it was them.
They would've had to pretend like
they were fake shamans,
and a shaman pretending not to be one?
No deity would be happy with that.
We moved on
to the next question,
and for some reason,
I didn't feel confident.
LADY WISH
6-YEAR SHAMAN
Help me, Granny. I can't tell.
Is there a deity?
My Granny spirit said,
"Since when did you read fortunes
with your head?"
"You're stuck because your thoughts
and greed got in the way."
So I decided to trust what I saw and felt,
and that's
when I could see things clearly.
I could see deities
in only numbers 1 and 3,
and the rest had closed doors
and looked dark,
so I knew they weren't with any deities.
Does she serve deities
in her own shrine?
Her name is Shaman Kangseon.
I ask you to tell me
if she serves deities.
Young Master Dragon.
He used to be an actor.
The handsome guy.
I was an actor for about 16 years
before I became a shaman.
I'm a novice
with less than 6 months of experience,
the talented Young Master Dragon.
My deities said
although I never made it big as an actor,
they'd make sure
I make a name for myself as a shaman.
They often tell me this when I pray.
Because I've only just become a shaman,
I thought I'd feel things more powerfully.
That lady's pretending.
I was confident.
The saju readers have a shot
because they have all their birth details.
- They have the birth charts.
- Right.
You know, shamans are born
with a certain birth chart.
Shamans, celebrities, and people
with such occupations have similar saju.
Oh.
I think saju readers
will do better.
FATE-TELLER
9-YEAR SAJU EXPERT
META MYUNGRI JOON
15-YEAR SAJU EXPERT
Shamans' sajus share
something in common.
Excessive Wood and Water energy.
Water is the divine energy,
and Wood is the human energy.
Water enriches wood.
Water gives life to trees.
Receiving messages from deities
and delivering them to the world.
That's the disposition
shamans are born with.
Number 4's not it. He's a good actor.
There's one among numbers 1, 3, and 5.
FLOWER HEAVENLY FAIRY,
SHAMAN KANGSEON, FAIRY WOLHWA
The time is up.
Any Fate Reader who wants to give it a go,
press your button now.
- See?
- Everyone wants to do it.
That was quick.
Forty-one Fate Readers are up
for the challenge.
- Oh, good. Lots of new people.
- Yes.
Lady Wish,
please present your reading.
She used to be an archer.
A third-generation shaman.
I was torn
among numbers 1, 3, and 5.
As for number 1, I saw a Grandpa spirit.
A deity who has the ability to cure.
I think that's the guardian deity
that she serves.
A Grandpa spirit?
For number 3,
Shaman Kangseon, I see a young lady.
She also has the saju of a shaman.
Yes, spot-on.
Number 3.
Anyway,
from what I see and feel,
I say numbers 1 and 3 are shamans.
That's my answer.
LADY WISH
NUMBER 1 AND NUMBER 3
Same as mine.
I can see that number 1 and 3's
deities are angry.
- She's spot-on.
- How do you see that?
- We just can. This is easy for us.
- What do you see?
Next, Young Master Dragon.
Please present your reading.
First, I narrowed it down
to numbers 1, 3, and 5.
Number 3 seems like
she does serve deities,
but she's being punished
by the General spirit she serves.
I concluded that she's a shaman.
As for number 5, Fairy Wolhwa,
I used my bells to ask if she's a shaman,
and the bells trembled a lot.
I felt the strongest presence
of deities from her.
As for number 1, I was told
she could be a shaman,
and that's why I was torn.
So in the end, I chose numbers 3 and 5.
YOUNG MASTER DRAGON
NUMBER 3 AND NUMBER 5
Next, Juno.
Please present your reading.
She tells fortunes based on the name.
Just the name? That's it?
My forte is that when I see a name,
I can just tell everything about them.
SHAMAN KANGSEON, SAGE BEOM, PARK MIAE
When I look at someone's name
or meet them in person,
I see their past, present, and future.
I see the situation they're in
and give them advice
so they can head in the right direction.
That's what sets me apart from the others.
I thought Flower Heavenly Fairy,
Ms. Kim Ryurim,
and Shaman Kangseon, Ms. Seo Seunghee,
are most likely the shamans.
Before that door opened,
my heart suddenly started racing,
and I felt a pain in my stomach.
Oh, gosh.
The 2 of them looked like
their hearts were reacting strongly
to the sound of the bells.
I could see them jittering.
It seemed to be bothering them.
So I think it's most likely
that those 2 are shamans.
She saw them react
to the sound of the bells?
Their hearts?
- How do you see that?
- She tells fortunes with just the name.
How do you see someone's heart react?
All readings have been shared.
The survivor is…
Gosh, I'm really curious.
I'm confident
that I have formidable skills.
Well, I could see
their deities and spirits.
I could tell they were shamans
and spoke with confidence.
I'm a novice
with less than 6 months of experience,
but my spiritual power
is as strong as anyone's.
The survivor is
Lady Wish.
LADY WISH SURVIVES
Juno also got it right,
but Lady Wish was chosen as the survivor
since she presented her reading first.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
- Was it 1 and 3?
- Yes, 1 and 3.
Mm-hmm.
Wow, that was crazy.
The real shamans are
Flower Heavenly Fairy…
REAL SHAMAN
NUMBER 1 FLOWER HEAVENLY FAIRY
- Hello.
- I knew it, number 1.
…and Shaman Kangseon.
REAL SHAMAN
NUMBER 3 SHAMAN KANGSEON
I got goosebumps.
- They actually got it right.
- I know.
- That's amazing.
- It's incredible. How do they know?
- It's unbelievable.
- It makes no sense.
- How impressive.
- Seriously.
I'm impressed by those
who came up with the questions
and those who got them right.
I also thought
shamans are truly impressive.
Even if you don't get it
right, if those in your field do well,
you feel proud too, you know.
I want to show everyone else
that deities really exist,
and that shamans exist for a reason.
What a great feeling.
She must feel so good.
Lady Wish beat her to the punch,
- but Juno also got it right.
- Yes.
-Name divination.
-She tells fortune with just the name.
Juno also got it right.
- Yes, it was so close.
- Name divination.
So close.
I guess Juno's good.
What did you mean when you said
you felt their hearts tremble?
As for me, I use names to read fortunes,
but I'm actually Christian.
And you saw
their hearts pounding?
-Christians could have a trembling heart.
-Right.
I do really love Jesus.
But suddenly, before the door opened,
my chest hurt really bad, so for a while,
I prayed.
I got the feeling
that I should concentrate on their hearts,
so I thought it was those two.
-You could be called by spirits any day.
-No.
-I'm sticking to God. Sorry.
-Be alert for the calling.
Dear Lord.
Hallelujah.
Fate Reader Lady Wish survived.
- I'm through.
- Congratulations.
- Congrats.
- I survived.
I was so surprised,
but I was over the moon.
I'm a third-generation shaman.
My father's a shaman as well.
I didn't want to bring shame to my family.
I didn't disgrace my dad
or my Grandpa and Granny spirits.
Let's go!
Congratulations.
I have to get the next one.
That was one for shamans,
and I still didn't get it.
Here is the next question.
What is it?
I'm worried now.
I'm scared of what will be next.
I know.
What is this now?
What is it this time?
I smell money.
The fate for you to read
is a windfall and a bolt of lightning.
-I knew it.
-…a bolt of lightning.
I can smell money on someone.
Of the 4 people
standing before you,
one struck it rich by winning the lottery.
- He scored a windfall.
- For real?
No way!
Another suffered
a real bolt of lightning.
In other words,
he was struck by actual lightning.
For real?
- Actual lightning?
- Real lightning?
Actual lightning?
Lightning from the sky? Actual lightning?
-The kind that zaps you?
-Not misfortune?
- What?
- Real lightning?
He was hit by lightning?
Actual lightning? From the sky?
Read their fates
and find the windfall
and the real bolt of lightning.
They can't just pick 2 people.
-They must guess which happened to whom.
-Yes. That's harder.
A windfall
or a real bolt of lightning.
Number 2 has the hairstyle
of a guy that was hit by lightning.
What? Come on.
I mean, his hair…
- Oh, no.
- What?
What am I to do?
This is as hard as winning the lottery.
It'd be fun if I got it right.
This is so unprecedented.
This is crazy.
It's insane.
How did they
even find someone like that?
How could they come up
with such unusual questions?
I was in awe.
What a wacky question.
Please begin your reading now.
This is as hard
as winning the lottery.
It's confusing.
I've never tried
anything like this.
Those are the kind of things
that almost never happen to you.
So I found it really hard.
Gosh, I'm lost.
- It's hard.
- So difficult.
Wow, this is really difficult.
It's hard.
- The saju readers have an advantage.
- Possibly.
There must be a rich person saju
-that brings a windfall.
-There is.
-And one for lightning strikes.
-Those with a certain saju are loaded.
- Really?
- Yes.
Their dates and times of birth
are there. Saju readers can do it too.
LEE JAESEOK, LEE BEOMJUN,
OH SEONGBU, KIM SEONGOH
RYU DONGHAK
31-YEAR SAJU EXPERT
You can
make a rough guess with saju.
I can guess anything with a date of birth.
I thought I had
a good chance with this one.
I was determined to show them
what I can do.
This is interesting.
Yin Wood over Ox.
Oh, dear.
I don't see any Metal in his saju.
I'm a corporate saju reader,
so I can see the flow of money.
Earth controlling Water.
It totally means big fortune, a windfall.
I was almost certain
I knew the right answer.
BEENTAROT
9-YEAR TAROT MASTER
Let's have a look.
Mr. Lee Jaeseok.
Let's have a look
at his financial fortune.
Tarot masters tell
one's fortune
with specific keywords.
Was he struck by lightning?
Did he get struck by lightning?
So I thought we had the upper hand.
A windfall.
Riddle me this
I did a reading.
The first card I noticed
was the Ace of Pentacles.
The card symbolizes financial success.
So I was confident about my answer.
I picked number 2
as the one who hit the windfall.
He has a nice-looking nose.
The nose is called jaebaekgung.
It's a predictor of wealth and fortune.
And he has a great nose.
And the smaller man at the end.
His stature was slightly tilted.
I knew it had to be those two.
I'm done.
Wow.
The time is up.
Any Fate Reader who wants to have a go,
press your button now.
- Everyone's pressing.
- We have many challengers.
Saju readers… A lot of challengers.
A lot of tarot masters too.
Thirty-nine Fate Readers
are up for the challenge.
The first to press their button was
Business Sage Kim.
Please present your reading.
He's a saju reader.
He reads saju for companies.
First, as for the windfall,
I think it's number 2, Mr. Lee Beomjun.
Someone with
this many Companion Stars strikes it big.
I got the feeling that he's been
taken advantage of until now.
I also see
a mix of different Wealth Stars.
When the energy
of Water and Wood come in together
in one's annual fortune like this,
it's possible that they strike it big.
Some are fated to a windfall.
I guess so. It's so interesting.
That's why I thought
number 2 won the lottery.
I thought number 1 was hit by lightning.
People with Yang Wood over Horse
tend to have a tough life.
So I tried Hexagram Divination
from the Book of Changes
and got pungroeik,
a predictor of prosperity and growth.
PUNGROEIK
I thought that may have
something to do with it,
and that's why I said
number 1 was struck by lightning.
LIGHTNING, WINDFALL
He even tried Hexagram Divination?
Next, Osang Yoo Jinseok.
OSANG YOO JINSEOK
30-YEAR SAJU EXPERT
I've studied saju and myungri
for a long time.
"You can tell this much from one's saju?"
I'm eager to make people think that.
I will say number 2 is the guy
who won the lottery.
Let me explain why.
In saju, there are 3 "storages"
that symbolize wealth.
This man's saju is breaking them.
By "breaking," I mean
that the storages are open.
When one's storages are open,
they hit a jackpot.
That's why I say
he strongly attracts wealth and romance.
Romance too?
Now, Mr. Lee Jaeseok
was born with Wood in his saju,
but there's a lot of Metal
in his saju too.
I can take that to mean
he's under a tremendous amount of stress.
My answer is number 1's the lightning,
and number 2's the windfall.
LIGHTNING, WINDFALL
The 2 saju readers
gave the exact same answer.
Fascinating.
Next, Rumi.
Please present your reading.
- Spiritual tarot.
- Yes.
A lot of baseball players' wives
go to see her.
Oh, that's her.
First of all,
I think Mr. Lee Jaeseok's the windfall
and Mr. Kim Seongoh was hit by lightning.
The reason is, the cards I got
were the Wheel of Fortune,
the Magician, and King of Pentacles.
"He's proud he survived it."
That's how I interpreted it.
Ah…
Goodness.
If he were hit
by lightning and survived,
that's as good
as having won the lottery.
That's a great interpretation.
It all comes down to how you interpret it.
Next, Beentarot.
- Please present your reading.
- It's his first presentation.
- Yoon Gai's younger brother.
- Actress Yoon Gai's brother.
Honestly, winning the lottery and getting
hit by lightning are both very unlikely.
The cards for number 1
were the Ace of Pentacles and the Tower.
You can see money and lightning.
Very straightforward.
Number 4 got the Judgement card
and the Ace of Swords piercing through it.
So I say number 4 was hit by lightning,
and number 1 scored a windfall
by winning the lottery.
Our answers are the same.
Tarot is so fascinating too.
How did they get the same answer?
TAROT MASTERS
NUMBER 4
Next, Young Master Jiseon.
I knew even before they came in.
YOUNG MASTER JISEON
13-YEAR SHAMAN
My Granny spirit stood behind me and said,
"It's him."
So I thought,
"It's you. This mission's for me."
Based on my reading,
number 2 won the lottery
and number 4 was hit by lightning.
As for number 2,
simply put, there were nobles
among his ancestors,
people of high status.
I see a few of those lords with him.
People in his family
used to hold high offices,
which means they accumulated good karma.
So, their descendants
are able to reap the benefits
in terms of wealth.
As for number 4,
he's had a rough life.
Simply put,
nothing comes together for him.
That's why I say he was hit by lightning.
Oh!
SHAMAN
NUMBER 4
All readings have been shared.
The survivor is…
Young Master Jiseon.
YOUNG MASTER JISEON SURVIVES
The kid's crying.
No, don't cry.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, dear baby.
- He's the youngest, 18-year-old.
- Ow, geez.
Ow, geez.
Oh, what do we do?
- Oh, my word.
- Geez.
Gosh.
Why are you crying?
Young Master Jiseon.
- No, I just got a little emotional.
- You got emotional?
I think my mom and dad
will be delighted.
I talked to them in my head.
"I made it."
I'll brag to them later.
They've always been my biggest supporters.
I didn't get to see them
before coming here. So I will later.
I'm so thankful.
- Would you like some tissue?
- Yes.
I tried not to cry.
It's embarrassing
to cry around celebrities.
- He was so accurate.
- He's so good.
-He got it in one go.
-Seriously. It's truly incredible.
- He actually got it right.
- I know.
Mr. Lee Beomjun won the 467th
lottery draw on November 12, 2011.
Wow!
He received a windfall
of 1.435 billion won.
Gosh, I'm so jealous.
I wish I got a windfall like that.
On May 19, 2008,
Mr. Kim Seongoh was struck by lightning
-while riding his motorcycle
-No way.
-and miraculously woke up after 9 days.
-Oh, my days.
- It was literally a bolt of lightning.
- That's impressive.
Thank goodness!
What a relief.
Mr. Lee Beomjun,
the lottery winner.
Lottery winners often say they had a dream
about fire or poop the night before.
- Or a pig.
- Or ancestors giving them the numbers.
Mr. Lee, what about you?
Did you have any dreams?
Yes.
In my dream, I was walking down
the street, and a stranger showed up
-and stabbed me in the neck like this.
-Oh, gosh.
But when he did,
someone other than me
started bleeding from the neck.
The blood gushed out like a waterfall.
That's a good dream.
That's a great dream.
He saw blood.
I was at my ripe age of late 20s,
but I was so scared
when I woke up from the dream,
so I went to sleep next to my mom.
That's how real the dream felt.
I guess that dream was a sign.
-That's right.
-Oh, how interesting.
Mr. Kim Seongoh,
what happened to you
might be even rarer
than winning the lottery.
It's rare enough to get struck
by lightning, but you even survived.
It was drizzling, and I saw
lightning strike a spot ahead of me.
But I was in a hurry,
so I took my motorcycle,
and got struck by lightning
at the top of a mountain pass.
I fell off a cliff with my motorcycle.
- My gosh.
- Oh, dear.
Oh, my days.
But like a miracle,
I woke up after 9 days.
That's incredible.
Gosh, that's such a relief.
I was a professional golfer.
Wow.
But I couldn't play the sport
anymore after the accident,
and now I'm a trot singer.
What?
My goodness.
His life took a 180.
I thought
they'd never get it right.
I didn't think anyone would get it.
I'm grateful that Young Master Jiseon did.
Thank you.
I got goosebumps all over.
Young Master Jiseon.
Mr. Kim Seongoh got struck by lightning.
Will he be successful?
Well, let's see.
When people sing trot songs,
some sing for fun,
but some do it
because of han.
Mr. Kim sings with his heart and han.
Next year, around April and May,
he will definitely…
reach a high before he goes down.
He goes down?
- He'll go down?
- He goes down?
He'll still have his moment.
That's what counts.
That's right.
Swoosh.
For identifying
the windfall and lightning,
Young Master Jiseon survived.
- Wow.
- Good for him.
If you were faced
with 4 strangers
and had to guess who won the lottery,
would you be able to do it?
It'd be difficult, right?
But I, the youngest, pulled it off.
He started when he was 5.
I know.
He's the youngest shaman here.
A fun fact about him is that
his guardian spirit is a Granny spirit,
- so he wears a woman's hanbok.
- Young Master Jiseon?
That's why he's so elegant.
- How graceful.
- Thank you.
Congratulations.
- Congratulations.
- The youngest pulled it off.
- Yes.
- Bluetooth handshake.
"Bluetooth."
His mic pack's dangling
from his back.
Here is the next mission.
This is the fate for you to read.
- Mmm?
- Huh?
What's that?
- What the heck?
- Huh, what?
What a strange sight.
That's gross.
- This is insane.
- What is this?
What even is that?
What am I looking at?
-What the…
-What is this?
What the… What am I to do?
What's going on?
Oh, geez…
I can't believe this.
What are we to guess?
The next fate
for you to read is…
Translated by Jennifer Jean Lim