JINWON HIGH SCHOOL
Ms. Choi
was the only good adult I knew.
Everyone gave up on me,
but Ms. Choi did not.
I was...
in love with Ms. Choi.
- You're here.
- Yeah.
Why is it so dark in here?
- Here.
- Thank you.
The more alone you are,
the brighter your space should be.
I made too much geotjeori.
You don't like it fermented.
Put it in your fridge.
Do you expect me to eat all of this?
Gosh, this is...
What?
It's tied tightly.
So it wouldn't leak.
It won't.
Would you like a cup of tea?
Sir.
If an action carries emotion...
that's when it becomes violence.
Don't make me tell you
to forget my daughter.
Yes, sir.
I haven't eaten yet.
Let's have the geotjeori.
Is instant rice okay?
Do you really want to give
your father-in-law instant rice?
But you made me instant rice
last time too.
Cook some rice so it scorches.
You punk...
- I'll go buy some rice.
- Don't you have any rice?
If you want scorched rice,
I have some instant scorched rice.
No, I mean...
- I can make it from instant rice.
- I just want freshly cooked rice.
- Well...
- I eat instant rice every day.
The ERPB's approval ratings
have topped 50% for the first time.
In a survey
of potential presidential candidates,
Minister Choi Gang-seok's approval rating
has surged compared to the previous poll.
Some believe he has hit the nail
on the head about the public's concerns.
That's right.
The ERPB has yet to shake the label of
"a group that acts on personal vendettas."
Since the ERPB's key members
are the deceased female teacher's family,
it is likely that...
This is going to be yummy.
Don't you have hot water at home?
I can't be bothered.
It'll be ready by the time I get home.
That's why I said I'd buy you dinner.
Having a meal with your boss
feels like work.
Oh yeah?
Just talking to myself.
Jesus, is it still talking to yourself
if I can hear everything you say?
Do you think
I could just go home from here?
Why? I'll give you a ride.
Do you have plans or something?
I feel like something always happens
when I'm with you two,
and I always get home late.
Hold on.
What's going on?
Looks like they're trying to steal a car.
- I'll call the police.
- No, don't.
They're wearing school uniforms.
This is our job.
Hold this for a second. Here you go.
Then what should I do?
Stand by.
But the instant noodles...
I was going to go home
and clean my graphics card...
- Snap out of it.
- Oh man.
You shouldn't have had so much.
What's gotten into you?
Nice! This is fucking sweet.
Here we go.
Fuck, whatever.
- Stop.
- Shit.
- Who's that?
Hey, get out.
Get out of the way! Move!
- Whoa, what the...
- What is this?
Squirtle's Water Gun?
The Waterbomb festival?
- Move!
- I said get out.
I'm moving now. Whoa, shit.
- I'm going.
- Stop.
I'm going now.
I said I'm moving now.
I don't care. Damn it!
- Move!
- Hey.
I can't see!
- What the hell?
- Stop!
Is he Spider-Man or what?
- Get ahold of yourself. Damn it.
- Hey.
Yes?
I'm an ERPB inspector.
What are you doing with that girl?
Wow, the ERPB. Holy shit.
Move!
Inspector, are you okay?
Those damn punks.
Damn it. Move!
That was crazy!
Those bastards.
Im Han-rim, run!
What about me?
For God's sake!
Seriously!
Hey, hold on tight!
It's hot!
- He's damn good.
- Passed one.
How am I this good at driving?
- Fucking passed another!
- Fuck.
Hold on tight!
- What the hell?
- Isn't that guy dead yet?
Set them off!
Hey!
Stop the car.
Set them all off!
Fuck, it's hot!
I can't believe this.
Today is epic.
I got them!
Yes, fire!
Those punks. Seriously.
Go!
Bang!
Who cares?!
Is he still fucking behind us?
Shit, what do we do?
- What the hell?
- Those little...
Step on it!
This is crazy! Your driving is sick!
- Why are you still holding that?
- She said she was hungry.
Hey, it's splashing me!
Hey!
- Hey! Pull over!
- Careful.
- What?
- I'm not gonna.
Yeah, no. Not pulling over.
I won't. Why would I?
- Get lost.
- Hey, you punk!
He just flipped me off.
- Be careful.
- Damn it.
Passed you, didn't I?
Move!
Whatever, I'm going for it.
What are you doing?
- Those crazy bastards!
- Are you nuts?
Hands off the wheel!
Who are you guys?
We're juvenile offenders.
- What?
- We're 14 years old.
Right.
The police are here.
INCHEON GANGHWA POLICE STATION
We were going this way.
Inspector Im Han-rim was...
- Hey, there. Wake up. Are you okay?
- Inspector Im was...
She threw a bike under the car
and stopped it.
Are you all right?
She stopped them from fleeing.
Pull yourself together.
Yun-jin's just drunk.
She had three bottles.
- She drank loads.
- She had more.
She had a lot.
They think we were trying to do
something to her.
We're really all friends.
- That's right.
- Totally.
Are you really friends?
Yes, we are.
So just leave us alone.
See? I told you.
She said we're friends.
We're total besties.
- Exactly.
- Be quiet, punk!
You've committed car theft,
unlicensed driving,
and traffic violations!
- I'm sorry, sir.
But the engine was running,
and we just got in out of curiosity.
That's right. It's our hormones.
We're impulsive.
It's what happens at our age.
- It's our age.
- Yeah.
We're juvenile offenders for a reason.
We're really sorry.
We're sorry.
- We're sorry!
- Is that how you show you're sorry?
Im Han-rim, don't.
They know they won't be punished.
That's correct.
They've been here multiple times already.
They know the police can't touch them,
as long as they play stupid,
because they're underage.
They know the law too well. Sit still.
- Did you call the parents?
- Yes, but they'll be a while.
Our homeroom teacher said
he'd come right away.
- Hand them over when he arrives.
- Okay.
- Chief.
- Yes?
What happens now?
Serious cases go to juvenile court
and protective dispositions issued.
But for a case like this,
we let them off with a warning.
I heard there's nothing
the school can do either.
Here he comes.
- You can hear from him directly.
- Hello, Mr. Lee.
CUSTODY HANDOVER CONFIRMATION FORM
We'll be on our way now.
Come and see me first thing tomorrow.
We'll talk more then.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
We appreciate you.
- Goodbye.
- Thank you.
Get her home safe.
- Goodbye, sir.
- Take care.
It's unsettling, right?
Even I can't get used to
the way they speak.
I hear you're from the ERPB?
Yes.
I'm Inspector Na Hwa-jin.
Excuse me.
I'm afraid you two will have to write
another statement.
Those punks reported you both.
For what?
For child abuse.
You can report it
through the app these days, so...
Damn it.
I'm sorry.
I should have taught them better.
Not at all. It's not for you to apologize.
It's embarrassing
to say this as a teacher,
but the school is a mess because of them.
They know all too well
that adults can't do anything to them.
What about the school rules?
They say they're juvenile offenders.
Do you think rules will work on them?
It'll be hard to expel them too
because middle school education
is mandatory.
Sir?
Juvenile offenders played you?
Yes, sir.
I did hear that "juvenile offender"
is like a title from the heavens.
I guess former special forces
are no match for them either.
I want to too!
Who are they?
It's them. The invincible 14-year-olds.
Bye.
Shit.
Bye!
This is fun. Yes, fun indeed.
- Did you say Hyeonjin Middle School?
- Yes, sir.
Report to work there from tomorrow.
HYEONJIN MIDDLE SCHOOL
Jung Seung-jin!
- Hey.
- Yeah.
Why don't you say hi these days?
Why the look?
- Did I hit you?
- No.
Yes, I did, you dumbass.
- You're here early.
- Damn it.
Oh, hello.
Hello.
What's your name?
Jung Seung-jin.
Okay, Seung-jin. Get to class.
See you later. Put my bag on my desk.
You guys are so diligent.
You should skip school once in a while
so the other kids can breathe,
don't you think?
The ERPB is different.
They're really here.
You gave us a real gift yesterday.
I'm here to return the favor.
Give and take.
What's give and cake?
We need to carry out
a proper investigation starting now.
Are you free?
- No.
Why? Are you busy?
No, we're free. It's fine, right?
Okay, get to the counseling room.
To the counseling room.
Nice. We get to skip class.
The ERPB came for us. We made it.
- I'll be famous.
- I don't have a signature.
- I need one.
- This is mad.
What's this?
I told you I'll investigate.
I know.
This is a bluff to buy time, right?
- Busted!
- Busted, right?
They say they'll investigate.
But they're isolating us and are probably
taking the victims' statements.
Well, aren't you Detective Conan?
Then let's confess now.
Go ahead. Do whatever the hell you want.
No one will find out
what is said here.
If Min Ji-ung's crew has ever bullied you
or you've seen them bully others...
No such thing happened.
No.
We're not that close.
I honestly don't know anything,
so please stop asking me.
I'm not sure.
No, nothing like that.
Well...
Apparently, the student
you asked me to investigate
does hang around Min Ji-ung,
but they're not exactly friends.
What are they, then?
She wouldn't tell me
anything more than that.
And where is Yun-jin?
She's here today,
but she wasn't at her desk.
- Where is this?
- The recycling area behind this building.
I don't think this is it.
Let's look elsewhere.
The sly jerks move in packs
and make their hideouts
far enough away from the buildings
where cleaners or maintenance workers go.
They're easier to handle than teachers.
Given those variables
and conditional value...
- What about here?
- Where is this?
There's a standalone building
right beside this gym.
I think this is the place.
Look at this.
Come this way. This way!
There should be a key
somewhere around here.
Are you in there?
We don't need it.
Whoa! What are you doing?
NURSE'S OFFICE
Here. I'll take that.
Can I ask why you were in there?
Was it Min Ji-ung?
Why were you with them yesterday?
I told you we drank together.
Then why didn't you smell of alcohol?
And why, if you hadn't been drinking,
did you seem drunk?
Can I look inside that bag?
What? No.
Gosh, be gentle.
What's this? Medicine?
They're supplements.
Is that so?
Then I'll have one too.
I've been working late a lot
and need to recharge.
You can't take that!
If I shouldn't take it,
you shouldn't either, should you?
Was it these drugs yesterday too?
Was it because of these drugs?
Oh Yun!
You look quite pretty today.
Is it eye shadow? Or blush?
Blush. Can you tell?
Yes, totally.
- You look so trendy.
- Totally agreed.
Just lose a little weight.
I'm already a lost cause.
But if you slim down a bit,
you'll be Jang Won-young.
Maybe I'm going to grow.
I've been craving food like crazy.
It did seem like it
when I watched your Shorts.
Did it really?
Your dancing seemed a little sluggish.
In that case,
my diet starts again, starting today.
You've said that 300 times.
Man, you're pissing me off.
TTEOKBOKKI
MALATANG LEVEL 2
CHEWY COOKIES
DUBAI CHOCOLATE
Aren't you having lunch?
Can't you afford it?
No, I'm just trying to lose weight.
You'd be pretty if you did.
Do you think so too?
But you still need to eat something.
Starving won't help.
Hey.
Wanna try these?
Someone lost 20 kg with these.
I secretly swiped a few.
They went from 57 kg to 37 kg.
Apparently, K-pop stars are taking them.
They can't be bad.
Take one,
and you'll feel the fucking difference.
Look, it's a heart.
Aren't they cute?
Watch this.
Put it in here.
Just treat me if you lose weight.
- Don't drink it, then.
- I will.
TYPICAL DANCE SKILLS
OF A MIDDLE SCHOOL GIRL
Yun-jin.
You look damn pretty in your Shorts video.
Is it because you've lost weight?
Do I look it?
The pills are working wonders.
Want another?
Do you have more?
Of course.
Heart.
Is there any chance
you can get more of those pills?
I can get more.
Not for free though. I need money for it.
How much?
- How much is it?
- About 30,000 won?
It's 50,000 won.
What?
Damn nice!
- Fuck.
- Hey.
Could you get me some pills?
But I don't have any money right now.
Fuck! Street-begging bitch.
Sorry?
It's a joke. I was joking. You scared?
Scared?
Well...
If you don't have money...
you could just work for it.
Is delivering hard?
Is your head just for decoration?
You just give them the pills
and take the money.
You know?
Give and take, you fucking bitch!
What's wrong with you all?
Shit! I could just...
Oh Yun-jin!
I trust that you won't disappoint us.
Hand over the money.
Gosh.
Nice.
Up it 20,000.
20,000 won?
What if no one buys?
You've got a goldfish brain?
You bought it
even after the price went up, so raise it.
Say something.
Well...
Could I stop doing this now?
It's been really tough for me,
and I'm scared.
Fuck! Damn it!
Give me the pills.
- What?
- Give it here.
I guess you don't need
the pills either, do you?
Holy shit.
That's 50,000 won gone.
What now?
Want another chance?
Damn it.
What a waste.
Seriously, what the hell?
Do it properly, damn it.
Do better, all right?
SCHOOL POLICE REPORTING BOX
Hey, so long!
- Be gone!
- Bye-bye!
- Sorry.
- Watch it. The police are here.
Wow.
They're going.
It's all over for Min Ji-ung now.
What happens once they're taken away?
I hope they're forced to move schools.
Seriously, please.
- I hope they're expelled.
- But really, who reported them?
I don't know who it was, but thanks.
HYEONJIN MIDDLE SCHOOL
Heat transfers from hotter objects
to cooler objects.
This happens in three ways.
Let's start with conduction.
We often grill a lot of pork belly
for meals, don't we?
When the meat touches the hot grill,
the particles in contact start moving fast
and pass energy
to other particles in turn.
Hello, sir.
Hurry to your seat.
We'll carry on with the lesson.
You fucking bitch.
You actually snitched to the cops?
That's right, Yun-jin.
They got your letter.
We were investigated thanks to you.
But then, we were let go with a warning.
She must have thought we'd go to prison.
Yeah, as if.
Too bad.
We're juvenile offenders,
so we won't be sent to prison.
Get in there.
Get some rest.
Ji-ung!
Please open the door, Ji-ung.
Ji-ung.
I'm sorry.
Please open the door.
Ji-ung.
If you did something wrong...
you should be punished.
Isn't that right?
Let's take a picture
to remember this moment.
- I'm hungry. Let's go get some food.
- We can't hear you.
- What do you want to eat?
- Pork cutlet.
- Pork cutlet?
- That's crazy.
Can you testify
to everything you just said?
- So we can punish--
- Don't do that.
Is the ERPB any different?
Our homeroom teacher, the school,
and even the police couldn't do anything.
Ji-ung always came looking for me.
Every time I thought
it would be enough or he would stop,
he always came back.
I'm always the only one who gets hurt.
This will only end once I die.
The ERPB is different.
The ERPB is serious
about students who have been hurt.
So trust us.
I will protect you.
Sir.
WRITTEN STATEMENT
GO FUCK YOURSELF
You're gaining points nicely.
Thank you, sir.
It's more than just beating and bullying.
It's drug trafficking.
Those kids I told you about
have been hooked on drugs
and used as runners to make money.
Is this true?
Is that a problem?
Oh, it is.
Now I know.
But as juvenile offenders,
aren't you meant to learn right from wrong
by experiencing different things?
Isn't it the nation's way of giving you
a learning opportunity?
Slyness has its limits,
and you're testing my patience.
Oh, I see.
But I can't stop right away.
I need the money.
I'll stop when I'm no longer underage.
I promise. Really.
Okay, fine.
If you're not happy with this,
just arrest me.
Arrest me and lock me the hell up.
Only if you can.
But you can't, right?
- Annoying, right?
- Fucked, right?
- It's fucked, right?
- It's dog shit, right?
Fuck, don't come near me.
Daddy!
Welcome.
Come here. Good job.
You move back. Go sit at the back.
You think you can fucking run over us?
You're dead
the minute I catch you, bastard!
Welcome, dear passengers.
Stay away!
Han-rim.
- Why are you here?
- It's been a while.
Stay away, damn it!
I'll fucking kill you.
Min Ji-ung, your crimes
have been confirmed as school violence,
dealing designer drugs,
using minors for distribution,
violating educational rights,
and turning the school into hell.
So from now on,
you're screwed.
Where the fuck are we going?
I don't know.
Where the hell are they taking us?
Thank you!
Exit the vehicle.
Seriously, where the fuck are we?
START OVER WITH A DREAM
Welcome to the only juvenile prison
in the Republic of Korea.
A prison, huh?
Did you say
juvenile offenders aren't jailed?
Too bad. We can put you in jail.
Inspector Na, we're good to go.
Let's go.
Someone park the car.
Hello!
GIMCHEON JUVENILE PRISON
IS REQUESTED TO COOPERATE
Minister.
Do you really think this will be okay?
I will take responsibility.
You understand better than anyone
why juvenile offenders are protected.
If this gets out from a place like this,
it will create a stir
about exceeding authority
and violating human rights.
But is that really a reason
to sit back and do nothing?
There needs to be at least one adult
who scolds them,
telling them
that what they've done is wrong.
Please support me in this.
Gosh.
STUDENT RECORD
MIN JI-UNG
- Name?
- Yoon Min-su?
- Min Ji-ung.
- Yes.
Hyundai Seongmo Apartments.
Accessories, earrings, and necklaces.
- Hand them in.
- When can we go?
Put your feet where indicated.
Pull down your underwear. Squat down.
Go back a little.
Pull up your underwear,
take your belongings, and move on.
Step up.
Pull down your underwear.
Pull it down further.
A little more.
Squat down.
Lift your bottom up a bit.
Pull down your underwear.
Damn it.
No.
HOPE-DRIVEN CORRECTION
THAT OPENS DOORS TO BRIGHTER FUTURES
Stand up straight!
You will live under the same conditions
as the other inmates from now on.
You will receive
the same mandatory education,
and you will do volunteer work
in line with ERPB education policy.
Anyone have objections?
They will keep them to themselves.
Move.
- Follow me.
- Move.
We have newbies!
Hey, you motherfucker!
DAILY REFLECTION AS A WAY OF LIFE
We take a dump here?
Damn it.
Inspector Im Han-rim will instruct you
on matters related
to your shared living quarters.
You're really going fucking too far.
I'm going to report this
all over the place.
Mister, lady.
Can you handle the consequences?
You're so noisy.
Just let us out already!
There is
a way out.
I will let you out if you beat me.
What?
Inspector Im Han-rim,
I'll leave it to you.
- Wait.
- Come on.
- Is it okay for us to...
- Let's go.
Inspector.
I know they're just kids,
but it's still four on one.
Aren't you worried?
You're right. I am worried.
About the four.
Yes.
Just fucking do it.
- That gave me a fright.
- Damn you!
That hurts.
When an inmate uses violence,
the use of violence to subdue them
is justified.
This means that I can
justifiably beat the hell out of you guys.
That stings!
It hurts so much.
Damn you!
If you think it's unfair,
come at me anytime.
Please think it's unfair.
And come at me again.
- Wake-up time is 6:30 a.m.
- Wait.
Roll call will last 30 minutes.
Breakfast will commence at 7:00 a.m.
For the next three hours,
your favorite lesson will take place.
At 13:00, you'll exercise
and get a medical checkup.
At 14:00,
special activities will take place.
Computer classes will be held
after physical training and cleaning.
No yawning.
No balancing pens on your lips.
Right.
Inspector Im Han-rim!
Okay, Deputy Bong.
Report to the yard!
Twenty seconds. How many seconds? Go!
What is SSD?
It's a non-volatile memory storage device.
Inspector Im Han-rim!
Report to the yard!
Left!
You have ten seconds left.
- It's because I can't see!
- Time's up!
Four, three,
two, one, zero. Time's up!
You didn't finish.
Report to the yard!
I want to study.
You must pull them all out by today.
Is this the best you've got?
By today? How can we...
- Hurry up. Do it properly.
- I did this much.
What the hell are you doing right now?
Maintain focus and move forward.
It's so hot.
It's seriously too hot.
My hands hurt.
- Hurry up and move.
- Get the fuck out.
What the fuck are you looking at?
Get out, damn it.
Fuck, that's crazy. It's the red patches.
What the fuck is that?
You know, it's for murderers.
There are loads of them.
- Murder?
- Shit.
That's so fucking scary.
What? Is this place not going your way?
Try and see
if being underage works here too.
I'm also curious.
Hold off on serving!
These juvenile offenders
will be served first, starting today.
What the fuck?
- But I don't mind.
- Go on.
Go ahead.
You go first.
Make way for them over there. Go.
Hurry and line up!
- Hurry up!
- Move.
Hurry up, you fucking bastard.
Hurry up!
Fuck you.
You like sausages?
Sure, take a bunch. Here you go.
Our juvenile offenders
need to eat a lot and grow a lot.
A whole string of Vienna sausages.
Eat a whole row of them.
Gosh, we're all out of sausages.
Fucking hell!
Guys, I hope you understand.
They're juvenile offenders.
The rest of you can have what's left.
- Salad.
- You fucker.
Kimchi. Dried radish. Soup.
- Have some watermelon.
- I said eat up!
- Hey, eat up.
- Eat up!
Fucking hell.
You going to do it?
You do it all, dumbass.
Seriously, why do we have to do this shit?
- Damn it.
- Seriously. Fuck.
These are the dirty dishes.
The prison guard said
there's a lot of grease on them.
So I'd like you to take extra care
when washing them.
But these need to be washed quickly.
The rice often sticks to the dishes.
You've got to clean them thoroughly.
Scraping them works well.
Hurry and get started.
How much longer do we have to stay here?
Quit bawling. You're not a kid.
Does my dad know or not?
Fuck, why haven't I heard from him?
You'd have heard if he knew.
I can't believe Mom and Dad don't know.
And you can believe
they've locked up juveniles?
These bastards would be all fucked
if my dad found out.
That jerk seems like a dumbass too.
Let's tell them.
Let our parents know
we're here.
Well, how?
There must be a fucking way.
They'll only keep piling up.
- Gross.
- Oh my.
- Sorry.
- For fuck's sake!
I'm already pissed off,
you fucking asshole.
Right, guys.
I'm probably much older than you.
So? You want respect from us?
I don't want to give you any.
Hey, he's scared.
So what?
What are you going to fucking do?
Ji-ung.
Hey!
Ji-ung!
Get out!
Fuck you!
Hey, get off each other!
Get out!
What happened?
- What's going on?
- I fell over, sir.
Wasn't Min Ji-ung beating you?
No, sir.
He was actually helping me up.
- No, this asshole--
- Thanks.
I'll return the favor.
No, but...
Min Ji-ung.
That inmate foreman earlier...
You didn't hit him, did you?
Mess with anyone else,
but whatever you do, don't mess with him.
What if I do?
You'll be in serious trouble.
Do you know what kind of person
Kim Su-gyeom is?
He used to be bullied at school.
But he ended up killing the bullies.
Every last one of them.
Get lost, you fucking bastard!
Get lost. I said get lost!
What the fuck? That crazy bastard!
I remember now. It was all over the news.
The bully killer. That's right.
If not, that's fine.
Be sure to stay out of his way.
Damn you.
Not here.
Not here!
A spoon is missing.
We're conducting a body search.
There have been cases
where spoons have been made into weapons
or used for self-harm.
So this is intended as a safety measure.
Start the search.
- It's that bastard!
- Hands on your head!
I saw a spoon in that bastard's pocket.
I'm sure it's a spoon.
Step aside.
Turn around. Hands on your head.
On the left side.
Why would you have...
Trainee, think before you speak
from now on.
Understood?
- Carry on.
- Back to positions.
Turn around.
- Stand against the wall.
- Face forward. Raise your arms.
- Hands on head.
- Eyes ahead.
Stand against the wall.
What are you doing?
Hands on your head.
Out of the way!
I'm already here
serving the maximum possible sentence,
so killing you won't change a thing.
Inmate 1397, get off him!
Get inside!
From now on, this place is hell,
and I'll make sure to find you.
Let's play hide and seek all day long.
Stay still!
There are lots like me here.
Right, guys?
Right? Aren't I right?
Right?
MINISTRY OF EDUCATION
The worst human rights violators!
The ERPB must apologize!
Apologize!
The worst human rights violators!
Hey, he's here!
Minister!
Just a moment, Minister!
- Minister.
- Just stop for a moment!
- Minister!
- Hey!
I said stop!
Hold on, Minister!
- Minister!
- Sir!
- Wait a moment!
- Minister!
- Get out of the way!
Just a moment.
Minister, just a moment.
Is it true
that you sent our children to prison?
Yes, that's right.
How could you send
those young children to prison?
It's a field trip.
They'll end up there eventually.
- What?
- Ridiculous.
- Are you kidding me?
- What nonsense.
How could you?
You didn't even get our permission!
Would you have allowed it if we had asked?
- What?
- You should've at least let us know!
I seriously can't believe this guy.
This is driving me nuts.
Great detail there.
Why didn't you write in detail
what your kids did
and where they were taken
on those protest signs?
- Excuse me?
- Seriously?
I can't believe this.
Goodness, where do you get the nerve?
Excuse me, mister.
I'll do whatever it takes to drag you down
from there, so be ready for it.
Being a minister isn't all that
in this day and age.
Forget it. Don't bother.
Ji-ung's mom, let's go to the press
and bring this to the National Assembly.
- That's perfect.
- Sounds great.
- Let's go!
No need for that.
Come to the children's school tomorrow.
Why? Do we have to come
just because you tell us to?
It will be the last chance
to see your children.
So do as you please.
- What did you say?
- What?
- What do you mean?
- What last chance?
- Wait, come back!
Minister!
Go inside.
- Mom.
- It's Dad. Dad!
- Dad!
- Ji-ung.
Yes, darling.
My goodness, darling.
I'm so upset.
What on earth are you wearing?
Are you crazy?
Excuse me.
Why are our children in this state?
I looked into it a bit,
and you did all sorts of nonsense.
You got them to do the dishes?
Even I don't!
Also, I heard you put them
in the same space as murderers!
As a human, how could you do that?
How could you send children
as young as 14 years old to prison?
Don't you know they're underage?
Now.
Do you know what this is?
What is it?
Tell them. What is it?
They're just diet pills.
The kids asked me
to get them for them, so I did.
What's the problem?
Oh my God.
What are you doing? You must be crazy.
Oh my goodness!
What's the matter?
I swallowed it.
For God's sake.
- Mom! What do I do?
- Oh my!
Why? What's wrong? What?
You said they're diet pills.
Don't you want to lose weight?
What's wrong? Jesus!
Mom, what do I do?
- Mom!
- They're just supplements.
That's enough.
They're supplements?
Shit, I'm fucked.
You seem aware
these pills shouldn't be taken.
- Mom, I nearly got fucked.
- Why? What's wrong?
These pills,
the same shape as the ones he just took,
are designer drugs containing phentermine.
They were feeding them to their friends.
Mom, I really didn't know.
I didn't know what I was doing.
Mom.
He says he didn't know!
They're juvenile offenders for a reason.
Children have no idea
what consequences these things can have.
That's why adults should protect
juvenile offenders.
- Isn't that right? Aren't I right?
- What do kids know?
- They're young.
- Deputy Bong.
Please look here.
This is evidence that they distributed
and sold these drugs to their friends.
They have made
over 50 million won this way.
It's huge, isn't it?
MIN JI-UNG
56,131,893 WON
Juvenile offenders
who should be protected?
Sure.
EVIDENCE OF ASSAULT BY MIN JI-UNG
Then what about the victims here?
Who will protect them?
But they didn't know.
It's not too late to teach them now.
Isn't that right, sir?
- Let's pool money for the settlement.
- Yes, let's.
We'll use it to compensate the victims.
Then we just need to get the petitions
and submit them, don't we?
That's right.
We'll do everything necessary.
- So please go easy on them, sir.
- Just this once...
They're still young children
with their whole lives ahead of them.
Shouldn't they be given a chance, sir?
Shut up!
"You must not harm others."
"You must not hurt others."
These are the things
you should have taught them.
If you couldn't, the school should have.
If the school couldn't,
society should have taught them.
But everyone failed,
so the ERPB had to step in.
At least the ERPB will teach them.
When a person does wrong,
they will be punished!
Perpetrators should never stand taller
than their victims!
That's how they must take responsibility.
Mom, do something.
- Mom?
- Just a moment.
He says he is truly repentant, sir.
I mean, Minister.
I'm sorry.
You won't ever do that again, will you?
- No.
I'm sorry! I'm really sorry!
I won't ever do it again.
I have truly repented, sir.
Please let me off this once.
Please give me another chance.
Please, I beg you.
I really...
- Please.
- Right, you should've repented like this.
I really can't go back. I can't.
But we're not the ones
to forgive you.
You guys...
I will never forgive you.
I never had a single day of peace,
all because of you.
I was so terrified
that I couldn't even breathe.
To me,
school was hell.
From now on, this place is hell,
and I'll make sure to find you.
Let's play hide and seek all day long.
Why should I run away
when you're the ones who did wrong?
I want to go to school too!
I want to graduate too!
What the hell is she saying?
I'm a juvenile offender.
It means I'm allowed to kill you,
fucking bitch!
Ji-ung! Oh my God!
The parents' request
for the release of the children
is hereby denied.
No, wait...
- Hereby denied?
- What do you mean, denied?
What do you mean?
The children will be taken back
to the juvenile prison.
- No.
- What do you mean? No.
- Mister!
- Dad!
No!
Mom! What do I do?
Mom!
Oh no, my baby!
Ji-ung!
My baby! Move aside for a second!
Thank you.
From now on, the ERPB
will educate juvenile offenders.
Seventy years have passed,
yet there has only been empty talk.
The juvenile system hasn't changed,
but crimes have increased.
As a result, innocent students
are still suffering today.
Since someone has to make changes,
the ERPB will step up.
The law may exempt juvenile offenders,
but the education system will not.
Hey, babe!
Fuck.
Get inside.
If you did wrong, you should be punished.
I'm sorry.
Get inside.
Feel the victims' pain.
You'll learn a lot in there.
Get inside.
How long do we have to stay here?
Until you're of age.
After that,
the law will hold you accountable anyway.
Yun-jin, I'm sorry.
Yun-jin!
I'm sorry. I'll never do it again.
Please open the door, Yun-jin.
Yun-jin.
Good work, guys.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Are you sure this is enough?
Yes, sir.
I really missed this.
All right.
Thanks for helping me.
Not at all.
I offered to help in the first place.
But in return,
please promise me one thing.
Please make sure
no one ends up like me again.
I think the ERPB
will be able to manage that.
Can I really drink this?
Hey, juvenile offender.
Yes?
You know the BS gang boss, right?
But I didn't mention that thing.
- Not a single word.
- Well done.
But our boss tends to be quite cautious.
- Do you know what I mean?
- Yes.
Goodbye.
Subtitle translation by: Lisa Kim