The first time I saw a black cat, I thought it was a cat.
I was surprised by the fact that it was a cat.
нить
Yay!
This time, I犯 whereby the cat is always okay.
I found the cat's face where I raised the cat.
So I took a picture with my movement.
The damage was almostore.
An Zhan, do you think this place is familiar?
We were in the Cloud Recesses, and we both were in this kind of position.
It's a fight.
Oh, right, right, right, right.
It's me, Ye Fan Xiaojian, who brought you two to catch the bag.
It's a pity that there's no Tian Zi Xiao now.
Try changing. How can it be the same as before?
An Zhan, thank you.
What do you want?
Thank you for not telling my sister.
This knife is a loss. It's a loss of confidence.
I know. But Lan Zhan, I really didn't repair the evil knife that Xue Chong caused.
I repaired the Ghost Knife.
Ghost Knife?
This is what I got in the last three months.
I got it in the days of the day without a day.
But, in the end, I still have to thank you guys for the Silver Tree.
My Ghost Knife is made of Silver Tree, and it's a curse.
Using a bamboo flute to control everything.
The Ghost Knife is a new kind of knife.
It's like a fire that burns in the fire.
If it's burnt, it will burn to ashes.
The consequences are not good.
I know.
Lan Zhan, I understand your worries.
But I will never have a day that will be like the day of the evil knife.
Do you believe me?
I believe you.
I will help you.
Okay.
At the end of the day, I will surely freezing to ashes.
Who will stop Your Excellency?
REI?
Naw우.
Let me dead.
of my efforts
Of the day
I, Qinghe Nie Mingjue
lead the army as aizing
Attack on not bank
Take the tender determines
And
on charge
Gets killed
Sun早日
Go
Ring Same
хоть오리
꺼
I'll wait for you in Qishan.
Uncle Dong told you to go to Qishan with me.
Kill some people first.
Why didn't you go with them to see the city?
I'm not going to the city to see the city.
It's hot in Huagong.
You like to see the heat the most, right?
Wei Xiu!
You must take care of yourself!
I'll wait for you in the city.
No!
Go!
Don't move!
Master!
Hurry up!
We're going to help the army!
Go!
This method is really useful.
Thank you, Master.
Master!
This time, the attack didn't go well.
The two of them were killed in a flash.
I was wrong.
It seems that the power of the iron is really not as good as the small area.
That's right.
If the enemy attacks on the mountain,
these ghosts will be like the dead body and it will be hard to kill.
Even if they are broken and broken, they can be attacked.
If the iron power is really not so good,
how can we attack the night sky?
That's right.
Even if we have a thousand soldiers,
we can't fight with the dead body.
Since the front wall is not clear,
as far as I can see,
Qin is the king of Qin.
What you mean is that
I entered the night sky alone and killed Wen Ruohan.
If he dies,
the ghosts in his hands will be controlled.
In the end...
Master Nie,
killing Wen Ruohan is easy.
How can you risk your life?
But as the commander,
how can I send my soldiers to the bottom of the world?
If I die,
the Zewu Army will lead the whole army.
Master Nie.
Brother Mingjue.
I have something to tell you.
Please take a look.
This is...
Qi Shan's unyielding map.
How did they do this?
They met the Wen clan's army.
If they were killed by the sword,
if they didn't,
they would be killed by the sword.
If they didn't,
We would be the same.
It seems that Qi Shan's three formation
has expanded the power of the Yin Iron.
How is it, Lan Zhan?
It's not working.
It's been three months.
Master Wei.
What's wrong?
Go back and have a look.
Miss Jiang.
Senior sister.
Anxin.
Senior sister, what's wrong?
Don't cry.
Tell me.
Did that bastard bully you again?
Anxin.
I'm fine.
Let's go.
Master Wei.
You're here.
Tell me what happened.
Master Wei, it's not what you think.
You said you knew.
Tell me.
What can't you say?
It's like we did something
that we can't see in the world.
You...
Master Wei.
Anxin.
It's like this.
Since Miss Jiang's departure,
she has been helping others
and helping others.
Every day,
she will make more soups.
Two bowls of soup
are for two brothers.
You and Master Jiang.
This third bowl...
is for my son.
Nonsense.
It's A Yuan.
Master, it's not like that.
It's Miss Jiang's fault
that she personally gave it to you.
That's why she asked for A Yuan.
She was looking for me at first,
but I think it's not good.
So she gave it to A Yuan.
As long as she secretly put it in your account,
who knows...
Master.
Don't blame Miss Jiang.
But A Yuan clearly told me...
Is it a full-faced and ugly
and unkind confession?
Mianmian, keep it to yourself.
When Miss Jiang came to deliver the soup today,
she and our master had a fight.
I think...
Master Jiang
thought that Miss Jiang was visiting A Yuan.
So he reminded Miss Jiang...
and Miss Jiang...
Master Jiang, you really misunderstood.
Miss Jiang,
since we have already made a engagement,
why do you have to do this?
You think I'm making a engagement?
I sent Miss Jiang to Qinghe
and it was a mission.
Why do you have to come to the battlefield to suffer this?
I'm not coming with you.
I'm not...
I'm asking for A Yuan.
No, I'm not.
I'm not...
Miss Jiang, I'm going to see you.
Don't think that you can just go out
and just do whatever you want.
Some people are in danger
and are more than just a few.
Please, take care.
Take care.
Jin Zixuan,
why do you make me lose my temper?
Master Wei,
actually, my master didn't do anything.
It's a misunderstanding.
Yes, Master Wei.
Yes, it's a misunderstanding.
Please calm down.
Misunderstanding?
Master Wei.
Wei Ying, calm down.
Xichen,
this Qishan Prefecture is designed
to be a secret.
Where did you come from?
Although Qishan is a common thing,
it's not that far away.
The Prefecture is a few months away.
So even if there's a slight difference,
I'm sure it's between the two.
I'm sure it's a secret.
The disciple of the painting is a good person.
He's a good person.
But I've been observing the painting for several days.
I'm sure I lost it.
Otherwise, I wouldn't dare to give it to you.
You haven't told me
what you were thinking
when the cloud was burnt.
Who did you find?
You really thought it through.
That's what you said.
The person who sent the painting
and the person who saved you
is really a good person.
It's not that I don't want to tell you.
It's just that the master is not here yet.
He's hiding his identity.
If I don't pass his time,
I wouldn't dare to reveal his identity.
So please,
don't blame me.
I'm a good person.
How could I blame you?
If that's the case,
I'll believe you.
But
the Qishan Forest is really a secret.
The Wen Zeyi
has three Yin Iron
and three Chu as the Zhen Yan.
It seems that
I'm the only one who can survive.
Even you
have a war in the future.
For everyone,
there's no way back.
That's right.
If that's the case,
we'll both be the ones to fight.
No matter how I kill that Wen Zeyi,
we'll be the ones to
kill Bu Ye Tian.
Get out of the way.
Brother, Zewu Jun,
Mr. Jiang, Mr. Wei.
Wang Ji.
We've encountered
the warm-hearted Kuei Lei
in the journey back.
Now,
we should be at the back.
We'll be catching up soon.
Now,
both the rear soldiers
are chasing the soldiers.
We can't let them
go.
That's why
we have to follow them.
I don't think
they'll find us.
They all have their own way.
Now,
there's only one way to go.
Bu Ye Tian.
I'm afraid these three Kuei Lei
don't just want to kill us,
but also want to
make us
go into Bu Ye Tian.
Wen Ruohan
deliberately led us there.
Brother Mingjue
is heartless.
Now, it's not the time for seven days.
We're going to
climb the mountain with a rash.
I'm afraid it's
the great plan of the Clan Leader Nie.
We have a wolf and a fox now.
I'm afraid we'll be in danger.
Whether we go into Bu Ye Tian
is not our choice.
If that's the case,
we'll be here to fix the border.
We'll kill Bu Ye Tian.
Zewu Jun,
who did the plan of the Qishan
and Bu Zhen?
It's a gift.
Brother.
Wang Ji.
You don't have to
tell me who he is.
He is a friend.
Not a enemy.
Even if he wins today,
we'll go into Bu Ye Tian.
I'm sure he has his reason.
Brother Mingjue.
You said my body
is a demon.
I'm going to show you
the justice today.
How powerful
the power of our demon
is!
You're so strong!
Master Nie.
It's been a long time.
Ye.
It's you.
Master Nie.
I'm not capable.
I need to thank you.
Who?
Wen Xu
killed him.
Yan Yang Hall
is a good show.
Wang Yao.
You've made a good show
by yourself.
You don't want to see it.
Master Wei.
What should we do now?
Are we going to kill them?
Master Nie.
You're so strong!
You've done so much for us.
How many people are there
in this world?
Lan Zhan.
What other ways
can we escape from the heaven?
You.
Master Nie.
Why?
Why is there no movement?
Who is it?
Master Nie.