The Untamed
Episode 15
Yao clan of Pingyang, here to visit Clan Leader Jiang.
- Please get up. - Clan Leader Jiang.
Who did such brutal thing to Clan Leader Yao?
=Clan Leader Yao from Yao clan of Pingyang.
Clan Leader Jiang,
our Yao's disciples
after going through great loss,
finally ran back to Pingyang from Qishan
but still were slaughtered by Wen clan.
We Yao clan now
has been exterminated.
Clan Leader Jiang,
we escaped from Qishan,
so the Wens came for an account
leading to the massacre of Yao clan.
We are the only two left.
Clan leader is severely wounded for protecting us.
We had a narrow escape
but have nowhere else to go.
Clan Leader Jiang, we need your aid.
Please help our Clan Leader.
Dad.
Wen Ruohan has ordered
to track the disciples who escaped from Qishan
and to exterminate their clans
with no exception.
We Yao clan were isolated and weak
and never intended to contend with main clans.
I could never imagine we should be exterminated like this.
You just focus on healing yourself first.
Since you're here,
we Jiang clan of Yunmeng will try our best to protect you.
Thank you very much, Clan Leader Jiang.
You're welcome.
Now. Get a suite tidied
and treat Clan Leader Yao's wounds.
Understood.
Come.
Clan Leader.
Uncle Jiang.
Dad.
Now that the Wens have showed their fangs,
I suppose they won't spare us easily.
For Clan Leader Yao and his follower,
I'm afraid Lotus Cove is not safe either.
I was just pondering over this.
Wen Ruohan is slaughtering all cultivation clans rampantly.
At this moment,
I assume only the Jin clan of Lanling stands a chance.
But the Jin clan...
Uncle Jiang.
Jin Zixuan is somewhat a decent person.
Even if Jin clan were not to rebel against Wen clan officially,
as long as Jin Zixuan is on our side,
I believe that Jin clan
won't sit there and watch the disciples of other clans
fall into Wen clan's hands.
That's right, dad.
For rescuing Xian,
I went to Lanling for reinforcements
with Childe Jin.
Such being the case,
I shall depart tomorrow
to escort Clan Leader Yao to Lanling.
Dad, let me go with you.
No.
Cheng, Xian.
You two shall stay and guard Lotus Cove.
Yes, uncle Jiang.
I'll be away for a few days.
During my absence,
you have to follow
the instructions from Cheng and Xian.
Be diligent. No sloth.
Got it?
Yes, Clan Leader.
Dad, please rest assured.
I'll manage to defend Lotus Cove with all my efforts.
Uncle Jiang, senior sister.
Please come back soon.
Take care along the way.
Got it.
Let's go.
Li.
Li, come here.
As you came to say goodbye this morning,
I brought something for you.
They are refreshments made by grandma Liu.
You can eat some in case you're hungry.
This is the medicine for rheumatism.
If you...
If someone is attacked by his headache again,
tell him to take it.
Thank you, mom, on behalf of my dad.
Don't bother.
I'm thinking for you health.
The journey to Lanling is very dangerous.
Be careful.
Now go.
Dad.
Let's go.
The journey to Lanling is full of threats.
Why didn't dad take us?
Killing the Xuanwu
will be Wen clan's excuse to target at us.
Besides,
if both of us leave,
who's responsible for Lotus Cove.
Take it easy.
Uncle Jiang and senior sister,
they will spend just a few days to get there along the river.
They'll come back safe and sound.
Wen clan is so vicious that
they've even exterminated the minor clan
like Yao clan who had no feud
with them.
How abominable.
Wen clan's being ruthless
and lacks humanity.
It isn't new to us.
But they can even aim at minor clans like Yao.
I'm afraid
a much bloody chaos will be incurred in the cultivation world.
Jiang Cheng.
We should come up with a scheme.
Once Wen clan come at Lotus Cove,
what should we do to cope with that?
How to cope?
I'll kill every last one
of the coming underlings of Wen clan.
What's the matter?
Father.
What happened to you?
Have you got any clue of the whereabouts of Xue Yang?
Father,
I've sent people to search around.
No report yet.
Xue Yang is defiant
and making troubles everywhere.
I'm afraid he has died at the hands of others.
Father, are you all right?
Call Wen Qing here.
I need the acupuncture.
Didn't you send her and her brother
to Yiling?
Shall I call them back?
No.
The cave of the Slaughter Xuanwu in the Muxi Mountain.
You've sent people there.
What did they find?
They found that Xuanwu was already dead.
Dead?
The Slaughter Xuanwu
was the ancient mythic creature tamed by Xue Chonghai.
How could it just die like this?
Yes.
I suppose it must be that
Wei Wuxian and Lan Wangji killed it together.
However I found
there was sign of seal in Xuanwu's heart.
There must be something repressing that beast there.
That's why we haven't noticed it before.
Where is the repressing thing?
Gone.
Gone?
The thing that can repress the Slaughter Xuanwu for a hundred years
can't be ordinary.
Find it out!
Understood.
But father,
have you taken any other clans in Yunmeng into account?
Just kill them
if you want.
Yes, father.
Let's stop here.
We should return.
So early toady?
I've had enough.
Not interesting anymore.
By the way,
who are you that ranked rather low just now?
Just go fetch it with sixth junior brother.
First senior brother.
Why I am always the one to fetch it?
That's not fair.
I didn't want to either.
But madam Yu won't let me go out.
She is home now.
Maybe Jingzhu or Yinzhu is hiding in some corner
spying on me
and is ready to report me at any time.
If I go out,
I'll be lashed by madam Yu
until a layer of my skin fall off.
First senior brother, you fear of nothing
but our ma'am Yu
and dogs.
You!
What are you guys talking about?
Go fetch those arrows now!
Go.
Let's go.
Make it quick.
Jiang Cheng,
uncle Jiang and senior sister have been away for about ten days.
When will they be back?
I received the letter from dad several days ago.
I guess they'll be back soon these days.
I just wonder if we should consult with mom
to send people to greet them.
After such a long time,
I wonder if she's mollified.
Only if I can go out.
Whose kite is this?
It's mine.
How dare you!
Seize him!
First senior brother!
Bad news! First senior brother!
First senior brother! First senior brother!
Sixth junior brother...
He was captured!
By who?
And why?
I don't know!
I don't know why he is captured.
Capture people out of no reason?
Calm down and make it clear.
Just...just now, we went to fetch the kites.
The kite fell over there.
Kinda far.
We went for it
and found dozens of people.
All from Wen clan.
The leader was a young woman.
She was holding a kite
with an arrow.
She asked who owned the kite when she saw us.
Sixth junior brother replied it was his.
The woman got angry,
said "how dare you!"
and seized sixth junior brother.
And then?
We asked for the reason.
She was yelling repeatedly that he was conspiring against them
and ordered her men to seize sixth junior brother.
Kidnapping with no reason.
The Wen clan is going utterly out of control.
Yes. I agree.
The Wens have gone too far.
Quiet.
The Wens are coming.
Don't let them get the goods on us.
I ask you,
was the woman
carrying no sword
and looking flirtatious
with a mole on her face?
- Yes, that's her. - That's her!
Wang Lingjiao.
Wang Lingjiao such a...
What are you shouting about?
Can't I lead a peaceful life for one day?
Mom, the Wens are coming
and captured sixth junior brother.
You yelled so loud.
I already heard it inside.
What is the fuss?
He was captured not killed.
Look at you.
So anxious and resentful, even stomp the ground.
Have you got any air of a future clan leader?
Calm down.
So-called Lotus Cove
is just so so.
Madam Yu,
long time no see.
Lotus Cove is pretty good,
only that the wood is kinda dark.
Not bright.
Madam Yu,
I must say you are an awful host mother
who know little about decoration.
Here,
here,
and here.
If there is some red gauze,
it should look pretty.
Why you seize the disciple of Jiang clan of Yunmeng?
Seize?
You are referring to the one I just caught outside.
It's a long story.
Let's have a good talk.
Where is tea?
There is none,
if you don't serve yourself.
Don't your servants of Jiang clan do their work?
They have much more important work to do.
Doing such serving matter
dosen't need others' help
as a healthy person.
Madam Yu,
this is not good of you Jiang clan.
Servants can interrupt randomly in such public situation.
If it happened in our Wen clan,
such behavior means being slapped in the face.
Jinzhu and Yinzhu are not some normal servants.
They've been serving me
since they were little.
No one can slap them.
No one can and no one dare.
Listen to what you've said, Madam Yu.
In the cultivation clan,
superiors and inferiors must be differentiated
or it will be chaos.
Servants are servants after all.
Right,
servants should act like servants.
However,
why did you seize our disciple of Jiang clan?
Madam Yu,
I advise you to draw a clear boundary with that boy.
He was conspiring against us.
and caught by me on the site.
Conspiring against you?
What can sixth junior brotehr conspire about?
Come,
let's show Madam Yu.
This is the proof.
What kind of proof is this?
It's just a kite with a one-eyed monster on it.
Do you think I'm blind?
Observe it!
What's the color of it?
And what's the shape of the one-eyed monster?
So?
So,
Madam Yu,
what looks round
and golden?
Sun.
So many kinds of kites.
Why did he choose to draw a one-eyed monster?
Why did he choose to make it golden?
Why not other shapes?
Why not other colors?
You want to tell me it's a coincidence?
Impossible.
He meant it.
He shot down the kite
to insinuate he want to shoot down the sun.
His wanting to shoot down the sun
is the biggest disrespect to us Wen clan of Qishan.
Couldn't I say he was conspiring against us?
The kite does look round and golden,
but it is far from the sun.
What's the resemblance?
As you say it,
oranges shouldn't be eaten anymore.
Oranges look golden
and round.
But I remember that you like oranges.
So you came this time
just for a kite?
Of course not.
We came under Childe Wen's orders
to penalize a person.
This guy
back in Mount Muxi,
railed against our Childe and hindered him
when he was fighting a monster
dauntlessly,
which made our Childe tired and distracted
and almost fail.
He even lost his sword.
But our Childe is blessed
to have killed that monster at last
even without a sword.
I, on behalf of our Childe
ask madam Yu to penalize this guy
to set an example to
the other people in Jiang clan.
Mom.
Back off.
This Wei Ying
should be your servant in Jiang clan, right?
Considering Clan Leader Jiang's absence,
I suppose madam Yu can make the judge.
If there is anyone shielding him in your Jiang clan,
I may assume that
those old rumors
are real.
What rumors?
You know that, don't you?
Nothing but
some romantic affairs of Clan Leader Jiang.
You mean...
Mom.
Get aside, Cheng.
Or you'll kneel down too.
Jiang Cheng, stay out of this.
Wei Wuxian!
I've already said it.
You...
You undisciplined bastard.
You're gonna bring Jiang clan a big trouble sooner or later.
Stop!
Please stop, mom.
Jiang Cheng,
get away from him.
Already done?
Or what else?
This is it?
What do you mean?
What class do you think my Purple Lightening is?
Having taken this,
he can't get up until next month.
He'll suffer.
But he will heal one day, won't him?
What on earth do you want?
Madam Yu,
since this is a penalty,
you should let him
remember the lesson
and regret it for the rest of his life
without nerves to do it again.
Just some lashes.
Very soon,
he'll heal and get up fooling around again.
What kind of penalty is that?
Besides, lads at such young age
easily forget the pain once he heals.
This is nothing like penalty.
What do you want then?
Chop off his legs
to let him stay down forever?
For our Childe Wen's mercy,
we won't do brutal things
like chopping off someone's legs.
You need only to chop off his right hand.
That should satisfy Childe Wen.
Chopping off his right hand?
That's right.
Mom.
Mom, please don't.
She didn't tell the truth.
Madam Yu,
you'd better think it over.
We Wen clan of Qishan won't quit
before there is a decent result.
I'll bring back the hand you chop off.
With a result,
you Jiang clan of Yunmeng will be fine.
Or it's not so easy a case
when our Childe come in person.
Jinzhu, Yinzhu.
Close the doors.
Don't let blood be showed to others.
Yes, madam.
Mom.
Mom, mother!
Well then.
If it can bring peace back,
one hand is worthwhile.
Mother.
At the worst I can practice left-hand sword arts from now on.
Madam Yu, I start to adore you.
We'll get along well in the supervisory office
in the future.
Supervisory office?
Yes, the supervisory office.
It's my second errand in Yunmeng.
We Wen clan has newly issued the Supervisory Order.
One supervisory office for every city.
Now I declare
Lotus Cove is the new supervisory office of Wen clan
in Yunmeng.
What supervisory office?
This is my home.
Madam Yu,
I advise you
to discipline your son properly.
For hundreds of years,
all other clans should kneel down before Wen clan.
In the presence of Wen's emissary,
how could you say something like your home?
I thought the Lotus Cove was old
and had some traitors
so you are not equal to it.
However,
I can see you are obedient
and I like your temper.
So I decide to grant you the right...
You reckless mean maid.
You should pick the owner before you kick a dog.
How dare you barge into my house,
and penalize my family member before me.
Who do you think you are?
How can you be so impertinent.
How dare you!
I tell you,
Wen clan of Qishan and Wang clan of Yingchuan
won't spare you!
Shut up!
You mean maid.
We Yu clan of Meishan have existed in cultivation world for hundred years.
Never heard of some Wang clan of Yingchuan.
What filthy gutter did you come from?
Low clan.
Is the whole clan full of low beings like you?
You dared bring up the talk of superiors and inferiors.
Let me tell you what are superiors and inferiors.
I'm superior.
You're inferior.
Do you think you can bury the truth by killing me?
Do you think Childe Wen doesn't know I'm here?
Let me tell you,
Childe Wen will be here soon.
You!
He won't spare any of you!
You're talking like you're sparing us just now.
Do you know I am Childe Wen's people?
I'm closest to him!
If he knows what you did to me,
he will absolutely...
So what?
Chopping off hands or legs?
Or burn down our mansion?
Or send out an army of ten thousand people
to reduce our Lotus Cove into ruins?
Or set up the supervisory office?
Stay away! Stay away!
What do you want?
Stop there!
Wen Zhuliu!
Wen Zhuliu! Save me!
Cores Crusher?!
Purple Spider.
Wen Zhuliu, what are you waiting for?
Kill her! Kill her!
You original name was Zhao Zhuliu, right?
It wasn't Wen.
So desperately want to change your surname.
You guys fell over yourselves to get it.
How can the surname Wen be so precious
that it made you betray your ancestors?
Hilarious.
Just serving my master.
Wen Zhuliu, why are you still talking?
Can't you see the situation I'm in?
Childe Wen sent you to protect me.
This is your way?
You'd better be careful. I'll report you!
Excuse my offence.
Hypocritical.
Jiang Cheng!
Go stop her!
Stop her from setting off the signal!
Watch out! Madam Yu!
Mom!
Come here quickly!
Go!
Cheng.
Thank god, the wound is not severe.
Mom.
What should we do?
What should you do?
Haven't you seen that
they are prepared.
The fight is inevitable today.
Many pursuers will arrive soon.
You go first.
What if uncle Jiang and senior sister...
You shut up!
It's all your
fault.
Mom.
Why do you give me the Purple Lightening?
It's yours now. From now on.
The Purple Lightening has accept you as its master.
Mother.
Don't you go with us?
You damn boy.
Hateful! Extremely!
Look!
Because of you,
what disaster has happened to our clan?
Mother,
don't you go with us?
Mother!
Mother! Mother!
It'll loose where it's safe.
If you encounter any enemy,
Purple Lightening will protect you.
Listen up! Wei Ying!
Protect Jiang Cheng.
With your own life! Got it!
Madam Yu!
Stop wasting time!
Did you understand it or not?
Mother!
Dad... Dad isn't home yet.
There is nothing we couldn't share together!
It's OK even if he doesn't return.
Without him, I'm fine.
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Mother!
Why still bonding!
Why! Why!
Loose it!
Loose it now!
Loose!
- Loose it! - Jiang Cheng!
Listen to me!
Calm down!
Madam versus the Cores Crusher.
It's not a decided battle!
Didn't she
pin down that Wen Zhuliu?
How can I calm down?
How?
Even if Wen Zhuliu is killed,
Wang Lingjiao had set off the signal.
What if Wen Chao
sends an army to besiege our family?
Jiang Cheng!
Look!
It's uncle Jiang and senior sister.
- Uncle Jiang! - Dad!
- Senior sister! - Set us free now!
Let us go back to Lotus Cove!
Uncle Jiang!
- Dad! - Uncle Jiang!
Dad.
It sounds like Xian and Cheng.
- Senior sister! - Dad!
Quickly. Pull up to the boat!
Dad!
Cheng! Ying!
This is...
Uncle Jiang.
- Dad. - What happened?
Why are you bound by the Purple Lightening
sitting here?
Where is your mom?
Why did she bind you?
Dad, set us free!
The Purple Lightening belongs to your mom.
It can recognize owner.
I'm afraid it won't let me...
Dad, sister.
The Wens barged into our house.
Mom quarreled with them
and started to fight with that Cores Crusher.
I fear he would get the upper hand.
And someone just set off the signal.
It won't be long
before more enemies arrive here.
Dad. Let's get back to help her!
Let's get back now. Dad.
Cores Crusher...
Dad. Let's go back now.
- Dad. - Dad!
Listen. All three of you.
Don't turn your direction.
Don't go back to Lotus Cove.
Try to get to Meishan once you land.
Go to your grandmother.
- Dad! - Uncle Jiang! - Dad!
I go back for my wife.
Dad. Let's go back to mom together!
Dad!
You three must be safe and sound.
- Uncle Jiang! - Dad!
- Dad! - If something go wrong with you,
we won't be safe and sound either!
Dad!
Little fool.
Don't cry.
I didn't say that I wouldn't be back.
Dad
Li, don't cry now.
Don't cry now.
- Dad! - Ying.
You must watch out for
Cheng and Li. Always.
- Dad! -Uncle Jiang!
- Dad! - Dad!
- Uncle Jiang! - Dad!
Dad!
Dad! Dad...
- Dad! - Uncle Jiang!
Dad!