The Untamed
Episode 25
Look at your skinny arms and legs.
You seem so weak.
How can you carry a blade or wield a sword in the future?
You have to work out often!
It has to be enhanced that,
your master is the awe-inspiring Clan Leader Jiang.
Understand?
Jiang Cheng, you are just in...
My arrival today
is to send the invitation.
I want to invite you Jiangs to participate in the Crowd Hunt.
Childe Jin even came in person
just for such little things as sending an invitation.
It seems that us Jiang clan of Yunmeng
really has the honor.
This is my mother's order.
She sincerely hopes that Miss Jiang
could also come along to watch the hunt.
With Mrs. Jin's kind invitation,
I
would like to accept the invitation.
That's great!
I mean that
my mother will be so delighted
to see you.
Childe Jin, hence
please forgive us for not seeing you off.
Childe Jin,
haven't you heard it clearly?
Please.
Why you keep looking at me?
Am I that good looking?
So,
do you have any business to talk with me?
By the way, Childe Wei,
with my arrival this time,
my father reminded me to ask you that
when you and Second Childe Lan went for Yin Iron
in the Sunshot Campaign,
you have bound Xue Yang up to Yet Clean Realm.
Now the other three shards have been destroyed.
Childe Wei,
do you know
where is the last one?
I have no idea why Childe Jin asks me this question.
Just answer my question!
Why do you have so many questions?
Childe Jin, are you exercising your authority now?
You!
Childe Wei,
my father needs to assist cultivation clans to investigate Yin Iron.
If you don't want to help, then forget it.
Besides,
At the Sunshot Campaign,
the spiritual power of Stygian Tiger Amulet
has affected many cultivators of ours.
I hope Childe Wei can hand in the Stygian Tiger Amulet
in the Floral Banquet after the Crowd Hunt.
So the cultivators affected can feel relieved.
All people here must know the rules already.
I want to highlight again that
this row of targets
is the first barrier before entering the mountain.
Only participators who hit one of the target
outside the range,
can achieve his entering ticket.
The target has seven circles
which correspond to seven mountain paths.
The closer your arrow hit the center red point,
the easier the way will be.
And this year,
we have designed
a special activity
to delight our guests.
Go!
Hurry up!
If someone stood before the target,
it will be much difficult to hit the target.
Your skills shall be tested then.
Not that difficult at all.
Stand up! Stand still!
Who want to challenge,
just step forward.
I'm waiting to see
who can have a better shoot?
Anyone else?
Lan Zhan,
do me a favor.
What's the matter?
Can I borrow your headband?
Well done! Well done!
Great!
Childe Wei!
Well done!
The opening shooting
is to warm you up.
Of course you all are qualified to participate.
So how about
canceling the opening ceremony
and please start the hunt now.
That's just an opening shooting.
Practice your showy tricks!
Have you just covered your eyes?
How about covering your eyes in the whole hunt
if you are really that capable?
We'll see how capable you are and who's the winner
later in Mount Phoenix.
That's a deal.
Let's go.
Clan Leader! Clan Leader!
What happened?
Just now,
all specters and evil spirits
are like being controlled by someone
and plunged into our meshes themselves.
What happened?
I have told you not to overdo it.
There are set rules in the world.
I hope Childe Wei shall not be so self-centered
that people caring about you are affected by it.
Lan Zhan,
I heard you are tired for amending your family instructions recently
in Cloud Recesses.
I made some progress in composing the music score
and want to share with you
to see how it works.
Lan Wangji,
who do you take me for?
Can't you leave me alone?
I had once taken you as
my whole-life confidant.
Still, I am.
I have guessed that Mrs. Jin
would definitely ask senior sister out alone
with Childe Jin.
This place is dangerous.
There is mucus left by Stature Measuring Snake.
What's it?
A devil snake came from the southern uncivilized region.
It will just lift up its upper body
to compare its length with man's stature.
If it's longer, it will swallow the man.
It may looks scary
but nothing to be afraid at all.
This one has scales on it.
It may be a variation
which is hard to deal with to a common man.
Yet,
in this Crowd Hunt,
all preys are so common
and they can't hurt disciples in Jin clan of Lanling.
It is best that nobody is hurt.
Nobody is hurt?
Then what's the fun in hunting if no one is hurt?
If you come to our personal hunting ground
in Lanling,
you can see many rare preys.
I'm available next month
and I can take you there.
I appreciate your invitation.
Yet,
there is no need.
Why?
Because you dislike watching the hunt?
Then why you come this time?
I was...
I...
Do you dislike watching the hunt
or staying with me?
No.
Not the fact.
I...
Forget it!
Sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
You can interpret it anyway you like.
After all I'm not the one who invites you.
Forget it if you are unwilling to come.
You bastard!
Anyway,
senior sister can learn his real character
and never has any association with him.
Excuse me.
Wait.
Wei Wuxian, why you appear again?
That's my question.
Why you again?
You started the fight without any reason. Are you crazy?
Without any reason?
You are the reason!
Why you stop her angrily after being refused?
If I don't stop her,
shall I leave her alone in this mountain?
Hanguang Jun.
What happened?
Zixuan,
did Wei cause trouble to you again?
Leave it to me.
Wait.
Why?
Want another fight?
Wei,
what do you want?
Why you keep troubling Zixuan?
Who are you?
How dare you, don't know who I am?
Why should I know?
You...
Aunt.
Mother, why you come?
Don't be self-sentimental.
I come here not for you.
Li,
why you look upset?
I appreciate your care,
but I'm fine.
Has my intractable son
bullied you again?
No.
Zixuan. What's wrong with you!
What did you promise to me before leaving?
I...
No matter what
your son has promised to you, Mrs. Jin.
But from today on,
he and my senior sister
no longer has any association.
Wei Wuxian,
my aunt is your senior.
How can you talk in this way!
Aren't you being too proud?
I don't mean to disrespect Mrs. Jin.
But your cousin
has again said harsh words to my senior sister.
If we Jiang clan of Yunmeng can endure it again,
we no longer deserve the name of a gentry family.
Hence how can you say I'm too proud?
You are too proud to know yourself.
Today is a big day for the Crowd Hunt.
You are really the center!
Thirty percent preys have been captured by you.
Aren't you proud of yourself?
Thirty percent?
Hanguang Jun,
you may not know yet.
We were hunting in the hunt ground just now.
After quite a while,
we found it surprisingly
that none of the preys was in the hunt ground.
Yes.
After asking Lianfang Master in the hunt watching stand,
we came to know that
within thirty minutes
with a sound of flute came from Mount Phoenix,
almost all preys
walked into the meshes set by Jiang clan
one by one
to sacrifice themselves.
Wei Wuxian,
you are so selfish
and never think about the others.
Aren't you too proud?
You Jins have said that
in the hunt, capability talks.
Why you betray your own words?
What you practiced is just dirty malign tricks
not your own capability.
You can do more but play your flute.
How can it be called a capability?
I didn't play any dirty tricks.
Why can't it be own capability?
Or you can play the flute?
Let's see anything will follow your sound?
You break rules.
It isn't any better than playing dirty tricks!
Fine.
If I don't know what's called capability,
then please show me yours.
Astonish me please!
You!
It's understandable that you don't know you are wrong.
It's not the first time
that you have broken the rules.
Last time, at the Floral Banquet
and this time in the Crowd Hunt, you never carry your sword.
At such a solemn occasion,
you know nothing of etiquette.
Where do you place us
those who participate together with you?
Lan Zhan, I forgot to thank you
for shielding me from the sword just now.
Thanks!
Jiang clan of Yunmeng
has no better etiquette as this.
They even produce a demonic cultivator.
Zixun!
Family discipline?
Dirty malign tricks?
Wei Ying!
Don't you want to know
why I refuse to carry my sword?
It doesn't matter, even I tell you.
No need to carry my sword, me, Wei Wuxian,
will beat you all
just depending on the dirty malign tricks in your mouth
and leave all of you far behind.
Wei Wuxian,
you are no more than a son of a servant.
Don't be insane!
Wei Ying,
concentrate!
Xian!
Stand behind me.
Senior sister!
Li, don't be angry!
Let them to deal
their business.
Childe Jin,
you have just said
that it's Xian who alone
has taken thirty percent of preys
in Mount Phoenix away.
He broke the rules and was too proud.
I...
I don't know much about this.
It may really cause some troubles for you.
I will apologize to you all for him.
Senior sister!
Lady Jiang is really polite and decent,
and can tell the right and wrong.
What your junior brother has done
is indeed wrong
and caused some troubles.
Yet,
no need to apologize
for the sake of you and Clan Leader Jiang.
After all we Jin clan of Lanling and Jiang clan of Yunmeng
are like brothers.
Yet,
although I haven't participated in the Hunt before,
I do understand
that since ancient time to today,
there isn't a rule in the hunt
to forbid one participator to have too much preys.
You just said that
Xian broke the rule.
I want to ask which rule has Xian just broken?
Lady Jiang,
this may not be right!
Although some rules haven't been written out,
we all learn them in our hearts
very clealy.
Besides,
we've been obey the rules well.
That's right!
There are not much preys in the hunt ground!
No more than five hundred?
How many participators are there?
More than five thousand!
It was a hard competition already!
What's more, he has taken so many preys himself!
For you,
will you agree?
It's not his fault that you can't hunt the preys!
Capability talks in the hunt.
Although Xian took a different method,
he studied it with efforts.
You can't make the judgment
that he practiced the dirty malign tricks,
just because you can't hunt enough preys.
Besides,
let's focus on the hunt
not our family education.
Xian is a disciple of Jiang clan of Yunmeng
who grew up together with me and my brother.
We are like real bother and sister.
You referred to him as a son of a servant casually,
which is unacceptable to me.
Hence,
I hope you Childe Jin Zixun
can apologize to Wei Wuxian from Jiang clan of Yunmeng.
Li,
don't take it seriously.
Relax.
Mrs. Jin,
Xian is my younger brother.
A humiliation to him
is not something trivial to me!
Zixun,
have you gotten it?
Aunt!
- Brother. - Wangji.
Why are you here too?
My friends,
why you all gathered here?
What happened?
Laugh?
How can you still laugh?
Look at the Crow Hunt held by you!
Useless!
Mother, what happened on earth?
What happened?
Well, can't you figure it out yourself?
Aren't you good at judging the situation?
About thirty percent preys have been hunted
in Mount Phoenix.
How many preys are left to us,
the other five thousands participators?
Lianfang Master has prepared to
expand the region of the hunt ground.
Please calm down.
This hunt is just a farce!
Forget it!
I withdraw.
Zixun,
I have made the preparation.
No more than a half hour.
Childe Jin.
Childe Jin, no need to withdraw.
There is no rule left in this hunt anyway.
Why should I wait?
I'll leave first!
Childe Jin! Childe Jin!
Mrs. Jin,
I caused some trouble for you this time.
Li, nothing about you is a trouble to me.
My son has made you upset.
If you are unhappy,
I can beat him for you.
No need to.
Mrs. Jin,
I'll take my way then.
Wait.
Come back to me to tthe hunt watching stand.
Let Zixuan accompany you.
- Zixuan. - No need to.
I...
Wei Wuxian will accompany me.
Li,
you and Wei Wuxian,
a young man and a young woman. It's not proper
for you two to stay alone together often.
Xian is my younger brother.
Li,
your mother is a bosom friend of mine.
Forgive me for saying too much
that you two are no longer children.
If you often stay alone together,
people may make idle talks.
Besides, he has strong wicked energy on him.
He may does something evil.
Take my advice,
stay away from him.
Mrs. Jin,
Xian is my younger brother.
I'll never leave him.
Li,
are you still angry with my son?
If you are angry with him,
I will,
I will teach him a lesson indeed!
Sincerely no need to.
Mrs. Jin,
please don't force him.
No, I didn't.
Mrs. Jin,
I don't want to cause more troubles to Childe Jin.
Farewell.
Farewell. Mrs. Jin.
Li!
Zixuan, hurry up!
Lady Jiang!
Wait, Lady Jiang!
You misunderstood me.
It's not what you thought. Lady Jiang.
Not what you thought!
I wasn't forced by my mother.
Not forced!
Not forced at all!
It's me!
It's me who want to invite you.
I...
Zixuan,
my silly son,
why you run away?
Childe, Childe!
Li, let's go!
Come back with me to Jinlintai.
Later in the Floral Banquet,
I'll ask him to apologize again.
Let's go!
Senior sister!
It's fine, Xianxian!
Fine.
Then,
Mrs. Jin, please take care of my senior sister.
Wei Wuxian.
Jiang Cheng,
you just missed an interesting drama.
What's it?
Forget it!
I'll leave now.
Wei Wuxian, where are you going?
There is a Floral Banquet after the hunt.
Come with me.
I want to walk around the Lanling City.
I may not accompany you.
Lan Zhan,
farewell.
What a mess.
It's not your fault today.
Clan Leader Lan,
I hurried here for seeing rays of swords.
May I ask what happened?
It's better for you to ask your sister in person
at the Floral Banquet.
Yes.
It's not proper for us outsiders to make comments.
Clan Leader Jiang, we'll go there first.
Clan Leader Jiang,
Childe Wei in your clan
is really somebody!
This time, the Lotus Cove really made a hit.
Almost all evil ghost
were summoned into meshes set by Jiangs.
Many cultivators will then become their disciples.
Yes.
What can we do?
We don't have Wei Wuxian anyway.
Having Wei Wuxian is not something beneficial.
I don't want to have someone like him,
who causes trouble to me everyday.
Did you hear
that the treasure of Wei Wuxian
the Stygian Tiger Amulet,
is made of Yin Iron?
Really?
It's the lost one.
I eavesdropped that from Lianfang Master.
Although it's not certain yet,
think of it,
if it is not made of Yin Iron,
how can it be such a coincidence.
When the shard of Yin Iron lost,
Wei Wuxian then has the Stygian Tiger Amulet.
I guess
that the shard must be taken by Wei Wuxian.
You may be right.
Wei Wuxian is too proud of himself!
Anyway all night hunts have the Jiangs
will not have me.
The Jiang clan?
It has nothing to do with them.
To make it frank,
it's all Wei Wuxian.
In the Sunshot Campaign,
they all depended on Wei Wuxian himself.
That's why Jiang clan of Yunmeng has made their reputations.
Forget it! Let's go!
Go!
Stay away, you dirty homeless!
Wangji,
I feel that you are worry about something.
What's it?
Brother,
I...
I want to bring a man to Cloud Recesses.
Bring a man,
to Cloud Recesses?
Bring him back,
and hide him there.
Hide him?
He may be unwilling to go, will he?