Over here -How do I tie this?
Why do you suddenly want to learn kendo?
I need to find a way to calm myself -Because of Yezi?
Zhuxuan talked to me about making you propose after our ceremony
But you didn’t propose
It’s so common. Everything is ready but doesn’t work out in the end
I can understand you being nervous when you are giving the commitment to the one you love
I got nervous too when I proposed to Zhuxuan
I worry if the commitment is not what she wants
You’ve been with Yezi for years. She must can sense it -That’s why I couldn’t say it
If I say it out, everything will be different. What should I do then?
Your biggest problem is the lack of peace in your heart
That’s why you making make a mess of things
Only when you find your inner peace can you see them all clearly and see what you really want
Maybe you are right -Time to practice now
The sword
Right
Let’s begin with 30°’s bow
Now let’s sit on heels
Pet your left leg first. Right
Right
[05. We don’t know it through lifetime. We know it and we can be together for lifetime]
Now let’s welcome first team of competitors up to the stage
What if Xiang Zeyi doesn’t come? -He has to come -What if he doesn’t?
Yezi, Yezi listen. This kind of talent show is so not you, is it?
Why don’t we drop it -What is her? Is getting cold feet her?
Keep it down, I just worry what if -There is no what if -People are watching
It’s Yezi’s decision to make
I am doing it -That’s our girl
Shige (Senior fellow apprentice)
Are you the competitor Xiang Zeyi?
Are you the competitor Yezi?
You can do it
She is going to kill it
Is our knife hidden well? -What do you mean? -Yezi might really kill on stage
Yezi is better than that
If someone turned me down but I have to do the show with him, I’ll definitely sent him to Van Gogh
Now let’s welcome student of 2006, second class of oil paintings, Xiang Zeyi
And student of 2007, class of traditional Chinese painting, Yezi
They are going to sing the song Where The Lost Ones Go for us
Go Yezi
[This moment suddenly feels so familiar]
[Like yesterday and today are playing in the same time]
[My tone of saying it is so like you]
[Isn’t it the evidence of us being in love once]
[I know it needs luck to be spoiled by someone]
[But I still can’t give myself all out]
[I tried my best to change myself for you]
[But I can’t change the chapters that have already been written]
[I thought being with you also counts as forever]
[It’s still like yesterday but yesterday has already been far away]
[But I can still see it when I close my eyes]
[Where]
What’s she doing? -Is she running away?
Shige stop singing, go get her
Isn’t it supposed to be a duet?
Yezi -Sign your name here please. Your partner didn’t do it either
She can’t sing -It was so embarrassing -Tell me about it
What did you just say? -I said. Someone was so embarrassing. She shouldn’t do it if she is not capable
What, Yezi couldn’t sing and now you can’t talk?
Your room is full of cowards -Say it one more time and I’ll tear your tongue apart
Repeat it, I dare you -Let me go -Leave Yezi alone
Coward -You are
Leave Yezi alone -Stop fighting
I am saying it -Say it one more time -Zhuxuan, we’ll see -Cut it out girls
Zhuxuan we’ll see -See what? Say one more word about Yezi I dare you -Cut it out
Listen up Xu Wenjie, leave Yezi alone or I’ll tear your mouth apart
She has left
Is your nose alright?
Is anywhere else hurt?
No
Don’t touch it
Yezi
It’s OK now. It all past
We are here for you
It’s OK
Cry it out
Tomorrow will be another beautiful day
It’ alright. We are all here for you -All here for you
Silly girl
Here, my treasures
Liu, when did you hide them? -You wouldn’t know or they’ll be long gone
Nice
Let’s have a great time together. Let’s all get drunk
Get drunk when we can. Let the horrible day stay in past
OK. To this terrible night
All men can die now -Die
Girls, you are the best -We are the best
I’m telling you
Men are the worst creatures in the world
Yezi, don’t be sad. It’s just a man, nothing important
They don’t know us at all
You know
You are so right
Men are so full of themselves, they don’t get us at all -Agreed
All men can die now -Friends are the best -Yes
Yezi you finally thought it through. I am the best aren’t I?
Drink on our friendship -Cheers
That Xiang Zeyi and that Yuan Lang
And that
You are single
So is she
So these two men, can go f themselves
Let’s make a deal, no one can die first -No one dies
If someone dies, she is going to be a god in her next life
My house dog -Not bad
My dog
Why are you here, it’s so late
Why have you drank that much? -None of your business
Go away, man
You are drunk, aren’t you
You , put her down
Put her down I say
If you are not holding Yezi you know
Liu Xinran
Xiang Zeyi
I don’t like you at all, go away
She’ll be uncomfortable from the drinking
Please remember to give her much warm water, take care of her for me
I can’t stay here for too long
Please help me take care of her
All poured out
Xiang Zeyi
Why did yo turn me down? Why?
I’m leaving -Why are you crying? -You stole my water -Why are you crying
You just hit me you big head
You are both ugly
Can it be my fault?
It’s just the way it is
Why can he hold her but I can’t?
Funny. Is there anyone that I can’t hold?
Why would he hold her?
Why why are you here?
What do you mean?
Now we are even
Wait -What do you want?
How can we be even now? -What are you saying?
I’m saying that this is not my IPod. What you owe me can never be paid back
You just want to act shamelessly again
What if I do?
It’s useless to me since you don’t want it
Then no one shall have it
School hunk, I don’t want to play it with you anymore. I’m leaving
Xiang Zeyi, you scamp
You are mine now I’m telling you, you can’t shake me off
Surprise
What are you doing?
Yezi, our paintings -What -Passed
For real -Very real
Wonderful. Let’s celebrate tonight
Bottoms up
Hang on, time for our hero to make a speech
Thank you all -That’s all?
Boring
Beers are not enough, Zhuzi, two cans for each and we are done
Just two? Yezi you are a boss now but you are still so cheap
Go check inpatient room 302 again later -OK
Why are you here? -You look poor alone working
I thought I’d bring you meals and eat together
You married man have time to eat with me, surprise
She is having a girls’ time at Yezi’s house eating hot pot together
Gathering -Yes -They will drink too much and sleep over at Yezi’s house again
I remember that time in collage, you drank the most
No, Xixi also drank a lot -I
I remember Yezi drank the most. She even lied on the grassland and I had to hold her straight
I remember Li Sen being there at that night
Did anything happen between you two at that night?
Speaking of drinking, I don’t think I’ve drank again since that time in collage
You drank so much that time, and you didn’t even drunk
I used to think that never getting drunk was a good thing
Now it seems not so nice
That night you brought that much beer to my room, I got shocked
After all these years, I’ve meant to ask you what happened that day
There are words holding in your heart for so long that you only have the courage to say them out for just once
Whether the person understands them or not
I was to drunk to remember anything from that day -Really?
You remembered nothing?
Zhuzi was the strangest that night, talking about men were the worst and live long our friendship
Right -It was so not you, Zhuzi -Of course it was me. Friendship matters much to me
Matter much -You reminded me. Zhuxuan was acting very weird that night
Aren’t we here to judge her tonight? Why are you directing at me?
You planned before, didn’t you? -No -I’m just saying
Fine I’ll tell you. It was because of Yuan Lang
Don’t be so impulsive from now on
It stings a bit, hold it
I didn’t mean to, but she crossed the line
All good.
You really need to watch your actions
Got it. Thank you Shige
Right, Shige
I have a gift for you
I got it stained
But I made this myself
You don’t like it, do you?
Just say it, you hate it
Not only you don’t like this, you also don’t like
I won’t give it to you if you don’t like it
I always keep this bracelet in my wallet
Zhuxuan won’t know about this, she is a careless girl
You were the active one
I’ve never seen a girl special like her
She is the first one and the only one that makes my heart beat fast
I can’t hear no more Shige
Just eat
Isn’t it tasty? -I’m chocked -You want me to buy you water?
But whatever, he is mine now anyways. He can’t go anywhere even if he wants to
Zhuxuan, put everything aside. I have to say you are the best in pursuing a guy
Thanks -You are happy enough, with a Daniao willing to do anything for you back home
Don’t mention him, I am upset because of him
No more guys. Just like old times, long live friendship
If we really get each other’s heart
Then even if we’ve missed for millions of times
We will eventually meet again
Won’t we?