Same as before. Old rule
I remember Forever's old rule
Two glasses
Things won't be changed easily
eternity exists
My treat today
[We used to declare that we would never be apart]
Unpleasant smell of love
Sound as if you really know love
For me
Love forces people to change themselves for each other
They suspect and constrain each other
Torture but still can't leave each other
This is what love is like
Better to be free
How is it?
Not good
Unpleasant smell
Unpleasant smell of love
What does it matter?
Unpleasant smell
Why don't you say something?
I'm thinking about my ten crimes
I swear that I will never commit them again
What are you saying?
It's not that serious
I guess it is
Otherwise, why would you ask me out to such a romantic place in school?
There must be something wrong
What do you mean?
Nothing. Nothing
But why do you ask me out?
Stop it
Can't I ask you out though nothing happened?
Of course you can do whatever you like
Even fly up to the sky or jump down into the sea
What happened?
We won't quarrel anymore, ok?
It wasn't a quarrel at all
And a small quarrel is useful for our love
You mean that you enjoy quarreling with me?
It's not what I mean
I mean that even quarrel won't damage our love
Nice word
I will award you for this word
What are you doing here?
Isn't it an award?
I don't mean this
Zhang Daniao, how dare you
You said that we wouldn't quarrel anymore
Except beating you
Zhang Daniao, stay still
No way
Stop
No
What is it?
Is it for me?
Otherwise?
What are you doing?
I'm so happy
So many people here
I have told you that we are doomed to be together
Do you believe it?
Why are you so sure of it?
A gift for me?
Open it
A wallet too?
Look inside
It's too much
I can't take it
I earn it from the competition
I earn money and you spend it
I take the wallet
And you get the money back. It's too much
No way. You are my girlfriend
I earn money and you spend it
It's deal
Then I will pay for our meals henceforward
I keep you as a lover
Ok, you keep me as a lover
Let me see
Why do you keep it in your wallet?
Because I want people to know that I have already got a girlfriend
Then they won't bother me
I know your boyfriend is very excellent
He is tall, handsome, good at singing and has a good temper
People focus on him everywhere
They can't hear us
I want to tell them that I have already got a girlfriend
Then they won't bother us
Right?
You will graduate a year later
And I will work
When I make a million yuan a year
Let's get married
What are you saying?
What?
Get married
It's boring to play basketball with you guys. I'm done
What would you like to drink? My treat
Zeyi seems in a good mood today
It's obviously because of love
It's not his former one
Let me have a look
I warn you
Give it back to me if you want me to help you in a ranked game
Ok, take it back
You value it so much
Is it given by your girlfriend?
Yes, it is
Are you jealous?
What's the big deal to have a girlfriend?
Yeah, it's really a big deal
What are you doing?
You bully the weak and fear the strong
It's Xiang Zeyi that said it
But I dare not beat him
What have you said?
It seems that he has really fallen in love
For real?
Of course
How is it going on?
It's
None of your business
Come on
We just care about you
Why nothing happened?
You have known each other for long
Yezi is my girlfriend
So all of you must respect her
I will fall out with you if you bully her
Bravo
You have already been settled for life
You step into the tomb of love before enjoying the life
You know nothing
Xiang Zeyi, I'm on your side. Give me five
So we should call Yezi Mrs. Xiang, right?
Mrs. Xiang
It sounds good
Good idea
Not bad
I gotta go now
I'm not on your side this time
It's not bad to call Yezi Mrs. Xiang
And no one would dare bully her
What about your girlfriend?
None of your business, ok?
I know you are a coward
Are you looking for a fight?
I can teach you some skills
Get away
Let's go
Are you done here?
Time to go
Zhang Daniao
Get the ball
Go
I find that our department is becoming more and more famous after Xiang Zeyi declaring his love to Yezi
Don't say stupid things
You think you are smarter?
Smarter than you
Mrs. Xiang. Mrs. Xiang
Mrs. Xiang
Nice name. I like it
Where is Zhang Daniao?
He is getting the ball behind
Liu
I tell you two
call her louder
What a fool
Mrs. Xiang. Mrs. Xiang
Yezi gets shy
Mrs. Xiang
You two, bye
Bye, Mrs. Xiang
Bye
Since they have gone away with their boyfriends. I should
You won't leave me
I won't
Let's go
Mrs. Xiang
Don't be angry, Wen
That girl called Yezi doesn't deserve Xiang Zeyi
Wen, we are on your side
You will have Xiang Zeyi back
Let's go
What's wrong?
Explain to me
What's going on with Mrs. Xiang?
What?
I can't hear you. Speak louder
It's just a joke
Don't take it seriously
It's meaningless
Why?
We will be together forever, right?
Listen, you can't get rid of me
You got no face [Means shameless in Chinese]
Such a handsome face
You don't want it?
I don't want it
You want it
I don't
You want this face
It's too ugly
You want it
Forever
How romantic
No wonder Xiang Zeyi is the most handsome boy in Art School
Yezi
You were really moved when hearing it, right?
I feel so touched
Just so so
Look at you
Cherish your luck
Yeah, Zhuzi likes romantic things, but no one satisfies her
When will Yuan Lang do some romantic things to me?
Xu Zhimo said that
A person should once devote all to someone in his or her lifetime
Without expecting anything in return
Even though we may be apart in the future
Don't even expect that you will love me
But I beg I could meet you in the most beautiful years
Lin Sen
Lin Sen, how is it?
It's too disgusting
No, now hear this
Thank god for letting me meet you
I know every day is a new day
Every day is a funny day
Every day with you
Makes me feel more love in life
Tonight I will sleep with my missing for you again
Come to my dream
Hope I could meet you tomorrow
Yuan Lang
Brother
I can't stand it anymore
Or meet you in my dream
But it seems not implicit enough
Let's meet in our dream
This line is better
Give me a pen
What should I write?
It's too disgusting
Wait a minute
Let me think of it
Well, forget it
Done
Lin Sen
What about this one? Listen
I will sleep with my missing for you again
Let's meet in our dream
Yuan Lang
How is it?
Good
Should I add something to my name on the paper?
Zhuzi always adds some emojis to her name when she writes to me
What should I add?
Add a question mark
A question mark?
Question mark
What about a semicolon?
No, semicolon
A dash sigh
What about a pound sign?
Good
Ok, a pound sign
Yeah
Done
Yuan Lang
Why are you here?
It's for you
For me?
Yeah
What is it?
I don't know if it's good enough
Read it later
I gotta go
Bye
You are leaving now?
Today we are gonna talk about colors and composition of a picture
How do we record things that we have observed in our life?
Litterateurs use their pens
And painters use their paintbrushes
They make things all together on a paper
In order to show our life
We know colors very well
We have learnt three-primary colors in elementary school
But now we are in college
Of course three-primary colors are not what we are majored in now
That is
We should learn how to feel it
And know it sensitively
And the learning is all from observing our daily life
Then I have a question for you
Those two students over there
Please answer me
When we get to the college
What is it?
Let me have a look
Give it back to me
That student in red clothes
Please answer me what composition of a picture is
Yeah, it's you
Please
Ok, professor
What is composition of a picture?
It's to composite all things on a picture
Well
Referring to composition of a picture
No matter you work in painting or stage art
As well as dancing and photographing
All of them are concerned with composition of a picture
For example, when we perform the Swan Lake
If alll of us stand on the stage to perform
It will be a mess if we have swans in every corner, right?
So in order to
This is how composition of a picture is like
Ok, class is over today
Thank god for letting me meet you
With you in my life
Everything becomes more beautiful
With you
My life is of new significance
You do a good imitation
I was gooseflesh all over at that time
Yuan Lang
It never rains but it pours
He is stimulated by Xiang Zeyi's declaration of love to you
So what?
I also got something to tell you
Listen
Eat some meat
We will be together forever too
Yuan Lang and Zhuzi
Here, eat some vegetables
It's nutritious
Why do you interrupt me all the time?
I have something to tell you
Can't you just eat your food?
But Yuan Lang
Yezi, Xiang Zeyi
We gotta go now
But I haven't done yet
See you
What is wrong?
Is this how your friend skips out on a bill?
Your friend has gone out with her
It's your friend that forced him out
But he did leave
Ok
We should be sweet
Don't
Sit over there
No
Get away
Why do you drag me out?
I am still hungry
Stop eating
Look what a beautiful view here
Actually you want to stay with me alone, right?
Very well
Xinrang
I want to hold your hands like this forever
Let's have a walk together every day, ok?
We will walk together forever
Xinrang
Do you prefer a girl or a boy?
Our children will be good-looking as you
But if they look like me
Daniao
Actually I not only have romantic thoughts about future
But think more about the reality of life
Nobody knows what we will go through in the future
But I want a planned future
Do you understand?
What are you laughing at?
It's your first time to tell me about your thoughts
No matter what you think of
I will be with you forever
I promise you
I will be with you no matter what happens
My life will be perfect with you in the future
Where have they gone?
They said that they didn't want to bother us
But actually they want to be alone by themselves
And they left so many dishes
I am stuffed
I think that's great
We are alone now
And it's good to have a walk with you after the meal
Yeah
But it's not enough
You should have a walk with me every day
Ok
Forever?
Of course
It seems that everyone is very certain of being together for a lifetime
But a lifetime is too long
Could you insist to it?
Don't be upset
Believe me
Look at me
Let's go
Wait a minute
I tie your shoelaces again
You owe me one more time
Ok, I owe you
Go
You don't remember me?
It's really you
Never expect that you have grown up into such a successful woman
I also didn't expect that I would have a chance to cooperate with you, Mr. Shao
Miss Ye
Do you know why I choose this comic book of yours?
Your recent works are more mature
But I prefer the works during your student time
Because they are purer
I believe that
you are a person that stick to your original will
right?
Anything else I can do with the work?
This time
We will send an excellent manager to in charge with the adaption of this work
He name is Xiang Hui
You can communicate with him if you have any suggestions and ideas
Ok. I gotta go if nothing else
See you
Please
Well
He is also a man that sticks to his original will
You two will have a pleasant corporation
Happy birthday
Do you like it?
Liu, you know that I am quite a straightforward person
I have sent you 999 yuan
Remember to access it
Come on
Happy birthday to you, Liu
Happy birthday
Liu
What happened?
Why are you so quiet?
You got poison with your wine?
Zhang Daniao
What's wrong with you? You are always very active, aren't you?
Why are you so quiet today?
I'm fine
Cheer up, it's your birthday
That's right
Zhang Daniao
Don't annoy Xinrang tonight
It's her birthday. Understand?
Right
My blessing to you just now couldn't express what I feel
I should bless you one more time
My dear Liu
I wish you
Younger and younger
More and more beautiful
And succeed in both job and love
Come on, let's drink
Thank you
Cheers
I'm in
Do I hear you right?
You said thank you to me just now
There must be something wrong today
It's your first time to thank me
You don't like me being kind to you?
Your skin itches? [It means that you like to be hit in Chinese]
Perhaps
I feel so itchy
It's real. I feel itchy everywhere
So itchy
Waiter
I still have some work to do
Enjoy yourselves. I gotta go now
What's the Hurry?
I have got more surprises for you
Stay here
But I really gotta go
You
It's your birthday. Where are you going?
Xinrang
Hands off
Let go. We have already broken up
Xinrang
Yezi, it's only between him and me
Leave us alone
Yeah, it's only between you and him
But what happened?
So many people here
Calm down and have a talk with him
Yeah, don't break up with him thoughtlessly.
Xinrang
You have been with him for a long time
Why can't you have a talk with him?
Calm down. Sit down first
You should leave now
Xinrang
Can't we just have a talk?
I say, leave now
You want me to get away, right?
You really want to break up with me, right?
Ok, I leave
Daniao
Don't be annoyed
Have a seat
What are you staring at?
How annoying
Why do you break up with him suddenly?
What happened?
Tell us if anything happened
Don't bear it by yourself
Has Daniao done anything wrong to you?
Tell me. I hit him for you
Nothing
Then why is that?
I don't want to talk about it now
Give me some time if you are my good friends
Ok?
Ok
You can tell us whenever you like
Don't bear it by yourself
Yezi, thank you for your present
I lost it in the bar?
Yezi
Are you looking for it?
This one is yours
And the other one
You can take it to him, right?