You got up early. Good conditions
People feel good when good things happen -Did you make up?
How is your co-working with Yezi?
Sorry, I shouldn’t bring it up
But by now you should know that paper can’s hold fire for long, she will find out sooner or later
Saying it out can only upset one more person
There are few things we can change
You know, in these years you are the block to yourself. You are the only one that can’t let go
Maybe you are right. But it’s still not time
You know after that thing with Xinran, I finally understand
All woman wants is someone to rely on
They will believe in us as long as we are brave enough to make the decision
Hold it as long as you want, but you have to make the decision someday
Do you think I’m the one that she can rely on?
I wonder where did that Xiang Zeyi go? The one that was brave to love and hate, that didn’t care about others’ thinking?
The further you go, the longer your shadow gets
Can you leave you own shadow?
One more round
[15.The further you go, the longer your shadow gets]
Shao’s invitation of their anniversary party has arrived to our company, are you coming? -Yes
Who is your plus-one? -Who is it?
Xiang Zeyi? -Xiang Hui
You are not getting back together, are you? -Of course not
Xiang Zeyi, I mean Xiang Hui
They say Xiang Hui is already the animate director in Shao’s company
He has operated several big programs and he did very well
He’s got a good reputation in the field
So weird that our big Shige (senior fellow apprentice) has almost turned to a celebrity now
He must’ve gone abroad to study in these disappearing years
That’s why now he is back and becomes the legend in animation
What’s wrong?
Mr.Shao, your new AD is so good. He did well on those programs
Do we have any chance to meet him in person today? -Sure you can see him
They say he is only 30 years old. This young man is great
Where did you get such a talent? -Xing, we don’t ask a hero where he comes from
Ability values the most to me, not other things. Cheers -Cheers
Excuse me for a while
Mr.Shao
You make a great couple -Don’t joke anymore, Mr.Shao
You are the reason that I get to such a great party -Enjoy. Don’t hold tight, I only invited familiars here
I need to borrow Xiang Hui from you, people are curious about him
They can’t wait to meet our Director Xiang -Go ahead
Are you alright by yourself? -Of course
Xing
Is this that AD Mr.Xiang Hui? -We’ve heard so much about you. You look handsome too
Xiang Hui, these two gentlemen are in charge of our later programs
We are depending on them -You are joking Mr.Shao. We can’t do anything without your organization
Cheers
I wish we also have a talent like Mr.Xiang in our company
Mr.XIang feel free to come to me if Mr.Shao is treating you bad
Xing, are you trying to steal my man after minutes you met?
Mr.Xiang is young and talented, every company will love to hire him
Fine, just drink
Gentlemen let’s go meet other clients of other programs -OK -Please
Cheers -Nice to meet you -Nice working with you
Are you not used to the environment inside? -Too many people makes me uncomfortable
So I’m out to get some fresh air -First time when I was in a cocktail party
I was too nervous to even pick up a glass of wine, let alone talking to people
But I looked at your socializing before. You are not that little girl that got too nervous to speak on stage any more
I thought I’d never fit in places like this
Maybe people all grow up and compromise
But I realize that it may be hard to compromise, but you also get something from it
What did you get?
Never getting drunk?
Is this your first time watching me drink?
No. I’ve seen it for many times -Many times
Doctor.Lin
Aunt -Sen come home for dinner tonight
I have a meeting tonight -Do you? Last time you need to work late and this time you have a meeting
Why are you so busy lately? -Yes aunt, I’ve been busy lately -Fine
Remember to come if you have time, I’ll cook what you like for you -OK aunt
Xiang Hui
Mr.Shao
There is something wrong with this storyboard
The client asked to change the story and the colors of clothes in PPM (Pre-production meeting)
Mr.Shao, if we have to change the color, the color of characters won’t match that of backgrounds
So I suggest that we don’t change it. Why don’t we offer our professional thoughts to them?
Why don’t you give me two products, one of your suggestions and one of clients’
I’ll let them to decide
I’ve made the best one, why do you need the other one?
This is what our client asked. If we only present one plan to them,
they’ll think that we are not professional or careful enough
It’s also a challenge to our profession to offer two plans for them to choose
Just do it. I believe you can make it
What’s wrong?
Look for yourself
Is there any problem with them?
Any problem? Do you know how I was yelled at by those people of the publishing house?
Why?
Miss, we promised that new version of story will match their publishing theme of the season
The modern urban style
These, why are you still presenting traditional ones?
What are these?
It’s not we that promised. I said no in that meeting
But you said you’d change something to match their theme, that why I signed that contract
I also said that I’d carry on our studio’s style
You are throwing me under the bus. What do I say to them?
And you just need to change one episode, what’s the big deal?
What’s the big deal? Zhuzi, you do know how much personal style means to us
If we have to change our persistence for market, what’s the point of our studio?
Persistence
When can you be realistic? Throw away your so-called persistence for a while and just live your life now
I’m not saying anything else, Yezi, this month we moved into this new office
I threw up an idealistic exhibition for you. I cannot make ends meet now, my artist
Do you still remember we also have to eat? Our staff are depending on us
Now the publishing house refused our products, you tell me what to do next
Do you know how many people in this world can really make a living on their habits?
You are lucky enough to have this job and make a living
But if we building up this studio is to compromise to reality, I might as well give it all up
Artist are you seriously being mad at me about this?
People say I am careless and can’t measure things, but I am better than some stubborn selfish person
I am stubborn, you rude and reckless person
You are the one to talk. Have you thought about the studio? Have you thought about us?
You will learn about consequences when this studio breaks apart
What’s going on?
Are they fighting again?
It’s more serious than the last ones
Are you just stepping outside?
Take my work or we lose the contract -Why don’t you lose the contract with me too
No one is more important than your so-called persistence -Bosses, can you calm down a little
Take your hand off me -Just talk it through -Sit down -Hang on, we are canceling the contract, who do you pick?
Sit down and talk -Choose your side -Just sit down
Are you two having a divorce? -I’m old enough to be on my own
Even court can’t help you, you have to make it through
Couples always make up. There is nothing that can’t be settled
Fine, I’ll have to live on with what I chose
That attitude is not bad
Let’s call it even now -What to do with you two
Can you talk now?
Tell us, what happened?
If we still can’t present what chief editor Yu asks, we are all done
Tell me about it, my clients in advertising are so much harder to deal with than your editor
But we are running out of time and I worry -Then stop talking and start working
We are all here -Right. Eight hands. Let’s get to work
Come here Xixi
What are you doing standing there? Come back to work now
Take two chairs here, Xixi -Sit -Show me these two drawings -You take this part
That man used to be popular in our college -Really?
How do you know that I live here?
You’ve been ignoring my calls and I can’t see you lately
I am worried about you
Why?
I worry if you are doing well -I’m doing well
So well that I’ve forgotten about where I was for the past years
That thing happened
All because of me
I wanted to help
But you refused to see me
Do you know how that made me feel?
I just want to make up to you
How do you want to help? How do you want to make up to me?
I could’ve had good times with the one I loved
How about now?
I have nothing
I’m living in terror
I’m trying to forget who I am
You have no idea how I made through the past years in there
What about Yezi?
It’s unfair to her -And can this solve anything?
I know it’s too late for me to say or do anything
I just hope you can promise me one thing
What?
Take good care of Yezi for me
Thanks
Xiang Zeyi
I’ve paid for my mistakes
I have nothing to say with you
In fact
My heart breaks seeing you like this
I’ve been loving you for all these years
I’ve given up on pushing relationships with you but really hope that you have a good life
I hope you can start over
OK
Leave
I don't want to see you again
Hello
You are up early
Are you used to the house yet? It belongs to an old friend of mine, he went abroad so you just keep living there
There is no place that I can’t get used to. Thank you Daniao
Brothers don’t say this. BTW don’t forget about Yezi’s exhibition
I know
And you -I know, I’ll keep it a secret
Gotta go, bye