Why would you come here today?
I want to have a drink
Where's your boyfriend?
Obviously there is something wrong between you
I don't understand either
What?
If you were in love with someone
Would you marry him?
This is the only treasure my husband gave me before he died
Before he died?
We were very poor when he was alive
It was hard life
He was always drunk returning home
We quarreled every day
Sometimes we even fought
He was really mean to you
I hated him
But I couldn't leave him
We quarreled and fought for so many years
But one day
he's gone
I found he was all I had
I bought this bar
with money he earned by doing three jobs at a time
and insurance money of his car accident
and also the money I earned all these years
He used to promise me that he would run a bar for me
Now the bar is here
But he could never see it
Yezi
I don't know how to answer your question
It always hurts no matter you get married or not
Because we hope that we could be always same as before
Sometimes we keep our promise
Sometimes when we have a quarrel
we shout, 'don't you remember how nice you were to me before?'
We hope the people we love would never change
But when we shout that out
maybe we are the one that have already changed
Come on
[Who are the one that have already changed?]
[Zeyi, I'm kind of under pressure recently. We should stay cool for a while]
Xiang Zeyi
I have heard that you have broken up with Yezi
What's wrong with you?
I have told you
Yezi needs your company
Your company
Don't you understand?
Xiang Zeyi, say something
Xiang Zeyi
Lin Sen
Chen Yiman
I'm here today
to have a talk with you
Actually I love someone else
And I try to forget her
and start a new life
But I found that I failed to deceive myself
I'm sorry
I want to tell you that
I will ask my father to cancel our engagement
I know it's unfair for you
But I hope you could understand
I'm sorry
Finally I can stop acting like a good girl
Actually I got back home on my father's demand
So?
I want to find my boyfriend
and ruin our engagement by the way
so you have already got a boy friend
When I was a child
My parents divorced
My father then went on abroad
Mother and I lived a hard life at home
At that time, I usually escaped school
That's how I met my boyfriend
And my parents remarried when I was 16 years old
My father then took me abroad
So I had to be apart from him at that time
Actually I don't like this kind of suit
and symphony
I guess you don't like symphony either, right?
You are a nice guy
I lied to you
But you don't even feel mad at me
Tell me
What's she like?
She
Actually she is a girl with nothing special
But it might be the reason why she is special for me
Why you have bought so many stuffs?
So what?
It's too heavy
How is it possible?
Because it's not you to lift them
It's me
I have to rest for a while
Put them away first
No way
Pardon?
Will you put them away or not?
If you cook stewed pork chops for me this evening
I will do it
It depends
Put this one here
You should
put the fruits and vegetables separately
Who is that?
A friend of mine
A friend?
What did you say just now?
I said, you should put the fruits and vegetables separately
Ok
Put this in the refrigerator first
And later the fruits
Do your work first, ok?
Ok
Anything else?
Look at these
Which one would you like to eat?
This
Ok
Hello, Mr. Yuan
This is Renai Hospital
We have already got your report
The shadow on your brain might be a malignant tumor
Please hurry to the hospital to have a treatment
Doctor, at its worst
how long could I live at most?
Possibly
three months
[Better to drink the yoghurt in three days]
[Remember to have a walk sometimes]
Sorry, I'm late, Mr. Jiang
Have a seat
How do you think of that thing I have mentioned last time?
Thank you
Mr. Jiang, are you sure about that?
if you decide on it
Give me a reply as soon as possible
Ok?
Daniao, why are you here?
Why am I here?
Xinrang, tell me who he is
Xinrang, this is
Mr. Jiang, pardon me, let me make an introduction
This is
Liu Xinrang, you are my wife
How could you treat me in this way?
How I treat you?
You wonder how?
Then tell me who he is
Sir, I think there are some misunderstandings
Misunderstandings?
We
Misunderstandings, right?
Misunderstandings
Daniao
It hurts
A sculpture studio?
Yeah, that is it
Xinrang wants to raise money for her studio
So she placed some information about the project on crowdfunding website
I'm just an investor on this project
It's a good thing
Xinrang, why didn't you tell me?
Tell you?
You acted like having explosive once you entered
Have you given me any chances to tell you?
But you could tell me before
Before?
Forget it, nothing
Now that we have cleared things up
I shall leave you two alone
I should go now
I'm sorry, Mr. Jiang
Sorry to cause your misunderstanding, Mr. Zhang
Mr. Jiang, thank you trusting me
Nice working with you
Bye
Bye, Mr. Jiang
You know that we aren't young anymore
So it's risky to start a studio
I want to risk it myself
So how would I tell you about it. Alright
Xinrang, I will always support you
no matter what you do
Really?
Of course
Don't you remember?
I have promised to be your own shooting star
and make all your dreams come true
Let's go to have lunch
Go
You should forgive me
Then what will we eat later? Hot pot, ok?
It's all up to you
Hi
It's 2 o'clock p.m. now
I'm glad to live one day longer
I have thought of recording this video for long
But I didn't figure out what I should say
and I'm bad at explaining myself
It always drives Zhuzi mad
So let me start with ordinary opening remarks
To my family
friends
and someone else
When you watch this video
I have already gone
Hold on, I don't mention your name
It's not because you aren't important to me
but because I don't want to make you feel depressed
As a legal examiner
I saw people died every day
But one day
It happens to me
How should I feel?
I don't know either
Maybe it's how people are like
We always know too little
No more talking about this
I want to say
Lin Sen, you are my best friend
Stop being silent
No women will want a man that doesn't take any actions
You have loved her for long
So you must get her
Otherwise I will look down on you even on the other side of world
Zhuzi
Darling
After I am gone
you should have meals on time
or it will be bad for your stomach
Find a better man
and marry him
He will be a romantic man unlike me
I sometimes even make you annoyed
Darling
You are tolerant and have devoted a lot to our family
And I am a dull man
Thank you for bring me happiness
which avoids me to be a psycho
Thank you for caring about me
It makes me realize what a life should be like
Actually no one wants to die
Me, either
I remember you used to tell me
People are afraid of death
because they don't want to leave people they love behind
All right
I want to tell you that
You don't need to worry about me
No matter where I am
I will be always watching you
Please take care good of yourselves
I'm your good friend
and Zhuzi's husband
Yuan Lang
Sometimes we think that we are tough enough
always wearing a hard armor
to face all hardships in life bravely
But we seem to forget that
the hard armor is not inherent
but a best gift from our beloved
Maybe we are too accustomed to his or her company
So we will feel at a loss when the company is gone
Happiness we have owned now is just a chance from god
It tells us to fight for it bravely
to defend it cautiously
and to love someone with all your strength
Sometimes though we thought it would last forever
it will be just gone in a sudden