Minato-san,
please live with me.
Please let me live in your room
starting today.
Huh?
What does this mean?
What was that about having
no place to go back to?
While my house is being renovated,
my family will temporarily move.
We're moving to a new apartment
but it's cramped.
We don't even have our own rooms,
and we're a big family, so...
So that's how it is.
No!
Why would you choose to live with me?
Even if you're okay, but your family...
All of them approved.
Huh?
Here.
A letter from my mother.
(Dear Minato Akira)
I've told her about you
since the first day we dated.
I've also mentioned
that you saved me when I was drowning,
back when I was young.
The renovation will be
completed by this summer.
I beg you.
Please keep me by your side.
"Minato's Laundromat2"
(Minato)
Excuse me.
Wait!
You'll stay here.
The next room?
Why can't I stay in the same room as you?
No!
Even if you got permission,
we've only been dating
for a short while.
Living together
is 10 years too early!
We've had mutual feelings
for over 10 years.
Go to bed quickly.
You have to get up early.
Goodnight.
Today's breakfast can
be Japanese food, right?
Shin,
you see,
why would you bother...
It's fine.
Whether it's for one person or two,
it's all the same.
Bon appetit.
How is it?
It's delicious.
I'm glad.
Idiot!
Focus on your own meal!
It's because you keep looking away.
Bon appetit.
Well then, I'm off.
Yeah.
Oh, and Minato-san,
Can I...
What?
The spare key.
Don't just casually
mention it like that.
If I have a spare key,
I can prepare breakfast for you,
you can sleep in a little longer.
Oh, I see...
Wait a minute! No!
Listen up!
They said three years for
peaches and chestnuts,
eight years for spare keys.
It's not something
I can easily give you.
Well, it's not like that.
Go on, hurry!
Alright.
This is not good,
this is completely Shin's pace...
- Bon appetit.
How is it?
It's delicious.
Don't make me say it so many times.
Do you intend to
have a meal together everyday?
I'm not done!
The spare key, please.
No.
Please open the door, Minato-san.
If I sleep alone, I'll have bad dreams.
Are you a child?
Go back and sleep alone!
Then the spare key, please.
No way!
This is terrible.
If it's like this
it's meaningless to be
in separate rooms.
Minato-san,
lately, you haven't been looking at me.
That's not true at all.
Is there something you're hiding?
I'm not hiding anything!
Oh, really?
There's no way I could say it...
I'm off.
I love Shin too much
to look into his eyes.
There's no way
I could say something like that!
Ugh!
Draw three connected points.
Four is less than or equal to A,
so the result is less than 13.
Well, that's all for today.
Thank you, everyone.
- Thank you very much.
Yeah.
How's your mock exam preparations?
Do what you need to first,
that should benefit you more
than speaking to me.
I'm cheering for you.
Yeah.
I'll hang up then...
Are you already used to the job?
Yes.
You're in a relationship
with Hanabusa, right?
Yeah,
something like that.
Something like that?
We stay in touch as often as possible.
When we have free time,
we usually spend time together.
A relationship is like that, isn't it?
I think
it varies for each person.
You're right.
Minato-san.
Welcome back, Shin.
What are you doing?
It's almost Tanabata.
This year, I thought everyone
could write their wishes.
Do you want to write?
Yes.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Let me see.
(Wishing that Minato-san will
say he loves me - Katsuki Shintaro)
give me the key - Katsuki Shintaro)
Like hell I'm going
to display this outside!
Give it here!
Why?
There's no reason.
It's fine. Just hang it.
You two are so annoyingly lovey-dovey!
Hanabusa is here?
I've been studying inside all this time.
He says he can't concentrate at home.
Want to write too?
Huh?
Tanabata is coming up soon.
(Hope I can achieve an A grade in the
upcoming mock exam - Hanabusa Asuka)
Wow, Asuka.
That's a good specific wish.
Well, you know...
Hey, Shu-kun.
Huh?
Let's go on a date next time.
Sure.
Huh?
Seriously?!
In exchange for
the result of the next mock exam.
You must achieve an A grade.
The truth is it's a secret.
Huh?
Did you say something?
Let me hang it first.
Good night.
Shin.
I don't need breakfast tomorrow.
Go ahead and eat alone.
Why?
Could it be...
you've grown to dislike my cooking?
Idiot, that's not it.
I have to wake up early and
attend the neighborhood meeting.
I see.
What a relief.
As a substitute,
tomorrow's dinner,
I'll take care of the preparations.
- Huh?
- I mean...
You've been the one to cook every time.
Once in a while, let me do it.
You said you liked them, right?
Hamburgers.
Minato-san...
Look forward to it when you return.
Good night.
Good night, Minato-san.
(Wishing that Minato-san will
say he loves me - Katsuki Shintaro)
Shin...
(Wishing that Minato-san will
give me the key - Katsuki Shintaro)
Thanks for your hard work.
I thought that I would fall.
How heavy.
- Would you like my help?
- It's fine.
Are you okay?
- Oh.
- I'll help.
- Really?
- I'll leave it to you.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
Alright, this should be good.
Shin, welcome back.
Akira.
Akira-chan.
Grandpa!
Grandma!
Shintaro-kun is such a good child!
What's going on?
Geez.
It was really helpful, thank you!
We received a box full of vegetables.
I was wondering what to do with them.
- Right?
- Yes!
I was so happy when Shintaro-kun
offered to help!
I was surprised
when I heard that Shintaro-kun
is your close friend.
Is that so?
I'm glad I got to meet
Minato-san's grandparents.
Akira-chan,
you're lucky to meet
such a wonderful person.
Yeah.
By the way today,
I have something to discuss with you.
Discuss?
Actually...
It's about the demolition
of this apartment.
Demolition?
Yes, this place has become quite old.
We've decided to rebuild
with a new building.
Don't worry.
We've already prepared
a place for you, Akira-chan.
As for Shintaro-kun's place,
if you are fine with it,
why don't the both of
you live there together?
Understood!
Huh?
I'm glad!
It's a spacious house,
so feel free to use it.
Hold on a moment...
By the way, Akira,
when did you become good at cooking?
It's really delicious, yes?
- It's really delicious!
Grandpa, wait...
Minato-san.
Am I really allowed
to live here too?
It can't be helped.
They say the apartment
is going to be demolished.
But it's only for this summer.
Yes. Thank you so much.
Here.
Is this the place?
Yeah.
Grandpa and Grandma lived here before.
It's such a lovely house.
It's perfect for our life cohabitating.
It's room-sharing!
You're just a lodger!
It's not cohabitation!
It's the same, isn't it?
Excuse me.
This is Shin's room.
Thank you very much.
Is this Minato-san's room?
Yeah.
Shin,
since we're staying together,
I have something to tell you.
Yes.
Sit there and listen carefully.
Firstly,
I have allowed you,
Katsuki Shintaro, to live here.
Yes, thank you.
With the condition...
(The cohabitation is until
the renovation is complete)
that it ends
when your house renovation is finished.
Yes, understood.
(The cohabitation is until
the renovation is complete)
And also...
I also want to establish
some rules for our life together.
Rule one.
(House chores will be divided)
House chores will be divided.
Yes. House chores will be divided.
(House chores will be divided)
Rule two.
(Notify in case of being late)
Notify in case of being late.
Yes.
(Notify in case of being late)
Rule three.
(Separate bedrooms)
Separate bedrooms.
Huh?
That's it.
The three rules...
I object!
I'm not a kid anymore!
I also object!
You're not even 18 and acting like this!
Are we going back to that again?
Anyway,
absolutely separate bedrooms!
That's final.
Alright.
Organize the belongings.
Let's clean the house.
Shin,
there's a reward, you know.
A reward?
Yes.
What's this?
- Shin.
- Yes?
What are you doing?
Why are you escaping?
Don't look this way.
It's fine.
One, two.
Carry it properly!
I am carrying it properly.
Place it down.
It's heavy!
Don't come this way!
Shin, don't run away.
- Huh?
- Ahh!
It's dangerous!
Cold!
(The cohabitation is until the renovation
is complete) (House chores will be divided)
(Notify in case of being
late) (Separate bedroom)
Family...
Hey, Asuka.
The mock exam results
are here.
Yeah.
The garden looks much better now.
Yes.
Minato-san,
you've been bitten by mosquitoes here.
You're right.
I thought it was itchy...
It's annoying that they suck your blood.
You're jealous of mosquitoes?
Yes.
I'm the only one allowed to touch you.
How stubborn.
Why don't you look at me?
I haven't received my reward yet.
Idiot.
The spare key that you wanted so much
that you wrote it on a wishing paper!
If you don't want it, I'll keep it.
I want it!
Don't lose it.
What's wrong?
I...
am so happy.
So I'm looking for words
to convey this feeling.
It can't be helped.
Alright.
I'm so sweaty.
Shin.
Go take a bath.
Are you seducing me?
No!
Geez!
This summer
seems much more hotter.
- You'll be bitten by a mosquito.
- Quiet you.
Minato Shouji Coin Laundry.
Please take care of us next week too.
Please go inside.
Why?
I will use the key
and say "I'm back"
(Next Episode)
There's a festival in the market area.
(summer festival date in Yukata!)
Want to go together?
They're all cute.
(Different love styles)
We are dating.
You didn't need to pull back.
Why?
You don't understand my feelings.
We are dating.
Do you actually like me?