♫ Through the crowded, bustling streets ♫
♫ Who will I say goodnight to? ♫
♫ The vulnerability I long to embrace ♫
♫ Is buried deep inside ♫
♫ Under the moon's radiant glow, dreams surge and swell ♫
♫ Waiting for a reason to run wild ♫
♫ Can you walk with me for a while without saying a word? ♫
♫ Follow the neon lights into the night ♫
♫ I try to find you every night ♫
♫ What must I do to see through that distant line? ♫
♫ I want to feel the wind full force ♫
♫ My lonely soul begins to shake ♫
♫ What can we trust to forever endure? ♫
♫ I want to bring my freedom forth, and take your hand ♫
♫ When the warmth finally seeps into every memory's corner ♫
♫ The past was never wrong, having us is enough forever ♫
[Breeze by the Sea]
Remember, you need to say 20 lines to your dad.
Let's go.
Didn't you have something to say?
What do you want to say?
Is your allowance not enough?
From now on, don't help me anymore.
There's no need to wash my clothes or backpack.
There's no need to wake me up in the morning.
There's no need to make lunch for me.
Yue Shan can't finish her food, so she will share it with me.
From now on, I'll sweep the floor and take out the trash.
I'll also wash all the clothes.
You need to prepare for college, so leave these to me.
When I go to college, I'll need to take care of myself, too.
If I don't train myself now, who will train me later?
You also don't need to worry if I'm studying.
I have my own schedule every day.
If I don't get into a good college,
I'll burn incense and apologize to our ancestors myself.
I won't buy plane tickets to Taipei anymore
since I'll be there when I go to college.
That's all.
Is that all?
That's only 18 lines.
It isn't enough.
What else should I say?
I don't know.
I can't think of anything right now.
I'll say it when I think of it.
That's 20 lines.
Cai Jing Liang, you cheated.
I didn't.
How did I cheat? I said it just like that.
Wash clothes.
He will help me sweep the floor.
Sweeping the floor himself.
[AKIO]
I was quite reluctant at first.
However, after thinking about it,
I know it's all because of you
that Cai Jing Liang started talking to me.
I think this is more important than anything else.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
What's wrong?
I heard from You Cai that he was very touched
because you helped him accomplish something challenging.
Are you...
praising me?
So, how did you do it?
Nothing much, I just scared the kid a little.
Jing Liang isn't that easy to scare.
That's why I got this.
[Memories of Kinmen]
"Memories of Kinmen".
I see.
It comes with a signature.
I have 10 copies at home. Do you want one?
I see.
And...
this.
♫ When you miss me ♫
♫ Don't think that I'm not missing you ♫
♫ When you forget me ♫
♫ Don't think that I've forgotten you ♫
♫ Whether I stay or go ♫
♫ Love always holds onto your sorrows ♫
♫ Love spreads your hands wide ♫
Grandma, what are we making today?
Let me help you.
Keep your voice down.
He's still sleeping.
Can you take out the boiled eggs?
He should be awake by now.
Maybe he's too tired.
He probably didn't sleep until 3 A.M. last night.
Gosh, you know that, too?
Take the cherry tomatoes out of the fridge.
Okay.
Besides boiled eggs,
I'm not sure what else he likes to eat.
I prepared these,
but I don't know if they'll suit his taste.
It's okay. If he doesn't eat them, I will.
I'll finish them all.
Can you eat that much?
Sure. I'll finish them within three days.
Actually, he's not as scary as Xiao Guang said.
Yes, except for being a bit temperamental, picky,
and talking like...
He does have a bit of kindness.
- Kindness?
- Yes.
I don't think he's that hard to get along with.
- I'm so hungry.
- Right...
Sit down and eat.
You came out without making a sound.
I don't know if they suit your taste.
I'll pour you some water.
Fried dough sticks.
The ones in Kinmen are especially delicious.
Try some.
Think carefully.
These are fried stuff.
Gotta pee...
Sorry.
Sitting down to pee really keeps it from splashing everywhere.
You can use it.
I threw all the dirty clothes into the washing machine.
I also put an air freshener in the bathroom.
You can use the toilet with peace of mind now.
Actually,
you don't have to force yourself
to make such changes for me.
Hai Nuo already told me.
She said these are all things that matter to you.
I thought about it all night.
Since we're going to live together,
we have to make some changes for each other.
If you change for someone else, you're no longer yourself.
You'll live a hard life.
Didn't you always say that we should see more of the world out there?
You can still go see it.
Changing myself doesn't affect you, right?
Go ahead and use the toilet in peace.
- I'll go to the room.
- Go.
Okay, open wide.
You have a bit of a sore throat.
Please wait outside. I'll prescribe some medicine for you.
- Okay, thank you.
- Okay.
Dr. Chen.
She's the last patient, right?
Yes.
So, you're free after lunch?
Yes. What's up?
I want to take you somewhere.
I found out something.
Alberta province is eight hours behind us.
Eight hours behind. We need to remember that.
What time should we video call in the future?
Incredible.
The temperature there is much colder than ours.
It takes a whole day to fly there.
If we visit him in the future,
just taking plane alone will make our bones fall apart.
Come on.
Da Wu has been working so hard and he finally got into this hospital.
He didn't even complain, so why are you?
Did you prepare his favorite peanut brittle?
I already bought it.
Mr. Chen from Shengzu knows Da Wu loves it,
so he made it fresh just for him.
By the way, go to the post office tomorrow and withdraw our fixed deposit.
Why?
We need to transfer the money to Da Wu.
That way, he won't have to worry about running out of money.
He can focus better on his medical research.
It'll set a stronger foundation for his future.
But you should see if your son will even accept it.
Why do you care if he accepts it?
Just transfer it over.
That's a good idea.
He didn't take our money when he was studying abroad.
This time, we'll just transfer it directly to him.
After he leaves this time,
I wonder when we'll see him again.
You said you were going to see a friend.
Who is it?
You haven't met her before.
She left Kinmen during middle school and went to the UK.
She's an artist.
She won quite a few awards abroad.
She just moved back to Kinmen recently.
The door is over there.
I didn't know Kinmen had places like this.
Not bad.
And your work
is hard to describe.
Thank you.
Did you take that as a compliment?
You've been staring at my paintings for so long.
It shows you felt something.
That's the best compliment for an artist.
Artists are quite self-assured, right?
However, going with the flow is mediocrity.
What's important is how we carve out our own shape
in the course of history.
Have you achieved that?
Have you?
Here we are.
Xu Man, we're here.
Hey.
He's my customer.
Sorry, you're...
Bai Yin Mo.
I know him. He's our tenant.
I'd also like to introduce you.
- This is Chen...
- Dr. Chen.
Yes, Dr. Chen, Chen Da Wu.
Do you all know each other?
Kinmen is small, so everyone knows each other.
So, how does this painting make you feel?
How does it make me feel?
- Do you want to move these?
- Yes.
Okay.
I feel...
A blue sky, white clouds, ocean, and seaweed.
- Seaweed?
- Yes, seaweed.
A seemingly calm world with a feeling of entanglement
and struggle inside.
Interesting.
So, how's the weather in Kinmen?
It's pretty nice, right?
Mr. Bai, haven't you left yet?
Are you planning to stick around and help out?
No, I see you three are doing fine.
I'd better not get in the way.
Right, superstars think differently from most people.
Hai Nuo means you're not needed here.
Leave it to me. You can head back.
Hey, great artist.
Is there anything I can help you with?
- My name is Xu Man.
- Sorry, Xu Man.
Is there anything else you need help with?
Is there any meaning behind such an arrangement?
No meaning at all.
Da Wu, can you do me a favor?
When I cue you in a bit,
can you drive over these paintings with your car?
Why would you want to drive over these paintings?
Aren't these paintings your hard work?
They're more like a burden.
Okay.
Though I'm not sure what it means,
dealing with death is my profession anyway.
I'll give them a proper send-off.
Weren't you asking me if I had achieved it?
Don't tell me you're going to destroy these paintings
because of what I said?
You seem to think quite highly of yourself.
Didn't you say before
that someone was willing to pay a high price for these paintings?
After winning the awards, I got lost.
I started creating based on what others found beautiful.
That made me lose the original purpose of painting.
One of the reasons I came back to Kinmen
was to find myself again.
We really burned everything completely.
Where are the two of them?
They're outside.
It seems like what you just said
had quite an impact on them.
One of them seems to be carrying
a heavy burden whether because of life or work.
The other one's burden
is probably the pressure from his dad.
How about this?
Let's use your painting to lighten up the mood.
How do you both feel when you look at this painting?
It feels like muscle tissues and a colorful CT scan.
That sounds like what a doctor would say.
The blue muscle tissue means it's poisoned.
Come on. Imagination.
Your turn.
Isn't it just waves,
a blue sky, and clouds?
There's a sprinkle of sunshine.
It looks like a peaceful sea, but beneath the surface,
there's some turbulence.
That sounds a lot like what you just said.
No way.
Of course, you can't see it on the surface.
You might have to look at the back.
- The back?
- Is there something on the back?
I was making a metaphor.
- I see.
- There's really something on the back.
For my dear friend, Nuo Nuo.
Me?
It's for you.
This painting is how I feel about you.
Thank you, Xu Man.
I was worried you were going to burn this painting, too.
I wouldn't have the heart to.
How about a drink, everyone?
Anything in particular you'd like to drink?
How about you make them a special Kaoliang cocktail?
Sure.
We're closing soon, so we can't let you stay long.
Otherwise, it'll affect our work.
She's inside. Feel free to look for her.
Thank you.
Grandma, have you seen Mr. Bai's shirt?
I already washed it and hung it out to dry.
Why did you wash it again?
There were still some stains on it.
The washing machine didn't wash it clean.
I've got some clothes here with stains
and some pants that need mending.
Make sure you find time to take care of them.
Okay.
Mr. Bai might be busy,
- So, he's not good at...
- He can't take care of himself.
Why does my face hurt so much?
You're awake.
Hey, last night...
Men often tend to avoid taking responsibility when they drink too much.
I didn't do anything to you last night, did I?
You're so single-minded in your thinking.
Why...
Why does my face hurt so much?
I punched you last night. Don't you remember?
You guys fought last night.
Do you plan to continue this morning?
I blacked out last night.
Why did we fight?
Ask Li Hai Nuo.
Ask Li Hai Nuo?
What did you do to her last night?
What? Do you like her?
- It's none of your business.
- Fine.
If you won't admit it, I won't tell you what happened last night.
Keep talking like that and you'll really get punched.
Don't block the way, okay?
- What? Do you want to fight?
- Do you want to get hit?
- You have a bad breath.
- Come on. Hit me now.
- It stinks. Stop talking.
- Come on.
- Just do it.
- Shut up.
- Go sit on the couch.
- Don't be too...
I'm definitely going to hit you.
- You stink.
- You're screwed.
Today, it's either me or him.
How boring. Do I really have to film this?
Sit down.
What are you doing?
So, what are you competing in?
Wait. I'm not ready.
- What?
- Come on.
Is that all you got?
- Or should we play rock paper scissors?
- Come on.
Sure.
Rock paper scissors.
You should clip his face, not his ear.
Should I put one more?
Rock paper scissors.
Wait, I need to use the toilet.
Me, too.
That's Xu Man's room.
Where are you two going?
Nuo Nuo, just leave them be.
My goodness. Are you guys okay?
You're so ugly.
No, you're ugly.
Idiot.
I'm heading back.
Yes, me, too.
Sit down.
Up next is a little surprise.
Please take a look.
Let me tell you.
Back when I was a kid, my dad and I were really close.
He was really funny.
But then there was a shipwreck
and his best friends died.
That was Hai Nuo's parents.
Ever since that incident,
he started drinking a lot
and completely changed.
He became very strict.
He was very strict with me.
How strict?
Da Wu.
What about your parents?
What does that mean?
Are they gone?
Pretty much.
Sorry.
My dad...
My dad really loved me.
Then...
he had an accident
and passed away.
He left first.
Later,
my mom got a boyfriend
and treated me like an ATM.
Do you know what I mean? An ATM.
An ATM machine?
Does that mean the money you earned went to them?
That guy...
That guy lost all the money.
Do you know how much...
Do you know how many TVs
you could buy with that money?
TVs.
Why do you want to buy so many TVs?
It's just a metaphor.
Okay.
And then...
Right.
All right. It's fine now.
I'll save up money from now on.
I'll save what I earn and buy you a lot of TVs.
As many as you want, all right?
I'll buy you tons of TVs.
- Bros forever.
Happy ending.
Bros forever.
Last night...
We both...
drank too much.
Nothing happened.
Erase it.
Last night never happened.
If you tell anyone, you're dead.
You'd better keep your mouth shut.
[Li Shu Man sent a photo]
[You are now friends with Li Hai Nuo]
[You are now friends with Xu Nuo]
[Good morning]
Stickers from elders.
Not replying is rude.
But if I reply, it will never end.
Why do you look so happy?
Has someone replied to your stickers?
Let's see if you'll still laugh at my stickers.
That person is pretty kindhearted.
It's Mr. Bai.
I take back what I said.
I haven't seen you drink this much since high school.
It was a mistake.
Da Wu.
I heard from Mr. Hui that you bought a car.
- Did he tell you?
- There are no secrets in Sea Breeze Village, okay?
Then my dad will know soon.
Why are you afraid of your dad finding out?
Furthermore, that car is...
That car is going to be my mobile clinic.
So, you're staying in Kinmen?
What's wrong? Don't you want me here?
No, it's just that
I thought you were doing well abroad.
Why do you suddenly come back?
Don't ask about grown-up stuff, brat.
I'm already 25
and I'm a certified nurse.
Shouldn't I know more about my new boss?
Saving lives is a doctor's duty.
So, what's the difference where I save them?
Da Wu, you know what I mean.
Little shadow, you're such a nag.
I'm hungover. Just let me rest for a bit.
All right. Get some rest then.
You're back.
Bros forever.
Get me a glass of water.
Sure.
Xu Man already deleted the video you shot yesterday.
Shouldn't you delete it, too?
We're in Kinmen.
Relax, okay?
I don't get what that means.
Delete it.
No way. The weather is so nice today.
Why worry about something so trivial?
Fine.
If you don't delete it, I'll just keep bugging you.
All right. Go ahead.
Ms. Li, could you please delete the video?
Or else, I'll keep talking like this and annoy you.
Are you mimicking me?
Can't you tell? It looks so bad.
You're even worse at it than I am. No way.
That's totally your look.
Hurry up.
Here you go.
I already deleted it.
Right. I almost forgot to give you this.
A package from Hong Xiao Guang.
Yin Mo, the reality show proposal is out.
I know you don't like digital files,
so I printed a hard copy for you.
Lily asked you to take a look.
About the tape you wanted, I really looked everywhere,
but I just can't find it.
I'm sorry.
[Okay, thank you for your hard work.]
[Thank you for your hard work]
Boss sent me a sticker for the first time.
Have you sobered up?
I'm still a bit hungover.
Why are you here?
Right. You blacked out.
Xu Man.
I'm really sorry.
Did I ask you to teach me how to paint yesterday?
Then why aren't we doing it in the studio?
Outdoor sketching?
I get it.
You invited Bai Yin Mo, too.
You want to paint our duel from last night, right?
Come on. Give me a hint.
I also want to contribute to Kinmen's healthcare.
Did I invite you to paint my medical car?
As I mentioned, Da Wu has been abroad for so many years.
I'm really glad he's back to visit us.
Da Wu is really impressive.
He's so well-educated.
It's not easy.
Exactly.
If any of you have any health issues,
make sure to consult him now while he's here.
Make the most of this quality resource.
Our son is truly exceptional.
He's indeed exceptional.
Didn't I have a bunch of scrapped old cars?
He said he plans to turn them into medical cars.
I saw how dedicated he was,
so I sold it to him at a special price.
Medical cars?
Did he say how long he's staying?
He didn't mention any specific time.
Your son is as humble as you are.
He said he can't treat everyone equally.
Instead of treating strangers,
he'd rather take care of those who watched him grow up.
What?
Well...
Does that mean he isn't leaving?
Maybe.
If only my sons were as exceptional as yours,
that would be wonderful.
Whenever I think of my useless kids...
What do you think?
I don't know.
Didn't we already divide the work?
I'll do the fixing and you focus on making it look nice.
Okay.
Hello.
Okay, I got it.
Sorry. I suddenly have something to deal with.
- I'll leave this to you for now.
- No problem.
You weren't contributing much anyway.
Okay. Thank you.
Hold on.
Wipe your face.
Thank you.
Son.
Your dad has been good.
He said he'd drink less once you got back.
He really hasn't had a drink.
Son, here's the thing.
Your dad thought you'd be going abroad soon.
But then you bought that car.
He feels like he only hears about your plans
from other people.
Honey, say something.
Are you too lazy to talk?
Why don't you text me and I'll speak for you?
My stomach hurts so bad. I can't take it.
Without me around, let's see how long you'll keep up this silent drama.
Dad.
I've decided to stay in Kinmen as a doctor.
For now, I'll spend my mornings at Dr. Liu's clinic.
In the afternoon, I'll run a mobile clinic.
I know the elderly are afraid of seeing doctors.
Most of them wait until it's serious before seeking help.
So, I want to reach out first.
Even though there's a hospital in Kinmen now,
even with you as an additional doctor,
if someone falls seriously ill,
that person will still need to be transferred out.
It might not matter much to others.
However, it makes a world of difference to me.
I don't want them to have to be transferred every time.
If we reach out first,
prevention is way better than cure.
We can also do more health education.
Wouldn't that reduce a lot of unnecessary tragedies?
That's what public health centers do.
As the village chief, I also do that.
You've studied so much but choose to stay here.
Isn't that a waste of your talent?
I'm treating and saving people here.
I have many friends and family here.
Why I can't take care of the people who are close to me?
Yes, exactly.
Honey, I think Da Wu makes sense.
We also have aches and pains.
We need Da Wu, too.
What are you talking about?
I'm perfectly healthy.
I don't need him to take care of me.
Besides, you spent so many years working hard abroad
to finally get your medical license.
Now, you're telling me you aren't going back?
Was all the worrying your mom and I did for nothing?
No, all that experience is still useful.
I gained a lot of clinical experience abroad.
- These things...
- Come on.
Can the money you make here compare to what you'd earn there?
If you're going to do this,
why did you even study abroad in the first place?
Wouldn't it be nice if your son wanted to stay close and take care of you?
When I went out today,
everyone was so happy to hear that Da Wu is staying.
They all said as we get older, we need our kids nearby.
They're happy, but I'm not!
Don't wait for me for dinner!
Son.
You know your dad's temper.
Call him later or send him a text.
I've got things to do.
I won't join for dinner.
- Your fried octopus mouth.
- All right.
- The spicy stinky tofu is ready.
- Enjoy.
Coming.
Are you all right?
Go rinse it off. I'll take over.
I'm fine.
I got it.
You go handle your stuff.
I'm good.
- Stinky tofu.
- Thank you, miss.
- Please enjoy.
- Okay, thank you.
Okay, coming.
- How much is it?
- The total is 1,200.
Stop working.
It has been a long day. You must be tired.
Sit down and eat.
It's your favorite stir-fried oysters.
Today,
when I saw you working so hard even after getting burned,
I really felt that...
If we work hard for a few more years,
I can grow this business and hire a bunch of staff,
then you could just sit back and comfortably collect the money.
What do you think?
Maybe...
I don't want to work hard anymore.
It's okay.
I'll post a job advertisement online tomorrow.
I'll handle it right now.
Hey, Da Wu.
I want to ask you how to post a job vacancy online.
All right, see you in a bit.
It's all set.
Actually, there's something else I want to say.
What is it?
I made you some hangover soup. Hurry up and drink it.
Didn't I tell you I didn't drink?
Well...
It's all right.
Since the soup is already hot,
you should drink it while it's warm.
Drink it now.
Sit there and drink it.
Quick, drink it.
Da Wu said he'll be really busy today.
He isn't coming home tonight.
He isn't coming home tonight?
Tell him that if he doesn't come home tonight,
then don't come back ever.
Gosh.
Honey.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
It's really beautiful.
Thank you.
I'm leaving this part for Li Hai Nuo.
Let her take the lead with you.
Her paintings give people a sense of joy and relaxation.
I hope everyone you care about who sees it
will feel the same way.
I'm off now.
Bye then.
Xu Man.
Thank you.