My name is Cupid.
My job is to help people fall in love.
If I’m not this desperate, I wouldn’t call you.
Please don’t ask me why I need the money for.
You said I get used to having a partner.
It’s true.
You kept denying that you care about her.
I don’t care about her.
I still insist on that.
But I like her.
There’s only one person who can be my partner.
I will do everything to get my partner back.
[Cherry 461 Company]
Next.
Bananas.
Flip-flops.
Next.
A pineapple.
Three salted fish.
[You are so pretty.]
[Do you have a boyfriend?]
[Can I ask you out?]
I’m selling goods.
Why are you asking me about my love life?
I’ll say it only once.
My ideal guy?
He must be handsome, rich, and nice.
It’s hard to find a guy who has all three qualities.
But it’s okay.
Why do I need to date only one guy?
I’ll show you my boyfriends.
My first boyfriend is a hunk.
My second boyfriend.
He’s filthy rich.
My third boyfriend.
He’s so sweet.
But if you like me and have all three qualities,
you can hit me up.
I don’t mind having one more boyfriend.
If you don’t have them, don’t bother me.
It’s annoying. Let’s get back to our business.
Come on.
A cleaver.
Darn.
A coaster.
An empty box.
[Tee helps me carry my things today.]
[I just realized that he’s such a gentleman.]
[He also helps me.]
[He helps me too. He’s so sweet.]
Sorry, everyone.
I’m on vacation.
Our company is having a big problem.
There’s a company that helps people find love.
It interferes with our business.
My name is Cupid.
I work at Destiny.
My job is to help people fall in love.
Destiny not only uses marketing strategies
to compete with us,
but also helps the couples we split up reconcile.
We needed to refund several clients.
They position themselves as our enemy.
How can you still be in a good mood?
Especially you, Nut!
How can you do this to me?
What?
That.
Huh?
Don’t you know I’m sensitive right now?
I’m going to throw it away now.
It’s too late.
I’m going to throw it away now, eight words.
I’ll cut your pay for eight days.
What?!
Sorry.
Jued.
Yes?
I don’t know and have never heard of Destiny.
I just want to know how Tee is doing
when he works with Team A.
Oh?
He’s good.
He’s better than I thought.
I agree.
Tee is ready to run Team C.
No, I think he should be trained with us for a while.
Didn’t you say he’s done well?
Why does he need more training?
He can be better.
Enough.
That’s your opinion.
Let’s ask him what he thinks.
Boss, where should I sit?
Tee, you can use my chair.
It’s okay.
Can I borrow one of your chairs?
Can I share your desk?
Sure.
You can use this desk.
Get ready for the briefing.
Is the fruit basket for me?
No.
Then who is it for?
It’s none of your business.
The fruit basket is for you.
First of all, I want to apologize to you.
I’m not good at technology.
I got this black card from the bank,
but I don’t know how to use it.
For your app,
I have no idea how to use it.
That’s why I invited you to my restaurant.
It’s not a big deal, Mr. Ong-art.
We’re happy to help you.
What can we do for you today?
I have a girlfriend. Her name is Cherry.
She’s an online vendor.
A pineapple.
Next.
I love her very much.
She is the youngest among all my wives.
Because she is so pretty,
she has many admirers.
I hired a famous private investigator
to find her other men.
I have their photos.
Bee and Art.
They are photos from her Instagram.
You don’t need
a famous private investigator to do it.
He scammed you.
Even an elementary student can do it.
If it’s something you are not good at,
it’s the right thing to hire a professional.
Well said.
I have another problem.
Cherry likes me because I’m rich.
But her wealth has been increasing.
When she becomes richer than I,
she will definitely leave me.
Besides my wealth,
I had nothing else to offer her.
That’s why
I want you to get rid of my two love enemies.
Two men? Then it will be two cases.
Can I pay with cash?
Of course.
But we are currently very busy.
But we can jump the queue
if you pay for the VIP package.
Great.
Okay. Everyone, please dig in.
Kor.
Yes?
If I have a crush on my colleague,
what should I do?
You broke up with Boss not long ago.
You found a new guy quickly.
What kind of guy is he?
He…
He’s reserved.
Reserved?
If you come on strong, it might scare him off.
You should do some digging
to find his ideal type.
Then you adjust your style to it.
So he will develop an interest in you.
This is a smooth move.
You look beautiful.
Thank you, Nut.
What is this?
It’s a price tag.
You bought the outfit and wore it out of the store.
Aren’t you afraid you will get a rash?
I made cookies for you.
You made them yourself?
Yes.
You are pretty and kind.
You’re surely not human.
You must be…
an angel.
I’m kind of hungry right now.
It smells good.
Let’s eat it.
Tee, I saw you working hard.
I think a sweet will help you feel energized.
This is a homemade cookie.
I made it myself.
Thank you.
I never got this kind of gift before.
Really?
I made it for everyone. This one…
It looks yummy.
What is this?
Cockroach eggs?
No, they are chocolate chips.
I shouldn’t throw it away.
It’s delicious.
Boss #@!&%$
We are late for our meeting.
This is information about Art and Bee.
Isn’t this supposed to be my job?
It’s okay. I want to do it.
Thank you.
Hey.
You work for my team.
You should come with me.
No. I’m wearing a dress.
I don’t want to ride on a bike.
Fine.
If you want to ride in the van, then go.
Let’s go.
Come on.
Go.
Bee. His pen name is Masao_B.
He’s an online novel writer.
He has been dating Cherry the longest.
They have been together since they had nothing.
Yes?
Honey.
I just wired 50,000 baht to our joint account.
Though she became rich and has many boyfriends,
he still loves her very much.
I’ll do it too.
But I can add only 10 baht.
It’s okay, honey.
You can add the amount that you can afford
The money is for our future together.
Have a good day.
Bye.
Bee’s weakness is his dream and finances.
So…
Here.
It’s your time, rookie.
Do anything to lure him
to use the money from their joint account.
Then they will have a fight and break up.
Mission accomplished.
(Hello.)
Hello. Is this Masao_B?
I’m working at a series production company.
We are interested in buying the adaptation rights
of your novel “The Saleslady and the Young Writer.”
(Really?)
(My hard work finally pays off.)
(What do I need to do?)
It’s very easy.
We will handle the process of obtaining the copyright.
But you need to pay the fee.
So the copyright will be yours.
(Yes. How much is the fee?)
150,000 baht.
Can you wire the money to me now?
(Wire the money?!)
(I registered copyrights for my novels several times.)
(It’s free of charge.)
(You’re a nasty scammer.)
(I’m not a fool to fall for your stupid scheme.)
You have no skills to spin stories.
It’s okay, Tee.
Everyone makes a mistake on their first try.
I’ll handle it from here.
Of course, that should be the case.
Oh.
Are you Masao_B?
Yes.
I’m your fan.
I’m reading your novel
“The Saleslady and the Young Writer.”
I love it.
It’s so fun.
It’s very touching.
Thank you.
What do you like about it?
I like everything.
Is there anything you like in particular?
Umm.
Tell him you like the male protagonist who is rich.
He has unlimited money to pamper the girl.
I like the rich leading man.
But my male protagonist is not that kind of man.
That’s an antagonist.
Right.
Jued, tell him that you like the male protagonist
because he is sweet and hard-working.
He tries hard to prove his love for her.
I got it wrong.
I like the male protagonist
because he is sweet and hard-working.
He tries hard to prove his love for her.
What does the female protagonist do for a living?
She’s an online vendor. She sells everything.
How does the novel end?
This is a trick question.
You haven’t finished the novel.
I’m curious how their story will end.
You are really my fans.
I’m sorry for suspecting you.
There are so many scammers lately.
It’s okay.
It’s not a surprise
that a celebrity like you will be their target.
A celebrity?
Yes, you are a famous writer.
Don’t you know how famous you are?
How famous am I?
You can hold your own fan meeting.
Do you mean a small get together?
I mean a real fan meeting.
You have a fandom.
You can fill this café with your fans.
You need to book the whole café for the event.
The whole café?
Why don’t you hold a fan meeting?
So you will see how many fans you have.
I’m just an uncelebrated writer.
I don’t dare to hold that kind of event.
It’s a bit too much for me.
[The Saleslady and the Young Writer]
Honey.
Congratulations! You finally became famous
and have your own fan meeting.
Thank you.
But…
I don’t see anyone here.
My fans are probably on their way.
But it’s time for the event to start.
Why don’t they want to come early to the event
they bought tickets for?
I didn’t sell tickets.
I paid for everything myself.
What?
I want to hold an event to thank my fans.
So I paid for everything.
I rent this place
and pay for the drinks, snacks, and souvenirs.
How can you afford it?
I used the money from our joint account.
Are you stupid?
If you don’t have any fans,
why are you holding a fan meeting?
I have many fans.
Where are they? I see no one here.
You are sweet, but you’re the biggest fool.
Let’s break up.
One down.
Jued, well done.
You were incredible
when you pretended to be his fan.
I can do that
because you helped me do the research.
Can you stop praising each other?
You should start planning for our next target.
Our next target is Art.
He was a popular host
at the host club that Cherry often visited.
Mushroom.
She likes him.
So she takes him as her sugar baby.
He doesn’t need to do anything.
She provides him with a comfortable life.
Bananas.
Songkla mini mangoes.
Can you adjust the camera for me?
Go a bit to the right.
I haven’t checked the stock upstairs.
Can you go help me?
The target is moving.
Boss, get his phone.
Hurry and clean up the mess.
My wife will be upset if she sees it.
Yes.
I’m sorry.
What’s wrong with you, Boss?
Why are you distracted?
I’m sorry.
Let’s begin the next step.
I miss you so much, sweetie.
Your sticky fingers are working well.
But your skills to stir the pot still sucks.
Give it to me.
[Sweetie, can you come to see me?]
This is an eggplant.
No.
Watermelon.
Next.
[Are you hungry? I have a banana.]
This is a banana.
No, they are rubber balls.
[Or do you want to taste a bitter melon?]
[Sweetie, go straight.]
[Which way should I go next?]
Boss, tell her to turn right.
[Keep going straight.]
Boss, why didn’t you listen to Tee?
Turning right will take longer than going straight.
But that way is…
[Are you kidding me?
I’m going back to my live streaming.]
Hey!
How could you do this to me?
It’s not what you think.
The first step is successful.
What a surprise!
Can I join you?
What?
I took the lead.
You finally realized your feelings for her.
But she’s now interested in another guy.
Stop rubbing salt into my wound
and help me think how to beat that nerd.
You can’t beat him.
Asshole.
Watch your mouth.
I mean it.
You’re having a crush on her.
She doesn’t even know how you feel.
That’s why she’s interested in that guy.
What if she knows how I feel?
Do you have the guts to tell her?
After finishing this case, I’ll give it a try.
I’ll wait and see if you can do it.
Give me your hand.
Now, you feel refreshed, right?
Yes.
Hello.
Wait a sec. I have a patient.
Hello, Mr. Adisak.
How is your condition?
It’s much better.
I’m lucky
that my wife didn’t scold me for getting gonorrhea.
You are so lucky to have an understanding wife.
Some couples broke up because of it.
Yes, I’m very lucky.
Thank you.
Can you tell me your conditions?
I have rashes all over my body.
It’s itchy.
It looks serious.
Did you recently do something out of the ordinary?
Can I join you?
No.
I only apply the lotion
that I usually use before going to bed.
Can I see the lotion?
Here.
It looks normal.
I think you have an STD called gonorrhea.
Gonorrhea on my arms?
It’s an emerging disease.
It’s called pansomatic gohorrhea.
It’s very serious.
You need urgent treatment.
Otherwise, it will spread to your legs and knees.
Lastly, it will spread to your head.
Am I dying?
No.
This is just an initial stage.
My advice is to stop having sexual intercourse
for the meantime.
You should inform your family,
especially your partner, immediately.
To stop the disease from spreading.
I can’t tell my girlfriend.
If she finds out,
I’ll be dead before it spreads to my head.
It’s too late.
The messenger is delivering
your examination result to your address.
It should be delivered within ten minutes.
Excuse me. I have another patient.
Here is your lotion.
I have mail for you.
The mail is delivered.
Hey.
Do you see my mail?
It’s in the letter tray over there.
Next.
A cat collar.
A coaster.
Next.
A pan.
Can you help me find my letter?
Sure.
Why do you two look familiar?
I have a generic-looking face.
You got the wrong person.
I found it.
Thanks.
Sorry.
What is this, honey?
A sexually transmitted disease?
Does it mean I also have it?
I think so.
Me too?
How could you do this to me?
Stop.
Sweetie, please hear me out.
No, I don’t want to listen to you.
Get the hell away from me.
Go away.
Go.
Good job, Jued.
I’m sorry, sweetie.
Sorry?
Boss, watch out.
I’ll take you to the hospital.
It might sting a little.
Ouch.
Almost done.
I never knew Boss has a friend.
I think I’m his only friend.
Other friends have cut ties with him.
Why didn’t you run away from him?
I want to do that too.
But he always gets injured
when he finishes his mission.
I’m a good person.
I need to adhere to my professional ethics.
You are a good person.
You shouldn’t be involved with Boss.
He’s a sinner.
Karma always catches up with him.
You’re right.
He’s a devil from hell.
That’s why he’s punished by heaven.
Did he tell you?
What?
So he hasn’t told you yet?
Tell me what?
What?
You are annoying.
I already knew that.
Good.
(What are you doing?)
(Why didn’t you tell her?)
Follow me.
This way.
Yes.
I closed my restaurant for you guys.
Where is he?
That foul-mouthed guy.
If you don’t want him here,
we will not let him come.
Good.
Sure.
I have a surprise.
I’m going to propose to Cherry.
Really?
Congrats to you in advance.
Huh?
No, I don’t want to order gas.
I think we are talking about different things.
When I give you the signal,
you’ll pop confetti poppers.
Yes.
I’ll give you a big bonus.
Bonus?
I’m joking, Mr. Chan.
Wait for me.
Watch your steps.
Can I play it too?
Come and sit down.
Let’s eat.
Go, go.
This is a big meal.
Boss, how did you get here?
I rode my bike.
He means he didn’t invite you.
What are you doing here?
I completed my mission.
Even though I’m not invited,
I will come anyway.
Boss, get up. It’s my seat.
I don’t see your name on it.
Get up.
I’ll move to another table.
So you can have a seat.
What are you doing here, looking so down?
I want to be like you.
What do you mean by that?
You don’t care about anything.
Nothing can hurt your feelings.
What hurt your feelings?
I feel like I’m not good enough.
I’m poor.
I’m a loser.
I’m foul-mouthed.
My sweets taste bad.
I don’t look good when I wear a girly dress.
This is why…
no one loves me.
Why do you think you are not good enough?
You are understanding others.
You are caring.
You are honest.
Those who get to know you are lucky.
You are a good person.
Maybe…
you are too good for someone.
Do you mean it?
Yes.
You should believe that you are good enough.
Everyone loves you.
I also love…
Tee, I like you. Can I ask you out?
Jued, aren’t you dating Boss?
What?
Boss and I?
No way.
Why did you think that?
Then it means…
We are just work partners.
So…
my answer is yes.
I like you too.
Thank you.
There’s a bone.
How did it get in here?
Although I can’t get down on one knee,
my whole heart belongs to you.
Will you marry me, Cherry?
Congratulations!
Cherry.
Honey, please come back to me.
I’m now rich.
Bee won the lottery jackpot in the latest draw.
He received 60 million baht.
He hired Destiny.
We completed the mission.
But they didn’t stay separated for 45 days.
We need to refund the client.
You don’t need to refund him.
We will break them up again.
Where are you, Boss?
This is Rose, Team B of Break Up Service.
I asked her to help us with this case.