=Strange Tales of Jiangcheng=
=Episode 25=
But what have you done to your best friend?
A total of 32 boxes
of top-quality opium.
You know all my assets
are tied up in this.
You ordered them
to be sunk into the river.
Do you know how much salt
we need to trade
to make up for this treasure?
Zhuang,
Come on, calm down.
When you first asked me to partner up,
I've told you
we can't touch opium.
Your father is the director
of the Jiangzhou Police Station,
Lei Hai's confidant.
In Jiangzhou,
who dares to point fingers at you?
I just don't understand
what you're afraid of.
Zhuang,
we are friends
and brothers,
so I'm sincerely advising you
that we can make money,
but opium is harmful.
So we can't touch it.
The girls in Huanyinglou
laugh and chat with you every day.
They are flattering you
and are grateful to you.
Do you really think
you're a perfect man?
If your father weren't
the director of the police station,
do you think they would even
look at you?
Since we can't agree with each other,
let's talk on another day.
I'll ask you one last time.
Are you discarding
our friendship?
Will you just sink the opium
once I try to sell it?
You may sell opiumin Jiangzhou
over my dead body.
Mr. Xu,
I was just checking
if you need anything else here.
Mr. Xu,
are you done with your business?
Do you
want me
to call the girls back
to drink with you?
No.
I want to be alone for a while.
(Room Qingguifang)
Mr. Xu,
Madam Rong wants me to ask
if you plan to stay the night here.
I will stay with you tonight.
Is that alright?
Mr. Xu,
are you asleep?
Mr. Xu?
(Badger enchantment. It is better
to burn brightly than wither.)
Someone's dead.
A big shot.
(Huanyinglou)
(Room Qingguifang)
Someone's dead.
The man could just kill him.
How deep will the hatred be
to make him peel off
the victim's facial skin?
- It's terrifying.
- I wonder who did it.
Captain,
it seems that no debt is worse
than a love debt.
- Watch your mouth.
- I'm serious.
Captain, you don't know.
Mr. Xu
was a famous playboy in Jiangzhou.
There were countless rumors
about his love affairs.
Xu Shenxing had a strong smell
of alcohol on him.
He must have been attacked from behind
while drunk.
The murder weapon was a sharp dagger
which pierced through his entire chest.
There were no extra wounds
around his face,
which indicates
that the facial skin was peeled off
after he died.
Otherwise, if he had struggled,
there would have
been some marks left.
Mao,
go interrogate everyone at Huanyinglou.
Their madam, the singing girls,
servants, and waiters.
Don't leave anyone out.
Check if anyone has seen this doll.
And, find out whom Xu Shenxing met
before his death,
and if there were any new faces
that came to Huanyinglou.
Committing a crime in such a place,
they must have left some clues.
- Go.
- Yes, sir.
Chen.
- Captain.
- Go tell Director Xu.
Yes, sir.
Watch your words.
Also, find out
if anything unusual has happened
at Xu Residence
in the past few days.
- The more details, the better.
- Yes, sir.
Newspapers for sale!
Director Xu's son
was killed at Huanyinglou at midnight.
Thank you.
Newspapers for sale!
Director Xu's son
(Jiangzhou Police Station)
was killed at Huanyinglou at midnight.
I only have one son.
Who killed him?
Who?
Director.
Don't worry.
Song He and Huole
will definitely find out the truth
and seek justice for Shenxing.
Shenxing.
Huole.
(Xu Shenxing Case)
You've made tea?
How did you know
we were coming to you?
We are partners.
A murder happened here.
If you don't come to me,
who else would you go to?
Alright, tell me.
On the 18th of this month, at 8 p.m.,
Xu Shenxing, Director Xu's only son,
arrived at Huanyinglou by carriage.
According to our investigation,
shortly after Xu Shenxing
entered Room Qingguifang,
his business partner
Zhuang Si, the general manager
of Zhuang's Trading Company
came to the appointment.
(Xu Shenxing. Zhuang Si.)
Later, the singing girl Yinshuang
heard Xu Shenxing
and Zhuang Si
arguing over opium in the room.
And they parted on bad terms.
Additionally, Gu Sui,
the guard of Huanyinglou,
witnessed
that on the night of the murder,
he saw a suspicious stranger
who wore a silver ring
on his pinkie finger.
Later, when he was patrolling
the second floor,
he saw that person again.
And he seemed to know Zhuang Si.
Based on this, I have a good reason to suspect
that this stranger who had
a black mole on his right cheek
and wore a silver ring
on his left pinkie finger
is the murderer
hired by Zhuang Si
to kill Xu Shenxing.
(Huanyinglou. Xu Shenxing. Zhuang Si.)
(Facial skin peeled off.)
(Huanyinglou)
I believe Xu Shenxing's death
has nothing to do
with the presumptive murderer.
A hired murderer's task
is to kill,
which means to take somebody's life,
and that's all.
But in reality,
(Facial skin peeled off.)
the victim's facial skin
was peeled off.
Just think about it,
it is not like peeling an orange.
It takes a lot of time.
Especially in Huanyinglou,
where there are many singing girls
and guests walking around every day.
If it weren't for a psychological need,
no one would take such a risk.
So,
the murderer must have had a deep hatred
for the victim.
If that's the case,
the method is not right.
Actually, before you arrived,
I had already spoken with Xiaofan.
The murderer peeled off
the victim's facial skin
after he had died.
If it was purely out of hatred,
it would make more sense
if he did it before he died.
That way, it would cause the victim
the greatest amount of pain.
Right?
Absolutely right.
I think Detective Qin's analysis
is particularly spot on.
Captain, what do you think?
What if Zhuang Si hired the murderer
and took it as a smokescreen?
I don't think so.
When I was in the United Kingdom,
I reviewed a case
called the Whitechapel Murders.
The murderer was known as Jack the Ripper,
who had removed the victims' uterus.
My understanding is,
he wanted those women
to lose their sexual capability
and gender identity.
So in this case,
I think
that the murderer wanted the victim
to lose his real identity.
In other words,
the murderer wanted to create
a sense of estrangement
between himself and the victim.
You mean
the murderer and the victim
were acquaintances?
I tend to support this conclusion.
Tell me,
besides the lead on Zhuang Si,
do you have any other findings?
The clue
was provided by Cao,
the butler at the Xu Residence.
(To Xu Shenxing)
He said that on the 17th,
the night before the murder,
a rickshaw puller
(Xu Shenxing's life is in danger.)
delivered a ransom letter for someone.
You must have heard
about Mr. Xu's affairs.
Many people want to extort him.
So I'm not surprised
by such letters at all.
Moreover, at that time,
Mr. Xu was also at home.
So I didn't pay much attention to it.
Can you still recall
what that rickshaw puller
looked like?
However,
I do remember
which rickshaw company he was from.
Which one?
The Du's.
If we catch that rickshaw puller,
we can find out where the letter
came from.
The rickshaw puller has been caught.
- We also found out who wrote the letter.
- Who is it?
A scribe named Shen Yuan.
A scribe?
Yes, someone who writes
letters and contracts
for illiterate people.
No wonder the handwriting
was so beautiful.
Where is he?
He's missing.
Missing.
Missing...
(Huanyang)
Tell me about her.
The singing girl Huanyang.
A year ago,
she and Xu Shenxing were in love.
According to the guard Gu Sui
from Huanyinglou,
he once saw the doll
found at the crime scene.
I saw this doll,
in Miss Huanyang's room.
It's hers.
Where is Miss Huanyang?
About a year ago,
she was expelled from Huanyinglou.
Expelled? Why?
Originally, she was favored by Mr. Xu
who wanted to bring her
into the Xu Residence.
But due to some circumstances,
it didn't happen.
In a fit of anger, Miss Huanyang
picked up
badger enchantment skills.
But her plot was exposed,
and she got expelled from Huanyinglou.
So where is she now?
The southern suburbs.
Badger enchantment?
Alright.
I'll follow Shen Yuan's clue.
Leave Zhuang Si to me
Mao. Chen.
You two go to Huanyinglou again
to see if there are any clues we missed.
- Yes, sir.
- After it is done,
we'll meet at the old house
in the southern suburbs.
Move out.
Please.
(Letter Writing Service)
When did you
rent this house to Shen Yuan?
About
five or six years ago.
How long has he been a scribe?
Well,
I can't quite remember.
Anyway, the people living nearby
all go to him when they need
to write a letter or something.
He's gentle
and patient.
And, he charges a small fee.
If someone is short on money,
he'll do it on credit.
Has he always lived alone?
Always alone.
Sir. Sir!
Mr. Zhuang really isn't here today.
(Zhuang's Trading Company)
(Monday, August 19th, Jushangfang.)
When was the last time
you saw him?
Maybe it was the day before yesterday,
or maybe not.
He's the kind of person
who doesn't talk much.
We just nodded to greet each other
when we met.
So, I didn't pay much attention.
Please, don't look at me like that.
It's not just me.
You can ask the neighbors.
Their answer will be the same as mine.
How about these people?
They're the girls from Huanyinglou.
They also came to him
for letter writing?
Because it's close.
At the end of this alley,
it's Huanyinglou's rear wall.
(This work's exclusive right to
network dissemination of information)
(is enjoyed by
Shenzhen Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)