=Strange Tales of Jiangcheng=
=Episode 44=
(Governor's Mansion)
Commander.
Chen Biao has taken Ningcheng
and incorporated He Guang's troops.
He has seized a lot of weapons.
His momentum is strong.
What do you think
our chances of winning this battle are?
Given the current situation,
it might be difficult for us to defeat him.
Unless...
We've hidden the resource over the years.
Now it's time to bring it to light.
Understood.
(Jiangzhou Prison)
I'm Song He from the detective squad.
I need to have a word with Qin Huole.
Alright, Captain Song.
Isn't it a bit too grand for you
to send me off like this?
Jiangzhou is about to go to war again.
I've heard.
Does Commander Lei have a chance
of winning?
My father wants to send me away.
I'm leaving Jiangzhou today.
You're leaving?
I'm sorry.
The war is imminent.
I can't be a burden to my father.
But I really
enjoy working with you all
to solve cases
and fight for Jiangzhou.
Xiaofan,
don't cry.
Yes.
The three of us
will always be the best partners.
In the West, when people part,
they always give each other
a sincere hug.
It's a pity
that I can't do that today.
How about we...
Thank you all.
Once the war is over,
I'll come back immediately.
Take care.
You take care too.
When you come back,
everything will be better.
Definitely.
Bye.
Go in.
Hello everyone.
Watch me.
If you're not convinced, let's battle.
One more, one more time.
Alright, alright, again.
(Prisoner You Youyou)
One more. Come here.
You Youyou,
got imprisoned in the early years
of the Republic of China.
He's a veteran prisoner there,
who is well-informed
and famous for being a know-it-all.
If you can get him to talk,
I believe the time to find out the truth
will be greatly shortened.
However, this person is peculiar.
It will take some effort to get close
to him.
Mr. You.
- Wrong.
- Let me.
It's not mister.
It's master.
Master You.
Step aside.
You're blocking my wind.
Master You.
My name is Qin Huole.
You can also call me Huole.
I know, I know.
The famous Detective Qin.
What's up?
Tired of being a detective
and come here for a change?
How do you know me?
Lawyer Qin Weilian's son.
You just returned from studying abroad,
and were all thinking about
seeking justice for people.
I'm just puzzled.
You're young
and from a rich family.
Why don't you just
be a rich kid?
Have some fun
and live a lavish life.
Why are you messing around here?
Do you really want to be
a hero so much?
Who would want to come here?
I heard there's someone like you.
They say you've traveled far and wide,
had your leg run over by a train,
and carried a single knife on your back
to go
anywhere you want.
When I heard that,
I thought, wow,
I must come
and visit you myself.
I didn't expect
you to be such a talkative person.
Keep talking. I'd love to hear that.
Thanks.
If you like it,
I'll continue...
As for the thing you want to know,
I can't talk about it.
Master You.
I have a rule.
I mean what I said.
Don't come to me again.
But I haven't even asked yet.
How do you know you can't talk about it?
What if I say I can help you
overturn the case
and let you walk
out of here openly?
I have read your case file.
In the Yangliuzhuang case,
though you have confessed
and accepted the punishment,
this case is still full of doubts.
Master You,
you should have heard
that I assisted the detective squad
in solving several major cases.
I've heard of it.
So...
Unfortunately,
I don't want to go out.
Do you want to know why?
In this small area,
I am the master.
But if I go out,
I am just a nobody.
Kid,
you have a face that
is not so annoying.
I'll give you a piece
of free advice.
In life,
try to turn a blind eye
and you'll live longer.
(Allegiance to Lei)
Commander.
Have you sent Xiaofan away?
I have told Qingmang
to send a telegram back
as soon as they arrive.
Please rest assured.
Is there anything else?
Commander.
The news that Chen Biao is going
to attack the city
has already spread around.
Now the people in Jiangzhou are in panic.
I believe that at this time,
we must not let chaos ensue.
If we want to prevent chaos,
we need to control both the police
and the prison.
What do you mean?
The prisoners
are not some kind persons.
If they hear the news that the city
is going to be attacked,
some will develop ill intentions.
Even if we suppress them,
it will be very troublesome.
What about the police?
Besides Lei's Army,
the only armed force in the city
is from the police station.
If they...
No need to say more.
You've been with me for so many years.
You've made progress.
It's all thanks to your guidance.
Do you have any good ideas?
Commander,
I have thought about it.
It's simple to control the prison.
As long as you order them
to raise the alert level
to the highest,
we can be at ease.
But the police station...
Isn't Xu injured?
Then starting today,
the affairs in the police station
will be handled by you personally.
Yes, sir.
Make sure
to deal with these two issues properly.
Understood.
(Jiangzhou Prison)
Just eat this?
Yes, it's quite thin.
It's getting less and less.
Thank you.
Next.
The porridge is almost gone.
That guy is here.
Let's see what happens.
Let's chat.
- What are you doing?
- Don't move.
Don't move.
Let go.
What are you guys doing?
Take a look.
Indeed, a rich son.
(Prisoner Liu Sanbao)
Such tender skin,
like a woman's.
Liu Sanbao,
nicknamed San,
a notorious bully in west Jiangzhou.
He has injured and maimed people
many times in prison,
and has a large number of henchmen.
When you encounter him,
you must be very careful.
I was wondering who it was.
Turns out it's the famous
Master Sanbao.
You are quite informed, kid.
Master Sanbao,
it doesn't feel good to talk like this.
Why don't you do me a favor
and let me go first?
Let you go?
If I let you go,
who will eat
such a delicious thing?
Detective Qin, tell me,
do you want to eat it civilly
or forcefully?
Can you explain
the difference?
Eating it civilly
means everyone watches you eat.
Eating it forcefully
means everyone feeds you.
What if
I don't want either?
You didn't have to
if you were a detective.
Unfortunately,
now you're
just like us.
Newcomers
all have to go through this.
Eat it and we'll make peace.
Newcomer, what do you say?
Should I feed you?
- Eat it.
- Hurry up.
(Chen Zou, captain of Jiangzhou Prison)
Warden.
What's going on with you today?
You're even concerned
about the prisoners' meals.
Today?
(Duan Ming, warden of Jiangzhou Prison)
What I mean is
such a trivial issue
shouldn't trouble you.
This is my negligence.
Chen Zou,
do you know
what your biggest weakness is?
Please enlighten me.
It's being overly cautious.
Eat it.
Eat it, eat it!
What are you doing?
Look at this kid, so delicate.
He's not like us rough men.
Don't accidentally hurt him.
Even Master You can be nice?
If I remember correctly,
you set the rule
back then.
When I first came in,
I had to eat a whole big bowl of this.
So,
are you going
to break the rule
for this kid today?
No,
the rule can't be broken.
I mean, this...
Then you should
find a cool place to stay.
Don't spoil everyone's fun.
- Hurry up and leave.
- Right.
- Hurry up and go.
- Go, go.
- Hurry up and eat.
- Eat quickly.
We must watch him eat it.
Eat it.
Chew quickly.
No one can cheat.
- No cheating, hurry up.
- Hurry up.
What's going on?
Why are you so excited?
You even stopped eating.
It's nothing.
The warden is asking you a question.
Answer it.
Yes, sir.
Warden,
this newcomer
is wasting food.
We're teaching him the rules.
Is that so?
No, I...
Warden,
that's how it is.
I can testify.
That's potato.
It should taste pretty good.
Alright, I won't disturb you.
Carry on.
Thank you.
How are you? Do you feel better now?
I feel much better now.
But my stomach still hurts a bit.
This procedure
could have been skipped.
However, I consider
that you have a mission to complete.
To avoid arousing suspicion
among other prisoners,
I suggested Captain Song
keep it.
Did he agree?
Duan Ming, warden of Jiangzhou Prison.
(Honest and upright)
He's a reliable friend.
When you get inside,
he will find ways to protect you.
Go to him if you have any needs.
And go to him to contact me.
I want to give Song He a call.
Alright.
I'll call him.
Hello.
This is Duan Ming from Jiangzhou Prison.
I'd like to speak to Captain Song He.
Please hold on.
Captain Song is out.
I'll go get him now.
Captain Song.
- Yes?
- You have a call.
It's from Jiangzhou Prison.
Alright.
Jiangzhou Prison. This is Chen Zou.
Come in.
Warden,
this is the renovation plan
for the third cell block.
Please review it.
Hello, this is Song He.
(This work's exclusive right
to network dissemination of information)
(is enjoyed by
Shenzhen Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd)