SEE YOU IN MY 19TH LIFE
Normally, I start to
remember my past lives
between the ages of 8 and 12.
The memories flood me like waves.
I remember everything
from who I was
to what I did.
My good lives fill me with longing
while my bad lives bring me pain.
I wish they were just dreams.
But they're real.
Yes, I remember my past lives.
Let me tell you my story.
Mommy!
-Just keep living your life.
-Mommy!
I knew I was different at the age of nine.
That's when I recalled everything.
Even the precious memories
we shared together.
Don't worry.
I'll stay by his side.
Ju-won?
Seo-ha.
Seo-ha…
When my memories returned,
my first thought was…
Is he alive?
HAPPINESS, SADNESS, PITY, AND JOY
Hey!
Give me money.
-What do you mean, money?!
-Screw you!
-I'm so sick and tired of you!
-I said, give me money.
Hey.
Where's the money?
Stop, for goodness' sake!
You stop right…
MY 19TH LIFE
This life isn't going to be easy.
Give her a round of applause!
Ji-eum, what did all of that mean?
I said, "Hello, I'm Ban Ji-eum,
the Girl-of-all-trades from Siheung."
What language was that?
-Spanish.
-Spanish, everyone!
"The islands Ulleungdo and Dokdo
are not related to Japan."
It was around 1870.
During Japan's Meiji era,
the Great Council of State declared
that Dokdo is not Japanese territory
in this important document.
Give her a round of applause.
The future of Korea
has never been brighter!
Great job, everybody.
-Are you Ji-eum's father?
-Yes.
This is her appearance fee.
Thank you.
Great job, Ji-eum.
STARQUEEN: GIRL-OF-ALL-TRADES, BAN JI-EUM
DANCE PRODIGY
THE QUEEN OF STARQUEENS!
GIRL-OF-ALL-TRADES, BAN JI-EUM PERFORMS!
HOBAM NIGHTCLUB
FLAMENCO CHILD-PRODIGY
BAN JI-EUM
You blew it!
What are you doing?
What do you think you're doing?
-Go away.
-Hey!
Why are you searching through my stuff?
-Come on.
-Hey.
Look who's rich.
Let go!
It's okay.
I've even been born during a war.
This is nothing.
Where am I going?
I'm looking for the person
who will help me meet Seo-ha sooner.
I really want to know if Seo-ha is alive.
This is the only thing I can do right now.
AE-GYEONG'S SNACK BAR
A BEAUTIFUL ACCORDION PERFORMANCE
BY THE GIRL-OF-ALL-TRADES
DONGBAEK AERIAL GRAND CIRCUS
That little girl can do everything.
Oh, boy.
She's certainly going to make it in life.
How does she know that song?
Amazing.
My goodness!
That hurt.
That really hurt.
WEBTOON ORIGINAL SERIES
SEE YOU IN MY 19TH LIFE CREATED BY LEE HEY
Do you want a donut?
What's this?
Ae-gyeong, it's Uncle Jung-ho.
I'm in a tight spot,
so please lend some money to this girl.
Lend me money.
I'll pay you back many times more.
Little girl.
Who are you?
What a performance.
You are amazing.
That's me.
The Girl-of-all-trades, Ban Ji-eum.
How do you know this song
by Choi Beck-ho from 1995?
It's a song I sang often.
You're right!
I thought you looked familiar.
What a surprise seeing you here!
My goodness.
But why do you look so messy?
And where did you get this note?
Uncle Jung-ho's been dead for years.
A round of applause to the nine-year-old,
the Girl-of-all-trades, Ban Ji-eum!
Thank you.
Weren't you ten years old
when that picture was taken?
You used to follow your uncle around
performing plate-spinning tricks.
The tall, handsome acrobat next to you…
That's Kim Jung-ho.
Your uncle.
How do you know that?
You know, your uncle…
I'm the reincarnation
of your uncle.
What did you say?
MY 17TH LIFE
DONGBAEK CIRCUS TROUPE
Uncle!
Are you really going to die?
Ae-gyeong.
Remember what I told you?
You're going to be born again
and will come to protect me.
That's right.
So don't be sad.
Just keep living your life.
Promise me.
I promise.
Do you remember our promise?
What's my father's name?
Let me think.
Kim…
Is it Jung-seok? No, Jung-hyeok!
That's not even close.
Are you perhaps
Uncle Jung-ho's secret daughter?
I told you I'm your uncle.
I raised you and took care of you.
Because your parents died
so early in your life,
I had to give up on getting married
and raised you as if you were my own.
That's true.
But what in the world is going on?
-It's okay.
-Goodness.
I understand
how this could be hard to believe.
So you can take your time
getting used to it.
But for now,
help out a little starving kid and…
lend me about 100,000 won.
I promise to repay you, so don't worry.
Where would you even spend that money?
I need to meet someone.
Who would that be?
Seo-ha.
Seo-ha?
Who's that?
He's someone
I really need to meet in this life.
MY 18TH LIFE
On a rainy day
Sitting in an old coffee shop
With a glass of bellflower whisky in hand
Listen to the rich saxophone playing
With her bright red lipstick on
Hey! What's your problem?
Shouldn't you apologize
after bumping into someone?
Who are you?
You look like a kid.
What grade are you in?
A kid?
Hey!
She's going to love it.
You can give it to her.
Sang-a.
Apparently, the kids at her school
call her "Ms. Yoon."
She acts like a teacher
when she's still a kid herself.
The problem with Seo-ha
is that he's too impudent.
I may have spoiled him too much.
How do you raise a child
to be like Ju-won?
Around two years ago,
it was as if she fully matured overnight.
At times,
she's more like an adult than I am.
And sometimes…
I wonder if she's really my daughter.
In any case, she suddenly changed.
It was my 18th life.
Just as I was getting bored
of repeating life after life,
I met Seo-ha.
Was something down there?
What's so funny?
It's been so long
since someone piqued my interest.
THE MOON AND THE WEST WITCH'S FOREST
Do you need help?
Get away from me. I don't need your help.
You're too short to reach it.
I'm not a kid.
I said, get--
You did that on purpose.
Are you crazy?
Well…
What better way
to teach a rude rich kid a lesson
than a book to the head?
Look here.
If I start screaming right now,
what do you think will happen to you?
Do it then.
If you do…
I'll make you disappear like this.
What was that?
-How did you do that?
-It's a secret.
Are you a witch?
If I tell you,
will you entertain me?
Do you believe in past lives?
-Like before I was born?
-Yes.
I haven't thought about it.
I believe in them.
Come closer.
This isn't my first go at life.
Were you cursed by a witch?
What?
Why are you laughing?
Tell me!
-You're adorable.
-No, I'm not!
Ju-won, Dad's back from work.
Let's go home.
I'll be right there.
That was the most fun I've had
in 100 years.
Bye.
You can't just leave!
Did you have fun with her?
Not really.
Shall I invite her back?
I don't care.
She can do whatever.
Green light, red light!
Ju-won!
No, don't!
THE MOON AND THE WEST WITCH'S FOREST
Could you look after
my dear Seo-ha?
She'll die.
She'll live.
Hey.
Why were you counting the leaves?
There's one remaining.
What's left?
Whether my mom…
What about your mom?
I also…
remember.
-Remember what?
-My past life.
What were you…
in your past life?
-A turtle.
-What?
You know, a turtle.
Seo-ha.
Mun Seo-ha.
When I was younger,
I went to Mom's hotel and…
That's just a memory, not your past life.
You're wrong!
My mom said she doesn't remember it.
But I do.
That's not what I meant by past lives.
But good effort, kid.
Don't call me a kid!
What else would I call a kid?
Stop it!
Why do you hate that word so much?
My mom has to take care of me
even when she's sick
because I'm a kid.
Seo-ha.
When you feel like counting leaves again,
just call me.
I'll come right over and give you a hug.
Why?
I just want to stay by your side.
Do you…
like me?
I'll answer that on your birthday.
Oh, come on!
When I was with Seo-ha,
I felt like I was actually 12.
He made me forget
that I had died and lived again
seventeen times in the past.
I said I would stay by his side.
But I couldn't keep my promise.
Why couldn't you?
I was reborn.
I left him too suddenly.
I want to find him and see if he's alive.
But I was born into a lousy family,
so I don't even have the money
to get to him.
I tried to save up so I could look decent.
But my family is onto me like leeches.
I had no choice but to come here.
Ae-gyeong, I know you have a good heart.
So I hoped you would take me in.
As you saw on television,
my talents are endless.
Just put up with me for a bit,
and I'll earn my keep, all right?
And can I just say
that your restaurant is hopeless?
Don't have too many things on the menu.
How about you use this kimchi
and try serving braised kimchi?
What a smart little kid.
All right.
I'll give you the money.
Take this.
Make sure to find that Seo-ha kid, okay?
Thank you for this.
I'll pay you back ten times over.
All right then.
Ae-gyeong.
It must have been hard growing up alone.
I'll take care of you now.
AE-GYEONG'S SNACK BAR
ME, AE-GYEONG, SEO-HA
Oh, right.
Wait.
Taxi!
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Here you go.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
How do I open this?
I hid the key.
At the amusement park?
I didn't put in that much work.
I'll tell you where it is
if you're a good boy today.
You always do this.
Just give me a hint.
Should I?
All right, here's hint number one.
It's my favorite place.
Your favorite place?
Number two.
It's a fragrant place.
Is it your room?
Wrong. Now, hint number three.
Whenever one life ended,
I would say the same prayer.
Seo-ha.
Ju-won.
I would pray that this life
would be my last.
Or that my memories would never return.
Ju-won.
But I said a different prayer that time.
Do you remember what I told you?
When a person dies, they're born again.
Seo-ha.
Then…
will I get to see my mom again?
No one knows who your mom
will be reincarnated into,
not even your mom.
Then…
there's no point even if she's reborn.
But you'll know your mom
will be free from her hospital bed
and live a healthy life.
That's good.
I'm glad to hear…
she won't be sick anymore.
I'll stay by your side.
You're alive.
Seo-ha.
Thank you for being alive.
What is that woman doing here?!
Mind your manners.
If she ever comes back here--
It's none of your business. Get out.
The plan was just to see if he was alive.
But once I saw him, I couldn't get enough.
The grumpy little kid grew up so fast.
Uncle, open up.
If I told you I was Ju-won,
you wouldn't believe me, right?
If only you would believe me
like Ae-gyeong did.
That would be great.
Uncle.
I guess studying so hard
has made me thirsty.
What? My goodness.
What are you doing?
Oh, my goodness!
Oh, my.
Look at you go.
When you were upset, I was upset.
I wanted to ask you what was wrong.
Then one day,
you suddenly disappeared.
Eight years passed just like that.
YEAR 2015
HIGH SCHOOL QUALIFICATION EXAM
Time's up.
Put your hands on your head, please.
Our kid is going to KAIST!
Congratulations.
GIRL-OF-ALL-TRADES, BAN JI-EUM
EARLY-ADMITTANCE TO KAIST
It took Ae-gyeong a lot of effort
to accept me as her uncle.
But thanks to her,
I endured those tough times.
Soda is on the house!
MUN SEO-HA OF MI GROUP
MUN SEO-HA
AFFILIATION: MI MOBITY
MI GROUP'S SENIOR MANAGING DIRECTOR
MUN SEO-HA APPOINTED TO GERMAN BRANCH
I finally found
a way to get to you, Seo-ha.
Germany?
MI MOBITY 2020 RECRUITMENT FINAL INTERVIEW
YEAR 2020
I will do my best
to advance MI Mobity's technology.
Thank you.
Hello, you leave quite the impression.
Excuse me.
-Yes?
-I feel a special energy coming from you.
Sadly, I can also sense
misfortune in your life.
Your current life
may be shorter than your past life.
If there's a certain someone
weighing on your mind,
then showing your ancestors
sincerity and effort will…
-You're mistaken.
-Excuse me?
I died when I was 12 in my past life.
And this happens to be my 19th life.
You were right about one thing.
There is someone weighing on my mind.
You got that right.
What a strange person.
Hello, you have a great aura.
I managed to join MI Group,
where Seo-ha works…
Daehwan Motors
is desperate to headhunt her.
Daehwan Motors?
Why is she staying here then?
-Exactly.
-But isn't that pretty cool?
…but he seems to have
no intention of coming back to Korea.
EMPLOYEE SEARCH
EMPLOYEE INFORMATION
MUN SEO-HA
It's nearly impossible to meet him.
Should I just go to Germany?
Germany again?
Is this about your first love?
Yeah.
You said you last saw him
when you were nine.
Why look for him when you don't even know
how he turned out?
Oh, boy.
You're right.
I don't understand why you're so obsessed.
What's the reason?
There are moments
that are indescribable with words.
They're all still in here though.
You were such a mature kid.
Go meet him then.
He probably won't even remember you.
Does Seo-ha even remember me?
Should I just go to Germany?
Swimming again today?
It's still pretty cold outside.
Yes, careful not to catch a cold.
Thank you.
The German branch mainly hires
from the local talent pool.
Besides, only executive-level staff
get sent over.
Should I become an executive then?
But that would take too long.
What?
I can still apply to go, right?
Sure, you can.
Ms. Ban.
Have I upset you in any way?
You can tell me anything.
There's nothing of the sort.
I'll be leaving now.
Ms. Ban.
She really has you on a string.
For some reason, I can't treat her
the same way I treat others.
Was she a king in her past life
or something?
The yaw rate is spiking
according to the data.
How's the steering?
It's a little stiff.
But the clutch, torque converter,
and transmission are stable.
The steering is stiff.
The data doesn't look good.
You said it's hard to steer.
I'll do one more lap.
You should stop.
Hey!
Hello, Ms. Ban.
It's Lee Ji-seok of Daehwan Group.
Have you changed your mind?
I have no intention
of working for Daehwan.
We're showing a lot of effort, you know.
Were you not swayed at all?
Your company must have a lot of free time.
Finding and recruiting talent
is the most important job.
I'm quite selective in whom I approach.
And I'm quite selective
in whom I work for.
Objectively speaking,
Daehwan has a lot more to offer than MI.
Well, that's true.
-You're right.
-Then let's shake hands on it.
Unfortunately, he isn't there.
Who isn't?
The person I want to meet.
Hello?
Which Seo-ha?
You mean Mun Seo-ha of MI Group?
He went to the hotel?
Why would the chairman's son
go to the hotel?
He didn't go to HQ or Mobity?
What were you in your past life?
A turtle.
It's Seo-ha.
We finally meet again.
Seo…
CHINESE RESTAURANT LUSHUI
NOTICE OF CLOSURE
Seo-ha, you must have been
a turtle in your past life.
Was something down there?
Is something down there?
This place is
for authorized personnel only.
I see.
All right.
Are you serious?
Just come up with some excuse.
Tell them we're out of ingredients
or something.
You can't cater
to each guest individually.
You're really pissing me off.
Go!
CEO OF MI HOTEL, LEE SANG-A
(1990-1997)
Out.
Welcome, sir.
I don't care about what you've been up to.
And no one else needs to know either.
I'm assigning you
to the Strategic Planning Team.
Assess our stockholders within this week,
and get the earnings report from
the local subsidiary of the Trade Team.
If you don't want people
to know you're hard of hearing,
get in the habit of replying right away.
Are you
not listening on purpose?
From the back office to the front office,
to the food business department,
sales, and marketing…
I noticed a difference in approach
depending on the brand concept.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to…
restore Mother's hotel.
Get the hell out, you punk!
-Be careful, everyone.
-Careful.
-Leave it there.
-Okay.
Just a bit more.
How many times are we going to move this?
Okay, right here.
-That's good.
-My shoulder.
You want a massage?
Don't be gross.
Here.
How's the Strategic Planning Team
coming along?
The office will be set up within the week.
In terms of operations,
we have MI Hotel's financial reports,
analysis of rival hotels,
and job applications.
Let's see the applications.
Here you go.
"Ban Ji-eum"?
Graduate of a school for gifted children
with an engineering doctorate from KAIST?
She's a senior researcher at MI Mobity.
She has a senior position at only 24?
Are you sure she applied for our hotel?
Beats me.
She speaks English, Chinese, Japanese,
and Arabic?
She was the Girl-of-all-trades
on Starqueen,
and her hobby is flamenco dancing?
What's that?
COVER LETTER
I was most taken aback
by the artificial flowers in the lobby.
I believe that a hotel business
is ultimately about making people happy.
A lobby that makes your heart race
and guest rooms that excite you…
A hotel just like you, Seo-ha.
And guest rooms that give you comfort.
I envision such a hotel.
What a strange person.
Better to weed someone like her out.
You're right, but…
with a résumé like this,
she should at least get an interview.
My impression of her…
RÉSUMÉ
I guess it wouldn't hurt to meet her.
Ms. Ban Ji-eum?
Yes.
Is this the Strategic Planning Office?
Yes. Director Mun is waiting for you.
Right this way.
STRATEGIC PLANNING OFFICE
This way, please.
Director Mun.
Director Mun?
Seo-ha.
Nice to meet you. I'm Mun Seo-ha.
I'm Ban Ji-eum.
Have a seat.
I see you're employed at MI Mobity.
I am.
So why did you apply to the hotel?
I want to help you
return this hotel to its former glory.
I'm assuming you want that as well?
By former glory, you mean…
The end of the 20th century.
So around 1997.
Isn't that before you were born?
You're right.
A distant relative
once showed me some pictures
and they left
quite a deep impression on me.
I see.
LANGUAGES:
ENGLISH, CHINESE, JAPANESE, ARABIC…
How do you speak Arabic?
That's because…
A while ago…
It was around the tenth century.
MY 4TH LIFE
The arrack I distilled then
spread to the Middle East,
Mongolia, and Goryeo
and later became modern-day soju.
I had once worked over there
and found the language
interesting and fun.
She started working three years ago.
So when did she have time to go there?
I understand why you're applying,
but the work may be different
from what you're looking for.
If you're still unsure,
why don't you try dating me?
I'm sorry.
I must have heard you wrong.
No, you haven't.
I'll repeat myself.
Would you like to date me?
SEE YOU IN MY 19TH LIFE
Why don't you just tell him honestly
that you were Ju-won?
-Director Mun.
-Hey, cutie.
-Let go.
-My goal is to straighten out
the disgraceful practices
that have been overlooked.
Director Mun, you didn't mention my task.
Are young people these days all so brash?
"Pursue rather than wait."
I told you he was perfect.
It seems to me
that you have ulterior motives.
Run!
Marry me.
Subtitle translation by: Ji-hun Lee