Hello.
The one from the well disappeared
as soon as he came out.
I found a piece of him
just now.
A piece?
Is it--
The Fox Marble--
the Fox Marble you gave her is gone.
And now, something has awoken in her body.
What?
Why is that thing
in her body?
She was finally reborn after 600 years.
The only desire she had in her life…
was to live an ordinary life
with her family day by day.
Why?
Why is that thing in Ji-a's body?
It's all her fate.
Fate?
Who says so?
What did she ever do?
Do you dare humiliate the heavens
in the realm of the higher beings?
You knew everything, didn't you?
That's why
you kept telling me not to see her.
I feel like
I saved up my money for 600 years
only to get it robbed from me.
So?
I'll have you
pay back some of the principal.
I took you in
when you were nothing but a defaulter.
How dare you bring up the principal?
That's enough!
Calm down, Yeon.
Honey, you too.
Listen up.
The moment Ji-a loses a day of her life,
this world and the afterlife will
both turn into chaos.
Get out of my sight. Take him away.
Did you see it?
I wonder how you feel right now.
I feel like I'm about to cry.
I had to leap over many years
to meet her like this.
You're having complicated thoughts.
-Sorry?
-"That's a strange little boy.
Is he not the same serpent I knew before?"
If I seem different, it's because
the world is a different place now.
Both serpents and Nine-tailed Foxes
only exist in video games.
There's no need to stick
to such archaic backdrops, is there?
They'll begin looking for us as well.
Just as I hoped.
I want to see them as soon as possible.
Despite what she says,
she doesn't mean it.
She may be pretty harsh,
but that old woman thought of you
like one of her own.
Don't try to comfort me.
I already feel like crying.
Yeon, don't get too caught up in this.
Just turn a blind eye and move on.
There's no need
to jump into an obvious pit of fire.
She'll get hurt if I don't go.
Do you wish
to relive that old tragedy?
If you get into this,
it'll be either you or her.
One of you will die.
Your fate and her fate
were decided as such…
the moment it was reborn.
No.
Ji-a won't die.
I promised her
that she'll live an ordinary life
this time.
I'll protect her with my life.
There are many moments
when a kid needs his parents,
more often than I realized.
When you take your first steps.
There's no one other than your parents
who'd be thrilled
to see you get up and walk a few steps.
When I was the only one
who didn't bring gimbap to a picnic.
After a fight, when my friend said,
"I'm going to tell on you to my mom!"
I could never win against
anyone who had a mom.
Why couldn't my parents be meaner to me?
Then could I have forgotten everything
and lived an ordinary life
like everyone else?
What made you wait
for your parents so long?
It's simple for me.
I just miss them.
The Fox Marble?
Was it that significant?
It was the fortune-teller, right?
He said something about my fate,
then offered to let you go
in exchange for that.
But still,
how could you have given it away so easily
as if it were some candy?
I couldn't lose you.
I'm staying here for a while.
You want to stay here?
At my house?
-You'll eat and sleep here?
-Yes.
You're very liberal for a fox.
Or you can come to my house.
That's not what I mean.
Why all of a sudden?
It's the least I can do for your safety.
Please don't make me risk my life
every single time I try to save you.
I meant if you'll be okay with the sofa.
If you're using yourself to negotiate,
I can't argue with that.
Why are you up anyway?
I remember putting you to bed.
Oh, I had a weird dream.
-A dream?
-I saw this little kid,
and he said hi to me.
-And?
-That's all.
At first, he really creeped me out,
but once I woke up,
it felt sort of nice to see him,
as if he were someone I knew.
So it is.
He's the most precious thing to you.
Your brother.
I'll take a cola.
Cola?
I gorged on the neighborhood doves
the last time I got drunk,
so I'm holding back.
I had a stomachache.
Did you leave that dove by my door?
Did I take it that far?
I don't remember anything.
You aren't a stray cat.
So did you find it?
These are the Tiger's Brows.
You can use these
to see someone's previous life?
But why do you look so sad?
-I'm not sad. I'm pissed.
-Why?
I can't take how
I still have human feelings in me.
Is it because I'm impure?
Right, you said your mom was a human.
Did she hold you
and give you piggyback rides?
Did she cook chicken
and give you all the meat?
Quit it.
I was just curious
what it's like to be loved.
Love?
Mom.
Wait here for a moment.
I don't want to. It's scary here.
I'm just going to pick some hazelnuts.
I want to go with you. I want to go too.
Why do you trouble me so much?
I have nothing else to live for.
Do you want to die with me? Do you?
Mom?
Love is something
that can devour you if you aren't careful.
The one who loves more gets eaten.
I don't want that.
I'd rather be the one to eat.
Was it Sin-ju?
What did he say to shake your heart,
and make this naive carnivore
bring up a word like love?
I'll never be shaken.
Even if the sky falls,
your enemy is my enemy too.
Go home. I want to be alone.
Seven. Eight.
Nine.
Ninety-nine points.
Mr. Lee and Ms. Nam only got 25 points.
See that?
According to this scientific method,
there's something going on between us.
Despite that foxes from abroad
may be more liberal than us,
she still kissed me when we first met.
Goodness, watch what you say.
Why would I get neutered?
What do you mean, I'm in heat?
You shouldn't talk like that.
Anyway, your mom
didn't sound too happy,
but she finished that samgyetang.
She can be mean with her words,
but she's not heartless.
You know, right?
What? You want samgyetang too?
You had your food
less than half an hour ago.
You don't remember?
You drive me nuts!
Hey!
How long are you going to stand there?
-All night long.
-All night?
Don't mind me.
You're staring at me with such fiery eyes.
How can I not mind you?
Then I'll watch from outside.
That's terrifying.
If you don't like anything I do,
how am I supposed to protect you?
Go sleep on the sofa.
No, I can't see you from there.
-Then sleep here.
-Okay.
I didn't mean my bed.
I just meant this room.
I'm more modern than I look.
I can't sleep on the floor. My back hurts.
Go down if you're scared.
I'm not scared.
Aren't you going to sleep?
I'm not sleepy.
This is something
my dad taught me long ago.
If you can't sleep,
try to imagine something
that makes you feel great.
Like mint chocolate ice cream?
For me,
it's the smell of freshly cooked rice.
The sound of a pencil getting sharpened.
A new pair of sneakers.
Baseball season.
World literature collections.
Puppy paws.
My dad's gimbap.
No one writes them anymore,
but letters.
Your turn.
Are you asleep?
Yes. I say
a red umbrella.
No!
What are you doing?
Why are you laughing?
Wasn't I really cool just now?
I moved fast like Spider-Man
and saved you.
The kind of human I hate the most.
And look at his runny nose.
Mister, do you like Spider-Man?
-No.
-Why not?
-I just don't.
-I like him.
I don't care.
Hey.
Stop talking to me.
I feel crappy plenty enough.
I woke up at 4:30 a.m.
It's almost done.
What are you doing right now?
-Pollack soup?
-Yes, it's pollack soup.
Did you burn these?
Incredible.
I wouldn't say it's burnt.
How do I put it--
I was making pollack soup,
but I ended up--
-Go get more. I used it up.
-You used it all?
I put sugar in that one.
I'll do it. You can leave.
Hey.
Did you sleep well?
-Yes.
-Let's eat breakfast.
Pollack soup is the best for hangovers.
You made all this alone?
That's not what's important.
-It's the thought that counts.
-That's amazing.
Good morning, Ms. Nam.
Mr. Gu, why are you here?
I heard you two moved in together.
I brought him a change of clothes,
and to check in.
Where do you keep bleach?
Bleach? Why?
Your sink is covered with mold.
I rubbed the tiles
with baking soda and vinegar,
but I have to remove
hair from the drain too.
Don't keep leftovers in the fridge.
It's a big pile of germs.
-He sounds like a mother-in-law.
-I know.
I'm sorry to intervene on your household,
but, although Mr. Lee
never has done any chores,
-he's a sort of a neat freak.
-What?
Eat your food. So where's the bleach?
It's in the bathroom drawer.
Why didn't he keep searching?
Why did he even come out?
Wait.
-Did you burn these?
-I wouldn't say I burned those.
I failed to control the heat.
Don't be acting cute about it.
The pollack has infested me.
I'm not cute. I'm over 1,000 years old.
-Let's eat.
-Yes, let's eat.
Soft-boiled eggs.
Let's split it.
Yes?
May I--
Come in.
Here.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
And Ms. Nam.
I may be crossing the line
telling you this,
but please be safe.
If you get hurt,
Mr. Lee will get hurt by two, three,
or even tenfold.
I'm so jealous of Yeon.
He has such a thoughtful friend.
He's very dear to me.
I promise
to be as safe as I can be.
Yeon has also become very dear to me.
-Let's go. We're going to be late.
-Okay.
Coming!
Where are you going?
Me? To work.
By work,
do you mean my office?
Yes, of course.
You can't come in without an ID.
I'm a Nine-tailed Fox.
No one can stop me. I'll manage.
But why are you dressed like that?
Like an ordinary office worker
to blend in. You don't like it?
It's not that I don't,
but only the executives wear ties.
-Really?
-Yes.
Let's just lose the tie.
No, I'll be an executive.
-Hello, Director.
Hey, good work.
What did you do?
Did you just hypnotize them?
Yes.
Why are you a director?
Good-looking rich guys
always play directors in dramas.
So Mr. Director, what's your plan now?
I'll wait here.
Here? All day long?
If anything, I'm an expert at waiting.
I can sit here not only 24 hours,
but 24 years.
-Here.
-Okay.
Have a good day.
Call me if anything happens.
Sure.
Thanks, Yeon. For being there for me.
If you get into this,
it'll be either you or her.
One of you will die.
You and her fate was decided as such
the moment it was reborn.
This might be the end of my life.
It's not so bad.
I forgot to take off my nail tips.
Hello, I'm the new baby sitter.
Don't worry about everything else.
Just make sure he's fed well.
Today is the day.
The serpent will be fully grown
after today
with a new face and a new body.
TATTOO PUNISHMENT
IN JAPAN'S EDO PERIOD
A man in a navy suit came to see me.
He said there would be an accident
on March 3rd
at Fox Hill.
It was very faint,
but there was a trace of a mukhyeong
on his forehead.
Seo as in west, gyeong as in capital.
Tattooing the face as punishment was
one of the most severe sentences
which mutilated one's body.
Those with mukhyeong became shunned
and couldn't live with other people.
Seogyeong was an old name for Pyongyang.
SEOGYEONG
But why Seogyeong?
SEOGYEONG, MUKHYEONG
The leaders of the Myocheong Rebellion
were tattooed and exiled
after attempting
to move the capital to Seogyeong.
The Myocheong Rebellion.
A mob caused civil unrest
through divination and prophecies.
The criminals were tattooed with the word
Seogyeong or Seogyeong Rebel.
The bastard was a rebel.
Your parents weren't the target
to begin with.
He was after the daughter from the start.
Where are you?
I just got on his tail.
He's going somewhere in a rush.
-Alone?
-Yes, he's alone.
Keep your eyes on him.
So you're telling me to find a man
with a criminal's tattoo on his forehead.
And he's in with the serpent.
Yes, there must be a connection
between the serpent and Rang.
Damn it.
Did he lose his wallet or something?
Find the glasses.
Do whatever it takes to find it.
Glasses?
Who's he talking to?
-She's here.
-Begin the hearing.
Time out. Jae-hwan, show me your forehead.
What? Why?
Never mind.
Who's that guy?
-Who is he?
-A boyfriend?
-An informer, right?
-How much is the bet?
-It's 50,000 won.
-Tell us. Who is he?
I wonder. What is our relationship?
I want to know too.
What is that?
If you want to know
what that relationship is,
simply check your heart rate.
Your body doesn't lie.
Why is his heart racing?
His body could lie, I guess.
Did you hold hands with him?
We haven't held hands yet.
You didn't start by holding hands?
What did you hold?
Did you get a hold of a story?
Look at this rare item.
Why? What? What's with you? What?
I just want a good look at your forehead.
I know who took the glasses.
-Who is it?
-A little kid.
A kid?
You must've been drunk yesterday.
He's not family. He saved me from the zoo.
-So he's your savior.
-Precisely.
He tore the zookeeper in half.
You'll meet him soon enough.
Bye.
Did you think I wouldn't catch on?
Anyway, make yourself available tonight.
The president invited us to dinner.
Where is he treating us?
We're going to his house.
His house? That's so uncomfortable.
Uncomfortable? How so?
Only his closest associates
get invited there,
and he went out of his way to invite us.
Do you get what that means? Do you?
Anyway, forget it.
You're all eating samgyetang.
What's this?
I think there's a mistake.
We were about to order samgyetang.
Please enjoy. It's on the house.
-On the house?
What's with the VIP treatment, Ms. Bok?
I heard we had a very important guest.
Well, it's not an overstatement
when I say I brought
eighty percent of our office
to this restaurant, right?
You might go out of business
if you keep giving VIP's such as myself
so much free food.
Are you low on magnesium?
One of your eyes is twitching.
Please enjoy.
There are joyful and sorrowful legends
in each and every ingredient
used in our traditional dishes.
Just as the chef here.
Isn't she so eloquent?
Let's eat. Eat up.
You get such special treatment
only because you have me as the boss,
you good-for-nothings.
What have you been looking at?
At what?
It's nothing.
Come on.
Hey, it's that guy.
It's him, right?
It is. You sly fox.
Come and join us.
Me?
What a small city, right?
We all ran into one another
by coincidence.
It's not a coincidence.
Then why are you here?
Because Ms. Nam is here.
What's going on between you two?
Jae-hwan.
She doesn't like me,
but I've been hitting on her.
A crush?
While you let your looks go to waste?
It's true he's hitting on me,
but it goes both ways.
Why were you tailing me?
Why did Yeon put you on me?
Hey, bastard.
Do you think I'm the same little brat
that used to follow Yeon around?
I know that you aren't.
And I know
you can kill me right here
without leaving a trace.
Then tell me. Why did you follow me?
I'm sure
you know that best.
Are you playing games with me?
I lived my life for Mr. Lee Yeon.
And I lived thanks to him.
I mean that
I won't do anything to harm him
even if I was to die here.
Is that your loyalty or sympathy?
Or are you just plain stupid?
It's the same reason
why you can't seem to leave him alone.
We like him.
May I ask what you do for a living?
I don't work.
I knew it. I knew that was the case.
He follows Ji-a around
because he has too much free time
and doesn't know any better.
Can I break his ribs?
No. Calm down.
So are you really unemployed?
He's a landlord.
You own a building?
It's worth around 30 billion won.
Me?
Do you have any siblings?
-I have a younger brother--
-Brother-in-law!
Then how old are you?
I'm not that young.
-A thousand--
-He's older than he looks.
-Been there, done that, right?
-What do you mean?
He's asking if you've divorced as he has.
I see.
The guy who was married
for less than a year--
You're right!
So you've heard.
He doesn't have such a history.
He's like the main character
of a fantasy drama.
What's with him?
His routine. It's his thing.
Mr. Choi.
-Mr. Choi.
-Just eat.
I need to be somewhere.
Kid, are you okay?
You're so pretty.
I'm pretty?
Kids these days have really bad eyesight
because of smartphones.
-A eunuch.
-What?
What's a eunuch?
-Oh, it's a very sad situation.
-No, it's not!
-I can't show you--
-Don't do that around a kid.
He called me a eunuch.
Kids never lie.
Kid, are you ill?
You're scary.
-What?
-Your face is
really scary.
Is that the vibe I give off?
I just heard that kids never lie.
Hey, you're here.
-Where's Sin-ju?
-He's still breathing.
This wasn't necessary.
You should have just come to me.
You must adore him a lot.
Much more than the little brother
who's been in puberty
since the Joseon Dynasty.
Why did you tail me?
We both never beat around the bush, so,
why the serpent?
You finally caught on.
There are millions of ways to hurt me.
So why did you choose that?
Well, I wanted to see how it'll be
if history repeated itself.
I have a soft spot for drama.
Does it have something on you?
It does.
It's more of a deal
since I'm getting something in return.
Listen well.
There are certain beings
you should never make deals with.
I need to make a living too.
It's not too late to stop.
If you don't,
you'll pay a terrible price later on.
If I was ever in a situation,
where my life was in real danger,
would you come and save me?
You can save yourself.
Having fun with your first love recently?
But would she still stick around
if she found out
everything that happened in her past life?
If you lay a finger on her,
I'll really kill you this time.
Mr. Lee, I found that little boy.
I'll gladly let you kill me.
Let Sin-ju go.
You owe his life to me.
Mr. Lee.
Give me the glasses.
No, these are my magical glasses!
I don't go easy on kids.
Stop it. I hate it when people cry.
I would've killed you
if this was long ago.
I'll let you off
since the birth rate is low these days.
Come on, no way.
This can't be.
A black dog?
Yay! I'm so excited!
Faster!
Geomdoong, no.
I'll never love
such an insignificant thing again.
I'll never--
Why did you follow me?
Mister, are you Spider-Man?
You moved quickly just like him.
I honestly hate kids like you.
Then why did you buy me chocolate bread?
I'm paying my debt back.
"Take this, get lost."
Something like that.
A net? Like a hairnet?
And he seems stupid too.
Why did you have to be reborn as a human?
Let's go inside.
Ms. Nam, come on.
-Come quickly.
-Okay.
There's even a second floor.
I wonder how much this house is.
Why? Are you going to buy one?
It's not bad,
but it's too far from the subway station.
Goodness.
I can't believe
I'm seeing a bladder cherry here in Seoul.
This is a bladder cherry?
It looks like a lantern.
We used to pick the insides out
to make a flute out of these.
-These make sounds?
-Of course.
Mom used to scold me, saying that
snakes will appear if I blew on it.
Don't touch that.
It's very special to me.
Of course, I'm sorry.
There's just two rules to follow
in my house.
First, don't touch the bladder cherry.
-And no flutes.
-Yes, we don't want snakes.
Second, don't ever go up
to the second floor.
Is somebody there?
No, I live here alone.
And the caterers.
Just do as you're told.
You must be hungry.
-Mr. Lee.
-Yes?
Water.
-What?
-Water.
"Water."
Here.
The cap.
"The cap."
You want me to feed you?
I'm wounded.
Here.
Where's Ms. Nam?
A dinner occasion.
Shouldn't you be there?
She's with her colleagues.
I'll see her later.
Where's the fried chicken?
Right, the fried chicken.
It's on its way.
-One garlic fried chicken.
-Drumsticks.
-Did you order just regular?
-Yes.
You're really--
I'll let you off. That's good too.
Go feed the dog before the chicken comes.
Okay.
Wait.
Are you sure you're hurt?
Are you pretending just to boss me around?
I'm hurt physically
and emotionally.
Exactly. What did I tell you?
That necklace thief was suspicious.
Don't call her a thief.
She has a name. It's Yu-ri.
Yu-ri or whatever,
Rang is just using her to make use of you.
We just got off to a bad start,
but our relationship got 99 points.
You don't trust me. Here.
I checked our compatibility by name.
KI, GU, YU, SIN, RI, JU
NAM, LEE, JI, YEON, A
Nam Ji-a and Lee Yeon, "25 points?"
My back, my head,
my legs, and my broken heart.
I'm doing this again. This can't be.
Let's all make a toast.
Urban Legends team, keep the ratings up,
and stay on air for a long time.
-Let's do it.
-Let's do it!
-Tell him that story.
-When we went to Gonjiam,
I had a cross, a rosary, and a talisman,
the whole lot.
He even had a box of calming pills.
Of course, he was completely ready.
Even so,
his camera began to shake
as shooting started.
He almost got killed by Ji-a.
That's when I realized
humans can be much scarier than ghosts.
Ji-a has always been bold.
I caught that during the interview
and made sure she worked here.
I remember that. You said,
"You have to come work for us
no matter what."
I remember a story too.
It was when we were at that retreat.
We got there
and the microphone broke, so--
Were we ever at a retreat together?
Yes, we have.
Anyway, do you believe
in urban legends and ghost stories?
Long ago, I almost died once.
But I survived miraculously.
What I met back then wasn't a human.
Then what was it?
A miracle.
Gosh.
Where's the bathroom?
Straight down the hall.
I'll be back.
Sir, we once went to the awards ceremony…
Is somebody on the second floor?
I must have misheard.
What am I doing in someone else's house?
A nail tip?
I must be a champagne kind of guy.
-Stop him.
-That's enough, Mr. Choi.
How insolent of you.
Champagne isn't even hard liquor.
What's taking Ji-a so long?
-Should I go look for her?
-No, you're a guest. Stay here.
Return soon.
Come in.
Hey.
What time will you be done?
In about half an hour.
-Are you still at the animal hospital?
-Yes.
Give me the address. I'll be there.
No, Jae-hwan, Sae-rom, and I are
going to grab a cab.
Okay, then. See you at home.
See you later.
Sir.
The second floor is off-limits.
I'm sorry.
But is somebody in this room?
I heard something in there.
Probably the wind. I left the window open.
I see.
-Let's go eat some dessert.
-Okay.
Why are you crying?
I haven't seen you this happy in ages.
Sure.
Take a good long look.
And only try to remember me like this.
-You sound like someone about to leave.
-Leave? Where to?
Live long.
And be as happy as you can be
while Ms. Nam is alive.
Okay.
It's a misconception.
Ji-a, you're here. Are ghosts bad?
Is that why they're exorcised?
In that case, they should be arrested.
That's my take, sir.
I believe we're in a community.
It doesn't matter if they're ghosts
who have supernatural powers.
When we run into them,
when we meet them,
we should thank them.
"Thank you for letting us make a living.
Please do more weird stuff for our sake."
The least we can do is
ask them for such a favor.
You picked this up at his place?
-Yes.
-It's gross.
It's a glue-on nail tip.
Looks pretty cheap.
Whose is it?
It wasn't you or me.
The caterers had clean nails too.
And his wife passed away a decade ago.
You should ask
if he's seeing anyone.
To the president?
How will you get through life
with a mind like that?
It'd make more sense
if he had a secret hobby.
Doing nail art?
What kind of a hobby is that?
Your rice is fully cooked.
You're home.
Did you make rice?
I already ate.
I know that. But you said you like
the smell of freshly cooked rice.
When it comes to cooking, I'm--
I can at least make rice.
So this is how it feels
to come home to the scent
of freshly cooked rice.
I'll let you smell this every day
while I stay here.
Here.
-What's this?
-I picked it up on the way.
-Mint chocolate chip?
-I'll go get changed.
I thought you picked up recyclables.
What do you usually do at night?
Don't you enjoy American TV?
I also read books and watch the news.
I usually watch movies.
Shall we?
Should we?
-What's that?
-What is that?
It's over here.
Hey, is there a way out?
This is no joke, really.
What people said on the internet was true.
Did you get that on camera? Did you?
Why? Is the movie boring?
No, it's fun.
So much so that
I want time to stop right now.
Me too.
For me,
it's the smell of freshly cooked rice.
A new pair of sneakers.
Put these on and look in the mirror.
You'll find what you wanted to know.
New sneakers.
I have no idea what women like.
Excuse me-- Darn it.
What?
I sent your woman a gift.
It's a thing called the Tiger's Brows.
LEE YEON
How silly.
This woman means nothing to me.
Don't you think it was me
who used her to lure you out?
Yeon.
Did you see it?
Answer me. Did you?
Will you please look at me?
What in the world…
did you see?
I was
killed in my previous life.
You…
killed me.
You only wanted
to capture the serpent.
Lee Yeon.
You used me…
as a sacrifice.
If I'm reborn,
I want to try living as a human.
I won't let you win anymore.
Where is the serpent right now?
From birth, you've always been
nothing but a sacrifice offered to me.
She'll be my bride.
What are you most afraid of?
The Fox Hill.
Starting now,
I'm going to do everything I can.
Mom!
A little bit.
Hold out just a bit longer.
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon