THE BOOK OF THE DEAD
NAME: NAM JI-A
BIRTH: MARCH 3RD, 1991
DEATH: TODAY
Yeon.
Yes, it's me.
I'm sorry.
My body wouldn't move as I like
on my way to the inner room.
It's all right. You've held out just fine.
I can still feel
how it's creeping around in my head.
Let's hurry.
I want to remain as myself
in the last moment of my life.
So that I can
stay by your side.
Let's finish this.
Let's put an end
to this tiring fight.
Hey, are you okay?
Let's go.
Why?
Why do you do this?
What?
Do you enjoy making a mess of the world?
Is that it?
No.
To be honest,
reading books is much more fun.
Then why are you doing this?
I want Lee Yeon to die.
He's not just going to die
even if you do this.
That's exactly why.
He never gets tired
and keeps coming at me.
He keeps trying to defy his fate.
There's no turning back now.
He and I both
have already crossed the line.
Mr. Lee!
Are you hurt?
Not really.
Okay. Then it's time for you to get hurt.
How dare you trick me?
This was the only way.
Shut up.
You should've known when
he gathered us to tell us the strategy.
As if you knew.
If he had the sword,
he wouldn't have talked so much.
He would've started swinging first.
What did you say?
Mr. Lee is a man of action
or something like that.
So did you find the answer
you were looking for?
Well, sort of.
What was the answer?
-The key.
-What key?
The key it needs
to get in and out of its vessels.
Then can we drag it out of Ms. Nam?
That's not good enough.
Sorry?
I'm going to bury it for good
so that it'll never come back.
Stop right there.
Don't you hear me?
You'll lose everything
once you walk out that door.
I'll make sure of it!
What do I have?
Position as lord of Samdocheon,
powers to rival a deity,
and eternal life, I gave it all to you!
That's not what I want.
I want my wife and son.
Honey.
Living an eternity with you…
is my biggest punishment.
Stop right there.
I said stop right there!
Goodness.
-Mr. Choi.
-Yes?
Did anything happen?
Are you okay?
What did Mr. Choi say?
A police officer died.
-What's the cause?
-He had a heart attack.
But when Mr. Choi did CPR,
he saw weird spots
covering his entire body.
Also, he vomited an egg.
An egg?
Don't tell me
they're with Mr. Choi right now.
Where are you?
How can something so awful
happen to me at this age?
I saw a man die right in front of my eyes.
-It was right in my face!
-We told you not to--
Get away from him right now.
Okay.
Did Mr. Choi go to the police station?
Yes. He gave first aid to the deceased.
Is everything okay?
For now.
You need to see this.
DEAD BODIES COVERED IN SPOTS
AN OUTBREAK OF MYSTERIOUS DEATHS
The death toll is spiking exponentially.
I need to go out for a bit.
Where?
You can go home first.
But don't go alone. Go with them.
Yeon, you must hurry.
The old woman changed Ji-a's death date.
TRADITIONAL KOREAN CUISINE: SNAIL BRIDE
What's wrong?
Everything is unfolding just as he warned.
What did he say?
He'll spread an epidemic
and kill everyone dear to me.
Wait, my mom and dad.
I'll go. Please go home as Mr. Lee said.
-But--
-Don't worry.
Mr. Lee Rang, please.
Say, "Please escort me home."
-Not over my dead body.
-Then die.
It's not on me if the serpent takes you.
You're both in the same boat to me.
Don't you think that applies to you?
The female serpent.
Let's go our separate ways.
As you wish.
What a tough cookie.
What does Yeon see in her?
What? What's going on?
This…
Mr. Hyeonuiong?
Thank goodness.
I got here just in time.
My dear, are you hurt?
I'm fine.
The ones from Samdocheon
have begun to make a move.
I'm relieved.
It seems like
things will get serious very soon.
Granny.
Choose the words you blurt
out of your mouth very carefully.
I'm just as lousy as you are now.
Did you tamper with the book?
Did you choose to make me your enemy?
Did you really choose the path that
you'll never forgive yourself for?
No matter what you say, I won't revoke
what I wrote down in the book.
That is
what I have chosen.
Why is it Jia
over the one who caused this plague?
Were you able to slay it with a sword?
My sword doesn't kill you.
What's inside the girl is the problem.
You have to catch that
to cut down the one outside.
In order to do that,
the girl must die.
I'll say it one last time.
Put everything back to its place.
This is the rightful place.
This is how we end this.
No.
No one can
take Ji-a away.
I don't care if it's you, Granny.
It's already out of your hands.
Come.
That means until I die,
things like that car accident
will keep happening.
I'm glad I said goodbye to Mom and Dad.
I'm sorry.
Why should you be sorry?
You saved my life.
I tried my best to stop her,
but this was all I could do.
Where's Yeon?
He went to settle this with her.
Will he be okay?
I'm not sure.
She has never changed her mind
when it comes to something
that she thinks is right.
Yeon knows that too.
Then because of me, he--
He's putting everything he has
on the line right now.
I'll pay with my life.
Give me three days.
If I don't catch that thing in three days,
slay me.
I can't do that.
He's already out of control.
I have its scale.
-It's too late.
-I can catch it. I can catch the serpent!
How many lives do you think
it'll take in the next three days?
Who can say their lives are less worthy
than the one you wish to protect?
Let her live.
Please don't kill her.
I'll do anything.
I'll do whatever you tell me.
Grab the sword instead.
Stop acting like an idiot.
Just be yourself and fight me!
Please.
Yeon.
I wouldn't have started this
if I could undo it.
How could you do this to me?
I lost my son and my husband.
I can always lose you too.
You'll regret this,
Granny.
Where did it all go wrong?
If it weren't for me,
Yeon would've been living his life
as a mountain deity to this day.
No.
If I hadn't been born at all--
Dear, it's not your fault.
Why do you despise yourself
and try so hard
to deny your relationships?
I feel like it's all my fault.
We immortals are just like you.
We all live our lives
leaning on certain memories.
For me, it was the son I lost.
For Snail Bride, it's her loving husband.
And Yeon could go on because of you.
The serpent said
I'll end up
killing Yeon with my own hands.
That's why you two are
putting up a fight to protect each other.
Both you and Yeon.
Either way, it's a dead end.
Damn it. This thing doesn't light up.
You said you were going to quit.
I tried just about everything
to quit smoking.
I tried taking eundan,
nicotine patches, and chewing gum.
There's even medicine these days.
What I'm saying is I couldn't quit
even after all that fuss.
What are you saying?
What if nothing changes
no matter how much you struggle?
What if only one of you can live?
So nothing will…
change in the end.
Want me to blow on it?
This is already on you.
Or do you want this car?
Gosh, there's no point in talking to you.
And you,
do something about that runny nose
around me.
I have a weak stomach.
How long have you been wearing that?
Did you even wash it?
Run to the store and get new clothes.
I'm highly concerned about my hygiene.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Hey, why are these stickers on me?
I'll kill you when I get out!
The weather is nice.
It's very sunny.
Here's your coffee.
This tree has grown a lot.
You're right. It grew up so well.
So what's on your mind?
As all these years passed by,
where in the world were we?
Tell me about it.
Apparently, we've been missing
for a long time. Isn't it odd?
All I remember is being asleep.
It's weird we don't have any bedsores.
And Ji-a looks anxious for some reason.
I thought of Ieo Island's legend.
Ieo Island?
A fisherman accidentally
drifted into a fantasy island,
and when he returned,
a hundred years had passed.
But I'm grateful Ji-a grew up well
just like that tree.
Is this all we have?
It's delicious.
I want some naengmyeon.
Yu-ri.
When is she coming back?
I'm thinking about a good time
to bring her back.
Why do you only think about it?
Once I've thought it through,
Yeon will end up losing something.
It has been 600 years.
I'm going to put an end
to this tiresome fight once and for all.
What if you fail?
Rang.
That's why I need you.
If anything happens to me,
I want you to finish this.
I want you to be my final weapon.
I refuse.
I don't care if the serpent
destroys this world or kills your woman.
We want to protect different things.
-Rang.
-You can protect her.
I'll get Yu-ri back
and save you.
Why are you laughing?
I don't think I'm cut out
to be a good kid.
I'm leaving.
Keep the house safe, Geomdoong.
Why do you call me Geomdoong?
Si-yeong.
Why, hello.
What brings you here at this hour?
I came to have some samgyetang.
By the way, are you feeling okay?
What are you talking about?
I may look weak,
but I do 200 squats a day.
Do you want to see my thighs?
Come on. Take a seat.
Sure.
Si-yeong.
Seven police officers
were hospitalized just this morning.
What about Mr. Choi?
You already saw how he's totally fine.
I keep telling him to see a doctor,
but he won't listen.
If he's fine,
shouldn't we be fine too?
Let's worry about editing first.
Come along.
Goodness.
I'm sorry to bother you
before you're open.
I've been feeling queasy all morning,
but I feel so much better now.
What's wrong?
Why do you look so pale?
Do I have a fever?
Not at all. Goodness, you're so cold.
Give me your hand.
Your hand is cold too.
How can a person turn this cold?
It's a snake egg.
He's asleep again.
Time to wake up.
Sir, time to wake up.
Sir?
Director?
What's going on?
He's dead.
Hey, call 911 now.
I'll go get help.
What? Dead?
Everyone on our floor?
One second.
Breaking news. There's been an outbreak
of mysterious deaths all over Seoul.
It has been two days since the first death
from a hospital in Geumran-gu.
The authorities presume
this is caused by an unknown disease
that is highly lethal
and highly contagious.
The victims were covered with red spots
all over their body.
The autopsy result
of the first victim showed
serious damage on the inside,
as if his organs were
mutilated by an animal.
Kim, a 32-year-old man,
did not have any pre-existing conditions…
What do you think?
It's tacky.
It's not my style.
Then it must be fine.
Where are you going?
To get a cup of tea.
To celebrate, I'll let you see him.
-See him?
-Your boyfriend.
You can go see him.
Yu-ri.
Yu-ri, are you okay?
I need to see you now.
Now?
Where?
I'll go to you.
Come out.
I know you're hiding inside me.
If you don't come out in three…
I'll kill myself.
One.
Two.
Three.
You crazy broad.
You're just a shell.
How dare you summon me?
"A shell"?
You live in someone else's body
without paying rent.
Stop acting like you're the landlord.
There will be a new owner soon.
in a day or two.
Your body will soon be completely mine.
That's longer than I expected.
Why?
The Fox Marble disappeared
a long time ago.
It's just an aftereffect.
That marble made me sleep for too long.
Say your goodbyes in advance.
Once I take over,
the one who'll be trapped
and asleep forever
will be you.
That means until that time,
you're incomplete.
Darn it. What can you do anyway?
What if I died before then?
You could never do that.
When humans have
something they want to protect,
they can do anything.
They can end up doing something crazy.
Help!
What's wrong?
-Miss!
-Get up!
What's wrong?
Is anybody around? Someone call 911!
Is anyone there? What do I do?
Listen to this brat.
That's all.
You can go back inside.
That's all I wanted to know.
Girl.
Lee Yeon will be doomed because of you.
He will never give up on you.
If you have time
to be concerned about my love life,
look after your other half.
He couldn't get over his broken heart,
and seems to want to drag
both you and me to hell.
He wouldn't do that.
My death date was changed.
Do you think he didn't know
the lady of Samdocheon would do this
if he massacred innocent people?
Are you in there?
Yes, I'll be out in a second.
Yu-ri.
Are you alright? Let me see you.
I'm not hurt.
That's a relief.
I was worried to death.
How did you get here?
Did you run away?
Why didn't you tell me it was the serpent?
Where's Mr. Lee Rang?
He's up.
He won't say it,
but he's very worried about you.
I'm relieved.
Let's go.
Mr. Lee will be thrilled--
We can't.
What?
We can't go.
Both me or you.
What do you mean?
I'm holding you down
and stalling right now.
What do you…
No.
Let me go.
I already said we can't go.
To celebrate, I'll let you see him.
Your boyfriend.
You can go see him.
Why should I do as you say?
Because if I see Sin-ju today,
he'll die.
Hey, Dad.
Hey, Ji-a. Where are you?
I'm outside. Why?
A friend of yours came to see you.
My friend? Who?
I told you not to let anyone in.
No, it's because I know him.
Mom or you wouldn't know anybody.
Is it Yeon?
No, the fair-skinned young man
I told you about.
The carnation.
What?
I told you.
I won't be nice to you from now on.
I won't let you do this.
If you hurt my parents, I'll--
Don't fight against your fate.
I can destroy everything you care about.
Who are you?
You aren't her friend, are you?
No, Mom.
Don't do that!
I want to hang myself.
No!
You can't go out.
No, I have to go.
My parents are in danger. Please.
No.
Go to sleep.
How did you know I was here?
I just came back from Samdocheon.
It was the old woman's clairvoyance.
She changed Ji-a's death date,
thanks to that plague you spread.
She's still alive.
I just got off the phone with her.
Lord Hyeonuiong is protecting her for me.
Well, that won't last too long.
You said you were just there.
Why didn't you beg her for her life?
I've begged enough.
It didn't work.
Once Ji-a dies,
your other half that's in her
won't be safe either.
So?
What is it you really want?
Do you want to guess?
Your existence itself is destitution,
back when you were a human child
and even now.
You're so cursed
it feels like the almighty wanted
to screw with your life.
That's the serpent.
Are you picking a fight?
No, it's the contrary.
What?
What if there's a better way
to make up for your neediness
than obsessing over me or Ji-a?
What if you took over a position
that a lowly mountain deity
wouldn't even dream of?
Try to make some sense.
The deity of deities.
No way.
I'm talking about the lord of Samdocheon.
Let's take down
the lord of Samdocheon together.
That's new.
It's unexpected.
I can't believe
you decided to betray that old lady.
If I can save Ji-a,
I can do anything.
So, you're going to join hands with me?
Of course, even if it means
I must team up with the likes of you.
What's the condition?
Let Ji-a go.
Take back your other half that's in her,
and don't ever look for us again.
That's my only condition.
Would you believe that this isn't a trap?
I wouldn't if I were you.
What?
Then try to guess.
What do you think I'll say?
No is what you'd like to say,
but you'll end up accepting my offer.
What makes you so confident?
We're both at a dead end.
If you don't accept my offer,
you'll lose your other half,
and I'll lose Ji-a.
Then we'll both end up going to hell
after a bloody fight.
That's all I've wanted
since my last date with her.
Call me if you change your mind.
You have until sunrise tomorrow.
You knew the serpent went to kill them,
but you're holding me down? Why?
Did he threaten you?
Or were you mind-controlled
like when you stabbed Mr. Lee Rang?
-It's neither.
-Then why?
Why did you do that?
Who cares about those petty humans?
"Those petty humans"?
I thought you came to see me.
I was worried sick about you!
But
I was nothing but bait.
You took advantage of me.
-Sin-ju--
-Stop.
If you say another word…
I might regret loving you
for the first time.
You must've been worried.
They're both fine.
I erased their memories too.
They won't even remember
having met the serpent.
Thank you, Yeon.
It's all my fault. I was away.
It's not your fault.
I know you've been protecting my parents.
Thank you, sir,
for protecting Ji-a in my place.
What are you going to do now?
I'll work with the serpent.
What?
What do you mean?
Because of my old woman?
Yes.
So she
ended up letting go of you.
She gave me a chance.
Another chance to fight.
Can you be more specific?
We got two more days.
You'll be safe in the meantime.
Then I'll be--
Of course. Why would you die?
I'm still here guarding you.
Then you're working with him to--
Of course, that's what it is.
I knew it, Mr. Lee.
-What was her condition?
-Nothing.
I just have to bring in the serpent.
-Yeon.
-Later.
I'll tell you the details later.
I'm going out to eat with Ji-a.
I'll go get changed.
What if the ending won't change
no matter how hard you try?
What if
only one of you can live?
So the ending…
won't change.
Then I don't even need to think about it.
What's your plan?
I'll eat
this thing.
I'll take the serpent in Ji-a in my body,
take the other half, then jump
into the Samdocheon.
I'll make sure
he never comes back to life.
If you jump in there yourself, you--
I know.
I won't be allowed to be reborn.
And that
I'll never go back to be with Ji-a.
I'm sorry to cause you trouble.
I could've gone to the hospital.
They couldn't help you.
This disease isn't
what you people think it is.
It's very cold.
Hang in there.
This terrible fight will end soon.
So until then, hang in there.
I knew it.
Hye-ja, you aren't
an ordinary person, are you?
Goodness, my lord.
I was wondering why you were closed today.
I'm sorry.
My goodness.
Come on out.
I--
Did you bring him here knowing who he was?
What in the world are you talking about?
He's your husband.
What?
He's your husband from the past life,
the man you never got over.
Is anybody there?
Hey! Someone's dying here!
Damn it. Damn it!
Are you okay?
-Goodness, you have spots all over.
-Detective.
Get me to a hospital.
It's no use.
It'll only postpone death.
The mortality rate is 100 percent.
Goodness.
What happened to you?
Wait.
Since when did detectives
put on shoes
that didn't have a speck of dust?
Man, this darned dress code.
Who sent you?
Was it Yeon? Or--
What does it matter on the brink of death?
I'm sure you aren't here to watch me die.
I like doing that a lot.
Look, I even brought popcorn.
I even take tours of funeral halls.
What do you want? Tell me.
You're dying.
How dare you try to make a deal?
Are you still stuck in the past
when you had that serpent behind you?
Once the serpent dies,
this damned sickness
will also disappear, right?
Probably.
Get me out of here.
Why should I?
I've served him
much longer than you realize.
Which means
no one knows him better than I do.
So?
Are you trying to
talk your way out of this?
And get well for free?
No, thanks.
I'm not such a good fighter,
and I hate getting scars.
I get what you mean.
That's why you're here.
You don't want blood on your hands.
He ran away!
Who?
The serial murder suspect.
Who let him out?
Well, the CCTV shows--
What? Why can't you say it?
It was you.
What?
GOPBUN'S GRILLED TRIPE
Let me take your order.
Yes, an order of grilled tripe set
and a bottle of soju.
And lots of cheese.
Sure.
-Enjoy your meal.
-Thank you.
That's a lot of cheese.
What?
You're so pretty.
Gosh.
Promise me.
What promise?
Let's come back
on the day of the first snow.
Okay.
And you'll spend Christmas with me.
We'll go back to the beach
we went to together.
Okay.
Also, on New Year's Day,
come to my house
and have rice cake soup with my parents.
And on my birthday…
What do you want?
Okay, I'll buy it for you.
And what must you do
to keep all these promises?
I need to live a long life.
Cheers.
What is this?
-Did someone force you?
-Why didn't you say it was your birthday?
People don't remember lunar birthdays
nowadays.
Only their moms would.
It smells good.
I have two tropical fish in my apartment.
Do they have names?
Deok-bae and Chun-sam.
Both are of the Gyeongju Kim clan.
I promised to buy them a huge tank
once I get paid this month.
Will you adopt them from me?
You need to make a wish first.
I want to eat cake from Jae-hwan again
on my next birthday.
That was the last.
This might be
the last bottle of soju
we'll drink together.
I'll drink it little by little.
Why would you say that?
Earlier, the half inside my body said
I have only two days at max.
After two days,
I'll become an empty shell.
That won't happen.
Won't everything be okay if I disappear?
Once I die, the serpent will be gone.
Then everyone I love--
including my family, friends, and you--
won't be hurt anymore.
Don't ever think like that again.
But you know,
if that happens,
how will you live once I leave you?
Then
I'll live a long time blaming myself
thinking, "I failed to protect you again."
I feel the same way.
I don't think
I can live a good life without you.
That's why we have to protect each other.
Let's never give the serpent
what he wants.
Hey, Jae-hwan.
What?
I told you not to come.
Why are you here?
How did this happen to you?
How?
Don't touch me.
It's contagious.
Let's not see
each other's ugly faces again.
I didn't think this would be our farewell.
I know. You should've died by my hands.
Now that it's come to this,
try your best to survive.
You just made up with your brother.
Can you handle the consequences?
No.
Yeon will never forgive me.
I might never see him again.
It's still better than him dying.
That's enough.
People who live a sad life like you
never have a happy ending.
The bladder cherries are gone,
and I only have one human life left.
Don't curse me.
I'll use all my money before I die.
Bye.
You can protect her.
I'll get Yu-ri back and save you.
How could I not recognize him?
He kept bothering me,
so I gave him such a tough time.
He must have known you missed him a lot,
then came to find you here.
What's the point?
I finally found him again,
but look at how he's doing.
This is too much. Seriously.
Do you think it's a coincidence?
What?
These complicated relationships
all began to gather in one place
around Yeon and that girl,
the woman from the past life,
his family, friends, and
enemy.
I feel uneasy.
It feels like
something we can't handle
might begin to unravel.
You should stay here for a while.
Stay with me.
Hey, send him away.
Don't stay. You might catch it.
I would've caught it already.
Maybe it's a latent period.
Come on. Beat him up.
I still won't leave.
I'll protect you. You'll need a caretaker.
I'm going to talk to him for a minute.
Keep an eye on her.
How's Mr. Choi?
He coughed up an egg,
but he didn't get any better.
What's with the egg?
There's a baby snake in there.
That's what eats people up.
I can't bear to see her die.
Never.
Everything will be over soon.
I just need him to take my bait. Then…
So until then,
hang in there a little longer.
Give me a little more time.
Let's take down
the lord of Samdocheon together.
Call me if you change your mind.
You have until sunrise tomorrow.
Just one more bite.
I'm finished.
Ms. Kim.
-Ms. Kim.
-Ms. Kim!
Ms. Kim.
Fine.
Let's take down
the lord of Samdocheon together.
Yeon and the serpent?
You must be kidding.
No.
Sorry?
He's committing suicide.
That idiot is
going to kill himself with the serpent.
Lee Yeon,
you will fall into your own trap.
And now, we're up on the same stage.
It's a stage
we can't come down from
until we're both dead.
What are you doing here?
You have to die for me to survive.
I'm going to end everything myself.
Don't do this.
If you do this, you'll--
Goodbye.
What?
There was no rain in the forecast.
When did you get here?
As soon as the unexpected shower fell.
To take me home?
I don't want you to get wet.
What about work? Are you all done?
It was an easy video,
so I edited everything quickly.
Who in the world is
trying to ruin Ji-a's reunion?
It's Mr. Choi.
-And me.
-What?
I didn't drive today.
You're right. You left your car.
Your house is only 20 minutes away.
We don't have time to go on dates
because of your parents.
Buy me a bowl of ramyeon.
Then I'll let you go.
Okay.
Isn't this too little?
It is. We're way short.
I said we should get two.
Do you know the two conditions
that make ramyeon delicious?
One is kimchi. What's the other?
Someone who steals a bite.
I'll help you make it delicious.
You eat so well.
I want some soup, but I'll pass.
Why?
I might crave soju.
I knew you were smart.
Did you know it reaches 40m
if you line up the noodles?
That's the height of the 13 floors.
Are you showing off your trivia?
I don't even want to be
half a bag of ramyeon away from you.
Is that sweet talk with ramyeon?
You're always cute, aren't you?
I've been known for being cute
since my Baekdu Mountain days.
You look happy
for the first time in a long time.
I am.
My parents are waiting for me at home.
And I have you in front of me.
All my hopes and dreams came true.
Who'll make your dreams come true?
How would it feel to live as a human?
I don't care if you're a human,
or a Nine-tailed Fox.
We're here together now.
If I don't stop her,
she'll try to protect me again
instead of herself.
Don't do this.
You have to understand me.
I'm going to wait for you.
Just as you waited for me.
This is hell,
where I'm standing right now.
Do you know what it means?
If I fail, you kill me.
If anything happens to Yeon…
How did you…
This was your plan all along.
No.
-I can't do this.
-No!
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon