(The Heirs)
(Episode 4)
Cha Eun Sang. Stop right there.
Have a safe trip.
Call me when you arrive.
Why didn't you call me?
Didn't your friend tell you?
- He did.
- Then you should've called me.
Are you going to Korea now?
What did you want to say?
Give me your number.
What are you waiting for?
"Thank you for everything."
I thanked you.
"Bye." I said goodbye.
I did all I should do.
So don't leave your fiancee alone
to ask something trivial like that.
Here's the declaration form.
(Customs Declaration)
What are you doing?
I'm waiting for you
to finish writing.
Finish it first.
What's the matter?
I've thought about it.
I got a sad premonition
that we'll meet again.
That won't happen.
You say that because
you don't know Kim Tan well.
If that sad premonition comes true,
I think I'll want to see you first.
But I don't know anything about you.
That's why.
What do you mean?
Let's say this is
how we introduced ourselves.
Hey.
I'm sorry, but you cannot enter
unless you're in first class.
No, the girl who just walked in
took my declaration form.
If you wait here, I'll check.
I'm sorry, but she said she didn't.
What...
(Welcome back, my stepsister!)
If you're bored, go wash the dishes.
You said you weren't coming.
Why did you come and bother me?
Did you help me not to?
You told your mom that you changed
the flight.
Couldn't you just come back quietly?
You shouldn't have lost to your dad.
Unless you want to walk home,
let's go quietly. Without talking.
I'll tell Mom that you came
to pick me up,
so push it.
Gosh.
You must be dying to know
how Tan's doing. He's doing well.
Tan asked me how you are doing.
I said you're still mean
and living very well.
The fox is playing
because the tiger's away.
- Stop the car.
- Yes, sir.
Have you ever thought about this?
Why is the tiger away?
Maybe he just pretended
to be a tiger.
Maybe he ran away...
before people find out.
- What do you...
- Goodbye.
What? Where did everything go?
Hey, Eun Sang.
Ma'am. What happened?
Where is my mom?
Your mom moved out.
She's working as a resident maid.
What?
I'm sorry,
but can I borrow your phone?
The chairman is ill.
The mood in the house is down.
Sleep in the sauna tonight
and come tomorrow morning.
I saw that you wore jeans
without socks last week.
I know it's summer,
but I didn't like it.
It won't happen again.
But you're wearing a skirt today.
You wore shorts the week before.
Let me ask you again.
While you're tutoring, please
avoid clothes that show your skin.
No V-neck either.
Refrain from wearing perfume
or manicuring your nails too.
Yes, ma'am.
(High school math)
You scared me.
When did you get here?
You were so quiet.
Isn't my family annoying?
It is.
How come you don't quit then?
Your mom pays me a lot.
And I need that money.
Open your book.
I like it.
Like what?
Everything my mom told you
not to do.
I like it too, but I won't do it.
To me, one who pays me
is always right.
So your taste doesn't
help me make a living.
Do you get it?
It's page 16.
(Kim Won)
Page 15?
Why aren't you answering?
We're in class. Look at the book.
Is it your boyfriend?
It's integration by substitution.
Not rings. A necklace, please.
Necklace? Absolutely, sir.
Please take a look right here.
- The wishbone?
- Absolutely, sir.
Please show our guest.
Sir. If I may say, this necklace
will make your dreams come true.
What? That was the house deposit?
Then where else would I
get such big money?
I can't believe you.
Are you insane, Mom?
How could you give it all to her?
She was lying about the wedding.
I heard it. She called me.
Crazy witch. How dare she call her?
What did she say?
Did she say it was all a lie?
She said sorry
and asked if you're back safely.
Is that all? Did you let it go?
What if I don't?
What else can I do other than
hitting the phone?
So why did you give
all that money to her?
That witch betrayed her mom
and sister to live well by herself.
Don't you get mad?
Don't call your sister a witch.
What are we going to do now?
Are we going to live on streets?
Wait here.
Why? For how long?
How many minutes?
It's me.
Ms. Park. What's wrong with you?
Is spying on the first madam
going well?
It was just the other day.
What do you think?
Do you trust me?
What does that mean?
My goodness. Am I being threatened?
Yes. It hurts me too.
Seriously.
Who threatens with affection?
What do you want?
Madam. The first madam is here.
What? Why all of a sudden?
Did you tell her?
Not yet, but since she's here...
Wait.
What is it? Tell me what you want.
You have to tell...
Write it.
Put on something clean and neat.
When did you change your socks?
Put on new socks.
What are you doing?
This is where we're going to live
from now on.
What?
What do you do
aside from wasting food?
Why didn't you tell me
that the chairman is ill?
He's sick every other day.
How can I report it to you
every time?
Do you want him to die or live?
What? What did you just say?
You shouldn't be doing this
in someone else's house...
so early in the morning.
- You're so energetic.
- What? Someone else's house?
One who doesn't belong here is you.
You're not even on the family
register. Watch your mouth.
That stupid family register.
You can't even give birth.
You never disappoint me.
"That stupid family register"?
So is the child you gave birth to
with you right now?
- What?
- That's what family register is.
You and I both don't have a child.
Life is long.
Just because he's not with me now,
doesn't mean he won't be
with me tomorrow.
The blood is thicker than water
for a reason.
- You...
- So, first madam.
You need to manage your vigor well.
Don't get dragged out when you get
kicked out of the family register.
You should at least walk out on...
I can't take it anymore.
Keep going. Say some more.
Did you slap me?
Did you just slap me?
Can't you believe it?
You want me to slap you again?
Mr. Kim is coming.
- You're home.
- You should go see your father.
How was your business trip
to the US?
You went to the US?
I'm home.
I'll let you guys chat.
- Put the carry on in my room.
- Yes, sir.
He wasn't home?
Yes, life is long.
And blood is thicker than water.
What are you talking about?
Then did the chairman and Won
share water?
Let's see how well Tan will protect
his mom...
against his brother.
That witch.
She doesn't intimidate me at all.
Ms. Park. Ice.
Follow me. Bring medicine
to the chairman's room.
Me?
Hello.
Mom went to do Madam's errand.
Are you Ms. Park Hee Nam's daughter?
Pardon?
Yes.
Why are you standing there
like that?
Sit down.
I have to go to work soon.
What a lame excuse.
I met Tan.
I know people who went to the party
better than you do.
But...
no one talked about Tan.
You should rescind
your brother's exile now.
Or I will.
I understand your pain.
So, to be fair,
I turned a blind eye
to you hurting Tan.
But...
you're taking it way too far.
That's not fair.
Is making the weight of pain
the same...
your idea of fairness?
I have...
never hugged Tan
because you might hate it.
I think...
I'd end up regretting.
That sounds like...
you raised me with love.
Are you sure you wouldn't
regret anything about me?
Do you think...
I'm asking for your opinion?
I'll get going.
She's ridiculous.
Neither of us is a good wife.
I know. There's even a book
about it.
"You're a Concubine
Because It Hurts".
What?
Doesn't this family look ridiculous,
even to you?
You must be happy since you're poor.
You wouldn't have to deal with this.
Well, that can't be the reason.
Hold on.
If Won went to the US,
he must've met Tan.
I'm going in.
If you're going to the US,
you should've...
Ask Father if it's about Tan.
Did you meet Tan?
What did he say? Is he doing well?
Is he all right? Did he ask you
about me?
Don't you know his phone number?
You want me to give it to you?
He never picks up.
Right. Let me ask you
since we're on the topic.
Until when will you stop Tan
from coming to Korea?
Do you have to be this mean?
What did an 18-year-old do so...
I was an heir to Jeguk Group
at that age.
I was a major stockholder
with eight percent of voting right.
Fine. Then I take it back.
But Won,
I'm too ashamed to see Tan.
I'm still his mom,
but that lonely boy...
This isn't church.
Go make a confession somewhere else.
I'm a Buddhist.
It's been three years.
I've gotten a lot taller.
Is that all?
All you've done in the US.
Stop there.
Coming here took more courage
than you deserve.
Who's stronger?
Between the ladies fighting earlier.
Who should I worry about more?
They were obviously a wife
and a concubine.
Who's more influential?
No, they are a second wife
and a concubine.
Really?
The chairman looked like a nice
person, but I guess not.
Where's the first wife?
She passed away.
The mother of the president you saw
was the first wife.
So did Chan Young's dad
help you move in?
You must be her daughter.
Hello. I'm Cha Eun Sang.
What grade are you in?
I'm in Grade 11.
As you saw,
this family isn't exactly elegant.
Don't let what you see and hear here
get out of the fence.
You're in Grade 11.
You understand what I mean, right?
- Yes.
- Right.
I trust your mom because she
can't do it even if she wants to.
Thank you for being considerate
of me and my mom like this.
We'll move out as soon as possible.
While I'm here,
I'll stay quiet as if I'm not here.
If there's still anything you feel
uncomfortable about, please tell me.
I'll fix it.
Okay. I see.
Give her something delicious.
I'll do the dishes. Go rest.
Then can you get me a bottle
of wine from the cellar?
One from 2000.
Be nice.
What did she say?
That you're a nice lady.
Don't lie.
I'm not that nice to your mom.
Even her daughter is smart.
Don't wake up. Just go to sleep.
I'll finish it.
Thank you.
Here.
A gift from the US.
A snack to eat with a drink
when I think of your sister?
That's the best for a diet.
I'll get a part-time job.
You eat this, lose weight,
and seduce a rich man.
That's the fastest way
for us to get out of here.
Sure. Let's do that.
I'm sorry, Mom.
That I left you.
Forgive me.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I'm so sorry.
Here's your drink.
For delivery.
(Inspection hour)
Take-out, please.
Okay.
Here's your fried chicken.
(Check the deposit)
(Cha Eun Sang)
Chan Young. It's your debtor.
Yes. Give me your account number.
I can send it tomorrow morning.
You're coming to Korea? When?
Right. The break is over
soon already.
Did you sleep well?
No, I didn't.
I'm worried about Tan.
I stayed up all night.
But you were snoring.
Snoring?
Nam Yoon. The room is dry.
Does Tan even want to come back?
He didn't leave
because he wanted to.
I'll make him come back
even if he doesn't want to.
We cared enough about Won
for three years.
Do you even miss Tan?
Of course I do.
You only need Won.
Even better with both of them.
Really? Do you mean it?
You're allowing it then.
You take care of Won.
If he's too scared to be back
because of his brother,
he shouldn't at all.
Why do you keep changing your mind?
Whatever. I'm calling him.
He's not picking up again.
That punk. Goodness.
(Mom)
I always imagine...
those who were lonely
because I was with them...
would be lonely at least for once...
because I'm not with them.
I want to come home.
Father.
I miss you.
Mom.
After being so mean to me,
I'll believe it hurt you
at least once.
Mr. Yoon. It's me.
Now you have a mind to turn it in?
Yes.
Thanks for everything.
"One who wants to wear the crown,"
"bear the crown."
One who wants to wear the crown,
bear the crown.
Welcome back.
Did you like the food in the US?
You've grown so much
since the engagement.
Yes. How are you?
How Jeguk Group is doing
is how I'm doing.
The chairman will be happy.
Your mother called me four times.
You should call her on the way.
I'll call my brother first.
Who? Who's here?
I'm back.
For how long?
I'm going to stay.
Don't you remember what I said
when you went to the US?
Or did you not understand?
I know what you're worried about.
But you still came back?
I missed my family so much.
- And I missed home.
- To whine?
You can say whatever you want.
But I'm not going back.
I'll just party and have fun here.
Let me stay.
What you're worried about...
won't happen.
What?
The illegitimate son can't
do anything...
about what I'm worried about.
Stop acting up and listen.
One thing's for sure.
You missed the chance I gave you.
A chance for stepbrothers
to be a little nice to each other.
That's what it means
for you to come home.
You don't want to go back?
Then stay.
What can I do to you?
Everyone's on your side.
The chairman's waiting.
But I can't take you to your house.
Take care.
You went to the airport yourself...
without telling me.
I assumed you'd heard it
from the chairman.
When did Father ever...
Find a hotel for me to stay
for a while.
One close to work.
What should I tell the chairman?
Leave it. He'll assume.
Son.
Let me see you.
Let me see your face.
I'm back, Father.
Yes. Have a seat.
How could you ignore
your mom's calls like that?
Why did you call me so much?
Isn't Father nice to you?
Your father?
He was mean to me since I snored.
Recently, I got slapped...
Anyway, I've been very sad.
She hasn't changed.
Your mom always makes a fuss.
How was the house?
Was it nice to stay?
I told them to put extra care.
It was too big.
It was too bright in the day,
and pitch dark at night.
It was dark?
Why did you get him a dark...
When it's dark,
you can see the stars well.
And how was the school?
Did you learn anything?
I just had fun.
Go rest. You look tired.
Okay.
Look how tall you've grown.
If you grow so well without me,
I'm disappointed.
Did you make a lot of
American friends? Blonds?
With big boobs.
You didn't do drugs, did you?
It's expensive.
My son. You grew up so well.
Oh, that's right.
Rachel went to visit you.
Mom. I'm going to take a shower.
You can question me later.
Oh, right. Sorry.
You should hurry up and leave.
Yes, ma'am.
I can't prove
I was in my dream last night,
and that place feels the same.
Was I really there?
The second son?
What time is it?
You have to go out now
and come home late.
The mood in the house is bad now.
Since the 2nd son is back, the 1st
son hasn't come home for days.
Then just tell him to come home.
Why do you bother me?
I only slept for three hours.
Because the chairman is
in a bad mood,
the second madam is
being extremely hysterical.
Don't get in their sight
and get hurt for no reason. Hurry.
Where do I go at this hour?
I'll go after saying hi to my dad
when he goes to work.
I can just wait here.
You can, but not my dad.
My dad hates you so much.
If there's any misunderstanding,
we should clear it up.
I wish there was.
He just hates you for who you are.
There's a convenience store
down the street. Go eat something.
My goodness.
What? Do you live here?
Who is she?
Did Tan's family move?
Catch me.
Let me play.
Why? This is mine.
Why? Get yours from home.
Hey. Kids.
You shouldn't make a scene
in public places
She's sleeping here.
Mom.
- Mom.
Look at them.
Are you bragging
that you have a mom?
I had Mom when I was your age.
Choi Young Do. What are you doing?
Hey. They're picking a fight.
They're making fun of me
for having no mom.
Mom.
- Mom.
Kids these days are scary.
Are you hurt anywhere?
Mom.
My heart.
- Be quiet!
- Mom.
- Oh, hello.
- Hi.
You got prettier.
Guys. Hello.
Have you seen my dad?
- I think he's on the stage.
- He wasn't there.
Oh, your new soundtrack is awesome.
♪I only see you♪
Right?
That's Lee Hong Gi.
- Bye.
- Where are you going?
She doesn't know our songs.
- Bye.
- Guys.
The rehearsal was awesome.
We haven't done it yet.
Bye.
- 3, 4. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- 3, 4. Hello.
- Hello.
How's life treating you?
How about you?
I'm the universal star.
So is it going well?
In Taiwan, China, we're... Gosh.
Have you been to Taiwan, China?
- Hee Chul.
- Oh, Bo Na.
- Bye.
What are you doing here?
Are you the host?
Of course I'm the host.
You picked... Hey. Who do you
like more? Kyu Hyun or me?
It's... Chan Young.
Oh, Chan Young?
- Do you know him?
- Of course not.
Is he your boyfriend?
Is he your boyfriend or hostage?
You're so annoying.
Seriously, this old man.
Excuse me, old man.
Have you seen my dad?
Old man?
I topped the chart for 60
continuous weeks and I totally...
I thrived at the time.
I'm still doing well.
- What?
- Who am I talking to?
Bo Na.
Look at me, Bo Na. Lee Bo Na?
Where are you looking at? Bo Na.
Bo Na. Lee Bo Na.
Bo Na. Look here.
- Chan Young.
- Bo Na.
You'll hurt yourself.
When did you come back?
How did you get in here?
I met your father by the entrance.
It's been three hours
since I landed.
What? You didn't say anything when
we talked on the phone yesterday.
That's why it's more touching.
Hey, hostage.
Tell me if you're in danger.
Still, how could you not call me?
- I totally missed you.
- I missed you too.
- I missed you more.
- I won't lose this time.
I missed you.
Don't go anywhere.
- Let's go everywhere together.
- Sure. Let's do that.
Oh, now you want to go with me
instead of Cha Eun Sang?
I thought you were living with her.
Why would I do that with a friend
when I have a pretty girlfriend?
What do you want to eat?
Korean food? It's on me. Let's go.
But you were looking
for your father.
That's not important now.
I'm not going to have a daughter.
My goodness. Who said I will?
What a perv.
- Here.
- My. Thank you.
Is this why you wanted to eat
at home?
Enjoy. It's Chan Young's favorite.
I thought your favorite was sushi.
You're good at relationships.
He doesn't usually eat fish
unless it's cooked.
Is that true?
Come on. Don't be so hot
in front of Father.
This is what you should do
to get a girlfriend.
Do you want me to get a girlfriend?
I'm against it, Father.
Until Chan Young goes to college,
you must focus on Chan Young only.
Sure.
Since he needs to go to college,
you should break up with him.
That sounds like a father-in-law.
It's so good, Father.
Leave a lot of tip.
I could never get used
to giving tips in LA.
I got nervous every time I paid.
Oh, you met Tan in LA, didn't you?
Yes. It was the first time
since we were kids.
I almost didn't recognize him.
You mean Kim Tan?
You know him too?
Of course I don't.
How would I know him?
It sounds like you do.
With that reaction,
I'm sure she does.
No, I don't. I don't know him.
Then you know him very well.
What's wrong? What is it?
I think I got dumped.
Is Yoon Chan Young not coming back?
What a smart boy.
That's not it.
Then what is it?
Chan Young might have found out
that I dated Kim Tan.
What do you mean he might
have found out?
They met in the US.
Kim Tan and Chan Young.
What?
They fell in love and dumped you?
Come here. You need a smack.
So does Chan Young know or not?
I don't know if he knows.
- You said you got dumped.
- Yes. Soon.
I wonder what Kim Tan said about me.
I'm sure he's not over me yet.
It looks like they wailed
on each other.
Kim Tan wouldn't sue Chan Young
for hitting him, would he?
Hey. If they had a fight,
Tan would've beaten him.
Hey. Chan Young's good at fighting.
And don't take Kim Tan's side.
Don't take Rachel's
boyfriend's side!
I can't prove
I was in my dream last night,
and that place feels the same.
Was I really there?
You were there. I can prove it.
(New comment)
(Eun Sang:
You were there. I can prove it.)
Hey. Log out already.
Do you want to log out of your life?
No, I won't.
Did you think
I was that conscientious?
I'm a drug dealer after all.
Where are you?
Are you kidneys still healthy?
(No, I won't. Did you think
I was that conscientious?)
They are.
Come get them if you need them.
Be honest with me.
You want me to appear
in front of you, don't you?
I bought cheese.
Leave it there.
Why isn't she replying?
"Sleeping Beauty".
"Once upon a time,"
"there lived..."
I bought cheese.
Thank you.
I didn't tell you do it.
Your mom did, okay?
Okay.
"There lived..."
No, not this.
How many times do I need to tell
you? The one that says 2005.
Even if you can't read French,
you can still read the numbers.
Have you gone blind now?
I'll go.
Give it to me, Mom.
Let me get the wine from now on.
Will you? Right. That's better.
You're eating for free.
You should earn your keep.
Why are you doing this?
You should go study.
How can I study
when I can't even earn my keep?
"Everything together."
Even the wines are living in luxury.
Come on. Why isn't she replying?
Gosh.
- Mom.
- Yes?
Have you ever had a nightmare
in this house?
A nightmare? Why?
Do you have nightmares?
I keep seeing a girl's back.
With long hair.
The maid's daughter. She lives here.
She's your age.
What was her name again?
Cha Eun Sang?
I told her to stay as if she were
not here, not like a ghost.
Why does she live here?
Her sister in the US was
getting married,
so they sent her
all their house deposit.
So they have no other option.
Don't. Don't do this.
Mom went through so much
to make this money.
Leave.
Eun Seok.
(Cha Eun Sang)
I hate how my mom is suffering.
I hope Jeguk Group goes broke.
What are you doing right now?
Answer me now.
Gosh. Hurry up.
I'm drinking water.
You're all grown up now.
You kicked your brother out
as soon as you arrived.
Don't move.
What did you just do?
Are you insane?
But I'm taking only your name.
Call me if you want it back.
- Is this your number?
- What?
I can't believe I'm spending money
to get a girl's number.
- I got interested in him.
- So why?
Because he's pretty.
I can't get him out of my head.
Forget about school.
Let's stop hiding here
like a criminal and leave.
I forgot to introduce yourself.
You're mine from today.
Lucifer appeared in the school
of Satans.
I missed you, buddy.
Welcome.
(The Heirs)