(The Heirs)
(Episode 7)
Hey.
Why do you always sleep here?
It makes me want to protect you.
How did you know my number?
You also know mine.
Let's say we're even.
Why did you call me?
How's the ramyeon?
Do you want to eat some ramyeon?
You think I called
because I'm happy to see you?
How can friendships change?
I'll wake up the person
you'll be happy to see.
Wake up already.
Kim Tan is here.
Why are you so noisy?
What are you doing
in someone else's neighborhood?
Come on. Don't be like this.
What are you two doing?
Why are you here
and why is he there?
What are you two doing?
Didn't you come to meet her?
Cross the road.
Why would I come to meet her?
I don't know what you two
are doing there,
but go to your neighborhood
to misbehave.
This isn't
that kind of neighborhood.
He's just leaving.
Follow him quickly.
I didn't come to meet Kim Tan.
Are you saying that this situation
is a coincidence?
Did we meet after making
an appointment?
Bye, then.
What can I do if you say so?
Gosh, I'm confused.
Oh, my gosh!
How could a girl sleep at a place
like that? It's dangerous.
I didn't want to come home early,
but I didn't have
anywhere else to go.
Why don't you have anywhere else
to go? There are cafes everywhere.
You must also spend money
to spend time.
I'll go in first.
I'm not done talking.
Why did you meet Choi Young Do?
I didn't meet him,
I just ran into him.
He was sitting there when I woke up.
I told you several times
to be careful of Choi Young Do.
What did he say to you?
Didn't he threaten you?
No, he actually said
that he wanted to protect me.
That's a threat.
Please just listen to me.
Don't run into Choi Young Do
from now on.
I'm not nagging you,
I'm warning you.
It's not up to me.
You didn't even try your best.
How dare you say that?
What happened between
Choi Young Do and you?
I don't remember clearly.
I just know that
we hate each other now.
I'll go in first. You should come in
five minutes later.
Don't you think we could run into
each other once in the garden?
I'm doing my best not to run
into you as much as possible.
I'm home.
You should come home early.
I had to get this myself.
I'm sorry.
Mom, give me some water.
You should've just asked for it.
Why come to the kitchen?
Hey, give him some water.
Is it your first time seeing him?
He's my son, Kim Tan.
He's the second son of Jeguk Group.
You know the lady who can't
talk, right? She's her daughter.
Nice to meet you.
I saw you a lot.
Did you see her? When? At home?
At school.
I was like, "Who's that
country bumpkin?" It was you.
Nice to meet you.
I hope I see you often.
You don't have to see her often.
Didn't you see him at school?
I didn't.
Really?
But it's really hard
not to notice him.
Isn't that right?
She's strange.
I'm going upstairs.
I will also go to my room.
Did you look at him carefully?
Yes?
Now that you know his face,
why don't you report how Tan is
doing at school to me from now on.
Report?
Why?
You're going to a
private school for free,
but you can't do that for me?
That's not it.
I'm not saying
that you two should become close.
Just because you live in the same
house and go to the same school,
doesn't mean you two can
become close.
Just like you're living in different
spaces in the same house,
he and you should breathe
in different places at school.
Don't call him "Tan" and talk down
to him because you're the same age.
You understand that, right?
Yes, he's something
like a young master.
Yes, exactly.
You really are smart.
Give me a glass of water.
Yes, ma'am.
Why are you sleeping like that?
Lie down even if it's for a moment.
Mom, what is this?
Where did you get it?
Where would I get it?
Of course, I bought it.
You bought it? Mom, how could you?
It costs about 1,000 dollars.
With that money, we could...
You can let me handle this much.
Try it on. Let's see if my daughter
looks pretty in it.
You know I look pretty
in anything.
Thank you, Mom.
To be honest, I'm really happy.
Thank you so much.
Should I iron it?
What? We're going to take what?
A family photo.
It's going to be displayed at
the engagement venue and invitation.
Mom, are you sick?
Why would we take
a darn family photo?
Lower your voice. How dare you?
You're at my store.
What are you thinking?
Why would I take a photo
with those people?
Does taking a family photo make
us a real family?
- Bring this to me in pink.
- Yes, ma'am.
A temper tantrum only works
until you're three years old.
It won't work, so stop it.
You also could run my life
as you wanted until I was three.
I don't care whether you will take
a family photo or wedding photo.
I'm not going.
Where are you going?
I'm going home soon.
Where are you right now?
You heard about the photo, right?
You're not the only one
who feels bad right now.
I'm seriously asking you. Is there
no way to break off this engagement?
Do you want to go out with me?
You know I'm not talking
about my engagement.
Can't you be a little more serious?
I can't break off the engagement,
but I can break off the photoshoot.
Are you serious?
What will you do for me
if I break it off?
Ask me after you do it.
I see. You must want to take
the family photo.
What do you want?
Will you give me...
anything I want?
Gosh, it's cold.
What are you doing here this early?
Gosh. The driver didn't even
come to work yet.
I wondered when you leave since
I never saw you in the morning.
Do you leave this early to avoid me?
You're not the only one
I'm avoiding. I'll get going first.
Do you think I waited this early
to send you alone first?
- Hey.
- It will be no good...
if the struggle gets longer.
There's a surveillance camera
over there.
Please go to Jeguk High School.
Kids like Kim Tan
because he's handsome.
Kim Tan has good grades
- Kim Tan is...
- What are you doing?
These are the content
that you must report to my mom.
I heard everything yesterday.
Are you telling me to lie?
What part is a lie?
Never mind.
When she told you to report
about me,
you answered "Yes" immediately.
Were you waiting for it?
I can't really say "I don't want to"
at your house, can I?
I guess that's why you say
"I don't want to" and...
"Forget it" only to me.
Did I?
Why do you go to school this early?
What exactly are you avoiding?
Your car. I'm being
careful of your car.
My car?
Please drop me off
by the crosswalk.
No, we'll get out
at the school entrance.
We can't get out together.
There's no one at this hour.
Let's go together just for today.
I won't go to school this early
from tomorrow, so don't worry.
- Still...
- What's that?
I'm sleepy.
I woke up too early because of you.
What do you think you're doing?
Let's get out together later.
You look good in the uniform.
What are you doing?
Don't tie your hair up at school.
Give me back my hair tie.
You look prettier
when you cover up your face more.
Wear your hair like this, okay?
Don't do that.
What if someone sees us?
- Who would see us at this hour?
- Kim Tan?
Upstart, you're also here.
How did you come together?
What are you doing at this hour?
Did you sleep here?
It looks like you came to school
directly from a club.
It somehow ended up like that.
I might wake up from here tomorrow
if my mom knows I didn't go home.
Let's go in.
What?
You stepped on that.
This? It's okay to step on it.
It's fake.
Is it fake? Are you sure
someone didn't die there?
No way. Someone just drew it.
They draw it over and over again
whenever someone erases it.
It's like picking up a fight
in a way.
Who is so passionate?
How would I know?
Maybe it's Joon Young.
Anyway, Upstart,
have we met before?
You look familiar at this hour.
I'm not sure.
She doesn't go to clubs.
How would you know that?
Clubs must have certain standards
for their guests.
What?
She's not bad.
She just has a tacky style.
Gosh...
Hey, you came.
Oh, my. Do you live like this?
The house is amazing.
Really? Does it look nice?
This isn't a house. It's a castle.
How many rooms are there?
This is all worth being called
"Second Madam" in life.
"Second Madam" would be bearable.
I'm just a live-in girlfriend now.
Take a look.
I'll show you around the house.
But is it okay
for me to come here?
Won't the chairman say anything?
The chairman isn't here today.
And I'm not going to walk
on eggshells from now on.
Now that Tan is back,
nothing's going to stop me now.
Gosh, Lady. You're persistent.
What did I do?
I wasn't talking to you.
It's Ye Sol's school.
They've sent so many text messages
for the parent meeting.
They call me immediately
when I ignore them.
I should just kick them.
I'm jealous of you, Girl.
I can't go there even if I want to.
It will be only exhausting
if you go there.
You have to doll yourself up
from head to toe.
You must let people
see your handbag well.
"What do you do?
What does your husband do?"
They make a fuss doing that.
So what did you say?
What did I say?
I told them I sell drinks.
Are you crazy? Is Ye Sol okay?
Don't worry.
It takes one to know one.
I told them I sell drinks,
and they think I run
a mineral water company.
Gosh, Girl. You're fearless.
Life isn't that much of a big deal.
Madam, where is your bedroom?
How's thing about the first madam
going?
I forgot about it.
There are no photos of her
that I can use.
She always goes around to see
paintings and buys dishes.
Whenever I think she must be going
on a date, it's just Mr. Yoon.
She doesn't pray, but she's almost
like a Buddhist nun.
Really?
Let's do this then.
Do you have any ideas?
Change the target.
Let's put someone
who will become a flaw to...
Won, no, President Kim.
Women are the best way
to lose his father's favor.
Are you sure you're an expert?
If the first madam is a Buddhist
nun, Won is a Catholic priest.
What is wrong with everyone?
This house must've been built
on a bad site.
Oh, my gosh! Who is that?
Why are you coming out from there?
You're driving me crazy.
Did you hear everything? Again?
Is she the lady
you were talking about?
The lady who can't talk?
I can't stand it anymore.
Let's bury this lady today.
The old Han Ki Ae is coming out.
Why? Did she catch you
doing a lot of things?
Are you sure she can't talk?
What?
Oh, my gosh!
How did you know?
From the reflection there.
I see.
You really can't talk, right?
Then when did you lose
the ability to speak?
Forget it. Tell me later.
Get back to work.
After I suffered from a fever
when I was three years old.
(JBS New Staff Application)
Sign language? Is sign language
your specialty?
Yes.
That's unique. It's usually
"I can speak three languages."
That's one of the many reasons
you should pick me.
I've had a sense
of sacrifice and service...
- You're rejected.
- Why?
Didn't you want to join the club
to buy your uniform?
You're wearing one now.
You said you bought a handbag.
You must have sold it back.
I lied about buying a handbag.
It looked like that.
If you have anything left
to say, say it.
Please pick me.
If you don't, I will take revenge.
What does that mean?
Please pick me.
You signed too long for that.
What are you doing?
Don't tell me you're wasting
your time by interviewing her.
No, you can't pick her, Hyo Shin.
- What is your reason?
- She's my boyfriend's best friend.
Men and women can't be friends.
You can't pick her.
That's a pity.
I like a love triangle.
Hyo Shin!
Why did you come here?
Hello.
Hyo Shin, I'm here
for the interview.
You got it.
Hyo Shin, let's pick her.
Cha Eun Sang, you're the next
producer to be with JBS.
Congratulations.
Hey.
So? Did Eun Sang join
the broadcasting club?
I don't know.
Hyo Shin will take care of it.
Say "Ah".
Are you on a diet again?
No, I'm eating this for my brain.
A mock test's coming soon.
Gosh, that's so admirable.
What does that mean?
Why do you think I'm like Kim Tan?
Is the world all about
Kim Tan for you...
to hear "admirable" as "Kim Tan"?
I dated him for a short time.
I was too young then.
You're still not over him.
What are you talking about?
We just held hands.
- It's true.
- Is it true?
I swear.
By the way, did Kim Tan tell you
that he and I used to date?
No, Rachel told me.
But I'm a little upset because
I just found out you held hands.
You didn't know that we held hands!
What? Rachel told you?
Kim Tan is Lee Bo Na's ex-boyfriend,
and I'm your current boyfriend.
She introduced me like that.
Rachel, that crazy...
I'm sorry. My usual language
just popped out.
You can also call me
crazy beforehand.
- Why?
- Don't tell kids that...
Eun Sang is
on a welfare scholarship.
That's ridiculous.
Why should I do that?
Because I trust you.
No, don't trust me.
The past is the past,
but I still don't like Eun Sang.
I will get going now.
(October 16, 2009, Tan and Young Do)
Why are you here?
What about Myung Soo?
He went outside for a moment
because he missed his mom.
She's nearby.
What are you doing?
I'm thinking about the old days.
How long have you been dating Bo Na?
A year and a half? What stage
are you in with Eun Sang?
I'm about to confess
my feelings for her.
You've been friends
for half of your life.
Nothing's happened between you two?
What are you talking about?
Was there any attraction
or feelings for her?
What if there was?
Right. Of course, there was.
When?
When I was about nine years old.
Eun Sang was taller than me then.
So she beat up the kids
who bullied me half-dead.
My heart fluttered so much.
Is that really it?
Why did you hold my Bo Na's hand?
- Because I was cold.
- Is that it?
Bo Na was stronger than me then.
Bye.
(October 16, 2009, Tan and Young Do)
What brings you here?
Didn't you leave for good?
It would be less embarrassing
if you tried to hide how you feel.
I'm so dumbfounded since you said
what you were really thinking.
I was like that
because I was glad to see you.
What did you just say?
I'm going to live in another place
for a while.
I came to tell you that
in case you would worry.
But you're living
somewhere else lately.
I had a place to come back
until now,
but I don't have one anymore.
I thought you'd deal with this in a
smarter and more sophisticated way.
Bringing Tan to the company wasn't
a smart and sophisticated way too.
Tan is only 18 years old.
Do you only amount to that much?
I was only six years old
when mom passed away.
And I was only 12 years old when
I had to welcome a stepbrother...
as well as a stepmother.
I know that I will lose more
than I gain.
But it's not like I don't have
anything to gain at all.
Because someone will get hurt.
That someone's wounds...
will be a comfort to me.
Do you even have any idea
what you will lose?
No, but...
I will lose them if I have to.
I'll get going now.
Won.
Are you back for good?
Are you and your mom
curious about that most?
Get out. You're bothering me.
Can't we live together...
regardless of whether
we hate each other or not?
Only real families do that.
Don't you feel bad...
when you talk to me like that?
I do. But you feel bad too.
That's enough for me.
- Step aside.
- Won.
I told you to step aside.
How could you do this?
How could you leave home
just because I'm back?
It's because you keep following
me around.
- What?
- You came to my hotel...
and the company.
If you keep following me around
like a seven-year-old,
I have nowhere to hide from you.
How could I do this?
Don't you think you're taking
away places I can stay at?
Or should I go to the US this time?
When will you grow up?
I can't fight with
a high school student, right?
Please grow up quickly.
I'm sorry for turning up
at the hotel unannounced.
I'm also sorry for going
to the company.
It's also my fault...
to come back from the US.
It's all my fault, so stay home.
Won.
Let go.
How dare you grab me?
Am I not even allowed to touch you
like this?
I know I may be out of line,
but I understand you.
You understand me?
Are you mocking me right now?
Who are you to understand me?
You courageously came back, but
you don't have the courage to fight?
How dare you...
I'm not going to fight with you.
It's obvious that I will lose.
How could I win a fight
when I'm not...
even serious about it?
- So...
- I don't know who you take after,
but you're really noisy.
- Are you coming home now?
- Oh, my gosh!
Hello.
Are you rebelling against me?
Since your mother might come out,
I will get going now.
You're talking nonsense. Stop there.
- Why?
- Why aren't you giving...
my dream catcher back?
You didn't even say thank you.
I like it when the left hand
recognizes what the right hand did.
Bring it to the wine cellar.
Right now. Do you understand?
(Connecting)
Thank you for this.
This is kind of surprising.
I had nightmares right away
without it.
You're lying.
I turned music on. Just listen
to one song before you go.
I will because you chose
a good song.
Do you like this song?
You played this song before.
Yes, someone who I passionately
liked used to like this song.
Have you dated someone before?
When? Before going to the US?
What was the punk like?
I didn't say it was a boy.
You didn't date then.
So who is it?
My sister.
Do you still want to go to the US?
I didn't really want
to go to the US.
It didn't matter as long as
it wasn't Korea.
So?
Is Korea good enough to live
after you came back?
It's the same. I'm always
doing part-time jobs.
Transferring the school was
quite a shock to me.
I became unhappier thanks to that.
Tell me when you need my help.
That's okay. I'll just accept
your thoughts.
Who said I would give them to you?
What does it feel like to be born
as the son of Jeguk Group?
It feels like
I can't call my mother "Mother",
and I can't call
my brother "Brother".
I guess most young masters
from rich families are like that.
I didn't know you'd hold grudges.
Can I also ask you something?
- No.
- You didn't even hear the question.
Your questions were
always dangerous.
I enjoyed listening to this song.
Good night.
But even the first verse
hasn't ended.
Do I...
like you?
Cha Eun Sang.
Did I...
miss you?
(Jeguk High School)
- I told you to leave.
- How can we wait for that?
- Be quiet.
- But the class will begin soon.
What is it? Is it Young Do again?
- Go in a little later.
- You go in a little later.
Choi Young Do, did you rent
this school out?
Even if you did, this school
belongs to Kim Tan.
Who are you to tell
everyone to leave?
I had to find something out
from Upstart.
Don't be nervous.
- What are you doing?
You have come at a good time.
You psycho, are you crazy?
Can you see this?
Take a look.
You never spent money
for real before.
You're not an upstart, are you?
Lee Bo Na.
Is she really an upstart?
I heard that you know
a little about her.
I don't know. You're so childish.
What does that matter to you?
It matters to me.
If she pretended to be an upstart
when she's on a welfare scholarship,
she deceived the entire school.
How could that not matter to me?
Everyone is a victim then.
Isn't that right?
Can you just leave if you have
no intention to apologize?
Will it be too rude to ask you...
what makes you so cheeky?
Step aside.
Bo Na, what's wrong?
What happened?
Chan Young, Choi Young Do
finally went crazy.
You keep disturbing everyone
preparing for class.
You're starting to annoy me.
How come there are so many guys
willing to help you?
It's making me feel competitive.
I will go astray that way.
Are both of you okay?
Let's clean up quickly.
It's so annoying.
What am I doing because of you?
Thank you, Bo Na.
I hate you the most.
I'll do it. Help Bo Na.
This is big news.
Choi Young Do turned the Upstart's
bag inside out next door...
asking if she's really an upstart.
- When?
- Just now.
He was quiet for a few days,
and now he's starting again.
All right, everyone.
Take your seats, please.
Class has begun.
Everybody have your books ready.
Very good.
Everyone please turn to
page 1, 0, 9, 109.
"Beyond Your Dreams".
Today we will be discussing dreams.
Dreams in history...
are visions of the future.
Ways to predict what will happen.
No way, it couldn't be.
(Complaint)
(Accuser, Choi Young Do)
(The accuser sues the accused
for assault, so please punish him.)
Please drop the charge.
Come on. Don't give in so easily.
You're disappointing me.
Did you hit me without
even thinking through this much?
How nice did you think I was?
Please.
I got three weeks of
medical treatment.
I was in so much pain.
Tears were pouring
because I was so sad.
I'm sorry.
Please drop the charge. Please...
How could I do that when I was hit?
So my friend,
take this back and spend a lot
of money to get a good lawyer.
I'll do anything you want.
You're making me get soft-hearted.
Then... I can't guarantee you
that it will work,
but will you go on your knees?
Who knows? My mind might change.
(Complaint)
Hey, stand up.
It's none of your business.
- Stand up.
- Don't pretend to be nice.
Because you are not.
You're no different
from Choi Young Do.
As I expected,
our Joon Young is so smart.
By any chance,
did I bully you in the past?
Choi Young Do at least
remembered it.
I'm sorry.
I'll repay you like this instead.
I also hit you, so you should
make me go on my knees too.
Can I do that?
I'm looking forward to it.
How would I be feeling then?
What are you doing?
Who is fighting?
- Let's go.
What are you doing?
Don't you have to go
to the hospital? Doesn't it hurt?
This could happen between friends,
but my heart is so broken.
I'm so sorry.
Your father will be upset
if he sees this.
I won't sue him, so don't worry.
That's not what I meant.
I'm apologizing as Tan's mother
right now.
You've just transferred here,
and you're already causing trouble?
Did you have to do this
as soon as you came?
Have you forgotten
about the promise we made?
I'm sorry.
If you're going to be like this,
transfer to another school.
I warned you,
and you made a promise.
What more should I do about you?
Who should I tell this
to make you scared?
Should I tell your brother?
I'm okay, ma'am.
Don't be too harsh on Tan.
Your mother also recommended it.
You should consider transferring.
Wouldn't it be right for the person
embarrassed from getting hit to go?
Are you disregarding her
since she's not your real mother?
Just go...
before your right side
also gets beaten.
I'm waiting for that.
The chance that I don't have
to hold back anymore.
Do you want to hit me once more?
I think there will be
another chance.
(Kim Tan)
(Choi Young Do)
Choi Young Do.
Why are you avoiding me?
I'm not avoiding you.
Is it because the thing
we saw the other day?
Because you're embarrassed?
What about the other day?
What did we see?
Choi Young Do.
That's not embarrassing.
It's just hurtful.
What do you know?
Everyone has a secret like that.
It's also the same for me.
To tell you the truth,
I'm not the chief director's son.
What?
My real mom is a different person.
You're the first person
I'm telling about this.
Are you the son of a mistress?
So...
if a child is born between my dad
and the woman we saw yesterday...
You're just like the child,
aren't you?
I heard that Tan beat Young Do up.
What a pity. I didn't see that.
You should say it properly.
Young Do wasn't hit, he blocked Tan.
Why don't you just say that
Young Do's jaw hit Tan's fist?
You should stop hanging around
with Young Do.
You really won't be able to go
to college later.
You should hate the crime
within legal boundaries.
You shouldn't hate the person.
Isn't Young Do the victim this time?
Are you taking
Choi Young Do's side...
after I suffered like that?
You're subtly taking Kim Tan's side.
Old affection is scary.
I don't have any old affection
toward Kim Tan.
- Be quiet.
- Who cares if she hears it?
Do we have to walk on eggshells
around Kim Tan's fiancee?
Hey, Yoo Rachel.
Do you have something to say?
Don't you have anything to say?
You should go first. I'll catch up.
In the US, you told Chan Yong about
me dating Kim Tan, didn't you?
- So?
- How dare you say "So?"
What right do you have to babble
about someone else's past?
It's not like I made it up.
You should've...
taken care of your boyfriend
in the first place.
Why did you let him
flirt with another girl?
I already took care of that issue
with Chan Young.
I rather think there's something
between Tan and Eun Sang.
Considering the circumstances.
I have a lot of things that are
making me mad apart from you.
I'm helping you accumulate
your anger more.
I'll repay you
when everything is over.
That's funny.
Why did you come here in person?
I had an appointment near here,
and I felt guilty to just leave.
Your second marriage must not be
included in your guilt.
Don't make me regret coming here.
Isn't that Tan?
Don't do that.
That punk.
He came back to Korea,
but never came by to say hello.
It's been a long time, right?
How have you been?
You came back quite a while ago. You
should've visited me to say hello.
I've been busy with several things.
Is that so?
We should still have
a meal together.
That punk never says
something he doesn't mean.
Well, that's better
than being embarrassed.
Tan hit Young Do today.
What? Why?
Why? Because he did
something to deserve it.
And I'm pretty sure Young Do
takes after his dad.
One thing is clear. My fiance is
better than yours.
Get out. I'm not going with you.
Why did you come
in the first place then?
Young Do hasn't arrived yet.
Could you contact me when he comes?
I'll be in the lounge.
Okay.
And Manager,
CEO Kim Won of
Jeguk Group stays here, right?
Yes, that's right.
I come here often, but I think I've
been too indifferent to my in-laws.
Could you tell me the phone number
of Jeguk Group's chief secretary?
(Lee Esther)
This is Yoon Jae Ho.
This really is your number. It's me.
I must be more desperate one
between the two of us.
Do you think that's true?
Don't act ambiguously.
I got this number after
a lot of determination.
I'm giving you a chance to think
more about whether it's worth it.
I'll call you later.
Are you going to hang up now?
I'm going to hang up.
Thank you.
Are you dating these days?
It's close to an affair.
Even after watching me? Just stop.
Okay, let's hear things
that will make my head hurt now.
Report them to me.
Yes.
CEO Lee Esther of
RS International...
currently owns 1.4 percent
of Jeguk Group's shares.
She inherited 1.2 percent,
and bought 850,000 more shares...
when Tan and Rachel got engaged.
She also owns
Hotel Zeus shares, right?
Yes.
She owns 1.1 percent,
so she already has a voting right...
at the general shareholders meeting.
After she marries Hotel Zeus
CEO Choi Dong Wook,
she will own 3.4 percent
of Hotel Zeus shares...
and 1.8 percent
of Jeguk Group shares.
She will own 1.8 percent...
Do you think this marriage
will really happen?
Since it's not a love marriage,
I think it will happen.
Is that so?
That's definitely
our company envelope. Who is he?
We studied exactly up
to where I folded the page.
This is the range where
the final exam will cover.
It will also help you
if you study this.
Thank you.
(Don't Receive)
What would I have done without you?
Who is "Don't Receive"?
I also have a secret, Friend.
Hurry up and go.
Bo Na will lose her temper.
Bo Na doesn't lose her temper.
She's just being cute.
Gosh, you're a fool for her.
I'll get going.
- Call if you don't know something.
- Okay.
(Don't Receive)
- Why?
- I want to eat jjajangmyeon,
but they won't deliver one dish.
- What?
- Why don't you come here...
and eat jjajangmyeon with me?
Order two dishes and just eat one.
You're rich.
How could you throw away food
when the economy is bad?
Find someone else.
Why would I go there?
You'll end up coming.
Haven't you met Joon Young yet?
I told him...
that if he makes you come here,
I might drop the charge.
You punk! How could you...
I'm going to hang up.
Hey...
I'm sorry, but...
I'm really sorry, but...
What is your intention
of playing with me?
Intention?
You're not even going to
really drop the charge.
Why are you playing with people?
Joon Young came to me looking like
he was about to die...
to ask me a favor.
You might be just playing,
but to him...
Who said I was just playing?
Are you really going to drop
the charge then?
Yes.
- Why?
- Because you came.
What changes if I come?
My mind will change.
Why does it change?
It's something like, "You became
a flower after coming to me."
I'm not in the mood to joke.
Do you think
everything I do is a joke?
Don't you like flowers?
Do you dislike the part "flower"
or "coming to me"?
Pick one. I'll make you do
the part you dislike more.
I dislike both.
Gosh, I got dumped.
I'm going to take revenge.
Why aren't you answering my calls?
I'm in the middle of a meal
with an important guest.
You said you'd take care of it.
But why are we taking
a photo on the weekend?
I said I'm with a guest.
A guest? Who?
What kind of situation is this?
Don't be curious.
I'm not going to let you join us.
I also have no intention
to stay longer.
Anyway, take care
of the photo thing properly.
I'm not doing anything about it
because of you.
You never cease to surprise me.
Please drop the charge.
I can go since
you're done eating, right?
Where are you going?
To work?
It's me.
Do you know where Chan Eun Sang is
and who she is with?
- How would I know that?
- Do you want me to tell you?
Didn't you call to tell me?
Cha Eun Sang is in the suite
at Choi Young Do's hotel.
She's eating with Choi Young Do
alone.
I'm going to hang up.
The person
you're calling cannot...
Announcement for the
Jeguk High School parent meeting.
There's a parent meeting
next Wednesday at 2pm.
I'm Chan Eun Sang's mom.
I'm sorry, but due to
unavoidable circumstances...
What is it?
Both you and I can't go
to our kid's school.
Our lives are so sad.
I'll be out for a moment.
Where are you going at this hour?
Come on out.
Why? Did something happen?
Why didn't you answer my calls?
Can't you see that I'm working
right now?
Did you go to Young Do's hotel?
Gosh, Rachel.
Did you go there?
Does that hotel belong to
Young Do's family?
Are you crazy?
Why would you go there?
I even went to your house
in the US...
when you could've been
a drug dealer.
I don't do stupid things.
That's being stupid.
How could you trust me
and follow me?
Something bad could've happened.
Because you'd never do
something to me.
How do you know
whether I would or not?
Why did you go to Young Do's hotel?
Because of Joon Young.
Choi Young Do said he would drop
the charge if I went there.
- Did you believe that?
- I didn't, but what could I do...
when a friend came to me and
desperately asked for a favor?
How is he your friend?
You've met him
just a couple of times.
He knew that I am on
a welfare scholarship.
He even knew what my mom does.
But he still kept my secret.
How could I not go?
He's going to transfer soon anyway.
How many times did I tell you
not to be involved in such a thing?
You want to pretend
to be nice that badly?
Why is Choi Young Do
bullying me in the first place?
It's because of you.
That's why I'm like this.
I'm afraid something might happen
to you because of me.
I'm asking you.
Can you please not do things
that will bother me?
Can't you just stay low?
Why don't you leave me alone?
My life is already so hard as it is.
But I got on Young Do's bad side
for some reason,
and I'm getting more
uncomfortable with you.
I'm not asking for something big.
I just want to graduate safely...
and live a better life when I'm 20,
even if it's just a little better.
But I really don't know
what to do now.
Should I tell you
what you should do?
Get out of my house tomorrow.
- What?
- You can't get out?
Do you also want to continue
going to school?
Then start liking me from now on.
If possible, sincerely.
I caught feelings for you.
I said I like Cha Eun Sang.
So? What do you want me to do
about it?
Do we look good together?
Why are you asking
such an ugly question?
We look good together.
If you behave like that,
you and your mom can't stay
in this house.
- Sit down.
- What is the meaning of...
making me sit here?
Stand up. I told you to stand up.
What is wrong
with your table manners?
You punk!
(The Heirs)