(The tassel crowns the knight.
The sword is snow white.)
(In the silver saddle,
he rides like a shooting star.)
(He kills a man within ten steps.
Invincible he is all the way ahead.)
(He would leave once it's done.
No trace of him is to be found.)
=Sword Snow Stride=
(Season 1)
=Episode 30=
Greetings, Your Highness.
Don't worry.
My disciple will be right back.
Your Highness,
what are you doing?
Thank you for taking care of my brother.
Didn't I tell you?
He's my disciple
and I should take care of him.
Senior.
Ah?
Mount Longhu and Mount Hui
are only separated by a river.
You must be familiar
with the Xuanyuan Family, aren't you?
I know a little bit.
Why?
He wants to draw the Xuanyuan Family
over to his side.
The Xuanyuan Family
is an influential clan.
Besides,
Old Ancestor Xuanyuan Dapan
of the Celestial Realm
won't easily work
for North Liang, will he?
Take it easy.
Let's just have a talk.
Oh.
About what?
About interesting stories
of the Xuanyuan Family.
There are some.
Tell me about them.
Why do you want to know the stories?
I'm going back to Shu soon.
Maybe they'll be helpful.
You just want to gossip.
You just don't understand.
Shu?
Why are you going back there?
She's the princess of West Chu.
Oh. Ah?
Never mind.
Let's continue.
Your Highness,
I'm at least an Arch-Taoist
of Mount Longhu.
But you exposed her identity to me?
It doesn't matter.
You're Huangman'er's master.
We're a family.
Don't you fear that I'll arrest her?
Go ahead.
What?
Cao Changqing is following her.
Invincible Cao Changqing?
Yes.
My Mr. Chess Master.
Very well.
Let's get back to the interesting stories
of the Xuanyuan Family.
All right.
(The Xuanyuan Family, Mount Hui)
(Xuanyuan Jingcheng's wife)
Mother.
Why are you back?
Old Ancestor summoned me.
He asked me to enter Wending Pavilion.
If I get the instruction from him,
I may get back
the power of our family.
You don't need to tell me anything
about the Xuanyuan Family.
If one day
you take control of the Xuanyuan Family,
remember to expel me.
But you and Father are a couple.
Have I ever begged you before?
Fine.
You shouldn't have come back.
What makes you say that?
You've always been looked down upon
and you don't dare
to fight for anything.
I don't care.
But now I've got a chance
to get back what we deserve.
Why are you trying to stop me?
Xuanyuan Dapan
doesn't mean to instruct you.
Then why did he
summon me to Wending Pavilion?
For a chat?
He wants to marry you
for better martial arts.
Are you out of your mind?
He's Old Ancestor of our family.
He's a forefather.
Xuanyuan Dapan
isn't one of our family.
Xuanyuan Dapan isn't
one of the Xuanyuan Family?
How's that possible?
It's true.
He used to be a retainer
of the Xuanyuan Family.
Later, he was a son-in-law by adoption.
But isn't Xuanyuan his family name?
Whoever is adopted
should use their family name.
And then he even became their ancestor?
He reached the Celestial Realm, anyway.
His adoption is always kept secret.
Only old men like us are aware.
So, the Xuanyuan Family
are his offspring?
No.
None of his offspring
was alive
after years of martial struggle.
They all died?
Mm.
The Xuanyuan Family
was watching out for him.
At that time,
he didn't reach the Celestial Realm yet.
He had to bear it.
Then why is he still staying
in the Xuanyuan Family?
It's indeed weird.
His offspring died.
But he has been staying
in the Xuanyuan Family willingly
as Old Ancestor.
I'm afraid he indeed treats himself
as a member
of the Xuanyuan Family.
Right?
He's taking revenge?
Life is full of unpredictability.
Who would expect him
to reach the Celestial Realm
and even become
the ancestor of our family?
He was injured in his early years
so that he didn't have a child.
Now, in the Celestial Realm,
he has the chance
to have his own children.
Why did he pick me?
He's been waiting for this day.
He wants our family
to be his real lineage.
But he's so old.
He hates lineal descendants
of our family.
How's that possible?
Is that true?
This is a secret,
but your uncles know that.
Then why did they ask me to come back?
I'm their niece.
Why didn't you tell Yuan Tingshan
so that I would know the truth?
I told him.
What?
My father doesn't want me
to go back home.
There must be a reason, isn't there?
He didn't give me a reason.
I explained everything to him
so that he would tell you the truth.
Why did he keep it from me?
Your family
is quite filthy.
I'm leaving.
Don't worry.
I won't let Qingfeng get hurt.
What do you think you can do?
(Mount Hui)
Uncle Jingyi.
Tomorrow, Old Ancestor will see you.
You mustn't leave.
You should know what he's going to do.
His order
cannot be disobeyed.
But I'm your niece.
Our family needs a man
of the Celestial Realm.
Without him,
we would no longer be powerful.
So, you're sacrificing me?
After he marries you,
he'll indeed be connected
with our family.
Our clan has been inherited
for centuries.
It can't be ruined.
For our family,
you mustn't leave.
When I'm here,
you're not able to leave, either.
You knew everything?
Why didn't you tell me the truth?
You had to come back,
or I would be a retainer all my life.
After I enter Wending Pavilion,
you can be a member of my family?
After I marry you,
I can be one of your family.
I'll marry you
and change my family name.
Xuanyuan Dapan
is a master of the Celestial Realm.
He won't marry
someone else's wife, will he?
Yuan Tingshan!
Be patient.
I know you don't like me.
It doesn't matter.
After we get married,
you can like anyone you want.
I won't sleep with you.
What exactly do you want?
A chance.
A man like me
has been living a humble life
and I've only learned
the second-rate artistry of blade.
The lost martial arts
have always been kept
by famous clans like yours.
I won't have access to Wending Pavilion
or make it to the top
unless I'm one of the Xuanyuan Family.
Xuanyuan Dapan reached
the Celestial Realm.
Why can't I make it?
Funny.
You think I'll marry you?
Think about it carefully.
You will
marry a dying widower
or
marry me to get away.
You have only one night.
Don't think for too long.
I heard your daughter tried to leave.
Jingyi stopped her, didn't he?
Go persuade her when you have time.
We've raised her for years.
It's time for her to repay us.
Xuanyuan Dapan
will not stop.
I know that.
He wants
to enjoy all girls of this generation.
And you'll let him be?
He's in the Celestial Realm.
With him,
our family will always be prestigious.
When he's satisfied,
he's still Old Ancestor of our family.
And our family
can be inheritable.
Without righteousness,
what's the point of inheritance?
Who told you that?
I read about it from books.
Can you reach the Celestial Realm
by reading books?
Jingcheng,
after Qingfeng marries Old Ancestor,
you'll have no offspring.
Why not
hand your connections over to me?
I'm more humane than Jingyi.
I won't embarrass you.
You've been waiting for this day,
haven't you?
Don't put me on the spot.
If you don't understand,
I can go talk with your wife.
She always looks down on you.
Over the years,
she has been having a hard time.
Actually,
one can also reach the Celestial Realm
by reading books.
Fengnian, hawthorns for you.
Only these hawthorns are ripe.
He has stayed
by the hawthorn tree every day,
waiting to pick some for you.
It tastes great.
Thank you, Huangman'er.
Eh?
What?
Interesting.
(Great Prestige, Gold Path)
(Eternal Longevity, Cultivate for Eternity,
Unity of Everything)
(Xiaoyao Temple)
Xu Xiao's son?
That's me.
You two indeed look alike.
A little bit in appearance,
but a lot in spirit.
Who are you?
Xuanyuan Jingcheng.
Qingfeng's father.
You don't do martial arts, do you?
Why could you fly to me?
I have a portrait.
You look like the person in it.
I don't understand.
The person in the portrait
is closely linked with you.
You indeed look like her
in appearance.
Who
are you talking about?
You look as graceful
as your mother used to be.
Shut up!
Uncle Jingyi has blocked all the ways
away from Mount Hui.
Now that they want to give you
to Old Ancestor,
they won't let you leave.
I was dubious
of what Father told me.
But now I know it's true.
Mother,
do you have a way to leave?
If I did,
I would have left already.
So, we don't have a way out?
Xu Fengnian sent you
back to Mount Hui?
Are you saying
that I should ask him for help?
How can he interfere
with our family business?
If he didn't want to interfere,
he wouldn't have given you a ride.
I can't even leave Mount Hui.
How can I beg him for help?
You don't help your brother?
I don't need to.
That uncle doesn't mean to fight.
How do you know?
I just know.
So much for this.
God of Sword, you've got an heir
for your Snakes in Sleeves.
He's using it poorly.
He's the right person.
His Highness isn't talented enough
for the moment.
But given some time,
he'll inherit your great martial arts.
Come on.
He isn't as talented
as his little brother.
This boy is born in the Diamond Realm.
He's generally beyond compare.
Now that you're not here for a fight,
stop gossiping about my mother.
I wasn't gossiping.
I was telling the truth.
You indeed look like your mother.
What does it have to do
with your portrait?
(Jianjia House)
To be honest,
the person in the portrait
is your mother.
You met my mother?
My wife did.
She portrayed your mother.
Wait.
Why did your wife
portray my mother?
When my wife met your mother,
your mother was disguised as a man.
Your wife never knew that?
When she got to know the truth,
she had fallen in love
with your mother.
But she knew they couldn't be together.
So, she portrayed the person
in her memory.
To her,
she only wanted
to remember
the young swordsman who attracted her.
So, she only loves
the person in the portrait.
What do you want?
Xuanyuan Dapan wants to marry Qingfeng.
How old
is Xuanyuan Dapan?
Nearly a hundred years old.
Shame on him!
If people know about it,
our family will be laughed at.
Xuanyuan Dapan is
in the Celestial Realm.
No one dares to laugh at him.
So, great martial arts
can make people
ignore the sense of shame?
That's right.
So?
Could you leave Mount Hui
and take my message to Xu Fengnian?
No.
I haven't told you what message it is.
Even if North Liang is interested
in the Xuanyuan Family,
why must they work with you?
They could talk to your uncles.
Will Xu Fengnian really offend
a master of the Celestial Realm
just for you?
You have only one option.
Marry me tonight
and make me one of your family.
You've been waiting for this day, right?
On Mount Hui,
no one dares to marry you,
but me.
After tonight,
you'll have no more chance.
Fine!
Let's get married!
Let's do it tonight.
We would be stopped if we did it now.
Xuanyuan Dapan
wants all descendants
of the Xuanyuan Family
to be his.
So, what he wants
is more than marrying your daughter.
Why can such a man
be a master of the Celestial Realm?
The level of martial arts
has nothing to do with morality.
Mr. Jingcheng,
you didn't only come
to tell us about the scandal
in your family, did you?
I'm going to kill Xuanyuan Dapan.
But he's a master
of the Celestial Realm.
In the past twenty years or so,
I've learned all the secret martial arts
in Wending Pavilion.
Are you sure you can kill him?
In five years, I'll be able to kill him.
But now I'm running out of time.
When I fight him,
no matter I win or lose,
I'll die.
I'm not afraid of death.
But I worry
about some people.
Your wife and daughter.
After I die,
I don't know
how they'll end up.
Luckily, you've come.
In this world,
no one can save them, but you.
Why must I save them?
After Xuanyuan Dapan dies,
my daughter will take over Mount Hui.
But she's too young.
She needs time
to build up a stable foundation.
During that,
you can use her as a puppet
and take control of the Xuanyuan Family.
From then on, Mount Hui
will fall under the control
of North Liang.
Who told you that we wanted Mount Hui?
What worries you, Your Highness?
You have two brothers.
One of them, Xuanyuan Jingxuan,
has controlled Mount Hui for years.
But your daughter has no supporters.
Even if I support her,
she might not defeat them.
You made sense.
I understand what you're talking about.
You don't want to marry your daughter
to Xuanyuan Dapan.
You don't need to kill him.
Bring your daughter here
and marry her to His Highness.
It's a perfect plan.
Isn't it?
Xuanyuan Dapan can get
whatever he wants.
He doesn't care
even if Qingfeng is married
to someone else.
How about this?
Come to our sect for shelter
with your family.
We're neighbors.
It's convenient
to help each other, isn't it?
We can't come to you for shelter.
Why?
When we take action,
we'll certainly keep your daughter safe.
You're too close to Mount Hui.
If you interfere,
our family
will never have our day.
Only North Liang can help you?
Yes.
What about your brothers?
I'll kill Xuanyuan Jingxuan first.
When?
Immediately.
In two hours,
I'll go to Hill Guniu
and have a life-and-death fight
against Xuanyuan Dapan.
Your Highness,
I invite you to go and watch it.
What if I don't go?
Your Highness,
you can decide the destiny of my family.
If he were really sincere,
he should have brought Xuanyuan Qingfeng
as the hostage.
There's no such thing as free lunch.
He only gave you the bait.
Xu Fengnian is Xu Xiao's son.
As long as he appears on Mount Hui
within two hours,
it's like a declaration
that he'll interfere
with the coup of the Xuanyuan Family.
By then, even if he wants
to step backward,
he can hardly do that.
But it's true
that there'll be a fight
in the Xuanyuan Family.
Why don't we just watch
and make a decision
after the fight is over?
If I don't appear on Mount Hui
within two hours,
I'll lose the chance
to control the Xuanyuan Family.
It'll be risky if you go.
It'll be regretful if you don't.
Huangman'er,
do you think I should go?
Do you want to go?
I do.
I planned to go to Mount Hui long ago.
Now, the Xuanyuan Family is in chaos.
I want to see it personally.
Now that you want it, do it.
Good point.
Now that I want it, I'll do it.
Let's go!
Your Highness. Your Highness.
This is our bowl.
A bowl
costs two coins.
Mother,
I'm getting married tonight.
You have no way out.
I'll kill myself
if the worst comes to the worst.
Do you want to die?
Uncle Jingxuan,
please don't force me.
After you marry Old Ancestor,
you can learn any martial arts you want.
But I don't want to marry him.
You're born in our family, anyway.
Sister-in-law,
do you know where my brother has gone?
It's not my concern.
Over the years,
I'm sorry to have you suffer
when living with my brother.
I guess
you know how I care for you.
Uncle Jingxuan...
My nerd brother
doesn't know how women feel.
Women often feel lonely.
Am I right?
Sister-in-law!
Let go of her.
Don't interfere with the elders!
Let go of my mother.
Don't hurt her!
Your Highness,
there are many retainers
in the Xuanyuan Family.
Now that you're going up Mount Hui,
shall we bring Fengzi Battalion?
When I go there only for travel,
no matter how the fight ends up,
there's a turning back for me.
But if I took Fengzi Battalion,
it would be a different thing.
Then why didn't we take
Young Master Longxiang?
If we have to fight,
he can hardly control himself.
Ning Emei,
how many people do you think we need
to wipe out this mountain?
We're strong enough already.
Respect your uncle.
Keep that in mind!
Sister-in-law,
let's continue.
You'd better think it all out.
According to Old Ancestor,
tomorrow, I'll officially be the master
of the Xuanyuan Family.
From tomorrow on,
I don't need to consider anything.
Leave.
If I leave now,
how can I still be your daughter?
If you keep fighting me,
I'll break your limbs
and send you
to Old Ancestor's room personally.
Why must you struggle?
Wait!
If I survive,
I'll kill you!
Jingxuan.
Jingcheng?
You've been quick-tempered since little.
In some cases,
before everything is settled,
don't rush to judge.
What shall I wait for, then?
You?
Xuanyuan Dapan gave you the pill?
How do you know?
I can see that.
He gave me the pill
to enhance my strength.
Now I'm in the Void Realm.
I'm qualified
to be the master of our family.
Enhancing you forcibly
will give you no experience.
It's harmful
to the development of your martial arts.
Should I thank you for reminding me?
Your impatience
will ruin our family.
So what?
Jingxuan,
if you leave Mount Hui
and our family immediately,
I'll keep you alive.
Over the years,
you don't even dare to enter this house.
Even if I break your daughter's limbs
and rape your wife
right in your face,
what can you do?
The whole clan
of Mount Hui
is filthy.
It's kind of timely rain.
Let the rain
wash it up.
You're totally insane, I guess.
How dare you...!
It's time
to change the clan's fate.
(Mount Hui)
Master Jingyi,
Master Jingxuan was seen
to go to Master Jingcheng's house
and got in an argument.
He's hopeless.
All he cares about is such crap.
Let's go have a look.
Master Jingyi.
Master Jingyi,
Xu Fengnian is coming up the mountain.
The patrolling retainer asked
if we should stop him.
Assemble our retainers.
Yes.
(Mount Hui)
So, you can do martial arts.
You've kept it from us for years.
I never keep it from anyone.
You just think I'm a loser
when I only read books.
Can you get genuine spirit by reading?
Something like that.
You're finally going to do something?
We can't build the new
unless we destroy the old.
Xuanyuan Dapan has led our clan
to the wrong path.
Today,
I'll set things right
and get our clan back on the right path.
How arrogant!
Speaking of martial arts,
you and Jingyi can't defeat me
even if you fight together.
Well, show me
how talented you can be.
You're in the Void Realm.
I'll kill you with the same power.
How's this possible?
You're in the Void Realm,
but you have a poor mental state.
What a waste of the Void Realm!
Jingxuan,
your punch
wasn't even as amazing
as Xu Fengnian's brandish of his blade.
Wait, Jingcheng.
I'll go tell Old Ancestor.
You should be
the master of the Xuanyuan Family.
I will kill Xuanyuan Dapan.
To prosper our family,
some people should be alive.
I gave you a chance to make your choice.
Wait, Jingcheng.
I'm sorry.
I'll go tell Old Ancestor.
You should be the master of our family.
You should be the master.
He's dead?
(Mount Hui)
What a turbulent martial world!
If you keep walking,
you'll reach our private mansions.
Your Highness, why are you coming here?
How much further is it
from that old man's mansion?
It's not very far.
When we go up, we'll reach Guniujiang.
There's a flatland,
known as Snowfield.
Xuanyuan Dapan lives there.
Let's go enjoy the scenery
of Snowfield Guniujiang.
Li Chungang?
Your Highness,
are you going to break into Mount Hui?
What makes you think so?
Guniujiang is where
our Old Ancestor resides.
No strangers are allowed in.
It's raining.
What?
Do you have an umbrella?
Lend it to me.
A jar of Danggui Wine
is sent to you every year.
Have you really not tasted any?
(Danggui Wine)
You finally dared to do something.
It tastes good.
You can have a taste.
It's not that I didn't dare.
Our clan
(Danggui Wine)
indeed owed Xuanyuan Dapan.
He used to be a shield of Mount Hui.
But I didn't expect him
to want my daughter.
What?
I...
I came
to tell you something.
Xu Fengnian has arrived at the gate.
Master Jingyi and the retainers
are...
are in a stalemate with him.
I'm glad he has come.
Off you go.
Yes.
Bring Xu Fengnian to Guniujiang.
I'll take care of the rest.
Xu Fengnian will fight Xuanyuan Dapan?
Qingfeng,
I'll leave your mother
to you.
(Danggui Wine)
Xuanyuan Jingcheng,
where are you going?
Guniujiang.
Snowfield.
As the saying goes,
we can't expect a better world
without cleaning our rooms first.
It's time
to clean our rooms.
You're going to fight him?
But he's in the Celestial Realm!
I don't care.
I'll let no one hurt my daughter.
I've never regretted
marrying you.
You can keep the umbrella,
Your Highness.
But please leave immediately.
Now that I want to enjoy the scenery,
I insist on seeing it.
Make way, please.
This isn't
North Liang.
Stop him.
Father is going to fight Old Ancestor.
Why has Xu Fengnian come?
Your father invited him
for you, of course.
For me?
If Xuanyuan Dapan dies,
you can't take over Mount Hui
unless you have supporters.
The premise is
that Xuanyuan Dapan is killed.
If he isn't killed,
you can leave with Xu Fengnian.
I'll take him to Guniujiang.
Mother,
you're not going there?
I'm not.
If Father really kills Xuanyuan Dapan,
don't you want to see that?
Get to your business.
Leave me alone.
(A hard life doesn't matter,)
(as long as my beloved one comes back.)
His Highness is going up the mountain.
Make way, please.
The flower of pain
Blooms in my heart
I made a bet with the dawn
That you'll answer
Forgive this tragic end
Moved by the moment we met
In spite of thunder and lightning
In spite of my falling
When we are apart
I'll collapse
Capture an image of the memory
After all these ups and downs
The vanity
Who will open it again
It's worth it
It's enough
Drowned in sadness
Just to see through
I will whisper love to you
For a lifetime
End the worry in the world
It's worth it
I'll be there for you all my life
After the moments of beauty
You are my reason to be
If there is a way
To start over
Will you still remember me