THIS DRAMA IS FICTION
AND THE ELEMENTS OF THE STORY
HAVE NO RELATION TO REALITY.
How long has it been?
It's so uncomfortable.
Well, it's like a servant
beat the master's son.
It's fine.
Are you crazy?
Don't just call him "your father."
He's your uncle. Right?
It isn't that hard
to get you on your knees.
Come in.
You're older than him.
Why couldn't you get along with him?
I apologize.
Are you worried?
I won't fire you.
Your father...
used to steal dried persimmons
that are kept to serve the relatives
during national holidays.
So your grandfather
beat your dad terribly.
I was worried how that little kid
would deal with all those beatings.
I tried to protect your father
and I got beat for an hour myself.
I made your dad the president
of the baseball team.
I thought he was doing a good job
and checked up on him.
The employees weren't
treating him like a president.
He was changing a light bulb.
They looked down upon him
for having a country accent
and being uneducated.
I fired all the employees.
That's how much I cared for your father.
Yes.
After that happened,
I never gave your dad work.
I'd only go visit him to see if he was
living like an ordinary person.
He couldn't even resist
the dried persimmons.
His older brother was the chairperson,
but he couldn't even be respected
on the baseball field.
But you're different from your dad.
That's why I'm giving you work.
You work well.
I will...
do better.
If you work any better,
I guess the baseball team
will soon be disbanded.
Yes.
LET'S GO, DREAMS!
KANG DOO-KI! THE DREAMS!
Sir. You should have
told me you were coming.
-What is Baek Seung-soo doing these days?
-He's just...
I think we're being too nice to him
since his remaining time is limited.
Who is it?
He's the facility administrator here.
Are you...
-Sir.
-Yes.
-Why are you working at this late hour?
-I'm retiring tomorrow.
So I was just taking pictures
of the place.
Do you know me?
Aren't you the son
of President Kwon Jae-woo?
Right?
How do you know him?
I've worked here for a while.
You haven't changed from the kid that
used to follow his dad to work here.
I saw you at the baseball field
here as well.
President Kwon Jae-woo
administered the facility himself
despite his high position
and was a great person.
THE DREAMS SHOP
Weren't you a fan
of the Dreams back in the day?
I remember you being a fan of Um Sang-gu.
Such nonsense.
How are preparations
for the off-season training going?
We're in talks with a travel agency
to host a fan event.
We need to put extra focus
on preventing any injuries.
We need to be in talks with the venue.
Any other things to report?
There aren't any major issues.
The athletes are used to the place.
The chef at the training area
is an old man,
and he makes great fried rice.
If you taste it, you'll...
Let's end the meeting.
Find it delicious.
Sir, you're being called
to the president's office.
-By the president?
-No.
-If it's not the president...
-It's the director of Jaesong Group.
What are the important events
remaining on the schedule?
Well, the most important one now
is the off-season training.
-The period is long.
-It's very expensive as well.
But it's money that will be spent anyways.
We should find a way to make changes
so that the money is not being wasted.
But, sir, we're leaving the program intact
because of regional public opinion.
-If we get rid of that...
-Now that I think about it,
we've been too scared
of the worst-case scenario.
Mr. Baek will make a scene again.
Let's not be afraid
to get our hands dirty.
If we don't disband the team,
we can avoid a boycott.
All right.
I had something important to say.
Are preparations
for the off-season training going well?
Well, pretty much.
"Well, pretty much"?
-How disrespectful.
-It's fine.
We'll feel less sorry since he's so rude.
To make things short,
we're going to cancel off-season training.
What is this? Cancel what?
I canceled it.
You already did?
He just did.
Why are you doing this?
The costs for the training
are way too expensive.
It's not easy sending
that many people to another country.
I'm sure you came here driving a car
despite high oil prices.
What did you say?
What kind of professional team
doesn't do off-season training?
You seem to do things that other people
wouldn't dare to do.
But you always seem to follow others
when it comes to good things.
Who told you not to go?
You want us to go somewhere
within the country?
That is it.
Why are you going this far?
You've pretended to be reasonable,
rational, and not a dirt bag.
You at least made it seem
like a normal organization.
Baek Seung-soo.
I'll be very frank.
The reason why I'm going this far...
is because I can.
I thought about it, and I realized
that I can do this.
You shouldn't disagree with me,
but do things just I do.
Just tell the people that this is how
things turned out and to do as such.
It's easier to suppress your inferiors
than to go against your superiors.
You will be leaving soon,
but I hope you learn this lesson
before you go.
I know exactly why you still haven't
disbanded the team.
Aren't you going to take care
of the company's image?
Are you blackmailing me?
No.
That's your problem.
If we fail to manage our public image,
we have no reason
to keep running this team.
We'd get rid of it instantly.
It's your job to manage
public opinion too.
Mr. Baek.
Do you still not have any regrets?
Even when you're making it harder
for everyone around you?
That brat.
You're going to regret this!
Why was the off-season training canceled?
It's the parent company.
Then where do they want us to go
for off-season training?
-We can go anywhere within the country.
-But we're going to a warmer country
since the players might be injured.
Should I check the fields in Jeju Island?
I already checked.
They're all fully booked on Jeju Island.
Should I look into the places
to the south?
But it's not that different
even in the southern area.
We'll be considered incompetent
wherever we choose to go,
but it'd still be different.
Oh, come on in.
-Hello.
-Hello, have a seat.
We're having problems
with the training site.
The site we booked
for the off-season training
was canceled before we knew it.
Then where are we going?
-Aren't we going to the training?
-We are.
-We'll go somewhere domestic.
-It'd be Jeju Island.
Jeju Island was fully booked already.
-Then we should prepare measures.
-Where are we going then?
It's so tough to work with
a general manager who's being hated.
We shouldn't be blaming
our general manager for this.
We should agree to something
and talk to the president or--
Well, there's no room
for compromise with them.
There's also nothing I can do
if you blame me.
But we tried to book a site
that's located as far south as possible.
Please read these.
This is the best one
of the options we have left.
Since we'll be training somewhere cold,
I've prepared a lot of other things.
INDOOR FIELD AND FACILITIES FOR RAIN
I get your decision on the location.
But how are we going to have
practice games?
The players can't keep
playing against each other.
-We're liaising with the college teams.
-College teams?
It's meaningless
if it's not against a professional team!
Do you have any alternatives?
This is driving me crazy.
Don't you know the players' muscles
will stiffen and lead to more injuries
in cold weather?
Think about why the other teams
would spend money to go overseas.
Do you...
still not have any regrets?
You're making it harder
for everyone around you.
Yes. I admit.
If we get poor results this season,
you may think it's because we didn't
have proper off-season training.
I promise to give you
the best alternative.
I apologize.
I'm going to a meeting
with general managers tomorrow.
I'd like to talk to Jang Jin-woo.
Jang Jin-woo?
Yes, I want to hear from him
what it was like when our team
finished in second place.
I'll get going.
-Okay.
-Goodbye.
I think I know what it is.
-Me too.
-I think I figured it out first.
-No, you didn't.
-Yes, I did.
That's the non-honorific.
-Isn't it?
-That was smart.
It's been a while
since you took a beating.
Today's meeting
with the general managers was held
because General Manager Baek Seung-soo
submitted a questionnaire.
We'll talk about organizing
the regular-season schedules.
Yes. It's simple.
Since a lot of teams are located
in the Seoul metropolitan area,
when the teams in the provinces
travel for matches,
they spend a lot of time on the bus.
I feel that it'll be unfavorable to them.
Let me talk.
Did the Dreams play badly because of that?
No, that's not true.
We were bad at baseball.
Are you claiming favorable terms
until there's equality of outcome?
I'm claiming fairness, not equality.
I'm asking for your consideration
for the provincial teams
when it comes to the training.
Why?
Please consider the difference
in the distance.
Even if you become very considerate
all of a sudden,
the provincial teams
will take the top three places
in terms of the travel distance.
It sounds like you want to say
that you play badly
because you're on a bus for too long.
You can now forget about the fact
that my team is bad at baseball.
We'd like to get results
that match our skills,
not lose because we're tired
from the long-distance travel.
I knew you'd say that,
so I've brought some materials
on the correlation between travel distance
and championship numbers on each team.
-Please turn it on.
-Yes.
Let's see.
The teams with the longer travel distances
are ranked first, third, and fourth
on the number of championships in history.
Why are you laughing?
In 1985, the average starting salary
of the geography majors
at University of North Carolina
was $100,000.
With the current exchange rate,
that's over 110 million in Korean won.
Do you know why it's so high?
Among the graduates,
there was Michael Jordan.
Don't be fooled by the average number.
How old are these statistics
on the number of championships?
Wow.
That's it for today's meeting.
-Good job, everyone.
-Thank you.
Let's go together.
Hey. You can't surprise me like that.
What do you mean?
Was there a problem during the meeting?
No, you were fire...
-You were fired.
-Were you surprised?
We've become quite attached.
It gave me a heavy heart.
Mr. Baek. Congratulations on your return.
Yes, are you saying that with sincerity?
The Dreams aren't even our match.
And you signed with Gil Chang-ju
because we took away Miles.
I thought that was the reason
that happened to you.
So I felt really bad.
I would have still
signed with Gil Chang-ju
even if I could hire Miles.
-My gosh.
-Seriously?
Mr. Baek, your pride is going to
get you in trouble again in the future.
Where are you going
for off-season training?
We usually go to Arizona in America.
We would train for two weeks
in Florida and move to Japan.
It'll probably be the same this year.
What about the Dreams?
We're looking into it.
Wait, you're looking into it now?
Didn't you sign the contract in summer?
What's your plan?
Goodness.
By the way, have you heard of any rumors?
What rumors?
-It's nothing.
-Come on.
What is it?
Drugs. They're planning to tighten control
on drug tests.
I heard a lot of players will be caught.
The KPB says it's better to catch them
before the season begins.
Why would they cover it up until now,
and not deal with it right away?
No reason.
-I'll get going.
-Bye.
Gosh.
How is Lim Dong-gyu doing?
-Kang Doo-ki is--
-Kang Doo-ki must be doing great.
He wanted to go to your team so badly.
Is Lim Dong-gyu...
usually like that?
He's so gloomy. He doesn't talk to anyone.
He wasn't usually like that.
But I can't say anything to him
because he trains so hard.
Almost too hard. I've never seen a batter
that trains harder than him.
It's been a while, Heung-man.
Are you investigating the things
I asked you last time?
Okay. Thank you for your effort.
Bye.
Mr. Baek.
Can you come here for a second?
Ball.
It's about the players
playing in the Australian league.
They're fortunately showing
good performances except for Yoo Min-ho.
It's saying he can't pitch at all.
-He made three balks and got switched.
-What is it?
A PITCH THAT VIOLATES
PITCHING PROTOCOLS
-Did he injure himself?
-No.
They did a medical test on him,
but it seems to be psychological.
It might be the yips.
AN ATHLETE FUMBLING
DUE TO PSYCHOLOGICAL REASONS
Mr. Yoo. You were a pitcher
when you were in high school.
How do you overcome the yips?
It's different case by case.
Were there more pitchers
who couldn't overcome it?
Right.
Mr. Baek. We're ready for the meeting.
Okay. Let's watch him for now.
I've given some thought
about the off-season training.
That's why I invited Jang Jin-woo
to the meeting.
To ask him the difference between now
and when the team won second place.
There are some differences.
First off, there was a pitcher
who won 19 times in a season.
Are you talking about yourself now?
Just stay still.
Now we have Kang Doo-ki.
Why do you think you could
pitch so well at that time?
It's very important for pitchers
to control their mind in the bullpen.
Do you know Ki-bum? The owner
of the restaurant near the stadium.
He used to be a bullpen catcher.
A CATCHER WHO HELPS A RELIEVER
WARM UP BEFORE A GAME
Go!
Your pitches are wonderful today!
I gained confidence by warming up
with him before a game.
He helped check my condition too.
It was very helpful.
Nice pitch.
And we had skilled hitters at that time.
Right, they were good.
They were especially strong
against left-handed pitchers.
Among our batting practice pitchers,
there was a great left-handed pitcher.
His nickname was
the Kim Kwang-hyun Off-the-mound.
Maybe it was because of that guy.
It's Heo Jin-wook.
I tested him because he was known
for his pitching,
but he was bad on the mound.
If he's slightly off the mound,
he's as good as Kim Kwang-hyun.
Why did he leave the team?
If you want to scout him,
I'm against the idea.
-Why?
-He threw a bean ball during a practice.
-To whom?
-To a hitter.
Why?
He had a conflict with the hitter.
He was said to be as strong
as Kim Kwang-hyun down the mound,
but he used such a scary pitch
to be threatening.
That's too dangerous.
He has a problem.
Still, we'll need to check
what the conflict was about.
The hitter was Lim Dong-gyu,
as far as I remember.
Then I'll need to check this even more
about Heo Jin-wook.
But about this issue, shouldn't we focus
on the person who threw a bean ball
to the key hitter
and left the team
instead of focusing on Lim Dong-gyu?
I didn't say I'd bring him back,
but I'll go ask him what happened.
Will his strength
be bigger than his weakness?
What's our batting average
with left-handed pitchers?
Our team's batting average is .262.
So .269 with right-handed pitchers
and .239 with left-handed pitchers.
When other teams are up against us,
a lot of left-handed pitchers
played on the mound.
They indeed sent those pitchers out
on purpose.
SENDING A PITCHER WITH A HIGH WINNING RATE
AGAINST THE OTHER TEAM
Oh, there's one more.
Players didn't suffer
a lot of injuries at that time.
How are we doing
with conditioning our players?
Our team has the highest number
of injuries.
Who's responsible
for a lot of injured players?
The manager.
That's right, but the next person
is the conditioning part, right?
-Why are you looking at me?
-That doesn't make sense.
What doesn't?
Guess who was the conditioning coach
at that time.
-Who?
-Lee Jun-mo.
IN CHARGE OF
THE PLAYERS' NUTRITION, REST, SLEEP
Search his name online.
You'll get all the information you need.
Lee Jun-mo?
Breathe out on the count of three.
In one, two, three. Breathe out.
-Is it okay?
-Yes.
-Your diet is out, so please check.
-Okay.
Did he cause trouble too?
He's a personal trainer for celebrities.
He earned a lot
because he's a star trainer.
-I doubt if he wants to come back here.
-Will it help if we scout him?
He could tell the players'
physical problems
just by looking at the way they walked.
He was the specialist
in terms of preventing injuries.
But we don't even know where they are.
Even if we do,
who's going to persuade them?
Mr. Heo Jin-wook.
Mr. Heo...
Wait, Mr. Heo?
-Who?
-Mr. Heo Jin-wook.
Go inside there.
Inside?
Thank you.
Are you Mr. Heo Jin-wook?
-What is it?
-When do you finish work?
Who are you?
Well, I'm from the operations team
of the Dreams. I'm Han Jae-hee.
-Do you have a death wish?
-No.
Get lost. I won't pitch.
I wonder if there's a story behind that.
I'll never do it if it's with the Dreams.
Get lost.
Keep your shoulders steady.
One more time. Raise it.
Hello.
What brings you here?
I'd like you to be my trainer, Mr. Lee.
-There are other skilled trainers.
-The Dreams want to learn from you.
The Dreams?
Guess how I feel when I hear that name.
Longing?
Bad. I feel horrible.
Keep your shoulders down.
Why are you so negative?
-Excuse me, miss.
-Sure.
No one wants to improve there.
Do you want the Dreams to be strong?
Of course.
Will everyone think the same?
-What if that's not true?
-Is there anyone else other than you?
Yes.
-Then you don't need me.
-We need you so that we can be better.
I was young
and enthusiastic about work once.
I was so passionate.
It's true things went well
for the team when I was there.
At that time, you even checked
the players' fluid intake.
I tried to check their urine color,
and they got the wrong idea.
It was meaningful even though it was hard.
But they didn't even mention
a contract renewal.
I wouldn't have done that
if I had been the team leader then.
I hear the general manager
is causing all the commotion.
So you kept track of us.
I need to continue training
my client for now.
Oh, and search my name
with my salary on the Internet.
It'll make you go straight home.
I know you get paid a lot, Mr. Lee Jun-mo.
Everyone does.
I came because I remembered your passion.
Money isn't everything.
Money is everything.
What? What's this reaction?
You brought the snack, so put it here.
Why are you smiling?
I was surprised at first because I'm still
not used to having you come into my room
when I'm looking
into baseball information.
Then I smiled because now
it doesn't matter to have you see it.
-Okay?
-Okay.
What are you doing?
I have a lot of things to prepare
for our players' training.
It'll be nice to have them say
things have changed with the new analyst.
It's weird for them to train
in a place like that as it is.
What? A place like that?
Are you criticizing the general manager?
That's not what I meant,
but you could feel guilty, I guess.
You better not run into me
in the office tomorrow.
Seung-soo.
I'm so happy to be able to work at home
without any worries
about getting caught by you.
Your plan failed, so I'll make
the team be the champion.
How can you make that happen all alone?
Anyway, you'd better be prepared.
The off-season training will be
way harder than you think.
Please enjoy.
COACH CONTRACT
This is the best condition
we can offer you.
It's our team's business
that we can't pay more than this.
Still, we're not asking you to work
just as much as the amount.
I know how much you usually get paid.
But I heard that your dream
was to work for a baseball team.
If your desperation is bigger
than the difference in the amount,
please work with us.
And I will never come visit you again.
What's wrong?
Tell me what's going on.
Just sit down.
Look at this.
It turned golden so well
that it looks super tasty.
You really know how to grill it.
Come on.
You've tasted it so many times.
What's with you?
Gosh. It's so aromatic and chewy.
Give it to me. I'll do it.
Wait. Let me see your hand.
Looking at your hand,
I see that nothing is easy.
All he'd been doing in his life
was throwing balls.
But he's now struggling with knife work
unfamiliar to him.
What's that out of the blue?
Hey, I worked as a bullpen catcher
to help you with your pitching
even after I retired.
I did such a thing
even though it didn't pay me much.
Right. You're completely fed up
with baseball because of me.
That's too much, though.
Did you take the position because of me?
Of course.
You were totally uncontrollable
without me, so I had no choice.
So I achieved 19 wins that season.
What's this strange conversation
between you two?
What do you want to say?
Well, Ki-bum.
-Get me some water.
-It's right in front of you.
It's not cold.
I want cold water.
Ki-bum.
You psycho.
You're still sharp.
Let's do it together.
We need a veteran bullpen catcher
who can encourage our pitchers.
No way!
But...
It's not because of the restaurant.
It's unbelievable.
You guys are so shameless.
I know he's working really hard
at this place now.
But I can no longer see him
striving so hard to catch
the balls the young pitchers throw
with his callused hand.
It breaks my heart!
Goodness.
Throw it here.
Do you have a death wish?
Did you play in the pro league?
No.
Although I didn't do well as a player,
you might really get hurt.
Then you should just throw the ball
right into the glove.
If you couldn't do so,
I wouldn't be following you like this.
Of course, it's a piece of cake for me.
And I said I won't.
I know, but just do it.
Come on.
You have such great control.
-But you said you were not a player.
-See?
-This is how competent the Dreams are.
-Did you get training or something?
I did. If we can't find bullpen pitchers,
I should do it.
Look at you.
Then I'll keep doing this. You do that.
Wait. What are you talking about?
That's not what I want to ask you.
Why did you do that to Lim Dong-gyu?
What a wacko.
-So you don't want to tell me?
-I want to hit you first.
But we don't want a violent pitcher.
No matter what I do, I won't work
with someone like you.
Someone who looks down on me.
-Did Lim Dong-gyu do the same to you?
-Gosh.
I'm General Manager Baek. I came
because I seriously want to know.
Why would a general manager come here?
Are you guys all insane?
That's what general managers do.
Se-young also won't be able
to persuade the guy, right?
-He's already making a lot of money.
-She's still the team leader.
Why don't we trust her?
By the way, if we hire bullpen pitchers
and a conditioning coach,
will our team really become strong?
Why do you raise such a question
all of a sudden?
You weren't the same
when we signed with Kang Doo-ki.
You know, he's a top-tier pitcher.
I'm just not so sure if a coaching staff
can change the team.
If that's what you think,
can a general manager
make a change in a team?
It's a totally different story.
-It's not the same.
-I neither...
hit nor throw the balls.
So I do everything that can help our team.
You'll also go to pick Yoo Min-ho up
right after you get to the office.
Right.
The young pitcher couldn't throw much
and returned because of the yips.
You're going all the way there
to encourage him.
We might not be able
to make a huge change,
but we just do our thing.
You're right.
It was a nice finish with awesome putting.
Gosh, you scared me!
Knock before you come in.
Will it change anything
if we hire these guys?
We expect it to change something
and we also hope so as well.
By the way,
since when did their pay rise this high?
We're paying them as much as we need them.
Do you think our team is that well-off?
I thought it'd be enough with the money
we saved from the flight tickets.
You're making me sick.
Just leave it here.
Right. You need to get
Director Kwon's approval, right?
What did you say? How dare you...
Why would I need his approval?
Do you think I'm his sidekick
or something?
Why are you not answering? Say no!
Come on!
PRESIDENT'S OFFICE
So we succeeded in recruiting
Heo Jin-wook, right?
Yes.
Jae-hee told me why he threw a bean ball
at Lim Dong-gyu.
So you no longer oppose it?
Sure. You were right this time too.
I worked so hard
as a scorekeeper to join a baseball club,
but compared to you who claims
to know nothing about baseball...
Stop it.
Why do you say that?
Although it's quite tiresome,
we need someone like you.
If you oppose something, I reconsider it.
But you've never changed your mind.
I reconsider it and become convinced
that I was right.
Of course, there must be times
you are right.
I'm sure Heo Jin-wook will do well.
INTERNATIONAL FLIGHT ARRIVAL
Min-ho!
What brings you here?
Hey. Everyone has been talking about
what a crybaby you've become.
That's why we came.
You must be hungry.
Do you eat tteokbokki when you
come back to Korea or not?
You eat.
Is this the nation of tteokbokki?
Let's go.
I just made a joke.
Try to laugh, will you?
Enjoy your meal.
But we ordered the deep-fried squid.
What is this?
This must be the deep-fried squid, right?
Min-ho!
This is good. Throw a ball.
I'll...
hit a home run with this.
Open your mouth.
Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
You still have a lot of time
to play baseball.
If you're tired, you can take a break.
-Yes.
-He's right.
We have a bright future,
the Dreams have a bright future, okay?
Here. Promise us you'll take
good care of your health.
Here.
Is this how you do it?
You're the super rookie.
You learn pretty fast.
Now, Dreams!
-Dreams!
Excuse me.
I'll take the deep-fried squid
and tteokbokki for two people to go.
-Are you bringing them for Ms. Lee?
-Yes, no one hates tteokbokki.
Your grandmother.
Can I take some to go for my grandmother?
Order as much as you want.
They're all on me today.
We'll take 40 servings just in case!
I'm ready.
Are you taking those shoes out again?
I should at least have these out
to feel relieved.
Put them back in.
It reminds me of your dad,
and it's distracting.
The off-season training is long.
Leave those there so I can feel
at ease, all right?
You only want yourself to feel at ease.
Mom.
Stay healthy while I'm gone.
Sure.
Darn it.
-What's wrong?
-Do you think it makes sense to go
to the off-season training on a bus?
I heard the Dreams was also a team.
But how is this
a professional baseball team?
Who said so?
Kang Doo-ki.
-Do you think this is a team?
-It is a team, you brat.
Even though the club lacks the support,
we're all professional players.
-Isn't this a professional team?
-Sure.
Hello, fellow players!
I'm your senior, and I'm here to work
part-time as the bullpen catcher.
I'm Kim Ki-bum.
I'm trying to help Jin-woo.
But I don't know what else to do
in terms of economic sense.
Darn it.
Just for the off-season training,
I'll work part-time over there.
I'm Heo Jin-wook,
I used to be the batting practice pitcher.
It's nice to see you again.
I brought him because we might require
a specialized batting practice pitcher.
He'll pitch the ball to every corner
of your choice with his left arm.
You begged him to let you go
because your friend got in an accident.
But Lim Dong-gyu told you to pitch
100 more balls before you leave,
so you threw a bean ball at him.
That's a bit iffy.
It wasn't such a good decision,
but I don't think it'll be a reason
for me to never work with you.
He should make a promise
not to do it again.
Yes, he should.
Here. It's your contract.
You're crazy. You'd pay me this much?
You wouldn't come if I just told you
the team is like your family.
May I sign it? I didn't bring my seal.
Are you using the honorific
all of a sudden?
Thank you.
It's good to meet you.
I'll be your conditioning coach,
Lee Jun-mo.
I'll help you prepare for the season
while maintaining your condition.
You all know he's
the best expert in this country
-on preventing injuries, right?
-Also, I'll make the delicious shakes
that you all used to like
during the training period.
Thank you!
Thank you.
I'll try, and if I feel like
it's not going to work,
-I'll quit whenever I want.
-Sure.
You can irresponsibly quit
whenever you like.
I'm the only one allowed
to use the word irresponsible.
-Yes.
-And there will be no contract extension.
Sure thing.
I also prefer not to be treated
as someone useless after I've worked hard.
We would never.
LEE JUN-MO
They're all competent people who were
on our team until we won second place.
I've brought them so that we can get help
at least for the off-season training.
Listen. You should be dealing with
the problems of the practice games.
I apologize once again
for the poor training environment.
We're really sorry.
Now, here are some red ginseng drinks
to supplement your strength
before the training.
Here.
Think of it as a small token
of sincerity from the operations team.
-You prepared these for us?
-Let's all cheer up,
and finish our training without injuries!
Ready.
Stretch.
Go further.
-Okay, one, two.
-Next!
Stretch.
Go.
Kang Doo-ki's RPM is over 2,600
when he's throwing a slider.
Of course.
-Did you say 2,600?
-Look.
It's all right. Cheer up!
Min-ho. Just a moment.
Will you try pulling your elbow inside?
Keep going. Tell me if it hurts.
-It's fine.
-Rotate it this way.
HEO JIN-WOOK
All right.
Okay. That's good.
Lower.
-Are your knees all right?
-They're okay.
Every player has his own pain.
That must have been true.
And I have more body parts that hurt.
Take it.
What is it?
-It's medicine for hemorrhoids.
-I brought mine already.
It's from America.
The catchers in the MLB use this.
MLB?
Throw it.
Does it look like
I'm sick again this year?
I'm not.
It's much better this year.
From my perspective,
the Dreams had quite a lot
of dirt bags who needed to be dealt with.
Lim Dong-gyu, Ko Se-hyuk,
-Seo Yeong-ju.
-What?
I kicked Lim Dong-gyu and Ko Se-hyuk out.
But I won't kick you out.
Because I'm the only catcher you have.
Right.
-Right?
-You're one of the best defense catchers.
-You're unrivaled.
-What? Do you need money?
And I'm not one of the best.
I'm just the best.
I don't know how you would think of me,
but I'm not the kind of person
who feels excited after punching someone.
When I realize good things about those
who I had a conflict with,
I feel a little uncomfortable.
Seeing you training hard
and enduring your pain, for example.
So, what is your point?
Don't injure yourself.
Just that itself will raise your salary.
Are you worried about me now?
You're temperamental,
wild, and thoughtless.
I don't want you to act up
and feel left out in the end.
There's no need for it.
You just need to work hard.
That's my point.
How is our team's strength this year?
First off, Kang Doo-ki is with us.
Gil Chang-ju
is doing better than his heyday.
It's worth fighting.
I've arranged a practice game.
With a college baseball team?
No.
How did you arrange it with them?
I looked into the team
who booked a place on Jeju Island.
I thought you were going to Japan,
so why Jeju Island all of a sudden?
Our parent company was suddenly
against us training abroad.
They reserved a place on Jeju Island
and told us to go there.
Mr. Baek.
Be honest with me.
About what?
Lim Dong-gyu.
-I'm listening.
-Does he have a problem or not?
He has.
-Jeez.
-What is it? What is it? Tell me honestly.
-He can't even hit 50 home runs.
-What?
What's wrong with you?
Tell me honestly.
Did Lim Dong-gyu...
use drugs or not?
Hey, Lim Dong-gyu.
I've never heard of this.
If he can't play properly
in our games because of doping,
I'll make you pay for it.
Why are you telling me this
all of a sudden?
After the doping issue, the parent company
has changed its attitude.
Don't worry too much.
I'm sorry about grabbing you
by the collar just now.
I'm not sure if we can let it slide
just by your word of apology.
-Why don't we talk about a practice game?
-A practice game?
Between us and the Dreams?
Yes, I suggest two games.
If you come to where we are,
we'll provide you with food
and a place to sleep.
We've traded each of our players.
If we hold a practice game,
reporters will crowd in
to gossip about which team
was wiser with the trade.
A match between Kang Doo-ki
and Lim Dong-gyu.
I thought you'd be curious about it
as someone in the field,
not as the general manager.
We'll play two games,
and I hope we win both.
Experts analyze whose strategy
has been strengthened
and whose teamwork has gotten weakened
during the hot stove league.
But nothing turns out to be
right after the season.
I ran around here and there
to make our team stronger.
It's my first time in the baseball trade,
and I'm not sure if it'll bring results.
We aren't sure about that either.
I guess you wouldn't know
until you actually play a game.
I'm having a lot of thoughts.
Please check for me.
Okay.
Lee Min-woong has become muscular.
He's the starting pitcher
now that Doo-ki is gone.
And Yang Jin-ho is the second pitcher.
There's Choi Woo-hyuk too.
Even without Kang Doo-ki,
they have two pitchers with 15 wins.
LIM DONG-GYU
Hey, Baek Seung-soo.