OUTFIELDER CATEGORY, LIM DONG-GYU
-We've been doing this every year!
-That's what we're supposed to do!
I see.
We'll contact Lim Dong-gyu.
I'll buy drinks, so stop worrying.
All right?
All right. General manager?
General manager!
Did you see the Golden Glove Awards
last night?
Our very own Lim Dong-gyu
received two awards.
-Yes.
-That's why there is so much buzz.
He donated the prize, worth 3 million won,
to his colleagues
and Dreams Baseball Club.
He even donated his Fair Play Prize,
worth 4 million won, to homeless shelters.
He even received the Fair Play Prize?
That's the kind of player Lim Dong-gyu is.
About the trade negotiations…
The prize winner, Lim Dong-gyu, is here.
Hey!
Lim Dong-gyu!
Are preparations for the interview
going well?
Why do you keep making me
do all this work?
It's not like you have
anything else to do.
I get my pay even if I don't work.
All right, everyone.
For tonight's dinner,
we're all going to eat out
thanks to Lim Dong-gyu, who is paying!
General manager.
Do you like lamb?
I do not.
Come in.
I have a question.
-Is it regarding Lim Dong-gyu?
-Do you know him well?
I don't know him personally.
I don't know him personally either.
Do you know what WAR is?
Doesn't it stand for wins
above replacement?
Yes.
Lim Dong-gyu's WAR
is top five in the entire league,
even when you include the pitchers.
You're right. He must be a great athlete.
I'm talking about Lim Dong-gyu,
the Dreams' franchise star
to the Dreams' new general manager.
Did you hear the speech Lee Dong-gyu
gave while accepting his prize?
He said he wanted to retire
while still a member of the Dreams.
I heard him speak of him wanting
to have his number retired.
If he plays for a few more years,
he will be qualified
to have his number retired.
His uniform sales alone make up
70 percent of sales.
Out of all the fans who come
to see the games,
70 percent have his name
on the back of their shirts.
Are you aware of the weight
he carries while you carry this out?
I'm very curious to know
how much you actually know
about the Dreams.
I'm trying to know more,
and I'm sure that I know more
than you're worried about.
-But Ms. Lee?
-Yes.
Did the previous general manager have
to get your approval as he did his job?
No.
Then, do I have to persuade you
as I do my job?
It's just because
it's an important matter.
If it is such an important matter,
why do I have to get your approval
as I do my job?
Are you demanding of me something
you didn't of the previous general manager
because you think I don't know baseball?
Are you going to stay here?
I'll get going.
Mr. Lim Dong-gyu.
-What?
You can talk casually to me as well.
This is my home.
The Dreams is my home.
There is just so much that I've done here
for the past 11 years.
But one day, a crazy fool
who knows nothing about baseball
decides to come and take away my home.
I guess you don't know your real place
because everyone's sucking up to you
and calling you general manager.
Hey.
Do you leave your home
when your housekeeper tells you to?
I don't have a housekeeper.
I've hit 270 home runs on this team
during the last 11 years.
How many hits do you think
I have under my belt?
Do you know how many wins
we achieved thanks to me?
Do you know how messed up…
your plan and what you're saying are?
Mr. Lim Dong-gyu.
Your job is hitting home runs
and running around.
My job is to reorganize the team
and negotiate trades.
Is it just our places that are different?
No, our positions
are completely different.
Enough. I'll show you.
I'll show you just what kind of strength
someone who's played baseball well
for 11 years has.
Just watch and see.
Are you training at this late hour?
You must be tired with all the work.
I've made the decision on my own
without discussing it.
DREAMS MANAGER YOON SUNG-BOK
Are you going to carry this out?
Are you going to be against it?
It won't be easy.
But you know that it must be done.
I'll get going.
What is this?
Sorry.
I don't know how important you are,
but don't you think you should walk
with more care?
-Answer me!
-What are you doing?
-What would you like to have?
-Ma'am, two servings of Korean beef
Just give us two servings of pork neck
and a bottle of soju.
-And a beer each, please.
-Okay.
Come on. Let's eat beef today. It's on me.
Not yet.
What do you mean?
I'm not that pathetic
to fawn over a young boy
who joined the company by nepotism
just to eat beef.
But I want to eat beef.
I'll practice noblesse oblige.
If you wanted to eat beef,
you should've gone home, you bourgeois.
Don't try to stimulate the appetite
of the humble class.
I'll live without remembering
what beef tastes like.
Humble people also should enjoy
some luxury from time to time…
Wait.
Isn't he Lim Dong-gyu?
He is. Just pretend we didn't see him.
Why do we have to do that?
It's not us who decided on the trade.
-He's coming this way.
-Don't look at him.
-Hello.
-Hi.
You're here.
They're my friends.
It's good to see you.
I see. Nice to meet you.
I should treat you to some meat.
It's all right.
Meat tastes better when I pay for it.
Have a good time.
I can see you don't really want
to talk to me.
-Then, have a good time.
-Thank you.
Hello?
Who?
EMERGENCY ROOM
Hello.
I'm here to see a patient
named Baek Seung-soo.
The one who was assaulted?
Yes. How is he?
He's getting some rest right now.
May I ask what your relationship
with him is?
We work at the same company.
-Why did you call me, by the way?
-His phone had no saved numbers.
-And you were in the recent call history.
-Sorry?
-Why?
-We don't know that either.
What? Why didn't he save any numbers?
Yes. I think he got into a fight
and got beaten.
Does he think he's still a kid?
You should be a decent old man
as you grow older.
Can you stop backbiting me?
I should go. Bye.
And am I an old man?
You can go home.
Stop. Don't move yet.
I'm fine alone. Move.
We got a report call.
You got suddenly assaulted?
Please tell us about his appearance.
He had a big body
and was wearing loose pants
and a flowery shirt.
I think you can check the security camera
in the alley.
It's Lim Dong-gyu, right?
What do you mean?
I ran into him at a restaurant
before I came here.
And he came with someone
who looked exactly the same
as the one you described.
Isn't it just your assumption?
He's such a scary guy.
Is this because of the trade?
What he thinks regarding it
is not important.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
As for Lim Dong-gyu…
I'm not telling you that you need
my permission or anything.
Do you have to trade him no matter what?
What if he attacks you again?
That's my job.
Then I'll report him instead
for hiring a man to assault you.
-Never do that.
-Why?
Only a silly general manager would report
the most expensive player to the police.
I'd rather remain silent and sell him
at a high price.
Gosh. Is it that important…
I know it's important.
Still…
Seriously.
Welcome back…
Who did that?
Pretend you saw nothing.
Then I'll raise your allowance.
Who did that to you?
You know I wouldn't just let him
get away with it.
Then?
Don't you remember?
I even held out
in the Korean wrestling team.
Compared to that, it's nothing.
-Are you really okay?
-I am.
It's easier to deal with this kind of guy.
We both are just getting used
to each other.
BATTING AVERAGE
BY LOCATION, PITCH, SITUATION
HELLO SPORTS
Heung-man, it's me.
Here's your coffee.
The life of a young general manager
is very dynamic.
MMA teams would fit him better.
I would've taken a day off if I were him.
Look at him.
He letting everyone know he got beat up?
He's from a small league, he doesn't know
the importance of maintaining authority.
I don't think he'd last long here, anyway.
The proposal to trade Lim Dong-gyu
wouldn't even get permission.
-That's what I think.
-Never.
-The coffee you make is the best.
-It's my pleasure.
The guy you met last night
seems to be fine.
Thanks.
Should I take care of him again?
No, you don't have to.
I know you're tired too.
I guess you were too tired
to give him a good blow.
Sir, I'll call you again
when I get it done properly.
Is he out of the office?
HELLO SPORTS
It's Kim Kwan-sik.
What are you doing here?
I'd like to take you home today.
Don't make a fuss over nothing.
It'll be awkward on the way.
Did you think of anything to talk about
on our way home?
-No.
-Then I'll go by myself.
-Twenty minutes is too long for me.
-But I have a lot of topics to talk about,
so I can just pick some from them.
Don't worry. It's all about our work.
Are you still figuring out
what topic to talk about?
What?
Did you decide to trade Lim Dong-gyu
because you knew what kind of guy he was?
No, I didn't know he was this bad.
I'm not trying to oppose trading him
while I'm aware of the situation.
But…
when I try to come up with a player
that can replace him,
I feel frustrated.
Yes, I'm preparing for that.
Can't you prepare for that
with the operations team?
This is also our job.
-Do you know whose car that is?
-Pardon?
It's been following us for a while.
HEUNG-MAN…
Get out.
-Hey.
-Get out of the car.
I don't feel good about this.
I told you to get out!
-Get out.
-Get out of the car!
112…
-I said get out.
-112…
Don't call the police.
-What are you doing?
-Get out.
Get out now!
Yes, Heung-man.
Who on earth is Heung-man?
We should be calling the police!
We can't call the police.
-Get out.
-Get out of the car.
-Get out, you scumbag!
-Hey!
Open the door!
That's my car.
No.
You hit my car.
Why did they stop?
Who are you?
I'm Cheon Heung-man,
a former Korean wrestler.
Who are you supposed to be?
I even won the championship and all.
Is he on our side?
Enough about me.
I have a few friends in this town.
So we should have a lot of mutual friends.
Wouldn't it be awkward
when we meet at a bar later?
I'll give you a chance to quietly leave.
You freak.
Come here!
How dare you?
You little jerks.
Why did you do it?
We were driving, and…
We often do it.
-It's called driving for revenge.
-Hey.
Just because I've been obeying the law
by being an athlete,
do I only look like a good citizen to you?
It's called retaliatory driving,
not revenge driving.
Yes, retaliatory driving.
Were you really not told
by someone to do this?
What?
No.
If someone did order you to do this,
tell the person that this will be
the last time I'm tolerating it.
Yes, I will.
You're badly injured.
Is this from when you were beaten
yesterday?
Well…
I'm fine now. Thank you.
That piece of trash.
Do you want me to talk to him?
But they say his uniform takes up
70 percent of the sales.
-Excuse me?
-What?
It means that
he's a very important person.
But thank you.
This is exactly why I said
I'd get home myself.
This is also why I was driving you home.
Would they have done it
on public transportation?
By the way, who was that?
When I was the general manager
of a Korean wrestling team,
he was the captain.
He found the perfect time to come in.
He did.
-I'll be coming in late tomorrow.
-Okay.
On what occasion?
How frustrating.
Play, play!
You've come so far in this cold weather.
-Who are you?
-Right. Hello.
Wait.
I'm the general manager of the Dreams,
Baek Seung-soo.
You're Kim Jong-moo,
Wait.
No, I'm not.
Yes, you're right. What do you want?
Are you here to observe Son Seung-Min,
the third baseman?
-He's a prospect we're keeping an eye on.
-Come on.
Is this tampering here or what?
It's really not.
I just wanted to see his face.
What's wrong with you?
Sure.
Have you heard the rumor about us?
What rumor?
You must have heard.
You're quick with all the news.
So, why are you selling him?
-You can't find a power hitter like him.
-I'm not. It's not that I'm selling him.
Seriously.
I just got out of that noisy Seoul.
Now you want to cause me trouble.
What do you say we make it
a win-win situation by negotiating?
That's good!
Is he here?
-He's not.
-What?
I don't know what his deal is,
but why does he want to trade
Dong-gyu all of a sudden?
If we take him out of the team now,
they'll freak out.
We have pictures of him
everywhere in our building.
How ridiculous would it seem
from his perspective? Seriously.
It would sound more realistic
if he traded the general manager.
I don't know anymore.
As I get older, words like passion
sound burdensome
because of people like him.
It's because
he was never a baseball player.
Would he really sell Dong-gyu?
He says he's going to.
"No matter what."
Didn't you hear him say that?
If he does,
we'll see who he trades him for.
It doesn't matter who he trades him for.
In this town, Dong-gyu
is the president of baseball.
But it's not like he needs
our permission to do so.
But as someone new in his post,
he's a little reckless,
wouldn't you agree?
He's still the general manager
even if he's new.
OPERATIONS MANAGER
Kwan-sik.
To play in a team
that desperately wants you…
Listen.
I am in ninth place for holds this season.
You're going to regret doing this.
That's my record when I haven't
played much because of my injury.
I'm confident I can make
at least 20 holds.
Yes, I know you can.
But rather than being traded
all of a sudden,
I'm saying this for your sake.
-Kwan-sik.
-Come on.
The Dreams? Are you kidding me?
Hey, do you think this makes sense?
No matter how much
I've contributed during this season,
they're doing this
because they're short on batters.
And who goes to play for the Dreams?
-Is that even a team?
-The Dreams are also a team.
I apologize.
Whether you pitch well here
or pitch well there,
people will always clap for you.
Yes.
-Goodbye.
He's the one
that was kicked out of the Dreams.
He wouldn't like someone
badmouthing his former team.
What is it?
Hey, are you joining our team?
Who said that?
Was it your team?
They're saying you and Kwan-sik
will be traded. He's all mad.
What?
What a lunatic.
He's causing this mess to trade me
for a guy like Kim Kwan-sik?
He's good too.
I'm hanging up.
-Cheers.
It's good to see you.
Reporters.
I might change teams.
Golf teams? Did you get into a fight?
-Who did you fight with?
-No.
-Baseball teams.
-What are you talking about?
Stop kidding around.
I've dedicated myself to the Dreams,
but they're trading me for Kim Kwan-sik.
I can't even cry about it.
Your general manager is crazy.
Why would the Dreams trade
Lim Dong-gyu for anyone?
It's not certain yet,
so please keep it a secret.
Let's drink.
My goodness.
-The drinks tasted sweet like honey today.
-I know, it was so sweet.
-All right.
-What?
Thank you, everyone.
-Don't mention it.
-No problem.
-Go home safely.
-Bye.
Let's go.
Dong-gyu. Let's go for another round.
I'm sorry. It's too late.
Please support me
so I can keep thanking you.
Sure thing.
In that sense,
I prepared this for you.
You shouldn't do this.
Okay, you can count on me.
See you around.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
I mean, Ms. Lee was siding with him,
so I thought he promised
to recruit someone great
in exchange for Lim Dong-gyu.
But what is this?
I couldn't help but think
that Ms. Lee changed too.
I have to call someone.
She has no one to call.
What's with this mood?
Come here for a second.
Come here. I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Are you going into some kind
of an affectionate relationship
-with the general manager?
-What?
You know, like carefully getting
to know each other
as a man and a woman.
What was that for?
Right, you uncivilized people!
I did try to have
some friendly communication
with the general manager!
Good. There's no way
you can communicate with him.
-You badmouth me when I'm not around!
-Stop hitting me already.
He wants to trade Lim Dong-gyu
for Kim Kwan-sik.
-What?
-I mean…
It's true Kim Kwan-sik had good results
this year, but he lacks ground
and is a middle relief pitcher.
We need a starting pitcher.
Come in.
You're working on something, aren't you?
I'm interested in it very much.
Interested in what?
Lim Dong-gyu.
He indeed is influential here and there.
What do you mean?
Didn't you call me in
to say I can't proceed with it?
Mr. Baek, I hired you.
Don't I look like I'll support you
with a sense of responsibility?
Anyway, will it work?
Is that the look of caution
that I'm seeing?
I was just asking
how you'd wield your authority.
Okay. I'll try to wield my authority well.
I think I did a great job hiring you.
I mean, what kind of lunatic
would think of trading Lim Dong-gyu
with someone else in the Dreams?
I'll tell the president to approve it
no matter what.
I'll probably keep...
being on your side.
PRESIDENT'S OFFICE
What's that with Kim Kwan-sik?
It's pending.
I'll ask if any other teams
want to trade a player for him.
We can't trade him for…
Who told you that?
That's not important right now.
-Everyone knows about it.
-You don't even know where it started.
Must I resolve that misunderstanding?
It's because I didn't hear anything
from you.
-Because nothing has been decided.
-You can't even share what's pending?
Can't you trust me?
You don't work with trust.
I'm just saying
we should do our jobs properly.
THE DREAMS'…
GENERAL MANAGER BAEK'S OPINION…
SEND
THE ARTICLE HAS BEEN SENT
IS THE TOP STAR OF THE DREAMS
CHANGING TEAMS?
THE FACE OF THE DREAMS
SAID TO BE MOVING.
GEN MANAGER'S OPINION
WAS GREATLY REFLECTED ON THE ISSUE.
-Is he out of his mind?
-Who else could be their star
-other than Lim Dong-gyu?
-Why can't that new manager
-do a better job?
-He's so frustrating I may have cancer.
BAEK SEUNG-SOO, DREAMS
BAEK SEUNG-SOO, NEPOTISM
SEARCH KEYWORD LIST OF THE DREAMS
GENERAL MANAGER BAEK, OUT!
FIRE THE GENERAL MANAGER.
That's not true. We aren't trading
Lim Dong-gyu with anyone.
That article is wrong, so ignore it.
I told you that it's not true!
Yes, goodness.
I told you. It's a false report.
We know nothing about it,
so how can we trade him?
-No, we don't!
-Yes.
Of course. We will announce it
as soon as it's decided…
Hey. Where's the general manager?
I don't know. Where on earth is he?
Why do we have to clean up his mess?
I'm going to the general manager's office.
Really? I'm going with you.
-Good. Let's go.
-Gosh.
-Are you really going? Don't.
-We have to.
Let's go then.
Hey.
-Where are you going?
-Well…
-To the general manager's office.
-Why?
To make a statement.
"Not Kim Kwan-sik. There's nothing left
to ruin in this team."
Why didn't you tell me?
You're almost like his lackey…
Hey, he hates me the most
because I complain most often.
Why are you acting
like you're all active now?
Where are you going? Go with me.
Mr. Baek.
We need your explanation.
Why must we send Lim Dong-gyu out
by trading him for Kim Kwan-sik?
Does Dong-gyu even tell you
to do something like this?
Mr. Baek.
I want everyone to gather
in the meeting room in an hour.
-In an hour?
-That's it?
All right.
Let's return to our desks first
and gather again
in the meeting room later.
Let's go back. Let's go.
How is he going to persuade us?
Lim Dong-gyu doesn't
even have any injuries.
I'm afraid I won't be persuaded either.
Let's begin.
WHY LIM DONG-GYU
MUST LEAVE THE DREAMS
FIRST, HE'S A COWARD.
He's a coward.
You must be familiar
with his home runs and batting average.
It makes you think he's valuable.
His batting average with RISP is 0.307.
Even though it's lower
than his batting average,
-that doesn't make him a coward.
-But…
he's ranked third in game-winners.
Park Jung-chan is ranked first.
He's also a good player,
but in second place,
we have Jang Dong-soo
with a batting average of 0.270.
He averages 0.330,
but he has fewer game-winners
than a player who averages 0.27.
He's not a hero
when it comes to winning the game.
Didn't you say he doesn't know much
about baseball?
We'll see.
People often say his only weakness
is that he's easily affected by heat.
But the rankings
in professional baseball are…
decided in the summer.
POOR RECORD IN JULY, AUGUST
He's not a player who's weak against heat,
he's just a player who can't contribute
when we compete for the ranking.
Why do we need him so desperately
when he hits numerous home runs
after we're set to be in last place?
Our general manager did his homework.
THE BALLPARK IS CHANGING
Let me calculate which team
has hit the most home runs.
We have allowed the most home runs
and hit the least home runs.
Only Dong-gyu and the opposing batters
have taken advantage
of playing in a smaller field.
So, we've begun extending the fence
by seven meters,
and this decision was made
by both myself and the manager.
With the extended fence,
he loses 12 home runs
considering his hitting distance.
He's actually not a slugger.
He's a batter of middle and long distance.
With a small number of batters
with precision
and a slugger or two on our team,
the player who has nowhere to stand
if we extend the fence is Lim Dong-gyu.
The fourth reason.
This will be the most important.
It's his…
personality.
Hey, pitchers. Get in line in front of me.
I told you to turn the game around
and you didn't!
Baseball is played by the whole team.
Show some respect.
You scumbag!
-Stop!
-Hey!
-Stop him!
-What did you say to me?
You must remember Kang Doo-ki,
who was on our team two years ago.
He was a pitcher with ten wins,
and he had a conflict with Dong-gyu.
I heard that he left our team
as recommended by Dong-gyu.
There was not a piece evidence
of his comments,
but Doo-ki had left our team
with no excuses.
Even now, Dong-gyu demands
that we form the team with players
that he likes.
Mr. Ko, am I wrong?
Please go on.
Now, Kang Doo-ki currently has 18 wins
with an earned run average of 2.28.
He's now one of the top starting pitchers
in the league
and is a player who beats the ace players
of the opposing team.
It was Dong-gyu
who made Doo-ki leave our team.
He is ruining our team.
Now, the fifth reason
is the shift in generations.
Dong-gyu is a veteran who won't be able
to lead our team for ten years.
But fortunately,
we have prospects on our team
who can replace him
just waiting for the opportunity.
OUTFIELDER LEE JAE-HYUNG
Right?
An average of 0.420 and 14 home runs.
It's his record in the second-string team,
and at the end of last year,
he played 20 games
in the first-string team,
and he averaged 0.350
with 4 home runs.
He has also shown his potential
as a center fielder.
It's Yeon Joong-sub.
It's time we let him experience
and train in a first-string team.
-Mr. Baek.
-Yes.
But still, Dong-gyu
is the star of our franchise.
As an employee of the marketing team,
I know that most fans of our team
come to watch Dong-gyu.
And without him, we won't know what to do
with the uniform sales
and the ticket sales.
You want to throw out a player like him.
Have you thought about how it will
affect the image of our franchise?
Right.
We need a star of the franchise.
A player that can surpass his presence
doesn't exist on our team now.
That's why we should
bring a franchise player.
I don't think you know well
about what a franchise player is.
How and where are we going to find
someone like that?
Last year,
-I've negotiated--
-I'm saying...
we can't bring Kim Kwan-sik,
general manager.
Excuse me.
-Yes.
-Say something.
Have you thought about this enough?
All right, then, we'll also get permission
from our employees and proceed.
Yes, I hope
this will be a win-win situation.
Who was that?
-What have you done?
-Let me continue.
We're in need of a starting pitcher,
so we need a pitcher who can be a match
for the opponent's ace player, right?
What if a pitcher like that said
that he won't come back to our team
if Dong-gyu is still with us?
What if he's a player who's able
to boost our players' morale,
has the most number of fans on our team,
is from our region,
and is a Golden Glove winner
who used to be on our team?
No way.
Nice!
Good.
What a pity.
Doo-ki!
It's been decided. I'm sorry.
You've done great.
Thank you for sending me to the Dreams!
Ms. Lee.
Please prepare a uniform for Kang Doo-ki.
Kang Doo-ki?
He's coming to our team?
Yes, I just got the call.
He will be joining our team now.
Wasn't it Kim Kwan-sik?
Right. You should prepare
another uniform for him, too.
Kim Kwan-sik, too?
Yes, we'll be handing over the draft right
of Son Seung-min,
the high school player
who most likely will have priority.
It's a two-for-two trade.
Seung-min's position is third baseman.
I've made this decision because
I heard Park Wan-gu
will be discharged from the army
two months later.
I heard Wins Above Replacement
is important nowadays.
Considering WAR,
Doo-ki is ranked number 1
in the whole league with the WAR of 7.5.
Dong-gyu has a WAR of 6.2.
We're at the bottom with 14 more defeats,
so we'll still be at the bottom
with Doo-ki.
Let's all work harder.
Is there anyone
who still opposes this trade?
Yes.
But Doo-ki is the starting pitcher
of the national team.
Is the trade even possible?
Yes. Why?
I don't care if it's Lim Dong-gyu.
I'm not giving you Doo-ki.
He's the ace player of the national team.
Doo-ki has the earned run average of
over 4.00 against the Sabers, doesn't he?
If we're looking at it that way,
why don't you check Dong-gyu's records
in the summer?
He's trying to maintain his stats.
He's only good in the fall.
Exactly. We don't need a player
who's only good in the fall.
You should be playing well consistently.
What was Dong-gyu's batting average
against the Sabers?
Yes, it was 0.420.
Yes.
Instead,
you must turn over Son Seung-min to us.
Yes, if you give us Kim Kwan-sik.
What? Seriously?
Yes.
Is it a shame that I've managed
something so difficult?
That's just how it is now.
If you still oppose it,
please call out my name before I leave.
I'll walk out slowly.
Goodness.
He recruited Kang Doo-ki?
When did he…
This doesn't make sense.
Is it true?
You'll approve, right?
Pack up.
Now.
And take this with you.
About the car repair,
I just paid for it.
Hey.
Drop this nonsense.
You'll trade me for Kim Kwan-sik?
The fans won't let that happen.
I'm the only one
about to be a retired number here.
Do you want to see everyone up in arms?
Why would everyone be up in arms?
Everyone was happy
to have Kang Doo-ki on the team.
Kang Doo-ki?
A player like him gets his number retired.
He's good at baseball.
He's respected by his colleagues.
Of course, it was impressive
to see you donate gear
and pay for the get-together,
knowing you'd be traded.
Thanks to that, the club doesn't know
about our bad relationship.
You did well until the end.
The first-line national athlete
is joining our team thanks to you.
Why would Kang Doo-ki…
You.
This isn't the end
of my 11 years on this field.
It's not even hard
to kick someone like you out!
Don't you dare take a step from here.
Hey, Lim Dong-gyu.
What, you punk?
Just go.
You approved of the trade.
Yes.
Why?
You know.
We need Kang Doo-ki a bit more than you
right now.
There's nothing we can do about it.
Play well there.
This is insane.
Mr. Lim.
Let me tell you
about the current situation.
No one is sad to have you leave.
You know why?
Because Kang Doo-ki is joining
in exchange for you.
Ask anyone on the street
about who's better.
Be honest with me.
You'd agree it's Kang Doo-ki.
Right?
Thus, the general manager has reason.
I'm a rational person,
so I had to approve of it.
You should've found reason
like he did.
KANG DOO-KI RETURNS TO HOME TEAM
-I was happy to have Lim Dong-gyu.
-Is Kang Doo-ki joining the team for real?
I'm excited to have Kim Kwan-sik as well.
Thanks for your hard work, Dong-gyu.
I hope you win there.
SEARCH KEYWORD LIST OF THE DREAMS
The Dreams.
I've come!
PRESS CONFERENCE
WELCOMING KANG DO-KI TO THE DREAMS
-Kang Doo-ki!
The two traded players showed
different expressions.
Lim Dong-gyu seemed sad
to leave his home team
on which he played for a long time.
Isn't that your company?
Mom.
Our team…
What?
If we're lucky…
If we're really lucky…
Gosh, what?
Our team might not place last next year!
What are you saying?
I signed and approved your work this time.
-You know that, right?
-Yes.
Seeing how you work,
I couldn't help but root for you
as another man.
Mr. Baek.
In the past two years,
we finished with 43 wins
and 46 wins.
Right.
We won too many times.
Don't you think?
Why do you think I hired you?
I told you.
I hired you
because of your unique experience.
Win…
then disband.
Win and disband.
Win…
and again,
disband.
Just do what your experience says.
I'm not asking for much.
Yes, sir.
What kind of a guy
do you think Baek Seung-soo is?
I don't work with humanists.
It's a team that's bad at baseball
and has no future.
We do need changes.
Who's responsible for choosing players?
I think I need to find out.
Has the scouting team ever drafted
a player that does his part?
They say our team is a graveyard
for rising stars.
What're you doing
with those priority draft rights?
-You boiling soup with those?
-It's an unprecedented
pro-team scouting scandal.