♪I want to take control
of my own future♪
♪I want to fight back
and break this silence♪
♪My fate needs no pity♪
♪Let them witness my glorious moment♪
=Princess Revenge=
=Episode 19=
Dongfang Yan,
do you think
I'll always win?
You've never lost.
Ms. Xi.
Mr...
Mr. Yan?
I... I didn't see that at all.
Just what's going on
between both of them?
What are we?
Xi.
All this time,
I've always been
a composed person.
You're just aloof.
What?
Nothing. Go on.
The only time I got worked up
was three years ago.
Your sudden disappearance
three years ago
made me realize
that your absence
slowed down time.
That was the very moment I realized it.
Well, do you...
Take your time to think about it.
You'll decide
what we are.
Lie down.
Get some good rest.
I'll wait for your answer.
Goodnight.
You're acting
like a jerk.
If so,
I'll leave after you fall asleep.
(I fell asleep in
Dongfang Yan's arms last night?)
(Although I'm without a human heart,)
(I've always been by your side.)
(Let me hear his heartbeat.)
Xi.
Morning.
Are all domineering CEOs early risers?
(Dongfang Yan...)
What's the matter?
Did I press on your wound?
Yeah.
Does it hurt?
It does.
I'll apply some ointment on it.
You've had the ointment on your face.
What are you doing?
You've been acting strange
since you woke up.
A B cup is said
to be a man's best asset.
I was wondering if you have one.
Get changed
and head down for breakfast.
(Though I failed
to hear his heartbeat,)
(that was indeed a B cup.)
Here.
Dongfang Yan.
A good-looking man
who cooks well like you
is husband material.
But I'm a nobody to you.
Considering
how discreet our relationship is,
I should be
your secret lover.
♪My eyes are wide open♪
♪I see you clear♪
You're mine now.
That's not enough.
♪Oh, what's your soul saying?♪
♪Oh, is your world changing?♪
♪Your face tells me always♪
♪Things your mouth often spares♪
♪And I hope you know
I'll do what it takes♪
♪To bring joy into your day♪
♪Oh, what's your soul saying?♪
(If would be far too easy)
(if she found out
about my identity now.)
♪Oh, is your world changing?♪
(Yet you get to)
(feel me at this very moment.)
♪Oh, is your world changing?♪
Mr. Yan. Ms. Dongfang.
Ms. Bai is here.
Dongfang Xi.
Please have mercy on Ye Yunzhou.
At least spare his life.
Ye Yunzhou has been jailed.
You want me to spare him?
But did he even have mercy on me?
But you're alright now.
Can't you be kind for once?
Yunzhou is now...
Bai Zhitao.
Your kindness
is nothing but terrifying.
I can give up on my identity
as the adopted daughter.
As long as I can save Yunzhou.
Is that worth it?
Your hands were meant
for signing Dongfang Group's documents.
But now you do house chores
for a man like that.
Is that worth it?
As long as it's him, it's all worth it.
We've known each other
since we were young.
We went from breaking up
to getting back together.
It hasn't been easy for us.
Since you met when you were young,
he has always lingered in your heart.
And you kept idealizing him.
But in truth, he is no longer
the one you once had in your heart.
Anyway, Ye Yunzhou
poses no threat to me.
However,
if you get on the wrong bus,
you can't just stay on it
just because you've already paid.
Sometimes,
getting off is the best choice.
Thank you.
But I believe Yunzhou is the right one.
Why haven't you finished cooking yet?
Are you trying to starve me?
Our family really must have
run out of luck.
The women your brother found
keep getting worse one after another.
Even that Dongfang Xi was better.
I pleaded with the Dongfangs.
They will release him.
Yunzhou.
You've suffered.
Let me take a look at you.
Zhitao.
This time, I really owe it to you.
With you here,
I'll definitely make a comeback.
What?
Aren't you the Dongfang family's
adopted daughter?
You can surely help me.
I gave up that status.
What?
Can't we just live a simple, happy life?
You really are kind.
Can't you tell
I'm insulting you?
Yunzhou...
You actually turned down
such a golden opportunity!
Dongfang Xi was right after all.
Your kindness is just stupidity.
Scram!
Zhan.
You're here, Xi.
So, are you feeling better?
Much better.
Look, I can even
swim freestyle now.
Why aren't you pretending
to be badly hurt to win sympathy?
Wasn't that your specialty
when you were little?
On the contrary...
Did I press on your wound?
Yeah.
Does it hurt?
It does.
What's it?
Nothing.
That day,
you left this at the swimming pool.
You found Cinderella's glass slipper.
Now you have to marry me.
Dongfang Zhan.
We are family.
Always.
♪I like to live on a happy planet♪
♪There's a tide. Raise your head
and follow me. Refuse to sleepwalk♪
♪I can shout Yo for myself♪
♪Nothing can stop me♪
♪Reach out your hand.
Who loves too much to let go?♪
♪Let's work together
to achieve our dreams♪
♪Go after it. Don't wait♪
♪Time has long told me
that it waits for no one♪
♪Enjoy every encounter
and feel the night and day♪
♪Sometimes I stay
with both troubles and sorrow♪
♪Nostalgia doesn't mean conservative♪
♪Thoughts are like the universe♪
♪Not just on stage
and behind the scenes♪
♪Reach out my hands.
Who loves the most to let go?♪
♪Wait, wait. Don't wait any longer♪
♪My dream
is waiting for me to pursue it♪
♪I wander like a duck♪
♪An amphibious player♪
♪I'm not great, but I'm really gentle♪
♪I like to live on a happy planet♪
♪There's a tide. Raise your head
and follow me. Refuse to sleepwalk♪
♪I can shout Yo for myself♪
♪Nothing can stop me♪
♪I like to live on a happy planet♪
♪There's a tide. Raise your head
and follow me. Refuse to sleepwalk♪
♪I can shout Yo for myself♪
♪Nothing can stop me♪