W-Wait, Akari.
Oh... sorry.
Actually, I came with my husband...
What?!
Oh... it is late, isn't it?
Sorry.
How did you get here?
Train? Taxi?
By taxi.
And... I asked my husband to wait
for me at the station for now.
Geez...
You should've told me this before coming.
I'm sorry.
No... I'm the one who's wrong.
I'm sorry for acting so childish
and causing you trouble.
Oh...
You came because
you were worried about me, right?
Thank you.
I'm fine.
Please apologize to your husband for me.
What?! No, what are you doing?
You're scaring me.
I'm sorry for being dishonest.
But I'm going to be honest now.
I'm really overwhelmed
by my feelings right now.
I don't know why I'm so drawn to you.
Even today, I couldn't sit still...
Come in.
Damn it,
you seducer.
No one has ever said things
like that to me before.
I'm actually quite reserved, usually...
Welcome!
Sorry for making you wait.
No, I was just having a drink anyway.
Did you talk to her?
Yeah.
Still in love with her, I take it?
Don't just stay silent.
Deny it, at least.
Thank you for letting me go.
It's nothing...
If something happened, I'd be the one
who couldn't sleep at night anyway.
Why did it have to be a woman?
Of all things...
I'm sorry.
Please go ahead with the divorce.
You don't get to decide that.
I mean, you cheated, right?
You had an affair, right?
I won't divorce you.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
Fansubbed by amrayu for SARS-Fansubs & Drama-Otaku.com
Support at ko-fi.com/dramaclubpodcast
or patreon.com/dramaotaku
Even Though We're Adults
- Ayano!
- Yes?
The boxes marked "clothes"
should all go to the second floor, right?
Yes, thank you.
- Mom, do you have scissors?
- Yes, yes, yes.
Excuse me,
is it okay if we bring in the furniture first?
So the day has finally come...
I really don't want to live with other people.
I'm sure my sister-in-law doesn't
want to live together either.
She probably thinks
it's going to be a pain.
I'm the most troublesome one... I guess.
Eri.
I'm ordering sushi later.
Where do you want to eat?
In here.
Got it.
I'll bring it to you.
You'll have some too, Ayano?
Yes, please.
Wataru, you help out too.
- Okay, okay.
- Ah, the clear soup.
- I'll take care of it.
- Thank you.
- Use the kettle in the kitchen.
- Okay!
Is this for Eri?
Yes.
She doesn't seem up for joining us today.
Is it because I'm here?
No, not at all.
There are times when
she can't handle even family.
And times when she can manage small outings.
It comes in cycles.
We've tried different ways
to get her to go out more,
but now we're letting her do as she wants.
When she feels better,
please try to become friends with her.
Yes, I'd like that too.
Thank you.
Oh...
The sushi was delicious, wasn't it?
I'll wash it.
Oh... it's mine,
so it's okay.
Um... sorry I didn't help out today.
Oh... no, not at all.
I look forward to living with you.
Me too.
Eri.
Do you like herbal tea?
- Oh...
- What?
Um, well...
If it's okay with you, Eri.
Yes?
Would you come with me to
visit your father at the hospital?
What? M-Me?
Sorry for asking so suddenly. Um...
I wanted to tell him about our move.
But Wataru seems busy.
And if it's just me,
your father might feel awkward.
It would be a big help if you came along.
Of course, don't feel like you have to.
Hmm...
Hospital visit with Eri?
Did she actually talk to you?
Yeah. Was it too much to ask?
I don't think so.
Should we go on a day
you can come too?
No...
At this point, I don't know what
to talk about with Eri anymore.
Is that how it is
with brothers and sisters?
Well... with Eri...
I don't know, it might be difficult.
I see.
It's totally fine if you can't make it.
Okay, got it.
- I'm leaving then.
- Okay, have a good day.
- See you later.
- Be careful.
Your father
seemed happy to see you, didn't he?
He was probably just surprised
since I never visited before.
I'm such an ungrateful daughter.
Being a hermit and all.
He was worried about you,
so he was extra happy, I think.
We had the same issue at my home.
"The same issue"?
My sister Kaede also
quit high school and
became a hermit herself for a while.
Oh... I didn't know that.
Yes, she did.
I see...
Um.
Can we stop by the supermarket
on our way back?
Sure.
This will keep in the fridge
for about three days.
Really? I didn't know that.
Oh...
What vegetables do you like?
Vegetables, hmm...
This time of year...
- I'd have to say chrysanthemum greens.
- Huh?
- Oh, welcome home!
- I'm home.
I'll go now...
- Thanks for today.
- Good night.
Good night.
- I'll start getting dinner ready.
- Thanks.
Did Eri make all of this?
Yes, isn't it amazing?
You two went to the hospital together?
Yes. Your father seemed to be doing well.
I see.
Hey.
If my mom asked you
to do something about Eri,
don't feel like you have to
force yourself.
I'm not forcing myself at all.
I've been wanting to talk with her.
I see.
Is it us who are forcing ourselves?
Welcome!
Oh, Morita.
Hello.
Huh? Are you sure
it's okay for you to be drinking?
It feels like forever.
My husband can finally handle Mai by himself,
so I can go out now.
Besides, today is...
Right?
Akari, would you consider
coming back to work at our salon?
What?
So everything's working out well...
Here's your order.
Enjoy.
...so what do you think?
That's way too sudden.
I know about it, you know.
That you two used to have
a complicated relationship.
What? Wait, hold on...
But that's resolved now, right?
Yukako is married now.
Sigh... You really never know
when to shut up.
Hey, do you remember our customer Kijima?
Oh yeah.
He still comes in occasionally,
and he says, "If Hirayama comes back,
I'll become a regular again."
You're skilled, and it's such a waste.
When you put it like that,
I'm flattered, but...
...that's not what I meant!
It's not right to try to headhunt someone
at their current workplace.
Oh, I'm sorry.
But if you're interested,
please think about it.
Excuse me.
Oh, yes.
I'll be right there.
- Think it'll work?
- I think so.
Is this a turning point?
This bar where I met my new love.
Thanks to this, I feel like I've resolved
the awkwardness with my ex.
Gin and tonic, please.
Yes, coming right up.
Let me take your plate.
Thank you.
Hirayama!
Please.
Okay.
But...
this new love is going nowhere.
Thanks for your hard work today.
She'll never leave her husband anyway.
I'll never be her final choice.
I should move on, next, next.
Find a woman with
no boyfriend or girlfriend.
Or maybe I don't even need
to cling to relationships anymore.
Okubo Ayano
Completely cutting ties—
delete? reject?
Which is it?
Hello?
Whoa... um...
Hello, Akari? Are you okay?
I'm fine. Sorry about that.
I just wanted to hear your voice.
I'm happy
to hear your voice too.
Good night.
Man, I really want to take a bath.
Right?
Excuse me.
Oh my.
I hope this goes well.
What's going on?
Hey.
Um...
- Excuse us. Goodbye!
- G-Goodbye!
I'm leaving now.
It didn't seem like bullying or a fight...
I had something similar happen to me once.
19 Years Ago
Ayano, squeeze me too.
Squeeze?
Yeah, hug me tight.
You mean a hug?
With both arms, like this.
Like this?
Yes.
And then what should I do...
Just stay like this.
Huh?
Nao?
I just want to be held like this.
Hey,
let's go on a Christmas date.
You don't have a boyfriend, right?
No, I don't, but...
Wear your long black coat.
Ayano!
Nao.
See? You look so cool.
Tall with short hair,
it suits you perfectly.
Squeeze me.
A-Again? We're outside.
What do you mean, "again"?
It's fine.
Everyone's doing it, so we won't stand out.
Ayano, is there someone you like?
Not really right now...
I wish you were a boy.
After that day,
I grew my hair out until graduation.
It's great that everyone could make it.
Right?
When was the last time we all got together?
- When was it?
- Wasn't it at your wedding?
Huh?
Wasn't it at Kiyo's?
- When was Kiyo?
- Kiyo was three years ago.
- It's been three years already?
- Three years, huh.
- Nao!
- Nao's here!
Nao, congratulations on your marriage!
- You haven't changed at all.
- Not one bit.
- It's been forever.
- Seriously.
Congratulations!
Congrats!
Thank you.
There we go...
Did everyone order already?
- Yeah, we ordered.
- Really?
Sorry, I got pregnant
at my age before marrying.
What?
- Seriously?
- No way!
That's news to me.
Oh, I thought I'd just tell
everyone today.
That's so like you, Nao,
but still...
Sorry,
I'm always so impulsive.
Excuse me, here are your
grilled vegetables and steak.
Thank you.
- This looks delicious.
- Wow, that looks amazing.
That was a surprise.
Take it easy.
I'm totally fine.
What about you?
No kids yet?
Oh... yeah,
we're still having trouble conceiving.
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
How's your morning sickness?
I'm fine.
Hey, when was the last time
we saw each other?
It's been three years.
Really? That long? Wow...
- You haven't changed a bit, Nao.
- Not at all.
Who? Me? What?
Everyone!
Thank you all for your hard work this year.
Thank you!
Eat and drink as much
as you want today!
Here's a hand warmer.
Thanks.
I'm really sorry about earlier.
That was so insensitive of me.
Don't worry about it at all.
I'm hopeless,
always being so thoughtless.
You're not thoughtless at all, Nao.
- Get in.
- Thanks.
- See you.
- Yeah, thanks. Bye.
Because Nao noticed
I was rejecting her,
that's why a distance grew between us
from that day on...
I wish you were a boy.
I was hurt back then.
Me being a girl, as a girl...
I wanted to squeeze Nao.
Nao was my first love.
Even though I know how painful it feels,
I buried my feelings for Nao.
And fell for Akari
without any real commitment.
I'm the insensitive one.
Akari
Okubo Ayano
- Um, boss?
- Yes?
Um...
I'd like to discuss next year with you.
Don't tell me you want to quit...
right?
Oh...
I'm sorry, Akari...
I want to see you...