[My Heroic Husband]
[Episode 25]
My Lord. My Lord.
You see… I've brought my daughter here.
Is it possible for us to not hand in 10,000 taels of silver each month?
That's easy. It's not a big deal.
My Lord. My Lord. We run a cloth business.
We can help to make some bedding and clothing for you.
Could you please arrange some business for us?
No worries.
If she serves our Lord well tonight,
you will get anything you want.
Thank you, My Lord. Thank you.
Father, let's go.
Father, how can we get in?
It's midnight. I'm afraid they're all asleep.
We should make do with sleeping here for a night.
We can think about how to get in tomorrow.
If we disturb them, we would be killed.
Okay. I'll listen to you. I'll listen to you.
Let's go.
Let's sleep here.
What are you doing here?
We're doing nothing! Nothing! We're leaving!
Stop. Sorry to disturb you. Sorry!
[War horse]
Dig in! Aren't you hungry or sleepy?
You're lucky that I'm on duty.
If it was anyone else, he wouldn't have cared about you.
Thanks, my Lord. Thanks, my Lord.
Thank you so much.
But you two are so weird.
During the one month I'm in Lin'an, I have only seen people run out of the city.
You're the only ones who ran into the city.
What? Are you maddened with hunger so you risk your lives?
We-We wouldn't have come here
- if we hadn't wanted to find our lost relatives.
- Yeah, yeah.
Who are you looking for?
My cousin named Su Tan'er.
And my nephew-in-law, who's named Ning Yi.
Ning Yi?
He is our Counselor in Badao Camp.
Counselor? Not possible. They must share the same name.
He can't be the Counselor.
Right. He'd be humiliated if he has relatives like you.
Yeah, yeah.
My Lord. We may see that we are poor and shabby now.
But that's all because of this long trip.
Yeah. Our family is very rich in Jiangning.
You are merchants?
That's bad news.
A few days ago, all merchants were killed.
I'm afraid your nephew-in-law is already dead.
He was killed?
He just passed away like that?
What about our property?
Xi Gua.
What's the matter?
Aunt, there is one thing I don't understand.
I want to ask your opinion.
You always like to compare with Bao Wen Han.
My brother has been used to it.
However, the whole grain price matter can help us build prestige and win the people's support.
He won't blame you.
It's not about this.
It's about one of my friends. He wanted to buy me a dinner.
A dinner?
My sister-in-law asked you to dine out with Dou Jing Zhi again?
I told her that nothing forcibly done is going to be agreeable.
I'm going to talk to her. If you don't want to go, then don't.
It's not like that.
It's not Dou Jing Zhi.
Then, do you want to go?
Yes.
Do you have a crush on him?
Do you mean that I have a crush on him just because I want to dine out with him?
Not necessarily.
But this is the first time for you to dine out with a man alone.
You should experience something like that.
I'll help you dress up. Let's go.
[Restaurant]
Come on, everyone. Cheers.
Come on.
Xi Gua, what are you doing? Come on. Cheers.
Wait.
You're just meeting me. Why did you do your hair?
Come on. Come on. Cheers.
Well. You all did great job on the grain price.
- Let's get drunk today!
- Thanks, commander.
Speaking of the grain price, without Counselor Ning
we wouldn't have known how to teach Bao Wenhan a lesson.
- I'm flattered.
- There were a lot of misunderstandings between us.
But starting from today, you and I will be good friends.
All right! Fan. Fan, just forget it.
There were some incidents before. Sorry to have offended you.
- Bottoms up!
Come on.
[Restaurant Dong Li]
Father, look.
I don't have to.
It's the smell of home.
Father, I'm dying of hunger.
Shall we go inside and beg for some food?
What are you doing?
- Buddy, can you give us some food?
- We're starving.
- You came to the wrong place.
- No. Don't you…
Buddy, listen to me.
- Leave now!
- It's not like that.
Now, leave!
Leave! Leave!
No violence.
No violence. You can't hit us. Are you blind?
Just two beggars. Leave it.
Buddy, watch your language. Still not leaving?
You can't hit us. You can't hit us. Are you blind?
They're really beggars.
Yeah, it's okay. Don't mind it. It's okay.
Right, I think so. People in Lin'an are not so annoying like them.
Come on.
Come, Father. Let's take a break.
Yeah, okay.
Father, why can't he just be nice?
Why did he hit us?
He's such a snob.
It's a huge waste
to discard a big white steamed bun.
We've experienced
so many ups and downs in just a few days.
Did you see the assassin? It seems that she has entered the city.
Chase her!
We should blame the one who stole our carriage.
She seems to be there. Let's go.
Well, we lost all our money and direction because of her.
If we meet her again, we have to catch her.
And then…
- Chase her!
- Hurry!
- Father, am I having an illusion?
- What illusion?
That's our carriage.
The assassin is on the carriage. Chase her!
Hurry!
Father, she isn't here.
Over there, Father. There.
Let's go.
Easy, Father.
We won't catch up if we walk slowly.
You two, go there with me, the rest keep searching!
Yes!
Father. Father.
Our carriage.
It's ours.
Hurry up. Hurry.
It's our carriage!
Come and take a look. Are our belongings still there?
Are they there?
The tael is still here. All of it.
Let's go. Hurry up. Hurry.
Let's go. Father. Come on.
It's here. The carriage is here.
No. Heroes, there's a misunderstanding.
Do you want money or my body?
The ones on the carriage are the assassins.
Catch them!
Hero, please listen to me.
Hurry. Let's go.
- One last shot.
- Cheers. Come on!
Thanks for your promotion.
I'll be your backup!
- You have me!
- Fan.
- Coming!
- Come! Drink!
- Cheers!
- Drink.
I can't.
I'm drunk.
Fan, good liquor should be drunk on the good time.
He is getting older, while his tolerance is getting lower.
I want to ask you.
Why would you suddenly help me?
You still care about the citizens in Lin'an.
So, I helped you.
Xi Gua!
- Xi Gua.
- Aunt?
Counselor Ning is here, too.
I've looked for you in the camp for a while.
I just know you came here after I asked someone.
You didn't like the one I introduced to you last time.
So, I've found a better one for you.
This is the best soldier in Fang Qiong's team.
Enough, Aunt.
I haven't avenged my father.
I won't marry anyone.
You're being silly.
Who's going to marry?
Madam.
Xi Gua doesn't like this kind of person!
What the heck is he doing here?
Don't make her do this anymore.
He's drunk! Let's go.
Watch the stairs. Slowly. Slowly.
Xi Gua.
Come on, have a seat. Take a rest now.
Yeah, you should drink.
The more liquor you drink, the younger you'll become.
You'll find nobody malicious after drinking it.
Your worries will be all gone after you finish your wine.
I, Chen Fan,
have traveled all over the world and lead an unrestrained life.
There are countless girls who have crushes on me.
Why should I have to
put all my eggs in one basket?
You're right.
No more words.
Brother Ning, I've been taking
the medicine you gave me.
Have I successfully avoided my doomed love?
Almost.
Because it's your destiny to fall in love with someone.
If you want to change your destiny,
you have to go through another five courses.
But if I take of this medicine often,
I will get weak limbs in the morning.
This is… too troublesome for me.
You don't understand.
Good medicine usually takes slow effects,
because it never hurts your health.
Come on, I will feed you the medicine for today.
Take it with the wine.
It will be more effective.
It's said that the more knockout powder with liquor,
the sooner you become richer.
It not only helps change your marriage,
but it also removed all of your worries.
Miss Xi Gua, it's the first time we met.
I'm Yang Da Lang.
Nice to meet you.
Miss Xi Gua?
Sorry.
I'm not the miss.
Brother Ning.
How did you get out?
We pretended we were drunk and walked out one by one
saying we'd like to use the toilet.
Commander Liu is busy with her blind date.
She doesn't have the time to watch us.
What about the other two?
Over there.
- Let's go. Here.
Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go.
Chen Fan is asleep.
Let's go now.
Brother Ning, you are so garish.
Everyone knows you. How can you get out the city?
Yeah. You might get us into trouble.
- What should I do then?
- It's okay, Brother Ning.
I will help you change your look.
You're even capable of that?
Let's go.
Aunt, I've got a lot to do in the camp. I have to go now.
Xi Gua, sit down!
Please don't mind it, Young Master Yang.
Xi Gua is really short-tempered,
but her character is quite good.
Girls always should be reserved, you know.
So, I hope you can forgive her.
Sure, sure. Miss Xi Gua.
Stop!
Don't call me like that.
My name is Liu Da Biao.
Miss Da Biao, it's an honor to meet you. I–
Aunt, I'm really busy with the affairs in camp.
I have got to go.
Where is my counselor?
Counselor Ning. Counselor Ning!
Xi Gua!
You told me that you like brave, battle-wise, plump and sturdy…
and tall men!
I'd searched several camps before I found him.
How can you change your mind so suddenly?
When did I say I like such guys?
That's what I hate the most!
Your Counsellor Ning told me.
Three days ago, he came to me and
asked me to bring him to meet you at noon.
He said it's to celebrate the grain battle.
So that we can have two happy events come at the same time.
Didn't you get dressed up for this occasion?
What nonsense was he…
Hey! Liu Xi Gua, where are you going?
Chen Fan. Where is Ning Yi?
Chen Fan.
Where is Ning Yi?
He… He… was here just now.
Fine. Fine.
You paid lip service to me.
Actually you still want to escape.
Stop! Stop the cart!
Get out! Go back!
The gate is closing.
No one's here. Let's go.
What are you doing?
Feng Yuan, is this the disguise you put on me?
Why am I feeling I'm garisher now?
Brother Ning, that's all we got.
Besides, I only knew this one hairstyle.
You should've told me earlier. You… Let's go.
Great.
As long as we can escape, we won't need to cook soup, massage
and serve those bandits!
Stop the cart! Get out! Go Back!
If we get caught, it won't be as easy as cooking soup.
We would be torn in to pieces and made into steamed meat buns.
Shut up!
You two! Close the gates!
- Yes.
Hurry up!
The gate is closing. Let's go.
Let's go. What are you looking at? Let's go!
Isn't that the maid of your wife?
Haven't you sent them out of the city?
Why is she still here?
- You guys go first.
- Brother Ning. Brother Ning.
We can't just run out and leave Ning alone.
Maybe… Maybe we could.
You are a friend who sells friends! Traitor!
- I won't leave Brother Ning alone.
- Fine.
A friendship recognized by a scholar shall last forever.
We should hold on to the last.
But, you…
Let's go. Let's go.
Xiao Chan!
It's me.
Young Master.
Xiao Chan, why are you still here in Lin'an?
Where is Tan'er?
Young Master, why did it take you so long?
Why did it take you so long?
Young Lady... Young Lady...
I lost her.
Young Master,
I haven't found her. Did you find her?
Get up. Get up!
- Old Geng.
-Young Master, I lost my Lady.
It's not your fault.
Let's find her back together.
I lost my Lady.
I lost her!
I'm going go back and find him.
We managed to get off the boat,
All we saw were corpses.
She was so scared.
But luckily, we didn't find yours.
My Lady, Young Master is not here.
I didn't find him, either.
Not here?
Great.
Great! Great!
My Lady, let's go find him somewhere else.
Okay. Okay.
Let's go, My Lady.
Since then, we have been living in this house.
We wanted to find you and go back to Jiangning together.
My Lady, it's remote and safe here. Let's stay here for now.
We will go back to Jiangning together after we find Young Master.
She went to the street every day to inquire about your information.
But it was gain-less.
Miss, excuse me. Have you seen the person in the portrait?
No.
Hello. Excuse me. Have you seen the person in the portrait?
Have you seen the person in the portrait?
No.
What should we do?
- Where is he?
- Still no clues?
- Let's go ahead.
- Let's go.
Misses, excuse me. Have you seen the person in the portrait?
No.
Have you seen the person in the portrait?
Let's go.
Excuse me. Have you seen the person in the portrait?
No.
Hello, have you seen the person in the portrait?
Let's go. Let's go.
What-What's happening ahead?
Let's go take a look.
- Let's go.
- On that day, My Lady and I were inquiring about you.
But suddenly we saw bandits and you were together.
My Lady, that guy looks like Young Master.
Hubby!
My Lady, you can't go there like this.
There are bandits in front. If we just go there like this, we will be in danger.
He is leaving if we don't.
My Lady.
Let's go.
- Let's go, my Lady.
My Lady, if that guy is Young Master, then he is pretending to be loyal to them.
Given his moral quality, he won't betray us.
I trust him.
But if he is in the bandits' team,
how can we find him then?
So we started to collect information about bandits' camp
in order to make sure if it was you.
Young Master. Ning Yi.
- Ning Yi.
- My Lady!
- Young Master!
- Ning Yi.
- Make room. Make room.
- Young Master!
- Ning Yi! Ning Yi!
Lady didn't catch up with you when you went out of the city gate.
She was quite depressed.
Later, we haven't been able to find you when we looked for you on the street.
Until one day…
My Lady, I've seen him.
- Where is he?
- He's selling grain on the street.
My Lady, he's over there.
I never expected she would be kidnapped.
If I had thought of it, I would have gone to you and stopped her.
I would have prevented her from danger.
I never found out she was so close to me.
Brother Ning, don't worry. It hasn't been long since she disappeared. I'm sure we can get her back.
Nothing is difficult as long as we work hard.
Given your intelligence, there must be a way.
Old Geng, do you still remember what the abductors look like?
Not really.
But when I fought with him, I cut his right arm with a dagger.
His wound wouldn't have been healed in such a short period.
Then, they are not common people
since they could even fight against you.
They must be from the Badao Camp.
Brother Ning, we left with you.
We should go back together.
It was not easy for you to escape. No need.
Many hands make light work. We will help you get your wife back.
In all great stories, there is always the strong bond of friendship.
Young Master!
Young Master, please take me with you.
I lost my Lady. I want to find her back with you.
Let's go.
[Wu's Capital]
I really don't understand why you like this porridge made of stinky preserved eggs.
Don't be fooled by its appearance.
It adds a special favor to some dishes.
I don't like it. Please just give me some white porridge next time.
It's dark and stinky to eat.
It's not because you don't like it.
It's because you can't eat anything now.
I'm not like you.
Mo Ying failed to assassinate Fang Tian Lei.
The situation in Lin'an City is complicated.
I'm not in the mood for porridge!
If so,
if I tell you a good news,
can you eat a bowl of porridge with me?
Good news? What good news?
Qingde County near Lin'an reported a message.
Someone has collected 500 dans of grain
from several counties in one night and delivered it into Lin'an.
There are still people transporting food into the city?
They must be from the bandits.
No way.
If they were bandits, they would have been caught by the local government.
The Magistrate in Qingde County said
that the guy leading a group of rabble
went to the local government with my knife,
claiming to be Ning Li Heng.
The matrilocal husband in Jiangning?
Don't you think this is a favor from the heavens?
Just him alone?
Is he really that capable?
One stinky preserved egg
can also bring a huge difference to a bowl of white porridge.
Go on.
The army led by General Dong should have arrived at Lin'an now.
Yeah.
If we can seize the opportunity to
help General Dong win the first battle,
then they can go north right away.
I hope everything is as you wish.
Did you find him?
Commander, so far we have no further information.
The men who guarded the gate said
they are sure that they have not left the city.
So, they must still be in Lin'an.
- Keep searching!
- Yes.
You were so drunk yesterday.
I get drunk easily.
Seriously, I haven't seen anyone lamer than you!
Indeed.
Do you still remember how you came back?
Your Ladyship.
Commander.
You got up so early.
Were you in the camp all the time?
Yeah.
We drank too much yesterday.
So we went back after we were done.
As you can see here, we're drinking tea to sober us up.
Where is Chen Fan?
He's sobering up, too.
Go tell Chen Fan that he can stop searching.
Yes.
What's wrong, Commander?
What are you looking for? We can help you with it.
It's my business.
You don't need to know it!
Yeah, sure.
Well, then, we'll continue.
You want to join us?
No, thanks. You guys continue.
Okay.
Come on.
Have a seat.
Counselor Ning.
Commander asked me to come here to deal with something. Open the gate.
Yes.
[Lin'an Jail]
What do you want me to do, Counselor Ning?
Nothing. Commander asked me to deal with something here. Leave me alone.
Yes.
Are you looking for someone?
You can tell me who you want. I can help you with it.
No need. You can go back now.
Is there any other dungeon here?
This is the only one in Badao Camp.
That is to say,
she was kidnaped by some other camp.
Let's go to the drill ground.
Father.
I think I heard Ning Yi's voice just now.
Shut up.
I can hear his voice every day.
It's all illusion.
Nobody's there.
[Fang Manor]
Holy Master.
This is all the money we've collected since we came to city.
According to the old rule, we have exchanged it into gold.
That's 50,000 taels of gold for you.
Please accept it.
Thank you, Brother Bao.
It's my pleasure.
That's what I should do.
Commander Bao,
there are many rich merchants in Lin'an.
Each house should at least pay 50,000 taels of silver.
Why is there only this little after it's exchanged into gold?
What do you mean, Madam?
We've worked so hard on it.
We tortured merchants cruelly and dug deep.
And that's all we could find.
I had no other way.
Again, I was planning to clean out the rich
and cash in on the poor by selling the grain.
But I didn't expect that my plan would end up in vain
all because of Badao Camp.
If you think this is too little, you can't blame it on me.
All right.
I see.
You may leave, Brother Bao.
Yes, Holy Master.
Holy Master, he's getting more and more ignorant.
Not his fault?
I'm afraid this is not even a drop in the bucket.
No worries, Madam.
I know what to do with him.
Buddies, roll up the sleeves of your right arm.
Hurry up!
Hurry!
Come on.
Brother Ning, you're here.
Xi Gua told me about it. It was a misunderstanding yesterday.
Don't mind it.
It's okay. I won't.
What are you doing?
- Looking for someone.
- Who?
To be honest with you,
my wife was kidnapped by someone.
Are you married?
No wonder you know so much about girls.
Wait.
Your wife was kidnapped?
To tell you the truth,
I doubt the people who kidnapped my wife are here.
What?! How horrible!
Listen!
You have to cooperate with the Counselor!
If I know who kidnapped my brother's wife,
I will not forgive him!
Yes!
Brother Ning,
seldom have the people in Badao kidnapped any married woman.
I wonder if your wife is a beautiful woman.
Yes.
If your wife is beautiful and was hanging out,
it's very likely Bao Wen Han's kidnapped her.
You know him. He is such a lecher.
When we just came here, he assigned tasks to his men every day
just to kidnap several women on the street.
I'm afraid your wife is…
♫ When did the bright moon begin to appear?
Raise a glass of wine to the sky to ask ♫
♫ I don't know what year is the heavenly palace ♫
♫ I wish to return to the heavens on the wind;
But I'm afraid of the beautiful jade moon palace ♫
♫ It'll be too lonely at the top for me ♫
♫ Dancing lightly and enjoying the clear shadows
under the moon is like living in the mortal world ♫
♫ The moonlight spills over the bright red pavilion
through gauze-draped windows ♫
♫ Soft to shed her light upon the sleepless bed ♫
♫ The moon should not have any regrets
but why is it full when lovers are parting? ♫
♫ People have sorrow and joy, they separate or meet again.
And the moon has the transition of cloudy and clear ♫
♫  There has not been anything perfect since the olden days ♫
♫ So let us wish that people live as long as they can! ♫
♫ They will share the beauty of the moon
from thousands of miles away ♫
♫ People have sorrow and joy, they separate or meet again.
And the moon has the transition of cloudy and clear ♫
♫  There has not been anything perfect since the olden days ♫
♫ So let us wish that people live as long as they can! ♫
♫ They will share the beauty of the moon
from thousands of miles away ♫
♫ People have sorrow and joy, they separate or meet again.
And the moon has the transition of cloudy and clear ♫
♫  There has not been anything perfect since the olden days ♫
♫ So let us wish that people live as long as they can! ♫
♫ They will share the beauty of the moon
from thousands of miles away ♫
♫ People have sorrow and joy, they separate or meet again.
And the moon has the transition of cloudy and clear ♫
♫  There has not been anything perfect since the olden days ♫
♫ So let us wish that people live as long as they can! ♫
♫ They will share the beauty of the moon
from thousands of miles away ♫