[My Heroic Husband]
[Episode 33]
Ning Yi.
Get out!
Holy Master,
I'm afraid we're losing the fortress of Xuanwei Camp.
East Gate and West Gate have both been occupied by their armies.
Master,
North Gate was lost.
Dong Dao Fu and his vice generals have already entered the city.
Now that they want to die with us, why don't we allow them to?
Gather all our people at the powder magazine.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Go!
Master,
go find Xi Gua.
Send her out of the city at all costs.
Master, hurry up and go!
Yes.
Ya!
[Badao Camp]
How's the situation out there?
Dong Dao Fu's army has entered the city.
Holy Master has sent a signal to gather all the people at the powder magazine.
How could they attack at this time? All right.
Go gather our people!
Yes!
Xi Gua, the Holy Master ordered you to go to the powder magazine,
because he wants a cluster suicide.
We're about to lose Lin'an. Don't seek your doom.
I have to go, too!
I have to go save the Holy Master.
Hurry! Hurry! Open the door!
Get all the gunpowder out!
Let's confront them!
What... What... Why are there so many holes in the roof?
Holy Master.
All the drains are blocked.
Brother.
This gunpowder is useless now.
Fang Tian Lei!
Leader, we've gathered all the people.
We're ready to go now.
Okay, follow me.
Let's go find them in the powder magazine.
You can't go!
A'Sha, you protect Counselor Ning.
He is not good at fighting. Keep him safe.
No matter what happens, find a way to get him out of the city.
Yes.
Fang Tian Lei,
are you content with this gift I prepared for you?
Not bad.
I was looking for a good fight with you.
Yet you came without invitation.
Xi Gua!
How's the Holy Master?
Holy Master has ordered all people of the Badao Camp
to send Liu Xi Gua out of the city without delay.
Yes.
I won't leave.
I'm going to the gunpowder magazine to save Holy Master.
No.
Dong Dao Fu's army will come here soon. I can't let anything happen to you.
Let go of me!
- Let go of me!
- Xi Gua!
That's all the manpower in Lin'an.
Holy Master wants me to protect you.
I have to send you out.
He is my uncle.
I have to save him.
Liu Xi Gua!
Take her away.
You go and join Xi Gua.
No. We'll leave together.
I'll be worried if Chen Fan protects her by himself.
You're going to protect Xi Gua even if you have to sacrifice yourself. Do you hear me?
- Zheng Biao!
- Yes!
Make your way out with Fang Qiong.
Yes.
Go!
Fang Qiong, go!
Wang Jin.
Holy Master, hurry up and go!
Wang Jin!
Dong Dao Fu! I will kill you!
Dong Dao Fu!
I will kill you!
Bring the traitor Fang Tian Lei
back to Wudu for trial.
Yes!
[South Gate]
Stop!
Stay put.
Who are in the carriage?
Let them pass.
This black powder can't be used after it's soaked in water.
These and those... are all soaked in water.
What are we supposed to do?
Yes. There was heavy rain.
Fang Tian Lei has no gunpowder to use.
But we don't, either.
Yes.
Lady Lou, it's safe outside temporarily. You'd better leave now.
It's safe outside. Let's get out of here.
Let's go now! Go.
Leave!
[Suburb of Lin'an]
Don't be afraid. I will not kill you.
We'll just use your place for now.
Take them away after they're tied up.
Yes.
- You two go up there to look out.
- Is Madame settled in?
Yes.
After the wedding ceremony, Holy Master asked us to escort Madame
and leave the city in disguise through the South Gate.
I have arranged for her to live in a cottage in the far outskirts of Lin'an.
Some guards were left to serve her.
No one will find out her identity. Don't worry.
So it seems Master has long expected Dong Dao Fu will attack the city.
But since it was already expected,
why does it only take some rain,
just a night's rain, to defeat us?
And why did the guards at the South Gate
let us pass so easily?
Lin'an has a lot of rainfall.
Here it comes again.
Yes.
This rain comes too fast.
I have to help him to win the battle in Lin'an.
What if you can't win?
No way.
It can't be him.
No.
Xi Gua, what's wrong? Don't scare me.
Are you worried about the Holy Master?
You can remove your worries.
Madame has already settled down.
Holy Master...
He will come back safely, too.
Why...
did we lose?
Why?
So, you work for the Secret Investigation Department?
Am I right?
Yes.
Do you know how my father died?
After this battle is finished,
don't go to save the Holy Master,
no matter what.
These are all the people you have now.
Don't lose the whole Badao Camp.
From the moment you came to Badao Camp,
you've never said anything true.
You lied to me.
Go for ten miles to the east,
you'll see the camp of your enemy.
There's some food behind the camp.
If you steal some,
you won't starve.
Come back!
You address me as "Your Ladyship."
You said I could work for the people.
You said you recognized what I did.
You said you genuinely wanted to help me.
I believed you
because you did a lot of thinking and said so much to me.
But is all this fake?
Lin'an cannot go on like this anymore!
The situation in the North is tense.
If they lose this battle in Lin'an, the Wu Dynasty will be done for.
None of my business!
And it has nothing to do with Badao Camp.
It's none of my business, either!
I admit it.
Since I came to the Badao Camp,
all that I said was fake.
I did everything for you
to achieve my own purpose.
These things are true.
But my friendship with you
and your buddies
is also true.
In the long history,
there are too many people who rose in revolt like you.
I don't want to see you become
one of those cold figures in the history books.
But...
But why you?
Ning Yi,
why did you lie to me?
Why do you work for the Secret Investigation Department?
My father...
My father was killed by the people from the Secret Investigation Department.
I shall take revenge!
I will avenge his death!
Ning Yi,
I will not forgive you!
Liu Xi Gua.
Get out!
I will not forgive you.
From the moment you come to Badao Camp, you won't have any say.
I want you to be my Army Advisor, so you'll have to be.
I heard you wanted to flee.
What's wrong?
Do you feel wronged being my army advisor?
As long as you do what you promised, I'll give you the whole Badao Camp,
let alone a group of my people.
If you want to call me Xi Gua,
I don't mind it, either.
As long as you are not my enemy, I will be fine with anything.
A'Sha, you protect the army advisor.
He is not good at fighting. Keep him safe.
No matter what happens, you have to send him out of the city.
Ning Yi,
don't let her down!
Can you do it?
He can, Aunt.
[Tomb of Bao Wen Han]
[Tomb of Lou Shu Heng]
Lady Lou, the cart is overloaded.
We'd better leave this box of books here.
This is the map drawn by Leader Bao.
It shows where the outlaws in the Wu Dynasty are hiding.
Keep it.
Yes.
Come and load the cart.
[Lin'an]
Dong Dao Fu has eliminated all eight camps of bandits.
Holy Master Fang Tian Lei was taken alive.
Lin'an has become peaceful again.
[Fang]
[Wu]
Great, great!
Move! Move! Make way!
Serves you right!
This is what you deserve.
Finally! Relief!
Take your medicine.
You're welcome.
Heat this medicine with three bowls of water and condense it into one bowl.
Kneel down!
General,
the bandits around the city have all been eliminated or captured.
The leader of the bandits, Fang Tian Lei, has been captured.
He has been put in prison.
After I check all the gunpowder and weapons, we're ready to return to the capital.
Good.
What about the gunpowder?
Thanks to the rainproof lining, the black powder, and the gunfire
in the grain hopper have been preserved intact.
That's great!
[Badao Camp]
[Wude Camp]
Fathe, we only became the richest people here for one day.
How about you borrow 30 cash from Tan'er?
Let's use it to pay for the buns first.
I don't want to. It's embarrassing.
At that time, we even told him we were the Su family from Jiangning.
How humiliating it would be if people knew it!
Well, we can go together.
I can't tell you what to do now, can I?
General Dong, Lord Commander.
Don't mind the courtesy. Go back to your work.
Soldiers!
These guys are the ones who saved Lin'an. They're our heroes.
Please don't. Don't call us like that!
We'll feel embarrassed.
Yes, you flattered us.
Just call us warriors.
Warriors have always been praised since ancient times.
Now we should praise the courage of scholars.
Yes, it's a pity that we even missed Brother Ning's wedding.
Yes, yes, yes.
Go back to work, please.
General, come on and take a look! The plaque has been hung up.
Wude Camp.
Great.
Since the Wu Dynasty's Army came to Lin'an,
the security and order of Lin'an have basically been restored now.
Brother Ning, that is to say, your whole family is
living under the nose of the bandits, yet they are still safe and sound.
And you even came up with the idea to cover yourselves up,
deceive everybody, and help me take back the city.
Yes.
Now that I think about it, it's quite incredible!
When your army broke into the gates, I did have some concern.
Before this, Lady Lu said
you failed in the siege of the powder magazine.
Your identity was almost exposed.
I was kind of uncertain about today's attack.
But in the end, I still chose to believe the person entrusted by Old Qin.
General, come on.
Allow me to introduce you.
This is my wife, Su Tan'er.
Tan'er, this is General Dong.
Greetings to General Dong.
Miss Xiao Chan also contributed greatly to this battle.
Yes, of course.
You've seen these four heroes.
Like me, they are also matrilocal husbands.
Nephew-in-law.
I see.
Lady Lu is not only the elite of the Secret Investigation Department,
but also my martial arts teacher。
I feel sorry.
Without Lady Lu, I would have died many times.
Yes, yes, I am...
These are the people that
I should introduce you to.
That's pretty much all about it.
General Dong, your time is valuable.
Okay.
I've met all the heroes.
What I can't understand is you only have ten people in total.
How did you do it?
That's a long story.
We shall start from the very beginning of this mission.
It's empty.
Oh, no.
This is a trap.
Let's go.
We had planned everything that time, yet the gunpowder was gone.
After that, we presumed that after the assassination, Fang Tian Lei
had transferred all gunpowder and weapons.
Under the name of the Holy Master, now I order you two get married.
The wedding ceremony will be held on the day after tomorrow.
I killed a leader of the bandits, Bao Wen Han.
Accidentally, I was ordered to marry Liu Xi Gua.
At that time, there were only three days remaining
before Master Qin would come to take the city.
I'm well aware that Fang Tian Lei wouldn't trust me.
The marriage must be for something else.
So I could only go with his plan.
I asked my teacher to follow Fang Tian Lei
and Zheng Biao, the man in charge of the powder magazine.
We found that they hid the gunpowder in the granary.
How about it?
There was too much gunpowder.
It would be impossible for just the few of us
to transfer the gunpowder.
I then came up with a plan with my wife.
My dear. This is the grain hopper that the bandits used to store the gunpowder.
I want you to help me make some waterproof linings.
Make sure that the linings fit perfectly
with the inner wall of the grain hopper and each peck of gunpowder
so they will not go bad even if soaked in water.
That's all?
Yes.
So simple?
It's not simple, my dear.
It's critical. You have to be very careful with it.
Black powder will spoil when it touches water.
If the gunpowder becomes useless, it could affect
the safety of the civilians of the Wu Dynasty.
I know.
But it's still simple.
Shall we make a bet?
If a box of gunpowder is soaked in water,
I'll do all the cooking from now on.
I believe in you, my dear.
For the next few days, we have to work around the clock.
Now, I'll teach you how to make waterproof cloth.
This is the formula.
Pass it around.
The paint should be mixed evenly.
Check it thoroughly.
Use more paint.
Fang Tian Lei had invited all eight camps to my wedding.
He was luring me to send information out to you.
Because there would be a weak defense,
we could use this opportunity to attack the city.
But in fact,
that night was a good opportunity to deal with the powder magazine.
I asked them to take advantage of this ceremony,
and go to the granary with the waterproof linings when they changed shifts,
and pad every grain hopper with the lining.
Then we made some holes in the roof.
Slow down, Father.
Slow down.
Be careful, Father.
These kids are so rude.
They don't have any respect for the old.
Nor do they know how to love children.
My son,
you should recognize the reality.
You are too old to be called young.
You're not young anymore.
Father,
in your heart, I'll always be a child.
Well. It's so dangerous here.
Let's do it quickly.
You're right.
Here, Father, take this.
Come on.
Father, hold them tight.
Father.
By the way, Gao.
Brother Ning specifically instructed us not to
lay water-proof cloth in those boxes by the door.
No worries. I got it.
Father, take my hands. Grab my hands, Father.
When the big rain came, it looked like there was a flood.
Why are there so many holes in this roof?
Holy Master.
The drains are all blocked.
Fang Tian Lei thought all the gunpowder was soaked in water
and couldn't be used anymore.
Before they had time to check it carefully,
General Dong then attacked the granary.
He could only finish the fight against General Dong.
General Dong. We were not introduced by him.
I am Su Zhong Kan, the second master of the Su family.
This is my son, Wen Xing.
We're the ones who came up with this excellent plan.
Apart from that, we used to test the feasibility of this plan.
It always works. It's absolutely feasible.
Yeah, yeah.
How dare you say that.
You finally admitted it now.
It was all because of you.
My lady lost all the Cloud Gauze in the storage.
And it almost delayed the opening of the cloth store.
All thanks to the Young Master.
Xiao Chan, that's not fair.
Yeah. That was ages ago.
- Chan'er, you need… you need to let go of it.
- That's right.
Uncle and cousin used this to fool the enemy.
They've made amends for their fault.
Tan'er is quite right!
Yes, yes.
General, sorry you have to see this.
After that, Lady Lu asked me to attack the city when the rain fell.
At that time I was extremely puzzled.
Why could we only attack the city after the rain fell?
Now I finally understand it.
You were protecting the gunpowder magazine under the guise of holding a wedding ceremony.
Yes.
Only in that way would Fang Tian Lei know that he had lost all of his advantages.
Only then would they fight to the death against you.
The Wu Dynasty is lucky to have you as the commander of the Secret Investigation Department.
General, you flatter me.
Lady Lu, the captivity name-list
didn't mention anything about the adopted daughter of Fang Tian Lei.
Yes, her people in Badao Camp have been quite chivalrous and righteous,
and they were good to the people.
The Secret Investigation Division has offered amnesty and enlistment to them.
If they're really like what you said,
we can try to persuade her into working for the Secret Intelligence Division. That's great!
It's just she is the adopted daughter of Fang.
I'm afraid she will cause more trouble.
Don't worry, General Dong. I will deal with it.
[Prision of Lin'an]
Fang Tian Lei.
Dong Dao Fu, if you still want to get something out of my mouth,
I suggest you forget about it.
I am just doing my part as a comrade. I mean nothing else.
You'll be questioned by someone else.
Ning Yi, I will rip you apart!
You bastard! Answer my questions!
What did you do to Xi Gua? Where is she now?
Badao Camp is still safe.
They should be hiding somewhere in the mountains.
There is no need to worry.
I came here today to ask you a few questions.
What a coincidence! I also have a few for you.
Did someone tell you to attack Lin'an?
Yes.
Did you come here to prevent the army from heading north?
How did you know that there would be a downpour this morning?
Well,
I didn't actually.
Lin'an has a lot of rainfall. I was just waiting.
Waiting?
I was waiting for the rain.
The rain was the signal to attack Lin'an.
So, I'm doomed.
One last question,
Fang Tian Lei.
The person who ordered you to prevent the army from heading north,
who is it?
Dong Dao Fu also asked me this.
My answer is still the same.
If I don't tell you, what can you do to me?
Just leave, Ning Yi.
You will never get to know the answer to this question.
Waiting for the rain. Excellent!
[Wudu]
Urgent report from the front line.
Your Majesty. Urgent report from the front line.
- Read it now, quickly!
- Yes.
General Dong Dao Fu has taken Lin'an back.
The Secret Investigation Department cooperated from the inside with the people outside.
Commander Ning Li Heng carried out an excellent plan
to make Fang Tian Lei, the head of the bandits, fail to use the gunpowder.
They've not only kept the people of Lin'an safe but also won the time to take back the city.
On Sept. 19th, the fifth year of Jinghan's reign, Lin'an was recovered.
Fang Tian Lei, the head of the bandits, was captured alive.
Minister, there is something that's been troubling me.
I think if Fang Tian Lei comes to the capital, he will cause you trouble.
Do you want me to send someone to kill him instead?
No need.
Once Lin'an is taken,
Fang Tian Lei will become useless.
How much trouble can he cause?
Let him be. I have more important things to do.
Minister He,
His Majesty wants to see you.
His Majesty ordered Dong Dao Fu to lead 100,000 troops due south.
Lin'an had been recovered. The bandits had been eliminated.
Fang Tian Lei, the head of the bandits and his followers were all arrested.
They would be executed in a few days. This was the moment for celebration.
This is a dynasty with all the people of one mind.
Great. Excellent.
God bless! Great!
Now Bo Yong is in good health.
And Tan'er and Ning Yi will be back soon, too.
I... I'm going to the temple to offer prayers.
You should stay home. Maybe they'll be back in a minute.
That's right.
Well. Then I'll prepare some food and drinks that they like.
We'll give them a warm welcome.
Yeah, that's right.
Let's go.
Father, look.
This is our family's cloth store.
Look at you!
Look. The eighth branch of Zhu Restaurant.
In the blink of an eye, so many stores have been opened.
I really didn't expect that we would come back alive.
Well, I am really starting to miss my wife.
The days that we can argue and fight were so great.
Yet I didn't cherish them.
I wonder if my wife is in good health now.
We left here so long ago, yet we didn't even bring any gifts.
The husband's safe return is enough to comfort his wife.
Now that you came back safely, this could be the greatest gift to your wives.
Good for you, Shen Miao.
After this trip to Lin'an, your insights into love have grown.
People who've experienced life and death will change their opinions about earthly life.
What are you doing?
I think we are still dreaming.
Shut up! Close your mouth!
Elder Master. Elder Master.
Elder Master. Lady and Young Master have come back!
Excellent! Excellent!
Let's go!
[Su Manor]
Mother.
I've missed you so much!
I've looked forward to your return all this time. You're finally back!
- Was it a tiring journey?
- No!
- Did you get hurt on the way?
- Grandfather!
I'm great! We're okay. Don't worry about us.
Father!
Grandfather! Grandfather!
Father! Father!
♫ When did the bright moon begin to appear?
Raise a glass of wine to the sky to ask ♫
♫ I don't know what year is the heavenly palace ♫
♫ I wish to return to the heavens on the wind;
But I'm afraid of the beautiful jade moon palace ♫
♫ It'll be too lonely at the top for me ♫
♫ Dancing lightly and enjoying the clear shadows
under the moon is like living in the mortal world ♫
♫ The moonlight spills over the bright red pavilion
through gauze-draped windows ♫
♫ Soft to shed her light upon the sleepless bed ♫
♫ The moon should not have any regrets
but why is it full when lovers are parting? ♫
♫ People have sorrow and joy, they separate or meet again.
And the moon has the transition of cloudy and clear ♫
♫  There has not been anything perfect since the olden days ♫
♫ So let us wish that people live as long as they can! ♫
♫ They will share the beauty of the moon
from thousands of miles away ♫
♫ People have sorrow and joy, they separate or meet again.
And the moon has the transition of cloudy and clear ♫
♫  There has not been anything perfect since the olden days ♫
♫ So let us wish that people live as long as they can! ♫
♫ They will share the beauty of the moon
from thousands of miles away ♫
♫ People have sorrow and joy, they separate or meet again.
And the moon has the transition of cloudy and clear ♫
♫  There has not been anything perfect since the olden days ♫
♫ So let us wish that people live as long as they can! ♫
♫ They will share the beauty of the moon
from thousands of miles away ♫
♫ People have sorrow and joy, they separate or meet again.
And the moon has the transition of cloudy and clear ♫
♫  There has not been anything perfect since the olden days ♫
♫ So let us wish that people live as long as they can! ♫
♫ They will share the beauty of the moon
from thousands of miles away ♫