I just didn't think your excuse to break up could be this bullshit.
Me chewing loudly?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I told you to stop chewing. Why wouldn’t you?
Do you have a fucking problem with me?
I’ll wear my earphones if you want me to eat here.
Seriously?
I asked, who are you texting?
I started talking to this girl after I broke up with Ink.
Earphones are my 33th organ.
Not because I’m crazy about listening to music as a musician,
but because I’m used to controlling the things I’m about to hear.
Tee-Do!
Open the door!
Hey!
Tee-Do!
What would you like me to cook for you?
No one wants to hear what they don’t want to hear.
But sometimes it can’t be avoided.
My life is full of things I don’t want to hear.
Let’s try one more time.
Did you understand the lesson, N’Tee?
Let’s practice.
I’ve always believed that if someone is brave enough to tell you something, you should listen to them.
But what if what comes out of their mouth is not speaking voice?
Ouch! Tee!
Are you alright?
Why did you punch your friend, N’Tee?
That kind of voice calls for the devil inside me.
It makes my life, including my love life, harder.
Why don’t you eat candy instead?
Okay.
I’ve tried, but I’ve never been able to finish a movie hearing any kind of chewing sound.
I’m sorry.
Euang! Euang!
Hold on.
Why are you breathing so loudly?
Do you have asthma?
How did I do?
Alright, but there was too much saliva.
I don’t think so.
I could feature you when you play the cello.
Maybe you could change the genre.
No, no.
$%)$(%$%
Hey!
My new love is about to blossom.
Thanks for letting me borrow your cello bow.
Hey!
You’re welcome. Hehe.
Hehe?
New girl?
Does this one chew loudly?
Chomp chomp.
I don’t know.
I don’t dare ask her out.
The earphones that match my dating outfits are broken.
I’m scared I’ll flip out if I hear her chew.
We can help you dine with her without wearing your earphones
but you have to bring her here.
What if Watee finds out?
His birthday quota is up.
We can get everything done before he’s back.
Do we really want to do it?
I have nothing to do with this.
I’ll cook.
Today I’ll survive without this organ of mine.
Come to my house tomorrow.
I can’t see them.
You have to watch from here.
Move a little left.
Are you alright, Teedet?
I’m fine. No symptoms.
I thought this was going to be a simple meal.
My friends helped me prepare it.
Where are your friends?
Did you make the sauce yourself?
Yes. I made everything myself.
Looks yummy.
Smells so good.
Guys, this is Soundlab.
Hi.
What’s your name again? Chao Rap?
It’s Soundlab.
Oh, Soundlab.
Okay. Enjoy your dinner.
Shall we?
You shouldn’t have prepared all this for me.
I’m actually a mainstream girl. I can eat anything.
It’s no problem at all.
One of my friends is a good cook.
He makes the best beef mignon, soufflé,
ratatouille, etc.
I want you to try his food.
I’m scared to open it.
It must be too fancy for me.
Just try. You’ll love it.
Then I’ll open it now.
Congee?
I think it’s abalone or shark fin congee.
It’s minced pork.
Minced pork?
Yes. I wanted our first date to be simple.
Don’t look at me.
I knocked on his door but he didn’t answer.
Plus, I could only think of congee as something people won’t chew loudly.
You weren’t thinking of my light decorations.
Have you ever made this sound while eating congee?
I think she has more manners than that.
Did you just insult him?
It’s just a statement.
I forgot to tell you that I don’t eat meat.
Oh?
It’s okay. I can pick only what I eat.
Are you sure?
No worries at all.
I brought my own food.
What’s that?
Fried vegetables.
Shit!
Are they crispy?
Shit is happening.
Game over.
This is going to end in a mess.
RIP.
He’s going to flip out.
What do we do?
Stop chewing right now!
What’s wrong?
Why did you have to fry your vegetables?
Are you crazy?
I wanted to eat them fried and I didn’t fry them on your head!
You cause noise pollution.
They’re just crispy!
Stop eating!
P’Tee! P’Tee!
Yes?
Shall we eat?
Let’s.
I turned this on for the first time for him.
Bark, Jack.
So crispy.
Yeah.
You want some?
I like them wilted. Sorry.
Oh.
Bark quickly. Open your mouth.
Come on.
That must've felt good.
My ass is all wet.
No smell, right?
Come on, Jack!
Yummy?
It's good, right?
It's noisy.
Come again?
I didn't hear you.
It's noisy!
I heard you.
Yes, it's quite noisy.
Yes, it is.
You're okay?
Yeah.
Thanks to the sound of the blender, the barking and the farting from my friends.
They make me feel better than hearing the person in front of me chew fried vegetables.
Guys.
My blender stopped working.
May I use the bathroom?
Sure.
No, I'm fine.
You should eat.
You haven't eaten at all.
Alright.
I'll do that.
Please.
Hi. Do you guys want to join us?
No, thank you. We're here to give our friend support.
But we're just eating.
We're talking about that one.
Oh.
Do you think she suspects anything?
Have a seat.
Are you full?
Yeah.
Do you really have to mow the grass now?
What did you say?
It's my turn on the schedule.
Right.
We take turns doing it.
My father is visiting from another city
He brought us some fruits.
I didn't kick him out because he's your father.
See, Tee-Do? You managed to dine with her without your earphones.
Next time, you'll be able to do so much more.
Let me focus on surviving the meals first.
Thanks a lot, guys.
Dining with girls without my earphones - Check
You should invite her to our place again.
What do you mean?
Who are you inviting?
Oh,
I want to go to the Rear Palace.
Tee-Do goes there a lot.
I want him to take me.
I read on the internet
that there's an alley where cool guys wear jeans.
There is a famous fried pork place.
And I'll buy you sushi from Orathai's.
Price starts from 5 baht.
Super yummy.
We should resell it.
Tai Orathai. (Singer's name)
No, they're not the same person.
The area is close to a few temples.
Excuse me.
Hello, Dad.
This way, Dad. Come.
Thank god GPS led me to the right place. I almost got lost.
Hey.
My father is visiting from another city.
He brought us some fruits.
Dad, this is Watee. He's the owner of this house.
Watee.
Hello.
Is he the one who shares the same name as you, Tee-Lek?
My name is T-Rex, not Tee-Lek.
Where are you from?
Are you from Ratchaburi? I wonder if we're related.
I've lived here since I was born.
Ah.
What a beautiful house.
It's so nice and shady.
That tree must be 20 years old.
I like to plant that tree as well.
Right.
Is he alright?
He's fine.
He rarely talks but today he talked to you a lot.
Really?
Yeah.
Come in.
I'll wash these for you.
That’d be great.
Is he gone?
My dad?
He left already.
I didn't kick him out because he's your father.
But don't bring strangers into this house again.
My dad’s visiting from his hometown.
You wouldn’t let him come see me?
My house is neither a prison nor a hospital.
No visitors are allowed.
Hey.
Wasn't that too harsh?
His father is not a stranger.
Apart from the clattering noise from people’s mouth and the sound of chewing,
another kind of human sound I don't like is the sound of arguing.
T-Rex, Watee must really feel uncomfortable around strangers.
He respected you by not kicking your father out.
He just wanted to warn you about next time.
Watee, T-Rex thought by 'strangers' you mean friends, partners, and other acquaintances.
He didn't realize that includes family.
I'm sorry.
I won't bring him here again.
I hope that everything I said would prevent some arguments in the future.
P'Tee, do you want to go to the movies tomorrow?
Who's at the mall on the main road near our house?
Cinema 8, 5:00 pm show time. Come quickly.
Excuse me. What are you laughing about?
This is a horror film.
I always laugh when I'm scared.
He always does that.
Dude.
I smell something bad.
Do you?
It's butter.
I'm allergic to the smell of butter.
It's the popcorn.
Look, I got rashes all over.
What do we do?
Should we go to the hospital?
I'm not eating this anymore. I'm full.
Good for you. It can make you fat.
I almost died.
It's so hard for them to finally end up together.
What's love without obstacles? It would be too mainstream and not as fun.
But if Ethan wasn't a ghost, Laura might have fallen in love with him from the start.
Maybe Laura loves Ethan as a ghost.
Who knows?
Eww!
Ethan loves Laura.
Laura loves Ethan, too.
This is probably the first time in years that I remember the names of the protagonists from a movie I'm watching with a girl.
Watching a movie with a girl I like - Check
It's midnight. Happy Birthday.
Thank you.
Was I the first to wish you a happy birthday?
You're so mainstream, but it's okay. I like mainstream.
See you tomorrow. I'll pick you up.
Everything seems to be going well until the next morning comes.
We should stop talking.
No one's chewing next to him.
Why is he wearing headphones?
No idea.
Good weather today.
What's wrong?
Am I that scary?
No, except when you turn into a hulk and destroy a pot plant.
Oops.
I want to be normal like other people.
What's wrong with you?
Shit!
What do I do?
Hey, you.
What?
My mom told me not to talk to strangers.
I'll treat you to ice cream.
Okay.
Eat them next to my ear.
Be as loud as possible. I want people on the main road to hear you.
Fatty, who taught you to eat that loudly?
Eating two sticks isn’t going to help you lose fat.
Do you know you should eat some vegetables in every meal?
P'Tee.
Why the hell are you here so early?
What's wrong with you, P'Tee?
Why did you call my name?
You’re afraid I'll forget my own name?
My name is Teeee.
You're not going to stop?
Thank you so much.
I'm sorry. Did I scare you?
Clearly you did.
I can treat you to another one.
No, thank you.
I don't want it.
I actually think you're cute.
I was a chubby kid too.
You're adorably chubby.
Go home to your mom.
No!
Soundlab!
And she said in her status that
"Guys who are rude to children and girls are not gentlemen."
Can you choose what you're afraid of?
I don't want to be afraid of beautiful women either.
Doesn't everyone like them?
Yeah.
Honestly,
I just want to be able to eat like normal people.
I've always eaten alone.
It’s lonely.
I feel you.
Why didn't you tell me?
I used to think that if I loved someone enough, love would help me overcome my fear.
Maybe you don't love me enough.
What's wrong?
Why didn't you tell me?
I came to return the cello bow.
So I guess
this is why you made me eat congee the other day.
I'm sorry.
I used to think that if I loved someone enough,
love would help me overcome my fear.
I guess it can't help me.
Maybe you don't love me enough.
Let’s find out.
Hey!
I'm going to start now.
Okay.
1,
2,
Soundlab, wants the best for me.
Soundlab wants to help me.
Soundlab wants me to get rid of this sickness.
No one can help me!
Are you alright?
Yes.
Let's continue.
Keep chewing.
You're not alright.
No, I won't.
I can't let you be the only one trying to put up with the sound you hate for me.
I have to avoid making the sound you hate too.
How about I invent a recipe for non-crispy popcorns in my next lab class?
Softcorns?
But first, let's clear these up.
We don't want Watee to kill us when he gets back.
Soundlab.
Have you been waiting long?
Sorry.
Mmm...
It's okay.
Let's go eat some...
ice cream.
Ice cream?
Alright, we won't be making any sound.
Here.
This is what I dropped in the drain the other day.
Wow. It's a cello bow
with my name on it.
You won't have to borrow mine anymore.
How mainstream.
Of course.
There's more.
What else?
Here.
Happy Birthday.
These are our first movie tickets together.
And these are lifetime free coupons for air popcorns.
Cute.
Isn't it cool?
Yes.
I'm going to use one of these now.
Now?
Don't you want to wait until we're at the cinema?
I'd rather use it now.
Okay.
It's there already?
I'm perfectly fine.
Won't you share it with me?
You want some?
Sweet.
Yummy?
Do you feel like it's stuck in your throat?
Yeah. I ate too much popcorn. My throat is dry.
I prepared for that.
Oh.
Here.
It'll make you feel refreshed.
Don't worry. I have one for myself.
But P'Tee,
doesn't this require chewing?
Will you be alright?
Let's try it together.
Are you sure?
Let's do it.
I don't know if this love could help me overcome my fear.
But at least there's someone right in front of me who's willing to go on that journey with me.
Kissing my sweetheart - Check
Teedet! Teedet! Teedet! Teedet!
Shorty! Help me! Shorty!
Shorty, wake up! Shorty!
I saw a shadow. Shorty.
Are you dreaming?
Let’s go check outside if you don't believe me.
Directed by Nuttapong Mongkolsawas
Apples.
Crispy or soft?
Crispy, of course.
They're eating so much.
I'll be back late tonight.
My father is in town.
I have concerto rehearsal at uni.
I might sleep there tonight if I finish late.
No! I can't sleep alone!
Your fear of ghosts has become everyone's problem.
Get packing and leave this house.