=Culinary Vendetta=
=Episode 11=
Your wife thinks too highly of herself.
She never greets me properly each day.
I don't care about her noble background.
In the Chu Family, she only has one role.
She's my daughter-in-law.
Can you manage her properly?
Why should I manage her?
If I want to climb higher,
I still need to rely on
her father's influence.
Mother.
You shouldn't bother with her.
Just pretend she's not your daughter-in-law.
If you're truly feeling
lonely and bored,
I'll ask Father
to take a few more concubines.
They can play cards with you.
Then you won't feel so bored anymore.
What kind of nonsense are you saying?
To put it bluntly,
you're not strong enough.
Look at Chu Junyao next door.
He's brave and skilled in battle.
He's earned military merits.
Other than His Majesty,
he doesn't take anyone seriously.
Who does Chu Junyao think he is?
Starting today,
there will be no place for him
in this world.
What do you mean by that?
Impressive, truly impressive.
That Qin woman lost her husband,
and if she loses her son...
Let's see how arrogant she can still be.
(General Mansion)
Has the general returned?
Madam, he has not returned yet.
Qianqian.
- What?
- Mother-in-law.
This morning, Junyao went to North City
to arrest someone.
He still hasn't returned yet.
Don't worry about it.
His martial arts are unparalleled.
Even an army couldn't stand against him.
Besides, he's just gone to
capture someone.
From here to North City,
the journey is very far both ways.
It's bound to take some time.
I know that.
But I can't help
feeling uneasy.
Chuntao.
Yes.
Send someone to North City
to Mount Ban to find the general.
Alright.
Put your mind at ease.
As for Junyao, he is blessed.
You must believe he'll be fine.
Come on, have some tea.
Oh, sister-in-law,
I'm just looking for you.
Su Qianqian, you look so pale.
It's as if you've lost your husband.
Yang Cuihua!
Watch your mouth!
As an elder,
speak with more restraint.
Sister-in-law,
I was just worried out of concern.
You know how I am.
Don't take it to heart.
Where is Junyao?
I've missed him these past few days.
Junyao? He's doing quite well.
No need for your concern.
Sister-in-law,
you don't need to be so formal.
After all, he's my own nephew.
Now he's even become a general.
Tomorrow,
I'll go to the temple to get a Peace Amulet.
May it keep him safe and sound.
As a general,
it's inevitable for him to face fights.
If anything happens to him, at least
there will be something to hold onto, right?
You!
Aunt,
have some tea.
Aunt.
I'm so sorry, so sorry.
I didn't notice the step here.
Truly, I'm so sorry.
How careless can you be, Shaoqing?
Help Aunt rinse with cold water.
It might leave a scar.
Sister-in-law,
go ahead and laugh to your heart's content.
Your turn to cry will come soon enough.
I can't stop laughing!
Qianqian, you are amazing.
Here you go.
Well done!
(General Mansion)
My lady, it's freezing outside.
You should go inside first.
As soon as he returns, I'll inform you.
(Junyao, you must return safely.)
(You are my only support in this world.)
(Heavens, please bless us.)
(I hope both the general
and Zi Xuan return safely.)
(General Mansion)
Sister-in-law,
it's such a cold day.
Why are you standing out here alone?
You must be waiting for Junyao, right?
Seeing how deeply you two
care for each other
truly makes me envy you.
What's there to envy?
We are the ones destined to be together.
She
is just all alone.
Honey, she must be worried about Junyao.
You shouldn't make things
harder for her.
On the way back just now,
I saw so many homeless people
freezing to death,
with no one
to even collect their remains.
It was truly heartbreaking to see.
What if one of them was Junyao?
How much that would pain me!
Don't worry, honey.
If something
truly happens to him,
I will ensure his funeral
is grand and dignified.
Junyao will definitely be fine.
No need to make such cold remarks.
That would certainly be for the best.
Sister-in-law,
don't let this endless snowstorm
chill your heart.
The general is back.
(General Mansion)
I knew you would return.
With you here,
no matter how far away,
I will always come back to you.
I was so afraid of losing you.
Silly girl,
you will never lose me.
Zi Xuan.
He's unharmed.
Everything was planned so well,
but he still managed to escape.
Young Master,
Chu Junyao is unstoppable.
He killed many of our men.
He even took Constable Zhang away.
We truly couldn't defeat him.
Useless fools.
I told you we should've killed Zhang.
At the very least,
you shouldn't have used him
to lure Chu Junyao.
If we use a fake one,
how could it possibly fool Chu Junyao?
Now you understand
what it means to lose on both ends, right?
We have lost,
but they haven't won either.
What?
What do you mean?
You truly plan to burn bridges.
You're quite clever,
but also very foolish.
You rely on sheer luck.
As long as you stay in the capital,
how could you escape my notice?
Since I've fallen into your hands,
then I implore you,
for the sake of my service to you,
to grant me a swift end.
I was considering giving you a swift end.
But you still have some use left.
Does that mean
I won't have to die?
Guards!
Take out his eyes.
Pierce his ears.
Cut out his tongue.
Break all ten fingers.
Yes.
Vicious woman! Vicious woman!
You will face a grim fate.
Vile woman.
So, in that case,
what they took was merely
a useless person.
Naturally, that is the case.
Honey, your foresight
is truly remarkable.
However,
it will be much harder
to kill Chu Junyao.
Then let's wait and see how things unfold.
It hurts, doesn't it?
It doesn't.
But my heart aches for you.
Then,
how much does it ache?
It aches deeply.
This person is truly ruthless.
Zhang had his eyes gouged out
and his tongue cut.
Even his hands and feet were crippled.
Not only cruel and merciless,
but also meticulous.
Bringing him back is pointless.
It's clearly a trap to kill the general.
It seems this path won't work.
Though we are surrounded by darkness,
we are the sparks of hope.
What we must do is to grow stronger,
to become our own sun.
Then the darkness
will be pierced entirely.
And light will shine upon the world.
Trivial efforts are not worth it.
Putting lives at risk.
Threatening the foundation
of the Chu Family.
This cannot be tolerated.
Let's go.
Follow me to the Chu Ancestral Shrine.
Yes.