=Culinary Vendetta=
=Episode 18=
Uncle.
I know your aunt
isn't quite a good person,
selfish and self-serving,
always looking for small gains,
and causing trouble.
But...
After so many years together,
I suddenly lost her.
I just have a feeling deep inside,
as if it's been emptied out.
Uncle, don't worry.
I promise I will find my aunt.
Another human bone...
The sixth site, right?
Fetch the coroner.
Understood.
Let's go search elsewhere with the dog.
Princess.
They brought in a hound dog.
They are now searching the mansion.
Don't come near, stay away.
Why are you staring at me, dead dog?
Stay away.
Princess, I'm afraid of dogs.
Help me.
Guards, take her away!
You...
Why are you arresting me?
Why arrest me?
- Let go.
- Speak up.
Where is she?
Who?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Take her away.
Interrogate thoroughly.
Princess, Princess!
Princess, save me.
Wait.
Yue'e.
Don't worry.
It'll be alright.
I told you,
if you work for me,
you and your family will be okay.
Take her away.
Yes.
Princess.
First Madam.
You took my maid without proof.
Shouldn't you explain yourself to me?
An explanation is warranted.
- Someone.
- Yes.
Take good care of the princess for me.
No one may enter or leave her room,
except for meals,
until the matter is resolved.
You!
You, scoundrel.
I suggest you honestly confess.
So you won't face further punishment.
Confess?
What should I confess?
Only because of a mad dog,
you're trying to force a confession.
Let me tell you,
I haven't done anything wrong.
I'm a maid from the Ning Mansion.
You dare target the Ning Family like this.
The marquis won't let you off.
That hound dog is trained.
He's barking at you.
This means...
he... he saw Second Madam.
Second Madam must have been haunting you.
You agree, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
You...
Stop...
Stop scaring me like this.
I heard
that if someone dies unjustly,
she'll become a Vengeful Ghost,
seeking revenge on her enemies.
Why did that dog
only bark at her?
Why?
Because the dog
can communicate with spirits.
He definitely saw
that Vengeful Ghost on her.
There aren't real ghosts, are there?
Did you hear anything?
Why do I feel a chill around my neck?
It's a bit chilly.
There's no sound.
The fire.
Look.
It's really coming.
A ghost!
What are you doing?
What did you see?
I died so badly.
Why do you want to hurt me?
Get away, stay back.
Second Madam.
Stay back!
Go away.
Why are you trying to harm me?
It's none of my business.
It was the princess.
Every grievance has its cause.
Go find her.
See? She admitted it.
Your testimony has been fully recorded.
Explain yourself properly.
You can still survive.
How dare you deceive me.
Survive?
I do want to survive.
Who doesn't?
All my family is in her hands.
How can I survive?
So what if you have the evidence?
As long as I die.
These testimonies would be useless.
My family can survive.
Oh on.
She committed suicide.
What do we do now?
The evidence became useless.
I'll inform my lady.
At this point,
you remain so composed.
I really admire you.
You're making it sound like
the sky's falling.
Speaking of admiration.
I really admire you.
I thought you were just a nobody.
I could easily crush you.
But I didn't expect you
to be a venomous snake.
For my Su Family,
I'm willing to become a venomous snake.
Anyone who harmed my family
won't live well.
Your personal maid Yue'e has confessed.
You even killed your mother-in-law.
Are you still human?
You dare to falsely accuse me.
You threatened her
by putting her family in danger.
But you've overestimated her.
It's human nature to be selfish.
(Yue'e, how dare you betray me!)
You think by bribing Yue'e,
falsely accusing me,
I would fear you, huh?
Do you think the Nings
are easy to push around?
You're getting angry out of shame.
I know you'll deny everything.
But this won't change
the fact that you're the murderer.
If the law can't punish you,
then I'll bring justice into this.
Su Qianqian, you jerk.
I want you to pay.
And Yue'e, that servant.
I'll kill your entire family.
(I suppose Father should be here by now.)
Marquis.
Marquis, please have a seat.
The Chu Family
is really on the decline now.
When did a woman ever take charge?
Marquis, you're joking.
If the Chu Family is truly in decline,
then why marry off your beloved daughter?
That's exactly
why I came here today.
Since your family can't treat Mingzhu well,
then I'll take her back today.
She is involved in a murder case.
I'm afraid you can't take her today.
A murder case? Is there evidence?
The investigation is ongoing.
Then there's no evidence.
How dare you detain her without proof.
Do you think you can bully the Nings?
Marquis, please calm down.
We haven't detained her.
We're serving her great food and drinks.
However,
her maid, Yue'e,
admitted involvement in the murder.
Mingzhu is naturally involved.
Don't worry.
The authorities will investigate fairly
to give her justice.
What if I must take her away today?
Three days.
If no evidence is found in three days,
I'll send her back to the Ning Mansion.
But if you insist on taking her today,
I'll escalate it to His Majesty.
I'll fight to restore honor
for the Chu Family.
Alright.
Three days.
If you don't release her after three days,
don't blame me for being mean.
Currently, there's no evidence
of her wrongdoing.
In three days,
we still have to release her.
It's so frustrating.
We know the killer is that vicious woman.
But we can't do anything about her.
Compared to the Ning Family, Mingzhu
is completely insignificant.
If we bring down the Ning Family,
she'll be easy to deal with.
We have gathered important evidence,
waiting for a right time
to bring them down.
We're at a crucial moment.
We need to stay calm.
Honey, I understand.
I won't act on impulse.
Releasing Mingzhu in three days
makes them drop their guards.
Juan.
Thank you.
No need to thank me.
Well...
One of my hands is crippled.
Yet you still choose to stay by my side.
In this world,
there aren't many women
as good as you.
Though there are plenty of good women,
I won't abandon you.
Because you truly care for me.
You bravely chased away the bandits for me.
I've decided
I'll never marry anyone but you.
Juan.
Yes?
Actually, I need to confess something.
That hero rescue scene...
I set it all up.
You would...
be about to marry me.
I couldn't bear to deceive you anymore.
Actually, I already knew that.
I recognized Xiaoming and his friends.
If I wasn't with you every day,
do you think you can be the hero?
You... you...
What do you mean by that?
Actually, I've liked you for a long time.
One time I saw you give your money
all to a beggar.
That's when I knew
I want to be with you forever.
This...
That means a lot.
I'm so moved.
Don't worry, Juan.
I'll always take good care of you.
Even though your arm is useless,
you have me.
What are you afraid of?
I'm not.
I'm not afraid of anything.
I just want to be with you.
Brother Teng.
Let's have a simple wedding,
and invite Master, Master Chu,
and some friends.
That works, no problem.
It's up to you.
(Divorce Letter)
I want a divorce with Tianze.