The weather is dry!
Be careful with fire!
The Demonic Sect!
It's the Demonic Sect!
♪Master punishes me to copy the mantra
five hundred times♪
♪Focus the spirit, I study
the Eight Trigrams' deduction♪
♪But I only wish to be an unknown
vagabond like a carefree immortal♪
♪Just seeking a moment of leisure
in this fleeting life♪
♪Free and easy♪
♪There's no need to become
a celestial being♪
♪Roaming freely among mortals♪
♪Divining fate with one hexagram♪
♪The way of Dao is hard to distinguish♪
♪Might as well go with
the flow of heaven♪
♪With a jug of wine, drifting
through mountains and rivers♪
♪There's no need to become
a celestial being♪
♪Roaming freely among mortals♪
♪Chanting incantations
and spells without attachment♪
♪Heaven and earth are boundless♪
♪Seeking a good distraction♪
♪Nodding and swaying,
laughing away worries♪
♪The martial world is
full of grudges and resentment♪
♪Too many tides rising and falling,
always hard to predict♪
♪There are always skies
beyond the skies♪
♪Let the world be harsh,
I adapt with ease♪
♪Human ways follow the Dao,
Dao follows the heavens♪
♪Be it walking on walls
or facing the chaos of the world♪
♪Watch me throw wild punches,
laughing off everything♪
♪The way of the hero,
the traveler understands♪
♪Fearless of power and doctrine,
defying the shadows♪
♪Upholding justice, helping the weak♪
♪This journey is sure to be
full of obstacles♪
♪But I will silently chant in my heart♪
♪Justice comes in all forms, and martial
arts bear no label of good or evil♪
♪Dao follows nature, I defy the heavens♪
♪I defy the heavens♪
♪So carefree, don't laugh at my madness♪
♪Wielding my sword, walking the world♪
♪Defining good and evil,
black and white♪
♪What hero's invitation♪
♪Why should I honor it♪
♪None of it matters as long as
you're by my side♪
♪So carefree, don't laugh at my madness♪
♪Wielding my sword, walking the world♪
♪Countering every move, with brothers
at my side♪
♪Let's unleash our ultimate move
together♪
♪Countering every move,
with brothers at my side♪
♪The path of a hero may not work♪
♪But we'll make our own way♪
=Hidden Master=
=Episode 15=
Is it good?
Not bad.
I bought you all the most famous snacks
from Huizhou City.
Here's your food.
This is it?
Yes.
I want meat! Big fish, big meat!
You look like big fish to me.
- But I'm injured!
- You...
Yingdan is also not well right now.
Yingdan, how's your backlash?
It's already fine.
Right.
Crane Knight sent a letter saying
they're rebuilding the Blade God's
old home.
It'll be the future gathering place
for the Divine Blade Sect.
Those two brothers are inseparable now,
and said they'll manage
the sect together.
Heng and Mr. Gou
are also inseparable now.
Ling'er, don't bring that up.
Ling'er's right!
In this life,
it's rare to meet and
truly know each other.
Although you two are master
and disciple,
you are more like brothers.
That bond is even rarer.
Well, he's always been sharp-tongued!
Only because you pissed me off!
You...
Enough.
Everyone's here?
Yingdan.
Gou Lingfeng.
Which great hero did this to you?
Deng Yunfeng,
why are you everywhere?
Just focus on healing.
I dropped by to check on you all.
I brought you some specialties
from the capital,
Osmanthus pastries.
- I'll take those.
- Any meat?
You look like meat to me.
- I...
- Enough already.
Thanks for the trouble.
- No...
- So lively!
My Lady.
- I brought some food and liquor
- My Lady.
to celebrate Mr. Gou's release
from prison.
Thought I'd help him drive away
bad luck.
I didn't expect everyone to be here.
Yeah, truly bad luck.
Then I'll get to the point.
When I returned to the capital,
I learned
you "Zhu Gou Team" have made
quite a name for yourselves.
My godfather thinks highly of you.
Would you consider joining the court?
Enough, Deng Yunfeng.
Do you have to bring up
a buzzkill topic at a time like this?
It's good to you all.
Mr. Gou,
you were a convict,
then got involved in
the Divine Blade Sect mess.
If not for Eunuch Deng's pardon,
you'd be unable to clear your name.
This is a favor
you should remember.
Deng Yunfeng,
you saved my master this time,
- and we're really grateful to you,
- Yeah.
but the few of us
are used to being free.
We don't want anything to do
with the court.
Alright, alright.
We've all gathered today.
Let's not waste the fine food
and liquor.
Yeah!
Heng, here!
Is it good?
So good.
Yingdan, is it good?
I can help myself.
I've been so busy lately,
I haven't had time to congratulate
Your Ladyship and Lord Deng.
Your Ladyship is clever and bright,
and Lord Deng just took office
as Inspector,
such a promising future.
You are a perfect match,
truly a blessed union.
What's wrong, Yingdan?
- Yingdan.
- Yingdan, are you alright?
No, I'm fine. Just choked a little.
Stop acting tough at this time!
I said I'm fine.
Be careful, Master!
Gou Lingfeng!
Put me down!
(Martial Artists Association)
The clerks responsible for core intel
and mission dispatches in the guild,
were replaced by Deng Yunfeng
with his own people.
Fine.
All these years I've spent so much money
training those people!
Now he's cutting me off at the root.
Alright.
Deng Yunfeng,
you just wait.
(Qingyu Garden)
Lord Deng, time to say goodbye.
You've had enough to drink tonight.
Head back and rest.
My Lady,
you know Zhuge Heng has someone
in his heart.
I don't understand why
you're still so hung up on him.
Do you need a reason to like someone?
You should focus on
your own issues first.
I...
(Qingyu Garden)
Lord Deng,
you're still here?
How's your
backlash?
How do you know about that?
Yingdan.
- Lord Deng.
- I...
It's getting late.
If there's nothing else,
please leave.
Yingdan, I mean no harm.
Let me show you something
very important.
Do you remember this?
Little Stone.
Your hair looks better tied up.
You're bleeding.
My blood is poisonous!
Get away, Little Stone!
Quick, take this antidote.
I'm sorry, Little Stone. I'm sorry.
You're
Little Stone?
Yes.
Then...
Why?
Why what?
Why did you leave without a word?
The poisonous kid has no friend.
Her friend is gone.
We're not playing with you.
Let's go.
Back then,
you
were my only friend.
Yingdan,
I was adopted by my godfather.
I wanted to say goodbye,
but you didn't come.
All these years,
I've been looking for you,
always.
I'm sorry.
But I'm back now.
Yingdan,
I've thought of you all these years.
I never forgot you.
Actually, back at the MAA,
I recognized you.
But I knew you wouldn't forgive me.
So I just watched over you from afar.
But every time I saw you with that
big idiot...
Who are you calling a big idiot?
Gou Lingfeng!
You can't insult him like that.
I'm sorry.
Seeing you two
so close every day,
I was jealous.
Sometimes I wonder
why couldn't that person be me?
Yingdan...
Lord Deng,
it's already very late.
Go home.
Yingdan...
Heng,
while you were gone,
we were all worried sick.
After the incidents
with Swallow Knight and Crane Knight,
I realized
my time with Master
is a rare blessing.
If I miss it,
I might lose it forever.
Heng,
I'm so glad you've come around.
But I've lost
the trail for the Moon Sword Skill,
and the manual was taken by Grandmaster.
Heng,
I'll stay with you no matter what.
Thank you, Ling'er.
Ling'er,
I, Zhuge Heng
swear this under the moon:
When my vengeance is fulfilled,
I will marry you,
and love you for all my life.
Heng...
But right now, I'm just
a man without a home.
All I can offer you
are these empty promises.
Heng,
I have no one.
It's only thanks to you
I have a home now.
I wouldn't want more.
So,
you're saying yes?
Heng,
look! A fish took the bait!
Heng?
My Lady,
how do you know the Moon Sword Skill?
I want to help you take revenge.
Please, teach me.
Mr. Zhuge,
come find me
at midnight every night to practice.
But keep it quiet.
I don't want to be talked about.
Alright, My Lady.
I promise I won't tell anyone.
Then let's begin now.
What are you doing?
That toothy grin scared me!
Yingdan, why'd you
fall asleep out here?
You might catch a cold.
You even brought the blanket out.
Come on.
You scared me so bad last night.
I was worried sick.
It's fine now. Don't worry.
Why are your eyes red?
Are you still not better?
I said I'm fine.
So you really are fine.
Gou Lingfeng,
you're the first person who dared
to touch me.
Hurry up and touch me back!
Or you'll lose out. Go on, quick!
Gou Lingfeng!
You...
You've got the strength to hit me.
Now I'm truly relieved.
I really came at the wrong time.
Please, carry on.
I didn't see anything.
Put down those cups!
I told you,
I'm just worried about Yingdan!
There's nothing between us!
Master, the way you look at Yingdan
tells another story.
You talk too much!
Yingdan, your eyes are really red.
Did Deng Yunfeng insult you last night?
Who?
Deng Yunfeng came last night?
I saw him, drunk, came
looking for Yingdan.
Did he make you mad?
I... I'll go and...
-Enough, you two.
- I'll beat him up!
Inspector Deng was attacked!
Everyone, to the MAA now!
That karma hit fast.
Got it.
You hear? Something big happened!
What?
Inspector Deng was assassinated!
No way.
- It's true!
- Yingdan.
- So many people.
- The night patrol saw it.
He barely escaped death,
but he's completely out of it.
Inspector Deng's life's still uncertain.
Guess the heavens do bring justice.
That news is making people so happy.
Seems like you're the happiest one.
He deserves it for disturbing Yingdan
at midnight.
Besides, he always acted
too high and mighty.
I'm definitely not the only one
who couldn't stand him.
And a court officer like him
meddling in our MAA affairs?
He clearly had other motives.
Exactly.
Don't be too harsh.
Deng Yunfeng did help us before.
And think about it,
with his martial skills,
anyone who could hurt him
must be pretty formidable.
With the Hero Gathering coming up,
many things are happening,
trouble's brewing.
Seems like Huizhou's about to get messy.
Perfect.
You startled me!
This is exactly the chance
for me to strike down evil!
(Righteous and Mighty)
Everyone's here?
We've called this assembly
because, as you may have heard,
something serious happened last night.
Our newly appointed
Inspector Deng Yunfeng
was attacked within
the MAA
and seriously wounded.
Quiet, please.
So today,
we're issuing
a public task.
(Mission Notice)
Everyone can join the investigation.
Inspector Deng stated
that anyone who solves the case,
or provides critical clues,
will be promoted one rank,
and earn double points!
Double points?
This is my chance to level up!
Why are you here?
To laugh at me?
Do I look like I'm laughing?
Yingdan,
you came too.
Are you feeling better?
It's okay.
I'll live.
- You...
- Deng Yunfeng.
Look,
we even brought you something!
- No? Forget it.
Yunfeng,
lie back down.
You're not healed yet.
Yingdan,
thank you.
why are you being so nice to him?
Deng Yunfeng,
I heard that assassin was pretty good?
He beat you like that
with just five moves?
What's wrong with you?
Maybe that assassin wasn't
all that great.
More likely the one who got beat
was just weak.
Yingdan,
that's not true.
Actually, I was relieving myself.
The guy ambushed me!
I didn't even have my pants up!
Otherwise,
how could he have succeeded?
Yunfeng,
this is a healing balm I made.
- Here.
- Okay.
Thanks, Yingdan.
Inspector Deng,
have you got any more leads?
That assassin was extremely skilled.
You should be careful too.
He could create countless shadow clones,
just like the Demonic Sect's
Phantom Shadow.
The Demonic Sect's getting out of hand!
But don't worry.
Once I'm recovered,
I'll wipe out every last one of them!
- What's wrong with you?
- Enough.
- Stop staring at me!
- Stop playing the hero.
Walls have ears.
You want another beatdown?
Zhuge Heng.
Inspector Deng's clues are important.
Yingdan, let's go.
Yingdan!
I'm not done asking!
Are you eating or not?
Whatever.
What's with that look?
- It's not the Demonic Sect.
It wasn't them?
You two seem to know a lot
about the Demonic Sect.
- Yes.
- No.
Speak.
Yingdan,
that Phantom Shadow
Deng Yunfeng mentioned,
I can do it too.
And it's not what he described.
You know it too?
Based on his description,
it actually sounds more like
our Sword Alliance's
Shadow Swordplay.
- Shadow Swordplay?
Sword Alliance?
Let's go check it out.
Yingdan,
I don't think I'm up for it
the next couple days.
Let's wait a bit.
Zhuge,
you've been out all night
these past few days.
Are you up to no good?
Spit it out.
Tsk.
Kids grow up, huh?
Can't control him anymore.
Where are you going, Yingdan?
Why are you calling me like that?
Deng Yunfeng calls you that way,
so I will too. Yingdan!
- Yingdan.
- Enough!
Whatever.
Yingdan, where are you going?
To bring Deng Yunfeng some food.
He's injured
- and needs the nourishment.
- You can't!
He doesn't deserve it.
- He doesn't, but you do?
- I...
We're all part of the MAA.
We should help each other.
Yingdan,
he's not a good guy.
He's not a good guy?
And you are?
You don't even know him.
Do you know that?
I'm not wasting words with you.
I...
Who is it?
Gou Lingfeng.
Vice Chairman He wanted to see you.
There's an urgent mission.
Another mission?
He specifically said
only you can go.
Just me?
Yes.
Alright.
What's wrong, Vice Chairman He?
I wanted to tell you something.
Don't tell me the case
is already solved?
The Sword Saint is dead.
The Sword Saint is dead?
Zhuge's father?
I just got the notice
from the Sword Alliance.
What a pity.
The once-famous Sword Saint
is gone just like that.
You are the closest to Zhuge.
I'll leave the task of informing him
to you.
Inform him?
He's changed his heart that fast?
Careful, don't choke.
It's been long since I've had
a hot meal.
I didn't expect you to be
such a good cook.
Yingdan,
how's your backlash going?
I've already made the antidote.
Don't worry.
Really?
Relax.
That's great.
Alright,
it's getting late.
Rest early.
I'll head back.
Yingdan,
can you stay with me
just a little longer?
I still need to help you
find the killer.
I can't let them hurt you again.
Take care.
- Yingdan!
- Xiaobai!
Something big just happened!
What is it? Why are you so panicked?
Zhuge's dad is gone.
- No way.
- It's true.
I saw the obituary myself.
Thought it was a new mission,
turns out it was this.
How are we even supposed to tell Zhuge?
Exactly.
He lost his mom when he was young,
he already had it rough.
Now he's lost his dad too,
it's even worse.
Mr. Zhuge, you did it.
What's wrong, Mr. Zhuge?
My Lady,
I'll never forget your immense kindness.
If you ever need help,
just say the word.
I'll do anything for you.
Mr. Zhuge,
don't say that.
You saved my life once.
I can't believe
this day came so fast.
I can finally take my revenge.
Let me drink with you in celebration.
Congrats on your wish coming true.
I'll fill it up for you.
Here.
To you.
Thank you, My Lady.
Mr. Zhuge,
who exactly
is your enemy?
Well,
I'm sorry I can't tell you that.
Please understand.
Mr. Zhuge,
if you want to cry, then cry.
- Yingdan, you tell him.
- No, you.
I really don't know how.
Just tell the truth.
Zhuge.
You're up early.
Where have you been this time?
You reek of alcohol.
Yeah, disgusting.
Drinking a bit's fine.
Zhuge, you need to understand
that all of us
eventually have to leave this world.
Right.
Leaving doesn't mean disappearing.
So even if someone's gone,
don't be too sad.
Exactly.
You gotta stay positive.
Books say,
even if someone leaves,
their spirit can stay by your side.
Yeah.
Watching over your life,
caring about everything you do.
Master, are you dying?
It's not me.
Zhuge,
if your dad's gone,
you can always find another.
What about mine? Want him?
You outta your mind?
I'm not Deng Yunfeng,
going around collecting fathers.
What is wrong with you people?
If there's nothing else,
I'm going to bed.
Zhuge!
Zhuge Heng!
If none of you will say it,
then I will!
You really let me down.
Ling'er.
Why didn't you tell him?
What's up with everyone this morning?
Yingdan,
what's going on?
Ling'er
found out too.
No way.
He'll have to face it.
Say it directly.
Fine.
- You do it.
- No, you do it.
- You.
- You tell him.
I...
- What should I say?
- I...
What are you two trying to do?
- Zhuge.
- Zhuge Heng.
Where are you going?
To the Sword Alliance.
Zhuge,
the Shadow Swordplay isn't urgent
right now.
- I...
- It's not just about that.
So you already know?
Pretty much confirmed.
My condolences.
The Sword Saint was a hero.
Even in death, he'll be honored by all.
What did you say?
What did I say?
You said my dad's dead?
Wait... you didn't know?
No.
Then what do you know?
The Shadow Swordplay
is our secret technique,
only the Sword Saints can wield it.
When I was little,
my dad tried to teach it to me.
But I never wanted to learn.
So you think
your dad is the assassin?
Not necessarily.
I haven't been back in a long time.
That's why I have to go back this time
to find out the truth.
You're killing me here!
We were racking our brains
trying to figure out
how to tell you your father died.
- We thought you'd be devastated.
- Yeah!
Why are you not sad at all?
That old man
"dies" like every other week.
So the 32nd time, I knew
he wasn't really dead.
Then on the 33rd,
he said he was dueling an immortal
and got killed.
But I knew
no one could kill him,
not even an immortal.
So
I didn't go back.
he faked his death to get you
to come home?
Yep. He's not dead.
He faked it,
and dragged us all
into it?
That's just cruel.
So now I suspect this whole thing
is just another trick to lure me back.
But this time, I have to go.
If he actually hurt Deng Yunfeng
just to make me come home,
that's way too far.
Their father-son relationship is
- so twisted.
- So twisted.
Heng,
I'll go with you.
Ling'er, it's dangerous.
You'll be safest here.
We'll be back soon.
(Sword Alliance)
So this is the legendary Sword Alliance?
Looks more like a market to me.
I heard they turned it into shops
long ago.
It was the Sword Saint himself
who pushed for it
against everyone's wishes.
Why does this place look so familiar?
Slap a new sign on it
and it's basically the GFTA.
You think every shop
belongs to your family.
What is that about?
Stay away from me.
I can't let anyone know I'm back.
I need to stay undercover.
Young master, you've returned.
Zhuge,
you might find it hard
to stay hidden.
That disguise is totally useless.
You two go look around.
I'm gonna find my second uncle
and see what's up.
Let's go explore.
Uncle?
Wait, you...
It's me.
Heng!
You scared me!
You're finally back!
(End of the Episode)
Yingdan, you are here.
Why are you here?
Sir, drop the act.
Was I that obvious these last two days?
A bit.
My hairstyle doesn't look bad, right?
It's cool.
But sir, let me just say one thing.
Don't hit me.
Speak.
Aren't you maybe a little
too concerned about the Floral Knight?
Am I?
That's to monitor
the actions of Zhu Gou Team.
You wouldn't get it.
Right, right.
You're totally right.
Everything you say is right.
♪A vessel of Xinfeng wine
is worth ten thousand cash♪
♪In Xianyang most of the chivalrous
and gallant are young men♪
♪Sharing like views
and tastes they drink heartily to each other♪
♪While their horses are tethered
to willows by tall buildings♪
♪A vessel of Xinfeng wine
is worth ten thousand cash♪
♪In Xianyang most of the chivalrous
and gallant are young men♪
♪Sharing like views
and tastes they drink heartily to each other♪
♪While their horses are tethered♪
♪to willows by tall buildings♪
♪Morning hues adorn the skies♪
♪Homeland tugs where my heart lies♪
♪Shoulder to shoulder we once strode♪
♪Now paths diverge,
we walk alone♪
♪When shall we meet,
the wind inquires♪
♪With wine in hand,
beneath the moon♪
♪No words can bridge the vast unknown♪
♪The silent night♪