On this trip,
I want to do something
we haven't done yet.
Something fun might
be coming our way.
We're DAY6.
No doubt about it!
Right.
Do you think Dowoon and Brian
have the barbecue ready?
Those guys?
I doubt it. Probably
too busy having fun.
Young K, hurry
up and come on in!
He looks the best when
he's doing nothing...
Guys, we're here.
Give us a hand with this?
Sure.
What did you buy so much of?
Just something to eat, and...
- campfire.
- Isn't it heavy?
- What?
It's fine.
Yeah? Glad to hear that.
- We bought a lot.
- I know.
We should have some beer.
- Gonna drink beer?
- Yes.
- We can't miss it.
- Right.
And have a campfire.
That sounds warm.
Dowoon already got a new friend?
Who's that old man?
That's Mr. Perfect, right there.
- They look happy.
- I know, right?
I'm warmed up now.
Feel so much better.
It’s nice and warm here, right?
- It really is warm.
- Yes.
Aren't you cold?
It's around 200 °C.
It’s basically winter!
Careful, you’re
gonna catch fire!
I know, right?
It feels nice.
This is a good vibe.
Vibe approved?
Vibe approved. Enough for me.
In the past ten years,
It’s the first time for us
to go abroad on our own.
- Right.
Not just in the past ten years.
We've never been on
a trip on our own, right?
Yes. First time traveling
abroad together.
Right?
- We’ve only traveled within Korea.
- Right.
We've traveled abroad
when we were already there,
aside from it, haven't spent
time abroad just for a trip.
Wow, it's been
ten years already.
I know.
The tenth anniversary.
Many of our fans got married.
Right. Ten years is
enough to get married.
They might have children.
I thought that was pretty cool.
When we first began,
they were students.
And now...
- They work.
- Yes. They got a job.
They say the songs
they used to listen to
sound different now.
Even for us, as we
go on for ten years,
everything feels
different every time.
Right. Probably.
All that time we spent
in the past ten years,
not just our songs,
it became good memories.
- Right.
- Yes.
One of My Day, who
was an employee.
Her position was an employee.
Her position was an employee?
No. What was it?
You're not asleep, are you?
- Well...
- A staff member.
Yes, she was a staff member.
She said the team manager
was giving her a hard time.
I was like,
'Seriously team
leaders, let's not do that.'
And she became the team manager?
No, the My Day who
are team managers said,
'Dowoon, I'm sorry.'
I think we're growing together.
Yes.
When we first began,
honestly,
there were only a few.
There were so few fans
that we could remember
their faces and names.
It's interesting
how we get to meet more people
from diverse areas as we go on.
I'm grateful for it.
Ten years ago,
I remember imagining what
we’d be like in a decade.
I didn't expect this.
With your sunglasses
on the back of your head.
I didn't see it coming.
You look cool.
We turned out too well.
We turned out so well
that I feel pressured.
Right.
There was a time when we
couldn't even fill MUV-Hall.
Right.
After all,
we've been doing
our best, for ten years.
We were able to do this
because of those who support us.
Without My Day, our fans,
it would've been
difficult for me.
I used to say it like a habit
that I wanted to quit.
I wanted to stop.
We were able to
do this for ten years
because we
cheered each other up and
were there for each other.
Right.
We supported and led each other.
But above all, My Day
was there for us
the entire time.
It's true that they
led us this far.
The singers who met good fans.
That's true.
I can't hear you.
What?
I was looking at the sun.
Nice weather, right?
I know.
By the way...
Why, Dowoon?
The weather is nice,
and the sight is awesome.
Why don't we sing
'You Were Beautiful'?
Why 'You Were
Beautiful' of all songs?
When we look
back, it was beautiful.
I think it's past tense now.
It was beautiful.
'Beautiful-ed.'
It's the song that
made us famous.
A song that made us known.
The song that made us famous.
Yes.
Not 'Congratulations'?
- 'Congratulations'?
- Not at that time.
- At the time...
- 'Congratulations' is...
There was barely any media
coverage about us at the time.
There was just one
article about our debut.
Right. There was nothing.
No music shows.
I was confident about
'Congratulations.'
It wasn't time yet.
Let's do it.
'You Were Beautiful'?
Yes.
Let's do it.
I did ask for this... but
now I'm embarrassed.
This was your idea!
Guys, let's go.
Let's go.
Check that out.
Doesn't it look like teeth?
Like teeth upside down, right?
Aren't they King Kong's teeth?
More like dinosaur's.
They look like teeth.
Not King Kong.
Dinosaur! You know?
Young K's talking. Looks
like King Kong's teeth.
- Dinosaur's teeth!
- A dinosaur...
Sunjin, why don’t you choose?
King Kong or dinosaur?
- King Kong, maybe?
- They look like King Kong?
More like a dinosaur's
than King Kong's, right?
Dinosaur or King Kong?
King Kong over a dinosaur.
Is it a dinosaur or
King Kong? You say it.
I’m the youngest, right?
Not you, actually.
Let me ask Sungjin.
They look like a dinosaur's.
Right?
He takes my side.
- But...
- Move your hand. He...
Stay still, will you?
Shouldn't you care about
the youngest the most?
- Stay put, guys.
- I was right.
Wasn’t I the one
who got us to debut?
Check that out.
Look at them.
Over there.
Give it up for them.
I always dreamed of that too.
Everything that my eyes see
becomes music.
It's cool.
I think we can…
- slow down.
- Okay.
Slow down, will you?
Or that could happen to us.
Wait, did the car get stuck?
Really?
Give it more gas!
One, two, three!
That won't be easy.
Why don't we help them?
One, two, three!
Wait, wait.
Give it more gas!
Why not?
We received so
much for what we did.
I won't forget it until I die.
- Thank you.
It's sunny today.
A sunny day. Look outside.
Ta-da.
Isn't it really sunny?
It's a really nice day.
Dowoon, are you filming a vlog?
What? No. It's
just for our record.
- For memories?
- Yes.
Say hi.
- Sungjin.
- Yes.
We met Sihasin yesterday.
We met Sihasin band.
I’ve always had that dream.
One day, I want to try
adding folk music to our sound.
And in a way,
we got to listen to
the original version.
That was really inspiring.
It feels like we're
filming content, right?
When I'm holding a camera,
you never answer me.
By the way, yesterday,
the drums.
- He said he made them.
- Oh, yes.
According to the environment.
He said he set them up
according to the environment.
You know what was so cool?
He steps on the
kick standing up.
I know.
He plays the drums standing up.
While singing.
And I can't do that.
You can do it.
Don't think that's impossible.
While watching him...
Don't limit yourself.
So watching him...
Dowoon, you can do it.
Okay. That's the end
of the conversation.
Wonpil, I'm sorry but
that jelly looked good.
- Do you want it?
- Can I have a bite?
What do you want to try?
The pink one please.
You're picky.
Ah.
Isn't that Jinyoung's...
No, you need to feed him.
Ah.
What's wrong?
What?
- What's wrong?
- Something wrong?
My phone's not working.
What?
- I don’t think I have reception.
- Is it the data? What is it?
- Is the GPS not working?
- I'm getting no signals.
Why not?
- Who knows?
- He wouldn't know.
Right. No one knows.
Let's keep moving forward
until we get the reception again.
What is this place?
What?
Over there.
Can you pull over?
Let's check it out.
- What is that?
- That's interesting.
It's pretty.
Strange.
- It's pretty.
- It says, 'Love is universal.'
What does 'universal' mean?
Something that's
common across all regions?
- Yeah.
- Amazing?
Universal?
It's nice. Do you
want to check it out?
- I want to.
- Me too.
- Let's go.
- I want to see it closely.
Let's go check it out.
We don't even know what it is.
We know where it is.
Gosh.
No. It's hot.
I'll stay in the car.
This doesn't happen
often. Come on.
Come with us.
- It’d be a waste not to see it.
- Do you have to?
- Of course.
- Let's go.
Come with us.
No. I'll stay in the car.
You guys go. Hurry.
Don't be so selfish.
What can I do about it?
We'll be quick.
We won't take long.
We're off.
- Be careful.
- Yes.
See you.
Let's go.
Guys, I’ll go check
it out over there too.
Please. How far
do you want to go?
They should be okay.
♪ In there ♪
This is insane!
It got everything.
This is basically a gym.
What is this?
It got everything.
It's hot.
This is nice.
It's very nice.
I like this place.
Do you want to check it out?
Everything is white.
I know.
But it's scary white.
Do you feel fear here?
It's cool.
Stuff we use in our
everyday life gathered
- to be reborn.
- Yes.
This is pretty cool.
How did they make all this?
With enthusiasm.
Right?
Probably.
What about Sungjin?
We should ask
Dowoon and Sungjin.
I think it's going to be fun.
Interesting.
Sounds fun!
But... where are we now?
Kinda reminds you of
our debut days, right?
Yes.
What do you think of first?
When we used to
perform at clubs.
Doesn't the stage
remind you of that?
- Yes.
- It's exactly the same.
At the time, all the
clubs in Hongdae...
- We went to every one of them.
- I think we visited all of them.
Almost all of them.
- Many of them are gone now.
- Yes.
And one more
thing I remember is...
When we just debuted.
- Early in our debut.
- The earliest days.
We prepared candies with notes.
We handed them out in Hongdae,
asking people to
come just this once.
No one knew us back then.
No one knew that we debuted.
No one.
I wanted people to recognize us.
So on purpose,
I carried JYP's paper bag.
The blue one?
Then people would
ask, 'What's that?'
Because we were
giving out stuff.
If anyone asked, 'What's that?'
then I said "We debuted in JYP."
- Wanting them to recognize us.
- Right.
We’ve gone through a lot.
Because we had those
days, we’re who we are now.
Anyway,
what about Sungjin?
Is this okay without him?
- Right.
Shouldn't we check on him?
What do we do?
Is he still in the car?
I said I'd go back soon.
He might get a little salty.
I bet that there’s 90% chance,
he's sleeping in the car.
He looked tired.
Is he sleeping?
Us?
He wants us up there.
He's telling us to come up.
But we're missing Sungjin.
What do we do?
We need Sungjin to do anything.
We can't do it without Sungjin.
What's there to worry about?
Let's do it.
- Where were you?
- You fell asleep, right?
Let's go.
We’re not here to do
great but to have fun.
One, two, three. DAY6.
DAY6.
We’re not here to do
great but to have fun.
One, two, three. DAY6.
DAY6.
Wow, it really is a desert.
It's so vast.
I know.
I want to sled here.
Isn't that a buggy?
Yes.
I only rode that in a game.
- Want to check it out?
- Should we?
- Let's go.
- Let's check it out.
- Check it out?
Are you coming?
Go ahead.
You saw it in a game!
Aren't you coming?
I've seen enough.
- You want us to go check?
- Go check it out.
- We'll be right back.
- Okay.
He's really not getting out.
Wow.
Wow, it’s so cool.
It'll be fun to drive here.
This desert’s got a whole vibe.
Vibe approved!
I've never seen a car like this.
- It's cool how it's open.
- Cool.
Wouldn’t it get sand in it?
It's bigger than I thought.
When I played PUBG,
I thought it’d be very small.
I know.
But a little... a little...
- What?
- It's a little...
- You're going to trust him?
Of course. We have to.
- But...
- No plan is our plan.
True. But...
- Up to you.
- Go?
I'm going. Suit yourselves.
Let's go.
Let's go. Okay.
I'm counting on you, Dave.
Awesome.
This is crazy.
Yeah?
This is really crazy.
Should we get Dowoon?
Gosh.
Dowoon regret
it if he misses it.
- He has to ride this.
- I know.
- He won't know until he rides it.
- Let's ride it together.
- You have to ride it.
- It's awesome.
This is good enough.
- No.
- You have to try it.
It's worth trying once.
Once in your life.
- It's not dangerous at all.
- It seemed fun!
Dowoon, if you miss this,
you’re missing out on
something huge in life.
I'm serious.
This is huge.
Be cool.
Okay okay.
Come on, Dowoon.
- Once in your life.
- Let's try it once.
Or gonna regret it big time.
Trust me.
Let's go.
Ride it.
- Really?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- For real?
Really?
Let's go.
Really? Just the four of us?
It's so nice.
This is awesome.
It's nice but, I
can't see anything.
You see with your heart.
I can't see anything.
Watch with your heart.
This is the vibe.
I can't believe I
get to ride a buggy.
Sungjin driving a buggy?
When else would we do this?
This is going to be memorable.
Wait.
What's wrong? Is it broken?
I think it's out of gas.
It's out of gas?
Why won't it go?
Did he say it was full?
Did you stop the car?
No. I think it's broken.
Interesting.
We need to ask Dave.
But we don't have his number.
Where did Dave go?
Wasn't he around?
Wait. Isn't that our car?
What?
No way.
Isn't that a Tasman?
What?
- Is that really our car?
- Isn't that Dave?
Wait. Did Dave just
give us this car
that's out of gas
and take that?
Is there anything?
He left his bag.
- For real?
- Let me see.
You're so busted.
- What's this?
- His number might be here.
- Right.
- What's this?
It's a license plate.
These are fake.
What?
Fake license plates?
What's this beanie?
He was a scam.
He stole our car.
Gosh.
Do we have to walk?
This car is down.
Young K, you told me I
would regret missing it.
I regret riding it.
- Dowoon.
- Okay okay, zip it!
Hey, should we try that?
You know, like from the movie.
Oh, Hitchhiking?
I’ve done it before!
How should we do it?
- The cars are going too fast.
- Let’s try it on that side.
- Cross the road?
- Yeah.
I used to hitchhike on
trucks back in middle school.
Let’s cross first.
Cross!
Let’s cross!
Dowoon, should
I do it like this?
Brian, like this?
Yeap, shake it up and
down, up and down like this.
Why is it… Ugh!
Try it this way, like this.
Let’s not lose our temper.
Let’s just keep trying.
Let’s try, it’s coming!
Wow, we’re actually doing this?
Is it working?
I'm not getting any reception.
No?
Why am I not
getting any reception?
Seriously.
Didn't we have a map?
You're right.
Where are we?
I think we're around here, no?
38 miles?
From where?
Here.
38 miles... I think I
saw it somewhere.
What? 38 miles?
Then Dave can't be far.
Tasman didn't have much gas.
Right.
Hey. Let's go.
We only have 38 miles left.
Let's keep going.
Keep it up.
Let's go.
It's a police car!
We're safe.
Well done.
- What?
- Yes. Well done.
Well done, everyone.
You too.
Thanks.
Don't mind it.
You did a good job.
We did the best we could do.
It's fine.
When he cheered
us up at the end,
- that meant a lot.
- Yes.
I almost flopped
down and slept there.
Right.
Gosh, that Dave guy.
This is exactly why I
don’t leave the house.
Nothing’s safer than
being under a blanket.
I know.
I want to turn the AC
on and have tangerines.
So good.
So sweet.
This might become
good memories...
One day...
One day.
- Maybe.
- Probably.
Maybe.
- Yes. Probably.
♪ Ah what happy days ♪
No. No. They weren’t happy days.
It was exhausting.
They will be...
They will become happy days.
Glad you guys are still smiling.
♪ I smile ♪
Isn't that a Tasman?
Dave?
Nice weather.
I know.
It was so hot.
It's cool here.
It's like the opposite.
- I know.
- Dowoon, are you cold?
No, it's cool.
That's life.
Well, life’s not
always like that.
Sometimes it's hot.
Sometimes it's cold.
- That's the way it's been for us.
- True.
I think it's all about enduring.
Honestly, when I heard about
this trip, for our tenth anniversary...
Were you anxious?
Yes. Because it's us.
Of course.
Because it's us.
Because it’s us... I was worried
something unexpected
might happen... again.
- Exactly as you expected, right?
- Exactly as I expected.
- We haven’t changed a bit.
- Yes.
Can’t help it.
That's always DAY6.
So much happened
in the past six days.
- I know.
- So much happened.
It feels like it would
be our first and last trip.
- Right?
- Trip abroad?
This will be our first and
last tenth anniversary trip.
- Yes.
- It will never come back.
Who knows? Maybe
another one this winter.
He means we won’t have
another tenth anniversary.
You carried a lot
on your shoulder…
As our leader, you
always plan the trip for us.
- But what happened this time?
- I know...
He has a plan,
but he also has bad
luck that ruins his plan.
- And that's me.
- Congratulations.
Thank you, always.
I owe you.
You’re the reason why
DAY6 is so dynamic.
- My life has been like this.
- I knew it.
Really, thank you.
- For this trip, and everything else.
- Right.
Every time.
For the whole ten years.
Yes. Both you and Wonpil.
- Right. Went through a lot.
- I...
Right. Everyone worked hard.
I... I'm actually...
You're always doing
great just by being there.
My existence alone is great.
Yes. Your existence alone.
I'm the lucky
charm of this team!
- Right.
- You're handsome.
I'm not so bad.
When I have a
hard time or struggle,
I think about them.
- My Day?
- Yes.
Yes.
They cheer us up.
Of course.
Without My Day,
not to mention our ten years...
They keep DAY6 moving
forward. Our true driving force.
The fact that
we're on this sand.
- We owe it all to My Day.
- Yes.
To be honest,
My Day have waited
a long time for us.
Yes.
When they were waiting for us,
they continued to send us love.
We wanted to make up for that,
so after we completed
our military service,
we got back together.
And we did our best
to return their love.
If you think about
our beginning,
My Day basically created
our concert culture.
Even when we were completely
lost or stunned on stage,
They were the ones
pulling us forward.
Of course.
It's already been ten years
for that young DAY6.
Look at us now.
Oh, ten years.
What would we look like
on our 20th anniversary?
- Ten years later?
- Yes.
We'd still be the same.
One thing is clear.
We won't be able to
perform as much as now.
Yeah, not as active
as we are now.
First of all, we
must stay healthy.
For us to perform a lot, we
must take care of ourselves.
I already feel different
from ten years ago.
I know.
It's so different.
So different...
I feel it when I perform.
- Dowoon.
- Yes.
Do you look forward to
where we’ll be in ten years?
Of course.
Yes.
- I think.
- Yes?
there won't be much difference.
Wait. That means
I'm not excited.
No. That means that's
how you want it to be.
Yeah?
To me, being ordinary is
the hardest thing to pull off.
Right. But we're not ordinary.
That's also true.
Who cares about
ten years from now?
We don't even know
what we're doing tomorrow.
So what are we doing tomorrow?
You never know
what'll happen tomorrow.
Where are we going right now?
Just where this road leads.
Where are we going?
To the end over there.
Sure.
If we just keep walking...
the earth is round.
Oh, we will get to
Korea eventually?
We'll get somewhere.
Of course.
When tomorrow comes,
maybe it’ll be better than today.
- Let's keep going.
- Yes. Let's go.
Let's go.
Let's just go.
That's what we've been doing.
♪ That’s how it was ♪
Catch me if you can.
Catch me.
I'm running.
We don't do that.
Nice.
Guys, thank you so much.
Dowoon, out of nowhere?
Without you, I wouldn't
have endured it for ten years.
Same here! Thank
you so much, everyone.
Ready to run for
the 20th anniversary?
- Totally.
- Let's continue to do this.
Where's our next
stage going to be?
You two look good on camera.
No, it's really hard!
What I did yesterday
wasn’t even driving.
Lost count of how many
times we tried hitchhiking…
Rock, paper, scissors.
- Sungjin might be sleeping in the car...
- Sounds true.
Or eating somewhere near.
- Can you do ‘Bravo’ this time?
- 'Bravo'.
Wow, talk about
next-level tuning.
All bright and bubbly!
Big round of applause!
Thank you, thank you!
Thank you so much, everyone!