♪Long and short,
sighs are whispers sharp as blades♪
♪East and west, hustling and drifting
in the martial world♪
♪Destined or accidental,
no one falls for me♪
♪Solitary is my middle name♪
♪Spring after spring,
is the matchmaker dozing off♪
♪You knock on the door of my heart,
a burst of blossoms amazing the dusk♪
♪Touching or hurting,
we tacitly agree it's a kind of fortune♪
♪The blue and the rosy
are heaven's match♪
♪Falling into an embrace,
cherishing a moment of tenderness♪
♪No need to mind at all
the blush on the cheeks♪
♪Amid laughter and talk,
longing becomes words on the paper♪
♪From now on, the delicate thoughts
speak no separation♪
♪In the song that warms the world,
I only care for one person♪
♪Before the autumn rain pours,
you hold the umbrella, and I wait♪
♪Being deeply moved,
this life bears no regrets♪
♪Flowers swaying,
we listen deep into the night♪
♪I wish the prime of youth favor you,
witnessed by the sun and moon♪
=To Get Master=
(Based on The Fierce Princess by Jun Su)
=Episode 16=
Mengdie,
the first time I saw you,
I knew you were the daughter of Mr. Chu.
Unlike that other girl,
your close friend,
who doesn't have a shred
of the hero's spirit.
You're on a different level.
Mr. Bai, you overpraise me.
I'm not worthy of that.
It's fantastic you agree
to reveal the second volume
of the Xiaoyao Technique
at the Houlang Conference.
It can revitalize
and stabilize the martial world.
Everyone,
let us all raise a toast.
To Miss Chu.
- Please.
Well,
Young Master,
toast to Miss Chu.
Miss Chu,
I toast to you.
Why, you!
I asked you to toast to Miss Chu.
Why did you drink first?
Last time, Young Master
banned me
from learning Xiaoyao Technique.
This time,
he'd be awkward seeing me again.
Mengdie,
now our two sects must unite
against the demon cult.
Those things before
were all misunderstandings.
Don't take them to heart.
Young Master,
Miss Chu is one of the top figures
in today's martial world.
Offer a sincere apology.
Don't let others
think Fengyu Valley is rude.
Mr. Bai,
I have long heard that Young Master
used to do menial tasks.
You have him interact with people.
I'm afraid he may not do well.
Be patient.
Teach slowly.
Exactly.
The Young Master
seems
a far cry
from the usual bunch
Fengyu Valley
picks.
Everyone, m-may I praise him like this?
I'm just a martial artist,
not good with words.
Not good with words.
A hero's past doesn't matter.
Plenty of legends
also started from menial tasks.
I have high hopes for him.
Baili,
after a few days of parting,
you still appear so reserved.
Why don't I just toast
to you with this one?
Young Master, hurry up.
I apologize for earlier.
Everyone,
I'm not feeling well.
I'll take my leave.
Take your time drinking.
Take your time.
Come on.
Gentlemen, let me offer
another cup to you.
Miss Chu,
I have long heard
of your extraordinary spirit.
Seeing you today,
you're every bit as strong as they say.
By the way,
why isn't Mr. Chu
here today?
My father locked himself away
for cultivation.
You are hurrying to the banquet, right?
It's in the front hall.
Please.
That's right.
Then I'll go ahead.
Catch you another day.
Please.
- You're...
- Chu Mengdie. Father's not here.
The banquet is in the front hall.
Please.
Thank you.
Miss Chu.
Stop. The banquet is in the hall.
It seems Miss Chu
is not in a good mood today.
It's you?
It's been a long time.
What?
Is it like one day apart
feels like three years?
You
miss me that much, huh?
The city wall
isn't as thick as your skin.
Stop with the sweet talk.
Given the current situation
of Jingyun Manor,
the second volume
is one of your few bargaining chips.
You're actually planning
to bring that out
at the Houlang Conference?
My father established Jingyun Manor
to guard the second volume.
He didn't want it
to fall into the clutches
of the demon cult
or anyone with bad intentions.
With the demon cult back,
I must bring out the manual
and do my part
for the martial world.
It's the least I can do
to honor my father's wishes.
I figured
I didn't need to say much about this.
But then I realized,
it's understandable
that someone like Mr. Nan
would have doubts.
You are forthright and straightforward.
I truly admire you.
However,
since you've got
the second volume of Xiaoyao Technique,
it's about time
you gave back that jade pendant
you stole from me, right?
Senior,
do you really have no worries at all?
What should I be worried about?
The future of Fengyu Valley.
You wouldn't believe it.
At the banquet today,
Baili Xingchen
didn't even know how to make small talk.
I had to step in and ease the tension.
During the banquet,
a bunch of people
were throwing shade
at us from Fengyu Valley.
Baili Xingchen is just mediocre.
He's practically a fool.
In the future,
he might mess everything up.
You think he is a fool,
but I see
his naivety and honesty
as strengths.
What makes you say that?
Baili Xingchen
is simple-minded,
just focused on training.
He's the perfect pawn.
More importantly,
his relationship
with Nan Chuimeng and Chu Mengdie
is unusually close.
At that point,
a gentle push will be enough.
But...
With his current martial arts,
at the Houlang Conference,
it's a risky bet.
Since you know,
turn things that are uncertain
into things that are certain.
I got it.
(Golden Goblet Restaurant)
It's a pity
that the flowering season is over.
Go ahead.
You need my help, right?
Shameless.
By the way,
Mengdie is now in Fengyu Valley, right?
You told me she was in trouble
at the manor last time.
How is she now?
She is fine now.
Now, she is
the head of Jingyun Manor.
Besides,
she's got the manual
as a prize for the Houlang Conference.
She is in the limelight.
I've been flipping through
the Jianghu News.
It mentions that almost half
of the martial world
will attend the Houlang Conference.
With the Xiaoyao Technique as the prize,
shouldn't you participate too?
Snag that top spot.
This is my most legitimate way
to reclaim the manual.
Then I will cheer you on
from the sidelines.
Song'er,
there's something
I'd like you to do for me.
I said I would cheer you on.
No.
I want you to sign up
and compete with me.
Are you crazy?
Me? I don't even know martial arts.
I'd just be making a fool of myself.
You'll be there with your husband.
We will be a perfect couple.
In the future,
it will be a wonderful tale.
Let me think about it.
Young Master,
Young Head invites you.
Who is Young Head?
Young Head of Jingyun Villa,
Chu Mengdie.
Oh, I see. I'm busy.
I'll go back.
Tell the Young Head,
the world is vast.
See her if fate allows.
W-What's wrong?
My lady doesn't like being refused.
Wait.
You... Wait.
Listen to me!
D-Don't be impulsive.
I always think carefully.
I am never impulsive.
Wait.
If you're not being impulsive,
what's this?
Baili, tell me.
Before, I was Lin Shu.
You took care of me well
in Fengyu Valley.
Now, I am Chu Mengdie.
You publicly banned me
from the Xiaoyao Technique.
I get it.
You just became the Young Master
and had no choice.
But now our two sects have allied.
Why do you still avoid me?
It's
also arranged by Fengyu Valley?
That's right.
I did it on purpose.
Just as you said,
you are no longer Lin Shu.
We were once like buddies,
but you know the buzz from the banquet.
People think we're poles apart now.
Hanging with me
won't help your rep.
Wait!
No.
You can kill me or whatever,
but don't take off my clothes.
Originally,
we're not on those terms.
I never saw you being reserved
in the past.
I can stop
if you answer my second question.
If your answer satisfies me,
I may consider sparing you.
The day I left Fengyu Valley,
why weren't you there?
I...
I just wanted to make...
Make a name for myself.
Once I gain fame,
I can...
What?
Then I'll match you in status
and protect you.
Why do you want to protect me?
By taking my dagger
and going along
with my hometown's custom,
you're my husband now?
No, Miss Chu,
I-I think you've misunderstood.
I just...
Just...
Forget it!
If you want to gain fame in Jianghu,
I'll help you get there.
No need!
I've signed up
for the Houlang Conference.
Once I win,
I'll gain fame for sure.
The Houlang Conference?
I am also participating.
You think
you can win against me?
I'll compete, win or not.
If I lose,
I'm all yours.
Deal.
You said it.
You are all mine.
Alright.
I'm tired.
Let's figure out the help tomorrow.
We are in public.
Cuddling is undignified.
We're already married.
I'm just hugging my wife.
What's the issue?
Who...
Who married you?
Nan Chuimeng and Chu Mengdie did it.
Not us.
Moreover,
if you want to marry me,
you need to show real effort.
Dream on.
The predecessors said,
"The intricate dice holds red beans,
a symbol of love that pierces the bone."
Song'er,
from now on,
let's
never speak of parting,
only of staying together.
How about that?
So, you agreed?
Agreed to what?
Agreed
to compete with me tomorrow.
You bad guy!
Dare to trick me!
I thought I agreed to...
To be my wife
and grow old together, right?
You're so bad.
In this perfect moment,
shouldn't you own up
to that debt you owe me?
You...
♪Long and short,
sighs are whispers sharp as blades♪
♪East and west, hustling and drifting
in the martial world♪
♪Destined or accidental,
no one falls for me♪
♪Solitary is my middle name♪
(Golden Goblet Restaurant)
Let me take you somewhere.
Where?
This is obviously a downtown area.
How can an uninhabited shack
remain here?
Perhaps people think
the feng shui here is bad,
because it's home to the demon cult
and the villain.
What exactly happened to your family?
I heard a few words from Han Yan.
She said your parents were framed.
Xiaoyao Technique
was originally yours.
My parents were once
disciples of the Tianming Clan,
the most prestigious in Jianghu.
The Tianming Clan
is elusive
and never meddles
in the Jianghu quarrels.
When the old clan leader died,
my father
took over.
My mother,
unexpectedly, found
the powerful Xiaoyao Technique.
As a result...
They were targeted?
To protect the Tianming Clan, my parents
dismissed the disciples,
who then scattered everywhere.
We hid in the city
as ordinary people.
But the manual made us a target.
Wherever we went,
people from Jianghu,
to seize the manual,
would soon come after us.
Three of us
eventually took refuge
in the Riyue Palace.
I've never heard
such nonsense.
They're the ones
who took your family's manual.
How can they turn around
and say you're a demon cult
and call you a villain?
Perhaps that's the only way
they can keep everyone in line
and feel better.
So,
I have to get back
what belongs to my family.
Don't worry.
I'll join you
in tomorrow's competition.
We'll get it back
and hide it somewhere safe.
We'll only pass it on to our kids.
I...
Our...
Kids?
I figured
we should just destroy the manual.
Although
it's our family's treasure,
it's also what caused our downfall.
But you just said
we should give it to our kids.
Look,
this tree is so green.
Today,
the sky is quite gloomy too.
Welcome!
Nowadays,
the martial world is in turmoil,
and the villain is rampant.
It has reached
a critical situation of survival.
This Houlang Conference
is all about picking
the real new talents
of the martial world
and future pillars.
(To make Mengdie
look at me in a new light,)
(I must take first place.)
Everyone's strategic mind
and martial prowess.
Participants
need to form teams of two.
This is to test the teamwork
and coordination
of the participants.
Ultimately,
the outstanding winner
will receive
the complete volumes
of the Xiaoyao Technique,
and have the authority to lead everyone
in an assault on the Riyue Palace
to eradicate the demon cult.
This is Baili Xingchen,
Young Master of Fengyu Valley.
He'll
represent our Fengyu Valley
at this Houlang Conference.
I believe in my decision,
and I expect you
to dazzle everyone
at the Houlang Conference.
(Baili indeed
has the protagonist's aura.)
(Even Nan Wentian,)
(this shrewd old man, is on his side.)
What are you laughing at?
Nothing.
I announce the theme of the first round.
Lanterns.
Master,
you called me here
for what?
I came to check
how you're doing.
Feeling confident
about winning?
Yes!
I'm thinking,
this competition is about reputation.
I'll risk it all
to win.
Good.
That's the spirit of Fengyu Valley.
I've had my eye on you for a while.
Win this competition,
and you'll be
the future leader of martial world.
By then,
I
might even need
your protection, Leader Baili.
Master,
don't tell me you've got
incurable illness
and you won't make it long?
Master.
I just don't want
to deal with valley affairs.
I need someone to share the burden.
Keep this safe.
After the competition begins,
open it.
Master, it's...
The wheel
is repaired?
Drawing rules.
Same colored ball means same group.
It's random.
I want to exchange with you.
I need to avoid Miss Chu.
Be serious about exam rules.
Cheaters
will be expelled.
This ball is quite green.
The drawing time is up.
It's sealed
once the timer starts.
Use the clues in the room
to leave the secret room.
Each has three sticks of incense's time.
A drum will beat
after each stick burns out.
If you're still
in the room after all three,
you lose.
What is this?
(With so many participants,)
(the chances of me and Song'er
being in the same group are slim.)
(Too coincidental.)
(Did someone do this on purpose?)
Turn a blind eye and a deaf ear?
What does it mean?
Hey,
didn't you say you wanted to win?
How can you drink tea...?
You are now the wife of Young Master.
Of course, you must protect him.
It's
really unlucky
to be in the same group with you.
(No way.)
(A competition with eavesdroppers?)
Mr. Nan,
please get it straight.
The two of us are now a team.
Have you found the clue?
No.
Didn't you say you wanted to protect me?
I was drunk last night.
I was talking nonsense.
W-Why are you coming over?
You can just say it.
Baili Xingchen,
you're playing hard to get now, huh?
What a pity.
We are assigned to the same group.
Otherwise,
you'll lose this round.
Impossible.
Even if I don't ask you,
I can find the clue myself.
Don't mess up and get kicked out
before you find the clue.
I'm not that foolish.
Alright.
Then let's start.
We might be in the same group,
but if I find the clue before you,
I win.
And vice versa.
Deal!
(Exit)
Let go of me.
No way.
I won't let you solve the puzzle
and have a good time with Baili.
There is no love between us!
Meeting Baili
made me understand
what real affection is.
You're actually this cold.
Well, then,
let's just sign a divorce paper
and be done with each other.
Alright!
Just sign it.
Okay.
I've prepared the divorce paper.
Mrs. Baili, please sign here.
From now on,
you and Baili can be free and happy,
and we'll be strangers.
When did you prepare it?
(Marriage contract)
What?
We were just spooning yesterday,
and now you want to back out?
I forget.
Which part do you forget?
Need me to jog your memory?
(Li Song'er, Gu Yuan)
Alright.
The competition begins.
I've already known the answer.
What's wrong?
What's up with you two?
Nothing.
She is using me to annoy Master.
Don't come over.
If the timing were better,
I'd really want
to have a fight with you.
Having a fight isn't your style.
I...
Forget it.
If a couple can argue,
that's actually kind of lucky.
Maybe.
Despite appearing
to be just a normal house,
the placement of these lanterns
corresponds to different spots
in Fengyu Valley.
Like right here,
where I'm sitting.
The spot above my head
(From top to bottom. Guess a word.)
is linked to a place in Fengyu Valley.
The top half
of "From"
and the bottom half
of "To".
Sit!
So, in Fengyu Valley,
who is sitting all the time?
Who is sitting all the time?
Wuwei Cave.
Nan Wentian...
Master Nan.
He has been sitting in meditation
at Wuwei Cave.
So,
this represents Wuwei Cave.
And there's just this one chair,
fitting the character "Sit".
Alright, Mr. Nan.
You figured out the trick
and sat here on purpose.
So, according to this thought,
this round is easy to solve.
This is Wuwei Cave.
The first volume
is kept in the cliff
at the back of Fengyu Valley,
which is right east of the arena.
While Wuwei Cave
is southwest of the arena.
Then here
is the arena.
A painting curtain in front.
Training!
Training arena.
Here.
Mountain pomegranates, like Xi Shi,
holding two branches.
Guess a flower name.
Azalea.
Here!
Success!
Just the first round.
No need to be so excited.
Look at the question, don't...
Don't stare at me.
You say you don't want my dagger.
How come it's so precious to you?
I'm used to carrying it.
Give it back to me.
No way.
What you gave me is mine now.
Alright.
You can keep it.
And you can look
for the clue yourself.
Okay.
Sugar and plums are a rare treat.
Guess food?
Sugar and plums are...
Won't you look anymore?
No.
I give up.
Wait.
Come on!
My path to glory in the martial world
is over at the first round?
Peacock flies southeast.
Guess a word.
Peacock...
Go get the key from the flowerpot.
Here it is?
The riddles
are based on the geography
of Fengyu Valley.
I roughly deduced.
The key
is under the azalea pot.
How is it?
Have you figured it out?
Will we be eliminated
in the first round?
Impossible.
How could I be wrong?
Forget it.
You're just wrong.
I will have to do it myself.
Since there is a keyhole,
there must be another key.
Trust me. It's fine.
Failing occasionally is no big deal.
We must bravely face reality.
I won't laugh at you.
I...
Can't open it.
How could it be?
You need to put in effort.
You can't wing it.
I wing it?
You can't even help a bit,
and you dare to question me?
If you don't believe me,
go find clues yourself.
(Oh!)
(That letter.)
(Only for Baili.)
(Since I emerged from seclusion,)
(chaos has erupted.
The demon cult is running rampant.)
(In my covert investigations,)
(I found that Nan Chuimeng
is also connected with the demon cult.)
(We can't let demon cult
get the Xiaoyao Technique.)
(You must win.)
(The key to the secret room)
(is hidden in a compartment
next to the flower pot.)
(Just open it, and you'll find it.)
♪Wherever the wind blows♪
♪I share day and night with you♪
♪No matter what lies ahead♪
♪Be it clashing blades
or the mundane world♪
♪The wind blows away the fog♪
♪In a glance, I look into your eyes♪
♪Not regretting
my solitariness in this life♪
♪Never looking back
to find the way home♪
♪Why be confused about where to go♪
♪A thousand threads of love
prevent me from stepping back♪
♪As winter passes,
frost flowers penetrate the bone♪
♪With spring's arrival,
longing colors the morning dew♪
♪Fortunate to express
infinite affection to someone♪
♪Better to draw a sword and dance
and write a book for you♪
♪We can run towards the future♪
♪Better not to speak of despair
but compose for love instead♪
♪Do not fail the past♪
♪Better to be as initial as time fleets♪
♪Everything turns to dust♪
♪In this life's ups and downs,
you are the home♪