♪Long and short,
sighs are whispers sharp as blades♪
♪East and west, hustling and drifting
in the martial world♪
♪Destined or accidental,
no one falls for me♪
♪Solitary is my middle name♪
♪Spring after spring,
is the matchmaker dozing off♪
♪You knock on the door of my heart,
a burst of blossoms amazing the dusk♪
♪Touching or hurting,
we tacitly agree it's a kind of fortune♪
♪The blue and the rosy
are heaven's match♪
♪Falling into an embrace,
cherishing a moment of tenderness♪
♪No need to mind at all
the blush on the cheeks♪
♪Amid laughter and talk,
longing becomes words on the paper♪
♪From now on, the delicate thoughts
speak no separation♪
♪In the song that warms the world,
I only care for one person♪
♪Before the autumn rain pours,
you hold the umbrella, and I wait♪
♪Being deeply moved,
this life bears no regrets♪
♪Flowers swaying,
we listen deep into the night♪
♪I wish the prime of youth favor you,
witnessed by the sun and moon♪
=To Get Master=
(Based on The Fierce Princess by Jun Su)
=Episode 13=
Chuimeng,
open the door.
I have something to say.
It's fine if you don't want to see me.
I just want to ask you
if everything you said
about liking me before
still counts.
I am so upset.
How could I be Gu Yuan's insider?
I'm really the substitute
sent by Chu Mengdie.
I am fake,
but my love for you is real.
The door isn't closed?
Is Chuimeng alright?
Am I acting well?
Mr. Nan doesn't want to see you.
Since you chose to deceive him,
you deserve it.
Can I see him tomorrow?
Miss, please go back.
Nan Chuimeng is
really has nothing to do with her?
Or these two are just acting here?
She doesn't know what happened,
thinking you are acting.
My lord.
Don't practice anymore,
or the poison will worsen
each time you do.
Your life will be endangered.
Alright.
Instead of persuading here,
you'd better keep a close eye
on Song'er.
Put it down.
No, Lin...
Miss Lin.
I'll do it.
No need.
I always do it myself.
I...
Baili Xingchen.
What exactly do you want?
And my name is Chu Mengdie.
Mengdie.
Look.
You have a heroic aura,
with a dagger at the waist.
So the woman in the painting
you showed me before
was you.
And you said it was a fish I saved.
I have been
avoiding you these days,
which is truly not manly.
Returning your dagger
was the only option.
Anyway,
thank you for taking care
of me these days.
I heard
there is a rumor.
Lovers eventually...
Lovers eventually becomes...
What?
Siblings.
Yes,
siblings.
It must be referring to the two of us.
Since you have reassumed
your female identity,
from now on, I will be your brother.
My foot!
Greetings, Young Master.
Young Master.
Master asks
you to the main hall.
Baili.
Come here.
A few days ago, I said,
whoever retrieves the Xiaoyao Technique
will be the future Master
of Fengyu Valley.
Yesterday,
someone has already
handed in the manual.
He is
Baili Xingchen.
I keep
my promise.
From today,
he is the Young Master of Fengyu Valley.
Master, this...
Baili.
You will be the Young Master
from now on.
I am getting old.
I'll entrust all the affairs
in the valley
to you.
I...
Of course,
Mr. Bai will also assist you.
I hope
you will not disappoint me
in guarding the century-old foundation
of Fengyu Valley.
Master, I...
Do you still remember
the task I entrusted to you
yesterday?
Chu Mengdie.
Fengyu Valley
promised Jingyun Manor
that once you marry Nan Chuimeng,
will teach you Xiaoyao Technique.
But you had someone impersonate you,
so,
the promise
is hereby nullified.
Are you breaking the promise?
Miss Chu.
You heard it.
This is the decision
of our Young Master.
Just now, you said to keep your promise.
And now you are breaking it.
Are you men at all?
Chu Mengdie.
Forget Xiaoyao Technique.
Master
is absent due to illness,
and we will inform him.
Good,
very good.
Congratulations to you all.
Take care.
In such a hurry,
something happened to the manor?
Young lady.
A few days ago,
when we were escorting a shipment,
Gu Yuan attacked us at night,
and many disciples got injured.
Gu Yuan?
He came this time
for the second volume
of Xiaoyao Technique.
But he did not succeed,
is bound to plunder the manor again.
Now that Master is traveling,
if you do not return,
all of us
really do not know what to do.
How dare he be so bold
to attack people of Jingyun Manor!
You three, go to the inn
and stay for the night.
We will set off at dawn tomorrow.
Yes.
(Golden Goblet Restaurant)
So it is you.
Who are you looking for?
Your husband...
Don't mention him.
He's changed after we married.
If it weren't for him,
I wouldn't have been kicked out.
Whenever I think of him now,
I just...
I just want to slap him.
I get it, calm down.
I'll give you a nice room
on the second floor.
Just take a rest.
By then,
all your anger will be gone.
(No. 2 Room)
Please.
Hurry up.
Later,
my husband is about to come.
Why aren't you speaking?
It's me.
I am scared.
I thought it's a trap
from Fengyu Valley.
I know
you've really suffered
these past days.
How are you?
Song'er, did you miss me?
Not at all.
All your favorite foods.
To satisfy your cravings.
Rice wine balls, Osmanthus cakes,
and Peach blossom cakes.
Do you know
how hard it is for me in Fengyu Valley?
I put on a show every day.
They even made me live in that hut.
It was in ruins.
I don't know how Mengdie tolerated it.
Why lock the door?
Open the door.
What should I do?
Are you up to something in there?
It's nothing.
Hurry up.
What are you up to?
Coming.
Why did you lock the door?
Are you feeling guilty?
None of your business.
Xiong Jiujiu,
are you following me?
What?
I came openly.
You live in such a nice room?
None of your business.
Xiong Jiujiu,
what are you doing here?
This is your stuff.
For the sake of Miss Chu, Master Nan
asked me to tidy it up
and bring it to you.
If I were you,
I'd find a place to bury it.
Are you done?
If you're done, get lost.
You drive me away in such a hurry.
Is there someone hiding in the room?
Xiong Jiujiu,
you broke into my room at night,
and even went to my bedside.
Are you coveting my beauty?
I...
You...
What are you talking about?
Someone broke in and tried to harass me!
You!
What are you doing?
Don't...
Someone broke in...
I'll let you off today.
Don't talk nonsense.
What a coward.
How dare you to mess with me!
Be careful.
If
he comes back,
it won't be good.
Laifu.
You're becoming more and more reckless.
Sweet.
Rogue.
I just thought it over.
This is not a place to stay long.
We have to leave soon.
Okay.
You go first,
and I'll go back later.
In case they get suspicious.
Fine.
♪I travel afar♪
Alright.
Go.
I'm getting sick of it.
♪I can't get over you
and feel conflicted♪
♪I can't stop thinking about you♪
♪I have seen all the bustling world♪
It's nice if I could take Gu Yuan
back to Zuimeng City.
Without these grudges...
That's what life should be like.
The most important thing now
is to find the protagonist first.
I can't let the story
develop into a bad ending.
Han Yan,
by doing this,
am I being a bit selfish?
Why do you ask that?
What did Song'er say?
The situation is dangerous now,
yet I left her alone
to deal with
the people of Fengyu Valley.
My lord.
I believe she will understand you.
Besides,
she is close to Chu Mengdie,
already an old hand.
The protagonists in the novels
all have to go through these.
Only then
can they achieve a perfect ending.
I hope so.
Mengdie,
don't blame me
for what happened yesterday.
The rules cannot be broken.
If you don't want to teach me,
I won't force it.
I will report to my father.
He has come out of seclusion?
What a great joyous event.
I am worried
the demon cult is on the rise,
and the righteous sects are declining.
His return can
help eradicate
the demon cult.
(It seems he still fears my father.)
Mr. Nan, rest assured.
It's our duty
to eradicate the demon cult.
However, what I've been through
in Fengyu Valley
needs to be settled clearly.
I'll take my leave.
Don't you
wait for Chuimeng?
No need.
I was never really his wife.
I have no option
but to break the engagement.
Farewell.
(Fengyu Valley)
Young lady.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I ate too much breakfast.
I'm going for a walk.
Giddy up!
How similar our fates are!
We are busy and far from home.
What are you doing here?
We're a couple in name only.
But I should be here
to say goodbye to you, right?
Nan Chuimeng.
Don't let Song'er down.
You two are close,
so do not be affected because of me.
Mr. Nan,
stop dreaming.
Just say it.
What do you want?
To be honest,
Song'er asked me to come.
Now, Song'er is having
many difficulties moving around,
so she asked me
to deliver a letter to you.
She asked you
to read it after you return
to Jingyun Manor.
I warn you.
While I am away,
take good care of her
and not let her down.
Otherwise...
Rest assured.
My love for her
is sincere.
I hope so.
If I'm not to see Chu Mengdie off,
how could I let her steal
Nan Chuimeng's jade pendant?
But if Chu Mengdie has
the jade pendant and tricolor bracelet,
it means she can get the second volume.
The relationship between
Jingyun Manor
and Fengyu Valley broke down.
In order to protect the Jingyun Manor,
if she knows
the whereabouts of second volume,
she'll go get it.
To lure her to do so?
What a brilliant plan.
I understand now.
These righteous sects always
talk about benevolence and morality,
but hardly any truly adhere to them.
Prepare the horses.
We must arrive before she takes it.
- Yes.
I still have
a long way to go.
The only thing
that can accompany me is the loneliness.
Women
will only affect my attack speed.
Why do I feel a little sad?
Forget it.
Don't think about it.
Go practice.
Why are you here again?
You witch!
Last time, Nan Chuimeng protected you,
and you escaped.
Today,
I am here under the command
of Nan Feiyan
to arrest you.
Guards!
Tie her up.
Let's see who will save you.
Yes.
What are you doing?
None of your business.
I...
Don't think you're the Young Master now,
and it offers you power.
Look at you, living in this shabby hut.
Why do you
hang around with her?
You are really narrow-minded.
What's wrong with this hut?
Is it inferior?
In the past,
I also had
a luxurious life.
At that time,
I thought that there was
a hierarchy among people.
But now, I don't think so.
What distinguishes people is not wealth,
but inner qualities.
One has a good character,
so what with him
living in a humble house?
What's wrong with this hut?
Maybe Baili will become a great hero.
Don't underestimate him.
As the Young Master,
I ask you to leave now.
If you refuse,
then you violate the rules.
Senior,
I think it's going to rain.
So what?
So...
Let's go collect the clothes,
go, go, go!
Miss Li.
What you just said was good.
I'm flattered.
I'm just so talented.
Oh.
You helped me.
I'll treat you to a footbath.
Miss Li.
I had a foot bath with Lin...
With Miss Chu.
Wait.
What's that on the sole of your foot?
This?
It's my birthmark. I was born with it.
Swallowtail mark?
I've finally found you.
(Purple Aura Rises)
What a surprise.
The silly boy has become
the Young Master.
You should understand
why I let him become the Young Master.
Just pawns.
You and I
are also pawns.
Forgive me.
You exude the demeanor
of a chess master.
I am willing
to go through fire and water
for you.
You understand me the best.
Remember,
to accomplish great things,
do whatever you should.
The world is treacherous.
You and I
have to yield.
I understand that.
But as I'm getting old,
I would think of the past.
These past few days,
I've often thought of Heng.
It's all destined.
Just a sacrificial pawn.
Don't be too sentimental.
Baili.
We have to leave.
Leave?
Where?
Leave Fengyu Valley.
You saw it.
You are the Young Master now.
But have they ever truly respected you?
In fact,
this is not surprising.
After all,
I am handsome,
talented,
and hardworking.
They look down on me
because I have obtained
what they could never achieve.
That is
a noble soul.
Fool.
He is really not Baili Xingchen
from Zuimeng City.
Baili.
Ask yourself,
do you believe what you said yourself?
No.
It's normal for them to look down on me.
After all, I am just a nobody
and not standing out.
I'm lucky to get
the first volume of Xiaoyao Technique.
You're not just lucky,
but someone set you up.
What?
The conflicts in the Fengyu Valley,
and the dangers of schemes,
far exceed mere martial combat.
So I have decided
to take you out
for experience in advance.
I will be the best supporter for you
to become the Master.
But you don't know any martial arts.
Why would I go with you?
I don't know martial arts,
but I have spent time with your master,
and I'm a friend of Miss Chu,
so naturally, I understand it.
Moreover, I am skilled
in undercover work.
How about it?
We join forces,
and we'll surely achieve great things.
Makes sense.
Let's
seal the deal.
However,
I have two conditions.
Please.
After I help you become the Master,
you must remember
your master's kindness to you.
No matter what he does,
you must not become his enemy,
nor do anything to harm him.
Swear it now.
(In this way,)
(if he becomes
the leader of martial world,)
(the battle between
Gu Yuan and martial world)
(can be avoided then.)
I swear,
in this life,
I will never harm my master,
no matter what he does.
If I violate,
may I be dead.
What about
the second one?
Young Master.
Why are you here?
It's too dangerous for you. Come in.
(Gathering of Scholars)
Please leave.
We have cut ties.
Stop acting.
It's not dangerous now,
because I am now the wife
of Young Master.
Baili.
Master.
♪Wherever the wind blows♪
♪I share day and night with you♪
♪No matter what lies ahead♪
♪Be it clashing blades
or the mundane world♪
♪The wind blows away the fog♪
♪In a glance, I look into your eyes♪
♪Not regretting
my solitariness in this life♪
♪Never looking back
to find the way home♪
♪Why be confused about where to go♪
♪A thousand threads of love
prevent me from stepping back♪
♪As winter passes,
frost flowers penetrate the bone♪
♪With spring's arrival,
longing colors the morning dew♪
♪Fortunate to express
infinite affection to someone♪
♪Better to draw a sword and dance
and write a book for you♪
♪We can run towards the future♪
♪Better not to speak of despair
but compose for love instead♪
♪Do not fail the past♪
♪Better to be as initial as time fleets♪
♪Everything turns to dust♪
♪In this life's ups and downs,
you are the home♪