It's not that.
I never...
Si-won.
You do stab in the back hard, don't you?
You said you wouldn't submit it.
What an ass.
You, come here.
I said, come here.
You used my laptop, didn't you?
I never submitted my work.
Then it must be you. Am I wrong?
You know...
Why wouldn't you submit it
when you've already written it?
Hey!
I just wrote it when I was young.
Why would you do that?
Si-won.
Congratulations! I read
an article about you too!
Come back here. Hey!
Cha Si-yeong!
Open the door.
You're so dead.
Knock it off. Just enjoy
your success, dude!
BLUEMING
COLORED BY YOU
I never even once changed your diapers
when you were young.
You've said that a million times already.
I'm just saying this because
you should know.
Do you like your dad?
When did I say I like him?
You sometimes defend your dad.
No way.
You shouldn’t seen how shameless he was.
You know I did my very best
to protect you guys, right?
He's an ass who has
zero sense of responsibility.
It makes me furious just
by thinking about him.
Are you okay?
I heard Si-won won the contest.
Professor Min talked about you
in her lecture.
- I'm so proud of you.
- Congratulations.
Tell me if you want me
to be one of your staffs.
You can tell me too.
Next time I have a question regarding
production support, I'll ask you.
Can you share your scenario?
We're not worried thanks to Da-woon.
Thank you, Da-woon.
Do you think Da-woon's read the script?
EP 06. THE WORST DAY
Let's grab lunch.
We can have dinner too.
Sounds cool.
Hey, Cha Si-won.
Is that you?
Sorry?
We took a bet. This is you, isn't it?
This is him! I was right!
What? Is this really you?
How is this person you?
I took a bet, and I'm lost.
Hey, you owe me 50,000 won.
Jeez.
Does this even make sense?
I can't believe this.
Where did you get this picture?
I heard there's a girl who went to
the same school with you, an Art major.
She's a friend of Hwan Yun-jeong
Go ask her.
I heard the commentary
will be released today.
Why don't you check that out too?
Si-won.
Congratulations.
I've forgotten about this.
It's terrible to be
the subject of a rumor.
I forgot about it for a while.
You should treat us!
Although it was the first
production support business,
it was great to see how capable
the students were at Bareum University.
The Grand Prix Winning work,
"my running bike,"
portrays a boy finding himself
in a green, yet confident manner.
And this was done at the unique pace of
the director in a fresh take.
As mentioned at
the intention of production,
the story was autobiographical
which made the film sincere.
Now that the commentary is released,
you shouldn't worry anymore.
Right.
Why not show people your scenario?
Exactly.
I should've submit mine too
so it's easy to make an excuse.
I was going to write Da-woon's name
as a director of photography.
I should've submitted mine too.
But none of it would make any difference.
And it's not like you did
anything wrong, Si-won.
Exactly.
By the way, did you see that?
Some strange picture of you
was on the Intranet.
I saw that too.
Who cares about that? We're
college students now.
Who would upload something like that?
It's so freaking childish.
The end of the term is coming
so you shouldn't be bothered.
Si-won, are you okay?
Did you ask your parents?
It's not true, is it?
I haven't met them yet. They're so busy.
Why don't you call them up?
You never know.
Okay, I will.
It must have been so hard for you.
Everyone will see me differently now.
Why would they? Don't think that way.
I know none of that's true,
and I shouldn't be
this worked up about it.
But I haven't felt
this way for a long time.
Si-won,
like the girls said, if you show
your scenario, everyone will see...
You don't know that.
- Huh?
- You've never been my shoes.
So don't tell me what to do.
You'll never know how I feel.
Have you seen this picture?
Have you seen it?
Hey, let me see the next one.
Yu-jin, I know you went to the same
elementary school, but that's too much.
Hey.
What?
Stop acting like you're the center
of the universe.
What are you on about?
Da-woon brought your bike here.
- Hello.
- I'm shooting a film.
I know.
Is it urgent?
It's...
About the production support business...
Oh, the commentary? You asked
me to write it, didn't you?
Don't you like it?
Yes, I do.
I like it.
Okay, let's meet the day
after tomorrow when I have time.
I'd better get going now.
Where are you?
I'm on my way to your house. Let's talk.
Why would you run?
You said you were on your way here.
I heard you brought my bike home.
How did you crack the password?
I just put your birthday.
Why on earth do you like me?
You knew.
I didn't think you knew.
Gosh.
Take a look at this.
What do you think about this boy?
Tell me honestly.
He's so cute.
Don't lie. Give it to me straight.
I'm being honest.
He's so cute.
Look at his chubby cheeks.
That's me.
That's me, the fatty.
How cute.
Didn't you see it?
It was on the Intranet.
What?
I don't know. Things are so messed up.
I hate me of that time,
and it popped out suddenly.
And I didn't even think about releasing
the scenario since it's autobiographical,
and it happened so quick.
On top of everything, I even said
horrible stuff to you.
Aren't I pathetic?
I don't know why, but I
don't have confidence in myself.
I have a feeling that people won't like me
once they get to know me.
People tend to have preconceived views.
Once they find out about
my pathetic family story,
they'll pity me thinking I had
unfortunate childhood
rather than seeing me as who I am.
I'm sorry.
I know it must have been hard for you,
but I just thought about myself.
No, it's okay.
I'm okay.
I know how hard it must have been for you.
I'm sorry.
I can't change the pathetic side of me.
I've been pathetic my whole life
that it must just show.
I want to be cool like you.
Cheer me up more.
I was worried that you
wouldn't like me anymore.
And I don't like French
Nouvelle Vague at all.
That stuff is harsh and it doesn't
give me any joy.
I admire that stuff, but I find
"Mean Girls" a lot more fun.
- I'll sleep over at your place today.
- What? Hang on.
Can I not?
COUPON FOR VISITS TO MY HOUSE