Say something!
What's the point of living like this?
Nothing changes. You don't mean
anything to me now.
Do you want me to make a scene at
your office for you and that woman?
- Shall I do that?
- Go ahead.
Do whatever you want. Jeez!
- Hey! Where are you going?
- Gosh.
Your kids are just nine and ten years old.
What will they do if you leave like this?
My mom didn't divorce my dad even after
she found out that he was cheating on her.
Mommy is...
All I have is you now.
We'll be fine.
Let's make sure we don't get looked down.
Don't cry, mommy.
Mommy.
I have this one and this one.
Check this out.
I have the same one at home.
It's nothing fancy.
Is anyone worried about anything?
This is a worry-doll that takes away
your worries. Isn't it awesome?
My parents gave it to me
as my birthday present.
My mom told me to be nice to you.
To me? Why?
Your dad moved out, didn't he?
- That's not true.
- He's moved out.
My mom said, your dad left
to live with someone else.
Yu-jin and I heard everything.
Didn't we, Yu-jin?
Yeah.
Are you stupid? Stop looking at me,
you stupid gorilla.
Gorilla.
Let's go.
I had to be flawless
not to be looked down.
BLUEMING
COLORED BY YOU
ABOUT 3650 DAYS LATER
I had to be flawless
not to be looked down.
Here's the lecture plan for the year.
Check your team members.
CHA SI-WON, HYEONG DA-WOON
It's about creating a space,
looking into it, and make a storyline.
As you know, the scene of the scenario
is one of the most important factors
and you can think of it as the foundation.
Okay,
your assignment is to take pictures hourly
so you become aware of the difference
of the sunlight by the location of the sun.
Your team members are...
I'll make teams according to
your name order.
INTRODUCTION TO PRODUCTION ASSIGNMENT:
SUBMISSION OF 5-MINUTE OF SHORT FILM
So I made the teams randomly.
You're probably sick of having teams
under your name orders.
So I made them with random choices.
Jeez, Si-won and Da-woon are team again.
You must be fate.
Hey, Do Ba-wu, what are you drinking?
What do you want to drink, guys?
It's too much hassle to pay
a person by person.
It's on me this time. Place your orders.
Then...
- I'll just have iced Americano.
- Iced Americano.
- Thank you.
- I'll have iced Americano too.
I'll have the same.
How about you?
I'll have green tea frappucino
with an added shot
and have espresso whipping cream on top.
Sure.
I'm just kidding. I'll have
iced Americano too. Thank you.
EP 02. HOW TO SURVIVE AS A HUNK
Can I have five glasses of iced Americano?
Cheers!
- It's our first time to drink together.
- Right.
- Da-won is so caring.
- Si-won!
Excuse me.
- Oh, you're here.
- I know, he's so cool.
- Sorry, we're late.
- Don't be.
Let's see. Come this way.
- Hey, Da-woon.
- Yeah?
- I heard you're the top in the department.
- The top?
Who said there isn't a hunk
in the department of film studies?
Here he is. Jeez.
Why are you all about the look?
- Hey.
- Whatever.
Shut it.
What do you mean 'shut it?'
Don't you think you're being too harsh?
You shouldn't think like that.
Quentin Tarantino?
Wow, you have that vibe.
Who do you like?
I don't know yet.
Maybe it's because I haven't watched
a lot of movies.
I don't have a favorite film director.
- Si-won.
- Huh?
You're the leader of the class.
Don't you think you should visit
others' tables too?
Yes, why don't you do that?
You think so?
Okay. Excuse me.
What did he say? He's such a boomer.
What's wrong with hair?
Here comes the leader of the class.
Here he is.
Hey, you leader.
- He even brought his glass.
- Of course.
What were you talking about?
You looked like you were having fun.
- Us?
- Yeah.
What did we talk about?
We talked about movies.
We've been trashing about that.
What?
That senior guy at the orientation.
He said if it was annoying when people
ask what movies we like.
Isn't it natural to wonder
about that though?
What kind of movies do you like?
You can tell what kind of person you are
by the movies you like.
I like French nouvelle vague.
I like directors like François Truffaut
and Jean-Luc Godard.
- You must know a lot of movies.
- Not really.
You definitely are the leader material.
You're so cool.
Why do you like those movies?
You know, I just like them.
They're very realistic and cynical.
Which one's your favorite?
"A bout de souffle"
- "A bout de souffle?"
- There is.
- Yeah.
- What's that?
What do you like then?
Me?
I don't have a favorite yet.
Thank you.
I'm not going to tell you.
Why not?
Are you pissed at me?
Here we go.
Shall we make a toast?
I love to drink.
Are you okay?
Did you throw up?
Leave me alone.
Isn't that my bag?
Oh, yes.
You look like you drank a lot.
Why don't you go home first?
I'm not drunk.
You think you know everything.
You don't want others to see
you drunk, do you?
It looked like you cared about
how others see you.
Are you okay? Hey.
Yeah.
I knew something was fishy about you.
They should've seen this side of you.
You know what?
You...
There's something fishy about you.
What did you say?
You made me come to the place
you work on purpose.
It's like you wanted to show me
that you are superior.
What?
It's like that last Tuesday too.
You saw me in the lecture room but
you didn't even bother to say hello.
But when the others greeted me,
you then greeted me.
Last Tuesday?
Tuesday, on the day of the semester
general meeting.
No, I mean, at the beginning
of the semester.
You're off your face.
And you always look down on me.
I do?
You're a scary guy, Hong Da-woon.
Okay.
- You're awesome.
- That's not what I meant.
I know you're awesome,
but I don't' want us to be close.
I find you scary.
You know what I mean, yeah?
Did you laugh again?
It's not that.
Sorry, I did laugh.
You find me pathetic.
I've been thinking that you
and I are so alike.
I didn't think you'd feel
pressured around me.
Oh, when you're around people,
they feel pressured?
Jeez.
You're so narcissistic.
Hey,
you are born with everything
at the tip of your hands
and loved by your parents so much.
You're the exact type that I hate.
I...
No matter how hard I try,
there are things that I can't achieve.
There are things I just can't...
Are you crying? You're so drunk.
Okay, easy there.
- Get up.
- Because of you, my 20s are ruined.
Let's go. I know. Take it easy.
Let go of me.
Aren't they Si-won and Da-woon?
Can you drive first?
They must have been drunk a lot.
Where are we going?
Where am I?
You didn't tell me where you live.
It's so hot.
You'll get cold once you fall asleep.