[English subtitles are available]
What are you doing outside when it's so cold?
I'll freeze to death if I keep sleeping here.
Let's go now.
Why is it so dark in the morning?
It's as dark as my future.
What's wrong with your future?
Look ahead. The sun is coming out.
There're only good things coming your way from now on.
The sun is so bright.
Yes.
You don't have to go to the office today, right?
Yeah, it's the weekend.
That's nice. I'll have to get to my restaurant right after a shower.
You must be tired.
Did I upset you?
No, not at all.
We're really fine, right?
Of course.
I'll call you again.
Okay.
No matter what, I shouldn't have kissed him.
Dohoon, come to your senses.
Gosh. What a mess.
Gosh.
It's already 10 a.m.?
[Lee Yoonsoo]
Hello? What is it?
I'm sorry to trouble you,
but I didn't turn off the stove before I left home.
Can you take a look for me?
Okay.
It was a close call.
Gosh.
Gosh, thank you so much.
Come to the restaurant for dinner tonight.
I'll make you something delicious.
[Dohoon-
It was tender inside. He ate with his eyes closed. No special reaction.]
It was tender inside. He ate with his eyes closed.
No special reaction.
Was my feedback so insincere?
He liked sweets when he was in college too.
The client didn't like the proposal, so get to the office right away.
Gosh.
How can they change their mind so suddenly?
When it's cold, it's natural to want some hot soup.
The delicious meat stock made with soybean paste
and dried cabbage that's in season during the kimchi-making period
make up the perfect combination
to make the dried cabbage short rib soup
that can help you easily overcome the cold.
Wow, it's so charming.
This is the best food I've ever had.
I should've ordered an upsized portion.
I'm not lying. It's really good.
Right?
The door's opening.
Isn't it good?
It's the weekend. This is too much.
I finally got my wife's permission for a day out.
I was practically rolling down the mountain
to get here.
I was in a Pilates session just now.
I finally decided to enroll in the class today and this happens.
Luckily, I finished the first half of my game.
Mr. Jung. You're dressed casually too.
All my clothes are in the laundry.
Ms. Sung should be dressed as usual.
I guess she only works at home too,
wearing her usual black turtleneck.
Wow, everyone's here early.
Mr. Han is here. I'll go get him.
Gather in the meeting room.
Hello.
You must have been enjoying your hobbies.
How idle.
Mr. Han.
What is the chairman not satisfied with?
About the proposal you sent me via email,
it looked fine on the phone
but when we saw it on the big screen in the meeting room,
it didn't look good.
It looked familiar too.
Yes, that's right.
If you want to subvert the cliché,
you have to reference the cliché to a certain extent...
Don't you think I know that?
The problem is that even the portions meant to subvert the norm felt familiar.
What's with his tone?
We don't even know each other. Why is he talking down to me?
I feel like it's not enough. It doesn't have a punch.
It's like it can be more interesting,
but it ended before anything interesting happened.
That's why it has been bugging me.
You're right.
Since I already opened it, should I have just read everything?
It's really bugging me.
Previously, I mentioned that it should be meme-able
but also be elegant,
in hopes that you would
improve upon your original idea.
But I think it didn't meet my expectations.
I've already emphasized that we need to make it more elegant.
Please give us more time
to revise it according to your critique and submit it again.
It's not like this is our first time working together,
so of course we trust you.
I won't set a deadline,
but try to send an improved version to me as soon as possible.
Yes, sir.
I'll get going then.
What? Is this all?
No.
I can't let you waste your precious weekend, right?
Enjoy your own hobbies.
Take care.
Come up with some ideas, okay?
I have to go now. Let's talk again next Monday.
Why did he call us over for this?
It's enough to discuss it through a phone call on Monday.
Hana. Mr. Han did it on purpose.
Darn it.
Ms. Choi!
Didn't I tell you to wait until I get new employees?
All the projects are going well and we're so busy right now.
How can I accept your resignation at a time like this?
It's been almost a month since I told you about my resignation.
Besides, from my perspective,
I'm already resigning.
Do I have to take into account everything about how the company operates?
Please agree to my resignation by next Monday.
Babe.
That's why I asked you to stay until this project is over.
Now I've realized that you're quite irresponsible.
Ms. Choi.
You've heard that, right?
She's so loud.
You're the one whom I'm most sorry towards.
But you've been doing well,
so I feel at ease about resigning.
Why are you suddenly quitting?
You can lead the project well even without me, right?
Good luck.
Mr. Jung, did I interrupt you?
No.
After shouting, I feel much better.
It's nice.
So this is how you relieve stress on your own.
Here, Mr. Jung.
Thank you.
This isn't mint chocolate latte.
You said you didn't like it,
so I bought you a hot Americano.
I didn't really like
mint chocolate latte at first,
but thanks to you, I've had it several times.
And now, sometimes, I sort of crave it.
That's how everyone falls in love with the mint chocolate flavor.
Sangwoo. Did you like mint chocolate latte from the beginning?
I went on a trip to Venice in Italy.
There was a cafe called Florian.
I heard that Casanova always got the mint chocolate latte there.
That's why I tried it too, and guess what?
I felt like I could relate to Casanova.
So you're saying that you're quite the playboy like Casanova?
Let's get back to business.
Did Ms. Choi betray you?
How are you able to change the topic so quickly?
I wish she had told me earlier.
I'm quite disappointed.
If I were you, in such a situation,
I would have fought with her just now.
You seem very mature.
You can control your emotions well and you're always calm.
No, you're wrong.
I don't get angry easily
because I'm exhausted
and in my power-saving mode.
Was the food good?
Yes, thank you.
Now that the weather's cold, the food tastes even better.
I drank yesterday
and this soup was perfect for nursing a hangover.
Thank you.
Excuse me, but can you take a photo with us?
Of course.
Come on.
Okay.
-Thank you.
Please come often when we open officially.
Yes, we will.
Thank you.
Bye.
You're here. It's cold, right?
It's cold outside but it's warm in here.
They're customers.
Your outfit is so cute.
It's a long story.
You look good in that too.
-Have a seat.
-It's okay.
You want to eat right away, right?
Yes. Shall we eat together?
Okay. I want to eat too.
Looks good.
Yoonsoo.
Joowon.
Is there food for me too?
We were just about to eat. Come sit down.
He's Lee Joowon, a part-timer at the restaurant next door.
Introduce yourself properly to him. He was my college senior.
Hello.
I'm Lee Joowon, who comes here often to get free food.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
You must come here often.
He often makes new dishes here
and I come here sometimes to try them and give him feedback.
That's how we became close.
The name of this dish is dried cabbage short rib soup.
It's also known as the Energizing Meal.
Short rib soup sure is energizing.
Let's eat.
Thank you for the food.
You can't call this just food.
It's a masterpiece.
Yoonsoo.
Are you going to keep creating masterpieces?
My appetite is raging because of you.
What should I do?
He exaggerates a lot.
I'm not exaggerating.
It's unbelievable how deep and refreshing this soup is.
Even with just a sip, I already feel like I'm full of energy.
And how did you
make the short ribs so tender?
Wow. It's amazing.
What about you? Do you like the food?
Wow, it's so charming.
This is the best food I've ever had.
I'm not lying. It's really good, right?
I thought he was Baek Jongwon from the show Alley Restaurant.
Right! The beef is so thick and juicy...
Come on. The beef was boiled, not grilled.
You're exaggerating by saying it's juicy.
Right?
What a punk.
Fantastic.
This is the Energizing Meal,
but it feels like he was the only one energized.
He just went on and on.
He is indeed talkative and noisy,
but he's kind.
He's quite helpful to me.
He must come here quite a lot.
Sometimes.
You should bring your colleagues here for a meal sometimes too.
Okay.
But I don't really like that that guy comes here often.
What? Are you jealous?
I don't think I can provide feedback as well as he can,
so don't go to all the trouble to cook for me.
I enjoy cooking for you.
I cook for you because you like my food.
It makes me happy too.
I told you before,
that you can refuse if you don't like it.
You can eat now.
Thank you for the food.
This will taste different from what you ate during the day.
I remember now.
What?
Although you make common home-cooked dishes,
it tastes different from other food.
It feels like there's some special ingredient in your food.
Even I don't understand what I'm saying,
but now, I don't want to eat food made by others.
Let's finish this up quickly
and go have a drink at my place.
It's the weekend. Let's drink to celebrate.
It seems like the pot was really burnt. There's still a burnt smell at home.
If it weren't for me, the consequences would have been unimaginable.
Thank you so much,
but can you spray this for me?
I'll go wash up first.
Okay.
But I have to spray it on you first.
Chefs can't help it that they smell of food.
I'll go wash up quickly.
Okay.
We're close enough for me to read it.
No.
This is still something private after all.
But I'm sure it'll be okay to just take a look.
Dohoon. Don't do anything that goes against your conscience.
I'm sorry,
but can you get me a towel from the drawer?
Okay.
Yoonsoo, I brought you a towel.
I brought you a towel.
What are you doing?
If you don't like it, just refuse.
Let me explain. It's...
Dohoon.
I'm sorry, but can you take me home?
Who are you, you scumbag?
Who the heck are you?