[English subtitles are available]
Yoon Soo, I brought you a towel.
I brought you a towel.
What are you doing?
Dohoon.
If you don't like it, just refuse.
[Choi Minjoon]
Give me a minute.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Were you toying with me?
Toying with you? What do you mean?
You said you didn't like me at first,
but then I reciprocated to your flirting...
So is it fun toying with me?
Let me explain. It's...
I don't want to hear your explanation.
Let's talk another time. I'm leaving.
Dohoon.
Every time I smell the scent of lilac,
I think of someone's birthday.
You've finished your improved proposal, right?
Yes, Ms. Sung.
I just sent it to you via email.
Send an email of it to Mr. Han with an additional explanation of the concept.
Yes.
I think they'll accept it,
so you can start working on the storyboard.
Yes, I will.
Mr. Jung.
Why do you look so pale?
Are you sick?
No, I'm fine.
Just finish up with what you're doing and go home.
Yes.
Ms. Choi.
Your resignation has been approved today.
Thank you, Ms. Sung.
You can pack up and clear your desk by today, right?
Of course.
I've started clearing my desk since a long time ago.
There's only this one left.
Ms. Sung.
When we meet somewhere else,
I'll greet you warmly too.
Mr. Jung, you know how I feel, right?
Right?
This isn't the only company in this world.
Don't work too hard and devote all your energy here.
If you find a better workplace, move on.
Best of luck.
Mr. Jung.
You don't look well. Are you okay?
I didn't sleep well last night, so I think I caught a cold.
It seems like you have a fever too. Did you take some medicine?
I took one.
Shouldn't you get some rest today?
Sangwoo.
How about this? Let's have dinner together tonight.
It's just right. I've been feeling bad about constantly postponing our meal anyway.
Let's have some drinks too.
Mr. Jung.
You said you'd buy me drinks last time.
Order whatever you want.
Wow.
I want... Dakgangjeong.
I want stir-fried pork belly.
Or grilled mackerel.
Is there nothing you want to eat?
Let me order for you.
-Cheers!
Mr. Jung.
I think you're drunk after just one glass of soju bomb.
Right. Hana is not a good drinker.
I'm not drunk.
Hana, are you okay?
Not at all.
Why is nothing going my way?
What do you mean?
Sangwoo, can I like you?
No, there's someone I like.
See? Nothing is going my way.
She seems drunk.
Give her some time. She'll sober up soon.
Mr. Jung, you must like drinking.
No.
But one should drink whenever it calls for it.
Only then can one relieve stress.
By the way, did you know that Hana was fond of you
since the first time she saw you?
Yes, I sort of felt it.
Oh, you have good instincts.
Normally, the person involved never realizes it.
Was there anyone who had a crush on you?
You mean at work?
Even if there was, I wouldn't have known.
I'm a little slow.
It always turned out
that there were a few people around me who liked me.
The problem is that I always realized it too late.
The problem was always that.
I can't figure it out no matter how hard I try.
I don't know why someone would like me.
I think I know why.
When I look at you,
I want to care for you.
It's like you trigger one's maternal love.
Is that why he cooks for me?
What?
Nothing.
You just got here and you already have a ton of work to do.
Someone also quit, so the atmosphere is a bit strange.
You probably don't know this, but I feel reassured thanks to you.
I'll treat you to a lot of delicious food.
So please don't quit.
I won't quit either.
It seems like he isn't back yet.
Aren't you drinking too much?
You're right.
I always go over my limit whenever I drink.
It's a waste to not drink this,
so let's go after this glass.
Cheers.
I think you would have the answer to this.
Has it been often for you where friendship developed into romance?
Yes.
That's usually how I got into relationships.
Has there been a time where your lover was still entangled with their ex?
Yes, of course.
How did you overcome it?
There's nothing to overcome.
In my opinion, there are only three situations.
You just need to be aware of where the other person's focus is.
Whether they're over their ex,
trying to get over their ex,
or they're just a two-timer.
You'll just have to act according to the other's focus.
Then what should we do in each situation?
If they're over their ex,
then it's simple.
If they're trying to forget their ex,
then be good to them so that they'll forget their ex.
If they're two-timing,
then kill them.
If not, you've to be mentally prepared for whatever might come.
That's a great analysis.
Either make them forget their ex,
or kill them. Okay.
I'm going to kill you.
You deserve to die.
Aren't we going for a second round?
-No.
-Let's go for a second round.
Please take care of her, sir.
-Yes.
-Let's go for a second round.
A second round...
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Mr. Jung.
I told you I have a crush on someone, right?
I invited him to dinner so many times
but he kept rejecting me.
But he suddenly asked me to drink with him today.
Isn't this a good signal?
Then it must be one of the three situations you mentioned.
Either he likes you,
or he's starting to have feelings for you
and is interested in dating you,
or he doesn't like you
but there's no one to hang out with.
What if it's the third situation?
Either stay away from him,
or just let him use you.
Come on. I doubt you like someone who's bad.
So you must be in the flirting stage.
Sangwoo, how are you like in a relationship?
Me? I've never thought about it before.
I think I'm like a woodcutter.
I chop the same tree with my ax relentlessly until it comes down.
You're really manly during times like this.
Sangwoo, I'm sorry,
but can you take me home?
-Alone, I...
-Gosh.
Don't worry.
Mr. Jung, which unit do you live in?
Unit 302, right?
Yoonsoo lives in Unit 302.
I live in Unit 301.
Park Sangwoo.
The person who made you Dakgangjeong is in Room 302.
And you live in Unit 301.
He's not my friend. That jerk...
Mr. Jung, what's the password?
Um... 1004.
1004... give me a moment.
I feel so sick.
The door is open. Mr. Jung, go in.
I'm going to fall...
Are you okay?
Mr. Jung.
I told you I have a crush on someone, right?
The person I like... is you.
I liked you since the first time I saw you.
I know that as colleagues who meet every day,
if I confess like this,
it's inappropriate and will make things awkward between us.
But even so, I'm confessing...
because once I confess, the answer becomes clear...
whether the other person will accept me or not.
Who are you, you scumbag?
Who the heck are you?
Who are you?
I'm his neighbor. Who are you?
You're mistaken. I'm his colleague.
Mr. Jung is drunk so I just took him home.
If he's a colleague, you should've left after bringing him home.
You clearly were trying to kiss him earlier.
You're rude.
Don't just say whatever comes to your mind.
I saw you leaning closer to his face just now.
Mr. Jung seems to be having a fever, so I just wanted to check his temperature.
When did he start having a fever?
He didn't look well since he came to work today.
Did he take his medicine?
How would I know about that?
I think he took one.
Are you Yoonsoo?
It's rude to ask such a question since it's our first meeting.
But let me ask you.
You're not two-timing Dohoon
and your ex, right?
I don't know what you heard,
but it's between us, so stay out of it.
If you keep stressing Dohoon out because of your ex,
I won't just sit back and watch.
Act properly and don't confuse him.
Take good care of him.
Why did you drink so much when you're not feeling well?
What a fool.
You should eat something before taking medicine.
Right, I should make some porridge.
80% of abalone's nutrition is in the organs.
But if you don't cook it well, the porridge will smell fishy.
I realized that the best seasoning for porridge
is sincerity.
The sincerity that stems from the belief
that he'll recover after finishing a bowl of the porridge.
I hope that my sincerity would work.
I made abalone porridge. Get up and have some.
I don't want to.
That won't do, you need to eat it before taking medicine.
I'm too tired to even talk.
Then just open your mouth. I'll feed you.
Why? Is it hard to swallow?
It's hot.
I'm sorry. I'll cool it for you.
Thanks to you, I'm awake.
I'll eat it myself.
Does it smell fishy?
No, not at all.
You happened to have abalone.
Do you remember that day when I couldn't cook for you
and we had pork belly?
I bought it because I wanted to cook steamed abalone for you then.
You created the trouble and then resolved it for me.
I'm sorry.
I feel bad because it feels like you're unwell
because of me.
You can tell me the truth...
about your relationship with your ex.
You misunderstood. I have nothing to do with him.
I'll explain everything to you after you recover.
Don't be ridiculous.
Why would someone who has nothing to do with you
wait for you in front of your house?
Who? You saw him?
How did you know it was him?
The bracelet I saw in your photo album
was on that man's wrist.
So he came all the way here?
We broke up a long time ago.
It was just his wishful thinking.
You know I like you, right?
I have something to ask you.
I told you to dodge if you don't want to.
Why didn't you dodge when I kissed you?
I thought about dodging,
but my body wouldn't listen to me.
So did you like it?
You got me all drenched
and then suddenly abandoned me.
When I saw the name on the phone,
I left without realizing it.
I'm sorry.
I've something to ask you too.
You once said that whenever you smell the scent of lilac,
you would think of someone's back and birthday.
You were referring to your ex-boyfriend, right?
His birthday is in spring, right?
Your birthday is in November, right?
Yes, how did you know?
I think it was during the final exams period in November.
Do you remember the stairs that lead to the Student Hall
at our college?
November?
Didn't you see me for the first time in class during the spring semester?
I first met you in November the year before that.
No, that's before I returned to school.
I'm right. You were in your military uniform.
The final exams period is so torturing.
How many subjects do you have left?
Three.
Three?
I only have one subject left.
Seriously.
But I got an F grade for three subjects.
Gosh.
Hey, I'm going to buy cigarettes. Wait for me.
Okay, go ahead.
Okay. Wait for me.
Okay.
Hello, mom.
I'm stopping by the school. Yes.
A birthday celebration?
It's fine, I'm still a soldier.
Yes, I want to return to school.
I'm almost done with my stuff. I'll go to the hospital right after.
Okay. Let's celebrate my birthday there then.
Okay.
Mom, do you want to eat anything? I'll buy it for you.
Right. You can't eat it anyway.
I'll try to get there as soon as possible.
Okay.
You've been waiting for months.
Why can't you wait for a few more hours?
Okay, see you later.
[Jung Dohoon]
Then, I saw your name Jung Dohoon on your uniform.
The next year, I happened to be in the same class as you.
I remember that day.
That day was the day I regret the most in my life.
That day...
I should have just gone straight to the hospital instead of going to school.
Then...
You don't have to hold back in front of me.
You can cry as much as you want.
You have me by your side now.
Open your mouth.
Didn't you say Yoonsoo makes you anxious?
Yoonsoo's not that kind of person.
He's someone who can handle his own relationships well.
Feel free to come back any time if you're having a tough time.
There will always be a spot for you at my restaurant.
What? You still haven't broken up?
No, you misunderstood.
We broke up a long time ago...
He's pestering you because you're so accepting.
What an interesting situation.
So it turns out that everyone has their lover.
Sir.
Please act your age.