How did you spend the night alone with such a cold body?
what are you doing?
You`ve torn my clothes to shreds
Then I shall punish you
I really can't run away now
Actually, insomnia is something I got because I was scared
So you rely on me every night, don`t you?
I rather like the fact that, though separated by walls, we can still hear each other's presence
I love it so much
Whenever I hear you
Osian typing, I felt like
I wasn't alone
That voice made me feel safe
Shall we use music to soothe?
Then shall we give it a try?
This song is so sad
That's because you're tired
Because my insomnia and your insomnia overlapped
But whenever I feel uneasy, I can always hear the sound of your typing
That's my mind,
noisy and anxious
But whenever I feel uneasy, I can always hear the sound of your typing
Next time, I don't want to bite the thread; I want to bite your lips
If you fancy biting my lips, you`d best be careful, you know
Because I adore being captured by you