Dozens of manuscript
Countless negative reviews
The self-esteem I had built up crumbled like a sand castle
I can barely breathe at night
Now I've become someone who can't even write a single line
My life was like a stopped clock
Then I heard the ticking of an unfamiliar clock
Excuse me, could I borrow your charger?
My charger is broken
What is it?
It's type C
thank you
I'll return it to you tomorrow
It's night so I can't sleep
Oh yes
So sorry for coming so late at night
Well... yes
I'll go
excuse me
Why?
could I borrow a lighter?
Why does Oh Sian consistently write novels centred on murder?
For the dead cannot voice their displeasure at my work
then
If I die, will you write me as a criminal? Or
As a victim?
It depends on my mood
That's good
Just as you can read people's minds through words, I can do it through songs
Is that why?
I feel like your novel and my song are very similar
Would you like to express your novel with this song?
What are you talking about?