[English subtitles are available.]
Episode 6
Yah!
Whoa!
Your Highness!
Hurry!
Carry His Highness away!
[Gate of Eternal Peace]
Yah!
Great.
With these 10,000 war horses,
our troops will be unstoppable.
Feiye.
You did a great job.
I’m flattered, Your Majesty.
I just did my duty
to welcome the bride outside the capital.
However, the food supply for 10,000 horses
will be a huge expense.
I’ve given my order
to take the northern grassland
as a pasture
specially for these horses.
If so, the local residents
will have to move.
Think twice, Your Majesty.
With these horses,
the locals can be protected.
They can make a living by other ways.
No more talking about this.
It’s your big day, Your Majesty.
I’ll take my leave.
No hurry.
We rarely have free time.
Let’s take a hot spring bath and play go.
Yes.
[Grand Commandant’s Mansion]
Thanks for your hospitality, my lord.
Do you know
why I summoned you here?
You want me to kill someone
for you, right?
Given that
you asked me
to look into that case,
I presume
the one you want me to kill
could be Prince Qin.
You’re indeed insightful.
So, on the day of Prince Qin’s wedding,
I sent Yuze
to lure him
to Chief Justice
and assassinated the Chief Justice’s family.
In the end,
I passed the buck
to him.
Why did you assassinate my men?
When my mother was alive,
the Chief Justice’s family
were all loyal and faithful to me.
Why did you slaughter his family?
Tianmo.
You are
indeed competent to achieve big things.
Tianmo.
To do big things, you shouldn’t mind trifles.
I think what you did was reasonable.
That’s so-called resolution.
Thank you for your praise.
Prince Qin gets more and more
powerful.
The death of Chief Justice
won’t draw
too much attention
from His Majesty.
If you really
want to kill Prince Qin,
we can do it
without any trace.
You can get Prince Qin killed
by someone who is more powerful
than him,
in a fair and square way.
You mean
His Majesty?
Yes.
Have someone else to do the dirty work.
You will be well-protected.
No one will find it out.
So,
apparently,
it must be
someone around you.
But...
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
Do it as you said.
Uncle!
Thank you, my lord.
I will surely get it done.
Feiye.
To win the war,
you got badly injured.
All your injures
are incurred by guarding Tianning.
I feel sorry to you.
It’s my duty.
I’m a commander of Tianning
and succeeded the title of Prince Qin.
That’s what I should do.
I feel ashamed of myself
to make you
worry about me in the court.
It’s not fault at all.
You won the war.
But you’re already a lord,
with no higher title for you.
I know
you don’t like
gold or treasures.
How about
I offer you the land you conquered
and confer you as a duke?
I dare not.
I still remember the chaos of Zhou Dynasty.
I dare not to be a sinner
in the history.
Feiye.
It’s been a while
since we played go together.
Would you like to play go with me?
Yes,
I’d like to, Your Majesty.
When two armies fight,
the many winning the few,
or the strong
winning the weak are supposed to be normal.
The weak defeating the strong,
or the few defeating the many
are just tales.
Plus, other conditions
like timing, location and relations shall be met.
An occasional win
is but a fluke.
It isn’t good.
Feiye.
Do you agree?
You have a point.
Using the many against the few
is indeed advantageous.
But if you are adept at tricks
and attack
surprisingly,
leveraging the advantage,
it will be much effective.
If your power is absolutely overwhelming
to destroy
any enemy,
who dares not concede defeat?
Take Xiqiu as an example.
If my guess is right,
the letter to surrender and pay tribute
is supposed to
be on the way here.
Feiye.
That was a tough battle.
You may rest at home in the future.
There are strong enemies outside
and treacherous officials inside.
I dare not slack.
Xiqiu is defeated.
Beili must have concerns,
and is unable to
wage a war in a short term.
As for other issues,
six ministries and nine ministers will take care.
You may take a break.
People need to rest, anyway.
You have a point, Your Majesty.
I’m not good at the game.
Sorry, Your Majesty.
Never mind.
Your Highness.
It's your first day in the palace.
How come Tianhui
hasn’t come yet?
Will he not come?
Don’t worry, Madam.
Even if he’s suspicious of me,
it’s my first day here.
I’m sure
he’ll show me respect.
His Majesty comes.
-Greetings, Your Majesty.
-My respects, Your Majesty.
Long live, Your Majesty.
Rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I’ve long heard you’re gorgeous.
You do
live up to your fame.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I’m just a woman.
To get along with Your Majesty,
beautiful face is unreliable.
I’d like to be an understanding wife
who can relieve your worries
when you’re troubled.
Good.
You are kindhearted.
I’m contented.
Your Majesty.
You come late.
You must be busy with work.
I was idle
and made a pot of tea.
This is the tea Xianhao from Xiqiu.
Try it, Your Majesty.
The aroma is intoxicating.
It’s indeed good tea.
I’m glad you like it, Your Majesty.
It’s your first day in the palace.
I was busy with work
and came to you late.
Are you angry with me?
Of course not, Your Majesty.
How could I be angry?
You are the king
occupied with state affairs,
yet you still come to see me.
I’m overjoyed.
How could I be angry with you?
You’re understanding indeed.
With you by my side,
what else shall I desire?
As your concubine, it’s my duty
to relieve your worries.
As long as you have me in your heart,
I
will be contented.
Your Majesty.
It’s 11 p.m.
Is it so late?
I’ve got state affairs to attend to.
You may go to sleep early.
I’ll come to see you tomorrow.
Good night, Your Majesty.
Princess.
Will your behavior
piss off King Tianhui?
Madam.
Take it out and throw away.
He won’t be pissed off.
Although
he didn’t kill my father
directly,
he is my enemy.
How could I not bear a grudge?
I'm sure he knows that.
Well,
when the eunuch said it’s 11 p.m.,
His Majesty stared at you for a long while.
Why didn’t you keep him?
More haste, less speed.
Tianhui is suspicious by nature.
The more impatient we are,
the more suspicious he will be.
More doings, more mistakes.
The top priority now
is to eliminate his doubts first.
Then it will be much easier.
But, in my opinion,
Tianhui
was captivated
by your beauty.
Serving him by beauty won’t last long.
Also, you saw it, too.
Even though
he was captivated with my beauty,
he still chose to leave.
That is King Tianhui.
Thus,
we should be more careful.
[Gorgeous Chamber]
Let me toast you.
I feel sorry for you, Your Highness.
Chief Justice
was your man,
and had a long-standing grudge against Prince Qin.
When all his family were killed,
Prince Qin was there, too.
The evidence is solid.
Why doesn’t His Majesty punish him?
It’s because he’s powerful
and just returned in triumph.
People support him.
Even His Majesty showed respect to him.
Your Highness.
You officially
declare a war against Prince Qin.
You must be
very careful.
What can I do?
He is always arbitrary.
Even my father
considers
his feelings sometimes.
My men were killed.
This case is closed
because there’s no solid evidence.
Even my father didn’t say a word.
How dare I say anything?
Forget the unhappy things
today.
I got some superior tribute tea
the other day.
I’ll give you two.
This tribute tea
is only enjoyed by my father and grandmother.
The tea is good.
Don’t leak it out.
-Yes.
-Thank you, Your Highness.
Master. Master.
Master.
Chancellor
and Chief Guard
perished suddenly one after another.
The case of Chief Justice
isn’t closed yet.
Another two officials of mine died.
They dared to murder imperial officials
under my nose.
How bold!
They’re looking down on me.
Whoever did this,
get it
to the bottom!
Show no mercy!
Yes, Your Majesty.
He leaves early and returns late.
I haven’t seen any trace of him.
Not to mention the birthmark.
It’s been ten days.
What should I do?
Your Highness.
Madam Zhao.
Are you unhappy?
I’m fine.
Don't worry about me.
His Highness is a good man, actually.
Her Highness
is easygoing as well.
It’s just that he’s annoyed lately
and in a bad mood.
He will be fine
after some time.
I heard that
His Highness is framed.
Then some officials perished.
Has His Highness been exonerated?
Her Highness is upset
about this case.
It’s said His Majesty
ordered General Mu to look into it.
But until now
there’s still no progress.
I think His Highness
is also busy with looking into it.
The family were wiped out overnight.
Not too many people in the capital
could do that.
His Highness was caught red-handed.
It’s reasonable
that others suspect him.
Also,
two officials perished.
It’s too hard
for His Highness to justify himself.
Right.
I heard that
they were poisoned
to death by some
unknown poison.
It’s impossible
for His Highness
to use dirty tricks like that.
Poisoned to death?
Yeah.
Now that they were poisoned,
the poison can be figured out.
Then find out the source.
How come there’s no
any progress?
I don’t know about that.
You said poison masters are everywhere
and I am useless.
I’ll prove myself to you.
Make an excuse
and go to Cold Stone
to check things out.
His Highness works so hard.
Please make some chicken soup.
I will take it to him myself.
You should do it earlier.
His Highness will be delighted.
I’m going to cook now.
The coroner only found they were poisoned,
but couldn’t find out
what the poison was.
His Majesty also ordered
imperial physicians to assist.
But even the physicians
couldn’t find out
what the poison was.
Come in, princess.
Your Highness.
You’ve been working hard for days.
I bring you some chicken soup
for your health.
Give the soup to Xifeng.
Your Highness.
Let me serve you.
I’m off, Your Highness.
You may leave if nothing else.
Your Highness.
I have something to say.
Say it.
Xiqiu’s Princess makes peace by marriage.
She is no ordinary woman.
Xiqiu’s little prince just ascended the throne.
In a short time,
those powerful officials
were killed.
And that lord.
We have to be alert of him.
Right.
Besides, General Baili’s investigation
goes well.
He’s got a clue on the corruption case.
What about His Majesty?
Until the false accusation is settled,
His Majesty has a reason
to keep you here
and take this chance
to thin out our men.
So,
the coming of Chu Qingge at this moment
isn’t a bad thing.
Tianhui is suspicious by nature.
He must suspect
that Chu Qingge is up to something
by the marriage.
While he
deals with Chu Qingge,
we will get a chance.
Report or dismiss.
I have something to report.
Your Majesty.
Chief Justice’s family
and two officials were killed.
It’s been investigated for days,
yet the culprit is still at large.
Your Majesty, please look into it
to console the dead.
Mu Qingwu is solely in charge of
this case.
Mu Qingwu.
Yes, Your Majesty.
How is the case going?
I’ve investigated all the pharmacies and clinics
in the capital with my men,
yet no one figured out
what poison the dead took.
The poison is indeterminable.
So,
we don’t know
how the poison was applied.
Sorry for my incompetence.
Please punish me, Your Majesty.
Father.
I think it’s not
all Mu’s fault.
Only Chief Justice's case
has witnesses.
Other cases have no clue at all.
General Mu
has done his best.
Your Majesty.
This case is quite clear.
Why hasn't it been closed?
Just because the suspect is Prince Qin?
The saying has that, the guilty rulers
shall be punished as commoners.
Please judge it, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Apparently, all the evidences
point to Prince Qin.
But, by now,
no solid evidence
proves that Prince Qin is the murderer.
Your Majesty.
Someone witnessed
Prince Qin showed up
in Chief Justice’s home.
The two ministers perished
exactly like the former victims.
Also, they were Prince Qin's political enemies.
Isn’t it clear enough?
General Mu
deliberately conceals the evidence
and covers up for Prince Qin.
What do you mean?
I’m just telling the truth.
It’s the court.
Mind your manners.
Uncle.
In your opinion,
how to deal with it?
Your Majesty.
I think
both of them have a point.
Prince Qin
is the prime suspect now.
If you
don’t do anything to Prince Qin,
it’s hard to convince others.
But there is no solid evidence.
In your view,
how to handle it?
I think
you may
demote Prince Qin
and deprive his military power.
And determine it
when everything
is clear.
Feiye.
What do you think?
I follow your orders, Your Majesty.
Uncle.
I didn’t think it’d be so easy
to deprive Prince Qin’s military power.
He doesn’t seem to
be so capable as we thought.
Don’t be careless.
This time it went well,
but Prince Qin
may turn the tide anytime.
We shall bide our time for now,
in case it attracts Prince Qin’s attention.
If he finds out
any trace,
we’ll lose everything.
Got it.
Don't worry, uncle.
We should thank
your man, Mr. Gu.
This man is extremely intelligent.
He looks kind,
but ruthless in heart.
You need more men now.
Try to get more people like him
to be your advisor.
But remember.
Once you find out he is treacherous,
be sure to kill him.
By the way, uncle,
I went to escort Concubine Qing
with Qin days ago.
I found Concubine Qing
was quite hostile to Prince Qin.
Prince Qin defeated Xiqiu by a landslide.
Of course she's hostile.
If Concubine Qing can gain the favor
and give a blow to Concubine Xiao,
maybe
the second prince will be implicated, too.
Let’s wait and see what happens.
Feiye.
Don’t mind what happened today
on the court .
I had no choice.
When Mu Qingwu figures out the truth,
I’ll uphold justice for you.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I also hope
we can figure it out as soon as possible
to clear my name.
Now that you think this way,
I’m relieved.
I’m no longer an official.
I don’t have to go to court.
I’ll relax at home for a few days.
No, I don't agree.
I am no longer an official.
If I still go to court for state affairs,
I might be accused.
Please grant it, Your Majesty.
Since you insist,
I won’t force you.
You just got married days ago.
Are you contented
with the marriage ordered by me?
I’ve been away on war for years.
No one takes care of my mother.
Thanks to Your Majesty,
my wife can help me look after her.
She is
from a family of imperial physicians
and knows some medical expertise.
When we have ailments,
she can also treat us.
Thank Your Majesty and Dowager.
I’m glad that you’re contented.
My mother said
Princess Qin is a beautiful woman.
She is a good match with you.
Thank Her Highness for her praise.
Princess of Xiqiu is already in the palace.
Xiqiu dares not to do anything for now.
But Beili is still there.
Beili is good at using scouts and spies
to infiltrate in the state
and get it fall apart in silence.
It really worries me.
Rest assured, Your Majesty.
As long as I’m here,
I will ensure the safety of the state.
The Crown Prince is weak-minded.
Other princes
have no matriarchal support.
They are incompetent.
Brother, I only have you
to rely on.
Yes.
[Pavilion of Leisure]
I’m adept at poison testing.
I’ll go out as a maid
and find out the poison
that killed Chief Justice
and other two officials.
Then find out the culprit
based on the clues.
That way,
I will be proved qualified
to be with
Prince Qin.
Once he lets his guard down against me,
I can take actions easily.
Wait for me to come back.
How come
they look like being asleep?
Your Highness.
Do you feel anything fishy?
Have you smelled
anything weird?
Smell?
It’s like...
It smells like sandalwood.
The corpses got into Yi Manor
and became material evidences.
Burning sandalwood is likely
to ruin the clues on the bodies.
No way could they do this.
Well.
Since they didn’t get the smell in Yi Manor,
they must have gotten it
when they were alive.
What kind of incense is it?
It’s strange.
They’ve been stored here for over ten days.
The smell is still there.
Go to check all the mansions,
especially about spices, incense and the like.
Yes.
Their bodies
have the similar smell as well.
And the death state
is the same as Chief Justice’s family.
But Chief Justice’s family
died together.
They died separately.
Chief Justice’s family
were supposed to be poisoned
in a confined space.
These two officials
were poisoned separately.
I see.
Go to check
what they ate and used before they died.
Excuse me.
Where is Yi Manor?
Go straight forward.
Turn left at the corner ahead.
Thanks.
Turn left.
[Flowery]
Qishao.
Thanks for your Mythical Herb.
The poison girl?
You’re beautiful now.
I barely recognized you.
Thanks to your Mythical Herb.
I helped you.
How will you repay me?
I have some business
to do.
When it’s done,
I’ll go to visit you at Yaogui Valley.
Will you keep your promise?
How can I
trick my savior?
Besides,
I haven’t seen White Ear for long.
I miss it.
OK.
That’s a deal.
Pinky promise.
Well.
You’re a man.
What are you doing here?
This is my store.
The well-known store,
Flowery,
is yours?
Yes.
Because many natural flowers
and herbs in my valley
are perfect
for you girls to make rouge.
Come.
You get
beautiful now.
But remember to
do facial care properly.
This is
a new cleansing lotion I developed.
Wash your face with it.
It can cleanse your face
and nourish your skin well.
Take it as a gift.
You’re so generous.
When I’m free,
I’ll treat you dinner.
-I'm leaving then.
-OK.
Qishao.
We’re in Tianning.
Don’t be too close to her.
Or we’ll get her hurt.
No missing.
No unwarranted thought.
-Greetings, Your Highness.
Rise.
I didn’t think
it’d bother
Physician Han and Physician Gu.
Thank you.
We serve the royal.
It’s my duty
to relieve your worries.
You’re loyal indeed.
I heard that your apprentice
is adept at medical skills.
May I meet her?
Your Highness.
Did you mishear it?
I’ve never had any apprentice.
Maybe I misheard it.
You may leave.
Your Highness.
Our princess
told lies bluntly.
[Gorgeous Chamber]
I’m late.
Forgive me, Your Highness.
Never mind.
Please sit.
You seem to be in a good mood today
and come to watch Yuze’s dance.
Yuze is an amazing dancer.
I haven’t seen her for days,
and miss her a lot.
But today
I ask you to come
for I want to thank you.
Not at all.
It’s my duty to relieve your worries.
That’s what I should do.
You’re modest.
Prince Qin is troubled by murder cases.
Father deprived his military power.
It’s a matter of time
for him to be imprisoned.
His Majesty deprived Prince Qin’s military power?
Imperial Censor requested His Majesty
to punish the murderer.
Hadn't Mu Qingwu been
too stubborn,
Prince Qin would've been imprisoned.
You asked them to impeach Prince Qin?
Exactly.
Sir, is there anything wrong?
Nothing.
I think
we’d better not take actions in future.
Why?
This matter
has nothing to do
with you.
If you continue
involving in it,
I’m afraid
Prince Qin will be suspicious.
You’re indeed intelligent
and insightful.
My uncle
also told me like this.
I’ll go back and order them
not to take actions.
Have a drink, sir.
[Mourn]
Stop.
What are you doing?
Sir, please do me a favor.
My uncle is there.
I’m going to recognize him
and bury him.
You can’t claim him
without Chief Justice’s warrant.
The former Chief Justice
is lying there.
New Chief Justice hasn’t taken office.
At home, my aunt cried
and fainted many times.
She’s a widow and I’m an orphan.
Please have pity on us.
You can’t claim him
without Chief Justice’s warrant.
Let me just take a look.
Please.
Then I’m going back to tell her.
Leave here now. Leave.
Or I’ll beat you up.
Alright.
You’re so mean.
Miss.