[English subtitles are available.]
Episode 37
Ya!
Stop!
I shouldn’t have let him sleep.
Hey,
when can we arrive?
Your Highness,
in one hour, at most.
Good.
You are almost home now.
I bet you must have all sorts of feelings
right now.
What a pity!
The minute you are back,
I’ll put you into the death cell.
Because that’s where
you really belong.
I want to see father.
Father?
You are not qualified.
Your Highness.
Her Highness asked us
to welcome you here.
Good,
let’s go!
There are too many guards.
We won’t be able to save Qishao.
Let’s wait for a better chance.
You don’t have to follow me.
Now that I’ve promised you,
I won’t go to the Southern Regions.
Miss, please forgive me.
I promised master
that I’d keep you safe
as long as I’m alive.
But because of the plague
befalls the Southern Regions,
the people there are suffering right now.
Miss,
my duty
is to protect you.
I don’t care
about other things.
Other things?
Those are all people!
A plague
can take
thousands of people’s lives.
How can you…
Watch out!
Help! Help!
Don’t!
Help!
Seems that this man
is infected with the plague.
The plague?
Are you from the Southern Regions?
I…
I haven’t been to the Southern Regions.
I heard a plague broke out
in the Southern Regions
on my way,
so I came back.
Unfortunately,
I still got infected.
Since you haven’t been to the Southern Regions,
you couldn’t be infected.
Wait.
I don’t think it’s the plague.
It’s not?
It’s poison!
This poison
is infectious!
A poisonous plague?
Have you
eaten anything
or touched any medicine recently?
I picked up a bottle
days ago
and I took a sniff,
I felt uncomfortable instantly.
And the symptoms have become severer these days.
His symptoms
are similar to the plague report
received by the Imperial Hospital.
Since he fell ill
after he smelled the bottle,
then what’s in the bottle
must be the source.
Where’s the bottle?
I…
I threw it down the hill.
Where did you pick it up?
The border between
the Southern Regions and the capital.
Darn it!
If I’m right,
the plague this time
is not a natural disaster,
but a human plot.
In this case, His Highness
won’t be able to address it.
If he fails to control it,
he will be in danger.
And the civilians will end up suffering.
Physician Gu,
the imperial physicians only know medicine
but not poison.
I’m sure I can help.
Okay.
Miss,
I’ll go with you.
I think Prince Qin
has arrived in the Southern Regions.
Your Majesty,
he should be there
by now.
I guess
Prince Qin is working hard
for the people
in the Southern Regions right now.
How concerned he is about our country!
But, Long Feiye,
it won’t take long though,
you’ll have to concern
about yourself.
What a pity!
No one will play Go
with me anymore.
Concubine Qing arrives!
Greetings, Your Majesty!
Rise.
Darling, what brought you here?
If I were not here,
Your Majesty would be busy with state affairs
and forget to take your medicine again.
Your Majesty, don’t work too hard
and harm your health.
In that case, I’ll never
forgive myself.
Got it.
Come here.
Your Highness.
According to your order,
we’ve set up
quarantine areas
in the different places of the Southern Regions.
Civilians who are already infected
have been transferred to accept treatment.
Civilians that we’re not sure
whether they have been infected with the plague
have also been transferred to specific
quarantine areas.
Both quarantine areas
and residential areas
have been disinfected.
Relief grains
are also provided
at specific place and time.
Remember.
Make sure
the suspected patients
are separated
in the quarantine areas, too.
Yes.
What’s more,
remind civilians in the city
to stay at home more.
If any family member
shows symptoms,
report it to the government right away.
Examine carefully at the city gate.
Stop any suspected patient
from coming in.
Remember,
at this critical moment,
the government
shall act
more orderly.
Don’t make any mistakes.
So the people will
be confident in the court.
Yes.
Your Highness
is indeed thoughtful!
I’ll go take care of it right now.
Any soldier gets infected?
Thank you for your care, Your Highness!
They are all healthy.
I guess King Tianhui asked General Mu
to come with me
to find out my relationship
with the Southern Regions.
Minister Sun,
remember to keep distance from me.
I got it.
Your Highness,
I think the plague this time
is quite odd.
Odd?
Yes.
What do you mean?
Usually when a plague breaks out
on a large scale like this,
it’s mostly triggered by flood,
drought, livestock epidemic,
or abnormal changes
of the weather.
But nothing happens
in the Southern Regions this year.
So the plague came from nowhere.
More importantly,
our therapy
doesn’t work at all.
So you mean
this plague
is a new epidemic?
Highly possible.
Your Highness,
I’ll inform the imperial physicians
and ask them to study it right away.
Hope they can
find the cure soon.
Make it as quickly as possible.
I’ll take my leave.
Still alive?
Tell the Imperial Hospital
to send more physicians
to keep him.
Yes.
Besides,
whether he’s cured or not,
make His Majesty stay there.
Yes.
His Highness arrives!
Yizheng.
Greetings, mother.
Let me look at you.
Is everything
going well?
It went well at first.
But that little bastard
Jun Yixie
held me back
and made me suffer a lot.
I knew we shouldn’t have kept
such a bane.
I was going to come back
after I caught Poison Master,
but my identity was exposed early,
and Tianning became such
a crisis-ridden place,
so I had to come back first
to make another plan.
As long as you are back safely,
the others don’t matter at all.
Mother,
I caught Jun Yixie
and brought him back this time.
He defied me and father’s order,
released Poison Master,
and colluded with our enemy.
It’s all capital crime!
I gotta ask father
to punish him heavily!
No need
to bother your father with such a thing.
You can make decisions by yourself.
Your father is seriously ill,
I’m afraid he’ll die soon.
Mother,
then my throne…
Yizheng, don’t worry.
I’ve arranged it for you already.
Guards! Guards!
Guards!
-Stay out of this!
-Guards!
Or, you’ll be killed!
I… I want some water!
Guards!
But, mother,
why do you
treat father that way?
You still don’t get it
after these many years?
I’ve gained a high position and power,
but your father
never favored me.
I actually don’t care about it.
As long as I’m still the Empress,
and he passes the throne to you
after he dies,
I can put up with everything.
But being ill so seriously,
he still hasn’t issued his will!
It really pushes my button!
Maybe
he wants to pass the throne to Jun Yixie?
Your Highness,
this is the latest number of infections
reported from different places.
Bazhou, 239.
Xuzhou, 237.
Bozhou, 356.
Huazhou, 560.
Xizhou, 572.
Dengzhou, 320.
Yunzhou, 437.
I see.
Go take care of the thing
I asked you.
Yes.
I’m on it.
The new antidote
still doesn’t work?
No.
Continue the study.
I’ll report the situation
to the court
and ask them to send more help.
Yes.
I’ll take my leave.
Miss, let’s go.
Your Highness!
What are you doing here?
Now, go back!
Your Highness!
I have something important to tell you!
Gu Beiyue,
is this how
you take care of Han Yunxi?
Your Highness,
Miss Yunxi is here
for you
and the civilians of Tianning.
We found something
about this plague,
so we are here to report it to you.
You guys don’t need
to worry about this!
Take her back, now!
I can leave.
But I need to confirm something.
See that?
It’s poison,
not an ordinary plague.
I can’t believe
that the plague in the Southern Regions
was caused by a poison!
Since you’ve found this out,
give us the antidote
and then leave.
I don’t have the antidote.
You don’t?
Then why are you here?
I’ve also never
encountered with such a poisonous plague.
I need to stay here
and observe the symptoms of the patients,
so that I can study the poison
and develop the antidote.
No.
I’ll ask the imperial physicians
to do it.
You may leave.
No?
Then tell me,
which of you
knows poison better than me?
If I don’t stay,
can you figure out the antidote?
If you can’t, how can you
save the civilians of the Southern Regions?
You’ve been here for a long time,
yet you haven’t found out the reason
of the plague,
so why do you ask me to leave?
Miss,
thanks to you,
the patients
are all getting better now.
Don’t be happy so soon.
Their poison is just relieved.
They haven’t been totally cured yet.
It takes time.
Luckily,
our treatment
is working now.
Hope we can
get through this successfully.
I’ll go decoct more medicine.
Her Highness arrives!
Mother.
Yizheng.
You are not feeling well.
You must have
overworked in Tianning.
I’ve asked them to make tonics for you.
Remember to have some.
After your father dies,
we’ll only
have each other.
You’ve got to take good care of yourself.
Mother,
I’ve visited my father.
He’s unconscious,
but keeps mumbling
Jun Yixie
and his mother’s name.
Why does he neglect us like this?
Back then,
if it hadn’t been for you
and my grandfather’s power,
how could my father
have taken the throne?
So in his eyes,
I can’t even compare to that little bastard?
When that bitch
was still alive,
she always behaved humble
to win your father’s favor.
You father thought I didn’t know
that he mistreated her and her son
to actually confuse me.
Unfortunately,
I’m not
a stupid woman
who relies on a man.
But I do blame myself
that I didn’t
find a chance
to kill that bitch’s son!
Jun Yixie, you little bastard!
You want to fight me over the throne?
You wish!
What are you doing here?
Qishao, let’s go!
You guys leave. I can’t go!
If I leave with you,
I’ll become a fugitive of Beili.
In that case,
I can never see my father
and settle my relations
with Beili,
neither can I
get my mother’s ashes.
Qishao, you don’t know
that His Majesty is seriously ill now.
The Empress and Crown Prince
have blocked the news.
They are going to kill you
after His Majesty dies.
Qishao,
let’s leave here first.
Then we can make a plan.
Come on!
Qishao.
His Majesty is dying.
I’m afraid changes may happen in the palace.
Go back to the palace
and get your mother’s ashes.
We’ll go distract them.
No.
Go!
Zhuyu!
Split up!
Thank you for saving me.
You are welcome.
It’s you!
Where’s that little bastard?
Someone saved him out.
Saved him out?
A bunch of rubbish!
Your Highness, spare us!
Jun Yixie,
don’t think you can run away from me!
Your Highness.
What brought you here?
I heard that you’ve been working hard
to develop the antidote,
so I brought you some food.
Thanks.
How is it going?
I’ve never seen
or heard of such an infectious poison.
It’s highly toxic.
It won’t kill
a healthy person right away,
but it’ll linger on in one’s body.
It’s really difficult for me to figure it out.
I’ve tried many methods
with the imperial physicians.
They can’t detoxify the poison
but can only relieve the symptoms.
Is there anything I can do?
Just take protection
and prevention measures to get it under control.
Leave the antidote
development to us.
You still have many things to do tomorrow.
Go back and rest early.
What about you?
I’ll continue to develop the antidote.
Let me keep you company.
♫ Choose a speck of redness ♫
♫ From so many colors ♫
♫ Just like ♫
♫ A rouge dream ♫
♫ That melts ♫
♫ In the bridal outfit ♫
♫ And makes people heartbroken ♫
Miss!
Yunxi!
Yunxi! Are you okay?
How is she?
Miss Yunxi
is infected.
Your Highness,
you are in charge.
At this critical moment,
you can’t be crashed.
At this point,
I can’t leave her.
Then keep her company.
Son.
Is it really you?
Yes.
It’s me,
the son of the worthless maid
you hated the most.
No matter how you treated me before,
you are after all
my father,
so I’m here to save you.
I failed you
and your mother.
Son,
thank you
for saving me.
Don’t say this to me.
I’m saving you
because I pity you.
It’s too late
to say thanks to me.
My mother has died.
And I
end up like this.
You think saying thanks
can offset what you did?
Listen,
I will never
forgive you.
Don’t worry.
You are seriously ill
and incurable now.
This medicine
will help you die quicker.
That’ll be
enough for me.
My son.
Take this.
Back then,
the Empress’s family was too powerful.
For the sake of my throne,
I didn’t dare offend her family,
so I made you and your mother
suffer a lot.
I was too weak. It’s all my fault.
As the Emperor of Beili,
you couldn’t even
protect your wife and your son!
Stop making excuses for yourself.
Because you chose
to be the ruler of this country.
I’m not like you.
You totally abandoned
me and my mother for the throne,
which, however,
means nothing to me!
I won’t choose this
because I don’t give a damn!
You think giving me the throne
can make up for what my mom
and I had been going
through these years?
Father.
Good luck!
I’ll bid farewell to you now.
Son!
You… You…
Are you looking for this?
Give me back my mother’s ashes!
No rush!
Let’s play a game.
As we did when we were little.
I’m the Emperor,
and you are my servant.
Shouldn’t a servant
bow before the Emperor?
Now, kneel.
Okay.
But you need to kowtow three times.
Do it.
You are my Emperor.
How should you bow to me?
What should I do now?
You are infected with the plague.
What?
It’s impossible!
[Haidong Village]
You are an expert in medicine.
Give me a treatment.
Don’t go.
We are brothers.
You can’t watch me die.
Now you admit
that we are brothers?
Help me!
I’m begging you!
Please help me!
Help me!
Please!
Have you made a decision
about your successor?
Actually,
with or without your edict,
the result will be the same.
Now all the officials in the court
have served my family.
Even God can’t stop
Yizheng from becoming the Emperor.
I suggest you
understand the situation better,
so that you don’t have
to suffer as much.
Do you hear me?
Where’s the edict?
Qishao.
Jun Yizheng treated you so badly before,
why are you
saving him?
Such a despicable and mean man
deserves to die.
Father’s condition
is getting worse and worse.
If he passes away
one day,
our country will
have no emperor.
Without an emperor,
it means
our country will
be put to an end soon.
What worries me right now is not my father,
but the civilians of Beili.
But you are also a prince, Qishao.
This is not a life
I want though.
I don’t care about the throne.
Besides,
the Empress has deep-rooted power
in the court,
I don’t want to bring trouble to myself.
But
as such an ungrateful person,
he’ll forget
how you saved his life
as soon as he’s cured.
Maybe,
he’ll even hurt you again later.
Don’t worry.
I have my way to control him.
I don’t want to own you anything.
Tell me what you want.
I’m not as selfish as you are,
taking about conditions with whatever you do.
Moreover,
you’ve never kept your word anyway.
Even if we had a deal,
so what?
Do you believe
I can kill you now?
I do.
That’s your real thought.
You insult me
and want to kill me,
because you are worried
that I’ll fight you over the throne.
Let me tell you, Jun Yizheng.
Listen carefully!
I’m not interested
in the throne at all!
So,
you can be totally relieved.
You are not interested?
Who wouldn’t crave for the throne?
I can’t be relieved
as long as you are in Beili.
You should say you can’t be relieved
as long as I’m alive.
Father didn’t leave you the edict
to make you his successor,
right?
That… That’s nonsense!
I always keep
my word.
I meant it when I said
I wasn’t interested.
Then give me the edict!
Although
I’m not interested,
this edict is
my amulet.
As long as I’m alive,
healthily and safely,
I won’t tell anybody
about the edict.
But if I die someday,
I’ll let the whole world
know that you are
unworthy of the Emperor of Beili.
So,
you’d better pray
for a long life for me.
What’s more,
let me warn you, Jun Yizheng.
In the future, don’t do those
evil things again.
If you want to sit tight
on the throne,
think more for our people.
The poisonous plague in Beili
is spreading right now.
Have you ever thought
about addressing it for them?
Besides,
stop thinking about making alliance
with Chu Qingge.
Because you are not
as smart as she is.
Guards!
Arrest him!
What did I just say?
In such a short time,
you already exposed your true color!
Wanna kill me to shut my mouth
and get the edict?
I’m afraid you can’t take the throne
even if I’m dead.
Because the plague you got
is just relieved for now.
Jun Yizheng,
no matter you want it or not,
you have to keep me alive.
The poisonous plague
is just temporarily suppressed.
To cure the civilians,
we need other prescriptions.
And I gotta
look for them in person.
-Qishao, let us go with you.
No need.
The poisonous plague is still spreading in Beili.
You guys stay here
and try to keep it under control.
I’ll be back as soon as possible.
Yes, Qishao.
Your Highness.
Please take care of Miss Yunxi.
I’ll go check the quarantine areas.
Yunxi,
please get well,
so that you can remember
and hate me for a whole life.
Move him over there.
There.
General Mu.
I thought our medicine
has suppressed
the spreading of the plague.
How come
more people are transferred here?
I don’t know either.
It’s really strange.
Many
uninfected places
are attacked by the plague suddenly.
In theory,
we’ve already
put the plague under control.
Why are there so many people got infected?
I have no idea.
I just got the news
this early morning.
By the way,
do you know Haidong Village?
The people there
are so pitiful.
How so?
I heard the people there
got infected first,
and they were also hit by the plague the hardest.
We just went to the village,
where hardly have any people left.
There are only corpses.
Gu Qishao?
Physician Gu.
You also think Haidong Village
has a problem?
You think so, too?
The plague in your Tianning
has spread into our Beili.
How could I ignore it?
Besides,
this is where the plague
first took place.
The situation is getting worse and worse.
I think
the reason why the poisonous plague happened
must be hidden here.
I don’t want to have
any contact with Beili people.
Excuse me.
Physician Gu.
You’d better work with me.
We have a goal in common,
and I’m also
well-versed in poison,
you won’t lose anything.
I also want to ask you
a question.
I know what you wanna ask.
Princess Qin is infected.
What?
How could you and Long Feiye
fail to protect her?
How did she
get infected?
It’s not the time to ask that.
We should find the source
of the plague as soon as possible.
Then Miss Yunxi can be cured.
Seems that the entire village
has been infected.
Hold on.
There might be a problem with the water.