That's Miss Andrea!
Help!
Dad!
Manuel!
Stay away,
and keep your kids back.
For now, stop claiming Manuel
as yours.
Ma'am, I'm really sorry,
but only immediate family
allowed here.
He's bleeding into the airway.
Go to the ER now!
- Manuel.
- Dad?
- Stay away!
- Dad!
Stay away!
If Dad dies, Mom, I won't
be able to forgive myself.
Mom, please forgive me.
Jessica, I'm sorry.
Help us with Dad.
Have some mercy on my mother!
Have mercy on us!
Stay with your useless family!
Go to hell together!
Hello?
Being hurt doesn't give you
the right to disrespect others.
Please, for Dad's sake,
we don't need
negativity right now!
I don't care
about your family.
So that's why something
seems strange with you.
Jane, my foot!
- Andrea, I'm sorry.
- Don't call me your sister.
You're not my sister.
When did they get here?
When?
Coleen!
Last week.
You really are shameless!
Ate Andrea, please don't be mad
at Ate Coleen.
I said, stop calling me "Ate"!
Stay out of this.
You're not even family.
Wash these dishes.
Didang, here.
I'll do it.
Sorry.
I'm going back to the house.
But you and Jessica
need to leave first.
Auntie Felma said we could stay.
Dad was talking to you calmly.
Why can't you meet him halfway?
Who are you to tell me
what to do, huh?
Don't answer back, dear.
Dad, it's just so frustrating!
You've been humble and
apologetic for the longest time.
But she's still being
so stubborn!
I'll go check on Mom.
Auntie.
Jessica.
Jessica!
Jessica, please.
Please.
I'm really sorry.
Manuel's life
is in danger, Miles,
because of that scammer daughter
of his!
Honestly,
that woman should be held
responsible
for what happened to him.
Come on, Hazel.
Nobody wanted this to happen.
Look, that Andrea girl
is just a victim
of that lending company.
And her friend
or boyfriend, whatever,
is just caught up in it.
She's not a victim.
Is it my fault she's so stupid
and fell
for that easy money scheme?
I don't care about her man.
What matters now...
is Manuel.
Miles,
I don't know what will happen to
me if I lose Manuel.
- I don't want to lose Manuel.
- No, no.
Don't say that. Please.
Hazel.
What are you doing here?
Isn't it clear?
Only the patient's family
is allowed here.
Hazel, please.
Let's not fight.
Manuel needs us.
No.
He doesn't need you all.
And you, none of you,
have any right to my husband.
Mom!
Get out!
Why are you pushing?
Do you want me...
to have the guard drag you out?
Jessica, call the guard!
Come on.
Calm down, Hazel.
I'm sorry, Miles.
They really have some nerve.
This is the family waiting area.
You have no right
to throw us out!
Family waiting area.
Did you hear what you just said?
Family.
Who's the real family here?
Who's the real Cruz?
We're Manuel's
family, too!
No!
Only us!
Only Jessica and I
are his real family!
The legal family.
And you?
You're the
illegitimate family!
We're also his children.
We carry his last name.
We have rights too.
Bastard children...
who disowned their father.
- That's enough.
- Don't you feel guilty?
Especially you?
Manuel's life is in danger
because of you!
I said that's enough.
No.
These people
are shameless!
You hurt my daughter,
and now this happened to Manuel
because of you!
So,
if Manuel survives
this operation,
you'll never get near him again.
Even if he dies
on that operating table,
you won't even get to see
his body.
You're a demon!
No matter what you do,
- you can't stop us! Demon!
- Andrea!
Stop!
Wait!
We're in a hospital!
What are you doing?
There are other patients here!
Show some respect!
Guard!
Ma'am, Sir.
Please, that's enough.
I'm asking you nicely.
Please step outside.
Nurse Miles, I'm begging you.
Please don't make us leave.
We'll stay in the hallway
if we have to.
Please understand.
We're in a hospital.
We have rules here.
We can't just ignore that.
We promise
we won't cause any trouble.
No. You've already caused
enough trouble, right?
So I'm sorry, but I really
can't grant your request.
- Nurse Miles, I'm just asking.
- Son...
let's not push it.
Can we please just
ask for a favor?
Could you please
give us an update...
after the operation?
We'd like to know
how Manuel's doing.
Ma'am, I'm really sorry.
But patient updates
can only be released
to immediate family members.
But don't worry, okay?
I'll talk to Hazel.
But I can't promise
you anything.
I'm really sorry.
Please excuse us.
That's enough.
Sorry, Mom.
It's my fault.
Sorry.
What's up, sis?
Did you get rid of them?
You know, Hazel,
what you did back there
is so unbecoming
of a senior nurse
of Southcrest Premiere Hospital.
Miles,
you know my story.
You have to understand.
I was just protecting
my rights as the legal wife.
My daughter and I
have rights to Manuel,
not that illegitimate family.
Yes, you're the legal wife.
You have rights, I get it.
But don't forget
you're also a nurse
here at this hospital.
You represent the hospital,
even when you're not on duty.
What should I have done?
Entertain them?
Assist them?
Should I have gotten close
to them?
No.
You shouldn't have engaged
with them.
You should have
let me handle it!
I'm sorry.
But they triggered me, Miles.
You saw it, right?
They started it.
They were the first ones
to come at me.
Yes, but you could've
avoided it, right?
For heaven's sake, Hazel.
You shouldn't let
your personal issues
get in the way
of your profession.
Not in this hospital,
not on my watch!
Look,
please don't hold this
against me, okay?
We're friends, I get it.
I understand you.
But in this hospital,
I'm your boss.
Learn to respect that.
Follow orders!
Let this be a warning to you.
I don't want this
to happen again, okay?
This isn't the only entrance, we
can go through the parking area.
Or even here, it's a different
guard on duty now anyway.
Not the one with Nurse Miles.
The one who threw us out.
Son...
even if we get inside, we still
won't get near your father.
Hazel's always watching.
No, Mom. Let's wait
until she falls asleep.
Then we sneak in.
Hazel works here, son.
I'm sure she'll leave
instructions
with the other nurses.
And Alice is also there,
always following her orders.
So please, let's just go home.
No, Mom. I can't.
I won't be at peace
until I know how Dad's doing.
Let me handle this.
I still have one more
patient anyway.
I'll wait
until Joel comes out of the OR.
Then...
I'll try to get news about Dad.
I'll call you right away.
Thank you, dear.
Why, Mom?
I just missed you.
I missed you, dear.
I missed you, too.
I miss all of you so much.
Especially Dad.
I miss Dad so much, Mom.
Jessica, any updates?
Did the illegitimate family
come back?
No, Mom.
Good.
Darn Felma
and her shameless kids.
Now...
I'm the one who got scolded.
Jessica,
listen to me.
You saw
what could happen, right?
Now that they're patching
things up,
they might team up
to take your dad away.
You saw them.
They showed up in full force.
Only the youngest
who attacked you wasn't there.
But dear,
don't let it happen.
Don't let your dad
go back to them.
Because if he does,
he'll push through
with the annulment.
We fight, okay?
We fight back.
Mom, why is the surgery
taking so long?
Still no update?
I know.
It's been two hours, and the OR
nurse still hasn't come out.
She said your dad is stable.
But as of now,
the surgery is still ongoing.
And there's no estimated time
yet for when it'll finish.
The wait is killing me, Mom.
Dear,
I know.
I feel the same.
But for now,
all we can do...
is pray for your dad.
Don't worry.
He's in good hands.
Mom, I'm scared
of what Hazel said.
What if it comes true
and Dad doesn't survive
the surgery?
Mom...
I haven't even told him that...
I've forgiven him.
I haven't said sorry for all
the hurtful things I said.
All Dad knows is I'm mad at him.
He doesn't know...
I still love him so, so much.
Dear...
Manuel will fight.
He'll make it through.
And when he wakes up,
Hazel won't be able
to stop him anymore.
Because your dad himself...
will come to us.
Thank you, son.
Coleen?
Coleen, dear?
Mom?
Jeff.
How's Dad?
He was still in...
the OR when we left
the hospital.
Why did you leave him?
Hazel kicked us out.
She said only she and Jessica
have the right to be with Dad.
She's so cruel!
And Jessica?
She just agreed?
Jessica couldn't really do
anything, dear.
But Mom, maybe she could've.
She could've at least stood up
to Hazel,
or offered to update you about
Dad, so you wouldn't worry.
Coleen, you really think
she'd do that
after what happened between
the two of you?
Sorry, but you picked the
wrong time to fight with her.
I want to go to
the hospital.
I want to see Dad.
If I need to apologize
to Jessica, I will.
Even if she lashes
out at me, it's fine.
Coleen, don't. We don't stand
a chance against Hazel.
Dad's with her,
where she works.
She gets to act
like a queen there.
So what, we just give up?
No, sweetie.
Let's get through
the night first.
Let's pray that...
the surgery is a success.
Then, when he wakes up,
we'll go see him.
That's enough.
We won't let Hazel...
get her way.
You will see your dad.
Especially now...
that Andrea wants...
to make things right with him.
Is Dad's surgery almost done,
Mom?
It should be, dear.
I hope so.
It's been over five hours.
Hey.
What are you still doing here?
Why are you still here?
Want me to call the cops?
Don't be so assuming, Hazel.
I didn't come here for Dad.
I have another patient.
Oh, right.
Your dad's not your only victim.
Even your boyfriend,
who got stabbed.
Poor guy.
Joel?
Hey, how are you feeling?
How's the pain?
He's out of the woods.
Good thing the wound
didn't hit deep into his liver.
But he'll need to stay a few
more days to recover properly.
Okay. Thank you.
Coleen, sit down for a bit.
Mom's trying to stay strong.
But I can tell...
she's hiding her fear and worry.
I noticed, too.
Our family's going through
so much.
I know.
Feels like
we're living in a drama series
with everything happening.
But even with all the problems,
at least something
good came out of it.
Look at Mom and Andrea.
They're okay now.
I hope...
I hope our family
becomes whole again.
I hope so, too, Jeff.
Has Andrea called yet?
Maybe she has news
about your dad.
Not yet, Mom.
Jeff, please call Andrea.
Sonny's been detained.
- Take it easy.
- Sorry.
Atty. Yeban is already handling
the case for him.
Sorry.
Hello, Jeff.
Andrea?
Any news about Dad?
None yet.
It's like Hazel's the warden,
standing guard outside the OR.
How's Joel?
Here...
he's awake now.
He just came out
of the recovery room.
Thank God. That's a relief.
Tell him to get well soon, okay?
I'll visit
once I get the chance.
Andrea, dear.
Take care of him, okay?
Yes, Mom.
I won't leave him.
I owe him my life.
But sis,
please still find out
about Dad's condition, okay?
We can't sleep,
thinking about it.
Okay, sweetie.
I'll handle it.
Go ahead, Andrea.
Take care of Joel.
Sorry, Joel.
Sorry that you're in danger
because of me.
I've messed up your life.
Since we met,
you've been dragged
into all my problems.
You've always been the one
helping me.
Supporting,
taking care of me.
Now it's my turn.
Thank you.
Not because...
you saved me.
Thank you for being my friend.
Thank you
for being my best friend.
Dear God.
Dear God,
please don't take Manuel.
Not now.
Not yet.
Please save him.
Are you pregnant? Yes!
We're going to have a baby!
If he goes back to Hazel,
I'll accept that.
As long as you save him.
But if you must take a life,
Lord...
take mine.
Take mine, Lord.
Don't take Manuel's.
I've been with our children
for a long time now.
What I want is...
for Manuel...
to experience being loved
and cared for by Jeffrey,
Andrea,
and Coleen.
Lord.
Please save him.
Save Manuel.
Dear God...
There are so many machines
attached to Dad.
Is he safe?
I don't know.
Darn it! Do we really have
to sneak around
just to know how Dad's doing?
Get out of there!
Andrea!
Let me go!
Since Manuel signed
our marriage certificate,
you lost your rights to him.
We won't lose our rights
to our father.
That's not going to happen.
Andrea!
I won't sue,
but let me and my kids
be near Manuel.