Sweetie, you called.
You know, I've been trying
to locate you in Australia
for so long.
Because I really
wanted to come see you.
Please come here.
I'll send you our address.
Sweetie, your mom
might get mad.
I also want you to come.
So I can apologize
to you in person.
Coleen, Andrea, please
take care of Mom and Dad
for now, okay?
I feel like going
home right away.
All right, I'll miss you.
I'll be back soon.
Mom?
Dad?
I think someone's following me.
Help!
Joel, stop it.
First, it was Coleen.
Now it's you.
Report this to the police.
We already filed a report.
Where are you now?
We're at the hospital, Dad.
We're buying Mom's medicine.
Isn't it the only place
you can get it?
Andrea, go ahead to the car.
I just need to use the restroom.
Okay.
Just wait for my orders.
Hey!
What are we going to do now?
Why did he send this to me?
Where are you?
Jojo?
Hazel?
What?
Are you two working together?
What are you planning to do
to Aunt Felma and her family?
That's none of your business.
I'm really sick of you.
You wanted to involve yourself
with Felma's family.
You're not even related to them.
You're an outsider!
No.
I won't let you hurt them!
Leave.
Just go.
What are you going
to do with him?
I'll handle this.
Go on.
Make sure no one sees you.
Don't pass by the
area outside, okay?
Go!
There you are.
So? What now?
Is that it?
You got it?
What do you even need that for?
You don't have to know.
Don't ask anymore.
You know those meds
are dangerous.
I said don't worry about it.
I just have to do something.
Go back to your duty.
Ma'am?
Sir?
Ma'am? Sir?
Help!
He's not answering.
Excuse me, Sir.
Where's the restroom?
Ma'am, over there.
Okay, thank you.
Joel?
Doctor, what happened?
Doctor, why?
Joel...
Joel?
Doctor, why?
What happened?
- Joel?
- Andrea!
Andrea!
Alice.
- Alice, please...
- What happened?
Please help Joel.
I'm begging you.
Save him, please.
Alice, please...
Doctor, what's going on?
You know those
drugs are dangerous.
Just don't ask anymore.
Check his vital signs.
No pulse.
Joel...
No BP, Doc.
Start CPR.
Joel...
Give him one amp of epi!
Sir, just 20 minutes
of exercise, okay?
All right.
Okay.
I don't know.
The janitor found him
in the restroom.
Probably a junkie.
Looks like an overdose.
Excuse me, Sir.
Trisha, can you take over
my patient for now?
There's an emergency.
Sure, Jojo. I've got it.
Thanks.
Okay, later.
One amp.
Give him one amp of epi!
Why did you stop?
Ma'am, it's no use.
I'm sorry.
Time of death: 5:03.
Andrea...
No!
Joel!
Please wake up, Joel!
Joel...
Joel, I love you.
I love you so much.
I don't know when or how
it started, but I love you.
Please, don't leave me.
Wake up, Joel. Please.
Please...
Alice!
Joel!
Joel, please!
I swore an oath to save lives,
even the lives of people I hate.
I won't let you hurt them!
What do you even need that for?
Don't ask anymore.
Hazel!
Hazel.
Did you do that to Joel?
People inside the hospital
are saying he overdosed.
Did you kill him?
Do you think I wanted
this to happen?
All I wanted was...
to make it look like
he was using drugs.
So if he told Felma,
they'd think
he was hallucinating.
I didn't know his body
was that weak.
And besides, Jojo,
we couldn't let him go.
If he told Felma,
she'd report us to the police.
We'd both end up in jail.
Do you want that?
You killing him was
never part of the plan.
Me?
Just me?
Both of us.
You're already in this.
We're just getting
revenge for Jessica.
Why did it have to come to this?
What? Are you getting scared
now?
Are you backing out?
It's too late.
We already started this.
There's no turning back.
Just think about this.
If it weren't for Felma's
family's abuse,
our child would still be alive.
We'd still be together.
You want to make it up to
Jessica, right?
This is your chance.
Get revenge.
And one more thing.
Get yourself together.
Because we're not done yet.
Ma'am, how are you
related to Joel Santiago?
He's my friend.
We need to speak
with his family,
so we can include his personal
belongings in the investigation.
I already called his sibling.
What exactly happened to Joel?
Based on our initial
investigation,
we found a puncture mark
on his left arm.
It suggests a drug
was injected there.
We also found a syringe
in his right hand
and a small vial of medicine.
We're verifying with toxicology
what kind of drug it was.
This could be a
drug overdose case.
But...
But Joel isn't a user.
I've known him for a long time.
No, he doesn't do drugs.
We still need to speak
with his family.
You can talk to his siblings,
his mother, or anyone.
All of us know Joel
wasn't an addict.
Maybe he was dealing
with something,
something he couldn't tell you.
Are you saying Joel
harmed himself?
No.
He would never do that.
In fact, he was fine.
We were fine.
He was happy with our
friendship, with my family.
With the family he had.
He had so many plans.
Andeng...
Dad...
Dad.
Joel's gone.
My best friend is gone, Dad.
Sweetie, I saw how
he took care of you.
That's why this hurts me, too.
Andeng, in your text,
you said the police think
it was an overdose.
I don't believe
Joel would do that.
That's what I told them, too,
Dad.
But...
but...
Who would do this to Joel?
Why would they kill him?
Why? Why, Dad?
Jessica!
What did you do?
I didn't do anything!
Jessica!
Okay, fine.
You're angry.
You want revenge.
But to destroy her reputation?
To break her spirit?
To tear my family apart?
I'll help Coleen.
Let's get back together, Manuel.
Let's rebuild our family
and fulfill Jessica's last wish.
I will never get back
together with you!
Yes, Hazel, you're my wife.
On paper.
But Felma, she is the one
I truly love.
I came back to you
because you said you'd help
clear Coleen's name.
That doesn't mean I love you.
He'll love me once
we're together again...
Once I show him my love.
How I take care of him.
I'll devote myself to him
until he finally sees
that I'm worth loving.
Don't get your hopes up.
He loves me.
Only me.
Rejection after rejection.
You've wronged me
over and over, Felma.
I'm not just getting revenge
for Jessica, Manuel.
I'm also getting revenge
for myself.
I'm sorry, Joel.
I didn't mean for this
to happen to you.
But all of you better
be ready...
because I'm not stopping.
I'm not stopping.
It all happened so fast.
I was just texting Joel earlier.
And now he's gone.
So he was a drug addict?
Didn't really fit him.
He really wasn't a user.
He was a good person.
He knew what was right for him.
Maybe he was depressed.
You know?
Didang, it just feels
impossible.
He was always making
Andrea happy.
What's impossible about that?
Some people are like that.
You think they're happy.
Always smiling. Always joking.
But deep inside, when they're
alone, they're depressed.
They've already given up
on life.
Joel wasn't like that.
He never gave up on Andrea.
He was trying to win her up
to the last moment.
So what really happened?
You know what, Ma'am?
Maybe we should call Jeff and
ask him. They're close, right?
Maybe he knows something.
No.
This isn't the right time.
Especially now.
He's finally with his family.
Hazel!
Perfect timing. Come here.
Do you even understand
what you did?
Hazel, you killed someone.
That's not what we do.
We're nurses.
We save lives.
I know.
So why do you seem so calm?
Are you even thinking straight?
I am thinking straight.
That's why I acted fast.
What happened to Joel...
wasn't intentional.
Is it my fault his body
was weak?
Fine.
Let's say I did mean it.
He deserved it.
Because everything Jojo and I
worked for would've been ruined.
Sit down.
Let's eat.
My God.
Your anger has completely
consumed you.
Maybe getting justice
for Jessica was right,
but killing someone?
Hazel, I don't even recognize
you anymore.
So...
you don't want to be
my friend anymore?
Let me remind you.
That drug I injected
into Joel...
came from you.
So what does that make you?
An accessory to the crime?
If I knew you'd use it like
this,
I never would've given
it to you.
But you still gave it to me.
So you're just as guilty
as I am.
Hazel, do you even have
a conscience?
Can you really blame me?
After everything Felma
and Manuel did to me?
So, if I were you...
instead of guilt-tripping me,
just leave me alone.
Let me do what I want to
that illegitimate family.
Please pass the rice.
Thank you.
Thank you, Andrea,
for everything you did for Joel.
And to your family, too.
Thank you so much for welcoming
our brother
as part of your family.
Thank you for...
sharing him with us.
It's really sad, Andrea.
Joel used to talk about you all
the time.
You were the only one he ever
took seriously.
If you'd said yes back then
maybe it would've led
to marriage.
You could've been
our sister-in-law.
You know, Andrea...
Even if you didn't say yes
to Joel,
it still felt like we gained
a brother-in-law.
And a son-in-law.
To be honest,
I treated him like...
like my own son.
Even if we'd ended up
together...
if this is how things were going
to turn out for him,
maybe it would've been better
if we'd never met at all.
How's the investigation going?
I talked to the police.
They said they're looking into
the possibility of foul play.
That someone else did this
to Joel.
But when they checked the CCTV
in the area
to identify who did it they
found nothing.
The cameras were broken.
You know what? I could also
ask for...
help from Colonel Sarabia.
It's reassuring that the
hospital administration
is cooperating
with the investigation.
Whoever did this to Joel...
whoever killed him...
I hope they're caught soon.
And I hope they rot in prison
for life.