Hey! What's this?
Who are you? I don't know you!
Dad! Uncle!
These are the flight details.
Yes, sir. The plane landed
about an hour ago.
Jeff texted.
What did he say?
"Sorry, I couldn't make it home.
There was an emergency."
This isn't how I imagined
revenge, Hazel.
I thought we were just
going to ruin Manuel's family.
Why?
Getting cold feet?
Daisy!
Where's Dad?
He's not here yet.
He texted earlier.
Said he couldn't make it.
No, he did make it, Auntie.
I know who did this.
It was Hazel.
That demon
hasn't changed at all!
- Andrea!
- Sis!
- Don't hurt Andrea!
Where's my brother?
Bring him out!
Get out of here,
all of you!
Get out!
We received a report
of trespassing.
Arrest them,
especially that woman!
Look! Look at her!
Mrs. Hazel Cruz, you're the one
filing the complaint?
Yes.
They barged into my house.
She attacked me.
Because you murdered my friend
and had my brother kidnapped!
Andrea.
Enough, sweetheart. Please.
Andrea...
don't waste your time on her.
I can't just stay
quiet, Uncle.
Miss Chairwoman, this woman
has done terrible things
to my family.
She did so many
evil things to us!
I'm sorry,
but that's not my concern.
Mrs. Cruz's complaint
is trespassing.
And assault.
Hazel, can we just let this go?
Can you not get involved, Noah?
You're always there. Why?
Who are you, anyway?
Let's keep our voices down.
Mrs. Cruz, would you like
to discuss this or...
I'm pressing charges.
I'll file a restraining
order against them.
Hazel, can you not?
Why shouldn't I?
Mind your own business!
When you violated a restraining
order before,
I had it dismissed
by Atty. Yeban.
So what?
Are we keeping score now?
Yes.
Because if I hadn't done that,
you'd be in jail right now.
It's a good thing Coleen
convinced Hazel...
not to file charges.
Here, I made some coffee
to calm everyone down.
This won't calm your nerves.
Maybe juice instead.
Coffee's fine, Didang.
- Oh, sir.
- Yeah.
Where could they
have taken Jeffrey?
Don't worry, Andeng.
We won't stop
looking for him.
Hello, Colonel Sarabia?
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have
let Jeff come home.
I should've stopped him.
- This is my fault...
- Andeng, stop.
Don't blame yourself.
Yeah.
It's Hazel.
She's behind all of this.
She's a monster.
If she hurts my brother,
I swear.
Hazel's evilness...
won't win.
We'll find your brother.
No one's giving up.
Not now.
Not ever.
But wait.
If Hazel kidnapped Jeff,
how did she know
his flight details?
When they found out Jessica
wasn't really their sister,
they hurt her.
They abused her
until she got depressed.
Until our daughter died.
Even if Jessica wasn't
their real sister,
they treated her like one.
They never saw her
as just a half-sister.
Felma accepted her
as her own child.
Joel and Jessica came
into our lives.
Especially Jessica.
I loved that child so much.
And you're blaming us
for her death?
That happened because of you.
Because of what you did!
Hazel, killing someone
was never part of the plan.
Just me?
No. We.
You're part of this, too.
Jojo?
Jojo.
Are you okay?
Why did you text me?
I'm so confused.
What Hazel says about
Manuel's family doesn't add up.
What do you mean?
I have a really bad image
of Manuel's family.
A few times,
sure...
maybe...
people can fake kindness.
But theirs is consistent.
I want to keep
hating his family.
But...
Alice,
tell me.
What do you know?
Is what Hazel's saying true?
Do you really want to know?
Yes.
Try turning on me.
You know me well enough, right?
You know what I'm capable of.
No matter who it is.
Hi, Alice.
What are you and Jojo
talking about?
Care to share?
Why'd you suddenly go quiet?
Hazel's a good friend.
That's not what I asked.
What do you know?
Alice...
you're hiding something.
Come on. Why are you asking me
all this?
Talk to Hazel yourself.
I might say...
something I shouldn't.
How are you, Jeff?
Still holding up?
Hazel.
I knew this was you.
I'm touched.
You really do
know me well.
You knew I'd be
your special guest.
Let me go.
Let me out of here!
Why did you bring me here?
Let me go!
You monster!
Monster!
You're evil!
According to Colonel Sarabia,
the hair follicle test showed
Joel wasn't a regular drug user.
So they're focusing on possible
foul play.
That's what I've been saying
from the start.
Joel wasn't an addict.
Of course, dear.
We believe you.
What about Jeff's case?
Any updates?
Have they checked
the airport CCTVs?
Here.
Based on the footage
Colonel Sarabia brought,
you can see Jeffrey here.
Then a white van pulls up.
It stops for a moment.
When it moves again,
Jeffrey's gone.
Sir Manuel,
that's you and Sir Abel.
- Oh, yeah.
- That's right, Dad.
And the interval...
You almost ran into Jeffrey
if the van hadn't blocked you.
Too bad.
Even though they didn't
see Jeffrey get in,
they're investigating
the white van.
I also hired
a private investigator.
Just to be sure.
Van kidnappings
are common these days.
What's strange is that
it's been days already.
No ransom demand.
Unless they have another
motive for Jeff.
Why are you doing this
to my family?
Do you even have to ask?
It's simple.
I want revenge.
I want to collect
on everything you owe me.
You're the one
who owes us, Hazel.
Ever since you took our father.
Ever since you got
pregnant in Saudi Arabia.
Fine.
Let's count, then.
I'll make the
list for you.
First...
I filed charges against Coleen
for what happened to Jessica.
And...
recently,
when she almost got hurt?
That was me, too.
You animal!
Let me out of here!
There's more.
What I asked them to do
to Andrea was simple.
I told my guy to harass her.
- And he did.
- You shameless monster!
Come here! Monster!
You're disgusting!
You don't deserve any respect!
And then there's Joel...
Honestly,
that jerk
wasn't even on my list.
Who was he, right?
He meant nothing to me.
But he tried to be a hero.
Showing off for all of you.
So he got dragged into it.
Hazel, so you have something
to do with Joel's death.
You're a demon!
Pure evil!
You're a monster, Hazel!
Hold on.
You know, if you really think
about it,
you people are the reason
Joel died.
Andrea, to be exact.
She let that man into her life.
So I was forced
to dispose of him.
You're a murderer!
You're a monster!
Murderer!
That man had nothing to do
with this, and you killed him!
Didn't you hear what I said?
I didn't mean to.
I didn't want to do it.
But I had no choice.
Better him than me, right?
You know what?
You guys...
bring out the worst in me.
So if you think about it,
this is your fault.
Joel's death is on you.
Do you understand?
You're evil, Hazel.
You're worse than a demon.
Even demons should be scared
of you. If I get out of here...
If I escape,
I'll get my revenge.
I don't care if you're a woman!
I'll kill you!
- I'll get my revenge!
- Oh, relax.
Let me out of here!
Let me go! Let me go!
I'm so scared! Jeff, no!
Don't!
Go on. Gag him already.
He talks too much.
Let me go!
Do whatever you want.
Go, just cry.
Why do you look so scared?
Like you just saw a killer.
Aren't you?
What do you even want?
I came to visit you.
It's been a while
since we last talked.
Maybe you missed me, friend.
I've just been busy lately.
And...
I told you, didn't I?
I'm starting to grow
a conscience.
And I'm just following
what you told me. To shut up.
So I really did.
Jojo's been bugging me.
But I didn't tell him anything.
You haven't said anything yet.
Because you know I've got eyes
all over this hospital.
If I didn't,
you would've sold me out
a long time ago.
I really didn't, friend.
Promise.
I won't tell him anything.
Come on.
Let's go home together.
Manuel,
what if...
what if Jeffrey wasn't taken...
for ransom, but...
My god.
I hope not.
I want to tell you not
to think like that.
But I can't help it either.
Daisy's ex,
the one we had locked up.
What if he got out?
What if he escaped?
Does he have people outside?
What if he found out
Jeffrey, Daisy, and Tetay
were reunited in Australia?
What if he's getting revenge?
That's possible.
I'll check on it tomorrow.
I'll bring Abel with me.
But something else
keeps bothering me.
What happened to Jeffrey...
Joel's death.
And what just happened
to Coleen and Andrea...
It's like someone's playing
with us.
No, a demon.
I feel like
cracking her skull open
just to see what kind
of twisted brain she has.
Why are you asking
Alice questions?
What are you
trying to find out?
Do you doubt me?
Hazel,
what you're saying about how
Manuel's family treated Jessica
doesn't match what I've seen.
It's hard
to fake kindness forever.
The truth always shows.
So what are you implying?
That I'm lying?
I don't know.
Something feels off.
If you don't believe me
anymore,
if you don't like how I do
things, just say it.
I'll get revenge for
my daughter myself.
Stay out of it.
After all, you were never
really there for Jessica anyway.
What could we expect from you?
Hazel, all I'm asking is that...
you're honest about what I need
to know about Jessica.
Maybe our anger
and revenge on Manuel's family,
who isn't as evil as we think,
have gone too far.
Just admit it.
You're scared.
You're backing out.
Let me remind you.
You're already involved
in Joel's death.
It's fine if you want out.
Just don't turn me in.
Because if you do,
you're going down with me.
Who's that man with Hazel?
Help! Help!
Here you go, Ma'am.
Miss Felma, are you okay?
Is something bothering you?
Sorry.
I just needed to let it out.
It's hard for a mother
when you don't know
what's happening to your child.
Why?
Is there still no news
about Jeffrey?
Every day that passes,
the fear gets worse.
What if...
something bad happened to him?
Where could he be?
Is he eating on time?
Is someone hurting him?
Who took him
if he really was kidnapped?
Can I take a quick
bathroom break?
Oh, sure, Ma'am.
That's my phone!
- What's that?
- My phone!
That's mine!
That father-and-daughter
moment is so cute, right?
It reminds me of Jessica.
Your kid's cute, too. Look.
To be fair,
you really are Manuel's son.
He was just as sweet to Jessica.
You shameless witch!
Give it back! That's mine!
Don't touch it!
You know...
I'm sure your family
misses you so much.
They're probably looking
everywhere for you.
Desperate to find you.
What do you think?
I'm sure they can't wait
to hug you,
be with you, be a family again.
But...
how should I say this?
That's never
going to happen.
Ever.
But you know what?
I just had an idea.
What if we give them
photographs and memories?
Right?
Let's give them that.
So, game?
Brilliant idea. Admit it.
- You're a monster!
- All right. Get ready.
Ready, ready, ready.
Okay, hold it.
- Ouch!
- Smile!
Now, go wacky.
Wacky!
Here, over here.
Angle it this way.
It doesn't look nice.
Fix it up.
We're sending
this to them.
- One, two, three, smile!
- Monster!
Look, look!
Oh, wow!
I'm good, aren't I?
Great shot!
So, who should I send this
to first?
Felma?
Manuel?
Or Andrea, that nasty girl?
Maybe her first?
Or how about your baby sister,
Coleen?
Who? Tell me.
Go die!
I hope you die!
My phone!
That's my phone!
Okay.
You're thanking me?
You're welcome, Jeffrey.
The pleasure is mine.
That shot looks amazing!
Where did she go?
She disappeared so fast.
Looking for me?
Are you stalking me?
Maybe you could ask Madam
Hazel when she comes later.
Let's just ask for ransom.
Yeah, boss.
You animal!
It's hard, Manuel.
I just want to be sure
Jeffrey's okay.
I'm sure God won't abandon
our firstborn.