- Where are you going?
- Son...
- I'm going back to Hazel.
- No!
What if he changed his mind
and doesn't show up?
Manuel will come.
Because if he doesn't,
Coleen will rot in jail.
- Andrea! Coleen!
- Jeff!
Fine, I won't leave,
I'll stay here.
I won't go back
to Hazel anymore.
But we should prepare ourselves
for the possibility that Coleen
might end up in prison.
Welcome to our new home.
What do you want?
Let's talk for a bit.
- Come on, just for a while.
- No, Hazel, I'm sleepy.
Jeff, you smell like alcohol!
What? Did you
and Dad drink last night?
Dad's gone,
he's with Hazel.
Why is Dad with Hazel now?
Jeffrey, come on!
Get your siblings out of here!
My head hurts!
Jeff, just tell us.
What do you know?
Wait! Fine, fine!
Okay, I'll tell you.
Jeff, don't you dare
tell your siblings.
Especially not Coleen.
Dad, what's the big deal?
Why keep it from them?
Because if Coleen finds out
about my agreement with Hazel,
she'll blame herself.
Especially once she learns
she's the reason
I have to go back to Hazel.
So you'll just
let her be angry at you?
I'd rather she gets angry
than feel guilty.
Anger fades, son.
But the guilt...
you'll carry it for life.
Coleen is such a good kid.
She doesn't know
how to hold grudges.
That's why I'm sure someday,
she'll forget she was mad at me.
Dad, I don't even know
what to tell them as the reason.
I can't think of anything.
I know one.
Hazel's hurting herself.
She took a lot
of sleeping pills,
so they rushed her to the
hospital.
Just because of that,
he's going back to Hazel?
He actually believed her?
He fell for her act?
Sweetie, I saw Hazel
when I dropped Dad off.
She looked awful,
like she wasn't even herself.
And she needs someone with her.
That's what Dad's thinking.
She might try something again.
Sorry, okay?
Maybe it sounds harsh...
but Dad should just let Hazel
do whatever she wants.
He has no responsibility
toward her anymore.
Andrea, they're not even
annulled yet.
Whatever we do,
they're still married.
And Jessica is gone.
Dad doesn't want
another tragedy.
What if...
What if Dad left because of me?
Because he's angry at me?
No, no, no, Coleen.
That's not
what it means, Coleen.
And why would Dad be mad at you?
Maybe he believed Hazel
that I really pushed Jessica.
Dear, no.
Dad trusts you.
What if he only said that?
What if he can't
accept me anymore
because he thinks
I killed Jessica?
Good morning!
I'm here now, Hazel.
I kept my end of the deal.
When will Timo withdraw
his statement?
Come on, Manuel.
Relax!
Why are you in such a hurry?
Patience is a virtue.
- Come on.
- Hazel, when?
Tell me when.
It's still early.
Don't worry.
I won't break my promise.
But for now, eat first, okay?
Come on, breakfast is good.
- Come on.
- I'm not hungry.
Huh?
Manuel!
You need to eat
before you take your medicine.
Patience.
Patience, Hazel.
Relax, don't take it to heart.
His heart
will soften eventually.
What matters is I have you back.
I don't care if Felma keeps
saying she is the one you love.
Because Manuel is with me now.
You already talked
to Diana, right?
About withdrawing
your statement?
Yes, Ma'am.
But, Ma'am, I'm scared.
I already lied,
and now I'll take it back?
Isn't that perjury?
My case will get worse.
Just say...
you were looking
or someone to blame.
Because you thought it might
lessen your sentence.
Why? You don't want to?
Timo...
I didn't want to do this.
Don't push me.
Do you know I can make
your life here miserable?
I even mentioned that to Diana.
I know, Ma'am.
That's why she was forced
to convince me, right?
There you go.
Then withdraw your statement.
Because it's not
just your life I can ruin...
or make miserable,
but also your child's.
Your children's and your wife's.
I'm a dangerous enemy, Timo.
So if you don't want
trouble for your family,
just do what I want.
Oh, by the way,
I have good news.
I arranged for your wife
to give birth
at Southcrest Premier Hospital.
Oh, see? Fancy.
She won't have to suffer.
What? Manual went back to...
Hazel?!
- Oh no!
- Oh, Auntie.
Auntie, what are you doing?
You're calling Mom?
Yes.
Don't.
Don't call her.
She won't answer anyway.
She won't even talk to us.
How's your mom?
She's locked herself
in her room.
She won't come out.
We just let her be.
Poor thing.
Here we go again.
Your mom's suffering again.
Ah! Hazel.
Hazel is the reason
for all this.
That wretched little pest!
Oh my! Andeng, come here!
Come with me,
I'm going after her!
Auntie, what for?
Dad has already made
his decision.
What can we do?
What is this?
I don't get it.
I don't understand Manuel.
What was he thinking? Huh?
Your dad is really
getting on my nerves!
But wait...
What are you
and Hazel doing here?
How did you know Manuel
and Felma were here, huh?
- Yes, how?!
- Because of you!
Because of what, Auntie?
Andrea.
Is what Jeffrey said true?
Manuel went back to Hazel again?
He left you all again?
Noah, excuse me.
Hello, Abel?
Come to FMP.
Right now!
Why would Manuel do this now?
When your whole family is
already going through something?
Dear, how's Coleen?
Well...
She's not okay.
She thinks Dad believes Hazel.
That she really pushed Jessica.
What about Felma?
How's your mom?
It feels like we're back
to the old days, Uncle.
The first time Dad left us.
We can't talk
to Mom properly again.
We're struggling again.
So... it's a done deal
with Timo?
He'll recant his statement?
Yes.
He should, right?
I'm helping his wife
and kids, after all.
Helping or paying them?
Well, what's the difference?
When people are desperate,
they come with a price.
Anyone can be bought.
No matter how decent they are.
So you cornered Timo?
Threatened him?
Oh, pretty much.
And look, he cooperated.
Because if he didn't,
if he fought back,
I'd be forced to use violence.
And that would be sad.
His family
would get dragged into it.
Hazel...
- What?
- Violence brings no good.
Haven't you learned?
Huh? You saw
what happened to you.
Because of the violence
you caused,
you lost your child.
Oh, please.
You think I want to do all this?
But what choice do I have?
I'm forced to fight,
to be violent,
because of the villains
in my life.
Especially Felma,
she stole Manuel from me.
Oh, stop giving me that look.
That's how it is, Alice.
You do everything
for the person you love.
That's how it should be.
Even if you hurt people?
That's not love,
that's obsession.
Call it whatever you want.
What matters is that
I got my husband back.
But you used your own child.
My god, Hazel.
It's like Jessica's death
means nothing to you.
That's not true.
Isn't it?
Because, from what I see,
everything you do
has nothing to do
with justice for Jessica.
It's just all about you
taking Manuel back!
Your friend!
What? I'm already calling him!
Bro, what happened?
Why are you with Hazel again?
Did she force you?
Do you want us
to go rescue you again?
No, bro, It's true.
It was really my decision.
So what now? Your decision
to hurt your fam...
Your own family again?
Darling...
can you not interrupt
for a second?
What is it, Manuel?
Huh?
Tell me the truth
because I'm so confused
right now.
I want an explanation,
and it better
be a good one!
Hey! I've heard that in a movie.
You just translated it into
Tagalog.
Can you go over there first?
I want to hear
my friend's explanation.
No, bro.
I'm married to Hazel, right?
So, of course,
I have obligations to her.
Especially now that
our child has died.
Of course, she needs me.
Tell me the truth, Manuel.
Did Hazel threaten you?
What did she say?
She'd massacre Felma
and your kids? Huh?
Where's that little demon?
Let us talk to her!
I heard you.
I'm here.
Paz, Abel, please
don't be angry at Manuel.
Can we just respect
his decision?
And maybe give us a chance
to fix our relationship.
We got back together
because of Jessica.
This is for our daughter.
"For our daughter"?
Hazel, don't you dare
use my godchild.
Jessica is dead.
We dreamed of her.
She told Manuel
to take care of me.
Really?
Stop it, Hazel.
With all the lies you've fed us,
you think we'll believe you now?
Tell me the truth, you witch!
Tell us, Hazel!
What did you do to Manuel?
Did you curse him?
Hex him? Bewitch him?
Paz, Paz, enough.
Hazel had nothing to do
with my decision.
I came back to her on my own.
Oh, really? That's your final
answer, Manuel?
That you went back
to that evil woman?
Fine! Then here's
what I'll say to you
You're an animal!
A soulless,
heartless, useless animal!
So that's why Hazel
was at the resort,
because you had an agreement!
You went to the resort?
Promise me this, darling.
Starting today, you will never
talk to Manuel again.
And if he calls,
you won't answer.
End it! Cut all ties with him.
Friendship over.
Unbelievable.
Manuel is such a traitor.
He came home to the Philippines
just to fool
his family, to hurt them again!
He said he'd get his marriage
to Hazel annulled
so he could go back to Felma!
But what did he do?
Traitor! Full of false hopes!
I'm so angry at Manuel!
I'm furious!
Darling, you're too affected.
You're acting like someone died.
Were you the one
who got left behind?
No.
Then there you go.
Don't be so dramatic.
I'm just hurting for my friend.
Because your friend hurt her!
Darling, enough.
I understand how you feel.
But Darling, honestly,
your acting is Oscar-worthy.
Trying to be the star.
Tone it down.
Go for Best Supporting
Actress instead.
Am I being dramatic, darling?
Let's ask them.
Hazel, I'm asking you.
Did you go to my family outing?
What were you doing there?
Sorry.
I was just scared...
Scared that Felma
might take you away.
At the resort?
I'm sorry.
I wasn't thinking straight.
But I didn't
cause trouble, right?
Felma and I only talked.
Yes, Manuel, she explained
that they just wanted to spend
one last day with you.
And after that, the next day,
she said she'd return you to me.
She returned you willingly.
Felma did that?
Yes.
Didn't she tell you?
She even said,
"Manuel is all yours now."
You're a liar, Dad.
You said you believed me.
Is it true you pushed Jessica?
Dad, I didn't.
Then why are you surrendering?
I'm sorry that
I couldn't save you.
Coleen, I know your sister.
And in my heart, I know
she doesn't blame you.
There's a subpoena already,
you're not alone.
We're all fighting with you.
We'll do everything
to defend you.
She had no reason
to do anything bad
or hurt Jessica, none.
But now, I guess
that wasn't true.
Sir Noah, please come in.
Hi, Didang.
How are things here?
How's Coleen?
Sir, she hasn't been
leaving her room.
What about Felma?
Well, Sir, it's bad news,
good news, then bad news again.
Bad news, good news,
then bad news again?
Here's the thing, Sir.
Ma'am Felma hasn't been
coming out of her room,
just like Coleen.
It's been days.
And she won't eat.
She doesn't talk to anyone.
We're all really worried.
Andrea said the same thing.
Then... what's the good news?
Well... she came out earlier.
And the other bad news?
That's the thing, Sir.
She came out, but food wasn't
the first thing she looked for.
It was alcohol, Sir Noah.
She returned
you to me willingly.
She even said,
"Manuel is all yours now."
Manuel?
I prepared your food.
Come on, eat now.
Don't treat me like a baby.
I can feed myself.
I just want to take care of you.
Are you thinking
about Abel and Paz's call?
Maybe next time,
don't talk to them.
Are you forbidding me, Hazel?
If all they'll do is stress
you out, then why answer?
I'm just protecting you, Manuel.
And besides, let's focus
on starting our new life.
We owe it to our daughter.
Let's not think
of anyone else for now.
And what?
So now I can't talk
to my family? My kids?
Hold on, Hazel,
That wasn't part of the deal.
What deal?
Didn't you say you didn't want
them to know
you're sacrificing yourself
to clear Coleen?
Because she might feel guilty?
Manuel, your kids are angry
at you anyway.
What else is there
to talk about?
Better to let things
cool down first.
Let them accept that you
and I are meant to be.
And eventually, you know,
a day will come,
we'll all get along.
Even me and Felma.
There are wives and mistresses
who end up getting along, right?
I told you not to call
Felma a mistress!
Yes, Hazel, you're my wife.
On paper.
It's Felma...
Felma is the one I love.
Hazel, let me be clear.
I came back because
you said you'd help me
clear Coleen's name.
That doesn't mean I love you.
I know.
I know that, Manuel.
But don't rub it in.
It still hurts.
I just hope, Manuel...
you don't close
your heart completely.
I'll prove to you
that I'm still worthy
of your love.
I can even turn my back
on justice for our daughter...
just to save
your child with Felma.
So, please.
I'm only asking
one simple thing.
Don't talk to them for now.
That's all.
I hope you grant me that,
because if you don't...
I'm sorry, but...
I might stop convincing Timo
to withdraw his statement
against Coleen.
He's already having second
thoughts anyway.
Are you threatening me, Hazel?
No, Manuel.
But it's unfair.
I'm doing everything, right?
For you.
For your child.
And you can't even grant me
this one simple request.
Be fair to me.
Because if not...
maybe you should...
just go back to them.
Maybe we should just end
our agreement.
Why the long face?
Dad isn't answering.
Maybe his phone was confiscated.
I expected that.
That's why I gave Dad
an extra phone.
This is fun!
There are so many of us!
You're so hyper.
Didang! What is that?
Ma'am, that's the dish
you asked me to cook.
No!
What are you trying to imply?
That I'm lying?