Felma, Felma!
Arjun, get the car
ready! Hurry!
I suggest you go through
an executive checkup
as soon as you can.
Doctor, it's just
my head hurting.
Could you please listen
to the doctor?
- Dad.
- Go to Timo.
Tell him we're willing
to help him,
as long as he tells us
everything Hazel
ordered him to do.
Why are you here?
You won't get anything from me.
We promise we'll help you.
I can't risk my family's life.
Didang!
Yes, what is it?
You didn't wake me up!
Hey, what are you saying
I didn't?
Why are you blaming me?
Why always my fault?
Come on, Didang!
Relax.
I tried to wake you up earlier.
You said, Didang,
give me five hours.
So I let you sleep
for five hours.
I said five minutes.
Huh?
Hours! Minutes!
- It's just a minutes?
- Minutes!
Sis, can I go with you to the
hospital?
I'll just change my clothes.
No, Coleen,
I'm in a hurry.
- Ma'am Felma.
- Mom?
Mom.
Mom, sorry.
I was about to go
and pick you up, Mom.
and pick you up.
Where's Auntie?
Weren't you supposed
to be together?
She should've brought you home.
Dear, dear,
all the tests are done.
The results
will come out tomorrow.
Your Auntie Paz
dropped me off here.
Besides, I'm feeling well now.
Ah... wait for me.
I'll just change my clothes.
Let's go to the office together.
Where's...
Where's Jeffrey?
Joel picked him up early
this morning.
Where would they go?
Timo, don't be afraid
to tell us.
Because if Hazel's
threatening you,
then we are your only hope,
Timo.
Get out of here!
I don't even know you!
You won't get anything from me!
Just help my wife
and kids, okay?
And my mom.
I said stop!
Won't you leave?
I don't know you!
If you want to know the truth,
come back tomorrow.
Aren't you leaving?
Are you guys crazy?
What's this, boss?
I don't know them!
No, no, we're leaving.
We're leaving now, thank you.
- We're leaving, Sir.
- Who are they, Sir?
Does Manuel know
what you're going through?
Ah...
No.
I told Jeffrey not to tell him.
I don't want to add
to his burdens.
Ah, you're keeping it
from Manuel.
But not with Noah?
Oh, I get it, confirmed.
What is?
The truth that Manuel
is still the one you love.
Right? You don't want
to burden Manuel,
but it's okay if it's Noah?
Oh, Sis, I don't say
you're using Noah, okay?
It's not like that.
Because we both know you don't.
I know Noah helps willingly.
Even if you drive him away,
he will never turn
his back on you.
My only point is, sis...
As your best friend...
it's okay if you burden me.
It's okay, just lean on me.
I will even carry you
if you want.
Just don't always rely
on Noah, okay?
I don't want to burden...
anyone of you, sis.
So... stop lecturing me.
Because I still have
a lot to finish.
You're distracting me.
Ouch!
So am I the burden now?
Really?
Okay, Madam.
Go back to work.
I'll submit
to the accounting department,
these papers that you signed.
Okay.
Would you like
some coffee, Madam?
- No thanks.
- Water?
Thank you.
Jeffrey...
Do you think
Timo will give in...
and confirm Aunt Felma
and Uncle Manuel's suspicion?
I'm not sure.
He looks desperate, Bro.
And he seems to be scared
for his family.
I hope Timo becomes convinced
that we'll help him.
So he can tell us the truth.
But if he's going to speak up,
why didn't he do it earlier?
Why tomorrow?
I don't know.
Hazel might have people inside.
And she knows
a corrupt police officer.
Right? So maybe
he has men inside.
Maybe Timo's just being careful.
That's possible.
We'll find out tomorrow.
Hello?
Why did you call?
Jeffrey Cruz? Joel Santiago?
Yes.
But they didn't stay long,
Ma'am.
I think it's less than
two minutes.
Timo sent them away.
Did they see me earlier?
I don't know, Ma'am.
But I don't think so.
Because Timo didn't
tell them anything.
For now, nothing.
What about their next visits?
What do I do, Ma'am?
Should I take care of him?
No! What do you think of me?
A murderer?
Just scare him.
I just did, Ma'am.
My hands were itching.
It actually got tired already.
Then teach him a lesson again.
But this time, use your feet.
So that it'll be clear to him
that he can't speak the truth.
Okay, Ma'am.
Please stop, please stop.
I'm begging you.
Sir, please stop!
This is your CT scan report,
Miss Felma.
And this one concerns us.
What is it, Doc?
Tumor located here.
Basing it on the density
and borders,
it's likely to be
a frontal lobe tumor
in your brain.
I have a brain tumor, Doc?
How's your mom's checkup?
They'll find out today.
Mom is in the hospital.
Felma's sick?
What's her illness?
Are you concerned?
I'll be a hypocrite
if I say yes.
I'm just curious.
Jeffrey, I welcomed you
to my house.
Please don't be rude.
I'm not being rude.
Hazel, come on.
Leave us for now.
Just call me
if you need anything.
This tumor, Miss Felma...
could be the root cause
of your symptoms.
Because it's pushing
the tissues around it.
The location is critical.
The frontal lobe controls...
our judgment, behavior, memory,
and motor functions.
We will schedule further imaging
To see the tumor's
boundaries clearly.
After that...
we can determine whether...
the safest approach
would be the medication...
surgical, or...
Doctor...
am I going to have surgery?
Ah...
That is our long-term solution,
Ms. Felma.
It's called surgical resection.
Then once we remove the tumor,
we will send it
to histopathology
to determine if it's benign
or malignant.
Our next steps
will depend on it.
How safe is the operation?
We have advanced equipment.
Complete monitoring
and an experienced
neurosurgical team.
We'll do everything
to save Ms. Felma's life.
But you need to understand
that there is no zero
risk brain operation.
Felma.
Excuse me.
Felma!
Felma, Felma.
Felma.
Felma, are you okay?
Are you okay?
I don't want...
I don't want surgery.
Noah, no.
I might not wake up.
Felma...
What... What do I do, Noah?
I think you need
to tell the kids.
No.
We just got through
Coleen's problem.
And then, Manuel left us.
Felma, they need to know.
It's their right.
I know, but...
but...
I don't want to tell them yet.
How about Manuel?
I hope Timo tells the truth.
And I really hope my and Felma's
suspicion was correct.
Yes, Dad.
Later.
We'll find out later.
That is, if he doesn't
get scared.
If his life
is threatened inside,
Colonel Sarabia must know.
Okay, Dad.
Remember to keep it between us.
Don't tell Coleen and Andrea,
especially your mom.
I don't want her to worry.
Yes, Dad.
Alice...
I need to move fast.
These three won't leave me alone
until they dig up
the truth about Timo.
I'll speed things up.
I will only add to his worries.
And Hazel's with him now.
He doesn't need...
to know what's happening to me.
Noah, I don't want anyone else
to know about this yet.
Okay.
Let's keep it between us.
For now.
And let's deal with it together.
Let's go back to the doctor.
No.
He will just say the same thing.
I have a tumor,
and I need surgery.
I want...
a second opinion.
Okay.
Emil, my cousin,
is one of the top
neurologists in Davao.
I can ask him to come here.
Felma, are you okay now?
Since you don't want
to go back inside,
do you want us to go home now?
So you can get rest.
I don't want to go home yet.
Let's go watch a movie?
Huh? Movie?
Yes.
Let's watch a movie.
Then let's go to a spa.
It's been a while
since I last had a massage.
Then let's have coffee.
Okay, let's do that.
Okay, let's go?
The car's over there.
Come on.
What are you going to do
with my passport?
Manuel...
I need details.
I'm booking a ticket to Taiwan.
Let's take a vacation.
You know, we deserve a break.
We need to take a rest.
Vacation in Taiwan?
Or are you bringing me
back to Canada?
Taiwan.
Vacation, Manuel.
Manuel, there's no reason for us
to go back to Canada.
I had our house sold.
Don't you believe me?
How do you think
we can afford this house
f we'll only rely
on my transcription job?
Hazel, I don't want
to go on vacation.
But Manuel...
I said no!
Okay, Don't get mad.
All right.
Ah.
By the way,
Your firstborn was here earlier.
What did you two talk about?
Why are you interested?
Am I not allowed to ask?
What do you need to know?
Oh, no.
Why?
Did he say something...
you're not supposed to tell me?
Like what?
I don't know.
That's why I'm asking.
What could my son possibly say
that you need to hear?
Jeffrey Cruz? Joel Santiago?
Manuel...
nothing.
Come on.
We'd better get ready.
You might get late
for your therapy session.
Go on.
How's Diana?
I gave Diana and her kids their
financial support in advance.
I even give them
additional money
for Diana's hospital expenses.
I also visited Timo yesterday.
I brought him some groceries.
Okay, Manuel.
I'll get ready now.
Hello?
You're burning hot.
Son of a gun.
Looks like Alonzo's
going to kill you.
Bro...
What's this?
It's the thing we talked about.
It's dangerous, bro.
I'm begging you.
Please help me.
No, bro,
I might get caught.
Alonzo might pick on me next.
For my wife and kids' sake.
I'm begging you.
Please help me, bro.
Please.
Darn it.
Fine, I will.
After this...
I'm staying out of your problem.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh.
- What?
- Oh?
- Why?
- No...
I remember the movie we watched.
- Oh?
- You know,
It's weird.
I thought it was a horror.
Oh.
Looked like
you didn't get scared.
I got annoyed with Arjun
because it was
his recommendation.
I want you to get scared.
Oh really?
- Yes.
- You want me to get scared?
- Seriously? Why...
- And so...
- Do you want a horror film?
- What for?
- So that it'll be more fun.
What do you mean by more fun?
Is it fun for me to get scared?
- What now?
- Shouldn't it be?
Felma?
Noah?
Wow.
What a coincidence.
What a small world.
'Andito rin pala kayo?
Oh, Manuel.
Felma seems to be doing well.
Look, she's even having
a date with Noah.
You know what?
You look good together.
As in, you really suit
each other well.
Mind if we share a table?
If you want to.
- No!
Oh, wow.
That was an intense reaction.
Don't you want
the four of us together?
Like a double date?
Hazel.
Has Auntie Felma
given an update?
Yes, she texted earlier.
She said everything is normal.
Even her lab tests.
She was advised to get some rest
to alleviate her stress.
Bro, I'm sorry.
Malabanan can't meet you
right now.
Huh?
Do you know why, Sir?
He's sick.
But, Sir,
he was doing well yesterday.
I don't know, bro.
He doesn't want to get up.
I think he's having
an upset stomach.
Okay, Sir, ah...
Maybe we'll just
come back tomorrow.
Thank you, Sir.
Son of a...
Are you blind, you jerk?
I didn't mean it.
No? Bastard!
Hey! Let go of me!
- He's hurt...
- You're crazy.
Wait a minute.
Come over here.
You call can leave now.
Visting hourse are over.