Dad, you need to wake up.
You're going back
to your family, Dad.
Our family.
Please take care of Manuel.
We're heading to the hospital.
We'll see you there.
Someone blocked the road!
I will sue you all!
Jessica, get out of that car!
Jessica,
hold dad, okay!
Dad, hold on!
Mr. Manuel, welcome back.
How are you?
Doc, can you please
let Jessica in?
I just have something
to tell her.
Thank you so much
for not leaving me since
the very beginning.
I love you. I love you.
I love you, Dad.
I love you so much.
I'll remember that, Dad.
We need to talk.
What is your problem?
Jessica, you're so selfish!
Didn't you even think something
bad could've happened to him?
Jessica, is that what
a daughter does?
It's like you're not even
dad's child!
I am dad's daughter, Coleen.
I am his daughter!
Don't you ever say that
I'm not his child.
No matter what happens,
I am and will always be his
daughter.
Fine.
You're my father's daughter.
Do you need to repeat it?
Yes!
So it sinks into your head
that I'm daddy's youngest,
not just you.
And don't you dare erase me
from his life, Coleen.
Because I'm his daughter, too.
And that makes me your sister.
No, Jessica.
I don't want you as my sister.
You think I want to be
your sister?
I no longer want to be with you
because you're fake!
You call me fake?
I'm telling you straight to your
face that I don't like you
because you're a stealer.
You stole dad away from me.
Then you went after mom.
And now, you're trying to take
my brother Jeffrey
and my sister Andrea, too!
I'm not taking them away
from you.
I just want to be close to them,
like we used to be, Coleen.
You're just too jealous
and insecure!
I am not insecure about you!
Yes, you are.
Jessica!
Where are you? Brace yourself.
You betrayed me!
You know what, Jessica?
I wish I had never met you!
I wish I had never allowed you
to meet dad!
So now the truth comes out!
You just want him all
to yourself!
You want to keep him away
from me!
I wish you'd just disappear!
So that my family would finally
be happy!
Disappear?
Coleen, you want me gone just so
you can have dad to yourself?
That's not what I meant!
No!
No, that's what you meant.
You want me dead, Coleen.
You want me gone so you won't
have to share anymore.
That's the cruelest thing anyone
has ever said to me, Coleen.
And coming from you,
my own sister.
I never thought the person who'd
tell me to die would be you.
Hello there,
Miss Felma and Coleen.
Jessica, can you tell dad
that I'm always thinking of him
and that I'm always praying
for him?
Of course.
Coleen.
Jessica.
Dad?
Coleen, my dear?
Dad!
Jessica.
Didang, help me bring them
inside through the back.
Jessica, these are some
of my clothes.
They should fit you.
Thank you, Coleen.
Dance with dad tonight, okay?
Jessica...
Jessica, I'm sorry.
Jessica, please. I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- No, Coleen.
That's not what I meant,
Jessica, please...
I swear,
that's not what I meant!
- No!
- Jessica, please, I'm so sorry!
Please, Jessica! Please!
During the trip,
dad seemed fine.
He was so talkative.
Uncle even had to tell him
to quiet down.
Maybe he got too excited
to see all of us.
He suddenly got stronger
because he managed to escape
the clutches of that witch.
- Please, Jessica!
- No!
- Hey!
- Let go of me!
Was that Hazel?
That sounded like Jessica!
Wasn't that Coleen's voice?
What now?
No! Don't stop me!
That was Coleen!
- Coleen!
Coleen?
Yeah.
I have to go.
What's going on?
Please stop!
No!
I haven't gotten even yet
with what you did to my child!
- Enough!
- No!
Ouch!
Are you two fighting again?
Can't you just make peace
already?
What are you doing?
Jessica!
Stay out of this!
Jeffrey!
That's enough!
- No! Please stop!
- Let go of me!
Mom! Enough!
Enough!
All you do is fight!
All you bring is trouble!
Jessica!
Jessica, wait!
- Jessica! Jessica!
- I'm done!
I just want to go home!
Jessica, please wait.
Jessica, wait!
Jessica, please!
Let go of me, Coleen!
Just let go!
Jessica, please, let's talk.
I'm sorry. Please.
No! You want me gone, right?
Fine! I'm leaving!
I don't want to see
any of you ever again!
Jessica, no!
What are you doing?
Jessica, please!
I realized my mistake!
I'm sorry.
Let's talk about this, Jessica!
- Coleen, stop! No!
- Jessica, please!
Jessica!
Oh my God! The girl!
Jessica! Jessica!
Jessica!
Please, help my sister!
Somebody help us!
Jessica!
Please help us!
Please help us! Call a doctor!
Please! Jessica!
Okay.
Good progress.
You're not having a hard time,
right, Manuel?
Not at all, Doctor.
Okay. We'll move you
to a regular room.
But you still need close
monitoring, okay?
Okay, Doc.
Okay.
Right now fixing your admitting
orders for the regular room.
In a bit,
you can be transferred.
Thank you, Doctor.
So, what the doctor said
is true?
You suddenly felt stronger?
Yes, Felma.
You know, I really feel stronger
whenever I'm with you.
Felma, you are my strength.
You and our children.
Psychosomatic.
Good emotions really trigger
good healing.
All right, I'll leave you two
alone.
Thank you, Doctor.
Ouch! It hurts!
Let go of me, Abel!
Let go of me!
- Why are you interfering here?
- A child got hit!
Hazel!
Jessica?
- Jessica!
- Hazel!
Hazel!
Coleen!
Coleen! Coleen!
Jessica!
Jessica, please wake up!
Help!
It's Jessica! Wake up!
Jessica, please!
We're going to the hospital,
please!
Jessica, please wake up!
You need to see a doctor!
Help!
Jessica, please, let's talk!
- Jessica! Jessica! My God!
- Help!
Jessica! Jessica!
Oh my God, Jessica!
- What did you do?
- Nothing!
- What happened?
- Nothing, nothing!
- Jessica!
- Coleen!
Come on, come on, come on...
Oh my God, Jessica!
- No! Jessica!
- Help! Call!
Ambulance!
- Call an ambulance!
- Help! Dear, hang in there!
Help! Jessica! Jessica, dear!
My God! Where is it?
Hurry! Jessica! Call them!
Dear! Hurry! Hurry up!
- Jessica!
Dear, hang in there.
God really is good.
He gave us a chance to be
together again.
You know, Felma, I thought we'd
never see each other again.
Manuel, did Hazel make you sign
a Discharge Against Medical
Advice form?
No, only the one for the health
insurance.
She forged your signature.
That's how she got you out.
That woman doesn't care at all.
Even if your life
were in danger,
she'd do whatever to get you
away from us.
Hazel is such a monster.
Once I recover,
I'll file an illegal detention
case against her.
And Attorney Yeban and I will
also file the annulment case.
Manuel, don't stress yourself.
I'm sorry I brought up the fake
signature.
Where do you think the kids are?
They haven't even checked in.
Maybe they just stepped out
to buy something.
They probably thought I'd be
stuck in the ER for a while.
I'll text them
as soon as you're in the room.
Do you think Jessica
is with them?
Most likely.
She's okay with Jeff now, right?
Andrea's fine with her, too.
Only Coleen is the problem.
I hope they make up.
If they still don't, I'll sit
them down until they make up.
And if they still don't
reconcile,
I'll really give them
a good beating.
This is exhausting. It's the
same thing over and over.
Oh, here it is. Come on.
Jessica!
We're almost at the ER, dear.
Okay? Hang in there. Dear.
Dear, we're almost there.
Almost there.
Status?
Severe maxillofacial
trauma, Doctor.
Positive for intracranial
bleeding, abdominal hemorrhage,
and a closed left femur
fracture.
GCS-11, E-324, B2M6.
Doctor, her facial bones
are broken,
so she's having difficulty
speaking.
Prepare for an emergency
exploratory laparotomy.
- Yes, Doctor.
- Is the blood ready?
Yes, Doctor.
Page the anesthesiologist and
the neurosurgeon on duty now.
Yes, Doctor.
Jessica, sweetheart.
Mommy is here.
Nurse Glo, please. Let me in.
I'm a nurse, too.
I know what to do.
Sorry, Nurse Hazel.
You know the protocol.
You can only go this far.
Wait a moment. I'm a nurse, too.
I know what to do.
I won't interfere.
I just want to be there
by my daughter's side.
We'll take care
of your daughter.
Wait, Nurse Glo!
Sweetheart, Jessica,
mommy's right here.
Coleen, sweetheart.
Are you ready to share
what happened?
I was holding her.
I didn't mean it.
No...
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
Not a single one of them
even replied.
Are they with Jessica?
- Miss Felma, hi.
- Doctor.
He's asleep.
- Is everything okay?
- Yes.
All right.
How's he doing, nurse?
Please check.
Are the vitals from earlier
okay?
Doctor, all vitals are good.
Okay. Please show me the chart.
Okay. Good. Good.
Let's do VS Q2.
Same IV to continue.
Continue the Piptaz.
If he stays stable for the next
24 hours,
we'll check vitals every
4 hours.
- Okay.
- Yes, Doc. Okay.
Manuel is good.
Okay?
- Thank you, Doctor.
- Okay.
What happened?
Tell us so we can understand.
You have to say it, okay?
Andrea.
Andrea, maybe we shouldn't
push her.
It's still too hard for her.
Sorry, dear.
Mom's calling.
What should I say?
Should I tell her?
Tell her the truth.
We need to tell her
what happened.
Wait, darling. No, not yet.
If we tell Felma,
she'll tell Manuel.
He might have a heart attack.
No, no, no.
Jeffrey, I agree with Aunt Paz.
Maybe it's better not to say
anything yet.
Your dad might be shocked.
Hello, Mom?
Jeffrey, why didn't you answer
my texts?
Your father has already been
moved to the regular room.
Where are you, kids?
Mom, we'll go home with Coleen
and Andrea first.
We'll get you some stuff.
Since dad will be staying here
a few days, right?
You'll watch over him, right?
Oh, yeah.
Good thinking.
Thank you.
Okay, Mom. Take care.
Andrea, message Didang.
Tell her to send mom's things.
Probably enough for 2 to 3 days.
Have her deliver it.
Okay, okay.
Uncle, Auntie...
You can go see mom
and dad first.
Okay, we will.
But...
when do we tell them?
Uncle, should we tell them now?
I think it's better to make sure
Jessica is okay first.
What matters most right now
is her condition.
I'll just go to the OR
and check her status, okay?
I'll go with you.
Me, too.
I'll come too.
Are you sure, dear?
Uncle, Auntie,
we'll go there for now.
- All right, all right.
- We'll go now.
It feels like it was just
yesterday I was here.
Manuel was inside then...
now it's Jessica.
What will happen next?
Alice,
maybe...
will it be my turn?
But...
if that happens,
will Manuel and Jessica
still be here for me?
Or...
maybe they'll be with Felma's
family?
Celebrating.
Hoping I won't survive...
Is that it?
Is that next, Alice?
Enough, friend.
Stop imagining all that.
Jessica!
Alice.
Alice, what's happening
to Jessica?
What?
I don't know, but...
I have a really bad feeling
something's happening
to Jessica.
Alice.
Let's see Jessica.
- No. Calm down, friend.
- Jessica.
Doc, we're losing her.
EP.
Charge to 160.
Clear.
Start CPR.
Rhythm check.
Charge to 250.
Start CPR.
Jessica.
Something bad is happening
to Jessica.
Friend...
Friend, stay calm.
Jessica is in good hands.
We're at Southcrest.
The people here are excellent.
The doctors are excellent.
Jessica.
CPR.
Rhythm check.
Charge to 350.
Clear.
Begin CPR.
What is it that you're not
telling me?
Are you waiting for me
to get angry?
Mom, can you not tell dad
just yet?
So you're here.
Where did you get that criminal
streak from?
Mom! Stop it!
Dad, maybe we can make this
real?
We'll make our family real.
There's one more thing
I wish for.
If it's possible,
could you also treat Jessica
like family?
You're defending your daughter?
After what she did to mine?
What did she do?
Coleen, admit it.
You pushed Jessica,
and that's why she got hit
by the car!
What happened?
I will not forgive
what they did to you.
So wake up.
I want you to see
what I will do to her.