Coleen, this is Arjun,
my executive assistant.
Attorney.
Artemio Vital, my lawyer.
I coordinated with Atty. Yeban
about filing for bail.
We're working on the paperwork
as we speak.
You're getting out.
Thank you, Uncle.
They said Coleen
has already posted bail.
How did that happen?
Mrs. Cruz, there are exceptions.
And it still depends
on the executive judge.
Maybe they personally know him.
Who are they?
A certain Atty. Artemio Vital,
who's representing
Noah Salvador.
Noah,
thank you so much
for helping Coleen.
I'm just glad to be of help
to my daughter...
what I mean is the people...
I consider family.
I don't even know what to say.
I didn't expect
you'd still be here.
Felma, you were once a very
important part of my life.
Again, thank you.
Sir, excuse me.
The car is ready.
We have a flight to catch.
Arjun,
rebook my flight going home.
I'll stick around for a while.
And free my schedule
for the next two weeks.
Yes, Sir.
Darn it.
So annoying.
Coleen hasn't even warmed
her seat in jail,
and they already let her out.
So Noah's a big shot?
He's really influential.
Are you trying to annoy me?
What "influential"
are you talking about?
Coleen will still end up
behind bars.
But Coleen and Felma now have
an even bigger support system.
The stronger they get,
the more determined they are
to fight back.
What are you trying to say?
They are on full force?
Happy family?
So Noah's just the extra wheel?
But you know what?
With his status...
I doubt he'd let himself
be just an extra wheel.
He once fell head over heels
with Felma.
Who knows?
He might try
to win her over again.
And so what?
Felma won't entertain him.
Felma loves Manuel, remember?
Felma doesn't have
to be in love with Noah
to be in a relationship
with him.
It might actually be better
if they end up together.
So I can easily
take Manuel back.
How?
Your husband is mad
at you, remember?
Because you keep picking
fights with him over Jessica.
Will you waste your time
on that?
You're still mourning the loss
of your child.
You're even fighting for her
to get justice.
Alice, all my moves
are connected.
So better keep your eyes open.
Just watch and learn.
There you go, sweetie. I've had
Didang replace your bedsheet.
So you'll have
a good night's sleep.
Thank you, bro.
We'll have a good night's sleep,
too.
Because we know
you're just in the other room.
Right.
And it's hard to sleep
in the cell.
I'm really glad Uncle Noah came.
Yeah.
And...
I'm glad he still cares for us.
It's like we have two dads.
But it would've been better
if things between them is okay.
They seemed awkward
with each other, right?
Were they awkward earlier?
Is that why you kicked me, sis?
They're not just the ones
who feel awkward.
Jeff and I, too.
I don't know
how I'll act or what I'll say
when they're both there.
I'm really thankful
to Uncle Noah.
But I don't know
how to express it...
without offending Dad.
And whatever we say to Dad,
we have to make sure Uncle Noah
doesn't feel out of place.
We should also consider how
that will be perceived by Mom.
You know what?
Don't worry about that for now.
Let's just be thankful
that I'm out of jail.
And I'm back home.
So...
let's sleep together tonight.
- Good?
- That's good.
Here.
- I'm okay with it.
- I'm getting ready.
But are you sure
you're sleeping beside him?
He snores so loudly.
Wow.
You're so mean.
But at least I only snore
when I'm sleeping.
Unlike you,
who snore when laughing.
Hey! No!
That's not true!
Felma.
Hopefully, you can finally
get some rest now that...
Coleen's here.
You too, right?
Yes.
Thanks to Noah.
I didn't know
he was such a good person.
Yes, he is.
And please don't get me wrong.
But...
when you weren't here,
Noah helped me raise the kids.
He helped me...
with work...
and with raising them.
Especially Coleen.
He treated the kids
like his own.
I was also thankful for that.
Because when I wasn't here,
he picked up where I fell short.
And now he's helping Coleen.
You know what...
I'll be forever thankful.
Yeah. I'm also grateful
to know that...
he has already moved on
with what happened to us.
Yeah, I noticed.
You're still friends.
That's all there
is to it, Manuel.
Noah's helping us
with no hidden agenda.
Of course.
We shouldn't give
it another meaning.
He's helping our daughter.
Wow!
He's like a knight
in shining armor, sis.
How does it feel
when your ex suddenly swoops in
to save you?
Oh, sorry. Second ex.
Because your first ex is Manuel.
I don't feel anything
but gratitude.
Really? Just gratitude?
You didn't feel your heart
skip even once?
Admit it, sis. You loved him.
Bro,
as far as I know,
Felma never fell in love
with Noah.
Because it's you
who Felma loves.
So, there's nothing
to be jealous about.
Why? Is Manuel jealous?
I don't think so.
And I assured him that
Noah's helping us
without any hidden agenda.
Sis, don't be too sure
that Noah's help comes
with no strings attached.
Girl!
Sis,
stop it. Someone might hear you.
If you were in my shoes...
Imagine...
someone going after Paz,
and it happens to be her ex.
Would that be alright with you?
Of course not.
She's my wife.
I'll beat that guy to a pulp.
That's what I'm talking about.
But Paz is your wife.
You have the right.
Felma and I are not
in a relationship.
And we can't be together
until my marriage to Hazel
is annulled.
I have no right to stop Noah
from getting near her.
Why?
Would you stop him?
Then you're jealous.
Manuel has nothing
to worry about.
He knows that he's
the one I love.
And Noah knows it, too.
But I'm just wondering...
why he returned.
And why did he suddenly
help you?
Because...
he loves Coleen?
And it didn't change.
And so are his feelings for you,
sis!
Noah's still in love with you.
Come on. Stop it now.
Before anything
else happens.
You're making me nervous.
Sis. I'll bet you
my monthly salary.
Actually, scratch that.
Just half. Mayette hasn't sent
me anything yet.
I really don't want to doubt
Noah's intentions in helping us.
Of course,
it makes me feel guilty.
He's helping, and I'm thinking
badly about him.
But I can't help
thinking about that.
It's because...
you love Felma.
It makes me
feel small, man.
When I wasn't here,
he'd been stepping in for me,
he's still doing it now.
Being here isn't enough.
I have to be wealthy and
powerful just to help my family.
You know what, bro.
You can still help
in another way.
Like this.
You learned that
so you can earn some money.
I know.
But it's different
when I'm employed.
I'll find people who can
actually help my family.
Bro...
I want to get strong
enough to walk again.
Maybe there's another way
for you to walk again.
Bro, I'll do everything
for my family.
Especially now that
Coleen's arraignment is near.
She badly needs
my support.
As I have said,
the arraignment is just to
confirm your identity, Coleen,
as the accused.
And the cases that
will be charged against you.
Okay?
Coleen, dear.
Dad,
Mom...
I'm scared.
I don't think I can handle this.
Dear, we'll go with you
inside to support you.
We'll face the judge
together, sweetheart.
Dear,
you can do this.
Jessica's watching you.
Keep in mind that you're
doing this for her.
Jessica wouldn't like it
if she saw you losing courage,
right?
Coleen, sweetie...
remember that you're innocent.
Just tell them the truth.
Think about the plans
you and Jessica made.
Those plans can only happen
when you're free.
We're here for you, Coleen.
You can do it,
my dear goddaughter.
You take after your godmother.
A fighter!
There you go again, butting in.
Uncle Noah?
Thank you.
Here.
Here you go, dear.
This might help you.
Thank you, Uncle.
Noah,
what are you doing here?
The same thing you're doing.
Giving my full support
to Coleen.
Dear, are you okay now?
Thank you, Uncle Noah.
Thank you for coming.
Coleen,
you can do this.
We are all here for you.
We're not going to
leave you alone, dear.
Okay?
- Attorney Yeban.
- Mr. Salvador,
- it's good to see you again.
- Good to see you also.
Do everything to
win this case, okay?
They're ready, Sir.
Thank you.
So,
let's go inside.
Come on.
All rise.
RTC Branch 17 is now in session.
Honorable Judge
Bryan Palestino presiding.
Silence is enjoined.
Read the case.
For arraignment.
Criminal Case 2025-828.
People of the Philippines
versus Coleen Ruiz Cruz,
for the crime of murder,
under Article 248
of the Revised Penal Code.
Appearances.
For the people.
Your Honor,
I respectfully appear
as the private prosecutor,
Attorney Nico Salazar.
Good morning, Your Honor.
Attorney Butch Yeban,
representing the accused.
Are you ready
for the arraignment?
Yes, Your Honor.
Where's the accused?
Yes, Your Honor. She's here.
It's okay.
The undersigned City Prosecutor
accuses Coleen Ruiz Cruz
of the crime of murder,
defined and penalized
under Article 428
of the Revised Penal Code.
Committed as follows,
that on or about
November 3rd, 2025,
in the City of Quezon,
Metro Manila, Philippines,
a place within the jurisdiction
of this honorable court,
the above-named accused
by means of treachery
with intent to kill,
did then and there willfully,
unlawfully,
and feloniously push
Jessica Cruz
towards an oncoming vehicle.
Thereby hitting the latter,
which caused her death.
Contrary to law.
How do you plead?
Do you understand the charges
against you, Ms. Cruz?
Yes, Your Honor.
And what is your plea?
Not guilty, Your Honor.
How dare you!
You're such a liar!
What do you mean by not guilty?
Mrs. Cruz!
You killed my daughter!
You killed her!
What were you saying?
Admit it!
Don't believe
her, Your Honor.
I didn't commit any crime.
Coleen, it's okay.
Order in the court! Order!
Order in the court!
This is not yet the trial.
This proceeding is not
the proper forum for testimony.
I'm instructing everyone to
maintain decorum in this court.
Please schedule
the pre-trial.
Coleen, sweetie,
are you still okay?
It felt so different
inside, didn't it, Mom?
I felt like I did something
wrong even though I didn't.
You did well, Coleen.
Always remember,
don't let what people say
or think get to you. Okay?
Just stick to the truth.
That will strengthen you.
Thank you, Attorney.
Thanks for your help.
The support of the family
is what helps Coleen.
Family and friends.
Also, your godfather
and godmother.
Sweetheart,
we're in this fight together.
Sweetie, I promise.
No matter when the hearing
is, we'll be here.
We're always present.
We're all here for you.
Thank you, Dad.
Thank you, everyone.
Wait.
Where's Noah?
We're sorry.
The number you have reached...
Who are you calling?
We're sorry.
The number you have reached...
Noah.
We weren't able to talk
to him earlier.
He might think that we
didn't appreciate his presence.
I don't think so.
We were able to talk
before the arraignment.
Maybe he had something
important to do,
so he had to leave
without saying goodbye.
I guess there's no need
to call him now.
Are you jealous?
Goodness, Felma.
Why would I get jealous?
Right.
You have nothing
to be jealous about.
Exactly.
You know my feelings
for you, right?
Also,
our situation.
Yes.
Nothing has changed.
I'll still file for annulment
of my marriage with Hazel.
So we can get married.
I don't know. Maybe...
I'm not used to him being here.
I'm used to us being the only
ones who care about our kids.
Forget it. Don't worry about it.
What matters is that
he helped Coleen.
By any means.
Thank you for
understanding, Manuel.
I only want...
to assure you that...
Noah and I are just friends.
That's it.
Hi.
Thank you for accepting
my invitation.
You want anything? Coffee?
I don't have all day.
Tell me what I need to know.
Direct to the point.
I like that.
Exactly what I want.
Fine.
I'll get straight to the point.
I want us to be allies.
What?
We both want the same thing.
Be with the ones we love.
You know what...
I think I already
heard this.
I don't give up easily, Noah.
I feel that you still love Felma
so much.
I feel the same way
about Manuel.
So let's work together
so you can get Felma,
and I can take my husband back.
I saw two women fighting
on the sidewalk.
One of them is Coleen Cruz.
She pushed the victim.
It happened so fast.
I tried to brake, but I ended up
hitting the woman.
That's not true!
He's lying!
I didn't push my sister!
No matter what I do,
I still can't encourage Coleen.
It seems not enough.
You don't have
to do it all.
Andrea and Jeffrey are there,
Manuel is too,
and I'm here.
I'm not doing this
to ruin their family.
You're not back in Felma's life
for Coleen's sake.
The truth is,
you saw your chance.
You helped Coleen just to
be the hero in Felma's eyes.