Hazel's serious
about her accusation.
She really believes
Coleen killed Jessica.
Let her accuse all she wants.
The truth will eventually
come out,
and it will prove that
our daughter is innocent.
They found an abandoned
vehicle in Fairview.
The police can't confirm it yet,
but there's a dent
in the bumper.
Right where the footage
showed Jessica getting hit.
There will only be justice
when that Coleen girl
is behind bars.
That's why I swear, dear.
I won't let Coleen
have a moment of peace.
Dad, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry you can't go
to my sister's funeral
because of me.
I'm so sorry, Dad.
Sorry, Jessica.
I hope you know
how much I love you.
Because no matter what happens,
you're my child.
Jessica, please forgive me,
my child.
Why did you take Jessica away
from me so soon?
You know how much I've suffered
when I lost Jeff, Andeng,
and Coleen.
And now that things were finally
starting to get better,
you took Jessica away from me!
It's Jessica, right?
Yes.
Please, calm down.
I don't know why
Andrea called you.
She said a lot
of hurtful things.
But please, don't let her anger
at mom drag dad into it.
I know I'm the result of what
mom and dad did to you,
their mistake.
And yet, you were so kind to me.
Thank you so much.
I feel loved and accepted
by a very special person
who is in any way
not related to me.
That person is Aunt Felma.
I want to honor her
for her kindness.
Jeffrey, why are you
still awake?
Why are you talking to me?
Are we even close?
Sorry.
Jessica!
That's enough!
- Stay away!
- Enough!
Outsider!
Aren't you tired
of being bullied
by your own children, Dad?
Won't you stop?
You weren't even part of this,
right?
Jessica, let's go.
Let's go home.
Let's just go straight home.
I'll recover there.
Dad, even if you feel fine,
you still need to see a doctor.
Dad, please listen to my sister.
Jessica, you're not
getting out of this car.
You're staying with us.
We're going home together.
I don't care about your dad.
And please tell your
good-for-nothing mother
that she disrespected my family
first when she stole my father.
And you.
Who are you, really?
Mrs. Wilson's calling, Jessica.
Andrea, please don't be mad
at Coleen.
How many times do I have to tell
you, don't call me sister!
And stop meddling.
You're not part
of this family.
Jessica is our guest.
Guests are welcome here.
But she isn't welcome.
Jessica let me in.
She hurried me.
I don't know why.
She pushed her down the stairs.
I'm sorry, I couldn't stop her.
You did nothing wrong, Jessica.
But me, I've done so much wrong
to you.
- I'm sorry.
- It's over.
Let's forget about it.
You're not even part
of this family!
Good thing that I don't belong
to your family!
Because I don't want to belong
to a family
that's rude and doesn't know
how to forgive!
And what will you do?
Stop dad's annulment
with your mom?
How dare you!
I'm your sister, Coleen!
I don't want you as my sister!
I wish you'd just disappear
so my family could
finally be happy!
- Jessica, please!
- No!
- Let me go!
- Jessica!
Jessica!
You shameless people!
How dare you!
- You shameless people!
- Friend!
I wish this were
just a dream, dear.
I wish that when I wake up
tomorrow...
I'd still see you.
I wish it were me
lying there, not you.
Because I'm the reason
for all this pain.
If I weren't here, everyone's
lives would be peaceful.
It should've been me.
I should've been
the one who died.
What do you think
you're doing?
Hazel, come on.
Don't! Stop!
Let go of me!
Let me go!
Mrs. Cruz, please,
don't be the aggressor.
We can't just come after them.
You could be charged.
If you want justice
for your daughter,
let's do this through the law.
Not through anger.
Attorney, I no longer care
about your laws!
What they did to me
was an insult!
Only Manuel and I should
be mourning Jessica.
Not them.
They don't belong here.
Hazel...
Didn't you forbid them
from coming?
Yes.
And I regret it.
I thought Manuel would
still come to comfort me.
But I never imagined...
he'd sneak in with his
illegitimate family.
So, friend,
what's your plan now?
To make Coleen pay.
And after that?
You're flying back to Canada?
There's nothing left
for me there, Alice.
I'm staying here.
I'll start working again.
And I'm moving out.
A townhouse, maybe.
Not a condo this time.
I already asked Maximo
to look for one.
Wait, a whole house?
Where will you get
the money for rent?
Mr. and Mrs. Wilson are still
sending support.
I already told them we won't be
going back to Canada for now.
They didn't even take back
the money they gave
for our plane tickets.
So, I've saved enough.
Then why a whole house?
Alice...
Because I'm preparing
for something.
I'm preparing for
Manuel's return.
Manuel's coming back, Alice.
Friend, I know you're grieving.
But don't be delusional.
Why would Manuel come back?
Jessica's gone.
She was the only reason he
might've looked your way again.
Just wait and see, Alice.
Dad, I'll sleep here
in your room.
So you won't be alone.
Okay?
Sir Manuel?
Sir Manuel! You're home already!
- Welcome home, Sir Manuel!
- Didang!
It's all right, Didang.
Thank you for welcoming
Manuel back.
I'm sorry.
Son, let me help you with that.
No, Mom, it's fine.
I can handle it. It's easy.
Come on, tell me.
What's wrong?
Dad...
just hold me.
Please don't let go.
My baby girl just
wanted a hug.
I love you so much, Dad.
Dad, I love you.
I love you so much, too,
sweetheart.
Ma'am...
That's it...
just like what I've
seen in the dramas.
But it hurts so much more
when you see it in real life.
Jessica, I'll miss you.
Didang, stop crying now.
Come on, let's go.
Dad, I can't imagine your pain.
I lost a child, too, yes.
But I know where my Tetay is.
I can visit her...
I can still see her...
I can hold her again.
But yours, it's different.
Dad, I'm here, okay?
I won't leave you.
If you ever need someone
to drink with, I'm here, okay?
Just say the word,
we'll drink all night.
Didang, please bring this
to Coleen.
- Yes, Ma'am.
- I'll be there in a while.
All right.
Where's your dad?
I called him already, but
he won't come out of his room.
Call him again.
I already went twice, Mom.
He said he was not
in the mood to eat.
Oh, no, he needs to eat.
He's taking so many medicines.
All right, Mom,
I'll go and call him.
It was supposed to be our first
dinner together again
as a complete family, right?
It'll happen, son.
When everything's okay.
Yes, but...
dad isn't the same anymore.
Because Jessica's gone.
We'll never be with her anymore.
Dad, come on now.
Please eat something.
You need to eat, Dad.
You're still recovering.
You know, Andeng...
It's so hard to accept that
your sister's gone.
The only reason I managed
to be away from you all
those years was...
because of Jessica.
When she was growing up,
I saw you in her.
When she was a baby,
she reminded me so much
of Coleen.
But the older she got,
the more she became like you.
Your hug, your sweetness...
Everything about her
reminded me of you.
Sometimes, I'd even call her
Andeng by mistake.
I wish you'd spent
more time together.
You'd have seen how alike
you really were.
And I'm sure,
you two would've gotten
along so well.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Mrs. Cruz, the case
you can file against Coleen...
is reckless imprudence
resulting in homicide.
If it's true that
she pushed Jessica.
They think I'm just making
accusations, Attorney.
But I know what I feel.
I know Coleen pushed
my daughter.
I can feel it,
a mother's instinct!
Okay, if that's your conviction.
But you know, Mrs. Cruz,
mother's instinct isn't
admissible in the court of law.
Mrs. Cruz, what we need
is evidence.
You really have no shame,
Coleen.
How dare you show
your face here.
Mrs. Cruz!
Are we leaving now?
Oh, where are we supposed to go?
We just got here!
Mrs. Cruz, whatever plan
you've got in mind,
don't go through with it!
What?
Now you know how it feels
to almost get hit by a car.
You were just almost hit,
but did you see my daughter?
She was thrown,
and she died!
Because of you!
No, I didn't do anything wrong.
What do you mean you didn't?
- I swear, I didn't!
- It was your fault!
It was your fault!
It was your fault
my daughter's dead!
- No.
- I won't forget that.
I can never forgive you!
- No! I didn't push Jessica!
- I'll never forgive you!
- No!
- I didn't push Jessica!
Please believe me!
I didn't push my sister!
- Please, I'm begging you.
- What...
It was an accident!
- Mrs. Cruz.
- I'll never believe you.
- And I'll never forgive you.
- Please.
- Do you understand?
- Mrs. Cruz, that's enough!
I will never forgive you!
Go home.
What are you doing, Attorney?
What?
Mrs. Cruz.
What were you thinking?
Why did you do that?
If you went through with it,
you're done!
What?
Hazel did that?
That woman's completely
lost her mind.
Andrea, what's that?
What are you doing?
Are you telling mom?
No,
but, yes, I'm telling
Attorney Yeban.
We have to do something
about Hazel.
Please don't.
Things are already a mess.
Let's not make it worse, please.
Coleen, are you serious?
She tried to run you over!
Oh, what's that?
What if she'd killed you?
She was just trying to scare me.
Please, Andrea, let's just keep
this between us, okay?
That's why I told you here...
So, no one else would hear.
No one else must know.
Please, Andrea, don't tell mom.
Especially not dad.
Nothing bad happened to me, see?
So what now, Coleen?
You'll just wait for her
to try again?
Wait until something bad
happens to you?
Please, Andrea.
Okay, fine.
But what were you even doing
at Jessica's grave?
You even went there
all by yourself.
I just wanted some time
with her.
I want to talk to her.
I want to pour out
my thoughts to her.
To tell her I'm sorry, Andrea.
So maybe I could feel
a little less guilty.
The guilt that I feel.
Is that dad?
What's he doing here?
After killing you,
she now visits you.
Calls you her sister.
Coleen needs
to stop pretending.
Why?
She feels guilty?
Then she should take
that guilt somewhere else.
Off a rooftop, a cliff.
A bridge, I don't care.
If she wants, she can jump.
Sweetie...
Sweetie, I miss you.
About earlier...
why did you do that?
You nearly gave me
a heart attack.
Oh, please, Attorney.
You're not having a heart attack
because of that.
It's because of all the
junk food you've been eating.
Mrs. Cruz, this isn't a joke.
That was a serious offense.
That was attempted homicide!
Coleen could file charges
against you.
And who's going to testify?
The ghosts in this place?
Mrs. Cruz, please,
don't be sarcastic.
I'm warning you.
Okay. Sorry.
It won't happen again.
Attorney...
can you leave me alone
for a while?
He doesn't want us
to see him grieving.
You know, dear...
I'm really trying
to accept that...
that you're gone.
But it's so hard.
It's unbearably hard.
You shouldn't have left,
Jessica.
You shouldn't have left.
You shouldn't have left,
sweetheart.
I miss you so much.
Coleen.
Later, okay?
Go to him later, all right?
I'm sorry, dear!
I'm sorry!
Jessica, my child.
Jessica, wait.
Thank you for loving me back.
Thank you for treating me
like your own child.
Why would I ever treat you
any differently?
Dad, please forgive me.
Mommy and I.
Please forgive us, Dad.
- Jessica!
- Dad, Dad!
- Jessica.
- Jessica, Jessica!
- Dad! Dad!
Who here is Miss Coleen
Ruiz Cruz?
What do you need from her?
We're just inviting her
to the precinct.
Do you have a warrant?