Okay, Felma, be honest with me.
What if you see him right now?
What are you going to do?
I no longer feel
anything for him.
You're changing the topic!
Whatever!
Manuel! What's wrong with you?
I've been calling your name.
You went to Daisy's place, Jeff.
Why didn't you talk to her?
I don't know
how to approach them.
Just admit that you're a coward
like your father.
Don't compare me to your dad.
I went abroad,
and I did everything I could.
What did you do in return?
You spent all
my hard-earned money.
Hazel, why don't you listen to
what they have to say?
They're your family.
You have to forgive each other.
You want to talk to Felma?
So that's the reason,
why you want me to get along
with my siblings.
You want to reconnect
with Felma.
- Hey!
- I came here,
-to stop you.
-Bro, If you don't want to help,
then don't! But don't try
to stop me!
- You can't!
- Manuel?
Ma'am.
Hey, Felma.
Why do you look like that?
I thought...
I saw Manuel outside.
What? You saw Manuel?
What is he doing here?
Why is he doing here?
Were you able to talk?
What did you say?
We didn't get to talk.
Wait a minute, Felma...
Manuel, the cheater
is in Canada.
Maybe you're just seeing things.
And if he's here in
the Philippines,
Abel would have told me already.
That's what I'm saying,
I thought I saw him with Abel.
I thought...
I really thought I saw him.
I suddenly felt nervous.
Felma, what's going on with you?
Don't tell me you're still
thinking about him.
I'm not!
His name just came up,
because of Jeffrey's issue
with Daisy.
Andrea told him that
he's just like Manuel.
That he abandoned his family.
And then, because of my upcoming
interview with Filipino moms,
old photos of Manuel were dug up
from our photo album.
Coleen kept all of them.
The pain suddenly came back,
along with the anger.
Felma, calm down.
Don't let Manuel affect you
like this.
That's the thing.
Noah told me the same thing.
Then that's what you should do.
Where have you been?
You went to see Felma,
didn't you?
I did.
I wanted to apologize to her and
our children in person.
How dare you!
You're so shameless.
Didn't I tell you not
to see her?
Hazel...
I've been away from them for
eighteen years!
Can't I see them,
even just for a moment?
What's the point of seeing her
for a minute?
You'll get back together
with her?
To be forgiven!
I don't believe you!
What is it, Manuel?
What did you talk about?
Maybe she can't wait
to get back together with you.
Hazel, can you stop this?
No way! I'm your wife!
I have the right!
I will never let her
take you from me!
Hazel, she's not going
to take me from you!
I didn't even get to see her!
Tell me!
What did she tell you?
What is your plan!
- Tell me!
- Stop!
Tell me now, Manuel!
Tell me! What's your plan?
- Hazel!
- Because I know,
- Mom...
- I'll find out eventually.
Mom! Dad!
Your mom is getting
paranoid again.
She's having
all kinds of thoughts!
Where are you going now?
- We're not done talking yet!
- Mom!
- Manuel!
- Mom, stop!
Hello, Jessica?
Dad, where are you?
I'm outside, I'm just trying to
cool my head.
Dad, what happened?
It's your mom.
She's been accusing me of all
sorts of things.
She even called me a liar.
Dad, just let it go.
We both know that mom can be
a bit difficult sometimes.
Just talk it out with her.
What do you want me to do?
Dad, please.
Okay fine.
I'll talk to her
when I get home.
Thanks, Dad. I love you.
I love you, Dear.
Bye, Dad.
Hey, did you talk to your dad?
Yes, he's just letting off
steam.
He'll be right back, Mom.
Where is he?
You talked to him,
and you didn't ask where he is?
How are we going to find out
where your dad is?
Yes!
We're having a baby!
Be quiet! It's embarrassing!
This is the right time
to get married.
Playing hide and
seek in the moonlight!
When I count to ten...
- you'd better be hiding!
- Aren't you supposed to count?
- Okay!
- Go on, no cheating.
- You better be hiding!
- Go hide!
I miss you all so much.
Is Dad the reason,
we don't go to Luntian Park
anymore?
That place is
very special to us...
But when...
he cheated on me...
and abandoned us...
I can't bear to see
that place again.
You can do it, Felma.
You can go inside
that park once again.
I can do it.
I did it.
From now on, I won't let you
affect me again, Manuel.
Never again.
Love?
Felma, how are you?
Felma, wait, can we talk?
I don't want to talk to you!
We have nothing left to talk
about!
Yes, we do, we have plenty of
things to talk about.
I have a lot to tell you.
Whatever it is...
I don't want to hear it!
Can I see the kids, please?
I want to see them, Felma.
Please.
I don't want you to see my kids.
Their life is peaceful now.
Felma, I know that you hate me.
But you can't decide for
the kids.
I'm their father! I have the
right to see them!
What did you say?
You abandoned them for almost
eighteen years.
And now you want to see them?
Because you're their father?
He lied to us!
Mom, is it true?
- Of what?
- Dad has a new baby?
He has a new family?
It's true, your dad has
a new family now.
What? My daughter is not
a cheater.
I wasn't able to study for the
exam, Mom.
Because I was taking care of
Coleen.
Why didn't you tell me?
How are you going
to take care of her,
when you're always tired and
drunk?
So you're the mother of this
thief!
My son is not a thief!
He stole my wallet!
I did it so you can pay
the car owner for the damage.
I don't want you to go to jail!
I don't want that to happen!
You have no idea what
my children went through...
when you abandoned us.
What rights are you
talking about?
Tracking app, right?
Our phone has a tracking app.
What?
Don't tell me you're going
to track him?
Mom, you can only use that
when it's emergency.
Oh, well.
This is an emergency.
Now, show me how to use that
tracking app or else!
You'll get in big trouble
with me.
Felma, I'm sorry about
what I said.
I didn't mean to say it
in a bad way.
I just want to see our children.
I really miss them.
Don't worry about them.
They're doing well.
Because I raised them well.
I know, Felma.
I know.
You took good care of them.
I want to see all of you.
The four of you.
I want to personally
ask all of you for forgiveness.
For everything that I've done.
It's too late now.
Felma.
I know.
But this is the only chance
I will get to see them.
I might not have another chance.
We're going back
to Canada tonight.
Please, I'm begging you.
I just want to see Andrea,
Jeffrey, and Coleen.
Please, Felma.
I'm begging you.
This is Jeff, and Andrea.
They're Felma's kids.
- Abby.
- Hello.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Hello, Miss Abby.
- And the pictures?
- Oh, yes.
These are the photos
my mom picked.
You don't have any of
your father's pictures?
We threw away
the pictures of him.
It would have been nice
to show his picture,
even just once.
You really don't have any
of his pictures?
Sorry, he's no longer part of
our family.
- Miss Abby! Here!
- We're not going to include...
I have my dad's pictures
in there.
Oh, so you saved some of
his pictures.
Excuse me,
I'll just have these collated by
the producer for sequencing.
Oh, Miss Abby, can you...
can you not include
those pictures? Please.
I promise, we'll only use one.
Mark, you can set up now.
Errol, come with me.
Let me go!
You chose Hazel and
your daughter with her over us.
You can go to them!
Felma, I'm begging you!
I just want to see our children!
Go back to Canada!
You don't have
a family here anymore!
Felma, I'm not going back
to Canada...
without seeing them!
You won't let go of me?
I will scream!
I knew it!
You're both shameless!
You really went
to see your mistress, Manuel.
And you, Felma,
the nerve of you! You whore!
I'll get you for this!
You kept a picture of
your father?
I did, Jeff.
Why did you give it
to Miss Abby?
He's been a part of our lives
too, right?
Why are we going to skip on him?
What for?
To disrespect our mom?
Jeff.
Okay?
Did you talk to your mom?
She should be here by now.
I've been calling her,
but she's not
answering her phone.
I'll call her.
Uncle, she probably didn't see
your call.
Okay, do that.
Call her again.
- I'll try again.
- She's not picking up?
She's not answering her phone.
How dare you!
Especially you!
You have no shame, you mistress!
Here, she's the mistress!
What? Are you running
out of men?
Is that why you're trying
to take somebody else's husband?
- Hazel, stop!
- Stop it!
- What now?
- I'm not a mistress!
You're denying it?
You're a mistress! A mistress!
Look at her! She's a mistress!
Look at her!
She's a mistress!
- Here's the mistress!
- Hazel!
- What!
- Felma is not a mistress!
- You know that!
- What do you mean!
Here's my bastard husband!
Here!
- Look at him, Look at him!
- Hazel, knock it off!
You bastard!
Is this what you meant
when you told your daughter,
you were just letting off steam?
You're meeting with
your mistress!
She's not my mistress!
You know that!
What do you mean
she's not your mistress?
Who is she, then?
There is the mistress!
- Look! that's his mistress!
- Hazel, knock it off!
Why do you want me to stop?
You're trying to defend her?
Hey! Wait a minute!
Where are you going?
We're not done yet!
- We're not done yet!
- Hazel, stop!
- Why?
- Knock it off, Hazel!
You're defending her?
- You're defending you mistress!
- Stop!
- What!
- I said, stop!
- There's Auntie.
- There she is!
- Auntie.
- Where's Mom?
She went to the salon.
Isn't she here yet?
- She went to Rovil?
- Yes.
Yes, I have his number.
Wait, I'll call him.
Put it on speaker.
Okay.
Good afternoon!
Thank you for calling Rovil's
Haven of Beauty and...
Rovil, this is Andrea.
Andrea Cruz.
Is my mom there?
Miss Andrea,
She left a while ago,
but I can still see
her car parked out there.
She hasn't left yet.
Can you check her car?
- Sure, I'll be right back.
- Thank you.
I wonder if she had car trouble.
Or did she stop somewhere?
No, I'll go get her.
I'll go to the salon.
It's not far from here.
Jeff, I'll go with you.
- Let's go.
- Call me.
- Jeff, Call me.
- Okay, I will.
- Hazel! Stop!
- No! Wait!
- Hazel, can you stop!
- Wait!
- Let go of me!
- We're not doing...
- anything wrong!
- Not doing anything?
You're defending your mistress!
Hazel...
Shameless!
I've been holding back for
a long time now!
I'm pregnant!
He got me pregnant!
Maybe now you'll
stop calling my husband!
Leave Manuel alone!
Don't call him anymore!
You understand?
Manuel?
- You monster!
- I'm not a mistress!
I was never a mistress,
and I will never be one!
- You monster!
- You bastard!
I have no intention of
taking him from you!
You can have him!
You bastard!
- You bastard!
It's locked.
No one is in the car.
Where can she be?
You can have him!
- Stop it!
- You monster!
That's enough!
Hazel!
Stop it!
I said, stop it!
Uncle.
- You thought...
- I will fight you!
- You're just a mistress!
- Stop it!
- As if!
- If you guys have a problem,
settle it at the Barangay
office.
No! Get those two away from me!
I have no time for a husband
that is a liar and a cheater!
And a desperate woman who thinks
she's gonna run out of men!
- What did you say?
- What?
- Stop it!
- No!
Knock it off!
- Stop it!
- No!
- Mom! Mom!
- Felma, that's enough!
Who are you?
Why are you hurting my mom?
Jeff.
Son.
I got this.
I'm sorry, Sir.
Sorry.
It's nothing.
- Manuel, let's go.
- Why are you here?
Why is that woman
hurting my mom?
Manuel, come on.
They want us to leave.
Come on!
Can you stop already?
- Jeff.
- Don't touch me!
Don't you ever come near my mom!
And that woman of yours!
Hey!
I'm not just his woman!
I'm his wife!
Talk to your mom!
She's having an affair with
a married man!
Hazel, stop it.
Uncle, let's bring my mom
to the hospital.
Come on.
Mom.
Her bag.
- Wait...
- I said, leave us alone!
- Hey! You're incredibly rude!
- Before I hurt you!
Manuel!
Hello, Jeffrey?
You found mom?
Andrea, please cancel
the interview.
What? Why?
We need to bring mom
to the hospital.
What happened to her?
She got some cuts and bruises.
I'll tell you about it at home.
Tell Miss Abby, we apologize
for the inconvenience.
Okay, I will, Jeff.
What are you looking at?
You're not gonna leave?
Get out of here!
Jeffrey will explain
everything later.
Wait here.
Miss Abby?
I'm sorry, but we had
an emergency.
We need to cancel
the interview.
I apologize.
We can reschedule.
Well, I hope Miss Felma is okay.
You can pack up now.
Yes, Ma'am.
I'm really sorry.
Let's go.
Take care of that,
and this too.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
Why did you have to meet with
that woman?
Look at what happened to me.
We didn't plan to meet up.
You didn't plan it?
You're a liar!
I was humiliated in front of
those people.
You humiliate yourself.
Weren't you the one
who charged at her?
And when she fought back,
you're telling me you got
humiliated?
Are you really siding with her?
You're defending that woman?
Hazel, can you please stop?
And if I don't?
You'll go back to
the hotel alone!
And you're going back
to Canada without me!
Wait!
I'm getting in!
You bastard!
- Mom!
- Felma! That's enough!
Who are you?
Why are you hurting my mom?
Why are you here?
Why is that woman
hurting my mom?
- Jeff.
- Don't touch me!
Don't you ever get near my mom!
And that woman of yours!
Get out of here!
- Hey!
- Before I hurt you!
You beast!
Why did you even show up!
- Jeff!
- Jeffrey, stop.
- Jeffrey!
- Jeff, son!
- Jeffrey, that's enough.
Uncle, I should have
punched him!
Just once! I should have
punched him one time!
Jeffrey...
it's a good thing
that you didn't do that.
You have proven to your father,
that you have grown up to be
a good person.
You're not a troublemaker.
He wouldn't think, that Felma
didn't raise you right.
Uncle, I don't care about
what he thinks,
I want to get back at him
for my mom.
Jeffrey!
Dad is a monster.
Up to this day,
he's still causing you pain.
And that devil woman!
His mistress!
Son.
Son, it's okay.
Auntie, please, ask Uncle Abel
where I can find my dad.
Coleen, I said stop!
I just want to see him!
And then what?
You're going to expect
to have communication with him?
You're gonna talk to him?
Your dad's wife
is the devil's sister!
There's no way your dream
will come true!
He told me that he was single
when he pursued me...
I fell madly in love with him.
Hazel, Jessica is missing!
- What?
- Jessica's missing.
She left her phone in her room.
I want to make it up
with you and Tetay.
How will you do that?
I will take you back from Lance.
I'm excited to see Tetay.
Have your man come out first!
- Let go of me!
- I'll kill her.
Tetay, dear!
Uncle! Uncle!