Manuel! Manuel!
Manong Bert's jeepney is here!
- Please move!
- Dear, will bring you
to the hospital, okay?
Please give way.
Dear! Dear!
Dear!
Manong Bert, let's go!
My child!
Andeng!
This doesn't seem
to work anymore.
Hang in there, we're almost
at the hospital.
Andeng!
Manong Bert,
please drive faster!
Andeng!
Manong Bert!
Love!
Andeng!
Dear!
Bert, why did we stop?
Can't you see that, Manuel?
There's a heavy traffic ahead.
What are you doing?
We can't just wait here!
Please help us!
Help!
Please help my daughter!
- Help!
- What happened to the kid?
My child has asthma
she can't breathe!
Let's go over here.
Dear...
Ma'am, Sir,
only one can stay here.
Only one companion
can stay here, Ma'am.
Love, I'll stay.
Update me.
Paging Dr. Mendoza
to neuro ward.
Dr. Mendoza to neuro ward.
Bro...
how's everything going?
How's our goddaughter doing?
Paging Dr. Fabian to ER.
Dr. Fabian to ER.
Oh, God.
Please help my daughter.
Please save her.
Is Jeffrey home already?
I asked Manang Sita
to look after him.
I also left Coleen with her.
Don't worry about them, Bro.
Thank you, Paz.
Dr. Gavino to Area 1.
Andrea's awake now.
Thank goodness.
I'm Dr. Gallardo, cardiologist.
So far, your daughter
is already doing okay.
We're still nebulizing her.
But for now,
her breathing has improved.
Thank you, Doc.
Oh. See?
I told you.
My goddaughter is strong.
It's nothing serious.
But the patient is not
completely out of danger,
Mr. and Mrs. Cruz.
Why?
The patient is showing
symptoms of a heart murmur.
Her heartbeat isn't normal.
Based on the ECG and x-ray,
our initial impression,
is that she has
a ventricular septal defect.
It means that the heart's
patient has a hole.
A hole in her heart?
How did that happen?
Does your child have
a regular check-up?
It's been quite a while
since the last one.
We are usually able
to manage her asthma attacks.
Her attack earlier was
just so severe.
She had difficulty breathing
and felt weak.
She ran around with
her playmates,
that's why we rushed her here.
That's one of
the symptoms of her illness.
Doc, what can we do?
To determine the size
of the hole,
in cases like this,
we need to perform
an operation.
So we can also close it.
If we can do it sooner,
it'll be better for her.
You need to be ready
because the operation
is going to be expensive.
Where would we get three hundred
thousand pesos, Manuel?
Just for Andrea's
medication alone,
our money is not even enough.
What about our daily expenses?
The house, food,
water, electricity,
our payment for the house,
and our baby's milk?
What about Jeffrey's school
supplies?
What if I work abroad?
Abel has been asking me
to go with him.
What?
Love, haven't we talked about
this already?
We'll stay together
no matter what happens.
But the situation
is different now.
Our daughter is sick.
Love, even if I worked overtime,
I couldn't earn that amount
of money.
You know the salary of a janitor
in our country.
Then...
I'll help you!
Aside from longganisa ,
I'll also make tocino and tapa .
And I'll ask Paz
to help me sell them.
I'll work part-time
so you don't have to go.
Love, I'm not
underestimating it, okay?
How much would you earn
from that?
It's still not enough
for Andrea's operation.
Paging Dr. Fabian to ER.
Dr. Fabian to ER.
Maybe these things
are happening...
because God is punishing us.
Because up until now,
our relationship
still isn't blessed.
Love...
are we really going
to talk about marriage now?
Let's do that later.
Let's focus on Andrea for now.
What if...
we get a loan?
From whom?
Where?
And how would we pay that?
We're already struggling
to make ends meet.
What will happen
if we get a loan?
Love...
I don't want us
to part ways either,
but...
for our daughter's sake,
I'm willing to make sacrifices.
I'm also willing
to make sacrifices.
You know that.
So, let me do it.
Abel is flying back
to Saudi soon.
Maybe I can go with him.
Love, he said...
I will earn triple my salary.
We'll save money faster
for our daughter.
You're leaving?
Dear...
I'm doing this for you.
So we can afford your operation.
But didn't the doctor say
if she avoids playing too much
and tiring herself?
It's okay not to proceed
with the operation?
He's right, Dad.
I promise,
I won't run anymore.
I'll try not to push myself
too hard anymore.
So I don't have to undergo
an operation.
So that you don't have to leave.
I won't ask for new shoes.
Let's just get this fixed.
Let's save the money for Andrea.
Dear...
my contract won't be too long.
Two years will pass by quickly.
I'll go home once
I have enough savings.
You heard what
your dad said, right?
Just think about
Andrea's operation.
You'll get better soon, Dear,
and you can play again.
When it happens...
your dad won't have
to leave again.
Yes, I'll stay here.
We'll stay together forever.
I promise.
Darling, call us right away
once the plane lands, okay?
So we'll know that
you're safe. Okay?
Of course. Take care
of yourselves, too, okay?
Be safe.
Your favorite.
Looks like it'll take some time
before I can cook for you again.
Come on.
I'm still here,
and you're already
making me miss you.
What if you miss us?
Miss me?
Sooner or later,
you're going to look
at other women.
What are you talking about?
You're beautiful.
Why would I need to look
at other women?
You're the only woman
in my life, Love.
You know that.
- Yes.
- Really? Promise?
Promise.
That's you, Dad.
This is me.
This is mom, holding Coleen.
And big brother Jeffrey.
Look at it whenever you miss us.
Thank you, Dear.
Be a good girl.
Always bring your inhaler.
Take a rest whenever
you're having an asthma attack.
To prevent your heart
from getting worst.
Have this, Dad.
Don't remove it, okay?
So you won't forget me.
Jeffrey, you'll be
the one holding
the family together for now.
You'll have to help your mom...
and your siblings.
Take good care of them,
do you understand?
Yes, Dad.
And don't give your mom
a problem.
Don't fight, okay?
Yes, Dad.
Bro, we need to go.
Okay, let's go.
Kiss now.
Friend, come on.
Hey, Sister. What is that?
They might miss their flight.
Dad.
Dad!
Come on. Don't cry.
That's not good for you.
That's enough. Stop.
Stop.
I promise, I'll go home soon.
Dear, that's enough.
Your dad will be late.
Take care always.
Love! Be safe.
Hello.
Hey. Hi.
Hazel, here's what
you asked me to get for you.
Thank you.
I can't go down
to the cafeteria.
I'm sorry for the bother.
It's okay.
Manuel is hardworking.
- Who?
- Manuel.
Hardworking.
Alright then, I'll return
to the ER now.
Okay, then.
Could you bring this
to the nurse station?
- Sure.
- I'll go down there.
- It's okay.
- Okay. Thank you.
Sir?
Are you okay?
Sir? Are you...
Sir! Oh, no!
Sir.
Please, please.
Okay. Please relax.
Are you okay?
- Yes?
- Peace be with you.
Ma'am, looks like he threw up.
- I'll have it cleaned
- Yes.
Okay, Thank you.
Okay, take it easy.
Just relax.
Where's Baby Coleen?
I left her in Paz's care.
She fell asleep.
How are you doing, Love?
We're doing okay.
I received the money you
sent us.
I bought Andrea's medicine
And I saved some of
the money for her operation.
I'm glad to hear that.
How are you, Andeng?
I'm a good girl.
Mayette and I don't run.
Really?
Dad, she had difficulty
breathing the other day
Jeffrey...
I told you that...
I went up...
to the library because
I'm going to get a book.
Why did you have to go upstairs?
I told you I'd get
the book for you.
I can't hear it anymore.
Love, how are you
doing there?
I'm still getting used to it.
I've only been here for weeks.
But I want to go home already.
I just think that
I'm doing this for you.
Especially for you, Andeng.
I want you to get better soon.
So that you can live much,
much longer.
Just now, I'm feeling
motivated again.
I miss you, Dad.
I miss you, too, Dad.
I miss you so much, too,
my children.
How are you doing?
Yes, just be patient.
Peace be with you.
Put it a little lower.
You know it's not that easy.
Go, a little lower.
I hope you do something for now.
Hazel!
You know that we don't have...
Manuel!
You're hurt.
Wait.
Please bring patient Quarashi
to the x-ray room first,
before you endorse him
to the ward.
Where's the request for x-ray?
Here.
Hey.
Why do you look at Manuel
like that?
Why did he save me?
We're not that close.
My exes wouldn't even do that.
So, the damsel in distress
has finally met
her prince charming?
What are you talking about?
No offense,
but come on, Alice.
I'm a nurse.
Manuel is...
a janitor.
So?
Manuel is a good person.
Hardworking, courageous,
he even saved you.
What else could you ask for?
I already have a boyfriend.
But still.
Even I did,
if I'm not married,
he has a chance with me.
Come on.
He's married.
That's what Abel said.
But I heard that he's only
living with that woman.
So, they're not married.
They're not a married couple
Love, thank you.
Okay, Love. I love you, too.
Cool! Dad remembered!
Yes! I have
coloring materials now!
Look. Yes, he sent a lot.
There's chocolate!
This is a lot!
- Mom.
- Oh?
Dad's letter.
Let me see. Give me what's mine.
Maybe I have one.
Where's mine?
Here's yours.
Jeffrey, look.
Dad wrote me a letter.
Andeng?
- I'm okay.
- Dear.
Dear.
Always jumping around.
You know you're ill.
- How would I know?
- Jeffrey,
stop lecturing your sister.
Give her some water. Come on.
Jeffrey.
Thank you.
I got excited when I saw
the package dad sent us.
I wish dad were here.
So we'd be happier.
Yes, I talked to him.
He sent this to us,
so we don't need to borrow
your Aunt Paz's phone.
My dear children,
your dad had an accident.
- Oh, no.
- What happened?
He got hurt
while helping a nurse.
He's doing okay now.
So you don't have to worry.
Why did he help the nurse?
Who is she?
Her name's Hazel.
His friend.
Mom is jealous.
Of course not.
- No.
- Mom, it's too obvious...
No, I trust your father.
It's not easy.
He's so far away.
He's with others instead of me.
Even though, your face
says it all, Mom.
You're jealous.
You really are jealous.
- Jealous!
- You'll wake Coleen up.
Stop.
Sorry. Sorry.
You're pregnant?
What did Jojo say?
Nothing.
That jerk is not answering
my calls anymore.
My god, friend!
That's a problem!
You know it's a crime here
to get pregnant out of wedlock.
What if you go back
to the Philippines for now?
Stay there until you give birth
What about my family?
How can I support them?
What happens if your baby bump
starts to show?
Who will you present
as the father?
- Please come!
- There they are!
- Oh!
- Honey!
- Hi!
- I fetched your guests.
- Hi, Charles!
- What are you?
- Happy birthday!
- Yes, come in!
Thank you.
You shouldn't have brought
something.
Please put it here.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, guys.
Thank you!
Sit down for now.
Okay, guys.
Make yourself at home.
As long as you're in our house,
you can do as you please.
Got it?
What do you think of these,
Honey?
Thank you so much, Honey.
You made me so happy.
I love it.
Okay, I'm going to take
- a quick shower.
- Okay.
Okay, guys. Make yourself
at home, okay?
Hey.
- Yes?
- You.
You're so lucky to have Charles.
He seems to be
so in love with you.
Don't worry.
You'll find someone
like him, too.
I think I found him.
Or more on...
like someone who can help me
with my baby.
Manuel, please answer my call.
Manuel, answer the call.
What happened?
You were so drunk last night.
You insisted on kissing me.
I didn't want it but...
but there's nothing I could do.
Your wife's been calling you.
Paz is even nagging me!
You can't be reached!
What happened?
Why did Felma call?
It's because of Andrea!
Where's Manuel?
He left his phone.
He was here earlier.
He's soliciting money
for your daughter.
Ouch!
Let go of me!
- What the...
- Don't ever talk
to my wife again!
Do you understand?
Are you scared
that she'll find out
what happened between us?
It only happened once.
It will never happen again!
On the day of your departure,
you'll get your passport.
Thank you, Ma'am.
I can finally go home.
You're going home?
Why all of a sudden?
Don't you want me to go home?
Of course, I do.
I couldn't wait
to see you and the kids.
Me, too, my Love.