Dad, we have a visitor.
Dad?
Coleen?
Dad!
I've done you so much wrong.
My dear, I hope
you can forgive me.
I'm glad to have met you
in person.
Me, too, Coleen.
And Coleen, Mom...
I'm sure she's hiding some crime
she doesn't want us to discover.
- Andrea.
- The person she wants to see
is here in the Philippines.
Where else would she go?
Jessica!
You're trying to run away
from me?
Come here!
Hazel!
- Jessica!
- Hazel!
- They escaped from me.
- Is it my fault
that you're dumb?
I know they're with Felma.
So you better give me
Felma's address.
What do you think I am? Crazy?
Please help me get them
through the back.
Hurry up!
Your brother's here.
So that's why you wouldn't
tell us where we were going.
This is where you were planning
to take us all along.
Is Coleen home already?
Coleen's here!
- Where did you go?
- Where else? To her father!
Yes.
I went to see dad.
We've already discussed this,
haven't we?
We agreed you wouldn't call
your father anymore!
Because you knew
this would happen!
Trouble!
Just meeting with me
already causes a big issue.
What more if they find out
we're here?
We need to get out of here
right away.
Dad, please don't leave.
I still want to spend time
with you and Jessica.
I agree with dad.
We don't want to risk your
relationship with your family.
All right.
I'll let you go.
But can we all eat
together first?
After mom leaves.
Please, Dad?
Didang.
- Didang?
- Ma'am.
Yes?
Can you check on Coleen?
Sure, Ma'am.
Let me cook this first, okay?
Wait.
You're going to cook?
There's still a lot of food.
Look.
Ma'am, this is Coleen's request.
Why is it too much?
Oh, well...
she said she didn't eat
anything last night.
And I'm planning to eat
the leftovers for lunch.
Didang?
Ma'am?
Why do you look so tense?
Me? Tense? No way.
Well, last night I clearly
heard you and Coleen arguing
in the room.
I'm glad that she got
to see her father.
But I have to protect my family.
I don't want our family
to fall apart.
Manuel and Coleen shouldn't
see each other anymore.
This woman is crazy!
125 messages, 80 missed calls.
Hazel's driving me nuts!
She behaves like a troll.
Call Manuel, will you?
I already gave you the address,
didn't I?
They're not there.
Call him and ask where he is.
No. I don't want to.
And why not?
I said I don't want to!
Oh, is that so?
Hey!
You can't call him.
You don't know my password.
It's my birthday, you idiot!
You're so obsessed with me!
Uncle Abel's calling, Dad.
- Hello, Bro.
- Hello, Manuel!
Where are you?
Oh, yeah? Can't even
answer now, huh?
Impressive!
Can you please stop
bothering my friend?
Just go back to Canada,
to your burden of a wife!
Got it?
Paz, wait, hold on.
Let me explain.
Don't tell me to hold on,
Manuel!
You're unbelievable!
Two decades.
For two decades, you've been
making life miserable
for your family.
Okay?
For heaven's sake!
Just stop causing trouble.
Just leave already.
Stop!
That's enough, Paz!
No, I'm not stopping!
I want to teach your so-called
BFF a lesson first, okay?
No guts, and no heart!
For heaven's sake.
This bastard, this liar,
is coming back into the lives
of Felma and her children again.
Enough already!
What's the deal?
Felma isn't even being bothered!
What do you mean he's
not bothering Felma?
Do you know what
that jerk is doing?
He's using his kid with Hazel
to beg for favors from Felma!
Isn't that manipulation?
Do you understand me?
You've got no shame left!
That face of yours,
I'm going to slap it right off!
What an ugly face you've got.
Stop it already!
You!
You're not a man.
You've got no balls!
That's enough!
No!
I want coffee.
I'm thirsty.
Stop it!
Dad, please don't mind
what Auntie Paz said.
What she said is true.
That's why we really
need to leave.
There's mom!
She hasn't left yet!
Ma'am, let me do the cooking.
I got this.
I know what my youngest likes.
She wants it toasted,
and she likes it when the
inside's nice and crispy.
Even I like how you cook it,
Ma'am.
I'll be right back, Ma'am.
Here's your favorite.
That's why I love you so much.
Of course, I love you, too.
Dad. Coleen.
Be quiet.
What's happening?
Dad...
what's with the smile?
I saw Felma smiling again.
The Felma I used to know.
Not the cold Felma we met with.
Mom met with you?
Yes, Coleen.
We haven't told you yet,
have we?
Actually, I asked for some help.
And she was willing.
That means, mom still
can't neglect you.
Wait, that means...
Coleen, let's not get
ahead of ourselves.
There's still Jeffrey
and Andrea.
That's another fight.
Dear, your sister is right.
We still need to leave.
Where would you go?
We saw an apartment for rent
on a FriendsBook page.
It's a bit pricey,
but dad and I are still thinking
about it.
Let me in
- because I need to talk...
- Ma'am,
you're causing trouble again!
Causing trouble?
They're not here.
I don't believe you.
- Give me the owner's number.
- Ma'am.
I'll call myself
because you're useless!
What now?
- I said give it to me, or else.
- Ma'am, I can't do that.
No!
Get out of my way!
- I need to see...
- Ma'am, that's not allowed!
What do you mean not allowed?
What do you mean I can't?
Don't you understand?
- This is important...
- Excuse me, excuse me.
Rudy,
is this the woman who caused
a scene here last night?
Yes, Ma'am.
And who are you?
I'm the unit owner.
So, can you not act like
you own the whole building?
My child was kidnapped.
By Manuel.
She's a minor. Am I not
supposed to lose my mind?
You mean that kind,
paralyzed guy?
Doesn't really seem like
a kidnapper to me.
As far as I know,
he's Jessica's father.
And he's my husband.
You want a proof?
Here.
Our family photo.
What now? Want more evidence?
So I can shove it
right in your face?
What?
Lost your attitude now?
You know what?
You could be charged as an
accessory to my husband's crime.
Maybe you're even involved.
What if you're an accomplice
in the kidnapping of my child?
What?
Yes.
So if you don't do what I say,
I'll make sure
to implicate you in the case.
Especially you.
Miss Hazel?
I'm sorry for...
scaring you...
just to get in here.
The truth is...
I'm desperate.
I'm broken.
I was just pretending
to be strong earlier.
Please, don't get me wrong.
I'm not a bad person.
I love my husband.
But he wants to leave me...
for another woman.
And what hurts even more...
he brainwashed our child,
and took her with him.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I know I made mistakes, too.
But maybe...
I deserve a second chance.
I need my family's forgiveness.
I want my family back.
Please, please, help me.
Please.
How?
Let me stay here.
If you'll allow me,
let me wait for them.
Okay.
- Really?
- Yes.
But what if...
they call you?
The guard might kick me out.
I'll help you. I'll explain
the situation to them. Okay?
Really?
Thank you so much.
That was easy.
People are so easy
to manipulate.
Coleen, stay there for now.
Your mom's still here.
- Didang.
- Ma'am?
Can you put this on a plate?
I'll bring this
to Coleen's room.
Oh, no need, Ma'am.
You already cooked.
It's okay, I'll take care of it.
I'll be the one to bring it.
Yeah.
I'll just put it here.
Didang, I've been
noticing something...
You've been tense
for a while now.
You're hiding something,
aren't you?
Ma'am, please, I'm not.
Tell me the truth.
There's nothing.
Didang...
Coleen, why'd you come
from the back?
Weren't you feeling unwell?
I'm feeling better now, Mom.
I just checked something
in the laundry.
My ID was in my uniform.
Oh, I saw that.
I took it and put it
on your table upstairs.
- Okay.
- I already placed it there.
Oh, I'll just eat here.
Okay, sure.
Okay.
I'll join you.
Let's talk.
And I'll be the one to take you
to school.
No, Mom, it's fine.
You go ahead.
No.
I'll take you to school.
All right, I'll wait
for you at the table.
Please come in.
Please close the door.
Sorry.
I had to grab some rice
so I could bring you this food.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, Didang.
It's nothing, really.
Too bad Coleen isn't here.
I was really looking forward
to eat breakfast with her.
She's feeling down too.
But of course,
she can't really show it.
Ma'am Felma might
notice something's up.
All right then.
Go ahead and eat.
You know, Didang...
only Felma can cook
longganisa this good.
I really miss it.
Ma'am Felma?
You miss her?
No, the longganisa.
It would've been nicer
if we were with...
Ma'am Felma?
There, did I guess it right?
It's Coleen!
What are you talking about,
Didang?
You're such a gossipmonger!
Come on, Sir Manuel.
I was just teasing you.
Oh, wait, I forgot your drinks!
I'll be right back, okay?
Thank you!
Okay, thank you.
When they get here,
I'll drag them to the airport
if I have to.
Friend, congratulations
on tricking the unit owner
into letting you stay.
But what now?
Are you just going to sit there
and wait?
I don't think Manuel and Jessica
are coming back.
They left everything behind,
documents, passports, even cash.
That's why I'm sure
they'll come back.
But if you're right that
Felma helped them escape,
she can cover everything.
She's got money.
So you need a Plan B.
Oh, yeah.
You're right.
All right, I'll call you later,
okay?
Oh, I know!
Buy some palabok
- for the meeting.
- Palabok.
Palabok. Because it's Jeff
and Andeng's favorite, okay?
- All right, go ahead and order.
- Okay, I'm ordering now.
All right.
Good morning.
Oh no, no one's
at the reception.
Hello!
Juicy morning, FMP buddy!
Felma's Meat Products, hello?
May I speak to the owner?
Miss Felma Ruiz?
Hazel, you troublemaker!
I recognize your voice.
Why are you calling here?
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
Who's Hazel?
This is Stephanie Lim
from Value More.
Value More, you say?
Sorry, Ma'am.
I thought you were...
Never mind.
At your service, yes?
Yes, Ma'am. I'm the PR head.
We would like to send
a VIP invite to Miss Felma Ruiz
for our upcoming event.
May I ask for her home address?
Please just send it
to the office.
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
We really wanted to deliver it
to her house
to make sure she gets it.
Because it includes 10,000 worth
of gift certificates
from Value More.
And also, we have a VIP invite
and card for Miss Paz Antonio.
That's me, that's me!
Did you say there's
a gift certificate?
Do I get one too?
Yes, of course.
10,000 worth of gift
certificates from Value More.
Get your pen and paper.
I'll dictate our addresses
to you, okay?
Thank you very much, Didang.
Oh, you're always welcome.
You know, Jessica,
that hand-me-down clothes
from Coleen really suit you.
It's actually pretty cute.
By the way, where's Coleen?
They are about to leave.
We couldn't even say goodbye.
Coleen wanted to come here, too,
but Ma'am Felma
wouldn't leave her side.
Looks like you really
liked Ma'am Felma...
I mean the longganisa, Sir.
You're so silly, Didang.
I'll be back for snacks later.
Why are you bringing that?
Shouldn't it be Didang?
- It's okay, Mom.
- Come on.
Didang is busy.
Oh, Didang.
Felma!
Felma, you're such a flirt.
Bring out Manuel and Jessica!
How did you even get in here?
That's good.
Andrea, how's it going?
Yes.
The attendees are on their way.
They'll be here in a bit.
But Felma's not here yet.
Maybe she's stuck in traffic.
She messaged me earlier. She
said she's dropping off Coleen.
But she knows there's a meeting
today, right?
Well, honestly, Auntie,
Coleen's upset.
So mom's trying to coax her.
It's because we all scolded her.
What?
Why? What happened?
Coleen went to see her dad.
So, mom scolded her...
all of us did.
You're all fighting again
because of Manuel.
That man really won't leave
you alone.
I'll just call your mom, okay?
I don't believe it. Manuel!
Hazel!
- Hazel!
- Jessica!
What's wrong with you?
They're not even here!
Manuel, Jessica!
How many times do I have to say
that they're not here?
- Just stop it already!
- Get out of here!
You have no right
to get inside my house!
- Oh, is that so?
- Coleen! Coleen!
- Call the guard house!
- Okay.
I know they're here!
They really aren't here,
so just stop it!
Thank you so much
for everything, Didang.
Please take care of Coleen.
Don't worry about that.
I'll be the one to see you out.
I'll just make sure Ma'am Felma
has already left.
I've also prepared
a quick exit route for you.
- Let's go.
- Thank you.
Okay! I'm going to sue you
for trespassing!
- I'll sue you for kidnapping.
- What's that?
Do you hear that?
You'll only feel ashamed
because they're not here!
Dad!
Your wife is outside!
- What?
- My mom?
Yes.
How did she know we're here?
I don't think she knows.
Sounds like she's just bluffing.
You need to hide.
No, I'm going to face Hazel.
Felma needs help.
Mom can't see you, Dad.
I'll take care of her.
I'm the one who'll help her.
Didang, I'll leave them to you.
- Okay.
- Also call the guardhouse.
All right, I'll do that.
Okay, I'll go back to mom now.
Follow me, okay?
Let's go through
the dirty kitchen.
Come on.
Slowly, okay?
Let's go.
She's not answering.
I'll just text her.
Andrea, call Didang.
I'll call Coleen.
Okay.
- Manuel!
- You're shameless!
- Jessica!
- You have no right
to enter my home!
What are you doing?
Go ahead,
I'll sue you for trespassing!
And I'll sue you for kidnapping!
- No!
- Manuel!
They're not here!
You'll embarrass yourself!
- You can even bring your...
- Manuel!
What are you going to do to me?
Throw me in the pool?
- Wow, that's so original.
- No!
I won't let my pool get dirty
because of you!
This! This!
This one's for you!
Take that!
That's for you!
Didang's not answering.
Coleen, too.
Listen.
When our meeting
attendees arrive,
we'll proceed with the meeting.
And when Felma arrives,
she can just catch up.
We have a lot to discuss.
All right.
What now?
That's it!
That suits you perfectly!
Mom!
Shameless witch!
- Mom!
- Shameless witch!
- Mom, stop it, please!
- Hazel, you witch!
- Don't stoop to her level.
- Coleen.
- Mom, please! That's enough.
- No, Coleen.
Not my daughter!
Darn you!
Let go of Ma'am Felma!
Won't you really stop?
Manuel, get out of there!
- They're not here!
- Jessica!
Get out of here!
Didang!
- What are you going to do?
- Leave her to me!
What will you do?
You're way out of line!
I've been trying to stop you!
You don't want to be stopped!
Dear, you're hurt.
Dear.
Get lost!
- Leave!
- Stop it!
Leave!
Darn you.
I'll come after you!
Until I get my family back!
- Get lost!
- Jessica! Manuel!
- Leave!
- Get out!
Leave!
Dear, are you okay?
Are you okay, Mom?
I'm okay.
Didang.
Didang, come here.
Coleen.
Let's bring her to the hospital.
Coleen!
So, that's how much you are.
You're so cheap!
You little devil, Hazel!
Just wait and see!
Why are you talking
to Manuel's wife?
Let's just forget
about the problems for now.
Hey, what do you have in mind?
I'm sneaking in tonight
so we can sleep next
to each other.
I'd love that!
Let's get down to business.
Your timing is perfect,
classmate.
I want you to find them.
Find these two.
- Didang.
- They all left.
Have you already booked a ride?
Yes, it's already
waiting outside.
Okay. Go. Be safe, okay?
Jessica?
Jessica!
Why do you have so much food?
I'm planning to eat
in the laundry area.
I'd like to eat
while doing the laundry.
Didang.
Was that Jessica I saw earlier?