I'm not a mistress.
Because first of all, I was his
wife before her.
I'm content with my
children, my grandchild,
and my fiancé, Noah Salvador,
whom I will marry soon.
The official diagnosis
matched what I told you.
What if we get a
second opinion?
It's a waste of time.
Is God punishing me?
Is this my karma?
Don't be too
hard on yourself.
I wish I had died.
- Dad, don't say that.
- I wish I had died!
Dad!
Miss Felma, I have
sad and bad news.
Dad is already paralyzed
from the waist down.
Mom!
- Felma! Felma!
- Mom!
I'm sorry for reading
the messages.
That's the reason why
you lost consciousness earlier.
Miss Felma
cares about you.
Would you like us
to call Miss Felma?
We can call her.
I won't call them again.
And I also won't receive
any calls from them.
It won't stop.
It's either you accept the call
or reject the call.
I wonder why she's
not answering.
I wonder what happened.
No, I won't answer it.
Okay.
I know you want
to answer it.
Answer it.
No.
No, I said I won't answer.
I promised you.
- Answer it.
- They'll eventually get tired.
They'll stop.
Answer it.
No.
Hello?
This is Noah Salvador.
Felma's fiancé.
Jessica, is your
father beside you?
Can he hear me?
Noah, please
give it to me.
Please give it to me.
Manuel, do you hear me?
Do you remember me?
We met here in
the Philippines.
- Mom!
- Felma! Stop!
I won't fight you
or disrespect you.
In fact, I'm going
to ask you a favor.
Please leave Felma
and me alone.
We'll be getting
married soon.
Let's have a
man-to-man talk.
What you and Felma had
is a thing of the past.
You can never
bring that back.
You're already married
and have another family.
Whatever happened
to you, I'm sorry.
And I hope you recover.
But stop involving Felma,
both of us,
and even the kids,
with what happened to you.
Felma deserves
to be happy.
And I intend to
make her happy.
So, please.
Leave us alone.
This is the right time
for us to get married.
We'll be a family.
We're still a family even
if we don't get married.
I know.
But I want to marry you.
That's what I
dream for you.
To marry you in a church.
It's just a
waste of money.
It doesn't have
to be grand.
We can have
something simple.
What matters is
that we get married.
Love, listen to me.
I'm good.
Now that we're having
a baby, my dream of us
becoming a family is
finally happening.
That's enough for me.
That already
makes me happy.
Maybe we're going through this
because God is punishing us.
Because up until now, our
relationship still doesn't have
a blessing.
Come on, love.
Are we going to talk
about marriage right now?
I'm sorry, Dad.
I did not expect someone
else would take the call
for Miss Felma.
Sorry.
You don't have to
say sorry, dear.
It actually seems like it
turned out better to hear
what Noah said.
How could you do that?
You didn't want
to answer it.
So I did.
And as your fiancé,
I think I have the right
to put a stop
to whatever Manuel's doing.
But he didn't do
anything wrong.
Oh, really?
So what do you call what's
happening between us?
Isn't it hurting
our relationship?
Because we argue
because of him?
Unless this relationship
really doesn't matter to you.
Because you care more
about how he feels
than how I feel.
Why?
What do you
expect from me?
What am I expected feel?
I waited for years for you
to get ready
to enter a relationship with me.
I respected your phase.
I didn't rush you.
Unless you were just
forced to accept my feelings.
But still, you committed to me.
We are engaged.
We should be taking
care of our future.
But your past keeps
insisting on being part
of your present and future.
Felma...
where do I fit in?
What should I do?
What am I
supposed to feel?
Maybe it was wrong for me
to answer Manuel's call.
But I'm getting
hurt, Felma.
I'm just fighting
for my love for you.
Why? Don't you want
to fight for me?
Hello? This is Noah Salvador,
Felma's fiancé.
Please leave Felma
and me alone.
We're getting
married soon.
The lunch is almost done.
Are you going to eat at
the dining,
or do you want it brought here?
You didn't eat
breakfast again?
Do you want to get sick?
What's your problem?
Don't you like my cooking?
Next time, tell me
if you don't want to eat.
So I won't get tired preparing
and cooking for you.
Don't you know that
my time is so limited?
I'm always rushing because
I don't want to be late.
But after everything,
you're not going to eat?
You've wasted
food and my time.
Aren't you going inside?
Maybe not.
Are we okay?
Noah?
I think we need to give
each other some space.
What do you mean?
Exactly that.
That space.
Are you breaking up with me?
Are you calling off the wedding?
How about you?
Is that what you want?
It's up to you.
Family.
Mom!
You're early.
Have you eaten?
- Let's eat, Mom.
- Good evening, everyone.
Hello, Pretty Mama.
This was unplanned, Mom.
This is the only time
Tetay and Daisy are available.
Didn't Uncle Noah
bring you here, Mom?
He did.
But I suddenly
have a headache.
I'm having a migraine.
So maybe I'll just
get some rest.
I just have to sleep.
I thought we could play later.
I'll make it up to
you next time, dear.
- Okay.
That's a promise.
Continue eating.
Pretty Mama, are you okay?
Yes.
Come on, Hazel.
Join me.
Go ahead. Finish your food.
I'll eat before I go.
I've already
cooked your dinner.
Tell Jessica to put it in
the microwave
when she comes home from school.
You should eat before
you go to work.
Come on.
I'll take care
of that later.
No need.
Just finish your food.
I'm almost done here.
- Come on. Join me.
- No!
Come on and eat.
- I said no. Wait.
- Come on.
What's wrong
with you, Manuel!
Look!
Instead of being done
with my chores already,
now I have to clean
that up, too.
Come on! I told you I can
handle.
You're so stubborn.
Gosh!
Instead of being able
to leave already,
it's taking even longer.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
I'm so late again.
I've already received
so many warnings
from the hospital.
Because of my tardiness.
But what else can I do?
There's still so much I
need to take care of here.
Manuel, come on.
Please cooperate, will you?
You're not helping,
and you're just making things
harder.
Come on! I'm already exhausted
from the hospital,
and when I get home,
I even get more exhausted.
I'm not a superwoman!
- Did you enjoy?
- I did.
Dad, thank you so much
for the lovely dinner
and quality time at your house.
But it would've been happier
if Pretty Mama had joined us.
She's having a headache.
Don't worry, dear.
There's still next time.
If only your mom would
agree to live with us,
then the three of us
could be together.
Dad, I'd love that!
Mom, please agree.
Sweetie, it's not that easy.
Because you and Dad haven't
gotten back together yet.
Dad, you should really
give it your all
in winning Mom back.
And Mom, please don't be
too hard to get, okay?
So you and Dad can
be together again.
And we can all live in
Pretty Mama's house
with Auntie Andrea and Auntie
Coleen.
And, of course,
with Didang.
You talk too much.
Let's go.
Okay.
But, Dad, start
courting Mom.
Yes, dear. I got that.
Tetay is right.
We should have a timeline.
This courtship should
already be counting, you know.
You'd better think
carefully about that timeline
you're talking about.
Let's go.
Tetay and I have to
go early tomorrow.
Perfect! Because after I drop
Tetay off,
I'll be taking you next. I'll
drop you off at your office.
What?
That's out of the way
to your office.
Well, if that's the only way
to your heart...
Okay?
You win.
Let's go.
Mom?
How are you?
Does your head still hurt?
Mom.
Go.
Vent it out.
I know there's a problem.
Your Uncle Noah.
What?
Are you having a fight?
I did something.
I wanted to explain
and say sorry,
but then he suddenly
told me that
we should give each other
some space.
Space?
As in a break-up
or just a cool off?
And how long, Mom?
Wait, what did
you do, Mom?
Mom, you know that it's normal
in a relationship
to have misunderstandings
and little arguments, right?
But I'm sure
that whatever happened,
you and Uncle Noah
will make up eventually.
He can't stay mad at you.
Andrea, sweetie...
I don't know if there's still
going to be a wedding.
Well, even if I were in
Uncle Noah's position,
I'd honestly feel hurt too, Mom.
Why do you even communicate
with that family?
With those people?
I called them because...
I wanted to fight with them.
I let out what I was feeling.
That's it. Move on.
I've moved on already.
I'm just checking in.
There's probably nothing wrong
with just asking
how your dad is doing.
Mom, I don't care.
And besides- let's say,
what happened to him
is really sad, okay?
But we don't have
to get involved anymore.
You used to tell us often
that he's no longer part
of our family.
And maybe...
that's just karma for what he
did when he abandoned us.
Andrea, don't think like that.
He's still your father.
Before.
But not anymore.
When he abandoned us,
he stopped being my father.
I've already forgotten
about him.
And my dad is now Uncle Noah.
He's the one who's been there
for us siblings all these years.
He's become our dad.
That's why, Mom...
we want you to get married.
So we can finally
be a happy family.
But what if the wedding
doesn't push through?
Mom, the question is...
Do you really want to marry
Uncle Noah?
Or would you just let the
two of you completely separate
because you can't let go
of your ex?
What's that?
It stinks!
Manuel!
What's wrong with you?
Why did you poop there?
I'm sorry.
I didn't make it
to the bathroom in time.
Why didn't you ask for help?
You would feel it.
You should've asked for help,
even if you had to shout.
Jessica!
She already went to school.
I don't want to bother you
because I know you're tired
and you got home late
from the hospital.
Oh, so now? What?
It's the same.
Isn't it?
I'm still the one cleaning up
your mess.
Look. Come on!
Look!
Mom?
Are you okay?
Are you not feeling well?
I had a snack earlier.
That's why...
That's why
I don't feel like eating.
Mom,
didn't Uncle Noah
bring you here?
Isn't Sinigang na Hipon
his favorite?
And Auntie Paz
was asking me earlier
why you and Uncle Noah
were ignoring each other.
- Is that true, Mom?
- You're having an LQ, Mom?
LQ at their age?
You're so mean.
Why?
- You're so bad.
- It's worse than LQ.
Why, Andrea?
Uncle Noah asked for some space.
Space?
Cool off?
That's for youngsters.
Isn't it a prank?
Who knows? Maybe it's a prank.
Stop it.
The food's right in front of us.
Mom...
just tell them the truth.
Tell them the real reason
why you and Uncle had a fight
that made him ask for space.
Andrea, what do you mean?
Mom, what is Andrea
talking about?
Mom?
What's going on?
Andrea, if Mom doesn't want to
talk, then you say it.
Because it's obvious
that you know.
Coleen and I
have the right to know.
And we've already talked
about this, right?
Dear...
don't.
Don't say it.
Let's not make this bigger.
Uncle Noah caught Mom...
checking on that guy
from Canada.
The worthless man, her ex,
who abandoned us.
I only did that because...
your father
is becoming paralyzed.
Are you really going to leave
Uncle Noah for Coleen's dad?
Our dad.
Coleen, you're the only one
who calls him dad.
Mom, I'm begging you. Please.
Make up with Uncle Noah.
Because, Mom,I can never accept
your ex-husband.
Mom, you got fired from work?
What bad luck, really.
It started when your dad's path
crossed with Felma.
Maybe that woman cursed us.
It's your dad's fault
that he met up with her.
Why are you still defending him,
Mom?
You're letting your relationship
with Uncle Noah fall apart
just because of your ex.
Mom, you've already found
an angel.
Are you in your right mind, Mom?
Don't talk to me like that!
I need to find a job right away.
But it'll be hard for me
as long as I'm tied down
taking care of your dad.
What do you mean?
I can no longer take care
of him.
I have to bring him
to a nursing home.
What?
No way! I'm not okay with that!
We have no choice.
And it's not up for your dad
to decide.
I'll accept whatever
your decision is, Hazel.
I have something to show you.
It's a surprise.
Hi, Dad!
Dad, how are you?