If Felma and Manuel get back
together with their kids,
you'll lose your place
in his life.
Only our marriage will be
annulled,
not my being your father.
I love you so much, Dad.
What are you doing to stop
your dad from filing the case?
There! Confess to them!
- Jessica!
- Let go of Jessica!
-Jessica, that's enough! Coleen!
-Coleen, come on!
She's talking to her mom again.
Dad, they're planning something.
You just love to assume
and accuse people of things!
- Jessica!
- Coleen, dear!
What is your sister Coleen
talking about?
When Mom found out about
the annulment,
She said if it pushes through,
I'm going to live with her.
Mom, did you know about Coleen's
father's annulment?
Yes, Son.
But I'm staying out of it.
Mom, if Dad's annulment
gets granted,
will you get back together?
I was about to invite
Mom for coffee,
but she's not in her room.
What about you?
Why are you still up?
Dad's not in our room either.
I was looking for him too.
I'm sorry, Felma.
Oh...
It's just hard to say
goodbye to you.
You know, if only we could...
If only we really could,
we wouldn't leave at all.
You have to, Manuel.
So people stop questioning
what's going on between us.
Fix what needs
to be fixed first.
Then you can come back.
Wait for me, Felma.
Please, wait for me.
Coleen?
What are you doing here?
Were you listening
to our conversation?
What?
Mom, Dad, stop!
My stomach hurts
from laughing so much!
What's going on here?
Oh, Jeffrey.
Oh, Isn't it obvious?
We're having a good laugh.
Having a good laugh
but why only you laughing?
No, Jeffrey.
I told them a joke,
but they didn't get it.
Maybe you will, Jeffrey.
Wanna hear it?
What are you doing here, Mom?
Why are you hanging out alone
with your ex?
Jeff, no! It's not like that.
I just asked them
for love advice.
There's this guy at school
who's courting me.
And I kinda like him too.
But there's a catch.
They say he's also courting
someone from another department.
And you went to them for advice?
He's courting someone else?
Coleen, come on,
It's obvious.
That's a huge
red flag right there.
He's already acting shady, and
you're not even together yet?
What more if you do
end up together,
get married, and start a family?
Wow, Jeff.
Jumping ahead a bit, aren't we?
Marriage and kids already?
I'm just saying,
I know guys like that.
Those types?
They're jerks.
Mark my words, give it time,
and he'll cheat,
get some girl pregnant,
then leave his own
family behind.
Look.
Oh, Dad, let's go?
Good night, Auntie Felma.
Good night, Jessica.
Coleen, stay here.
Let's talk about your problem.
This kid.
- I've been texting her nonstop,
- Hey, friend.
and still nothing.
You've been holding your phone
for a while now.
I know.
It's Jessica.
I'ven been messaging her,
but she hasn't reply once.
No calls, no texts,
nothing.
I have a bad feeling
about that girl.
Save it for later.
Someone might rat you out
for being on your phone
while on duty.
Come on,
this is a family emergency.
They'll understand.
Wait.
What is that?
Still not answering.
Should I just go check on her?
What? Do you want to get
suspended again?
You're leaving your post?
Do you want to lose
your job again?
I need to know what's happening
to my daughter.
I need her.
So what now?
You're going to tell her
to stop Manuel again?
Yes.
And on top of that...
I need to scare Jessica
into doing what I want.
I need her.
I need her to be on my side.
Who knows?
Manuel might use her against me.
What do you mean?
Atty. Salazar said,
that Jessica could testify
against me
to prove what Manuel
is claiming.
That I'm psychologically
incapacitated.
Oh my god.
If that's the case,
you really have to work
double time on Jessica.
Exactly.
But how can I do that
if I can't even contact her?
You're welcome.
Because if I hadn't seen
Jeffrey and Jessica then...
you would have been
caught by now.
What would they have caught?
There's nothing going on
between me and your dad, okay?
Stop reading too much into it.
Sorry.
Are you sure
there's nothing, Mom?
Yes, really.
I can look Jeffrey
and Jessica in the eye.
And even you...
and Andrea.
I can look anyone in the eye
because my conscience is clear.
I thought...
But honestly, Mom,
I'm still hoping that you
and Dad will get back together.
He's married to Hazel.
You really think...
I'd agree to be
your father's mistress?
I'm sorry, Mom.
I just wanted to ask something.
If his marriage gets annulled,
will you and Dad
get back together?
I'm not a child anymore to lie
or pretend I don't feel
anything.
But as long as he's married
to someone else,
we will never be back together.
Yes!
I hope their annulment gets
approved soon,
so we can finally
be a family again.
Maybe even this year!
Right, Mom?
That's enough.
Come here.
Dad, this place is beautiful.
Not too big.
but not too small either.
Dad, I think this is perfect.
Thank you, Uncle.
- You're welcome, my godchild.
- Thank you.
This is already semi-furnished.
It already has built-in cabinets
and a water heater.
We can even have a ramp
installed for Sir Manuel,
so he can move around easily,
It's very spacious anyway.
Thank you.
This is a prime location.
Near the hospital,
the police station
the church, and lots
of convenience stores nearby.
Very accessible.
Dad, this is way better
than the one I found.
I told you, bro,
you'd like this.
Well, if it's okay with you,
then it's okay with me too.
So, Ma'am? Shall we close
the deal?
All right. If it's okay
with you all,
let's go and close the contract.
All right, let's close the deal.
So...
is this our new home?
I like it.
It's nice. Cozy.
So, when do we move in?
Hazel, what are you doing here?
And how did you even find us?
I always find my ways, Manuel.
You'll help me,
or I'll tell your father
the truth that he raised a child
who isn't even his.
Oh, by the way, Ma'am.
I'm Mrs. Hazel Capistrano-Cruz.
I'm the wife.
- And...
- And the other woman...
is the mistress.
- Oh.
- I'm not a mistress.
Hazel, please not now!
- When?
- Tomorrow,
the day after tomorrow,
next week, next month!
But not now and not here, Hazel,
have some shame!
Why should I be ashamed?
I'm the wife.
And you, Manuel?
Who are you going to keep here?
Your mistress?
What, are you forcing me to file
a concubinage case against you?
Mom!
And you, Felma.
You really can't let go
of my husband, can you?
- Hazel!
- Mom, Mom, Mom!
- Mom? Mom Mom?
- Hazel, stop!
- Mom, Mom. Mom!
- I said stop, Hazel!
- hazel!
Manuel?
I'm so done with you!
Hazel, come here!
I'm sorry, Ma'am,
I'm really sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Are you embarrassed?
Aren't you a mistress?
You should be shameless!
- Hazel, stop!
- She deserve to be called out
in public, the homewreckers.
- Mom, enough!
- Hazel! Stop!
- Go home now!
- Why would I go home?
I should be the one living here!
- Go home!
- I'm the wife!
- Get out of here, Hazel!
- Go home!
- I said leave!
- Come on!
Jessica, stay here.
Go home!
I'm the wife!
Why should I go?
- You're making a scene here!
- Let go of my friend!
- Just go home!
- Let me go!
- You tolerate Manuel.
- Abel, let me go!
- Go home!
- Abel, what are you doing?
You're hurting me!
You have no respect
for women, Abel!
You have no respect for men
or for other women!
You're unbelievable!
Did you leave your shame
in Canada?
- What did you say?
- What? What?
That hurts!
There! You deserve it!
Serves you right!
Ouch!
You're really siding
with her over me?
I'm your mother.
You should be on my side!
Mom, when are you going to stop?
Never!
Not until I get you
and your father back!
So help me,
if you want me to stop.
No, Mom.
I will never help you.
Is that so?
Maybe it's time your father
knows the truth.
Mom, no, please.
What truth, Hazel?
Mom, no. No, no.
Mom, no, please!
- Mom!
- Abel! Abel!
What are you doing?
Move over.
Stay out of it!
You're just as indulgent
as Hazel!
You both have the same attitude!
I'm really sorry
for what happened.
I'm sorry, too, but...
I'm sorry.
I'm not renting my apartment
to you anymore.
Mom, please,
I'm begging you.
Please, Mom.
I also begged to you, Jessica.
You didn't listen to me.
If you don't want your father
to know the truth,
then you'll come with me,
so he'll follow us.
Mom, please.
Have mercy on me and Dad.
Please, Mom.
Did you ever have mercy on me?
No.
So if you won't help me
get your father back,
then I'll take you away
from him.
You're mine.
You're my daughter.
I want them...
to reject you.
I want you to feel what I felt
when my loved ones abandoned me.
Thank you so much,
and I'm sorry for all
the trouble we've caused.
What is it this time, Hazel?
Manuel...
there's something
you need to know,
Mom! No!
Mom, no. Please.
I want you to know
that Jessica...
No, please!
Let me tell him.
Please, Mom.
What is it that you're going
to tell me?
What is it, Jessica?
Dad, I've decided.
I'll stay with Mom for now.
Wait.
Dear, why is it so sudden?
What happened?
What did your mom tell you?
Did she threaten you?
Hey, I didn't do that.
Jessica, if you're being forced
or scared,
just tell your dad.
Stop! Stay out of this!
Stop!
Mom, please.
Mom, stop! Everybody stop!
I just want to spend time with
the both of you and Mommy, Dad.
I thought I would just split,
there would be days,
with Mommy and days with you,
Dad.
Dear.
I don't want more fights, Dad.
I don't want more pain po.
We're leaving now
Mom, let's go.
I don't understand, Felma.
I don't understand why Jessica
made such a decision.
Hazel did something.
I can feel it.
She did something to Jessica.
I need to go to sleep now.
I still have work later.
Come here,
sleep beside me.
You were seriously
going to tell Dad?
Yes.
Dead serious.
Because of you.
You forced me to do that.
What now, Mom?
What do you want?
I still want the same, dear.
I want you to do everything.
Everything you can
to stop the annulment.
I want to make it up
to your dad.
For all the times...
I failed to show the love...
he deserved from me.
He tried to love you, Mom.
But you didn't help him.
Instead of making him fall
for you, you pushed him away.
I know.
I know I failed.
But can you blame me
for realizing just now...
that I love your father?
We're the same.
We both didn't love
each other before.
Because back then, the one
I loved was your real father.
But...
look at me.
I love your dad so much now.
So, Jessica, please.
Dear, help me.
You will help me,
whether you like it or not.
Because if you don't,
I will proceed with the case
against your father.
If I have to fabricate
evidence, I'll do it.
And you will testify
in my favor.
I'd rather see
your father in prison.
Because neither Felma...
nor I...
and certainly not you...
deserve anything from him.
Hi, Sonny!
I know.
Oh, same here.
I haven't been able to reach
Elvie either.
Actually, it's been
a few days now.
She's probably vacationing
in some other country again.
I'll update you tomorrow, okay?
All right, bye.
Who's Sonny?
A college classmate.
One of the people
I recruited to invest
in Elvie's lending company.
Pick up the call
of your sibling.
It might be an emergency.
I don't care.
I'm standing by what I said
to her.
Oh, right?
So now she's with her dad.
Now, she doesn't have
a sister anymore.
Wow, you're really taking
things that far?
Cutting off?
Yes.
Even if you're my best friend,
if you're gonna fight with me,
then that's it, cut off.
Andrea, please answer.
Jeff's back.
Daisy left him.
She took Tetay with her.
Jeff said he's okay,
but he's not.
He's getting drunk every night.
I'm worried.
Read the text message.
Just the text message.
Then read it!
Andrea, please answer.
Jeff's back.
Daisy left him.
She took Tetay with her.
Jeff said he's okay
but he's not.
He's getting drunk every night.
I'm worried...
Jeff went back home?
Our agreement was that
no one goes home
until Mom's ex is gone!
Come on, come with me.
Where to?
To Jeff's.
You can't ignore them, right?
Let's go.
He's at our house.
I don't want to see
those people there.
Hello?
Darn you, Daisy.
Why aren't you answering?
I can't even reach my daughter.
You're blocking my call?
Son...
come on, let's have a drink.
Have a drink?
Us?
Are we going to pretend
we're okay?
- Oh...
- Like we're just buddies?
Like a normal father and son?
Okay.
If that's what you want,
then let's pretend.
So even for one night,
you won't fight with me,
and you won't avoid me.
Do you need someone to talk to?
I'm here.
I understand
what you're going through.
I know how it feels
to lose a family.
You're joking, aren't you?
We're not the same.
My family abandoned me.
You...
You abandoned your family.
That's different.
It's the same.
It's the same, Jeff.
We both lost our families.
So, come on.
Talk to me,
maybe I could help.
Are you trying to be
a father now?
Feeling like you're my dad now?
No.
Don't think of me as your dad.
Let's just talk,
man to man.
Man to man...
Are you sure?
You're gonna give me advice?
What do you know about it?
Isn't it you who left us?
You have no right
to give advice.
I know what it feels like
not being able to sleep
at night.
Your mind keeps racing.
You keep asking yourself...
how your family's doing.
I know that feeling,
your eyes are shut,
but your mind is wide awake.
Then you get up.
You look for anything to help
you sleep because,
no matter how many drinks
you have,
sleep just won't come.
I know how painful
that wound is.
Even if you can't see it,
you feel it with your whole
being.
You're an idiot.
You know the pain?
So why did you leave us?
Because I'm an idiot!
I'm an idiot, Jeff!
An idiot!
I gave in to temptation.
I made a mistake one night,
just one night,
but I've regretted it for the
rest of my life.
So, if you need help,
I'm here.
Jeff.
Don't touch me,
I don't need you.
- Wait a minute.
- I said don't touch me!
I don't need you!
Why you don't understand that?
Don't you understand that?
Jeff!
Felma!
Felma, help!
It's Jeffrey!
- Manuel?
- Jeff!
Manuel!
Andrea, I don't have any money
left for my medicine.
I'm completely drained.
And you're the one
who recruited me
to that lending company, right?
So give me back my money!
Hold on, Sonny.
We're both waiting here.
I don't have any money either.
It has become a huge problem.
We can't solve it anymore.
What's the issue with Andrea?
We've been scammed, Ma'am.
Oh, no, that's trouble.
Why do you want so badly
to leave with Dad?
If you want to go, go ahead.
But you're not taking
my father with you.
You will never take my father
away from me, Coleen.
I won't allow it.