You were still trying
to call someone!
You're my daughter!
- Hazel!
- Mommy!
- You're so stubborn!
- Mom!
-Hazel!
-Why are you like this, Jessica?
Why do you keep doing this?
- Dad!
- Manuel!
Sorry about that.
That's all my phone
could manage.
What matters is that we know
they're in Camalig.
Give me your
and your dad's passports.
We don't have them here.
They left their passports.
This is Jessica's.
And Manuel's.
Can you give me some money
so I can buy something outside?
You really think I'd trust you
to leave this house?
Go check on your dad first.
He might need something.
I haven't left Bulacan yet.
I had to make a stop.
So, how are you doing there?
Is anyone still hanging
around you?
Not anymore, I think.
That's good to hear.
You know what, Alice?
Mr. and Mrs. Wilson
already sent the money
I asked for,
and even the extra
for our plane tickets
back to Canada,
they also send it.
- Amazing, right?
- Wow! Congratulations!
But how?
Jessica and Manuel don't have
their passports.
Exactly.
That's why I still have to check
with the embassy
on what to do.
- Such a hassle.
- Chill.
So Jessica's cooperating
with you now?
Oh, no way.
I caught her calling Abel.
I really can't trust that kid.
And yet, you left them alone.
So what if Jessica goes out and
asks the neighbors for help?
All the doors and windows
are locked
from the outside.
My traitor daughter can't get
out.
Hey, wait.
How's your nosy neighbor doing,
by the way?
Oh, you mean Miss Nita?
She's so annoying.
I regret ever giving her
my number.
She keeps calling.
Asking if I need anything.
- Well...
- at least she's concerned.
More like a pest!
Anyway,
can't you really come with me
on this errand?
I'm really sorry, friend.
I already agreed
to a shift extension.
All right then,
I'm heading out.
Okay, take care, bye.
We're not stopping
until we find Dad, okay?
Are there still houses
around here?
There, look! Wait, wait!
Here, here, here!
- Huh? What?
- Hold on! This is it!
This must be Nita's Store
Jessica mentioned.
Yes, you're right.
Let's ask.
Good afternoon, Ma'am.
Do you happen to know
where the Capistranos live?
Are you the carpenters Hazel
hired?
The ones fixing up their house?
Yes, Ma'am, that's us.
- Yes, Ma'am.
- Ah! There.
Oh! Over there!
See that old brown gate?
There are plants outside,
that's the one.
Thank you, Ma'am.
We'll get going.
All right then,
If you need snacks,
buy them here, okay?
Yes, Ma'am.
Uncle, we won't stop until
we're with Dad again, okay?
- Hazel.
- Hello?
So today's the start
of your house repairs?
- What?
- Ah, oh...
If you need an extra helper,
my grandson Virgilio
is available.
What? Huh?
What are you talking about,
Miss Nita?
Your carpenters,
they're at your house now.
What?
There are people in my house?
Yes, they just arrived.
What happened?
Uncle, there's no car outside.
- What?
- No car.
That doesn't mean no one's home.
Maybe they just took the car.
Jessica?
Je...
Uncle, keep your voice down,
Hazel might hear us.
Be quiet.
I just need to get something.
Jessica?
Keep it down.
Jessica.
Open it now! Hurry, hurry!
Jessica?
- Jessica?
Jessica!
- Jessica!
Jeffrey.
- Jessica?
- Jeffrey!
- Oh! Jessica! Jessica!
- Are you okay?
- Uncle!
Jeffrey, mom's not here.
Get dad ready, okay?
All right, I got this.
Dad.
Dad, you need to wake up.
Jeffrey and Uncle Abel are here,
Dad.
They're coming up.
You're going home now, Dad,
home to your family.
To our family.
Bro?
Dad.
Dad, I'm here.
It's me, Jeff.
Son.
Sorry.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm sorry.
I didn't get there right away.
Sorry, sorry.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm here now, Dad.
I'm here,
I'm here.
Your son is here.
Can't we just call them instead?
Coleen, we agreed
they'll be the ones to call us,
so they won't lose focus, okay?
Coleen, stop insisting.
It's Joel.
It's Joel, honey.
Hello, Joel?
Oh, thank God!
Joel, thank you.
Thank you so much.
Take care.
Take care, okay?
Please take care of Manuel.
We're heading
to the hospital now.
We'll meet you there.
Thank you.
Dad, are you sure
nothing hurts?
- I'm fine, I can handle it.
- Dad, are you okay?
Are you sure?
- Okay, okay, here, here.
- I'll go first, I'll go first.
There you go.
All right.
Jessica, come on,
let's go home.
Come on.
Dad, we're taking you to the
hospital, okay?
You need to see a doctor.
Son, no need.
I feel fine.
Let's just go straight home.
I'll recover there instead.
Dad, you may feel fine
but you still need
to see a doctor.
Please, Dad,
listen to my sister.
Don't be stubborn, please.
Darn it, someone blocked
the road!
Get them out!
Hey! Hey!
Where are you taking Manuel?
Where are you taking him?
Aren't you scared
of the restraining order, huh?
I'll sue you!
I'll sue all of you!
Jessica, get out of that car!
Get out now! Jessica!
Actually, I was not
really comfortable
having Manuel discharged.
Okay?
His condition is still
very delicate.
However, the DAMA form,
the Discharge Against
Medical Advice.
as already signed,
Nurse Gayle witnessed it.
Yes, Doctor, I was in the ICU
when Ma'am Hazel had
Sir Manuel sign the insurance
and DAMA documents.
Did you see Manuel himself sign
the discharge form?
I'm sorry, I saw him signing
some papers,
but I didn't get
to check each page.
I was also monitoring
his vital signs.
Where are the documents now?
Actually, I called Nurse Miles.
Okay? She's on her way.
I actually had her photocopy
the forms.
Let me call her first, okay?
Jessica, get out of the car!
Bring Manuel out now!
Big brother Jeffrey,
I'll get down.
I'll distract Mommy
so you can get Dad away.
- Jessi...
- I'll sue you!
Hazel's just going to hurt you!
Dad, don't worry about me.
What matters is that you get
to the hospital, okay?
Jessica, you're not getting out.
You're coming with us,
we're not leaving you behind.
You're coming home with us.
Jessica! Get out of there!
Hello, Dr. Richard.
I'm sorry,
I'm already on my way.
Yes, yes, Miles, It's okay,
okay, It's okay.
Actually, we're in your office
right now.
Where are the forms the ones
I asked you to photocopy
for Patient Manuel.
Where is it?
They're in my tray, Doc.
The tray on the table?
The brown folder on top?
Ah, okay.
- All right, Doc.
- Okay, got it.
Okay, thank you,
thank you, bye.
These are the documents.
Oh...
The signatures look similar.
See here?
On the insurance form...
the end of the signature
curves upward.
It's consistent on every page.
Bring Manuel
out of that car! Hey!
Jessica.
Jessica, hold Dad tight, okay?
Dad, hang on!
Let's go!
Get out of that car!
Hey! Manuel!
Dad, are you okay?
You idiots!
You're all so stupid!
But on the discharge form...
the signature tails downward.
So you're saying
this is a forgery?
But you know what? We don't have
to argue about this now.
Manuel is on his way.
My eldest is bringing him here.
Let's just ask him if he
actually signed these papers.
If we can prove Manuel didn't
sign these documents...
he can press charges.
Forgery against Hazel.
and an administrative complaint
against you.
For negligence and violation
of hospital protocol.
But I don't want to fight you
over this.
What I want is for Manuel
to recover.
Take care of him, heal him.
Then we won't have
any more problems.
I'll tell Manuel
not to file charges.
We will get it done.
- May I?
- Thank you, Doctor.
Miss Felma, wait.
If I may, one more time.
May I apologize? Okay?
The hospital is not
at fault here.
This is totally on me.
Okay?
I should have checked the papers
before Manuel signed.
I should have talked with Manuel
before he signed.
I was not able to do that.
Okay, but let me promise you,
I assure you,
we will get this done.
We will have this fixed.
- Okay?
- Thank you, Doctor.
Harris, move faster!
You're useless!
We couldn't catch up!
Hello?
Abel took Manuel, Alice.
He ran away with him.
That's why I called.
Felma is here.
She just spoke with Dr. Richard.
What?
You mean they're bringing
Manuel there?
That Felma is really testing me.
She wants war?
Fine, I'll give her war.
I have to go now.
Harris, hurry!
You're so slow!
Did Hazel really forge
Manuel's signature?
Come on!
Why do you keep tolerating
your friend?
Our friend, Miles.
You know what's going on, right?
Felma's been pestering Hazel.
She just wants to keep Manuel
away from her.
That's all.
At the expense
of her husband's health?
Miles...
Hazel is a good nurse.
She knows how to take care
of her husband.
Let's just try
to understand her.
She's been through a lot.
Oh, really, Alice?
Is she the only one who's going
through something?
But you know what, this time,
she has really crossed the line.
But why am I even surprised?
We're talking about Hazel here.
She's been like that since
college.
She doesn't care who she uses,
who she steps on,
or who gets dragged down,
as long as she gets
what she wants.
Is Mr. Manuel Cruz here yet?
He should be arriving
any minute now.
Trauma Bay 1!
Dad.
Mr. Manuel, welcome back.
How are you feeling?
I'm okay, Doc.
Only the patient can enter
the trauma bay.
Doctor, please, can Jessica
come in just for a moment?
I just need to say something.
All right, no problem.
Where's Mom?
There's an emergency at FMP,
but she's coming here soon.
Doc, I took his vitals earlier.
BP is 60 over 60,
heart rate 112,
but his oxygen stat
is dropping to 89 percent.
Okay, switch his nasal cannula
to a face mask,
5 liters per minute.
How's the chest tube?
Nothing, Doc.
Chest tube intact, no leaks.
No leak? No bubbles?
None, Doc.
Okay, good.
How are you feeling, Manuel?
Ah, I'm okay, Doc.
I actually feel better
after seeing my kids.
Good, glad to hear.
All right, let's do this.
CBC, X-ray, stat,
set up his previous antibiotics,
And we'll finish your admission.
Okay? Okay, come on, let's go.
Thank you so much.
You never left me
from the very start.
How are you feeling now?
I feel fine, Dad.
I'm relieved.
I'm so happy you're finally
here and safe.
Dear, you know your mom won't
stop
until she finds us...
right?
If she comes here,
don't go near her.
Stay away.
Better yet, go to your siblings.
I know they'll protect you,
especially your older
brother Jeffrey.
Okay, Dad.
Love you, Dad.
I love you too, sweetheart,
so... so much.
I'll step out for a bit, Dad.
We'll be right outside, okay?
All right.
Love you, Dad.
I love you. I love you.
I love you, Dad.
I love you so much.
What's this?
That's a lot of "I love you's."
You took all of it.
Sweetheart...
just remember...
I love you very, very much.
Never forget that.
I'll never forget, Dad.
So here's what happened,
Darling.
I drove the van straight
ahead, right?
Then suddenly, this white van
blocked the road.
Two guys went out, both carrying
baseball bats.
They were about to smash us!
They thought I'd be scared.
But I hit the gas,
just like that, drove off fast.
The two of them went down!
I thought they were done for.
But they got back up.
Then Hazel showed up,
furious, banging on the van.
She thought I'd back away.
But Jeff and I just looked
at each other.
And with that look alone,
we both knew.
So I stepped on the gas, hard!
Sped off, all the way down
the other street.
Hazel tried to chase us,
but she couldn't catch up.
They were gone.
When I looked back,
they were gone.
Darling, she really thought
she could stop us.
Wow! You were amazing, darling.
Like a real hero!
But wait, I have a question.
You said you backed up
when you saw Hazel, right?
Why didn't you just go forward
and run her over?
Actually, Auntie Paz,
that's what I thought Uncle Abel
was going to do.
Just graze her a little.
Graze? You should've hit her!
Darling, of course not.
I couldn't do that.
That's bad.
- That was a bit too much.
- Sorry, sorry.
I just got...
too worked up over that witch.
Didn't mean what I said.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
We need to talk.
Vitals normal, Nurse?
All right,
Okay, okay.
Then...
No leaks there? Good.
All right, let's remove
your chest tube now, Manuel.
Oh.
Oh. Okay, I'll give you
some time.
- Felma....
- Manuel.
Coleen, what's your problem?
Let go of me!
- Coleen! Hey!
- Come here!
Coleen!
What's wrong with you?
How could you just let your mom
take Dad away?
We were all worried sick!
I tried to stop her!
Really?
You didn't even ask Andrea
for help
when you and your mom were
sneaking Dad out!
You even avoided her,
didn't you?
And when Jeffrey and I were
trying to reach you,
what did you do?
You insulted us!
You just liked my messages.
And when Jeffrey called,
you answered,
but didn't even say a word!
Coleen, that wasn't me.
Mom confiscated my phone.
Jessica, stop lying!
Of course, you're on Mom's side,
because you want Dad away
from us too!
That's not true!
I stole Mom's phone so I could
call Uncle Abel, remember?
For all I know,
you only did that
because Dad's condition was
getting worse!
Yes! Because I was scared
something bad might happen
to him!
And Mom might hurt him!
But more than that, Dad wanted
to see Auntie Felma,
Brother Jeffrey, Sister Andrea,
and you, Coleen!
That's why I took the risk
and stole
Mom's phone to make that call!
So what, huh?
You expect us to thank you
because you called when Dad's
life was already in danger?
You're so selfish, Jessica!
You were so focused
on getting Dad away,
you didn't even think
about his condition!
- Coleen!
- Jessica, you didn't even think
that something bad
could happen to him!
Jessica, is that
what a daughter does?
You don't act like Dad's
daughter at all!
- Andeng.
- Dad.
You're just too jealous, Coleen!
And you're insecure!
I am not insecure about you!
I wish you'd just disappear!
- Was that Jessica?
- That sounded like Coleen.
- Jessica!
- You want me gone, right?
Fine, I'll leave!
I'm done with all of you!
Jessica!
Is there something
you're not telling me?
Is there a problem?
You monster!
What are you doing here?
You don't know?