Take care of everything.
And the scholarship will be yours.
Is it Teacher Chadok?
He’s forcing you to do this.
No one is.
Why are you all here?
We’re here to turn in the assignments.
What were you doing just now?
We accidentally knocked down these piles of books
so we were helping each other put them back.
Sorry, sir.
Everything is back to its place.
May you please excuse us now?
Why did you drag me out here, Akk?
I must talk to that teacher.
Calm yourself.
Guys, is everything okay?
I’ve got something to talk to Aye…
I mean Ayan.
Right?
Right.
Attend class soon.
Otherwise, we'll all lose points.
Yeah.
He must be the one behind my uncle’s death.
Or else how did this notebook end up in his room?
Calm down.
I asked him before.
He said he didn’t take it.
And you believed his words?
When will you realize he’s dangerous, Akk?
Just quit being a student prefect.
I can’t.
Why can’t you?
If you want to, you sure as hell can.
Aye, are you alright?
Are you okay?
Home alone again?
My mom is out working.
My parents divorced when I was young.
I lived with my mom and uncle growing up.
You said your uncle passed away.
Yeah.
Want to see him?
Here he is.
You’re keeping him in your bedroom?
Um.
Can you give me a sponge bath?
It’s your own body. Do it yourself.
Why should I do that for you?
I’m nice enough to take you home.
Are you all right?
Where do you keep your medicines?
I’ll go get them.
In the drawer.
Amitriptyline, for relieving stress.
You take these pills too?
You will get better soon.
Take some rest.
Can you keep me company?
Can you leave after I fall asleep?
I’m not going anywhere.
Get some sleep.
When I was at your home,
I loved seeing you with your parents.
You’re so cute.
That reminded me of when my family was whole.
You don’t let go of my hand.
Your fever is low and you're starting to irritate me again.
Shameless.
Do you smell that?
Mom.
Hey. You guys are awake?
Come. I just made us dinner.
Let’s eat.
This is Akk.
Akk?
Yes.
Sounds unique.
Hello.
Hi.
You guys must be hungry.
Should we get started?
Sure, Mom.
Eat as much as you can.
Akk, does Aye pay attention in class?
I think you can guess the answer.
Hey.
Just be nice.
Oh, let me guess.
He’s a wicked student.
Ma’am.
Super duper.
Right?
Right.
In class--
My mom’s food is wonderful.
Eat more.
It’s great that Aye brings a friend over.
I didn’t bring him here.
He drove me here.
Hold on.
You’re sick and asked me to take you home.
Oh, Akk.
Is Aye dating anyone?
Is he having a crush on anyone at the moment?
Oh, and are you dating anyone, Akk?
No doubt.
Look at him.
Of course, he is.
Good.
I think that’s good.
Ma’am.
No, I’m not.
Don’t be nonsense.
When did I ever date anyone?
Me.
You’re dating me.
What are you doing?
What kind of dishwashing is this?
Can you promise me one thing, Akk?
please don’t leave Aye behind.
My leg still hurts.
You’re harassing a sick person.
You can get on my nerves.
You’re fine.
Hand it over.
Oops!
Trying to bug me?
No.
Are you sure you washed it?
The washing bubbles are still there.
Akk.
Hm?
What are you doing?
There’s a bubble on your face.
What kind of dishwashing is this?
A very mindful kind.
You’re messy.
You’ve got bubbles on your arm too.
You’re also messy.
Are you picking up a fight?
Are you done?
I’ll be leaving now.
I’ll take you.
No.
You’re sick.
Take some rest.
I can find my way home.
I will take you home.
It’s totally okay.
It’s not.
You took Aye home. We can’t let you leave alone.
Right?
Thank you then.
I’ll go get my stuff upstairs.
Sure.
You have such good taste.
Oh, yeah.
Like you.
Akk,
thank you for taking care of Aye.
That’s fine. I just…
Ever since it happened,
he’s been under depression.
But lately, I see his mood’s been lifted.
I saw the pills he takes.
He’s probably shocked by what happened.
I took him to see a psychiatrist.
He asked if he could transfer to a new school.
I didn’t want to oppose that.
I was afraid I’d lose him too.
Ma’am.
Aye is going to be okay.
Thank you, kid.
Can you promise me one thing, Akk?
Whatever happens,
please don’t leave Aye behind.
Guys.
The World Remembers is stirring things up again.
Check Twitter.
It’s the day to reverse the curse.
Find out together who is behind it.
When school isn’t a safe place,
it’s time we gather outside.
Outside?
I think more people are joining them this time.
Look how many people like and retweet it.
Right.
No.
We can’t let those students protest outside the school.
But, principal,
their protest might be so damaging.
Not damaging?
Don't you realize how much money the alumni club is threatening to take away from us?
It's due to your weak discipline enforcement.
Think about it.
That hashtag is trending in just a few hours.
Not long after this, the media is going to make news out of it.
How damaging do you think it will be to our school's reputation?
Deal with it.
Don’t let the media get involved.
- Yes.
- Yes, ma’am.
And that student prefect club of yours,
if it’s no use,
you better terminate it.
Manage.
Yes, ma’am.
Chadok.
Suppalo must remain Suppalo.
Take care of it.
I hope you don’t forget who made you who you are today.
The school has directed us to keep a careful eye on student protests.
Every student prefect must be extra strict on their watch.
Strict how?
The school has implemented a new policy that forbids students from mentioning the protest.
And if there’re violators?
They will be blacklisted and punished later.
Blacklisting its own students.
Yes.
We must find a way to stop them.
Otherwise,
the school will let someone from outside do it.
From the outside?
- Take one.
- Here.
Let us all grieve for the loss of the school board’s justice.
Come join us.
Hey!
Please join us.
See you.
Should we get them now?
For what?
For handing out armbands?
Guys, let’s mourn for it.
Ready?
[The World Remembers singing the funeral music.]
Wat.
Film them.
I want to know who took the armband.
Are you sure?
It’s just for us to see.
I will not send it to the school board.
Okay.
Here you go.
Please come join us.
Thank you.
Many horrible things have happened.
We've been looking for the truth behind it.
However, we never catch the bad guy.
Because there are never enough serious investigations.
You know why?
Why?
Because the school board lacks integrity.
They never really care to find the one responsible.
True.
Let’s see.
Is any of you here done with the Suppalo curse?
If you are, join us.
We have an appointment, guys.
Where?
At the Suppalo Curse Reverse Day.
Come and show them our power.
That’s awesome, Nian.
Those who have the armband, wear it.
If you haven’t got one, come and get it here.
Join us, everyone.
Thank you.
Nian!
[You freaking misfits, you have it coming.]
Damn.
Will we be cursed too?
Nian!
Are you all right?
Nian.
Are you okay?
Nong.
What the heck is this?
Yes.
So dramatic.
Was it you?
Do you really think I want my school to look bad?
Do you like it?
If he wants to talk to me, he should do it face-to-face.
[They should have protested a long time ago.]
[The curse will be back because of them.]
[They should just stop protesting.]
[Suppalo will not endure this anymore.]
[It won’t kill them to just stay silent.]
[ECLIPSE1234: Will you stop or not?]
Akk.
Was it you?
What the hell?
You did it.
This fabric banner and this threat post.
Are you this obsessed with the Suppalo curse?
Listen to me.
Thousands of people are tweeting about the fabric banner.
Do you really think I want my school to look bad?
That’s not my way.
If not you, then who?
Must be someone in this school.
But we can’t trace the IP address on Twitter, can we?
That’s why we need to create a fake link.
To make them click through. We will get the IP address from there.
Who would fall for that?
Your trap sucks.
See this.
[Magical! Do this and all your illness will be gone!]
So old.
If Teacher Chadok sees this, he will surely fall for it.
He doesn’t look like someone who can resist this.
Say we got the IP address. Then what?
Lots of people know how to hide or sham it.
If it’s really Chadok, he wouldn’t know how to do that.
Trust me.
Can you be less obvious about that?
If teachers pass by, it will be taken.
It’s my asset.
Whoever takes it will face embezzlement charges.
3 years imprisonment tops.
Or a THB6,000 fine.
Or both.
Got it?
Yes.
Aye.
We’ve got one click.
That’s me.
I’m checking if it works.
You’re a man of violence.
An authoritarian.
You’ll pay for that.
Why are you turning away? Help me here.
Do you want to be close to me?
Turn away then.
There’s something over your mouth.
Should we take turns now?
No.
This doesn’t look like my school at all.
It’s so messed up.
Akk.
Who else is a school fanatic apart from you and your father Chadok?
Who else is a Suppalo cult fanatic?
Mo.
Yeah.
Were you behind that fabric threat banner?
I wasn’t.
Then who?
I thought it was you at first.
I know you’re the one who burned that gang’s leaflets.
I just wanted to help you.
It was an easy job. It didn’t hurt anyone.
But I’ve not done anything lately.
Mo.
If you’re planning on doing something shitty, don’t.
Please.
Akk.
Do you realize you’ve changed?
I haven’t changed.
You’re wrong.
Seriously.
Are you still on the Suppalo side?
What will the student prefects do about the protest?
We’re told to collect the names of those who are joining.
What if I am?
Will my name be taken too?
Heck yes.
Why are you joining them anyway?
You’re the head of the class.
Besides, don’t associate with those guys.
The head of the class whose duties are only to welcome the teachers and turn in assignments?
Not just that.
You give me wake-up calls.
You cover for me when I’m late.
More importantly, you’re my report partner.
Even though most of the work is done by you.
I like the report video we shot at Akk’s house.
Do you like it?
Yeah.
I do.
Someone sent me a friend request on Facebook.
Named Bruce Wayne.
Yeah?
Yes.
I think I have a good feeling for him.
Are you nuts?
You have a good feeling for someone you haven’t met.
I’m surprised by that too.
But I want to see him in person.
What if he’s a bad guy who wants to deceive you?
Don’t think so.
I think I will call him out.
If he wants to talk to me, he should do it face-to-face.
Do you agree?
Yeah.
If I go to see him, Thua will know how I feel about him.
So?
Are you afraid he will reject you?
Why would I be afraid he’d reject me?
I’m the girls’ favorite.
But this is Thua.
But I’m not ready.
Why?
Are you afraid your cool looks will be ruined?
Heck no.
I just don’t really know what to do.
How do you feel about him?
You just like him.
Or it’s more than that?
I have no clue how I feel.
But when he’s out of sight,
I’m so worried about him.
When you spend time with him,
do you feel so happy that you forget all the sadness?
I think…
that’s love.
I like when you smile widely.
You’re cute.
Took you long enough.
Don’t act like you’re tired.
You said you’d track down the intervenor behind that incident.
Get up.
All you think about is work?
Don’t you want any good moments with me at all?
What moments are you talking about?
People dating always create their good moments together.
Who’s dating you?
Don’t be a wisecracker.
So?
Did the fish take the bait yet?
Not yet.
This fish is being cautious.
So witty.
Who is he?
What does this person really want?
I have no idea.
Have dinner with me.
What? I’m not hungry.
Well, I am.
Eat with me.
No.
Come on.
You’re eating with your boyfriend but looking so distant.
Are you cheating on me?
Are you?
I’m done arguing with you.
Eat and go home.
See?
You’re shooing me away.
You’re cheating on me for sure.
You’re so obsessed with something nonsense.
Mr. Nice Mouth has returned.
That’s a relief.
What are you talking about?
I see you’re so concerned about the intervenor that you became quiet.
So I tried to get myself yelled at.
I’m smart, right?
Yeah?
Should I thank you?
Hell yeah.
When people do something nice to you, you must thank them.
Got it?
Sure.
Of course.
Certainly.
You like wasabi?
Come here.
Yum.
Open your mouth.
Do it. A nice guy must be thanked.
Open it.
No.
Do it.
Yum.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
Akk.
You’re trying to get me.
No.
Why are you smiling?
Nothing.
I just like it when I get to eat with you like this.
I usually eat alone.
The food doesn’t taste as good as it does now.
You just keep rambling.
Just eat.
You eat this too.
Are you joining the protest?
Yes.
The school handles it so poorly.
I think I should do something.
But it’s not safe.
Do you believe in the curse?
Do you want to see me at the protest?
I’ll let you know later.
Are you joining?
I am.
But we should get to class first. Come on.
Are you also joining?
I want to see for myself if the Suppalo curse is really potent.
Every place has its tale invented to scare people.
It’s the method used to rule people.
And who invented it?
I don’t know.
What I do is the tale inventor must get the benefit from it.
I’m taking off.
Um.
I don’t know what to tell yet.
Filmmakers always start with something they want to tell.
There are so many things in my head right now.
I just don’t know how to convey them.
How about we start with favorite movies, books, news, or stories of people close to you?
What or who is your inspiration?
I like a screenplay that someone wrote.
His name is Nut.
He writes indie film screenplays.
What's his work like?
He likes to play around with the grey area between tales and reality.
Interesting.
You can start from there.
Sure.
And what’s the story you want to tell?
I’m interested in what’s happening in our school.
The protest and the Suppalo curse.
The School Foundation Day is approaching in a few days.
Take care of the orderliness.
Every student prefect must be extra strict on their watch.
The school has implemented a new policy that forbids students from mentioning the protest.
[You freaking misfits, you have it coming.]
The school board lacks integrity.
Don’t.
I can help myself.
No one cares what we do.
It’s just a friend helping a friend up.
You’re overthinking it.
Come on.
Hey!
Aye!
What the heck are you doing?
I haven’t got to swim yet.
Swim with me.
Hey!
What are you smiling at?
I smile because you smile.
I like when you smile widely.
You’re cute.
I’m not cute.
I’m solemn.
The president of the prefect club, you know?
Are you opposed to your own cuteness?
I am not cute.
You wanna fight me?
You’re cute.
Picking up a fight, huh?
Get this.
Am I still cute?
You are.
Shut up, Shortstop.
I’m not following your order, Big Foot.
We’re in school.
I’ve been wearing an inappropriate uniform.
Why am I not affected by the curse yet?
Watch it.
Why?
What are you gonna do to me?
Like you’re so scary.
When will you stop teasing me, Shortstop?
I will never stop.
Aye.
Don’t look at anyone else like this.
I’m jealous.
Who’s screaming?
Nian.
[Jumnong, Jumnun, Jumnian]
Directed by Tanwarin Sukkhapisit
Do you see what’s happening?
Are you going to let the school do this to us?
You’re students.
Your duty is to study.
Why is growing up so tough?
Sometimes, I just don’t want tomorrow to come.
Until tomorrow comes, let me hold your hand like this.
Should we go out?
I’m glad it’s you.
Kiss my cheek.
I want a good moment this morning.