HOW CAN I FORGET YOU?
Is Zhe okay?
Yeah, he's fine.
Are you cooking?
Oh, yeah.
Could you open the window
to let the smell out?
Are you hungry? I made breakfast for you.
I'm a bit tired. I'm going to rest.
He kept saying it was eight o'clock,
and when I told him to wait a bit,
he wouldn't.
I really don't know what to do.
- Mommy didn't answer the phone…
- Alright, alright.
Mommy will definitely remember next time.
- I assure you.
- Mommy didn't answer the phone
- I promise I won't lie to you, okay?
I won't forget again, I swear.
Alright…
Richard, don't forget to send me
the quote, okay?
Oh, sure.
Xiaojuan,
is there anything else I can help with?
It's fine, focus on your work.
- Thanks!
- Okay.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Sorry about that.
Yeah, it's our mistake this time.
I'll get back to you right away.
Okay, sounds good.
Would you like me to pour you a cup?
Sorry, that's actually my cup.
Oh, sorry about that. Well.
No worries. You can use any
of the cups here next time.
Or I can switch it for you now.
No, it's fine, just put it back
after you wash it.
Okay, sorry. Thanks.
- Ms. Liu.
- Hey.
Our boss really loves coffee.
He always brings back
a ton of high-end coffee beans,
so feel free to help yourself.
Want me to pour you a cup?
If I have another,
I won't be sleeping tonight.
About that singer you mentioned,
- Ning, right?
- Yeah.
You can go ahead and contact her.
- Check her availability and interest.
- Got it.
- No problem.
- Okay.
HELLO, I HAVE
A WORK-RELATED QUESTION FOR YOU.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Were you still sleeping?
I didn't sleep all night. Come on in.
- Just leave your shoes outside.
- Okay.
Wow, your studio is amazing!
Not bad.
You've got quite the vinyl collection.
You know, my bandmates and I always
fantasize about having a studio like this.
If you like it,
you're welcome to come anytime.
It's free. Free of charge.
Really?
Consider it a thank you
for referring me for the gig.
No worries.
But it's not a huge stage
or anything, right?
As long as there's money, that's good.
Of course.
If you're interested,
you can send us your rate.
Having fun is the most important thing.
I only took the job because you…
recommended it.
But I took a look at the event
description you sent me.
For the music part,
I might tweak the arrangement a bit.
I'll make some coffee. Do you want some?
Sure.
Sounds like a plan then.
Now, where's the contract?
No problem.
How did you get this? I bought one too.
That means you've got great taste.
Thanks.
Are you free tonight?
Want to grab dinner?
I've already got plans for tonight,
maybe next time.
A date?
Is it with your bandmate?
Hey, how about spaghetti
for dinner tonight?
I've already bought all the ingredients.
Let me tell you,
you won't believe
how crazy my first day at work was.
Hello?
Hello, are you busy?
I won't be home tonight.
I'm staying at Renxiu's place.
That's fine. Is Zhe doing okay?
Hello? Are you still there?
Hello?
I've got to get back to work.
- I'll talk to you later.
- Well…
The city bears, on their birthday,
decided to go camping in the mountains.
Wow, it's so beautiful here.
Let's camp here tonight.
- Welcome, come on in.
- Okay.
Little one, are you bored?
Sorry, my son doesn't talk much.
No worries.
Feel free to take a look at
the information.
Hey, little one, if you're bored,
how about drawing with this?
Thank you.
If it's more convenient for you,
we also offer remote digital financial
services for online consultations.
Zhe,
Mom and Dad just need to talk
for a little while.
We'll be done soon, okay?
I wanted to check,
have you planned for
an education fund before?
- No, we haven't.
- No.
I see.
Here's the thing.
We had a joint savings account before,
mainly for covering
our son's living expenses.
But now that we're divorced,
there might be some extra-curricular
classes he needs to pay for.
Got it.
We'd like to plan for
his educational expenses.
Understood.
Hey, Liu, sorry for the delay.
I'm near the MRT station.
Where's that café you mentioned?
Thanks again for your help today.
No problem.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Alright. Alright, see you soon.
Bye.
KAI MISSED CALL
Sorry, sorry.
I worked overtime and lost track of time.
So, is your new job at a big company
or something?
Why has it taken two weeks
just to schedule a practice session?
We finally got a time,
and you still forgot.
I'm really sorry.
How about I treat you all
to a late-night snack?
Food, huh?
- Alright, let's go.
- No need, Bigfoot.
You've got work tomorrow, right?
You've got your new life now.
You're not like us anymore.
I promise it won't happen again.
So when should we schedule next?
How about the weekend?
We can practice two days straight
and make up for the time you missed.
But you probably don't want to
because you want to be with Yi-Ming Jiang.
It's really because of work,
it has nothing to do with Yi-Ming.
- Weekend practice is fine.
- I get that you're busy with work.
We all need to make money.
But you can't do weekdays,
and on weekends,
you can't practice all day either.
We need to book you in advance
just to meet up.
Sorry… But aren't you…
getting too hard to schedule with?
I'm honestly doing
my best to coordinate my time.
You were the one who wanted
to form a band in the first place.
Now, with this on-and-off attitude,
I'm not into it anymore.
Wait until you've thought it through.
He's still upset.
That canceled performance
really disappointed him,
and now with you changing jobs,
he feels like it's out of character
for you.
Just wait for him to cool off.
This is good.
Sorry to interrupt,
I've been listening to your music,
could I get an autograph?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
Thanks so much.
What about you? Want an autograph too?
Thanks, but I'm good.
So… are you going to apologize to Kai?
I'll do it later.
Knowing his personality,
he won't listen to anything
I say right now.
It's just frustrating.
Work has been so busy with the event,
and now this happens.
How's your new job going?
Not exactly what I imagined.
What do you mean?
Even though I juggled two
or three jobs at once,
at least I had a lot of freedom.
I got to meet different people every day,
and face new challenges.
It was stressful sometimes,
but at least it was never boring.
Now, it's just sitting in the office,
seeing the same people every day,
doing almost the same tasks.
Meetings are full of finger-pointing.
Everyone's in little cliques.
It's exhausting.
But you've only been there a short time.
It feels like it's been a year already.
If you really don't like it, why not quit?
No,
I don't want my girlfriend to think
I'm just… all talk.
So you're staying
in a job you don't like for love?
Is that necessary?
I wouldn't call it a sacrifice.
Part of it is for her,
but part of it is for me, too. I'm 30 now.
I want to see how far I can go.
And besides, my mom's getting older.
If she can't work later,
I'll have to support her.
I can't rely on part-time jobs to do that.
I want my family to feel secure too.
You're thinking of everyone else.
What about you?
They're people I really care about.
Here's to you.
To me?
To your kind and thoughtful heart.
Thank you.
And I'll toast to you.
What for?
To…
Even though we haven't known
each other for long,
you always manage to encourage me
without even trying.
So…
does that mean
I'm pretty important to you?
And then, I ended up using
my coworker's cup
and even asked her if she wanted coffee.
- How embarrassing.
- Yeah, super embarrassing.
I've never done anything that awkward
at my part-time jobs before.
- You're so adorable.
- Really?
Kai always says
I'm scary after I've had a drink.
Not at all.
I think you're more smiley when you drink.
- You look beautiful when you smile.
- Thank you.
Ting-Ting,
I…
don't just want to be someone
who encourages you
or a close friend.
I'm serious about this.
I already have a girlfriend.
I know,
but I still hope you'll consider it.
I won't put any pressure on you.
I could play music with you,
travel with you,
do whatever you want to do.
I want to be there for you.
You're back.
I didn't hear you come in earlier.
Were you busy?
Did you drink?
You didn't ride your scooter back,
did you?
No, I didn't.
Are you free now?
I need to finish this report
and send it to my colleague before ten.
How about we see a movie tomorrow
since we have the day off?
I saw one that looks really good today.
Tomorrow?
I can't. I'm taking Zhe to the park.
I could come along.
Maybe next time.
I told Zhe it'd just be the two of us.
But I haven't seen him in a while either.
I'll just hang out nearby.
What time are you meeting?
Four o'clock. Four in the afternoon.
I can swing by after picking up
a package in the morning.
It's fine, you don't have to.
I'm not busy.
I'll go take a shower.
NING CALLING
NING MISSED CALL
TAKE YOUR TIME TO THINK ABOUT IT.
I'LL WAIT FOR YOU. GOOD NIGHT.
The wheel is missing.
Zhe, Mom already checked the park,
it's not here.
Maybe it didn't fall here.
It could be at home.
Let's go home and check, okay?
Zhe, Zhe,
Zhe, let's go home and check, okay?
Let's go home and check.
Alright, come on.
You're going to hit someone.
Sit here and calm down for ten minutes.
The wheel is missing.
Excuse me, did he hit you just now?
Did he hit you?
Are you alright? Sorry about that.
It might be safer
if you play over there.
Zhe, it's really hot here.
Let's go over there.
- The wheel is missing.
- Zhe.
- Alright. Zhe.
I told you not to come.
It's fine.
- The wheel is missing.
- Alright, it's okay.
Mommy is here.
- The wheel is missing.
- It's alright.
This…
never mind.
Why didn't you tell me
Zhe hasn't been doing well lately?
I didn't know how to say it.
Why not?
I'm really tired right now.
Can we not discuss this?
If you need help with anything,
you can tell me, you know?
I told you not to come today.
You always leave things unsaid.
You've been like this from the start.
Didn't I tell you that
you can talk to me about anything?
I want to share
these responsibilities with you,
but you don't tell me anything.
I don't know what to do.
Zhe isn't your responsibility.
You don't have to help me with this.
I don't understand.
I'm your girlfriend. Why do you
always treat me like an outsider?
I'm not treating you like an outsider.
Do you think I haven't noticed?
You don't even have the courage
to introduce me properly to others.
We're together.
Why do I have to explain our relationship
to everyone?
Is that really so important?
Yes, it's important.
We love each other.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Why do we have to hide?
When you were with Renxiu,
did you feel weird holding hands
in public?
I…
I don't get why you're comparing this.
In the end,
are you ashamed of our relationship?
That's not how I feel.
But your actions say otherwise.
Fine.
In front of others,
acknowledging it
might not be important to you,
but aren't two people in a relationship
supposed to support each other
and grow together?
I'm willing to do anything for you,
to make you part of my future,
why do you keep pushing me away?
Ting-Ting Zhong,
you're getting emotional right now.
This is really frustrating.
These things aren't even your concern.
Yi-Ming Jiang,
didn't we agree to face things together?
Didn't you promise me?
I've been working so hard
to find a full-time job,
all because I want to
make myself stronger,
to be someone you can rely on.
I want to ease your burdens.
And that barstool.
I know how much you liked it,
so I secretly ordered it,
hoping to surprise you.
I've done all this,
just hoping
we can have a good future together.
Now you're saying
it's none of my business?
What do I mean to you, then?
Do we really have to talk
about this right now?
Why can't we address our problems?
You want to talk?
You can't afford the barstools.
You hate working full-time.
Now you're taking all
your frustrations out on me,
claiming it's for my sake.
I never asked for that.
I never pressured you.
You talk about sharing responsibilities,
but you're putting a lot of
pressure on me. Do you realize that?
You want to talk? Fine.
Are you sure you've told me everything?
That you're not hiding anything from me?
So, everything I've done for you
is just a burden?
Is that what you're saying?
Get on.
Are you ready?