HOW CAN I FORGET YOU?
ONE YEAR LATER
Don't you think maternity clothes
these days
don't even look like maternity clothes?
Pick one of these two.
They're both so cute.
Can't I get both?
Alright then, both it is.
Hey.
- Hi.
- You're here.
Welcome, welcome.
The baby just woke up.
I brought a low-sugar cake.
- Perfect. I love sweets.
- Thank you.
- And a gift for the baby.
- Thanks.
Just put it over there.
Come on in.
Wanna see the baby?
Oh my gosh.
- So cute.
- Wow.
She keeps staring at you.
Yeah. Want to hold her?
- Can I?
- Of course.
Alright.
Hey there.
Hold your hands like this.
Good, just like that.
Yeah, support her neck.
- She even looks a bit like you.
- So cute.
- Hi.
- She's so adorable.
- Hello.
- I'm Auntie Ting-Ting.
And this is Auntie Yi-Ming.
Just like Yu-Shan, she's a water sign too.
- Super emotional.
- I am not.
Oh, really?
In the delivery room,
who was crying their eyes out outside?
I just couldn't hold back my tears
seeing you go through so much.
She was in pain for five hours.
Alright, Miss Crybaby.
This little one is a night owl like me,
so she needs someone
to soothe her at night.
Hey, babe,
did you record my labor
and the times you soothed her?
When she misbehaves in the future,
you can play it all back for her.
You can't do that.
I'm kidding.
She's smiling.
She's agreeing with her mom.
- Looks like she really likes you.
- Really?
Yeah, see? She's been smiling
at you this whole time.
Oops.
Yi-Ming Jiang.
Is that so?
Don't you think Jing-Chuan and Yu-Shan
are really happy like this,
with such an adorable baby?
Yeah.
Marrying someone you love
is truly a happy thing.
You can be happy with someone you love
without getting married too, though.
True.
But marriage is wonderful too.
It could be about
working together toward shared goals.
Ting-Ting Jhong,
do you remember saying once
that you didn't think marriage
was necessary?
- Did I?
- Yeah, you did.
But back then, I never thought
I'd be working full-time either.
Ideas change over time.
That's true.
So…
what do you think now?
I think…
marriage
or no marriage,
it doesn't matter.
What matters most is being happy together,
right?
Right.
Come on, let's go buy ingredients.
Wait for me.
- Ting-Ting Jhong.
What?
- Are you proposing?
- No.
No?
Then why are you looking at rings?
Aren't you?
Yeah.
- Hey.
- Wow, you're bold.
Just looking around.
What do you mean, "Just looking around"?
This isn't something to do casually.
Pick this one.
This one looks better.
No, this one's better.
Definitely this one,
and it's cheaper too.
Is cheaper the point?
No, the main point
is the thought behind it.
So it's okay if it's affordable, right?
Go on, choose this one.
Click "add to cart."
Alright, calm down.
I'm just browsing.
I'm telling you,
the way you propose matters
more than the ring style.
If you don't get it right,
you'll get nagged for life, like my dad.
Do you need help with it?
Do you want flowers, or balloons?
That's so tacky.
Then what? Come up with something.
I've got it.
What?
How about a street performance?
Then, play your bass,
the thing you're best at,
and in front of everyone,
pull out the ring.
Keel down and propose.
Me and Da-Jiao will grab some sparklers,
and create a dreamy effect with the smoke.
- So romantic.
- Not bad.
I don't think this is a good idea.
Why not?
We'll set it up perfectly for you.
You just seize the moment.
She won't say no.
I still think we need balloons,
just for a little decoration on the side.
Come on, stop teasing me.
What shape? Let's go with heart-shaped.
‪PLEASE SELECT A WIDTH
SPECIAL NEEDS
PLEASE SELECT THE HAMMERED TEXTURE
- Is that all that's left?
- It'll work.
- Take a look?
- Yeah, good.
How about the other stuff?
I'll check over there.
Is everyone here yet?
What's this?
We're all set. Got your ring ready?
Stop messing with me.
Oh, come on.
Here she comes.
Good luck. Good luck.
Hey, everyone.
We are Departed. I'm A-Kai, the guitarist,
this is Da-Jiao, our drummer,
and the most talented of Departed,
and our awesome bassist,
Ting-Ting Jhong.
Alright, I'll keep it short.
There are moments when music
speaks best to the heart.
Let's start our performance.
Hope you enjoy it.
Excuse us,
we'll take a five-minute break.
Feel free to take a short rest.
We'll be back soon with more great music.
What are you doing?
I'm not proposing here.
What do you mean, not proposing here?
She's not proposing here.
- Alright then…
- So, what now?
Just tell her directly.
- Okay, take a rest.
- You just…
Well, everyone,
let's all take a short break.
Excuse us.
Just a little break.
Are we still waiting?
- What's the plan now?
- It's a 5-minute break, didn't you hear?
BREAKFAST IS IN THE RICE COOKER.
SEE YOU LATER.
Mom.
- Need a hand?
- No, no, it's fine.
What's up?
Just cutting onions.
Get out, don't get in the way here.
I'm in the way?
Yes, you're in the way.
Yi-Ming is helping here. You can go.
- This is really good.
- Delicious.
The bamboo shoots are so sweet.
They're really tasty.
The neighbor auntie gave me
a bunch of bamboo shoots and veggies.
Remember to take some home later.
- Alright.
- Auntie.
Make sure to keep some for yourself.
I did. She gives me so much
every couple of days.
I can't even finish it all.
That's so nice.
Young lady,
don't just sit there eating.
You keep leaving everything
to poor Yi-Ming.
You need to help out, you know that?
I am helping.
You are?
This whole spread was made by Yi-Ming.
And who told me I was in the way
and to leave earlier?
You are in the way.
Now, are you, as my mom,
just trying to give me a hard time?
Auntie, this fish is so fresh.
- Right? Tasty, huh?
- Right.
Next time,
I'll introduce you to the owner
of the fish stall.
Once he knows you,
he'll save the freshest fish for you.
Sounds great.
- Yi-Ming, eat up. Be sure to eat more.
- Okay.
Have you lost weight recently?
Mom, you think everyone looks thin.
No, I don't.
Auntie,
next time it's your turn to cook.
I want to taste your cooking too.
Alright, but you'll have to help.
Of course. You too.
You? Forget it.
No way, come on.
Mom, help me out here.
You?
- Forget it.
- Yep, forget it.
- Hey, you two.
- Forget it.
- It's still here.
- Yeah.
So, what made you want to come here today?
Just… wanted to take a walk.
Memories, you know? Senior.
Hey, look.
Yi-Ming,
from the first time I saw you
on the volleyball court,
I liked you. And even now,
I really cherish what we have.
Even though, between the two of us,
I've always been the immature one.
Why would you say that?
But it's true.
I used to say I'd take care of you,
and give you a home.
But honestly, I didn't even know
if that's what you really wanted.
I was just using the way
I thought love should be
to ask for a response from you.
Recently, I've learned a lot.
Turns out, loving someone
means letting go of so many expectations
and still feeling happy.
I don't need to become someone special,
and you don't need to do
anything special for me.
But we can both feel
that we're loved by each other.
Will you marry me?
Maybe marriage isn't something
necessary for you,
or it's something
you've already experienced.
But I want to do this,
not to prove anything to anyone,
but because I want to keep
walking this path
with you in the days to come.
I will.
"Is this the one you like?"
Let me put it on for you.
Thank you.
Stop working already.
What's up?
What are you doing?
It's my turn today.
You go rest.
Just take it easy today.
Watch TV, read a book,
or do whatever you like.
Really take a break, alright?
Just a bean
You drink yours, I drink mine
The same complex taste
But a different love
These small differences
So ordinary, so beautiful
Of course, I'll argue with you
But after the silent treatment
We'll be honest again
Of course, I'll let you see
All my flaws
And I'll give you
The deepest, most unconditional love
As long as you remember my waiting
Can you remember?
Excuse me, miss, is it for a gift?
Yes, for my girlfriend.
Take your time choosing.
Let me know if you need help.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
- Miss?
- Yes?
I'd like to see that one.
The one on the left?
Ting-Ting is great with kids.
Yeah, she's very patient with them.
Xiao-Zhe really likes her too.
I know this sounds a bit old-fashioned,
and I know you're reserved by nature,
but have you both thought about
the next step?
Marriage and all that?
That look says it all.
Yeah.
Have you picked out a name for your kid?
Changing the subject, huh?
Feels like…
marriage
or no marriage,
it doesn't really matter.
What matters is
that you're happy together, right?
Right.
Come on, let's go buy ingredients.
I'm wondering,
if I can marry Ting-Ting?
She's the one who showed me
that I can live the life I want.
She taught me to be brave.
Marriage is something
between the two of you.
As long as you're happy,
that's all that matters.
As a mom,
I can finally let go of this burden
on my shoulders.
I'll take care of her.
I'm counting on you.
Mom, need a hand?
No, no, it's fine.
What's up?
Just cutting onions.
Get out, don't get in the way.
Let me help you.
Clothes drying on the small balcony
You wear yours, I wear mine
Carrying the same scent
To different places
Coming back a little different
Sitting side by side, sharing our day
The same day smells so natural
So simple, so easy