"Light From the Ashes" - Cai Weize
♫  Countless fireflies born from insignificance  ♫
♫  Riding the long wind to gather into a shining galaxy  ♫
♫  Proclaim to the world on top of the sky  ♫
♫  We will return in glory  ♫
♫  Clear the clouds and descend with the heat  ♫
♫  Melting ice and snow, overcoming twists and turns  ♫
♫  Finally at this moment of peak  ♫
♫  There is a figure that coincides with the past  ♫
♫  The glory of the past that never came  ♫
♫  The pride that the future will never pass  ♫
Our fingertips intertwined and condensed  ♫
♫  Into a song that ignited the battlefield  ♫
♫  The only light in an endless night  ♫
♫  Is you and me who overcame mediocrity  ♫
♫  Up on the clouds and down in the dust  ♫
♫  Fireflies making every effort to illuminate  ♫
♫  I came from the legend to carry on a legend  ♫
♫  Once it's disruptive, a decade of persistence won't be in vain  ♫
♫  Up on the clouds and down in the dust  ♫
♫  Fireflies making every effort to illuminate  ♫
This circle he's drawn represents that we will fight together.
Inside the circle is the pure land,
outside is the battlefield.
That's right, isn't it?
What I mean is, you guys shouldn't move out of the circle.
But...
Subtitles and Timing provided to you byðŸ’¥ðŸ¥ TEAM 7ï¸âƒ£ ðŸ¥ðŸ’¥ @viki.com
What is his plan?
How dare he face the monster alone?
Did he kill the monster, or was he eaten by it?
I'll go and check.
We need to give him a few more minutes.
The expert has his own strategy.
We must show our tolerance.
Then our tolerance is...
Waiting.
Fifteen minutes have passed.
We've shown our tolerance well enough, right?
Yes.
Then, the expert's strategy is...
There are only five minutes left to break the record.
If we don't go out of the circle,
we could become the biggest joke in the history of Glory.
This is called "Responding to changes by staying still."
We are turning ourselves into a joke by not moving.
Guild Master.
Everyone, get ready.
I'll count down from three.
Then out of the circle.
Three.
Two.
Congratulations to the players of Blue Brook Guild,
Blue River, Thundering Light, Lord Grim, Flower Lantern, and Bound Boat
for breaking the Frost Forest record
within 15 minutes and 24.11 seconds.
He did it! Only 15 minutes.
It is a whole five minutes faster.
What did I say.
This is the expert I invited.
This is called "winning all by staying still."
With Lord Grim,
the world of the 10th server belongs to Blue Brook Guild.
Don't move! Don't move, don't move.
The expert must be looking for me.
Lord Grim has left Blue Brook Guild.
What?
It's over.
Go, leave.
Go.
You get me a cup of coffee.
- Quickly.
- Okay.
You,
g-go water the flowers.
You.
Forget it.
Xiao Tang, why don't you choose a Launcher like me?
I can teach you about it.
But I like to see my opponent falling in front of me.
Here. Then choose Battlemage.
My idol, One Autumn Leaf, is in this profession.
I, Tang Rou, will never lose to anybody.
Everybody.
Mucheng.
Today is the first training session with our new captain.
This is our brand new synergy
and more so, a mutual understanding.
I believe with Sun Xiang's joining in,
and the efforts of all of you here,
Excellent Era will surely create another brilliant future.
My goal is to build a new dynasty for Excellent Era.
Starting from today, Sun Xiang is the core of our Excellent Era Dynasty.
He'll shoulder the responsibility as the captain
to complete the captain's mission.
Sun Xiang,
Excellent Era's future depends on you.
We will fight Blue Rain in the next competition.
Now, start simulation training.
Everyone, start training.
Congratulations to Chairman Tao for getting an excellent talent.
Thank you.
Ye Qiu's revenge on me was personal.
Fortunately, the petty guy was driven away.
Do you think I can return...
Ye Qiu retired voluntarily.
No one forced him out.
Yehui, you can eat whatever you like, but you should speak carefully.
Sorry. I have no other intentions.
I just want to return.
When Ye Qiu drove you away, he was still the captain.
Everyone, attack with everything.
Striker in the middle. Qi Master, cover him.
Launcher, keep up. Faster.
Launcher, attack to break their rhythm.
Launcher, what's the matter with you? You are always so slow.
Launchers do not rely on speed to win.
For fast speed, you use Assassins and Ninjas.
Do you mean there is something wrong with my tactical arrangement?
Have you arranged tactics?
Sorry, I didn't see any cooperation.
I only saw everyone following you, recklessly running around.
That's because you can't keep pace with me.
What era is it now?
Launcher still moves behind as support?
I think you were too comfortable while Ye Qiu was the captain.
That's why you are not used to this new playing style.
Ye Qiu's tactics are just that he fights in front and finds good positions.
While you hide behind in a blind corner to attack.
Over and over again, just a few moves.
It's so boring. Even if you're used to it, I'm tired of seeing it.
Not bad. You answered the phone after three rings.
It seems that you've been living idly these days.
I don't have a choice.
Recently, friends have called me one after another
sneering at my miserable situation.
It's already a conditioned reflex once I hear my phone ring.
Liar.
Your phone has always been on silent.
You never answer a call from anyone.
To look for you, one has to be in front of you and shout in your face.
Then quickly appear to yell at me.
You're not in front of me.
Aren't I?
Why aren't your room's curtains fixed yet?
Are you in my room?
I just wanted to see if you changed your room's password.
Hey, do you still remember your room's password?
First, don't scold anyone at the strategy debrief meeting tomorrow.
Second, if you want to scold someone, don't scold me.
Third, even if you want to scold me,
no more than three sentences.
What about the fourth?
First, at the training meeting, don't get angry at the new teammates.
Second, even if you get angry, don't sulk.
Just scold them if you need to.
Third, if you sulk, don't go past three minutes.
Fourth.
When angry and sad, rush across the street from Excellent Era and shout.
Shout what?
Shout...
one, two, three, four.
From now on, don't miss my call.
"One, two, three, four
This string of simple numbers is all the tacit understanding between us.
But I still want to stand in front of you
to press these four numbers for you.
My idol.
Boss, I'll come back to you later.
It will be Excellent Era's year-end press conference soon.
Should we organize an activity to support Ye Qiu?
The time has come to support our idol.
I'll pay all the expenses. Come on.
Seems like I need to show you something big to interest you all.
Possibility in impossibility
is the best interpretation of our idol, Ye Qiu's competitive spirit.
His unique skill, Dragon Raising Its Head,
is also a legend in the history of Glory.
First, use the strongest Battlemage blade-level move,
Rising Dragon Soars the Sky.
Then use his invincible hand speed and micro-operations
to forcibly change the trajectory of Rising Dragon Soars the Sky,
making it impossible for the opponent to evade the attack at all.
He has proven with his strength that
there is no strongest, only stronger.
Such an excellent video still can't attract you all.
What are you all doing?
Boss, what's wrong out there? So noisy outside.
- I lost the game because of it.
- Sorry, sorry.
I... I'll go out and have a look.
- Xiao Chu, I'll take a look.
- Hurry up then.
- Over there, over there. Tear it off. Lever it.
- Hey!
- Be careful. Quickly now.
- What are you doing? Do you know who he is?
Who cares? I just work for the money.
Stop looking. Hurry up and tear it off.
All right.
He is One Autumn Leaf, who uses Dragon Raising Its Head.
♫  Your old coat is like a sturdy umbrella  ♫
♫  That protects me from the harshness of the weather  ♫
♫  You are like my exclusive detective  ♫
♫  Every movement and expression is seen by you  ♫
♫  In my heart is the most amazing you  ♫
♫  Some days time just slips away  ♫
♫  Other days it seems to stand still  ♫
♫  In my heart is the dearest you  ♫
♫  My constant, unwavering support  ♫
♫  And also my unbreakable vow  ♫
♫  I'm always thinking of you  ♫
- We won!
- Nice!
My father is a fan of Ye Qiu.
Such a virtual role
let this group of people of different ages and occupations,
and adults who don't even know each other
become a group of loyal and passionate youngsters.
Father running this internet cafe
is more like managing his dream for Glory.
He told me that in one's life, there will be many impossible moments.
We must learn to live in these desperate situations
and constantly break through oneself
to look for unlimited possibilities for growth.
After Father died, I refused to sell the internet cafe.
I firmly believe that I understand the meaning of One Autumn Leaf.
I can become the real boss of Happy Internet Cafe
and make Father proud.
But today,
you left,
and was replaced.
My spiritual worship was destroyed.
♫  And also my unbreakable vow  ♫
♫  In my heart is the most amazing you  ♫
♫  Transform every mundane moment  ♫
♫  Into captivating experiences  ♫
♫  In my heart is the dearest you  ♫
Dad, you helped me choose Launcher as my profession.
You said no matter how far my target is,
as long as I focus my aim and never give up,
I'll hit my target.
I will not give up,
whether it's the internet cafe
or One Autumn Leaf.
Xiao Tang.
Xiao Tang, did you study strategies all night?
"No One Autumn Leaf"?
Guo Guo, can I help you?
This persistent spirit of yours reflect those in eSports.
I stayed up all night. But the effect is not significant.
Actually, Ye Qiu's play style is not something newbies like us can master.
He is an expert at creating miracles from the impossible.
It is called having brilliant tactics.
We can only grasp an understanding, but not master it.
You know so much about him.
The network manager told me this.
What you're saying sounds like a lie.
A confident truth is the truth.
Where does your confidence come from?
My confidence?
From the network manager.
Network Manager, come here.
Boss, wait a minute.
Xiao Tang, let me tell you something.
My Network manager imitates Ye Qiu just like Ye Qiu himself.
Not to mention you.
I won't compete with your network manager.
After all, his name is like Ye Qiu, so he wins.
Just by looking at the strategy, it doesn't work at all.
You need actual combat training.
You practice with him first.
Thank you.
Your network manager has already played with me.
He is handsome and speaks clearly.
He is also polite. You can let him stay.
I'm not talking about that kind of training.
If you don't want to practice, it's okay. Actually...
Actually what?
Is this a question of training?
It is... Come here. It's a question of homework for me or my control over her.
If she focuses on training,
she won't have time to ask about your homework.
This is a clever redirecting tactic.
You flatter me.
Everything is now ready except for one last piece.
Do you know who that is?
It's you.
I can't.
She is in fields beyond my knowledge.
I really don't understand her temper and thoughts.
She's too far out of my reach.
Come. Sit down.
Sit properly.
First, add friends to establish contact.
What are you waiting for?
Fine.
You little brat.
See? I was rejected mercilessly.
Wait a minute.
Refusal is a woman's natural privilege.
Being reserved is a woman's innate trait.
As a man, do you know what trait you should have?
Shameless determination. Keep adding her.
As a man, I have my own dignity.
What?
When the girl is interested, shameless persistence is called determination.
But if she is not, that shameless persistence
is called being tactless.
Really? Why do I feel like
you forget who the boss is and who the network manager here is?
Why don't we calculate your debt?
Or you can take another look
at who the boss here is?
I know, I know you are the boss.
How about your dignity?
You brat, add her.
Adding her is like going through an iron wall.
Did you watch the match yesterday?
Yes, I did.
- It was amazing.
- Very good.
The players have all arrived. They are waiting for your decision.
Blood Gunner Yagg, are you sure of that?
We got the news from our spy in the Herb Garden Guild.
The map was refreshed just a minute ago.
Herb Garden's Plantago Seed and the others have already rushed over there.
Tyrannical Ambition Guild will soon arrive, too.
Okay, hurry up.
Hurry and log on.
- Okay, let's go.
- Quickly log on.
You log on first. I'll be back soon.
Where are you going?
All of you, focus.
Captain Jiexi is watching you all here.
Herb Garden must kill the boss this time.
Captain Jiexi cannot be humiliated. Do you understand?
Understood!
Everybody, listen up.
Although we won the first kill last time, it took half an hour.
This kind of mistake is absolutely not allowed this time.
Yes, Guild Master!
What is your goal?
High level, high efficiency, and high concentration!
Good. This is your moment to show your capabilities.
Blood Gunner Yagg will be ours!
Get ready, everyone.
Victory is just ahead.
Tyrannical Ambition Guild has arrived.
Its leader is the shameless man called Cold Night.
Herb Garden Guild has also arrived.
Plantago Seed arrived long ago with his group.
But the two guilds haven't launched attacks yet.
This Blood Gunner is too powerful.
Whichever guild attacks first will be the first to lose.
Let's see what their plans are.
You got here really fast.
Not as fast as you who can fly.
Who will attack first?
You, you do it first.
You first, and we Tyrannical Ambition will follow.
We can attack first, but don't try to steal if you dare.
Exactly. I don't want to die for Tyrannical Ambition.
You're one to talk.
As a man dumped by Lord Grim, it's shameful for you to even be here.
Shame on you. Did you plant a spy in my guild again?
Old Blue, you were dumped? So miserable.
I really want to see how green* your face is right now.
(*Embarrassment)
Not greener than your Herb Garden's faces.
All right, cut the crap.
Soon, the more guilds come, the less chance we have.
Why don't we do this together?
How about it?
- Fine.
Three.
Two.
One.
Why aren't you going?
We are preparing. Why didn't you go?
We are also preparing for it.
Who is attacking the monster there?
Facing Blood Gunner's shooting from all directions, and he's not hurt at all.
Damn, he's impressive.
So cool.
Steamed Bun Invasion? Where did such an expert come from?
Nice knee attack.
He counterattacks while being attacked.
His game sense is not bad.
Here comes another expert.
Flexible mechanics and spot-on attacks.
He moves like a dancer.
Doesn't Sand Toss cause a blind effect only when it hits the eyes?
Why is he aiming at its head?
His game sense is equal to nothing.
That's impressive.
I have never seen such a cool method of suicide before.
I thought it was a big meat bun,
it turns out to be a small white steamed bun without stuffing.
Turns out he is a super newbie. A Glory noob.
Why don't you two go up and help.
All right, let's go. I'll cover for you two.
Old Night, I know what you're thinking.
Too obvious.
Old Plantago and I will not fight with each other and let you win easily.
There's not much HP left. That Bun won't make it.
Are we really just standing here?
- Wait.
- Again?
An expert has his own strategy.
You log on first. I'll be back soon. Go.
Where are you going?
Brother Expert, we are planning to attack Blood Gunner.
Are you interested?
Yes.
Are the conditions the same?
Send me the coordinates.
Brother Expert, you are here!
We are all ready.
Let's fight together later.
We Blue Brook Guild are under your command.
All the rare materials are yours.
Old Blue, you're not playing fair by asking for external aid again.
Killing Blood Gunner is a task for those who are capable.
I have the ability to find external aid. How am I not playing fair?
Right. Kill the Boss with your own skills.
What?
Brother Expert, why did you form a team with others?
Old Blue, you were dumped again.
My condolences.
What do you know? This is a strategy.
You bring in an expert to form a wild team. Impressive!
Ten o'clock position. Use Sand Toss at the Gunner's eyes.
Quick moves or the right movies... I suggest you choose the latter.
Don't stop attacking. Move to the 6 o'clock position.
Use Brick Buster.
Don't throw it.
Directly hit the back of his head to double the damage.
Uppercut.
Bun, slow down your attacks.
We have to control the rhythm.
Why?
Wait for the fishermen.
Damn, tacit and accurate teamwork.
The newbie is totally different now.
Was he... pretending earlier?
Old Blue, say something.
What kind of strategy is this? I can't understand it.
Guild Master, what is Lord Grim's plan?
Blood Gunner is on the verge of being killed.
Lord Grim is decreasing their output.
They're not going to make it.
It's the perfect time to attack now. You cowards.
It's just fighting head-on. Nothing to be afraid of.
Tyrannical Ambition, follow me.
Herb Garden is following after Tyrannical Ambition.
Guild Master.
Forget it, let's go!
Copy.
They took the bait. Bun, full output.
Okay.
Uppercut.
Bun, at the one o'clock direction, hide behind the large stone. Stay safe.
Lord Grim and Bun ran away.
It seems that they have reached the limit of attack.
You guys attacked too early. The first to attack dies first.
That's right.
Want to run?
- Blood Gunner is going berserk!
- Oh no!
G-Going berserk?
- Be careful.
- Withdraw, withdraw, withdraw.
Hurry up and run!
Too late.
I lost? As a Guild Master, how could I lose in a jungle area?
Lord Grim, you jerk.
Lord Grim.
Don't let me meet you in Glory in the future.
What should we do in case we meet him?
Of course, we will solicit him.
Start our output performance.
Congratulations to Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion
for the first kill on Blood Gunner Yagg.
This is my first kill.
Expert, you are awesome.
You played well, too.
Yes, I also think I played well.
Expert, call me to fight next time.
Sure, no problem.
My name is Bao Rongxing, a warehouse keeper.
My friends always call me Bao Zi (Bun).
In addition to enjoying the satisfaction my work gives me,
my hobby during my free time is playing Glory.
I didn't expect to gain an expert's recognition today.
My dream is to join a professional team,
play in a real match,
and become a real professional esports player.
The guild master lost the match just now.
What? Impossible.
I heard that there was an expert.
Expert, you didn't help me.
You said it yourself, the boss belongs to the capable player.
You humiliated Tyrannical Ambition and Herb Garden.
I bet they'll blacklist you to get revenge.
Really? I just talked with them
and have agreed to dungeon together next time.
Those two have no bottom lines and even invited you to dungeon together?
Don't you also want to?
I do.
Which one?
The Boneyard.
Prepare the items.
I'll let you know when I have time.
The expert is still on our side.
Items dropped from dungeons
have a limited effect in upgrading the weapon attributes.
But using rare items to upgrade weapons can max out their stats.
So the best weapons must use rare items.
The rarity of items does not lie in their drop rate
but in the spawn rate of the hidden boss.
That is the meaning of "rare".
You won again?
Just a little luck.
It is clear that you are powerful.
One must keep it low-key when modesty calls for it.
When it's time to be flashy, one must show off.
I... I really don't have a strategy.
You are really experienced.
Adding her as a friend failed, and the files were rejected.
What can I do? I am also very helpless.
If you failed to add her as a friend,
you can teach her using words and actions.
If she refuses your files, you can change your strategy.
There's nothing I can do either.
I am also very irritable.
"Irritable" can't solve the problem either.
Are you sure you can't finish the task?
I...
can definitely finish the task
under your guidance, Boss.
The deadline is 24 hours.
When the time runs out, you either succeed
or you die trying.
Subtitles and Timing provided to you byðŸ’¥ðŸ¥ TEAM 7ï¸âƒ£ ðŸ¥ðŸ’¥ @viki.com
"Glory Battlefield" - R1SE
♫  The road to the top is long and bumpy  ♫
♫  But with you, I have limitless strength  ♫
♫  Failure is like the dawn of victory  ♫
♫  So what if we start over again  ♫
♫  Youth is the time for unstoppable progress  ♫
♫  Accompanied by confidence and strength  ♫
♫  Even if beaten to flee with wounds and bruises  ♫
♫  Desperation always gives rise to hope  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We must give it our all to win the battle  ♫
♫  We laugh and cry, secretly grieving over failures  ♫
♫  Supporting one another as we change and grow  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We must fight for our dreams and win in style  ♫
♫  With victory, we hug and cheer with joy  ♫
♫  Passing countless shining moments  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We must give it our all to win the battle  ♫
♫  We laugh and cry, secretly grieving over failures  ♫
♫  Supporting one another as we change and grow  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We must fight for our dreams and win in style  ♫
♫  With victory, we hug and cheer with joy  ♫
♫  Passing countless shining moments  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We've spent countless shining moments together  ♫