"Light From the Ashes" - Cai Weize
♫  Countless fireflies born from insignificance  ♫
♫  Riding the long wind to gather into a shining galaxy  ♫
♫  Proclaim to the world on top of the sky  ♫
♫  We will return in glory  ♫
♫  Clear the clouds and descend with the heat  ♫
♫  Melting ice and snow, overcoming twists and turns  ♫
♫  Finally at this moment of peak  ♫
♫  There is a figure that coincides with the past  ♫
♫  The glory of the past that never came  ♫
♫  The pride that the future will never pass  ♫
♫  Our fingertips intertwined and condensed  ♫
♫  Into a song that ignited the battlefield  ♫
♫  The only light in an endless night  ♫
♫  Is you and me who overcame mediocrity  ♫
♫  Up on the clouds and down in the dust  ♫
♫  Fireflies making every effort to illuminate  ♫
♫  I came from the legend to carry on a legend  ♫
♫  Once it's disruptive, a decade of persistence won't be in vain  ♫
♫  Up on the clouds and down in the dust  ♫
♫  Fireflies making every effort to illuminate  ♫
What are you looking for?
If I can't prevent others from coming in, I need to make changes inside.
Tell me. How many locks should I put on the attic?
What? Locks?
Or I could demolish the stairs to the attic.
After all, he stays indoors.
There shouldn't be any problem if he stays up there for over 10 days.
Wait, Guo Guo.
What you are saying is so weird.
I will give him a computer.
After all, as long as he has Glory in his world, he'll be fine.
As long as he doesn't expose himself, the journalists won't know.
Perfect.
How is it perfect?
Even if journalists won't come, the police will.
Nothing will work. What should I do?
I'm running out of options.
Guo Guo, it's quite simple if you really want to keep him here.
Then what should I do?
Should I break his legs?
That's not impossible.
- As long as he has his hands.
- Of course not!
What nonsense are you thinking about right now?
I mean, if you want to keep someone from leaving,
win his heart first.
How?
Two words.
Spoil him.
Spoil him?
That's strange.
Why hasn't anybody called me?
Even though this plan is a little old-fashioned,
he is a man after all.
It should work.
Xiao Chu, he's coming.
Brother Ye.
You're up.
Why aren't you using the vacuum cleaner?
My boss said the vacuum cleaner is too noisy.
It might disturb you.
Oh, by the way,
your breakfast is ready.
Eat it while it is warm. It won't taste good if it gets cold.
- What's going on?
- This way. This way.
Over here. Here.
Da-da-da-da.
From this one to that one, they were all prepared for you.
- What's this?
- Explain it to him.
There are ten kinds of nutritious porridge.
Including Eight-Ingredient Porridge,
porridge with white fungus and lotus seeds,
and porridge with red beans and corn.
They were all prepared by the boss.
Of course.
- What should I do now?
- There is also salty porridge.
Well, Brother Ye, you don't like sweet porridge, do you?
There is also salty porridge here, like porridge with corn and spareribs.
- And there's shrimp meat...
- Stop. That's enough.
I understand what you're thinking.
Really?
She wants to use these carbohydrates so I'll die from overeating.
That way, she can inherit my Glory equipment, right? I see.
- I won't be fooled.
- No.
The package!
Brother Ye, your package...
Your package arrived.
What else?
Hello. Here's your package.
It's so hard to please him.
- What's this?
- This is...
This is a coffee maker that the boss bought for you.
In the morning, it can grind coffee beans for you.
At night, it can make cold brew coffee.
Whatever flavor you like.
Please sign here.
Suning delivers parcels so fast.
She thinks I don't stay up late enough.
She wants me to work overtime every day.
Sir, if you don't like it, it's refundable within 30 days.
- Really?
- No.
Go, go.
- Boss.
- Wow, so many porridges.
What a pity that they weren't prepared for me.
If they were prepared for me, I would have to thank that person kindly.
Why are you looking at me?
I love drinking juice.
But no one buys me a juicer.
You should appreciate what you get.
Is there something wrong with this computer?
This...
Where are you going?
Don't. Let me do it.
You're such an idiot...
Why bother doing such menial work?
I'll do it. I'll do it.
Boss, what's wrong with you today?
Don't you think I am
kinder to you today than before?
No.
Fine. Fine.
Fine.
Starting today,
you don't have to manage the internet cafe.
You can play Glory whenever you want. I will still pay you.
How about that?
I think it's a trap.
It's not a trap.
It's just my sincerity.
Why don't I make some coffee for you?
Here.
Be careful. It's hot.
I don't want a blend of Robusta.
I want freshly roasted Arabica beans.
Or at least,
those beans from Liberia.
Do you have that?
I'll go ask Xiao Chu to buy them.
So you don't have it?
How about drinking some tea?
I have red tea, green tea, white tea...
Whatever tea you want.
Which one do you want.
Flower tea.
I will go ask Xiao Chu to buy that, too.
Never mind.
No coffee. No tea.
Then give me a fruit tray.
Okay.
Here you are.
Boss, are you kidding me?
What's wrong?
Do you know how to peel an apple?
Didn't I peel it?
You try it.
You call this peeling apples?
I need something artistic.
This is too ugly. I won't eat it.
Artistic?
It's ready.
You are quite deft.
This rabbit is delicate.
Right? I am telling you... It's quite difficult to carve a rabbit.
Look at its ears. They will break if you are not careful enough.
It doesn't taste well. I won't eat it.
You are such a bra...
Brat.
Say that again.
Brat! Don't think that I'm being kind to you so you can push me around.
Boss, keep it up.
Just speak your mind and be your true self.
Otherwise, I have to put on an act for you every day.
It's exhausting.
Put on an act?
Yes. If you have to be a fan,
then I have to suffer and act like an idol.
I regard you as my idol, but you treat me like a monkey?
Fine. You want to treat me like a monkey?
- Don't you?
- Boss...
I just told you to speak your mind. Not beat me whenever you want.
I'm beating you now. So what? I...
You are so fierce. Are you afraid I will leave?
Fine.
Don't come back if you leave.
I wouldn't dare leave.
Hello.
It's me. Why don't we meet?
For so many years,
I was always a novice in Glory.
When I first met Su Muqiu and Ye Qiu, they were the experts in Glory.
As for me, I was just a loser,
who couldn't do anything well.
The jungle. The boss appeared in the jungle.
Position 234, 665. Come here right now.
I'm coming.
Manager, check out.
Your timing doesn't seem right. The time went too fast.
So the timing has been tampered with.
Give me the account book.
Boss, what's this for?
It's for timing. A good thing.
It's to steal the online time of our customers.
What a shame. You study business.
But you don't know what profit maximization is, do you?
But you can't have a conscience and make dirty money.
The most important quality for a great businessman is honesty.
What a businessman needs isn't character but brains.
If you want to make money, stop talking about morality.
"If you want to make money, stop talking about morality."
At that moment, what I hated most were those words.
What's wrong?
I'm going to meet an old friend.
I believe the competitive spirit we advocate
will definitely change some people's understanding
of this field in this future.
Next, we will give vigorous support to qualified people in this field.
We will form esports teams as soon as possible.
Sportsmanship, esports teams.
These two strange and familiar phrases thrilled Muqiu and I.
We wanted to hold the first Glory League competition,
inviting those trans-regional masters to compete together.
And change Glory into a real competitive sport.
Tao Xuan was fired, undoubtedly because he opposed a dishonest businessman.
And then he joined us.
Our poor 3-man trio only had broken screens and old computer hosts.
But we expected to do great things.
Xiao Ye, you are the commander-in-chief of the entire strategy.
As well as our commando team.
You are in charge of arranging the competition schedule.
The whole level of this competition depends on you.
Invite the players here, and defeat them one by one. Easy.
♫  Aim higher and rise above mediocrity  ♫
♫  Push past the limits and conquer the peak  ♫
With our competitive spirit, in our professional careers,
we spent our poorest but most satisfying period of time.
♫  Remaining steadfast on the pinnacle of greatness  ♫
♫  That's when I grasped who I was in the past  ♫
♫  Always trying to be my own hero  ♫
♫  Now, I have seen the legend  ♫
Wei Chen and Han Wenqing, the strongest players in the second server,
came to join the competition.
Our old self-built computer finally had to face
- the challenges from the masters.
- Let me do it.
Hello. Hello. Please come in.
Ready?
Begin!
Go around.
The strongest player in the second server is definitely worthy of his name.
Let's decide the winner through one move. How about that?
That's exactly what I want.
What's happened?
Why can't I move?
Wait. Give me a minute. I'll handle it.
You didn't seize the chance to kill me?
This is a competition; it's not a PK fight in the jungle.
Okay. It's fixed.
There will surely be no more...
An unfinished competition.
A broken screen.
They make up the memories of our youth.
Ye Qiu, come and have a seat.
It's been a long time since I played Glory.
Speak your mind.
Come back. Come back to Excellent Era.
Be a coach.
In fact, the position of coach has always been left open for you.
I never considered giving up on you.
I have no interest in standing outside the arena.
I prefer to stand in the arena.
Being a coach is only temporary.
As long as you retire for one year, you can come back immediately.
I've already come back.
In fact, we are all very clear that...
the Pro-League nowadays is quite different from that in the past.
Yes. I admit that tactics and coordination are very important.
However, as for your high-end play... most of the audience
doesn't even understand them.
What do they want to see?
They want to see that one person can fight against many players,
or save the desperate situation on his own.
This is what they want to see and hope to see.
I go to play games, not just to please the audience.
Your Dragon Raising its Head.
You said it was just for fun.
But all the fans regarded it as your personal representative skill.
Its practical value is limited.
Does it matter? It doesn't matter.
What matters is that it is irreplaceable.
Only you can use it.
Using Dragon Raising its Head is necessary.
It's not for putting on a dazzling display.
But you were very successful in showing it this time.
When you used Dragon Raising its Head in the All-Star game,
it roused the crowd immediately.
I don't believe you have never realized that.
Why not seize the chance and ascend directly to the throne?
You are right.
But that's not what I want.
Then what do you want?
Winning.
Do you think you can now
win back the glory that belongs to you?
I'll give it a try.
I... only focus on the future, and I'm never stuck in the past.
As for those stumbling blocks to the future of Excellent Era,
I will throw them away without hesitation.
But...
in this regard,
we are the same.
Recently, I have kept wondering...
If Muqiu were still here,
would we have been brought to this point?
Xiao Ye,
from now on, you are the core of our team.
The allocation of personnel is all to support you.
You can also decide the tactics.
I don't worry about your abilities.
You will definitely become number 1 in Glory.
Muqiu.
Here.
You are also part of our team.
After all, you are the only one who cooperates well with Ye Qiu.
But apart from the competitions,
you have to offer some technical support.
Issues like the design of the equipment are all up to you.
They should pose no problem for a genius like you.
Brother Tao, you are flattering me.
As for me, from now on, I'll handle the odds and ends.
Leave the logistical support to me.
I believe we will definitely become the number 1 team in Glory.
Here.
Here we go.
With Glory in your heart, you are invincible.
Waiter!
Throw these away!
All... Throw all of them away?
Including the computer?
It has been broken for a long time, anyway.
What's the use of keeping it?
Wait.
Indeed it has been broken for a long time.
Look! This is my design.
Unspecialized has always existed in Glory.
But due to the cool-down period from changing weapons and the high load,
there are many flaws in the continuity when attacking.
We can't connect the low-level skills
with different professions perfectly.
But look.
If there was a weapon like this,
it could change its form at any time.
What do you think of it?
Then it could use all the professional skills continually?
That's right.
I am designing a weapon like this right now.
I call it the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella.
Great!
So you have already thought this through.
And you've even been hiding it from me.
I haven't finished it yet.
There are still two forms left.
These two forms can't switch between each other at random.
But when I finish the design
and figure out the last two skills,
get ready to sweep away the other players
and surprise all of Glory.
Yes!
Xiao Ye.
I heard that Muqiu and you are designing a weapon for the Unspecialized.
Yes. With this weapon, I can be a true Unspecialized.
Wait, no. It should be called The King's Avatar.
However, if you don't change your profession,
you can only use the skills of the first twenty levels.
How can you play that way?
I can.
Brother Tao, look.
Even if I can only use the weaker skills from the first twenty levels,
it can still produce amazing transformations as long as there are enough skills.
The potential of the Unspecialized
is no worse than that of all twenty-four professions.
It could be even better.
Fine. Forget about the skills issue for now,
what about the league?
What if the Unspecialized is not allowed to be in the league?
What if the level of Glory raises its limits?
What if it raises its levels to the ninetieth level, to the hundredth level,
do you think playing Unspecialized still has value?
Brother Tao, in fact, you have been determined not to allow me to be an Unspecialized.
Risk. Risk. Risk.
It's about risk.
I can't ignore the danger of it just for your fun and games.
I have always agreed to your requirement
of staying low key and not accepting any endorsements.
Are you going to continue being so headstrong at this point?
Brother Tao, please trust me.
I believe Muqiu and I can resolve all of these problems.
Think it over carefully.
Persuade Ye Qiu.
I think this time we had better listen to Brother Tao.
Why?
My trial failed.
I sealed away the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella.
Are you kidding me? This is not a joke.
Look at what you designed before.
Look at the cannon. So gorgeous.
And the weapons in the rear.
Right? And this one.
This...
Actually, the Unspecialized is not a conventional profession.
Its style isn't very stable.
Even if we use it very well,
after Excellent Era recruits new members,
they won't be able to handle such flexible playing styles like we can.
That is indeed a problem for team play.
In fact, this isn't that important.
Most importantly, one day,
we can rise to the top of Glory together instead of depending on the weapons.
Therefore, whether we use the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella or not,
whether I fool you or not, it's not important.
Isn't that right?
How about this?
Let's make a bet.
First, we make Excellent Era into the best team.
Then the best member at that time
will have the right to revive the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella..
What do you think? Do you dare make that bet with me?
Here. This is a weapon I made especially for you.
I call this weapon Evil Annihilation.
What do you think? Do you like it?
Since the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella can't be completed,
let evil annihilation accompany you and rise to the top of Glory.
Su Muqiu,
you did indeed lie to me.
This is my secret.
Xiao Ye, when you find it,
Excellent Era and you must have reached the top of Glory.
My retirement led to many assumptions by the media and fans.
I hereby certify that...
my retirement had nothing to do with other people.
It was my personal decision.
With Glory in your heart, you are invincible.
Ye Qiu.
Tell them there's no need for PR at this point.
Okay.
The dungeon of the Heavenly Domain Challenge is a sky-high tower.
Normally, after the player kills all the monsters,
the tower gate will open
and send the player to Heavenly Domain.
But the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella can't do that.
Because the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella still needs to pass one last step.
It will be perfected after the player passes the dungeon of the Heavenly Domain.
Before that, the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella cannot be attacked
by any frost monsters in the dungeon.
Otherwise, the umbrella will be torn apart.
So, if you want to pass the dungeon of the Heavenly Domain,
with the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella,
you can only climb from outside the tower.
Transforming the form of the umbrella into a long sword,
you can use the skills of Blademaster, Spellblade, and Berserker.
Transforming the form of the umbrella into a rotor,
you can use the skill of Mechanic.
I hope one day,
the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella can reach the summit of Glory.
You have so much free time? Waiting for me here?
I am very busy, okay?
Watch this.
You are here to accompany your captain and try out the weapon, right?
I'm here to accompany Shaotian.
Subtitles and Timing provided to you byðŸ’¥ðŸ¥ TEAM 7ï¸âƒ£ ðŸ¥ðŸ’¥ @viki.com
"Glory Battlefield" - R1SE
♫  The road to the top is long and bumpy  ♫
♫  But with you, I have limitless strength  ♫
♫  Failure is like the dawn of victory  ♫
♫  So what if we start over again  ♫
♫  Youth is the time for unstoppable progress  ♫
♫  Accompanied by confidence and strength  ♫
♫  Even if beaten to flee with wounds and bruises  ♫
♫  Desperation always gives rise to hope  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We must give it our all to win the battle  ♫
♫  We laugh and cry, secretly grieving over failures  ♫
♫  Supporting one another as we change and grow  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We must fight for our dreams and win in style  ♫
♫  With victory, we hug and cheer with joy  ♫
♫  Passing countless shining moments  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We must give it our all to win the battle  ♫
♫  We laugh and cry, secretly grieving over failures  ♫
♫  Supporting one another as we change and grow  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We must fight for our dreams and win in style  ♫
♫  With victory, we hug and cheer with joy  ♫
♫  Passing countless shining moments  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We've spent countless shining moments together  ♫