"Light From the Ashes" - Cai Weize
♫  Countless fireflies born from insignificance  ♫
♫  Riding the long wind to gather into a shining galaxy  ♫
♫  Proclaim to the world on top of the sky  ♫
♫  We will return in glory  ♫
♫  Clear the clouds and descend with the heat  ♫
♫  Melting ice and snow, overcoming twists and turns  ♫
♫  Finally at this moment of peak  ♫
♫  There is a figure that coincides with the past  ♫
♫  The glory of the past that never came  ♫
♫  The pride that the future will never pass  ♫
♫  Our fingertips intertwined and condensed  ♫
♫  Into a song that ignited the battlefield  ♫
♫  The only light in an endless night  ♫
♫  Is you and me who overcame mediocrity  ♫
♫  Up on the clouds and down in the dust  ♫
♫  Fireflies making every effort to illuminate  ♫
♫  I came from the legend to carry on a legend  ♫
♫  Once it's disruptive, a decade of persistence won't be in vain  ♫
♫  Up on the clouds and down in the dust  ♫
♫  Fireflies making every effort to illuminate  ♫
Do I need to continue asking?
Captain, it's like this... He started it.
He asked me to attack the Dungeon with him...
I said no.
Then he threatened and tempted me...
Then he said he wanted to finish something that wasn't yet complete;
revive some sort of umbrella.
And he said he would add some excitement to Glory...
- I told him not to do it...
- Wait a minute.
He really said that?
His words were like this.
"I will add more excitement to Glory."
That's what he said. He was serious.
I'd be Sun Xiang if I'm lying... I'm telling the truth.
Sorry, Old Ye.
You had time to attack Dungeons after the competition.
It seems that you don't get enough training.
Captain, didn't you just say we'd turn over a new leaf?
- You'll keep your promise, right?
- No.
- Unless...
- Unless what?
Get me the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella.
Isn't that stealing...
Captain, isn't that a bit shameless?
Look. Blue Rain has always been aboveboard.
- Is it...
- How can this be shameless?
We'll just borrow it for research purposes.
We will return it when it's done.
By the way, you may not be able to beat him.
Captain, you should be responsible for what you say.
I can't beat him?
Listen to me. With my current abilities,
I could beat his umbrella into a stick in minutes.
Good. Three hours. I'll wait for you.
Only three hours?
Subtitles and Timing provided to you byðŸ’¥ðŸ¥ TEAM 7ï¸âƒ£ ðŸ¥ðŸ’¥ @viki.com
When will you finish that training camp competition with me,
Ye Qiu. Master.
- Quickly, quickly, quickly.
- Go, go, go.
- Nice! Don't rush it.
- Watch me succeed.
You're not good. Why are you so slow?
- You don't have many skills left. Come on.
- Use your ult. Hurry!
- Nice!
- Go, we've got a chance.
- Not bad!
- That was easy.
How many matches have you won successively?
You see, Yu Wenshou is weak.
He's too slow. How can he compare with you?
Be quiet.
I'd like to announce one thing to you all.
Our training camp will officially start the evaluations tomorrow.
Last place in the evaluation will be eliminated.
Is everyone clear?
- Don't go.
- Don't leave.
Yu Wenzhou, you are the only student I've ever seen
who has never won in the regular matches.
If you lose again this time, you would be eliminated.
If you want to stay in esports,
then you have to work hard.
Got it.
All right, everyone.
Line up and draw lots to choose your opponent.
- You first. Quickly.
- I'm heading back first.
You first.
- Don't be shy.
- Draw one.
- You'll just lose anyway.
- Just draw a lot.
- Seriously? You're slow even when drawing lots?
Come on. Quickly.
- Take a look.
- Who is it? Open it.
- Quickly.
- Come on, who is it?
Who is it?
- Don't hide it.
- Right.
Goodness! It's Ye Qiu.
Ye Qiu?
You won the first prize.
You've never won, and he has never lost.
-  We even don't need to guess.
- Yeah.
Good luck.
It's okay.
My classmates' mockery
made me felt utterly worthless.
So I started intensely practicing all night without rest.
Warlock versus Battlemage.
It'll be a very tough match.
The only turning point is whether I can release Cursed Arrow or not.
But it'll take ten seconds to cast a spell to get the maximum charge.
It is impossible for me not to be interrupted.
♫  Failure is like the dawn of victory  ♫
♫  So what if we start over again  ♫
The only possible way
is to completely control him for ten seconds.
♫  Accompanied by confidence and strength  ♫
♫  Even if beaten to flee with wounds and bruises  ♫
I can only stall him for five seconds.
The casting would still be interrupted.
I must find a way to stall for another five seconds.
♫  We must give it our all to win the battle  ♫
♫  We laugh and cry, secretly grieving over failures  ♫
♫  Supporting one another as we change and grow  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We must fight for our dreams and win in style  ♫
♫  With victory, we hug and cheer with joy  ♫
♫  Passing countless shining moments  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We must give it our all to win the battle  ♫
♫  We laugh and cry, secretly grieving over failures  ♫
♫  Supporting one another as we change and grow  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We must fight for our dreams and win in style  ♫
♫  With victory, we hug and cheer with joy  ♫
♫  Passing countless shining moments  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We've spent countless shining moments together  ♫
He's doomed.
- There's no suspense.
- There's no way he can win.
There is no suspense.
- They're starting
- It's starting.
Dragon Tooth Sprint. Master Ye is starting off so fiercely.
- No mercy at all.
- Sprint at the beginning?
Look up into the sky.
Master Ye Qiu.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One!
(*Good game)
Two minutes and eighteen seconds.
It became the driving force for me to work harder.
Ye Qiu also became
the opponent that I wanted to meet the most in a match.
It's done.
Captain, please wait a minute.
- What's this?
- Myriad Manifestation Umbrella.
Captain, let me report. I strictly followed your instructions.
I successfully and quickly got it. Mission completed.
Hey, why does Team Blue Rain steal things in such a high-key fashion?
It's outright robbery.
Long time no see.
You two heartless...
...heartfeltly good friends rarely get to meet.
Why don't you have a friendly chat to improve your friendship?
I'll take this with me and go now. Bye.
Are you very interested in my Myriad Manifestation Umbrella?
I'd like to see the power of the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella and the Unspecialized class.
I owe you that. Two minutes and eighteen seconds.
I owe that to myself.
Two minutes and eighteen seconds.
You hide yourself to prevent interruption.
- Very skilled.
- You flatter me.
It's a divine equipment indeed.
It seems that your casting speed has also improved.
But that's as far as it goes.
Oh? You've got another move.
Did you give it your all this time?
I give it my all in every match.
Myriad Manifestation Umbrella paired with an Unspecialized.
Maybe it can really change the League's structure.
It's just...
Maybe you can rely on the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella
and Unspecialized's various skills to make a difference now.
But how are you going to pass Heavenly Domain's challenge?
I'm not like you.
Thinking too much will kill too many brain cells.
If you have the time, I think you should first think about
how to prevent Huang Shaotian from running around.
Ye Qiu.
I hope that the next time I see you,
you can add some excitement to Glory.
We all suffer pains while we're growing.
In the world of Glory, we've learned to make peace with ourselves.
Okay, come on, let's smile.
Three, two, one.
Good. Okay, arms crossed over your chest.
Good. Three, two, one.
Good.
Let's look this way at a 45-degree angle. Over here.
Okay. Three, two, one.
No, still not good.
- His eyes are too obvious.
- Right. One is still big and the other is small.
All right. It's okay. I'll adjust them again.
- Make both eyes bigger.
- All right.
Let me try.
Hold onto it.
Look at a 45-degree angle.
- This works.
- This time, the picture is good.
- Good.
- His eyes now look the same.
- Captain.
- Go ahead. What is it?
Recently, a guy called Lord Grim appeared in the 10th Server.
All the guilds are not peaceful now.
I suspect that he's a professional player from another team
who is causing trouble for us.
This is the end of today's work.
Today's task is very arduous.
- Are you ready?
- I'm ready.
I'm ready.
Forty seven.
Forty eight.
How are you doing?
Fifty three.
It's so unfair.
You can fight a group, while I can only fight one-on-one.
Your attack speed is faster than mine.
The Boss we're fighting this time is Toya.
It's not too difficult to defeat him.
But the reason why he hasn't been defeated for so long
is because of the steps we take before we can fight the Boss.
They're closely linked.
They are not only trivial but also time-limited.
We can't make mistakes, Xiao Tang.
Mind your own business.
Xiao Tang and Brother Ye have been playing Glory for a long time.
It seems that they have pretty good teamwork.
But Sister Xiao Tang used to play with us.
Why does she only play with men now?
- Continue.
- Watch your position.
The two in front of you.
- Xiao Tang.
- Speed up.
Xiao Tang?
Guo Guo, wait a minute.
Xiao Tang, do a Sky Strike.
Okay.
Good.
- Xiao Tang.
- We need to try harder.
There's a new cake shop nearby.
I heard the cakes are delicious.
- Let's go there together.
- I'll go if I have time.
Watch your back.
What's the matter?
There are some questions that I don't know.
You're the only one who can solve them.
Can you teach me?
Of course. Why don't you write them down first?
I'll solve them for you later.
Let's continue.
You play every day.
Did I hire you to play Glory?
You'd better get to work now.
From now on, you just practice with Xiao Tang
and improve her skills. That'll be your job.
Hey, go left.
You brat, you're playing dirty.
Delete.
- Don't. It's my phone.
- What are you doing?
What? Who asked you to record it?
Guo Guo.
Xiao Tang.
Let's go and eat something, have fun,
and do something together.
It's my treat. Let's go.
All right, stop it. We are now doing the Dungeon.
Let's go later. Okay?
Back up.
Use your ult. Mind your HP.
Heal me.
Our training's intensity and difficulty are not quite suitable for you.
You should go back to the training camp.
After improving your skills,
you can come back again.
My name is Qiao Yifan.
I'm an Assassin in Team Tiny Herb.
I am a professional esports player
who always placed last in the assessments.
A pro esports player who has never been in a competition before.
Come on. Two, three.
Yingjie, come here and take photos with us.
Come on, come on.
Yingjie, Yifan went to the training school.
It probably will be very difficult for him to come back.
Leave this spot to us.
Get out of the way, all of you.
Let me take a nice-looking photo with the future captain.
Come on.
Let me knock you out with a brick.
Hey, that monster was clearly mine.
It belongs to whoever kills it.
Everyone, let's take a ten-minute break.
The next boss fight with Toya will be a tough one.
Didn't you just say it wasn't difficult?
This jungle boss is designed according to the standard of ten people.
Indeed it's not difficult.
But there are only three of us.
Crap.
Lord Grim is doing Toya's pre-task.
He's already in the last stage.
If everything goes smoothly, he'll achieve another first kill.
Is that so?
All the teammates,
gather in the training room in ten minutes.
It's an emergency training.
Your performance in this training
will be included in this month's evaluation.
If anyone's absent, their score will be zero for the month.
Wow! What kind of training is that? It's so extreme.
Absence means zero.
In this case, if I can perform well,
will I be in the starting line-up?
- Let's go.
- Let's go train. Let's go.
Let's go, Yingjie.
- Hello.
Yifan, wait.
- Yingjie.
- There's a new opportunity.
A new opportunity? What is it?
- Let's go.
- To where?
Hurry up.
- Sorry.
- Wait.
This is an activity led by the captain.
If you can perform well, then maybe you don't have to go to training camp.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Let's go.
- Captain.
Sit down.
- Take a seat.
- Yingjie, you go first.
I'll find you.
We'll start in five minutes.
I look forward to seeing your performances.
Go to Desolate Lands. We'll siege a guy called Lord Grim.
Thank you.
I have to find a computer in five minutes.
to make it in time for the assessment.
Stop.
What's wrong, Boss?
There's an ambush.
- Yingjie, you're the commander. Do it.
- Roger that.
Spread out and kill them one by one.
Liu Fei, lock in on their positions.
- Don't lose the targets.
- Okay.
- Yebo, be careful of Bao Zi. Don't underestimate him.
Xiao Yun, attack hard on Soft Mist.
- but watch your HP.
- Got it.
Take my brick.
Didn't you say you'd use Brick?
It's not bad that we died together.
You're good, Bao Zi. You got the first blood.
Quickly revive to help Xiao Tang.
- She's stuck in a fight.
- Got it.
No need.
Competing against me in APM?
I don't believe you can be faster than me.
Got yourself killed?
I told you to wait for Bao Zi.
Lord Grim kept it up for so long without falling behind.
I think it's almost impossible to defeat him head-on.
That's right, Boss Toya.
If they want to fight Toya,
they must pass through this cave.
The terrain here is complicated and is suitable for an ambush.
Shadow Clone.
Yingjie, watch your back.
Failure, is what I expected.
But I didn't expect you'd lose so fast.
Xiao Yun, rashness is your greatest enemy.
The match is never about who starts first wins.
Understood.
Liu Fei,
it's good to care about your teammates.
But whenever a teammate is in danger,
you'll lose your correct judgment of the whole situation.
This is the main problem you need to overcome at present.
Understood, Captain
Yebo.
Captain, I'll practice my low-level account well.
I'll find that Lord Grim again tonight and take revenge.
You think the reason why you failed today
is because you used low-level accounts?
I...
You all think like that, right?
You're all official members of a champion team.
Yet you have to siege an ordinary player in a dungeon.
It's not worth your efforts at all. Right?
Yingjie, what did you think of Lord Grim's skills?
He's very good.
How good is he?
He's very experienced. His attacks and skills are used effectively.
All his judgments are accurate.
He is better than all of us.
Yes, better than all of you.
He's great enough to kill all of you.
So, never underestimate any opponent.
Today is a good lesson for you all.
When you go back, take a good look at the video of the match.
I hope you'll learn something.
Who exactly is this Lord Grim?
What you've encountered today is the greatest Boss in the history of Glory.
Ye Qiu.
- Ye Qiu?
Look!
Interesting.
Hang in there, Yifan.
Ask him to stop.
I'll go and get him.
You've got ideas, but unfortunately, you didn't realize your problem.
And what's that?
- He's a grandmaster indeed.
- It's so hot.
- His play style is so cool.
- What are you doing?
It's today's training video.
Isn't it the part where Yingjie lost?
- Yeah.
- Yes, this is it.
It was a terrible loss, wasn't it?
Do you know what this is?
It's called Shadow Clone.
- Yebo.
- Let's watch it again.
Yebo.
Where is the captain?
I think he's gone.
Actually, it's nothing.
Captain's worried you'll be too embarrassed from losing.
After all, your opponent is the grandmaster, Ye Qiu.
- This is it.
- Ye Qiu?
Lord Grim is Grandmaster Ye Qiu?
- He's a grandmaster indeed.
- Right.
Yeah. When do you think I can be like him?
Just keep practicing.
There's no more water? Yifan.
If you've got nothing to do, can you get me some water?
Thank you.
Me too, Yifan.
- Look at you, Liu Fei.
- Look at you instead.
Look, you lost first.
Don't look at me. I didn't perform well today.
I'm not usually like this.
Actually, I think it would benefit Yifan to go to the Glory Bootcamp.
If he stays on our team,
he will always be the water boy. That's even worse.
Let's keep watching.
This loss is even worse.
Let's work hard.
Liu Fei. Yebo. Here you are.
- Thank you.
Look at this execution. Isn't it cool?
That's pretty cool. Isn't that you?
Impressive.
But speaking of, so what if he's impressive?
Is he any better than our Tiny Herb?
Exactly.
By the way, Yingjie,
I heard that the restaurant we always go to is getting renovated.
We may not be able to eat their takeout for a while.
So you'll also have to eat my portion while I'm gone.
♫  But with you, I have limitless strength  ♫
What's with that expression?
I'm just going to train for a few days. I will come back.
Come back soon.
Of course.
When I come back, you must defeat that Lord Grim.
I heard them say that the captain intends to train you to be his successor.
Yingjie, keep it up.
You too. You've got this.
I'm leaving.
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We must give it our all to win the battle  ♫
♫  We laugh and cry, secretly grieving over failures  ♫
♫  Supporting one another as we change and grow  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
Actually, I think it would benefit Yifan to go to the Glory Bootcamp.
If he stays on our team,
he will always be the water boy. That's even worse.
♫  Passing countless shining moments  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
Okay, thank you.
Subtitles and Timing provided to you byðŸ’¥ðŸ¥ TEAM 7ï¸âƒ£ ðŸ¥ðŸ’¥ @viki.com
"Glory Battlefield" - R1SE
♫  The road to the top is long and bumpy  ♫
♫  But with you, I have limitless strength  ♫
♫  Failure is like the dawn of victory  ♫
♫  So what if we start over again  ♫
♫  Youth is the time for unstoppable progress  ♫
♫  Accompanied by confidence and strength  ♫
♫  Even if beaten to flee with wounds and bruises  ♫
♫  Desperation always gives rise to hope  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We must give it our all to win the battle  ♫
♫  We laugh and cry, secretly grieving over failures  ♫
♫  Supporting one another as we change and grow  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We must fight for our dreams and win in style  ♫
♫  With victory, we hug and cheer with joy  ♫
♫  Passing countless shining moments  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We must give it our all to win the battle  ♫
♫  We laugh and cry, secretly grieving over failures  ♫
♫  Supporting one another as we change and grow  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We must fight for our dreams and win in style  ♫
♫  With victory, we hug and cheer with joy  ♫
♫  Passing countless shining moments  ♫
♫  This is our most glorious battlefield  ♫
♫  We've spent countless shining moments together  ♫