Would you...
like to try again?
The hot pot party?
That's not it.
Kissing.
What do you think you're doing?
Huh?
- What do you mean?
- Do you...
like me?
No...
- That's why...
- Just stop it!
What was that for?
If you don't like me,
don't do this kind of thing.
I'm sorry.
I'm going home first.
Hold on...
Wait!
Tell Ryu-san I'm sorry.
Why are you angry?
I won't understand unless you tell me.
Even if I say it, you won't understand.
What's with him?
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
And Mahiro...?
Just now he...
Did he really go home?
Seems like it.
What happened?
I don't know.
Hey, Souta-kun.
Why...
I don't get it.
"Naked Dining"
"Episode 8 The taste of adult suki"
Hey, Souta-kun.
It's time for me to go home.
Why did you leave me behind?
Mahiro.
I'm going out for deliveries.
What happened?
Did he...
say anything?
Nothing.
What happened?
Ugh.
Do you
like me?
That's why I wanted to make sure.
A kiss?
What?
Souta-kun tried to kissed you...
Shhh!
Keep your voice down.
What?
Well, I mean...
if someone you like tries to kiss you...
You know?
But...
it doesn't mean he actually likes me.
You don't know that for sure.
I do know.
I know because I love him.
What a troublesome kid.
Could it be that he thought
I was just teasing him?
That was why he got angry like that...
Alright.
After Taiwanese hot pot...
(Suki naam and Thai suki sauce)
Suki naam...
Thai cuisine?
Hello, Miki fruit and vegetable store.
Ah.
Souta-kun.
Huh?
Mahiro?
He's bit busy right now.
Yeah.
Yes.
Understood.
I'll tell him.
(Sounds like 'like' in Japanese)
He said suki.
Oh my.
Somebody's flustered.
What?
(Suki naam)
These are the ingredients for suki naam.
Well then, I leave the delivery to you.
Huh? No way.
Ryu-san, you should go.
No can do.
Why?
He wants the delivery
to be done by Mahiro.
But...
No buts.
Isn't the reunion with Souta-kun
a miracle for you?
I understand that it's scary,
but
you can do it!
Express your feelings properly.
Is it okay if...
you end up with regret like me?
What kind of face
should I make when I see him?
It's okay.
Calm down.
Just be honest about
how I truly feel.
You got this, no worries!
Here are the items you ordered.
Thank you.
You can pay later, it's fine.
Wait.
It hurts.
Ah.
Sorry.
Don't go!
Let's cook together, like we always do.
How...
can I do it alone?
Conveniently using me like that...
I want to cook with you, Mahiro!
I want us to cook together!
Is that bad?
The seventh dish of our culinary journey
is Thai-style sukiyaki for one person.
(Thai suki sauce)
Suki naam.
Does that mean it's sukiyaki?
No.
Well, to be precise,
'naam' means putting soup in.
So...
suki is sukiyaki then?
Yeah.
It seems that the 'suki' in Thai suki
comes from the word 'sukiyaki'.
Wow.
By the way, suki without soup
is called 'suki hang'.
Hang is without soup...
Did I say it correctly?
Well, let's get started.
Wait. Answer me first.
No.
What's wrong?
Stingy.
What are you saying...
Let's get started already.
Yeah, looks about right.
It's not eaten by dipping
it in a raw egg?
Yes.
We'll add this egg-coated pork
to the soup,
and then add the vegetables as well.
It's completely different
from Japanese sukiyaki.
Yeah.
It's closer to a spicy vermicelli stew.
Once the vermicelli is cooked,
it's done.
Oh.
It seems easier than I thought.
You can make it on your own next time.
Huh?
No way.
Let's cook together.
There are still three dishes left.
That's not what I meant.
You mean suki?
Yeah.
Oh.
You know...
Huh?
Yesterday...
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Forget it.
I wasn't fooling around with you.
Since that day...
Ever since you said you kissed me.
The feeling around here
is non-stop tense.
The feeling of liking someone...
I don't quite understand it.
Even so,
I wondered if liking men
would be possible for me.
But when I'm with you,
it's really fun.
And I always want to cook together.
I've been wondering about
what this feeling is.
I really don't understand.
Is it friendship?
Or what is it?
These thoughts
are fighting nonstop in my mind.
Enough.
I understand how you feel.
You don't get it at all.
Please hear me out first!
I said enough already.
I wanted to make sure!
I wanted to figure out what this...
uneasy feeling was all about!
So you gave me a kiss.
Yeah.
After you make sure,
what if it's not?
Huh?
After making sure,
and realizing it wasn't the case,
when that time comes,
what will you say to me?
I...
You see...
You're the worst.
Why did it turn out like this?
(Thai suki sauce recipe)
After you make sure,
what if it's not?
After kissing,
after making sure,
and realizing it wasn't the case...
Don't jump to conclusions!
(Thai suki sauce)
I...
Why am I...
why am I always like this...
Calm down,
Mahiro.
Souta-kun
is trying to face you, right?
But...
What does it mean to make sure?
What if it turns out to be different...?
Because he,
Souta is
different from me and Ryu-san.
It's obvious that he's different.
You knew that
from the beginning, right?
But
you still fell for him knowing that.
That's true.
I know that,
because I know, that's why it's scary...
Mahiro.
I should have never liked him.
If I knew I would feel like this,
Ryu-san.
It hurts...
It's painful...
I understand.
Cry as much as you want.
What the heck was that?
Switching when it didn't work out here.
Isn't that too fast?
What's wrong?
Did you get cheated on?
I was serious with it, you know?
Huh?
Serious about what?
Oh, I...
Yesterday,
I got way too into gaming, you see.
Yeah.
- The one that charges you, right?
- Yeah.
Play in moderation.
Right.
If you're too serious about it,
you lose.
Is that so?
I lost already?
It's unusual to see you
working overtime, Ichijou-san.
It's just my usual routine.
But you usually leave
the office on time, right?
That's just for appearances.
What do you mean?
Ah...
No, it's nothing.
If you don't mind,
want to talk about it?
Then...
Excuse me.
I'll leave, then.
I got rejected.
You got rejected?
I haven't confessed yet.
So, it was unrequited love?
Shimizu-san,
are you free after this?
I am...
How about a drink?
Join me for a drinking session.
I'm fine with that.
But I don't want
to be just a drinking buddy.
Alright, understood.
I'll treat you to some tasty food too.
That's not what I meant.
Don't treat me as drinking buddy,
but as a lover.
Huh?
This time,
it's not an act.
Please...
become...
my real lover.
(Next episode)
We are...
really going out.
Getting closer after quarreling
for the first time.
Regretting after all this time...
Ichijou-san
isn't a pro at love, right?
Everything that happened,
please pretend it ever happened.
(This is a work of fiction)