Did I say something wrong?
- Was I being insensitive...
- I...
I did it.
The kiss.
I...
kissed you.
What was that all about?
Oh no!
Let's cook first.
Let's focus on food for now.
I don't know why...
It feels like something is lacking.
Like some sort of stimulation
or something similar.
No, not that kind of stimulation!
Hot!
"Naked Dining"
"Episode 7
The spice in the sweet night"
Hey.
How are you?
No.
We just met.
Hey.
The Ghanaian food last time
was delicious!
It sounds so unnatural.
Maybe I should just ask directly.
Oh, Ichijou-san!
Welcome!
Oh!
Hello.
You see...
I came to buy vegetables...
If you're looking for Mahiro,
he's out for deliveries.
Is that so?
- Deliveries, I see.
- Yes.
Oh.
So that's the case.
Do you need something from Mahiro?
No...
You see,
he always helped me
choose the ingredients.
Oh!
- Mizuchi-san's menu, right?
- Yes.
What are you planning to make this time?
What was it again?
Using some seasoning called Shacha
or something...
It's a Taiwanese hot pot.
Do you mean.
Shacha sauce?
Yes, that one.
In that case,
Then the ingredients are...
Adding it to the sauce
makes a delicious dipping sauce.
Yes.
This one as well.
Oh, I see. You sure know a lot.
You're good at cooking too, Ryu-san?
Good?
Well, I'm from Taiwan myself.
Is that so?
Yes.
- By the way, Mahiro mentioned about a kiss...
- Kiss?
He wanted to sell imperfect produce
that look like they kissed the dust.
Oh.
Kissed the dust, huh?
I'll give you a discount,
how about that?
Yeah, I'll take that, too.
I'll put them in the hot pot.
Hot pot.
Ouch...
Let's calm down for now.
What should I do?
I'm home.
Hey.
Huh?
What's the deal with these vegetables?
Oh, these?
They're for tonight's hot pot party.
Hot pot party?
Yes.
A hot pot party for the three of us
at Ichijou-san's place!
The three of us...
I'll treat you all to Ryu family's
special dipping sauce,
so look forward to it.
Oh.
The shacha sauce, right?
Could it be that
I'm...
a nuisance?
No,
on the contrary,
I'm glad you're joining.
There's definitely something
between you and Ichijou-san, huh?
Something?
You've been acting strangely.
Really?
Yes.
I...
I told him something that
he didn't need to know.
Something he didn't need to know?
Yes.
Well, you know,
sometimes it's better
to not know the truth.
It's better that way.
That's true.
Yeah.
But
the truth has many aspects
depending on who sees it.
(Shacha hot pot Taiwanese dish)
You got this, no worries!
Good evening!
Welcome!
Mizuchi-san,
sorry to intrude!
So, Ryu-san is
from Taiwan, right?
Yes.
I thought it would be a good opportunity.
Besides,
hot pot is more fun
with more people, right?
Oh...
I'm sorry.
What's with the apology?
Three people are better than two.
No...
You see,
about that thing the other day...
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Let's get started!
Oh, sorry.
What did that mean...
Souta.
What are you doing?
Let's get started.
Yeah!
(Shacha hot pot Taiwanese dish)
So, this is Mizuchi-san's...
way of traveling around
the world with food.
Alright!
Leave tonight's Taiwan trip
to me as your guide!
Roger that!
I'll be in charge of the soup
and dipping sauce,
which are very crucial.
So, Ichijou-san and Mahiro,
please cut the ingredients.
Alright.
Let's start by washing these.
And
this one, too.
Try chopping the same way.
- Alright.
- Yeah.
Oh, wait!
Don't throw it away.
The coriander roots
will make the sauce taste better.
Oh.
- Cheers!
Wow, it smells amazing.
Isn't that right?
Dip them in my special Ryu family sauce
and enjoy!
It looks spicy.
Just try it.
Yeah.
It's not spicy.
Shacha sauce
is more umami than spicy.
- Oh, I see.
- Yeah.
Delicious.
As expected from Ryu-san.
It's incredibly tasty.
What a relief.
Yeah.
Yeah! This, this flavor!
By the way,
there are so many
different spices, aren't there?
I used to think that spices were
all about heat and stimulation.
Oh.
Well, it's true.
But spices are originally
used to enhance aroma,
add richness to the flavor,
and balance out any unpleasant tastes.
I see...
And so, there are times
that spices can indeed add depth
and excitement to our lives.
Deepens stimulation...
Huh?
Wow, amazing!
- The Niagara Falls of Taiwan, right?
- What's it called?
Shifen Pu Bu.
- Shifen Pu Bu.
- Oh, not bad.
- I'm right?
- Taipei building...
- 101.
- I didn't say it correctly?
- No.
That's not it.
Zhong Zheng Ji Nian Tang.
- Amazing.
- Wonderful.
Wow.
Shall we switch to soju soon?
Sounds good.
How should we drink it?
It's fine,
I'll go get it.
I'll have mine straight!
Then...
On the rocks for me.
Okay.
Hey,
Souta-kun,
do you have someone you like?
So sudden...
What's more, Souta-kun...
Talking about love makes us
closer as friends, right?
So?
Is there someone you like right now?
Umm...
What's wrong?
There isn't anyone?
Someone I like?
I wonder...
Lately,
I've been feeling unsure about
what it means to like someone.
You don't know?
I haven't liked anyone for a long time,
so I guess I've forgotten that feeling.
That sounds like
there might be someone you have in mind.
Huh?
I'm just guessing,
but maybe you're interested in someone,
but you're not sure
if you actually like them yet.
There are many types of love, after all.
Many kinds of love...
And you, Ryu-san?
Is there someone you like?
Yes.
What kind of person?
Wasn't it someone with a cute smile?
They're kind,
smiley,
they used to have a cute smile.
Used to?
They're no longer in the world I'm in.
I'm sorry.
Don't be so down about it.
Oh.
This is what they call the
epitome of holding back!
- Oh.
- I was going to eat it...
You should have said that earlier!
It's okay,
don't worry about it.
No.
You have to say
these things without holding back.
Otherwise,
you might lose something precious,
like I did.
Like you did?
Yes.
If I had been
honest and straightforward
without holding back at that time,
maybe...
we could still be together now.
Still?
Wait a minute.
They're not dead?
They're still alive.
But earlier you said
they're no longer in your world.
Because he would never return
to the world I'm in.
He?
Yes.
He...
I thought it was an unrequited love.
But
I've always liked him.
So, you know,
when he accepted my feelings,
I was really happy.
Just being together
already made me truly happy.
But...
Shinji!
Long time no see.
What long time no see?
Your friend?
Yes, that's right.
I doubted,
I felt jealous...
I convinced myself that maybe
he would be happier without me...
Hao Shan!
Wait!
(I loved the straightforward Hao Shan)
Wishing you happiness.
(Wishing you happiness)
He said it was exhausting
being with someone
like me who isn't honest.
That's why I want you two, young ones,
to live your lives being true to
your feelings, without regrets.
The feeling of falling in love,
be it a minority
or majority,
it does not matter.
It's a miracle to meet someone
who makes you feel that way.
A miracle...
Yes.
Falling in love with someone
is a miracle.
So, I want you
to cherish that miracle.
Mahiro
tends to hold back too easily.
To your loved ones,
express
your true feelings honestly.
So you'll find happiness.
Your kindness and consideration
are also part of your charm, Mahiro.
Isn't that right,
Souta-kun?
Huh?
Oh...
Yeah.
Because Mahiro is like this,
that's why Grandma trusted you
with the house key.
You mistook me for a thief at first.
You did the same!
Oh no!
I almost forgot something important!
What is it?
When it comes to hot pot,
you can't forget the finishing touch!
Ryu-san really goes at his own pace,
doesn't he?
Yes.
But.
But I never would have
imagined he had such a past.
Such a past?
Nothing...
It's...
How should I say it?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Here.
It's time for the climax of the hot pot.
The noodles
you eat with this soup are the best!
It's the best.
Dropping the egg in
at the end is the key.
Alright.
Ryu-san, thanks for the food.
It was so delicious!
What a relief!
I'm stuffed.
So sleepy.
Hey.
Souta-kun.
Can I stay over?
Huh?
Sure. There are futons here.
I'm going home.
Mahiro must stay over as well.
Ryu-san...
Ryu-san.
Look, I laid out a futon.
Alrighty.
Wait! That's my futon!
I wish you happiness.
Then,
I'll sleep here.
What is my heart throbbing for?
The feeling of falling in love,
be it a minority
or majority,
it does not matter.
It's a miracle to meet someone
who makes you feel that way.
Hey.
Already asleep?
Sorry, did I wake you up?
Oh, no.
What? Did you pretend to be asleep?
Do you want some?
Yeah.
Wait a moment.
Surprisingly, they go so well.
It changed a lot.
It's tasty.
I know, right?
Hey.
Would you
like to try again?
The hot pot party?
That's not it.
What is it?
Kissing.
(Next episode)
Heart broken.
One-sided love?
If you're serious, you lose.
I'm serious about it.
It's not like he likes me.
My heart aches.
It hurts.
(This is a fictional work)
Maybe it's not a misunderstanding.
Quit fooling around!