My Dear Brothers
EP17
Hou Chi
Bi Hong
Devil Lord Qiu Ping
Go straight to the next round of selection.
It's not fair.
The site of the second test
will be changed to Devil Sect.
It's not fair.
This is cheating for Devil Sect.
Right.
What did you say?
It's unfair.
I like it.
Even though I play favorites to the Devil Sect.
If you don't want to join, just quit.
You are threatening us.
Why is this test like a joke?
Shi Ji is a little wired
in this election.
Isn't that a little obvious to pull the string?
Do you think she has a crush on me?
Devil Lord
I'm here.
I want you to take all the examinees
to the Devil Sect.
Set off now.
OK.
Brother
Be careful.
The entrance to the Devil Sect
can't be known to these people.
Don't worry.
I will protect you and the Devil Sect.
I'm the leading man.
Trust me.
I do.
I'm not afraid of anything
as long as you're here.
Everyone, follow me into the Ark
at my disposal.
Do you hear me?
You heard him.
Do...
Let's go.
Come on.
Immortal Aunt
I'm a little worried.
This time,
Shi Xia not only came out of the Dark Forest,
but helped Your Majesty get the
qualification.
Now, no one can stop Your Majesty
from bringing Shi Xia back to Devil Sect.
It looks like Immortal Aunt lost.
I don't care win or lose.
I only care about my brother.
Although I have no memory of a lot of things,
I know that
my brother ate the Wan Du for me,
and endured great pain.
All that my brother did for me
meant he cared about me.
That was enough.
Immortal Aunt, I'm useless.
I can't get rid of Bai Li.
Senior
Did you really let that witch go?
Yeah.
No, Senior.
Hou Chi was so innocent
that he would be tempted again.
If he knows that it was her to take the risk to get him
the qualification.
In my opinion, we should just kill her.
But I promised to give Shi Xia a chance.
Since she helped Hou Chi
get the retake,
she should be spared.
It's not the right way to break faith.
You should not talk about the right way
with witch.
Senior
You are so soft,
what if Hou Chi is cheated
by the witch again?
Junior
You are ignorant of human affairs.
Even if we kill Shi Xia now,
it wouldn't help.
To end their relationship,
we need to start with Chi.
Come here.
Come on.
Look.
What have you done to the owner?
It's not easy to regain the exam qualifications.
Remember not to be obsessed with that
witch.
Get on your knees and make amends to the owner.
You swear
that you'll never
talk to that witch again.
Master
Forget it.
You may leave.
I will assume that you're not
my disciple.
Hou Chi
I promised, Master.
That's right.
That's my good disciple.
Hou Chi
Why are you here?
I heard you are sick.
Let me see.
The owner of the Yuhua Sect
is pretending to be sick.
Bi Hong
You've managed to get yourself a place
in the exam by accident this time.
It's good.
When you get to the Devil Sect, help Hou Chi.
Hou Chi
He's so good. Will he need my help?
What are you looking at?
I got you first-class seat,
and an unlimited supply of bubble tea.
Do you want it or not?
Your fingers...
All the fingers are healed
with no sign of injury.
I think it should be the strength of kinship.
I suppose that the
Yuhua Sect didn't kidnap you at all.
You were lying.
Shi Dong
I need you to explain everything to me.
I never said it's the Yuhua Sect that kidnapped me,
right?
You lied to me about your life.
You're going too far.
Didn't I just play the martyr?
I used to play with you a lot.
What's the fuss about this time?
Is it because of Hou Chi?
Stop rambling.
I just hate it when people lie to me,
and I hate it even more when I lie to people.
You made me like an idiot
to worry about you.
I regarded the Yuhua Sect as enemies.
Turns out it was you.
Well, well.
I'll be more careful next time.
You're my only sister.
You can't turn your back on me.
Who said I am the only one?
What about Qiu Li?
I'm just saying that Hou Chi
is the brother in name only.
We're really brother and sister, aren't we?
You can't disown me and cut ties
for such a trifle.
First, this is not a trifle.
Second,
it's a good idea to cut ties.
Shi Xia. Blood is thicker than water.
Immortal Aunt
Kinship.
Your Majesty said Shi Xia
was his only real sister.
You mean nothing to him.
The only sister.
I'm not
gonna let Shi Xia take away my brother.
Immortal Aunt. You're back at last.
Too bad, I can't stop Bai Li.
She has promised Devil Lord
to set the second test at the Devil Sect.
It's fine.
Come together then,
and stay here forever.
Welcome!
Warm Welcome!
Master, this is the Devil Sect.
Master
Master. Here we are.
Welcome! Welcome!
Welcome to our Devil Sect.
We have thousands of years of history
with vast territory, abundant resources,
and long history.
Without further ado,
now follow my steps
to show you around.
Come on.
Come on. Follow my steps.
Come on. Come here.
Can you see it?
No problem. Come on.
OK. The first scenic spot
is the most famous shop of our Devil Sect.
What's the name?
The milk tea shop of Devil Sect.
You know we...
Dude
I heard your Immortal Sect is great, right?
Yeah. What?
The daily sales of milk tea of our Devil Sect
can circle hundreds of circles
around your Yuhua Sect.
I...
Come on. Let's go this way.
Smell great.
Qing Feng
Go there with me.
Hi,
give me all the milk tea you have.
Oh, you guys have good taste.
You've found our
latest Devil Sect invention,
Holy Power Ship.
Our Devil Sect is all about equality.
Immortal coin in exchange for Holy Power.
Holy Power in exchange for immortal coins.
Shi Liu, fill it up.
OK.
Please, lie down.
It's Holy Power.
Great holy power.
Holy power can be removed from the body and
preserved in this way?
If it is properly used,
the people without
Holy Root also can practice.
Senior, what's wrong with you?
It's OK.
Just sand in my eyes.
Master Hou Chi
Master Hou Chi, look.
I got you all kinds of flavors.
I'm fine.
Try this!
I bought this Devil Sect
specialty especially for you.
Qing Feng, I'll treat you milk tea.
Devil Sect's specialty.
Devil Sect's specialty?
I hate Devil Sect.
You...
Waste my kindness.
Witch
Although this is the territory of the Devil Sect,
Yuhua Sect still don't welcome you.
Master
I'm just want to talk to Hou Chi for a second.
This is my gift to him.
I don't like sweets.
Take it back, please.
Hou Chi
You're eating candy by yourself.
The sugar figure looks good.
It's very creative
to make it look like a tree.
Is it sweet?
The Dark Forest is
the only way to the shrine.
I heard that everyone who went there
would lose something very important.
I'm fine, aren't I?
Bi Hong and I haven't lost anything.
Did I lose my gustation?
It's not sweet.
Not at all.
Lying.
Let me have a bite.
This, this...
I don't eat. It's all yours.
Why are you crying?
It's just sugar.
Alright, alright.
Come on.
It is all your fault.
Yeah. My fault.
Brother
I want to go home.
Senior
I've been looking all over for you.
What's wrong with you?
What's the matter?
Have you lost anything
since you came out of the Dark Forest?
No, I haven't.
See? I'm all right here.
That's good.
That's a relief.
Why did you ask?
Have you lost something?
I haven't.
I am very good.
I'm glad you're okay.
I'm gonna go.
Chi
Now, we're in Devil Sect territory.
You need to remember to
keep your distance from Devil Sect,
and socialize with Immortal Sect.
That's right.
Thank you for waiting.
Now, Shi Xia will invite the Shen Guan
to announce the second test question.
Please.
I declare
the mission of this alliance election
will be a search for the Holy Garment.
The first to obtain the Holy Garment
will pass the test.
Look for the magic weapon of Devil Sect
in the Devil Sect's territory.
You might as well just say
Devil Lord is the of the Alliance.
You are right.
Why don't you just say
I'm partial to Devil Sect?
Shen Guan is not biased.
The Holy Garment was the robe of Qiu Boyan,
the father of our Devil Sect.
It's been missing
since the Master died.
So, don't worry.
We Devil Sect don't know anything
about the Holy Garment more than you do.
Really?
What is our home-court advantage?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Your accommodations have been arranged.
It's the famous Seven-Star
Inn of Devil Sect.
The room rate is 20% off, excluding breakfast.
Well, the Devil Sect is doing
a pretty good job
of making money.
That's right.
I don't think they paid for the milk tea.
Keep an eye on Immortal Aunt.
Keep her away from Devil Lady.
I'm doing that.
She went out.
Then I'll go outside and keep an eye on her.
Holy root was
just a toy
to be plucked and played.
Now I find out
what it's really for.
Now, this book of secrets left by mother
finally come in handy.
Immortal Aunt
All candidates carefully selected
by Immortal Sect's
have come to Devil Sect.
When we gather all
their Holy Roots,
we will be able to cultivate
the best Holy Roots
in the world for Devil Lord.
It doesn't matter if Shi Xia is his real sister.
It's me who helped brother to become the Devil Lord,
and I killed Qiu Ping by myself.
All she did was only help her brother get into
the election.
But I'm the only one
who can help brother get to head of the
Alliance,
and obtain the immortal Holy Root.
Hi, please try this one.
This is the Seven-Star Inn of Devil Sect.
Seven-Star is the highest
level of reception specifications.
Leisure corridor with considerate design.
The seven-star guest room
can give you a noble enjoyment.
I don't think you Immortal Sect
have this kind of treatment.
No way.
Since you're here, enjoy it.
Immortal Sect who have always been ascetic,
we do not care about such external pleasures.
This is the wrong way.
That's how we treat people at Devil Sect.
Forget it if you don't appreciate it.
You can also sleep rough in the back hills.
Master
Master Hou Chi
This is yours. Please take it.
Master
Who arranged this room?
Hou Chi
I don't understand some of my skills,
could you please give me some advice?
Why hasn't my order come yet?
Hou Chi
Please.
Flirting.
Is it not crowd?
That's enough for mahjong.
Hou Chi
Do you still remember me?
I am the little junior of Lingxiu Sect.
How could he possibly remember you?
Yes, I do.
Hou Chi
This is the egg noodle I just made.
You don't even know he is in inedia.
Save it.
Thank you.
Hou Chi
It's a sachet I made myself,
and it's filled with herbs.
Put it by the bed,
it can help you with relaxing.
Fool.
He only practices at night and doesn't sleep.
Thank you.
Lingxiu Sect and Yuhua Sect have always been
on good terms.
I'll cut to the chase.
In fact, I came here today to invite you
to look for the Holy Garment with me.
So do we.
Hou Chi
There was Miss Shi Xia at your side.
But she has nothing to do with Immortal Sect.
So I was wondering
if I could be by your side
as Miss Shi Xia used to be.
Hou Chi
We'll leave, Senior.
Got out so fast.
Here you are.
I thought there was something new going on.
Isn't it just a doll?
What you don't like
is something many people want.
I took it. Don't regret it.
Regret?
Who cares!
Liar.
Just as big a liar as Shi Dong.
You give me my gustation back.
You should have known
there was a price to pay
for going into the Dark Forest.
It's too late to regret.
But you can take
something else if you want.
Like sadness, pain.
But not my gustation.
How could that possibly be a choice?
The Dark Forest takes
what's most important to you.
If you took too much pleasure in food,
of course, the first choice is your gustation.
Don't bother me
unless there's something else.
Immortal, do not leave.
What should I do
if I'm unhappy in the future?
I can't solve the problem by eating now.
Ling
Ye