Shi Hyun.
I'm a person that only makes you sad.
You found me
and brought me such great happiness like this,
but in the end, I'm someone who made you cry.
Thank you.
In the end, I'm the person who made you cry the most.
That's why I couldn't hold you back.
I... am going to wait for you.
♫ I can feel you anywhere ♫
♫ I can feel you anywhen ♫
♫ Your weary heart, I'll embrace it ♫
♫ During the cold days, ♫
♫ One shining star ♫
♫ Me by your side ♫
[Episode 25]
♫ You by my side ♫
♫ If we get a bit, I'll hurry to you ♫
♫ To a place where your hands can reach ♫
♫ In harsh winds, in harsh hardships ♫
♫ When it's hard for you to endure ♫
♫ You can ♫
I'll wait for you.
♫ Lean on me ♫
♫ I can feel you anywhere ♫
♫ I can feel you anywhen ♫
♫ Your weary heart, I'll embrace it ♫
♫ During the cold days, ♫
♫ One shining star ♫
♫ Me by your side, you by my side ♫
I must be insane! How come I can even hear his voice?!
♫ I'll protect you like I breathe ♫
♫ Even if I'm tired, always like this ♫
♫ I'll be by your side ♫
I must be insane, too.
I can hear your voice.
I keep hearing it.
I miss you... Eun Tae Hee.
Did you not sleep well again?
No.
Here. Our Eun Tae Hee...
Get up. Let's go to school.
It's pretty nice, going to school with you all the time.
You don't think that Kwon Shi Hyun is waiting for you again today, do you?
He came yesterday, too. It's already been a couple of days.
I know, right? I told you that I would just stay in the studio.
He must want to see you just once, even if it's like this.
It's his own feelings, so he should take care of it himself.
Aigoo. You want to see him, too.
Give me the car keys. Did I ever give you permission to drive it?
I should practice with a used car at least.
I know, but not that car.
Se Joo already got it checked out.
Are you nervous because the car got involved in an accident?
What?
They said the front of the car was changed or something. Did you get into a car accident?
Leave the key. I'm going to get rid of it.
Mom. By any chance, is Shi Hyun's grandmother bothering you?
What are you talking about?
Is your relationship with Ahjussi alright?
We're alright. Why are you asking?
Just because. I want you to marry each other without any problems.
If you need help, I'll help you.
Why are you looking at me like that? Does it feels strange because I've changed sides?
Why do you keep acting like a bad person?
That's why you're the one who's getting hurt.
Why don't you grab onto my hands first?
Why do you make me question whether our first kiss was a dream or not?
Why are you making me ask all these questions?
Let's just stay like this for a little bit. Just a little bit...
Your face when you smile is so pretty.
But all I ever did was make you cry.
I'm sorry, Tae Hee.
She called me many times.
I'll call you later. Make sure to keep your phone on.
What happened to you? Why do you keep leaving your phone off?
I'm busy because of the contest. Why?
What do you mean, "why?" It's because you were doing alright, but then I suddenly couldn't get in touch with you.
It's not like we call each other often or anything.
Tae Hee. You seem so different from the last time we saw each other.
I'm really taken aback right now.
What happened? Are you upset with me?
Upset?
Why? Do you feel guilty because of me?
What?
Do you remember the last conversation we had?
You said you were going back down to your studio, and that you weren't dating anyone.
But, then what? Did you end up dating someone from then on?
You can tell me honestly. I'm not even surprised anymore.
- Tae Hee—
- I had my phone off on purpose.
Not because of anyone else, but because I didn't want to get your calls.
I blocked your number already, so don't contact Kyung Joo! Just why—
Why did you come and mess with someone who was fine?!
Wait, Tae Hee!
Fine. You can explode on me and get mad,
but you're being too weird right now. What happened?!
Who do you think is making me have a hard time? I've always had a hard time because of you.
If it wasn't for you, Dad and I wouldn't have had any problems!
That's right. This time is also your fault. Should I tell you?
The person who you couldn't ever forget, the one who made you make things hard for Dad and me,
is my boyfriend's father.
Do you know how sorry I felt towards Shi Hyun?
Since you couldn't get over your feelings, you made Dad and I have a hard time, but just how many more lives are you going to ruin?
Thanks to you, it's over.
Please get out of my life now.
I won't ever meet you again. I won't see you anymore.
[Hye Jung]
Yeah, Hye Jung?
Are you on your way, Unni? I finished all the prep work for our lesson.
Yeah, I'll be there soon.
How did you hurt yourself, our future son-in-law? Oh, my goodness.
I just overworked myself while exercising.
Oh, my goodness. You should've been careful. What should we do?
I'm alright.
My teacher's here.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Ki Young Oppa...
Tae Hee.
Oh my. She is Hye Jung's tutor math tutor. Do you know each other?
Ah, yes—she's the daughter of a teacher whom I respect.
Right? As expected, you were from an elite family.
Then, I don't have to introduce you to my future son-in-law.
F-future son-in-law?
Oh? You look better than I thought.
In the video, you basically flew away.
Video?
Yeah. The guy who fainted in the bar in Cheongdam-dong.
That's you, right? Mr. L from a Seoul law firm. Should we watch it together?
Should I turn it on?! I'll do it.
- I got—
- Hey, stop it.
Hye Jung, what are you doing watching stuff like that? How low quality of you.
What do you mean "low quality"? You were the one that was complaining about being cheeky and then got beat up.
It's so satisfying to watch, Unni.
You kid, what do you mean "cheeky"? I'm someone who's going to be working in the law.
I'm pretty sure it's you. You complained first and then it turned to complete chaos.
I told you, right, Mother? After she started hanging out with Soo Ji, she got completely influenced by her.
Look at the way she speaks. Stop using your phone.
Ah, seriously—
Are you getting married, Hye Jung?
No. You know that I have a boyfriend. All the adults are just being foolish.
That's a relief. I don't recommend that guy as a boyfriend.
Do you know this phrase, Unni? "Only lovers survive."
I'm going to get into college and marry Joo Hwan.
Alright. You're so cool.
- Is everything going well with Shi Hyun and you?
- What?
Do you also know him?
I think that he really likes you. On opening day, he even brought you meat.
That's right. Let's hurry and get started.
What is it?
Just let me ask you one thing, Tae Hee. Is Shi Hyun still following you? Do you want me to take care of him for you?
Aren't you busy? What is there for you to take care of?
I'm being like this because I think about you. Those kiddos are really scary people.
Hye Jung used to be gentle, but after hanging out with Soo Ji a couple of times, she became weird.
This is also because of Kwon Shi Hyun.
Lee Se Joo and Kwon Shi Hyun were fighting like crazy over Soo Ji, so while I was trying to stop them, I turned out like this.
This situation doesn't involve me and I'm not even curious about it.
You need to cut them off immediately if you're still hanging out with them. Otherwise, you're going to end up hurt.
I'm going to sue Kwon Shi Hyun for this.
It's none of my business whether you sue him or not. It's up to you. Good-bye, then.
Tae Hee! Tae Hee?!
Just why is even Tae Hee acting like that to me?
Just go, you punk!
You, who say you don't use violence, and you, who only uses violence,
went in public, disgracing our family! How dare you get involved in a group fight!
Let's see the both of you fight here. Try fighting until one of you dies.
Try it.
Father—With whatever methods I can, I'll persuade Ki Young to drop the lawsuit.
You should know where you stand in order to not bring shame to our family!
How can brothers fight, and what is this nonsense with accusations and lawsuits?! You!
Young one.
Yes, Father.
Please ask a favor of your father.
Isn't his law firm more powerful than theirs?
Of course, Father. I'll take care of it.
While we're at it, close down your restaurant, too. If that's all you can do, just shut it down.
My restaurant is doing well now, so why?
You have to pay for the damages at least!
I can just work and pay it off.
Or you, give back the room where you guys roll around and play in.
My mom definitely gave that to me. No one can touch it.
Even if you don't get sued, you have to do at least that much for disgracing our family.
I understand. Then, I'll take care of that, Father.
No. I'll take care of whatever I have to.
If you ask me to leave this house, I gladly would do that instead,
but if you dare touch that place...
I'm not going to stay put.
Why do you look like you have a lot of concerns?
Seo Won was planning on suing you for the fight, so I took care of it already.
I'm sorry.
Why can't you hold yourself back?
I'm sorry that I keep disappointing you.
When your father comes back from his break, just leave and come with me.
You should go and get help from Yeo Min. You should start studying, too.
It's better to do this than getting scolded by your father all the time.
Grandmother...
Yes?
You were always adoring me.
There's nothing that I'm good at, but you always believed in me.
I also know that you have high hopes for me. So I've always felt apologetic towards you.
There's something you need to know before it's too late.
I...
am not my father's real son.
I only found out when my father told me after graduation.
I'm sure Father couldn't tell you because he didn't know how to.
I'm sorry. It was too hard for me,
so I'm saying it in a way like this.
I'll do whatever you tell me to.
Shi Hyun. Before I tell you otherwise,
make sure not to tell anyone else. Do you understand?
Yes.
Alright, leave.
Ahjussi.
My dad got hospitalized because he's unwell, right? Is he staying at Myeong Jeong Hospital?
He's just going to get some tests. He'll be alright.
Yes, I understand.
Hello, Doctor Kim. I have a favor to ask of you, quietly.
I'm sure you know right away just by looking at the scans, but a surgery right away is the only option for a good prognosis.
I understand.
Are you alright, Director?
It's not going to be easy, but it's not an impossible treatment either.
If the surgery goes well, you will have a high chance of recovery.
Let's end the wedding first, it's not fair to you either.
We can discuss our work at another time.
Nothing will change. I'm going to keep working hard on my work from my position.
If you feel sorry towards me, even a little bit, then just focus on your treatment.
Change into the hospital clothes. Since you're going to get a lot of testing done later, you should rest well.
I should probably change it.
[Myeong Jeong Medical Foundation]
Hello, I'm a scholarship student, Eun Tae Hee.
Ah, yes. I'm calling again.
Were there any people who left this month?
There was one student who left because of his mandatory military service.
Oh, there was also a female student.
You can move in next month, is that alright?
Of course. I need it.
I'm going to use the application you filled out before.
The earliest you can move in is in two weeks,
so when would be a good time for you?
I'll decide the date in person, when I go to turn in the documents.
I think there was a problem when I set it up through the phone before.
Yes. I'll get there before you get off work.
Thank you.
Did you eat anything yet?
No, I didn't. I thought I was going to die from hunger.
Seriously...
What—?
How could things end up like this?
How long has it been?
- Did you see your father?
- Yes.
You should stay longer.
I'm leaving to let him rest some more.
Is my dad really sick?
He can get better, so don't worry too much.
Okay.
I can move in the on last Saturday of April.
[Scholarship Program Office]
I'm not going to change my decision this time.
I will personally come here if I need anything.
Alright.
I'm certain that were was a call saying that you would cancel the move-in date for the dormitory.
I really didn't do that.
We're sorry towards you, anyway.
Did someone pull a prank or something?
No way.
What are you doing at the hospital? Are you hurt somewhere?
No, I had something to take care of with the scholarship foundation.
What about you?
My dad is hospitalized here.
Ah... why?
I'm not sure, he seems a bit unwell.
I see... You must be very worried.
What did you need to discuss with the foundation?
It's because of my dorm room.
Did they allow you to get back in?
Yeah, fortunately, they said that there's someone moving out.
Where are you staying right now?
- Well, just... I'm going to leave now—
- Tae Hee.
Can we talk for a bit?
Well, alright. I need to talk to you about moving out anyway.
Have you been well?
Excuse me.
I'll clean up and move out of the apartment soon.
I used to come here often with my mom.
When the weather was nice, we would enjoy the sunlight together. Or, when the weather was rainy, we would watch the rain.
I... keep thinking about the time
you came to visit me when I was hospitalized.
I had a rough day that day.
It was the day I found out
that she was the driver of your hit-and-run accident.
You were a good person, though, Mom.
But why...?
So that's why you were crying.
However, how did you find out about it that day?
Can I ask?
When I found out there was no accident record on my mom's car,
I went and asked a detective.
He told me that in Jeongeup,
there was only one hit-and-run accident that night.
I was doubtful, so I went to Director Myeong and asked.
I was wondering if you knew anything.
Did it ever occur to you
that your mother could've been the driver of the hit-and-run accident?
- All we can do is...
-"...hope that female student is doing well."
That's what she said.
Ah, I'm sorry. I keep reminding you of your rough times.
No. It's all in the past anyway.
I'm fine.
You must be having a hard time helping your dad while he's getting treatment.
Then, I'm going now.
She said that all we can do is hope that the female student
is doing well.
She can't look into a victim's personal information.
Then, does that mean she was at the scene of the accident?
Yes, Aunt. You see,
can I ask you something about the day I got into the accident?
All of a sudden?
What is it? Are you not feeling well lately?
Did you have a lot of nightmares about it?
It's nothing like that.
I'm just wondering if after I woke up,
did I say anything or did you find any evidence or something?
Oh... at that time,
when you woke up, you kept asking weird questions like
is "Ahjumma alright?" and "Did she go to the hospital?"
You also didn't recognize your mother,
and you kept hitting your chest and calling her Ahjumma.
That's right. I did that...
Tae Hee. You shouldn't think about whatever happened that day too much.
Even if it comes to your mind again, just push it away.
When people who are traumatized keep thinking about the accident,
they can still remember things like the color of the car even after a couple of years.
Although that's not the case for everyone,
just thinking about it will make you have a hard time. Just forget it.
Alright, Aunt.
It's fine. Just give her a little bit of time
and work it out with her again slowly.
If only I could.
I want to go back to twenty years ago.
Even if we can turn back time,
we can't change a person's heart.