- Kyung Joo.
- Hmm?
[Episode 2]
Kyung Joo.
What is it?
Are you upset?
That's right. Wait a moment.
What is this?
Happy birthday, daughter. I'm sorry that I forgot, it's a bit late.
- Mom
Who is it from?
Aunt Geum Sil is doing so many things instead of my mom.
Let's go in.
Oh, yeah. The mail.
Until when are you going to continue using my address?
[Seol Young Won Pottery]
Are you going? Hey, did you not even tell her about your admission?
I sent her a text.
Are you even her daughter?
Look who's talking.
Let's live with some sort of conscience. Get money from your mom.
Visit your father, too.
I don't want to.
Since I don't need to take their money anymore, I'm happy.
I'll give you one of these, make a wish.
I want a boyfriend who let's me win every time.
You should tell me your wish before you blow out the candle!
It has to be a secret for it to happen.
Then what about me? Let's do it again.
It's your new house. It'll be ready in a week.
I still won't go to the school you want me to.
You probably need something like this.
[Korea Gene Information Center]
This is medical evidence that you aren't my son.
Do you have to threaten me to this point now?
You didn't grow as I wanted. I don't expect you to change.
Move out and live quietly.
How long have you known?
You really are amazing.
You knew all along and just watched, while you loathed me on the inside.
People will think I'm making you more independent, making you live on your own.
Go to college or not. I don't care. I'll make sure it's not hard for you to get by.
When you get a call from the secretary office, show up without question.
That is my condition. This is something only you and I know.
I don't need to tell you how to behave, right?
Lastly, if you have any more questions, go to your dead mother and ask.
You don't need to wait for a week's time.
That's good.
[Award: Kwon Shi Hyun]
[Explanation of test result]
[There is a 2% chance that the DNA matching test has succeeded]
[Mutual Consent of Divorce]
[Kwon Seok Woo, Park Seo Yeon]
What were you doing?
Just... making a paper airplane.
You remember what I taught you when you were younger, right?
Whenever you are worried, or scared,
or have a wish, make a paper airplane and let it fly high in the sky.
That's when all the things that you worried about and were scared of will disappear and your wish will come true.
If you don't have a card, just pay in cash.
How much is it?
Are you a college student or a high schooler?
Are you a high school or college student?
I'm sorry.
I'll pay for it, sir.
On Board.
Thank you.
Excuse me. Here.
Just take it.
Were you trying to throw it away?
It's my will.
Excuse me, but that's not a good idea.
If you need any help, I'll try to help you with whatever I can—
I won't die, but in return, do me a favor.
Don't open it,
and throw it away in a few months.
Why has Dad never celebrated your birthday or my birthday?
We always held a party for his. What's with him?
What is this?
Just a minute, please!
[Seol Yeong Won Pottery]
A lot of graduation presents came. Should I open them?
You can have them all.
What are we going to do with you?
Just leave me alone, Ahjumma!
Ms. Choi, I'm here!
Do you think I was dumped?
Why the hell did you buy ice cream for me?!
Sorry.
Thank you.
Our Soo Jin looks pretty even with eye goop.
Shut up.
Call me if you need anything.
He's an old friend. Nothing will happen even if we were both naked on an uninhabited island.
I understand.
You're so cool!
I wish I had a better expression for it.
But why are you here alone? Isn't Shi Hyun worried about me?
He's weird. He has been doing nothing and just saying, "eh..."
He turned off his phone too.
He only accepts calls from the secretary office and is brooding.
You guys did something without me and caused an accident, right?!
About that. You know the day that you got rejected by Lee Ki Young?
I mean, on graduation day, I think there was a celebrity at the club.
- Drink up!
- I can't take it anymore..
- Eh...
What the heck?
He's still pretty cute.
I'll take the shot for him!
Should I drink for you?
- Well, there's no need...
- It must've been a long time since you had so much fun, Sunbaenim.
Instead...
What is it? W-what?
What should we do? If you get rejected,
you need to take twice the amount.
Did I get rejected?
Hold on tight.
Here.
This is Go Kyung Joo's mother.
I didn't know about this!
Why wouldn't you? She's like the godmother of all supermodels!
I knew it. You're the axis of evil!
Well, who told you to leave us and hang out with that jerk?
You will never lose a word, huh!?
- Come here!
- Hey, hey!
- Hey!
- Go get me chocolate!
I get so embarrassed just looking at the kids.
You saw it at the ceremony, right?
Yeah, so that's why I'm so shocked...
Even though it's their private life, they shouldn't have gotten caught.
It's not the matter of getting caught or not.
This kind of behavior is not acceptable for teachers.
That's right, Sunbaenim.
Of course.
There's another issue.
A few guys went to club that day,
and... what's it called when you meet with strangers?
You mean "booking?"
They did booking with a graduating student's mom.
This is unbelievable.
They kissed while everyone watched.
No, I heard that they were caught together at a hotel instead of the club.
They just stuck by each other all night together
until the very end...
But, I'm sure that she didn't know.
You don't know their age unless you ask them.
Of course, that is true.
If Kyung Joo's mother were to go outside,
who would think she has a daughter that's twenty?
To youngsters, you would just be a pretty noona.
That's not true...
These days, I understand women take care of themselves and whatnot.
But I'm saying that they should dress their age.
Who is that guy that's making all these rumors go around?
You didn't hear about it? He's the grandson and heir to JK Group.
What was his name again? Kwon...
My Kwon Shi Hyun!
I heard he's very sexy.
If you make eye contact with him, your breath just goes away.
He goes to the same school as Kyung Joo, but you don't know of him?
I do. Of course, I know of him. Of course...
That mother doesn't seem to be in her right mind and keeps contacting him.
She must be crazy. What is he supposed to do?
I am worried for that mother's child.
But I guess a smart girl like Kyung Joo can handle it.
They were all talking about me, right?
But how did they find out?
Joo Han, it's me.
It's no big deal, but you know the guy that we met at the nightclub?
Was his name Kwon Shi Hyun?
I know that you can understand Korean.
You heard what my mom has been saying on the phone, right?
What is she talking about?
What should I wear?
When did you have time to post all this?
Who is this?
He's too handsome!
Well, he is pretty handsome.
They don't even follow each other.
Shi Hyun. I guess your name is Shi Hyun.
Is she a celebrity?
I think I've seen her somewhere.
- Did the ladies not leave yet?
- No.
What about the cake? What is it? Did they say something again?
No.
I'm feeling tired, Tae Hee. I want to sleep.
Oh, sleep. I'll go in a bit.
Until when are you going to stay here?
I will return home when my dad comes back to Korea.
It's best for everyone that I'm not home until then.
I guess I won't be able to stay here long then.
Are you going somewhere?
You're not going anywhere so I should go somewhere.
Am I baggage to you?
Yes.
If you stay a few more days, I'm going to age.
Alright, I'll go to our hideout.
Forget it, do you want to get beaten by Soo Ji?
Stop grumbling and get dressed. Go show your face at the event so you won't get scolded more.
[Sponsors' Night]
[Seol Young Won Pottery]
Tae Hee? You're Eun Tae Hee, right?
Ki Young!
Just how long has it been?
Myeong Jeong group became really big.
These events are getting fancier.
Can you double check that this seat is indeed my seat?
Yes. This is indeed your seat, but—
Forget it.
Hello, Madam.
Hello.
Myeong Jeong's Sponsors' Night will begin in ten minutes.
I'm sure that table is VVIP seating.
Did you donate a little this time?
I came here on a tight schedule. Unbelievable.
Hello, I didn't see you come in.
I came, but I think I should get going.
What's wrong? Are you uncomfortable?
Uncomfortable?
You begged for a donation,
so I was worried that Myeong Jeong was in difficult times again,
but I see that you're doing okay now, so I'll go.
She's uncomfortable because she's seated all the way over here.
Kyung Joo's mom, how vulgar. I was just wondering once.
I apologize. There must have been a mistake with VIP arrangement.
JK Group gave a late reply about attendance.
JK Group? Who?
The vice chairman is coming. He said he will come even if he's late.
Really? Oh, there's even a JK logo.
[2018 Myeong Jeong Foundation]
If there was an error, fix it. I can wait.
I guess JK is actively sponsoring now?
Yes, they helped a lot this time.
I see you are close with Vice President Kwon Seok Woo.
Is there something between you two?
The vice chairman is single and you're single.
The table is ready, shall we go, Madam?
Are you going to go, too?
No. I was just looking around to see if there's anything to eat.
Do you have any of the black tea that I drink?
- Here's your black tea.
- Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Why is she trying to please those kind of people?
Where are you going to school?
It's the same one as yours.
Did you take the bar exam?
I went to law school. It's not Seoul National University though.
How's the professor doing? I should visit him soon.
Dad is in Germany. I'm fine on my own though.
You really grew up completely, kiddo.
Is it alright for you to just pinch a lady's cheek like that?
Since you're a lady now, if I ask you out, will you say yes?
What are you saying? It's so cheesy!
Wait a minute, Tae Hee.
So it was you. His first love.
Shi Hyun's father is going to come. Make sure you say hello.
Mom, what do you think he's doing?
How annoying, it feels like he caught me looking at him.
The university students of Myeong Jeong's 2018 scholarship
will receive full tuition for four years.
We believe these students will help brighten our future as a society.
First, student Eun Tae Hee.
Thank you.
Next, student Kang Ji Woo.
[Eun Tae Hee]
I didn't know Lee Ki Young had such facial expressions.
The guy who acted so high and mighty that he made it seem like something would break if he laughed.
Lee Ki Young is interested in Sam Yeong Food Group.
The adults in the family are trying to get him to marry Park Hye Jung.
So what?
I'm going to teach her that Lee Ki Young is not for her. She's only nineteen—
And you're only twenty.
I looked into her a bit
They're an extremely conservative family that believes that women and bowls break when left outside.
They didn't send her to school. She's lived a sheltered, home-schooled life.
Look at this. She's not wearing underwear.
Korean, English, math, music, art, and sports.
They say they teach her everything, but she's just getting tutored 24/7.
I've heard about her. My cousin is friends with her brother.
Ah, my boobs have gotten bigger and now they keep getting in the way!
I'm so damn uncomfortable! Once more. Yes.
He was just as annoying as my brother.
That's right. Move it across a bit more. Relax your shoulders.
- Park Hye Jung!
- What? What is it?
Why does a girl like you need to wear such short skirt? Are you exercising to show off your butt? Hurry up and change!
It fine to me...
Hello.
Yes. Hello.
Who do you think you are? An athlete?
You're think so highly of yourself. Just why does a girl have to exercise?
What the hell, shorty!
He's always like that to me!
Seriously! How dare you say that to me?!
It really hurts!
I hit you because I know it hurts!
Seriously, he's always like that to me!
However, that brother of hers wasn't able to hang out with my brother for long.
Ah, seriously!
Hey, Park Hye Jung!
Hey, you! I'm in big trouble now.
Help me, Hye Jung!
- After that, he wasn't able to walk properly for two weeks!
- Hey!
It keeps popping up in my head, so will you just enjoy it on your own?
Sorry.
Anyway, I want to introduce her to a whole new world.
Don't try to sound nice while saying it. Just be honest about it.
You just want to take away Lee Ki Young's bride. Isn't that it?
However, this experience will benefit her, too. What's the point in being too naive?
That's true. It's not the Joseon era anymore. Loyal women aren't honored as they used to be.
There's also one more person.
Myeong Jeong's scholarship recipient, Eun Tae Hee.
Well, she got 100% on her college exam, topped her class, and placed first in math, science, English, and everything else.
Anyway, if Park Hye Jung wants Lee Yi Kyung's head,
then she wanted his heart.
They say that men won't be able to forget their first love until the day the die.
And he had exactly that gaze while looking at her.
There are lasers coming out from your eyes.
Anyway, I'm in the middle of looking into her. You're going to help me, right?
Deal. It sounds fun.
- What about you?
- No, thanks.
Why?
Is it really necessary to go that far? It's such a nuisance.
"Go that far?" Why do I have to be the only one that's miserable?
You said you'll help me get back at Lee Ki Young! I want him to understand what's it like to be rejected.
I can't stand by, watching him get his way easily.
You know he only gets angry at his father.
- Shut up.
- Kwon Shi Hyun.
Guys, I'll do it.
What do I need to do? Do I just need to seduce Hye Jung or that smart student? Perhaps both? I'm fine either way.
The famous player in all the rumors is you. Don't you think her mother will know?!
Go away, kiddo.
[Secretary Yoon]
[The vice chairman will be there soon. He won't be there long, so come here.]
I'm sorry, but I'm out of this.
Shi Hyun.
Is there something that you're hiding from us?
Did you get kicked out of your house?
You got caught messing around with Go Kyung Joo's mother, right?
No. Stop.
What do you mean by that? Tell me honestly, until where did you go with her?
He's said that's not the case! Hey, I'll do it. I can like anyone.
Seriously, please, you can't. Go away.
He's acting strange, right?
Let him be. When he's ready, he'll tell us.
Where are you going?
What the heck? He was like that yesterday, too.
I'm sorry.
Why did you reject all of my calls?
I felt uneasy, so that's why I called you.
Were you afraid that I spread rumors?
You didn't perhaps, tell Kyung Joo about us, right?
If you did, and she finds out...
"Since I'm sorry, I'll date you too" is what I'll tell her.
Although, I have no rights to say anything, I ask this favor of you.
Kyung Joo... hates me a lot.
I know that she'll leave the house once she finds out,
but I have nothing to say and...
I'm... not Kyung Joo's biological mother.
She doesn't know. Without her, I won't be able to live.
I can't even tell if we're close or not...
I won't tell her.
Thanks.
You see, I kind of miss you from time to time.
I look funny, right?
Good-bye. I'll see you next time.
- Bye.
Ahjumma?
M-Marriage?
As we worked together, we naturally...
I didn't have any intentions of telling everyone this way.
President Myeong's vision is similar to mine.
Since we announced it, let's make this our engagement.
[Tempted]
- Preview -
It's a relief that you're not calling me, Kwon Soo Ji. Everyone I like just disappears...
She's going through hell right now,
so if you have common sense, just shut up!
Marriage, huh?
I'll give you one last chance. I'm against this marriage.
Is it about Shi Hyun? Do you like Shi Hyun?
Kwon Shi Hyun, do you still like me? Then, can you kiss me?
Tae Hee!
Do you guys know each other?
- Yes.
- No.
No.
How am I supposed to hate you?