♫  Tearing up all the memories of the past  ♫
♫  Leaving no regrets behind to haunt us  ♫
♫  Exchanging a whole lifetime, just to go back again  ♫
♫  If I decide to let my guard down  ♫
♫  Will I give my heart to the wrong one?  ♫
♫  Daring to give, not fearing destruction  ♫
♫  Love is unwilling to lay dormant  ♫
♫  Unafraid of shaking Heaven and Earth  ♫
♫  Even though we're on different paths  ♫
♫  I have no complaints and no regrets  ♫
♫  Because you are the unsolvable riddle set by fate  ♫
♫  So I pray for a miracle  ♫
♫  The stars turn, even if consumed by time, I only hope to search for you  ♫
♫  Searching for that miracle called forever  ♫
♫  Until death, we'll walk all the way together  ♫
♫  Love is the most beautiful meaning in life  ♫
Master.
Shifang.
All common people who are suffering.
The mouth of Pureness spring can foresee the future.
Whoever holds the Pureness key ring may catch a glimpse of the future.
If I could foresee the true weakness of Kun...
Why can't I see anything?
Master.
Is it because I am not determined enough?
Master,
help me.
I have to see it.
Xiu'er, to foresee the future,
don't use your eyes, but feel it with your heart.
Master, your eyes
I understand now.
In order to protect the power of the spiritual vein,
Shennong sealed the Nine Springs.
The leakage of divine power is an accident.
Otherwise, even as a guardian,
if he wants to use the power of Pureness,
he has to pay the price.
Xiu'er, what do you think is the reason Pureness exists?
Master.
It's a mockery from heaven,
making people think they can know the secrets of heaven.
But they find that they cannot escape from fate.
If I say so, would you be disappointed?
Pureness and people.
I protect them because I want to.
Xiu'er, you are no longer a little girl.
Don't be swayed by others in your way to move forward.
Just ask yourself, and be true to your heart.
That's really tough.
Master,
you once said,
that you were glad to have the opportunity to be a guardian of Pureness,
who could guide the future in the direction you want,
and protect the people you wanted to.
Today,
I understand it now.
Xiu'er, you have found your path.
Way of Heaven.
Fate.
That power that thinks it can control everything.
At the cost of these eyes,
show me what I want to see.
If they're not enough,
take my hands,
my legs,
and my life.
Alliance Leader Zuo, just surrender.
The Righteous Martial Alliance has been wiped out.
Righteous Martial Alliance fights for the common people.
Dying in battle today is also a way to fulfill my mission.
You are an opponent I respect.
Brothers, don't go far.
I'm coming.
General, Her Lordship and Lord Shuo Xuan will be here soon.
Today, I...
bestow this sword upon you.
Having lived for decades, I have never misjudged a person.
From now on, I will mobilize all our disciples against Zhu Yu.
Rest assured,
we'll handle the rest of it.
Her Lordship!
Bad news! Bad news!
What's wrong, Xiaoyuan?
Third Brother, Qi, and Luo Zhaoyan have gone to Buried Wind Plains.
I was careless.
I should have known they would never let a companion risk their lives alone.
Bring back Yue Jinzhao and Qi immediately. We can't lose them.
I'll go get them both.
I'll go, too.
You two, be careful.
Don't worry.
Your Lordship.
Rehai has already moved here.
Shuo Xuan, open Rehai.
Yue Qi, you are the young lord of the Yu Clan.
Zhu Yu, stop.
I will find the perfect solution.
Zhu Yu.
Qi.
Shuo Xuan.
Hurry.
Zhaoyan, open Rehai.
Yue Qi and Zhu Yu are bonded by blood.
Her blood is the key to removing the Bloodbinding.
Smudge the blood on Shuo Xuan and injure her
so that she enters the Core of the Demon Realm for treatment.
Yue Qi's blood and the power of Rehai
will remove the Bloodbinding between Zhu Yu and Mist Soul.
Zhu Yu's Vitality Energy will decrease rapidly
and that's your best chance to kill her.
Mist Soul.
- Your Lordship.
Your Lordship.
What's wrong, Your Lordship?
Mist Soul...
is releasing the Bloodbinding.
Your Lordship!
Yue Qi, it's you who did this.
Shuo Xuan, go protect Her Lordship.
Leave this to me.
You go after Zhu Yu. Leave this to us.
Let's go.
General Lin Yuan, long time no see.
Commander Ge.
We've been dealing with each other for years, but we had to end up at this point.
Second Sister, just beat them.
- Go.
- Catch them!
Ying Xuwei.
I saw the weakness of Zhu Yu at Pureness.
The first one is three feet along the lateral line.
Second one is in the center of the dorsal fin.
Third one is at two feet on the pectoral fin.
My daughter.
It is your blood that makes it difficult for me to blood bind the Mist Soul again.
Your Lordship!
Why do I have sudden palpitations?
Report. Commander Ge is injured.
Keep an eye on the Kun.
Yes.
Since when have you been so selfless?
Having spent many years with you, I am naturally influenced.
Pretty good.
If Brother Hanjiang were here,
he'd be very pleased.
Of course.
Senior Uncle, you gave me your demonic power.
It's the punishment.
To be tainted by the demonic power you despise, are you mad?
Senior Uncle, thank you.
Qingfei. Qingfei.
Why is she so seriously injured?
Kun's scales fell down,
and we held them up, letting others go first.
And then, Second Sister and Lin Yuan pushed me away,
but she got trapped underneath.
I managed to dig them up.
Lin Yuan is already dead.
And Second Sister is also seriously injured.
Xiaoyuan.
- I'm here.
- I am okay.
Now hurry up...
Go...
Go monitor...
the situation of the Sea of Clear Skies.
But...
You go.
Young Lord.
Xi Luo, don't waste time.
Whoever wants to interfere with Her Lordship today has to die.
Go after Zhu Yu. I'll handle this.
Qi, let's go.
Zhaoyan.
Xian Qing.
Qi.
You shouldn't have come.
We come here with the hopes of many people.
No matter what, we will try our best.
In the face of ultimate power,
how is hope any different from despair?
As long as there's a glimmer of hope, there'll be a chance to survive.
Since we all just want to survive,
let's see who has the most skills to do so.
All right.
If that's the case,
then entrust your fates to your swords.
What is fate?
If you ask me, I am my own fate.
Qi.
Zhu Yu stimulated her inner strength and accelerated the transformation.
This is the best chance.
Mother.
Qi, hurry up!
Jinzhao.
Jinzhao, how are you?
I'm fine, let's go again.
Qi.
- Are you okay?
- I am okay.
No one can stop me.
Zhaoyan!
The curse is gone, but I don't have much Vitality Energy left.
Formation.
Jinzhao.
Zhaoyan.
Xian Qing, no!
Brother Hanjiang,
without your elixir,
I wonder what it's going to be like when I lose my thousand years of cultivation.
Zhaoyan, move aside.
♫  If I were to trek through the river of memories, what would I pull up?  ♫
♫  Would it be the joy or penetrating sorrow from the years?  ♫
♫  What do I hear? The laughter running through the Milky Way  ♫
♫  My heart remembers who you are  ♫
♫  Grasping this short happiness over and over again  ♫
♫  Unable to ask you to stay with me  ♫
♫  The stories force me to sit with my regrets, to try and reconcile  ♫
♫  Why do my emotions still have to pull at my memories?  ♫
♫  I search for you, I draw closer to you  ♫
♫  Like the tide chasing you  ♫
♫  I asked fate to steal the answer to the riddle  ♫
♫  If I use this in exchange, could you not leave?  ♫
♫  I had you, yet lost you  ♫
♫  Only to redefine our reunion  ♫
♫  That is the puzzle our past life laid out for us  ♫
♫  Where are you, who stood by my side?  ♫
♫  Leave the sorrow that aches  ♫
♫  Passing through the sea of people alone, after you left  ♫
♫  Arriving at the end of time  ♫
♫  That feeling of being at the end for a long time  ♫
♫  It's like the smile you left behind  ♫
♫  Lighting up my skies over and over again  ♫
♫  I open both hands and slowly become weightless  ♫
♫  Unable to hold on, I should let go  ♫
♫  Too afraid to ask, so I say I can bear it  ♫
♫  It's as if the story is complicated and you don't understand  ♫
♫  We constantly turn and look back because we can't let go  ♫
♫  I search for you, I draw closer to you  ♫
♫  Like the tide chasing you  ♫
♫  I asked fate to steal the answer to the riddle  ♫
♫  If I use this in exchange, could you not leave?  ♫
♫  I had you, yet lost you  ♫
♫  Only to redefine our reunion again  ♫
♫  That is the puzzle our past life laid out for us (the puzzle)  ♫
♫  Where are you, who stood by my side?  ♫
♫  There are things I want to say, but my memories are fuzzy  ♫
♫  As if I'm broken, almost drowned by the loneliness  ♫
♫  Asking you, can I see you again?  ♫
♫  Wandering in the sea of people, who will stop when passing by?  ♫
♫  I know that look in your eyes, firm and gentle (firm and gentle)  ♫
♫  Look at me, only look at me  ♫
♫  I meet you, I bid farewell to you  ♫
♫  Brushing past waving, without saying a word  ♫
♫  The longing hidden in my breath  ♫
♫  Gentle and tender as if it were you  ♫
♫  I miss you, I forgot you  ♫
♫  Trying to calm the confused emotions  ♫
♫  Watching you walk towards me determinedly  ♫
♫  I hear you calling my name  ♫