♫  Tearing up all the memories of the past  ♫
♫  Leaving no regrets behind to haunt us  ♫
♫  Exchanging a whole lifetime, just to go back again  ♫
♫  If I decide to let my guard down  ♫
♫  Will I give my heart to the wrong one?  ♫
♫  Daring to give, not fearing destruction  ♫
♫  Love is unwilling to lay dormant  ♫
♫  Unafraid of shaking Heaven and Earth  ♫
♫  Even though we're on different paths  ♫
♫  I have no complaints and no regrets  ♫
♫  Because you are the unsolvable riddle set by fate  ♫
♫  So I pray for a miracle  ♫
♫  The stars turn, even if consumed by time, I only hope to search for you  ♫
♫  Searching for that miracle called forever  ♫
♫  Until death, we'll walk all the way together  ♫
♫  Love is the most beautiful meaning in life  ♫
Our honored guests have arrived.
My sincere welcome.
I have been waiting for your arrival, Commander Ying.
You can resonate with Rehai.
I imagine you're one of the guardians of the Nine Springs.
Which spring are you the guardian of?
Mist Soul.
I met Physician Bian some time ago
and I had many questions to ask.
You're here for...
I... came for Rehai.
Commander Ying, you really are direct.
I heard the Righteous Martial Alliance wiped out the Qiyuan Sect.
The disciples mistook Miss Yue for Lord Ming.
Not only that. Something unexpected happened.
You're very well-informed, Young Master Luo.
It seems that Luo Zhaoyan has already told you about this.
The Qiyuan Sect was giving out Qiyuan Orbs
for Lord Ming to absorb energy.
Now you've destroyed the Qiyuan Sect.
Is it because you've gathered enough Qiyuan Orbs?
Since you've guessed the answer, why bother asking?
Not so.
There are many things I still haven't figured out.
Like the story between the Hengdao Sect and the Sea of Clear Skies.
And why you, as the guardian of Mist Soul, are so interested in Rehai?
To achieve better collaboration, please answer my questions.
I hope... we can work well together.
This is... the key ring of Rehai?
This key ring of Rehai is an important item against Zhu Yu.
It's made from the dragon bone of Guixu.
Back then Shennong forged the Rehai key ring with dragon bone.
I duplicated it to confuse Zhu Yu.
Interesting... The key ring of Rehai can be copied.
Cang Feng.
Keep it safe.
Cang Feng, you're also a guardian of Rehai now.
I appreciate it.
Next time we meet, we'll discuss how to deal with Zhu Yu.
I've agreed to side with you against Zhu Yu.
In exchange, shouldn't you show me some sincerity, Commander Ying?
I wonder if the way to remove the binding shows enough sincerity.
Of course, it can.
Bloodbinding the spring defies the will of heaven.
It can only be removed with the help of a kin's blood.
The closer the kin, the more likely it'll succeed.
Blood of a close kin.
There's yet another way.
The blood of the whole clan works the same.
Zhaoyan, you finally came back.
What's with that look?
Did you do something behind my back?
No, Maiming, Miss Ming needs a favor.
My master died.
I heard that the Nine Springs Dragon Pool can bring back the deceased.
I'd like to go there through Rehai.
Miss Luo, I'm hoping you'll help me.
Maiming.
The Dragon Pool has a sentry stationed there.
No one can enter easily.
Miss Ming, you don't look well.
Why don't you rest tonight and prepare to enter the Dragon Pool tomorrow?
Thank you.
Your friends have all settled in?
Thank you, Maiming.
I'll go see Xian Qing and the others now.
Zhaoyan, I need to speak with you.
You told the others about Rehai.
It seems that you consider them important partners now.
We've been through life and death. I trust them.
I don't trust anyone.
I only trust you.
You and that wolf demon... what's going on?
♫  One branch, two lifetimes of flowers  ♫
Zhaoyan,
I know you better than anyone in this world.
You can't hide it from me.
Maiming, I've never hid anything from you.
♫  Under the Chinese parasol tree  ♫
I don't know how I feel right now.
I've always said my time was limited,
I wanted to use that short time to help the Luo family thrive.
But now...
You have limited time because I took your life.
You disguised yourself as a man to protect me.
Do you really not resent this fate?
Don't you hate me?
Maiming.
I've always been steadfast in this.
I'd be lying if I said I'd never felt resentment.
But since it's decided that I can't live long,
I might as well focus on how to live a brilliant life.
It gives me more freedom to present myself as a man.
And I've made many friends.
I'm happy, Maiming. Really.
Then...
The fact that you're a girl... they know already?
They promised to keep it a secret.
In that case,
I don't have to keep pretending either.
Zhaoyan, I have a gift for you.
A gift?
Appreciate orioles among the flowers.
Appreciate a beauty under the moon.
My sister is such a pretty girl.
Then, can I change back into my clothes?
I'm not really used to this.
The ceremony is coming. Our clan people are returning.
It's nothing weird to see a new face.
Why don't you experience life as a girl?
Or is it because you don't like my gift?
Fine then.
Zhaoyan?
Zhaoyan, I saw you.
Don't come over here yet.
♫  Ripples appear again  ♫
♫  Seeking the determination in your eyes  ♫
♫  Feeling my palms warm from being near you  ♫
♫  In a blink of an eye, light and shadow both freeze  ♫
♫  Searching for you all over the place  ♫
♫  Following the trajectory of your heartbeat  ♫
♫  As the distance closes between us, my breathing rate increases  ♫
♫  Until the solution of the riddle becomes clear  ♫
♫  One embrace is enough for an answer  ♫
♫  One glance solidified each other's certainty  ♫
♫  How do I describe it clearly?  ♫
♫  Why do I only want you?   ♫
♫  Your smile melts away the difficulties faced on this arduous path  ♫
♫  This journey is all worth it as long as you're here  ♫
♫  I won't listen to any rumors   ♫
♫  I'm confident I only want you  ♫
♫  One embrace is enough for an answer  ♫
♫  One glance solidified each other's certainty  ♫
♫  How do I describe it clearly?  ♫
♫  Why do I only want you?   ♫
♫  Your smile melts away the difficulties faced on this arduous path  ♫
♫  This journey is all worth it as long as you're here  ♫
♫  I won't listen to any rumors   ♫
♫  I'm confident I only want you  ♫
Zhao—
Leave them alone.
Zhaoyan really is a girl.
Didn't you know that awhile ago?
I'm just not used to it.
I guess we can't call her Brother Luo anymore.
Let's just call her Zhaoyan.
You look beautiful.
Walk... with me.
Y-You're Miss Luo.
Since Zhaoyan trusts you,
I don't have to hide anything anymore.
I'm Luo Maiming.
"Miss Luo" became "Master Luo" out of the blue.
We have to get used to it.
Where is Zhaoyan?
She fell sick.
She's feeling unwell. She told me to get you into Rehai first.
How is she doing?
It's a chronic problem. She just needs some rest.
We know Zhaoyan.
She'd come to say goodbye even if she was sick.
I persuaded her to stay and rest.
What's wrong, Senior Uncle?
Why is Xian Qing gone?
Yes, he was right behind us before.
I bet he has things to deal with.
Let's head to the Dragon Pool first.
Yes, let's take care of Senior Gu's issue first and meet them later.
Let's go.
Zhaoyan.
Maiming! Maiming, what's going on?
Yesterday... a distinguished guest visited.
Guess what he told me?
He told me how to remove the Bloodbinding.
Really?
Back then, I thought I needed to just sacrifice myself.
But I ended up in an eternal prison,
constantly reincarnated and borrowing life from others,
living like a walking dead.
I know that. I know, Maiming.
You have endured torture and suffering from the Luo family all these years.
Is there really a way out now?
Yes, he said only the blood of the closest kin will work.
You... need my blood.
Zhaoyan, do you still remember
that you live and die with me?
I do. Of course.
But all you have to do is ask, Maiming.
Why did you chain me up?
Because you've changed.
You're not the same Zhaoyan anymore.
What's going on?
Intruders.
Are you the sentry of the Dragon Pool?
We're with the guardian of Pureness and heading to the Dragon Pool.
Please let us pass.
Guardian of Pureness?
There's darkness hidden deep down inside this guardian.
What is this...
- Miss Ming.
- Sister Ming Xiu.
Qi, hold tight to me.
Stay lost in the maze of memories forever.
Where is Xian Qing and the others? You didn't hurt them, did you?
Even now, you're still thinking about him.
Where are they, Maiming?
Don't hurt them. Okay?
I shouldn't have let you go to Luori Village.
Giving that wolf demon a chance to approach you.
- So you're targeting...
- Yes.
I'll kill the wolf demon.
Are you crazy, Maiming? Are you mad?
What? You're worried about him?
Maiming!
By the end of the day, you'll be back to how you were.
Xian Qing. Xian Qing, run! He's after you!
You're here.
Maiming. Maiming...
Maiming... Maiming!
Xian Qing, hurry, go!
Luo Maiming, you've always cherished Zhaoyan.
And she's done a lot for you.
I'm the one you want. Why do you have to do this to her?
We've been keeping each other company for years.
But now she only cares about you.
In that case, I might as well kill her.
You want to kill her? Did I give you permission?
Maiming! Maiming, let him go!
Xian Qing!
Maiming, please!
Maiming, please let him go!
I beg you, don't hurt him!
Xian Qing!
I-I'm here...
Xian Qing.
Wolf demon, if I apply a bit more pressure,
your life will be at risk.
Try again.
Xian Qing...
Xian Qing.
Xian Qing!
Mother, Uncle killed the demon already.
We're safe now.
Today... is... your birthday.
- I don't want to celebrate it.
- What a pity.
I only want you.
Mother...
Mother!
Mother, wake up!
Wake up, Mother!
Is that Miss Ming's memory?
Judging from what the sentry said,
we have to find the way out of here through your memory.
Miss Ming, what happened after that?
Sister Ming Xiu, avoiding it won't help.
Miss Ming, I don't know what happened back then,
but you were adopted by Senior Gu.
So your family...
What has happened won't fade away even if you choose to avoid it.
Shut up!
Miss Ming, earlier, when I was hiding in my room,
it was Senior Gu who told me to face everything with courage.
I think that's what he'd also say to you.
Mother.
Mother...
Why didn't you tell me you were hurt?
Mother.
Master.
Now I understand why Ming Xiu hates demons so much.
That's why you never celebrate your birthday.
Sentry, we shouldn't have barged into the spring.
But we also have no choice.
Please stop your hurtful trick.
This scene is from her memory.
I simply restored it.
There are all kinds of memories.
Ming Xiu had so many nice memories with Uncle Gu.
Why didn't you show those?
You're just a monster who spies on people's secrets!
Xiu'er.
You dreamed about your mother again?
Master, are there any spells to bring her back?
The best comfort for the deceased is to live well.
As long as the living inherit the wishes and beliefs of the deceased,
the deceased are in a sense resurrected,
and their lives continued.
What happened?
Where are we now?
Sister Ming Xiu is gone.
Wh-What on earth is that?
- So ugly.
- Joy, sorrow, fury, happiness: the four human sufferings.
I appear in the shape of human memories.
How I look represents people's minds.
Enough of that. Where's Miss Ming?
The guardian of Pureness holds too deep an obsession
to leave the maze of memories.
Let Sister Ming Xiu out.
If she remains immersed in it, no one can get her out.
Xian Qing! Xian Qing!
Xian Qing!
So naive.
With your skills right now, I can crush you easily.
And you want to save her?
There's another way. Would you like to try it?
I heard... that the demons can't live without their demonic orbs,
it contains all their cultivated energy.
I'm so curious,
why don't you show me your orb?
Maiming! Maiming! Xian Qing, no!
Xian Qing!
No.
The person who sets up the game is asking the pawn to make a choice?
The demonic orb and demonic power...
mean nothing to me.
If you want them, have them then.
Xian Qing...
To have someone to die for in this lifetime,
makes it worth it.
No, Xian Qing!
I heard that demons die very soon after they're depleted of their demonic orb.
Xian Qing... Xian Qing.
Maiming... Maiming!
Xian Qing!
Maiming! Maiming!
The removal of Bloodbinding is between you and me.
Are you planning to give up your life now?
You wanted my life, didn't you? Take it.
Why involve someone innocent?
So, right now, are you making this decision...
because of me or the wolf demon?
♫  Look at the sky, the leaves fall like rain  ♫
♫  It's me, scattering all my love  ♫
♫  The distance that can't be crossed is fate  ♫
Maiming, even if it's not Xian Qing,
even if it was Brother Yue, Miss Yue, or our disciples here, I'd do my best to protect them.
The only one you're willing to abandon... is me.
Maiming, I never thought about breaking my promise.
As long as you don't hurt anyone.
Don't you want freedom? I'll help you.
I beg you, please don't hurt Xian Qing. Okay?
As long as you want, I'll be how I used to be.
Maiming.
Are you trying to trade your life for the wolf demon's life?
It's not a trade, Maiming. It's not a trade.
I don't want you to make more mistakes.
Maiming, as long as you want,
I'll be how I used to be.
I will protect you like I used to, Maiming.
♫  I'm lost in you  ♫
♫  Leaving everything behind, only to search for you  ♫
Maiming.
♫  If love arises with the wind, how do I calm it?  ♫
Xian Qing. Xian Qing.
Xian Qing.
♫  The distance that can't be crossed is fate  ♫
♫  If love arises with the wind  ♫
Xian Qing...
♫  I've done my best, but our paths just won't cross  ♫
Maiming.
Leave.
Go back to your friends.
Never come back to the Luo family.
Maiming...
Get lost.
♫  The meteor streaks through the sky  ♫
♫  Burning what once was  ♫
♫  Forgetting its name  ♫
♫  Behind the mask are deep feelings  ♫
♫  Only visible through the eyes  ♫
♫  Who can see them clearly?  ♫
♫  I'm destined to brave all the dangers for you  ♫
♫  Even if fate cannot be escaped in the end  ♫
♫  Staking everything just to feel the resonance of our souls  ♫
♫  Leaving love with an unspoken explanation  ♫
♫  Seemingly random paths  ♫
♫  Traces of what's been burned  ♫
♫  Concealing all the secrets  ♫
♫  A story full of unexpected encounters  ♫
♫  All carefully arranged by fate  ♫
♫  I'm destined to brave all the dangers for you  ♫
♫  Even if fate cannot be escaped in the end  ♫
♫  Staking everything just to feel the resonance of our souls  ♫
♫  Leaving love with an unspoken explanation  ♫
♫  I'm destined to give my all for you  ♫
♫  Even if all my efforts go up in smoke  ♫
♫  Regardless of everything, I will love you deeply forever  ♫
♫  Leave behind evidence that my love existed  ♫