♫  Tearing up all the memories of the past  ♫
♫  Leaving no regrets behind to haunt us  ♫
♫  Exchanging a whole lifetime, just to go back again  ♫
♫  If I decide to let my guard down  ♫
♫  Will I give my heart to the wrong one?  ♫
♫  Daring to give, not fearing destruction  ♫
♫  Love is unwilling to lay dormant  ♫
♫  Unafraid of shaking Heaven and Earth  ♫
♫  Even though we're on different paths  ♫
♫  I have no complaints and no regrets  ♫
♫  Because you are the unsolvable riddle set by fate  ♫
♫  So I pray for a miracle  ♫
♫  The stars turn, even if consumed by time, I only hope to search for you  ♫
♫  Searching for that miracle called forever  ♫
♫  Until death, we'll walk all the way together  ♫
♫  Love is the most beautiful meaning in life  ♫
You... You have betrayed Her Lordship.
And the Yu Clan. Why have you come here?
Do you intend to wipe out the entire Yu Clan?
I came to find Shuo Xuan.
You aren't worthy of speaking her name.
I do not want to harm you.
You are not allowed to trespass the Sea of Clear Skies.
Young Lord.
Young Lord, please follow me.
What is going on?
Shuo Xuan, you...
After Her Lordship's true form fell into a deep sleep,
Shuo Xuan used Meditation Spell to replace Kun's consciousness
and control her body.
Yue Qi, you have finally come.
Why do you want Rehai?
Why? The reason lies above you.
Many of our people were injured in this battle and are recuperating here.
I cannot make decisions regarding Rehai.
But I will consult with Zhaoyan.
You must not.
Ying Xuwei, what are you here for?
This has nothing to do with you.
You shall not lay your hands on Rehai.
Then I will send Kun to the human world.
Don't.
Shuo Xuan, let's just tell them...
the real reason.
Her Lordship's consciousness has fallen into slumber.
Kun's body instinctively needs energy to heal the wounds from the battle.
Repressing this instinct alone has already exhausted Shuo Xuan.
Without the power of Rehai,
eventually, she won't be able to hold on.
So you want the power of Rehai to cure Zhu Yu.
Rehai can only provide temporary relief.
If Kun cannot complete the transformation,
your Yu Clan, including Zhu Yu, must enter the time stasis.
Ying Xuwei,
do you want to see a catastrophe in the human world again?
I have an idea.
Let's hear it.
I possess the bloodline of Kun.
I can provide my spiritual power to Zhu Yu to calm her instincts.
In this way, it will not affect the human world.
Have you thought it through?
Zhu Yu has been sleeping for ten thousand years.
Providing her with your spiritual power could be fatal to you.
At least you still have a conscience.
But I have a condition.
The sleeping Yu Clan will enter the time stasis together with Zhu Yu.
The awakened Yu Clan may return to the sea.
- Yue Qi, how dare you?
- Shuo Xuan.
To seize Rehai to treat the Yu Clan, we harmed innocent humans.
We cannot make the same mistake again.
Even if we lose,
our Yu Clan...
mustn't lose our dignity.
Young Lord.
I'm counting on you.
I'm also responsible for the Yu Clan.
Shuo Xuan,
I didn't fulfill my duty as the daughter.
After this is settled,
you should take over as the Young Lord.
Yue Qi, what do you mean? Apologizing to the Yu Clan?
Or did you realize they're your burden now?
Shuo Xuan!
I am Zhu Yu's daughter,
but I've never lived among the Yu Clan.
Shuo Xuan understands and cares for them more than I do.
She is more suitable for the role.
Commander Ying, what do you think of it?
I agree.
Then, we must trouble you to open the Mist Soul afterward.
Young Lord!
Thank you.
Ying Xuwei.
I will follow Her Lordship into the time stasis.
Shuo Xuan.
Entering the time stasis...
equals eternal imprisonment.
You are young.
If we migrate to the sea,
we can start over again.
Her Lordship is our savior.
I should stay by her side.
I'm also doing you a favor by accompanying Her Lordship.
From now on, we are even.
I am willing to follow Her Lordship to the time stasis.
You...
I knew it.
We Yu Clan are all fearless warriors.
Shuo Xuan.
Please take care of her.
She is also my mother.
Mother.
Xiaoyuan,
go back to rest.
Now, everything
is finally over.
At the grand ceremony, the drums will sound.
The flower will pass on. The dancer will be found.
Beautiful women will sing harmonious songs.
Spring orchids and autumn chrysanthemums
shall never cease...
through the ages.
Second Sister, your left hand is about to rust.
Second Sister.
If you don't wake up, mushrooms will grow on you.
Second Sister, do you want to go and bask in the sun?
I'll take you out in a moment.
It's finally over.
Yes.
The Yu Clan has entered the time stasis.
And there are no disasters in the human world.
This is the best possible ending.
You have been greatly weakened. You must rest well.
We've arrived at the western wasteland.
Do you remember, Young Xiu?
This is where we met Zhaoyan and Young Yue.
Back then, they were all with us.
Everyone, thank you.
Let's part ways from here.
Miss Yue, where are you going?
Will you do something foolish?
Of course not.
People meet and part like duckweed. Don't force it.
Young Yue, take care.
Xian Qing.
Zhaoyan.
Sister Ming Xiu.
You take care as well.
You too.
And you?
I...
I want to seek the art of eternal life.
Maiming borrowed my life before.
Although the curse has been lifted,
the lifespan he took from me has not been returned.
The time I have left is not much.
If I were to die like this,
even if fate allows us to meet again,
I certainly would not remember the time I had with you.
I will not accept that.
I will go with you.
And you, Young Xiu?
I'll return to Mount Yuqing. You can have the Yunlai Stone.
Young Xiu, take care of yourself.
You should take care of yourself as well.
Miss Ming, take care.
Goodbye.
If we miss Miss Ming,
we can go see her at Mount Yuqing.
But Miss Yue...
We'll meet again if fate allows.
We have witnessed how much Miss Yue has grown.
I believe she will follow her heart.
♫  A preface to the sorrowful wind. Unable to bear to see your tears flowing  ♫
♫  Unable to bear to see your tears flowing  ♫
♫  Piercing deep into my heart, it tears at me  ♫
♫  Instead why not take my doomed fate away  ♫
♫  The mirror reflects the shadows but remains invisible  ♫
♫  Like those hidden emotions, icy and piercing  ♫
♫  Using the lightest words  ♫
♫  To make the harshest decisions  ♫
♫  No different from a death sentence  ♫
♫  If you truly can bear to leave with the wind  ♫
♫  How come tears suddenly shimmer in your eyes?  ♫
Master,
I'm back.
♫  Even the embraces feel forced  ♫
During this time,
I've experienced a lot.
And I finally understood
why you had given up your life for the lives of others.
♫  If our next meeting is uncertain, don't eavesdrop on me in my dreams  ♫
Now, I think...
I've made the same decision as you.
Right.
As for Xian Qing.
This thousand-year-old wolf demon had no desires before.
But now, he also has someone he cares for.
That he could end up with Zhaoyan,
I think, is also a gift granted to him by the endless time.
Master,
your Xiu'er has grown up.
♫  If you truly can bear to leave with the wind  ♫
♫  How come tears suddenly shimmer in your eyes?  ♫
♫  What was thought to be evergreen withers between my fingers  ♫
♫  Even the embraces feel forced  ♫
♫  If the flowing water and fallen flowers are all fate  ♫
♫  Don't talk about who failed love  ♫
♫  If our next meeting is uncertain, don't eavesdrop on me in my dreams  ♫
♫  Humming that tune of lovesickness  ♫
♫  In the dream  ♫
♫  humming that tune of lovesickness  ♫
I'm an old person.
I will need you to take care of me.
Okay.
How is your health?
Fine.
I quite enjoy having you take care of me.
We should be near the place in the legend now.
This art of eternity truly left no trace.
We've been searching for days, but without success.
I'm afraid we've started this journey in vain.
The world is vast. We will find it eventually.
But I don't want it anymore.
Since it cannot be found,
I will cultivate alongside you to seek immortality.
How about it?
Are you sure about this?
Although this place is secluded,
there are countless creatures here.
These plants also seem especially lush.
Is this the nimbus you spoke of?
This is indeed a good place for recuperating.
Good. Then let's cultivate here.
But I have no strength left now.
I'm afraid I'll need you to help me up.
You've lost all your strength.
I guess you can't help me with my hairpin anymore.
Of course I can.
But do you really understand the loyalty of the Wolf Tribe?
We've been through so much. It's about time, isn't it?
I am already aware of your intentions from the stream of memories.
You wish to exchange the life of Yue Jinzhao?
Yes.
I want Jinzhao to come back.
If you have a wish, you must make a sacrifice.
You can only exchange for his life
at the cost of your existence.
Okay.
The so-called existence refers to all your memories
and the memories others have of you.
When your existence disappears,
no one in this world will remember you.
Okay.
Jinzhao, if one day, something happens to me, you must not exchange yourself for me.
Because I don't want to forget you at all.
Don't talk nonsense.
All my memories...
are my time with Jinzhao.
With him gone,
my memory is meaningless.
♫  Will I give my heart to the wrong one?  ♫
Jinzhao was smart...
♫  Daring to give, not fearing destruction  ♫
...and impressive.
♫  Love is unwilling to lay dormant  ♫
He was good at everything.
He should live longer than merely four years.
♫  Because you are the unsolvable riddle set by fate  ♫
I beg you.
Bring him back.
In this case, you already know the price.
The disaster Zhu Yu brought still lingers...
because I failed in my duty as the Mist Soul guardian.
I have failed the world, yet I am powerless to make amends.
I can only make it up to Yue Jinzhao and Qi.
Your life is already meager.
The life you exchange for is bound to be short.
♫  The memories fall and swirl backwards  ♫
♫  Only following the heart, never asking if it's right or wrong  ♫
If only there is someone else willing to exchange for Yue Jinzhao,
♫  Then now we could be intoxicated together  ♫
♫  Facing life and death together, unafraid  ♫
...she will come.
♫  No matter how hard it is to meet again  ♫
Use all my life and what she's willing to pay to bring him back.
♫  Because you are the unsolvable riddle set by fate  ♫
Since you've decided, we will start.
♫  The stars turn, even if consumed by time, I only hope to search for you  ♫
♫  Searching for that miracle called forever  ♫
♫  Until death, we'll walk all the way together  ♫
♫  Love is the most beautiful meaning in life  ♫
Will Jinzhao...
♫  It's a miracle  ♫
...really forget me?
♫  It's a miracle. Protecting you is the trace of my existence of love in this life  ♫
Second Sister, this dragonfly is quite pretty.
Strange.
I just can't remember who promised to make a hundred grass dragonflies for me.
Second Sister.
Wake up.
Come look for that person with me.
Second Sister. Wake up, please.
Eldest Sister.
Wake up.
Strange. Why am I crying?
Everyone.
Today, I'll tell you about the battle of Buried Wind Plains.
In that battle,
to save the common folk, the Righteous Martial Alliance fought bravely to their demise.
Everyone.
Do you know who is most worthy of mention?
Who?
The one most worthy of mention is the man who risked his own life to fight the evil,
Hall Leader Ju.
Hall Leader Ju?
You don't know him?
Let me tell you about him.
Boy.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry, Miss. I bumped into you.
It's all right. Be careful in the future.
Don't get yourself hurt.
That's right.
You are a brave young man. You need to learn to protect yourself.
Here, your toy.
Thank you, Brother.
Mister, have we met before?
I don't think so.
I see. Please excuse me.
Young Xiu.
After so many years, you're still as lively as ever, Senior Uncle.
It seems it's true that the bad ones always have a long life.
However, why did you ask to meet here?
It was my idea.
Back then, we used to boat under the moonlight here.
But I have yet to see the daytime scenery.
Channel Manager: sandia28
Chief Segmenter: kitty100
Segmenters:
sabrinafair, kazumi_oka, grace_g, rorar_589,
ma_xt_26, alessandrina, yura12, raycarneiro and matoon.
Chief Editor:  kakashiandme
Translation Editors: jadeheart &amp; xiaofengcanyue
General Editor: rajv
♫  Twinkling stars, dotting the surface of the lake  ♫
♫  The bright moonlight illuminates your tender eyes  ♫
♫  Hearing the gentle heartbeat by my ear  ♫
♫  I make a promise deep in my heart  ♫
♫  The blooming flowers sway, lifting my gaze, full of emotions  ♫
♫  Whispering softly, expressing our intertwined feelings  ♫
♫  Talking and laughing quietly through the endless years  ♫
♫  A gentle breeze strums the heartstrings  ♫
♫  A red thread entwined in our fingers  ♫
♫  We've witnessed blossoms and braved the rain and snow storms  ♫
♫  Each moment is hard to forget  ♫
♫  Those carefree and fearless looks that you and I had  ♫
♫  Each one carefully cherished  ♫
♫  How I wish to stand by your side  ♫
♫  To watch the sunrise and sunset, the seasons change  ♫
♫  The wind kisses us, wrapping around us continuously  ♫
♫  And you embrace me in your dreams  ♫
♫  How I wish to be with you  ♫
♫  Inviting a spring breeze to become an eternal vow  ♫
♫  I really wish the wind could hear our loyalty, desire and love for each other  ♫
♫  It's the wish, the only wish for this lifetime  ♫
♫  The blooming flowers sway, lifting my gaze, full of emotions  ♫
♫  Whispering softly, expressing our intertwined feelings  ♫
♫  Talking and laughing quietly through the endless years  ♫
♫  A gentle breeze strums the heartstrings  ♫
♫  A red thread entwined in our fingers  ♫
♫  We've witnessed blossoms and braved the rain and snow storms  ♫
♫  Each moment is hard to forget  ♫
♫  Those carefree and fearless looks that you and I had  ♫
♫  Each one carefully cherished  ♫
♫  How I wish to stand by your side  ♫
♫  To watch the sunrise and sunset, the seasons change  ♫
♫  The wind kisses us, wrapping around us continuously  ♫
♫  And you embrace me in your dreams  ♫
♫  How I wish to be with you  ♫
♫  Inviting a spring breeze to become an eternal vow  ♫
♫  I really wish the wind could hear our loyalty, desire and love for each other  ♫
♫  It's the wish, the only wish for this lifetime  ♫
♫  How I wish to stand by your side  ♫
♫  To watch the sunrise and sunset, the seasons change  ♫
♫  The wind kisses us, wrapping around us continuously  ♫
♫  And you embrace me in your dreams  ♫
♫  How I wish to be with you  ♫
♫  Inviting a spring breeze to become an eternal vow  ♫
♫  I really wish the wind could hear our loyalty, desire and love for each other  ♫
♫  It's the wish, the only wish for this lifetime  ♫
♫  Looking back upon the past  ♫
♫  Searching for that moment from the past  ♫
♫  Sincerely, I begin to write, our hearts connected  ♫
♫  It is destined to be  ♫
♫  My heart flutters silently  ♫
♫  The years leave no trace behind  ♫
♫  Beginning with the moonlight  ♫
♫  I fill the page with my memories   ♫
♫  All about you  ♫
♫  All my laughter and joy is because of you  ♫
♫  All my life's unforgettable moments are because of you  ♫
♫  The past glides by scene by scene  ♫
♫  How many smiles and tears  ♫
♫  fell because of happiness  ♫
♫  I bitterly search thousands of rivers and mountains  ♫
♫  Alone in the empty valley I hear my echo  ♫
♫  In the tranquility of this world   ♫
♫  I'm searching for your presence   ♫
♫  I'll spend the rest of my life with you   ♫
♫  Never forgetting this, I keep bitterly searching  ♫
♫  I hope to share the rest of my life's joy and sorrow with you  ♫
♫  Among the vast sea of people  ♫
♫  I engrave your name  ♫
♫  Never doubt, the steadfastness of my heart  ♫
♫  Wait until the wind rises and the rain ceases  ♫
♫  Wait for the long lost silence  ♫
♫  Wait until we are close   ♫
♫  And watch the North Star  ♫
♫  My heart flutters silently  ♫
♫  The stories leave no trace behind  ♫
♫  Beginning with the moonlight  ♫
♫  I fill the page with my memories   ♫
♫  All about you  ♫
♫  All my laughter and joy is because of you  ♫
♫  All my life's unforgettable moments are because of you  ♫
♫  The past glides by scene by scene  ♫
♫  How many smiles and tears  ♫
♫  fell because of happiness  ♫
♫  I bitterly search thousands of rivers and mountains  ♫
♫  Alone in the empty valley I hear my echo  ♫
♫  In the tranquility of this world   ♫
♫  I'm searching for your presence   ♫
♫  I'll spend the rest of my life with you   ♫
♫  Never forgetting this, I keep bitterly searching  ♫
♫  I hope to share the rest of my life's joy and sorrow with you  ♫
♫  Among the vast sea of people  ♫
♫  I engrave your name  ♫
♫  Never doubt, the steadfastness of my heart  ♫