YoYo English Channel YouTube
It's like, but it's not like.
It's like...
It's like the difference between this vegetable bun and meat bun.
Although they are all buns, the filling is different.
Brother Yue is smart and handsome.
Dr. Bian...
Anyway, in my opinion, they are not related at all.
Could it be that Miss Yue has met Dr. Bian before?
No.
Miss Yue, have you ever heard of Rehai?
Rehai is a secret. Don't talk about it.
Miss Yue, do you have any differences?
Very powerful, very smart. Is it counted?
What about these?
Then it's not there.
It's not easy to teach. This is the last time I ask you.
But I have one thing to ask.
I have a question.
I have one thing to ask.
Can I not tell anyone about what I asked you?
Why?
This is very important to me.
So please keep it a secret for me.
Don't tell anyone.
Okay, I promise you. Zhaoyan, you are very good to us.
As long as Jinzhao doesn't ask, I won't tell anyone.
If Brother Yue asks, don't tell him, okay?
No. If Jinzhao asks me, I will tell him.
Sorry.
The villagers asked me to ask about the disease.
I'm late. Are you okay?
No.
Zhaoyan, what's wrong?
Let me see.
Thank you, Dr. Bian. It's just a sprain.
Master Luo doesn't believe my medical skills.
Zhaoyan, let Dr. Bian see it.
Thank you, Dr. Bian.
Master Luo's condition seems to be not good.
It's okay. I'll just rest for a while.
Thank you.
It's okay.
There is nothing wrong with the body.
But the vitality keeps flowing out of the body.
This is the curse of the Tanhua Luo family.
Don't be so rude.
I told you, you heard it.
Dr. Bian said that when these patients wake up,
they will understand everything.
Don't be afraid.
If you don't believe Dr. Bian, you have to believe me.
Right?
I'm here. What's wrong with that?
Everything is ready.
Just wait for the fish to bite the hook.
Zinzhao, can this trick work?
Of course.
The appearance of the injured has attracted their attention.
Wei Lianyan should be the most awake.
They will definitely do something late.
Miss Ming, Senior Xianqing.
You're back from the funeral.
Yes. I'm old.
I can't draw the funeral.
We have found the place to live.
Let's go to pick up Luo Xun and Qing.
Look. I drew the map of the whole village.
What did you draw?
The triangular one represents the house.
The circular one represents the cave.
Where are we now?
This is where we are now.
This is Dr. Bian's house, right?
Yes. That's right.
Master, your drawing is really easy to understand.
Okay.
We will hide near the Bianluo Huan's house.
When they attack, we can capture them.
Brother Yue, I don't recommend you to attack in the village.
The sword is sharp.
It's not good if it hurts innocent people.
Then let's force them to the Linyang Road.
Brother Luo, Shi Fang, and Senior Xianqing.
You three guard the place.
Qi, me, and Miss Ming.
We will guard near the Bianluo Huan's house.
Okay.
I'll stay to protect Dr. Bian.
No.
No, no.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Jingzhao, you don't seem to want me to stay
to protect Dr. Bian.
No.
I just want to know if you can do it.
Can you do it if I can't?
Since everything is arranged,
let's go back and fix it.
Okay.
Let's go.
Dr. Bian, did we know each other before?
Maybe.
It's so sour when I think of Qi.
How can the Bianluo Huan be sour in my head?
It's so sour.
I can't do it.
It's so weird.
Jingzhao, do you have water?
I'm making a bath.
Close your eyes.
Why don't you close the door?
Why don't you knock the door?
Don't open your eyes.
Jingzhao.
Here.
Are you thirsty too?
Who?
Get out first.
Why should I go out?
Aren't you dressed?
Is there water?
I'm really thirsty.
Can you enter others' rooms
and be a good man in future?
You are not another person.
I want to cry
Li Zhao, you look like a little girl in a yellow flower
Really
The little girl in the yellow flower you saw in my drawing book
Lu Yuqi is exactly the same as what others saw
When they were seen
Not a brain-shamed Chen Lu
It's a bad luck
Look, look, bad luck
I'm crying again this year
Jin Zhao
Don't make me eat, I don't want to play with you
Qi
Will you do this
Shave someone's head
No
why
Because Zhao Yun has a sister
There are bean bags in the kitchen
Mingxiu has a husband
You are so pitiful
No one else is only me
I'm not pitiful
I still have myself
Hua Hua's daughter
Hua Hua, you are a head
Water is coming
Drink quickly
Comfortable
Come
Qi
Why do you like drinking water so much
Jin Zhao, will you make grass-dried butterflies
No
Why suddenly ask me if I can make grass-dried butterflies
In Dr. Bian's grass club
There are many beautiful grass-dried butterflies
I also want one
How can a man like a girl
Just changed things
Then I will ask Dr. Bian for one
When did you get so familiar with Dr. Bian
Didn't I tell you ten thousand times
Don't talk to strangers casually
I have always been very familiar with him
I think Dr. Bian and Jin Zhao
You give me a very similar feeling
So I think he is very close
Jin Zhao
abajo
Jin Zhao, what's the matter
He apologized.
He said we'll be friends from now on.
He's a good boy.
He's much better than his sister.
He asked me if I knew about the hot sea.
Hot sea?
How did you answer?
You told me to keep it a secret.
So I said I didn't know.
But Zhaoyan also asked me to keep it a secret.
Zhaoyan asked you to keep it a secret.
Why did you tell me?
I promised her I'd keep it a secret as long as you didn't ask.
But you asked me.
I can't lie to you.
You're a good girl.
Come on, have some water.
Zhaoyan, are you enjoying the beautiful scenery?
Senior.
No.
Are you worried about tonight's operation?
We have limited people.
If we fail tonight,
we'll be in danger.
We'll be in danger.
If we fail tonight,
Dr. Bian and that patient
may be in danger.
Didn't you decide
the result of the operation?
If you decide to
hesitate in the middle,
Zhaoyan,
you're a good person.
What you said
is like what a family member said.
Maybe
I'm a good person
just like what he said.
I haven't seen such an innocent person like you for a long time.
You're interesting and cute.
Cute?
Senior,
I'm not the one who says cute.
Only my first impression is appropriate to a president.
The first performance of the new recruit
and the second challenge of the new recruit
are the first interesting performances.
First,
We must not lose to Qi Yuan tribe today.
We must not.
Let's go.
Brother Luo.
I'm going to trouble you tonight.
You have to guard the bag of rabbits with me.
Miss Ming, Senior, and Shi Fang.
You are ambushed on the Lianyang Road.
After Brother Luo and I lure them over,
we'll beat them up.
Qi Yuan, you watch the road first.
Then the driver and we will meet.
If you meet a powerful opponent on the way,
don't be stubborn.
We'll run away after we beat them.
I've been waiting for you.
Mao Wei, they...
We're caught.
Retreat.
Go.
I'll protect this place.
Why am I feeling sleepy all of a sudden?
Why...
Why aren't they looking at me?
Why aren't they looking at you?
I'm so sleepy.
Look at my egg.
There's a demon.
I'm going to kill you tonight.
Miss Ming, don't.
The Hall Leader Yu is familiar with the demon.
Why are you helping him?
Miss Xue Xuan is a demon?
Come on, keep running.
Where's Shi Fang?
Little Shi Fang was caught by a demon.
I'll go take a look.
Wait.
I'm going to go check on him.
I'll go check on him.
Miss Xue Xuan, are you a good demon or a bad demon?
You don't deserve to know.
I'm not a useless demon.
I just don't want to fight with you.
Miss Xue Xuan, are you going to kill me?
You're a dead rat.
Why do I have to kill you?
Are you...
Are you really related to Qi Yuan Sect?
I really don't like the little sect of Qi Yuan Sect.
You're blinded by the people of Qi Yuan Sect.
That's why you do things that harm the innocent.
Why don't you put down your weapons?
Tell me who's behind it.
It's easy to make up for it.
Harm the innocent?
You dare to insult Qi Yuan's reputation?
You're not allowed to.
Brothers, kill.
You...
It's you.
Miss Xue Xuan,
if one day we fight against each other,
I...
I will definitely defeat you and lead you to the right path.
You really dare to think about it?
Just because of your broken mechanisms,
you dare to fight against me?
You deserve it.
And...
You're a good disciple.
We're not on the same side.
In the future,
in the future,
stay away from me.
Xu Fang!
How are you?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Miss Xue Xuan didn't kill me.
Xue Xuan?
She's a demon?
She's gone.
Last time, she cared about Qi Jiu a lot.
This time, it's her again.
Next time I see her,
I must ask her.
Let's go and find Brother Luo.
Oh no, we're exposed.
If that person kills us,
why don't they tell us?
Liu Huo He!
You're a coward.
I'm the one who's watching Qi and Yue Jin Zhao.
Not you.
Do you think I'm willing to watch them?
Last time you reported in Jin Cui Zhou,
you've already aroused Yue Jin Zhao's suspicion.
If you dare to interfere again,
I'll be rude to you.
Let's go.
Bai Cun My Little Brother
Xie Shan Shu Yuan
Weeshan
How come I fell asleep?
Dr. Bian.
Let me see.
Are you okay?
That's good.
What about him?
He's about to wake up.
What about Jinzhao?
Why haven't they come back yet?
Could he be in some danger?
As expected.
He's awake.
He can't do without me.
That idiot.
Jinzhao, are you okay?
How could I get hurt so easily?
Zhu. Zhu.
Zhu.
My son.
Master.
You don't look well.
Are you hurt?
No.
I just saw a lot of people died.
I just wanted to catch them.
I didn't expect to force them to die.
I caused their death.
Master Ju.
As the leader of the Zhenwu Alliance,
you're afraid of these people
who use demons to kill demons.
I'm not afraid.
It's just that
they're all living people.
It's you who killed them.
It's them.
Master.
You're evil.
They're the ones who died.
How dare you question me?
You're planning to
harm people.
It's them.
Uncle Ju.
Listen to me.
We came here
because we knew
it might be the base of Qiyuan Sect.
The people who died
are the people of Qiyuan Sect.
So they deserve to die, right?
No.
We wanted to
lure them out and catch them.
But we didn't expect them to kill themselves.
Why don't we go to their house
and check it out?
See if there's any clue.
Brother Yue, don't say anymore.
I'm in charge of this.
It's my fault
that I couldn't stop them from committing suicide.
Everyone.
I'm willing to bear your sadness and anger
on my own.
You bear it?
You want them to come back alive?
Yes.
They're back.
You...
Xiao Zhao Yan.
Don't talk to them.
Yes.
Everyone.
I'm afraid
you're the heroes of Zhou Wu.
Why are you out here?
Are you okay?
I'm much better.
If you don't explain the situation,
the heroes can't escape.
Everyone, listen to me.
My name is Lang Mo.
I'm from the Mammut Fort.
I came to do business in Yunhui Castle.
The people of Qiyuan Sect
beat me to a pulp.
Then they locked me up.
There are many people
who were locked up with me.
It's them.
Impossible.
I don't know what happened to them.
Everyone.
Go and save them.
Are you telling the truth?
I swear on my life.
Okay.
Fine.
I'll let you
take a look at Zhu'er's room.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
Lang Mo.
I'll take you to the grass room.
I can go back by myself.
Mr. Luo.
Go.
What's going on?
They made a secret room.
Jingzhao.
Do you think there are Qiyuan Pearls here?
I don't know.
Xiu.
What's this?
This is a mystery herb.
I've been practicing it for a long time.
I remember when I was in Fujin Hall,
I found this kind of herb.
It seems that the mystery herb of Qiyuan Sect
is made of this kind of herb.
Although it tastes very light,
it does taste like this
in the house of the Dragon-Eye.
You mean...
Unless it's freshly spread,
otherwise,
it's hard to smell it.
Besides,
I've never heard that
the Chief Qi has this kind of herb.
Qi.
Did anything wrong
with the Pellet Ring last night?
Last night,
I fell asleep in the grass house of Dr. Bian.
So you don't know
what he did.
You suspect that
the Pellet Ring made Miss Yue fall asleep on purpose.
Xiao Yue.
Move forward.
Okay.
Xiao Yue has been in the grass house for too long.
There are several bodies on him.
I can't tell the exact smell.
Well.
Did we think too much?
Maybe it's just that Xiao Yue is too tired.
I also think that Dr. Bian is not a bad person.
He even helped us save Lao Mo.
Those disciples
said something interesting before they died.
That person will kill me.
It means that the person who ordered them
is now with us.
And this Pellet Ring is really powerful.
The people of the Yellow River can't be confused.
Let's pretend that we don't know anything
and observe it.
Let's go.
Go.
Go to Dr. Bian.
Hurry up.
Are they still alive?
Let's take them out first.
Let's split up.
Let's take action.
You guys take them out.
Qi He, Shi Fang and I
will stay here and continue to search.
This box
looks quite special.
This is a mechanical box.
Let me try it.
Be careful.
Push me.
Qi He.
Xiao Yue.
Qin Chao.
Let Dr. Bian and Xiao Yue see it.
Qi.
Take this medicine and give it to him.
It can temporarily suppress the poison.
If you hesitate,
he will die.
Shi Fang.
Come on.
Please.
Dr. Bian,
how is he?
The situation has stabilized temporarily.
What do you mean temporarily?
If it wasn't because you broke in,
Qi wouldn't have come back.
If anything happens to him,
I will never let you go.
I don't want anything to happen to him either.
Qin.
I want to drink water.
You should rest.
I'll take care of Qi.
Then...
Let's go out first.
Qin.
Water.
Here.
Mr. Yue.
He is really your sister.
Your reaction
is not like a normal brother.
The two of them seem to be a pair.
Not like a normal brother.
Why is Dr. Bian
so sad?
Doctors are kind.
Miss Yue is seriously injured.
She is a doctor,
but she can't do anything.
This kind of feeling
should be like a normal brother.
You are right.
Miss Yue is seriously injured.
She is a doctor,
but she can't do anything.
This kind of feeling
is like those disciples
committing suicide in front of us.
We can't stop them.
But they are gone.
Mr. Xianqing.
Why didn't I see you just now?
The box was in the room.
Do you want to see it?
I just care about Miss Yue's injury.
I forgot about it.
Let's go together.
You go first.
I'll wait for you.
Let's go.
Is Dr. Bian
worried about Yue's injury?
As a doctor,
I can't detoxify her.
I might be wrong.
If those disciples are not dead,
and Xiao Zhaoyan and others
follow the pattern
and get the antidote,
Yue won't have to suffer
this kind of trouble.
Dr. Bian,
do you think so?
Mr. Xianqing seems to have a good idea.
Time Flies
The shooting star in the sky
burns the past
It's all my plan
It's my destiny to bring you the truth
Even if the ending is hard to tell
I will give you a chance to exchange a little bit of my life
Leave it to love, a shameless explanation
It's my destiny to do my best for you
Even if the effort is not enough
I will give you a chance to exchange a little bit of my life
Leave it to love, a shameless explanation