The Taoism Grandmaster
Episode 18
Let's eat.
Okay, wait a minute.
Hurry up.
What do you want to eat, Shifang?
Which one do you want to eat, Shifang?
Or this one?
Sir, what would you like to eat?
Let's order when everyone is here.
Okay.
Xiao Zhaoyan, sit.
What are you doing?
I'm giving flowers.
Jinzhao, come and eat.
Sir, order please.
Coming.
Dear guests,
do you want to order the mixed or the plain one?
Or the plain one?
The plain one, please.
No need to look.
Order the best dish here.
Okay.
Wait, two dishes.
Sir,
there are mosquitoes and spiders in your restaurant.
Let the mosquitoes get rid of the bugs.
Yes, yes.
Okay.
Xiao Yue, Xiao Yue.
Didn't you say you wanted to make the tofu buns burn?
This is the paint I designed last night.
Look.
Dr. Bian is in a good mood
as a prisoner.
This flower is called night incense.
When the flower blooms, it takes its leaves into the medicine.
It has the effect of calming the spirit and nourishing the aura.
Brother Xianqing,
can I try it?
No need.
Thank you.
Look.
Here.
And here.
Excuse me.
Is the guest staying in the hotel?
No need.
Let's eat.
Xiao Zhao Yan.
Xiao Zhao Yan, you're not my master.
How is it?
It's delicious.
It's okay.
Just take a break.
It's not a good habit to be a wall.
You'd better stay and rest.
There are only three rooms left in the hotel.
You have to stay.
Xiao Zhao Yan is not feeling well.
I'll take care of him.
We'll go together.
Senior.
Sir, let me do it.
I'll do it.
It has nothing to do with me.
It's not up to you.
Shi Feng.
Follow him.
Okay.
Let's go.
Zhao Yan is in an emergency.
He's been so good all the way.
He's really the master of Luo family.
He was fine before.
He's been sick twice today.
Is he too tired?
If you like flowers, I'll give you something else.
This is not okay.
I'll take care of him.
Senior.
I need to talk to you about something.
Let's talk outside.
I'll go.
Stay here.
Don't play tricks.
Brother Qi.
Do you want some tea?
I won't accept
the false feelings of the enemy.
You've been staring at me.
Aren't your eyes tired?
This is also the task I'm assigned this morning.
I can only succeed, not fail.
Nan Min.
Zhao Yan.
Today, the curse has been cast.
You've been suffering again.
I love you.
You've been absent for a long time.
Aren't you going to seek the method of curing the curse?
You won't change your mind.
I won't either.
Xiao Zhao Yan.
I won't talk to you for now.
He's really hot-tempered.
Xiao Zhao Yan.
Senior.
I'm fine now.
I just have some problems.
I'll be fine after a rest.
Xiao Xiu is here.
Let her take a look for you.
Jin Zhao.
You can't say anything in your room.
You have to say it outside.
You're being too loud.
This fell from the
Bailong Huai last night.
It's the same as the way I braid my hair.
I suspect that it has something to do with your background.
No wonder I feel that
Dr. Bian is a bit like my master in my dream.
Qing.
Let's check on her.
Master Luo is weak.
You can rest well.
Thank you, Miss Ming.
Xiao Zhao Yan, you can rest well.
Thank you, Senior.
Xiao Xiu.
You seemed to have something to say.
I find that
Luo Zhao Yan's vitality is constantly losing.
It's like something is constantly devouring him.
Rather than saying that it's an old disease.
It's more like a curse.
Xiao Xiu.
The old disease is a disease.
It's not a disease.
It's a disease.
It's a curse.
Did the two dead demons
actually have something to do with the curse?
Also,
when I was trying to cast a spell on him,
I found that you spent a lot of your cultivation to give him.
Don't forget, Senior.
Twenty years ago,
I almost died for him.
Their cultivation has already cost me a hundred years of cultivation.
If I let him die,
I'm afraid I'll be a little bit unworthy.
Is it just that you're not willing to accept it?
You've been living as a wolf demon for a thousand years.
Why do you have to be so concerned about Luo Zhao Yan?
A thousand years of no desire,
I have to find something interesting.
This is your business.
It has nothing to do with me.
I'm just reminding you.
Don't take it on.
Let my master worry.
You're the one who pulled the trigger with Brother Han Jiang.
Why is there only one master
who is worried about it?
Miss Min, you're here.
Senior Xian Jing,
is Zhao Yan all right?
It's all right.
I just need to rest well.
What you want.
Thank you.
What is this?
Secret.
Let's go.
We can change shifts.
Don't forget what I told you before.
If anything happens, remember to use it.
Xie You Lin, Xie Shu.
Do you want me to make you egg noodles?
Go ahead.
Miss Yue,
do you want to play a game?
Okay.
Miss Yue's chess style is really unique.
Doctor Bian,
did you leave this at Luo's?
No.
It's not mine.
You're lying.
Jingzhao said
he saw the grass carp
fall from you.
Since you know,
why do you ask?
Because
you look like a person
I know in my dreams.
In my dream,
there is also a person
who can't see clearly.
He likes to
wear clothes like this
like you.
But in my dream,
he is very nice to me.
He taught me how to practice swords.
He taught me knowledge.
So I think
he is not my master.
Everyone has dreams.
If everyone
dreams like Miss Yue,
then life will be a mess.
Impossible.
I must have a master.
This is what my master gave me.
It's exactly the same
as your grass carp.
To you,
is your master important?
In my dream,
I feel warm
and close.
I feel like
I can be
a good person.
a very important person.
And more importantly,
as long as I find my master,
Jinzhao and I
can solve it.
Jinzhao.
Have you ever thought
if one day
your master really comes to you,
will you go with him?
It's destined that I will
fight for you.
Even if the ending is hard to escape,
I will exchange a little
of the time we spent together.
I'm so hungry.
Why hasn't Jinzhao come yet?
It seems that Yue has really been nice to you.
Good.
Jinzhao is a little cheapskate.
He's always
spending more money than me.
He always scolds me
and says I'm greedy for fish.
Most importantly,
every time I eat egg noodles,
he always steals my eggs.
Jinzhao,
why are you here?
You don't go in either?
Qi Yan, let's go.
Let's go out and eat.
I haven't finished asking.
Dr. Bian, tell me quickly.
Where did this grass-fishing fish
come from?
In our hometown, everyone changes.
The style is the same.
Jinzhao.
In the long, long cold winter,
warm and very considerate,
I invite you to watch the wonderful gathering.
Jinzhao.
Jinzhao, you're angry.
I was just kidding.
I still have a lot of things to do.
What are you doing?
But Jinzhao is very smart.
He can solve
all the big and small problems.
Jinzhao is very brave.
No matter what danger happens,
he can stand out and protect me at once.
Although Jinzhao is very petty,
as long as he has one copper plate,
he will buy me egg noodles,
show me the sea of flowers,
and the butterfly that can shine.
Jinzhao,
don't be angry, okay?
I'm not angry.
Why should I be angry?
You're lying.
You're obviously angry.
Then I'm not angry now?
How did you ask just now?
What?
Is Bianruohuan your master?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
You heard it just now.
The grass-bent fish is very common
in his hometown.
I should ask it myself.
The grass-bent fish can't prove anything.
Sister,
is it important to you
to find the master in the dream?
Of course.
We've been looking for the body.
What will you do
after you find the body?
Jinzhao,
you're so strange.
What do you mean by what I will do?
If one day,
you find the master in your dream,
will you go with him?
Have you ever thought
if one day,
your master really comes to you,
will you go with him?
I'm sorry.
I've had it.
Little Severalaps's
Sect 이게
胡自屿
小子
I just want to tell them that I miss them.
Do it yourself.
I'm fine now.
Don't delay the business.
I told you.
It's not a good habit to push the wall.
You need to rest more.
Rest...
I'm much better,
you go to bed.
I'm going to land.
I just saw
the moon has a beautiful color tonight.
My dad also have the same number as us.
Even you want to get married...
I want to go out and take a walk.
Xiao Zhao Yan, don't wait for me.
Go to bed early.
Add있는
Ningxiu,
are you hungry?
I think 119.
What happened?
Jingzhao asked me just now
If I find the master in my dream
Will I go with him?
How did you answer?
I don't know
I never thought about this question
How did Jingzhao come to this?
I don't know
Why did Jingzhao ask such a strange question?
For important people
Maybe it's easy to change
Where are you looking at the dog?
Wang Wang, Wang Wang, call me
I'll give you chicken legs
He likes spicy food
Really?
Really
Wang Wang, call me
I'll give you the most spicy chicken head
Why does the dog learn to bark?
Mom, mom, mom
Mom
You are so cruel
I hate spicy food most
Human is so young
It's so boring
Yes
Can human be as interesting as your little Zhao Yan?
Of course
Mom
Good morning, everyone
Morning
Little Zhao Yan
How did you rest last night?
I must have had a good rest
There was a dog that was watching the door last night
It was guarding the door of Master Luo's room
Senior Xing Qi, where did you go last night?
Why didn't you come back?
Sorry
Little Zhao Yan is still so polite
Let's go
Go
Stop
You want to escape? It's not that easy
You are so bold
How dare you take Master Sheng Xuan
Release him
I'll let you three go
They are seven now
Seven dogs
Master, is Master Sheng Xuan among them?
Master Sheng Xuan is one of them
I'm one of them
I'll kill you
But there is one
Xiao Xiu is naughty again
Get out of here
Master Sheng Xuan, we are here to rescue you
I called you Sheng Xuan
How dare you say you have nothing to do with Qiyuan Sect
You are lying
You are the bad guy of Qiyuan Sect
Miss Yue
Can you really tell right from wrong?
You brat, you have no eyes
Put down the knife
If you let her go, I can spare you
Otherwise, I'll let you know what is flying goose flying fire
Kill yourself
We agreed to disappear
Disappear
The king of medicine is also your king
You Qiyuan Sect caught so many people
What are you going to do?
You don't expect these disciples to save you
Doctor Yan, why don't you talk?
Seems to have something on your mind
Let me guess
Are you thinking
Why haven't the poison of the star incense on these guys yet?
You sprinkled star incense on the flower, right?
Look at this flower
This is the flower that Bian Long Huan just took
Is there anything suspicious?
I compared this flower and other flowers
This flower's pollen is obviously poisonous
Bian Long Huan is good at using medicine
Did he sprinkle these pollen?
Should be
And there is no mosquito in this inn
He specifically told the shopkeeper to light the wild grass
I'll take this boat to get some rest
Let him find out what the poison is
Can connect with the wild grass
Let him bring the antidote
Because this matter still needs to be announced to everyone
The combination of star incense and wild grass
Will make the person who is hit by it in one day
Once it is released, it will temporarily lose its power
It seems that I underestimated you
Okay, okay, okay, kid
Don't talk so much, okay?
You, you put the knife down, put it down
I will warn you one last time
If you don't release the Lord Shengxuan
I'll let you have no return
Please
Retreat, really retreat
Retreat
The seed of the martial arts is not self-explanatory
Please, everyone
Leave our third brother
Second sister, Yuan
You are waiting for them
So yesterday, Luo Xiong suddenly got sick
It's your birthday
Just to delay time
The combination of star incense and wild grass
Does it make the weak person sick?
Thank you for your advice, Dr. Bian
I will remember this chapter for Xiao Zhao Yan
Let go of my third brother
Yuan, don't forget your mission
Got it
Xiao Zhao Yan, how can you be so strong?
Be careful
Xiao Zhao Yan, are you running?
Senior, now is not the time to chat
We are also living and dying
I will kill you
Xiao Huan, let's go
Xiao Huan
Go
Bai Zi Lan
Senior
Don't be so strong
You can't beat him
You have to fight
Xiao Zhao Yan
I am a demon
Senior
Go
Jin Zhao
Senior