I would like to congratulate you on getting accepted
into the best law school in Korea.
Your intelligence and hard work have brought you here,
and you have now also become the chosen ones
to gloriously live your lives as law officers.
I always share a short saying, which is my life motto,
during my entrance ceremony speech every year.
Everyone, I just said it was a short saying.
You should clap when you hear things like that.
You're watching one's ability
to become brazen, which is the most important quality for lawyers.
Rudolf von Jhering, who published "The Struggle for Law," said this.
"One person has been obliged to battle and to labor
for another who enjoys and lives in peace."
Everyone, I'll be straightforward.
Will you live to battle and to labor?
Or do you want to live in peace?
Based on how you spend your days at this school,
you will be either obliged to battle or live in peace.
Don't get carried away by getting into this law school.
You must stay on your toes.
There are 30,000 lawyers in Korea.
Getting a lawyer license will not give you a comfortable life!
The director definitely has a presence.
I'm going to study really hard.
The speech was disappointing, and she totally misinterpreted the line.
My cousin who took the bar exam told me.
Jhering said that the purpose of the law is to bring peace,
and the means to attain peace is to battle and labor.
The life of the law is to battle.
Battling to bring forth the law...
- Kang Baek. Excuse me.
- ...is not a curse but a blessing.
"One person has been obliged to battle and to labor
for another who enjoys and lives in peace."
It means you should not forget that the peace you enjoy now came from someone's sacrifice,
and it encourages you not to stop working hard to walk the right path.
Why are you going that deep?
Just let it go.
She just wants us to study hard. That's a good message.
If I don't pass the bar exam... Goodness.
That will turn our peaceful life into a battlefield for sure.
Other people are living on a battlefield,
but can we say that there's peace just because your life is at peace?
Law officers are the last people to think so.
Sure. That's peace to me.
Attending law school is a way out of the proletariat,
and it's the only ladder that will bring me to the bourgeoisie.
- Mr. Revolutionist.
- Sorry, Kang Baek.
- Let's go and get some food.
- Starting this semester, I'm going to get a tutoring class from a lawyer.
If you want, you can join me.
What? Did you hear that?
Yes.
Back then, I didn't know she was your grandmother.
Sorry.
Don't be. I thought you were right.
You weren't upset?
So tell me.
You said the life of the law is to fight, Mr. Officer of the Law.
What didn't you understand?
Well, churches are unincorporated.
According to Article 275 of the Civil Law,
the assets of the churches belong to the members. I understood that part
but it confuses me when a church divides into two churches.
Then the Civil Law only considers this
as breaking away as a group or remaining in the original group.
Does it mean we can't consider this as a division of...
Guys, I brought... coffee.
I knew this would happen at some point.
Hey, I understand that you guys are young and all.
You guys can't kiss in this sacred study room!
- Nan Hee.
- Don't worry, I won't tell anyone.
You guys should be careful not to get caught.
I'll tell you a spot where you will never get caught kissing.
You should let your eyes rest from time to time.
You're reading on your days off too.
Gosh. I'm not scolding you or anything.
I'm just worried that you might read books all night.
"Maurice?"
That's a great book, and he was an excellent writer too.
Did you enjoy the book?
Yes,
but I couldn't read it again because it was heartbreaking.
But this book has a happy ending.
Well, it wasn't just about the plot.
Living as a homosexual must have been painful and lonely,
and thinking that he was only able to share his love through a novel
he couldn't publish when he was alive made me sad and pity him.
You pity him.
It really makes me so proud that you're always showing
interest in the socially weak.
You will be a much better law officer than me.
I don't think I can be.
No. I believe in you
with all of my heart.
Wrap up your reading and come to the dining room.
Let's have lunch.
Oh, don't let your grandpa see you reading this.
You know how he is, right?
He is going to throw a fit if he catches you reading this.
Don't take too long.
My beloved members,
no one is born homosexual.
Homosexuality is an acquired preference.
They either got addicted after watching gay porn
or were sexually aroused when they were kids.
That's when people become homosexuals.
In the Bible, homosexuality is considered an abominable sin,
and it says that they will be stoned to death.
However, in the Bible, as long as one repents from their sins
and decides to turn over a new leaf, everyone can be forgiven.
Take the sinner in Luke for example.
- When she asked Jesus for forgiveness...
- Are you all right?
He answered her with love, not punishment.
Yes.
Even if you committed the grave sin of homosexuality,
as long as you repent and come back to the arms of Jesus,
everyone including prodigals, murderers, and homosexuals
can be embraced with love.
That's the Christian way to live.
- Amen!
Amen.
A sin that will bring death.
Verse 13, Chapter 20 of Leviticus.
"If a man lies with a male, as with a woman,
both of them have committed an abomination.
They shall surely be put to death.
Their blood shall be upon themselves."
Leave.
Don't ever come back.
- Kang Baek.
- Leave.
It's over.
It's all over now.
- Don't do this.
- No! You stop this!
Just punch it with your hand.
It's nice. Isn't it?
We can make it as big as a face.
Right.
Make Italian food since we're having a visitor.
Well, Ms. Ham said she wanted us to make octopus gourd soup
and hot pot rice with pine mushrooms for dinner.
No. Actually, we received some excellent shrimps.
I will make bisque pasta and a pine mushroom appetizer.
You can make fresh pasta, right?
I don't have enough time to age it but I'll do my best.
Please tell the visitor that dinner is at 7 p.m.
- Sure.
- There's no need.
If you're talking about Kyung Yoon, he just left.
Already?
They have exams coming up soon. He came by just to say hello.
Kang Baek hasn't eaten anything lately.
I chose the menu for dinner without talking to you first.
I'm sorry.
Let's have Italian food for dinner as she suggested.
- Okay.
- That's fine.
I only told them to change it because the last time he was here,
he seemed to like pasta.
I would like some Korean food for tonight's dinner too.
You should prepare healthy meals Kang Baek likes for now.
Yes, I will do that.
Thank you.
I'll come down when dinner is ready.
Should I prepare a cup of tea in your study?
No.
I need to pray.
I must pray.
"When you pray, go into your room, close the door,
and pray to your Father who is unseen.
Then your Father who sees what is done in secret will reward you."
"Do not be like them,
for your Father knows what you need
before you ask him."
Hello. How may I help you?
I want to buy a birthday gift.
Is that for your girlfriend?
Yes.
This is the most popular piece this season.
It's a platinum—
This kind of design isn't...
Do you have one in a simple design?
Well, if you don't have couples' rings yet, how about a ring?
Pardon?
Oh...
The design is the same for both men and women,
and it won't be uncomfortable to wear it in your day-to-day life.
As it feels comfortable, many couples buy them for their wedding bands.
You can get them engraved without charge within the first month of your purchase.
I'll take them.
Okay. Do you know your girlfriend's ring size?
Well...
I don't.
I think the size might be about the same
or slightly bigger.
Then could you bring her here next time?
No. I can't do that.
I see. This is a surprise.
Yes.
You can exchange it for a different size within two weeks of your purchase.
I'll prepare a size bigger than yours,
so she can try it on first.
If it doesn't fit her, you can get it exchanged. How about that?
Sure. I'll do that.
I'll make sure the wrapping is done nicely.
I'm so envious of your girlfriend.
♫   A friend's voice   ♫
♫   from afar   ♫
♫   Will the turning train wheels   ♫
♫   answer?  ♫
You made it obvious that this was a targeted investigation
but you had to release the suspect before the 48 hours were up.
This time, you failed to file for an arrest warrant after the immediate arrest,
so the evidence won't be admissible?
- I'm sorry.
- An apology won't make this go away!
Without an arrest warrant,
even if there was consent, the evidence is obtained illegally.
We can't use any of the evidence from the cell phone!
How will you fix this?
I'm sorry.
We have no choice now.
Only charge him with animal abuse, and drop the other charges.
Let go of the other charges.
- Sir!
- Listen carefully.
I'm trying to clean up your mess.
You guys blew all the other charges like stalking and illegal filming!
The victim is dead,
and I don't want this case to get more attention.
This is very good news for you guys.
Starting now, you need to lie low and go along with the flow.
Okay?
There will be a disciplinary hearing,
so prepare for that.
A disciplinary hearing?
Wait. Him too?
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
Gosh. It's partially my fault too.
You didn't do anything wrong.
It makes me wonder if our mistake is that bad.
His lawyer just happens to be really good.
We were doing what everyone else was doing.
It was wrong that we did it because everyone was doing it.
We often make that excuse when we don't want
to be responsible for breaking the protocol for minor things.
The world has changed, but we stuck to our old ways of doing things.
That's our wrongdoing.
Sorry.
We should catch the culprit.
It's all good as long as we catch the culprit. Okay?
Gosh. I thought I was going down for this.
Look at this. I was just trying to get on the good side
of the prosecutors and the Blue House. Darn it.
They can't come to an agreement, so I'm in a tight spot in between.
At times like this, I should just play dumb.
There's nothing I can do.
Goodness.
Do you think the culprit of this case will be caught?
When there are so many people hoping that won't be the case?
I'm surprised that you wanted to see me in private.
It makes me wonder if I have become an important person now.
You are very close to Hye Ryul
and my ex-son-in-law,
so it never occurred to me that we should meet in private.
I hope you won't be offended by that.
After all, we will soon be in-laws.
"In-laws?"
Yes.
Ever since Ji Yi was young, it was you who always said
that you wanted her to marry my grandson.
Right,
but...
my daughter is only 25 years old.
She is just tall.
She is still a little kid.
I know
what's stopping you.
You must want to find the best husband for your precious only daughter.
Isn't that how you feel?
If she marries Kang Baek now, it won't be easy for the time being.
Right. She is like a delicate little flower.
She was coddled all her life.
While raising her, I never wanted her
to experience any unpleasant feelings like sadness and pain.
So if things get even just a little stressful, she can't take it.
Do you remember Moo Ryul's wedding?
You came to her wedding.
Of course, I remember. It was such a grand wedding.
It was just a year after Jusung's first search and seizure
since its establishment.
Was it?
Oh, right.
It was the talk of the town for a while.
Jung Chan Young was the head of the Special Department.
Looking back now, I don't know how he had the nerve to do such a thing.
He is not that gutsy.
He started his own firm after that. I hear it's doing very well.
Yes, it's doing really well.
Rumor has it that he earned more than 200,000 dollars in just three years,
then there are people like me who get a civil service salary,
even when they work themselves to the bone.
When I think about that,
it makes me sad that I have this job.
That being said,
I'm thinking I could help you become brave,
like Jung Chan Young.
What do you say?
Pardon me?
Whether it's a defense counsel made up of big-firm lawyers
or an in-house legal team,
it's all useless unless it's your own family.
Jusung finally realized it.
That's why they initiated the marriage talk with my family,
not some influential politician or business leader's family.
The tip-off Jung Chan Young received...
By any chance, was it...
No.
"I should just admit to giving the tip-off."
It's better to use that to have leverage.
I hear you wish to get into politics.
How much longer will you walk on eggshells around everyone and wait?
I can help you make it happen with this.
Can you think of anyone who can look into the secret?
Well...
That's...
You see,
this is the kind of family you're marrying Ji Yi off to.
The reason Gun Do has never gotten into trouble
despite all his frivolous antics.
Now, you know why.
The call can't be connected. Transferring to voicemail.
You're drunk.
Not enough to not understand what this means.
Are you sure?
Kang Baek
doesn't even care about me now.
My friend, who I confided in, is blackmailing me,
and to be honest, I'm falling behind in class.
My parents fight every day because I'm a failure.
- Ji Yi.
- I don't even know what I'm doing here.
Why am I holding out? What for?
I'm really exhausted.
I just want...
to forget about everything
for just one night.
Does this have to mean something?
Get some sleep.
It's dangerous to drive at this hour.
Kyung Yoon won't be back until around lunchtime.
If someone sees me, that will be more dangerous.
And...
I'm sorry. This won't happen again.
Then let me walk you to the parking lot, at least.
It gets really dark here at night.
Ji Yi.
- Let's talk.
- My answer is no.
What?
Your proposal. My answer is no.
I won't go to you.
I don't want to have to apologize to both of you anymore.
If you happen to see Kyung Yoon, can you tell him to call me?
He is not coming to class, and I can't reach him.
Why? Because of Kang Baek?
Are you afraid he will tell Kang Baek about that day?
If that's what this is about, don't worry.
I know that Kyung Yoon is discreet,
- but I feel anxious.
- No, that's not what I meant.
Kang Baek...
doesn't care who you sleep with, so you don't need to worry.
He doesn't love you.
- Stop.
- He never loved you
and never will.
I told you to stop!
I know that too, so stop!
I love him, and that's all that matters!
I'll just love him more to make up for it!
That's enough!
That will do!
Ji Yi.
I thought that would be enough too.
Turns out, it's not.
It doesn't work that way.
Kang Baek's friend stopped by while you were out.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Thanks to the visit, Kang Baek seemed to be in a better mood
but he went back to his room.
Don't worry too much. Everything will get sorted out soon.
- Really?
- Wait and see.
Oh, right. I forgot.
So it's not Yoon Gu Ryeong.
You sure heard that fast.
Even in this office, only a few people know.
Oh, please. It's what got me this far.
So clearly, you came here with a goal today.
I'd like to achieve my goal, but the thing is,
I do not know how much you love your son.
In other words,
it depends on what and how much I'm willing to do
for Kang Baek?
That's right. This time, the stakes are high.
I'm here to ask you for a favor that requires
strong determination.
You say it's not easy, straight up?
What a new approach.
The reward is worth it.
A murder case
is not closed until the culprit is captured.
The culprit,
I will give it to you.
All ready and set up just for you.
What are you saying?
I'm saying I'll make it look like an ordinary murder case.
For Kang Baek
to escape clean.
I don't know what you heard,
but Kang Baek didn't do it.
You've met him before.
- He wouldn't...
- You're right. Kang Baek isn't the culprit.
The culprit I'm giving you
is the guy who killed Hong Nan Hee.
Prosecutor Ko.
I mean, does the truth matter now?
Suspend the execution of Dolphin's sentence
for about three months.
I'm sure you'll come up with a good reason for it.
He said his body aches these days.
Suspension of execution for only the ones with late-stage cancer?
You're right. It's not easy.
Please hurry.
The procedure is complex, and you'll need Mr. Jang's approval.
He wants the payment in advance.
He said he was backstabbed by prosecutors many times before.
What are you getting in return?
You care about what I'm getting?
How delicate of you.
I might as well answer since you asked.
I'm planning to go independent.
It's been a while since I walked the prison wall.
(T/N: Crossing back and forth between the line of legality)
I got sick of watching others making money when I did all the work.
Mr. Han will be disappointed.
I'm not sure if he'll be disappointed
or if he'll want to kill me.
The call can't be connected...
I thought only special intimidation didn't apply.
Evidence for stalking and illegal filming must be in the phone.
We made a mistake.
We couldn't unlock the phone.
Even if we did it, it was inadmissible.
We can't use it anymore.
I'm ashamed.
Geez.
You came to my house on my day off, and that's what you say?
What about that punk?
Is it over now?
If he passes the bar exam, he becomes a lawyer, doesn't he?
I'm sorry.
Hong Nan Hee is dead.
She can't do or become what she wanted,
but the murderer's better off?
How...
How is that possible?
Yoon Gu Ryeong didn't kill Hong Nan Hee.
According to NFS' result, the iron pipe he was holding
had cats' blood. In fact, a lot of blood.
Multiple cats.
So?
Meaning he used the same iron pipe,
but he would change the weapon just for the murder?
That's awkward.
Conclusively,
he's left-handed.
The culprit is right-handed.
There are many who are right-handed.
So who's the culprit?
The call can't be connected...
Mr. Oh!
What?
Is there a problem with the warrant application?
No, that's been done meticulously.
I just heard about this.
- Hye Ryul.
- Yes.
About Yoon Gu Ryeong...
He'll be prosecuted for animal abuse, what he got caught red-handed on.
He won't be charged for the rest.
His phone is important,
but it became inadmissible. Nothing more can be done.
By the way, making the cellphone inadmissible evidence
because it contains no scene of the accident,
isn't that Professor Na's field of study?
Ladies and gentlemen.
Are animals objects?
If they are, why is that?
If they aren't objects, what's the reason?
Anyone?
Law students who argue that animals are objects,
often claim harming others' animals
should be considered property damage.
Come on. Answer the phone!
Answer it!
Are you okay?
Prosecutor Han!
Ah Jeong? Are you okay?
- Yes.
- Are you hurt?
- Get up.
- I fell from shock.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
My goodness. I'm really sorry.
Give me your phone number just in case.
- I'm really okay.
- Still.
Wait. I'm sorry.
Here.
I'm really sorry, Ah Jeong.
No, I wasn't paying attention.
Are you getting a call?
Yes.
If you feel pain later, make sure to call me, okay?
- Prosecutor Han.
- Yes?
Was that Professor Na who called?
Yes.
Are you here to meet Professor Na?
Yes. I should get going.
- Take care.
- Yes.
Prosecutor Han!
You love
Kang Baek more than him, right?
You'd do anything for Kang Baek, right?
That's what parents do.
What are you trying to say?
Nan Hee...
Professor Na killed her.
Nan Hee was seeing Professor Na,
not Kang Baek.
Are you happy that I'm gone?
Are you happy that I'm dead?
Yoon Gu Ryeong knew it too.
Even that they had a fight that day.
I wondered if I should tell the police,
but I couldn't.
I couldn't make Kang Baek the son of a murderer.
I didn't think he'd be able to bear with it.
I wanted Professor Na to turn himself in.
That's why I posted the picture online.
What picture?
The pictures of Nan Hee and Professor Na
lying in bed together.
It was wrong of me.
I had no idea people would gossip about Nan Hee so much.
That Professor Na would feign ignorance,
and even defend Yoon Gu Ryeong.
You'll protect Kang Baek no matter what happens, right?
Even if you have to give up on someone,
you are the only one
who can put an end to this.
Hye Ryul.
What is it?
Honey.
Just what is it?
What's wrong?
Do you
love Kang Baek?
Of course, I do.
He is our son.
Even if we get divorced?
Yes, even if...
Even if we get divorced,
he'll still be my son. Forever.
Then why did you do it?
Yoon Gu Ryeong
will be free of suspicion now, thanks to you.
Without a post-warrant, one's phone can't be used as evidence.
You know that.
You knew, but you still bailed Yoon Gu Ryeong out to save yourself.
While Kang Baek was struggling in the gutter,
you did that to save yourself!
That's not it.
If you had truly considered him as your son,
could you have done that?
A parent
is willing to sacrifice themselves for their child,
but what you said was all a lie!
When you said you loved me, it was a lie.
When you said Kang Baek was your son,
and that you cared for him more than anyone else, it was all...
No.
I know it's shameless of me,
but I meant it all.
I never...
My mom, Moo Ryul, Yoon Gu Ryeong, and Lee Ah Jeong.
They all know.
Ah Jeong
waited for you to turn yourself in.
She just couldn't make Kang Baek a murderer's son!
You care less about him than his friend does,
and do you possibly think you have the right to be his father?
How dare you say
that you love him and that he is your son?
Honey.
You don't think that's true, do you?
- I didn't—
- Why didn't you just have an affair with a random woman?
Then Kang Baek's friend wouldn't have come up to me
and told me about your affair!
You shouldn't have let anyone know in the first place!
Then... Then you wouldn't have had to defend Yoon Gu Ryeong,
nor would you have had to feel humiliated
to face my mom and sister!
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry even to apologize.
Kang Baek knows.
What?
He knows about you and Hong Nan Hee!
He knows all about it.
- I'm done.
- Eat some more.
I prepared this dinner with care.
I'm afraid I'll have indigestion.
Even so.
Let him do as he wants. He's not a little kid.
I'll go upstairs.
Since you're not a little child, start going to school again
and proceed with your marriage with Ji Yi.
If a wedding feels too much, get engaged first.
Father.
He's old enough to know what's right.
Yes, I better do what's right.
I'll be going. Excuse me.
Honey.
I can't watch him stuck in his room anymore.
He should know when to get over it and move on.
I love the scent. Pine mushrooms are already in season.
By the way, is Jang Il even willing to marry Ji Yi off to our family?
He's hardly in touch with me these days.
He is definitely trying to spare his bones.
He has made it to be the head of the Central District Office.
It's not that he is trying to spare his bones.
He just has a lot of options in mind.
Honey, don't be too harsh on Kang Baek.
He must be going through the worst.
Let's leave him be and keep him safe for the time being.
I'm worried he will stand on the brink of a precipice.
You just don't listen to what Kang Baek says.
He said he will do what is right.
It means he'll be investigated as a testifier
and turn himself in, like he said the other day.
He told me that he will be investigated as scheduled,
that he asked the police to come get him if he can't make it.
His marriage or engagement is not the issue here.
Why...
Why do you not listen to him?
Do you pretend not to know?
Or can't you hear him?
I'll tell Hye Ryul and Professor Na to come home soon.
Okay.
Let's gather again in the reception room in an hour.
We'll organize our thoughts until then.
- Hi, Mom.
- Are you with Professor Na?
Yes.
Hurry home. Kang Baek...
No, just come straight home.
We'll talk here.
Refusing to be investigated may not be the answer.
Let him cooperate,
and we'll have him plead the Fifth.
He is not in the condition to be investigated right now.
He must avoid it no matter what.
But he already made a call,
or do you want him to be taken like the actual culprit?
They have no evidence.
That is why they summoned him as a testifier, not a suspect.
If he makes a mistake during the investigation...
Hye Ryul, stay out of this from now on.
Professor Na will take charge instead.
- Grandpa!
- Someone unrelated is better.
I'm his father.
Are you blood-related?
You're unrelated here.
- Legally, I am—
- The law doesn't hold any meaning.
The reporters are everywhere. Find a way to be unexposed.
What?
Okay.
Hye Ryul, go to work and request a warrant.
Distract people's attention with Jusung's issue.
Don't let Kang Baek say a word. Not even a single word.
Do whatever it takes to do that, at least.
They say the rich thrive for three generations even if they go down,
but they also say not many of them last three generations.
Either way, it's decided within three generations.
Then, will the third generation be the end of this family?
Do you want it to be the end of you guys?
I'm sorry.
Honey, how did the talk go?
It's late at night. Let's go to bed and talk about this tomorrow.
Honey.
I don't know anything about the law but I'm still worried.
I was so shocked to read those online comments.
What do you mean?
They say Kang Baek was engaged to a rich girl
when he was dating the dead girl.
That he only played around with her.
They were gossiping about all that ridiculous nonsense.
I still have a headache, and my heart feels stiff.
You're tender-hearted as is.
Don't read such comments for the time being.
My law firm will take action.
It's about our great-grandchild. I can't stop minding it.
Honey.
You know how fast it spreads
when something is intriguing, groundless, and speculative.
Right.
If we push ahead with his wedding,
it will only give strength to this story.
When Kang Baek graduates, after some time from now, reconsider it then.
I understand the current situation but he is our only great-grandson.
I feel bad to marry him off in a rush like this,
and when he gets married,
I want to attend his wedding as a legal great-grandmother.
No matter how urgent it is, a great-grandchild shouldn't
get married before his great-grandmother.
Let's follow the order.
Oh, right. You're right.
It was you!
You did it!
What are you talking about?
I was out working all day and just finished the family meeting.
Of course, you didn't do it yourself.
That's not what you're like,
but Hong Nan Hee died because of you.
Look, Ham Gwang Jeon.
I may not be the best husband material
but don't frame me for murder.
It doesn't matter
whether you killed her or not.
Whether you admit it or not,
I must cover up everything you've done.
That's how things have been.
In the end, this is what you were going for.
You even gave her a scholarship for this, didn't you?
To get something on me.
I thought you realized
how scary one could get if they had nothing to lose.
You need to feed them as much as they wouldn't starve to death.
You need to keep them as warm as they wouldn't freeze to death.
Only then, do they become docile.
Otherwise, they attack you instead. Shouldn't you be aware of it now?
Is that why you never let me get too close to you?
To tame me?
No.
I fed you too much with too much warmth
that you've become oblivious as to who the master is here.
Is that why you're seeing Yoo Ye Hoo, that guy?
Because he is docile?
He has been true to you for more than 10 years.
So aside from everything else,
he is good at waiting for sure.
Don't describe him like that.
Then let me put it in another way.
When Hong Nan Hee died,
what were you doing?
Why?
Can't I accuse you of murder?
No.
I have an alibi,
although you won't be pleased to hear it.
There's no need to talk more.
Keep Kang Baek safe.
Then I will
keep your only son, Yoo Hyun,
safe.
Come in.
Take a seat.
Yoo Hyun,
something was omitted in your scholarship application.
This scholarship is from an outside organization,
so the grade must be converted into 100 in total.
I see.
I better submit it again.
You're better than my family.
What was that?
There are hundreds of students, but you're this attentive to me.
I thought I could have a talk with you at the same time.
As a director myself, I need to be aware
of whether my students are doing well at school
or if they're having any inconveniences.
I'm doing well.
From now on,
I'd like to do better.
Excuse me?
They say seeing is wanting. It can also mean
that you never want what you haven't seen.
Actually, I didn't want much in life.
But then,
now that I've joined the law school here,
I keep wanting to have more.
You better study harder then.
Of course.
However,
some things can't be gained through studying.
For example, what Kang Baek has.
When I see him,
I get angry without realizing it.
As his uncle,
I shouldn't feel that way about my nephew.
You...
Since when...
Well,
what about you?
Kang Baek. Does he know?
Of course, he is in the dark.
Don't worry.
I'm not stupid enough to play this big card recklessly.
Instead,
help me,
so I won't have to expose it,
so I won't get the urge to do it.
Will you?
♫   Why is the world turning a blind eye?   ♫
♫   I have to   ♫
♫   give it back  ♫
♫   If I take one last step   ♫
♫   I was going to give it to someone   ♫
♫   In the end, someone ended up getting it   ♫
♫   That pain that nobody wanted   ♫
♫   I can't even stop   ♫
♫   Because if I go one step further, it will end   ♫
♫   Countless twinkling   ♫
I should've told her, but I couldn't!
I was too scared!
Just what happened that night?
I killed Nan Hee. I'm going to turn myself in.
Now, there's only one thing we can do.
He was arrested.
Are you giving up on Na Geun Woo?
The murderer is in this family.
That man killed Hong Nan Hee.
We received a tip-off.
Liar. You're lying!
Let's stop now. Let's please stop, Mom!