- There she is.
- She's here.
- She's here!
- There she is.
- She's here.
The approval ratings show that you're on the rise for the presidency.
Any comment on the ratings?
You're investigating your in-laws, the Jusung family,
so some people say this is just a formality. What's your thought on that?
Some people believe you're disobeying order to cause a scene,
so you can use that to get into politics.
Any comment on that?
You and your husband are being discussed as presidential candidates,
and this will only make more enemies for you. Do you feel any pressure?
You could be the subject of an internal investigation.
You're more used to executing the law,
but has it crossed your mind that you might be on the receiving end?
As you're new to this, you will have to provoke people to answer you.
You can never ask questions to deadlock your target.
Aggressive questions are the best example of that.
That's the tip I always give to my juniors when I teach them how to ask the right questions.
At the end of the day, prosecutors also ask questions.
To conduct an investigation, we must ask questions and get the answers.
Think of it as a conversation.
If you can figure out the intention from the answers to your questions,
you can be as aggressive as you want toward your target.
But aggressive questions prevent the target from opening up,
so you lose a lot more than you can gain.
As you are clearly motivated, you will be a great reporter.
Bye.
Prosecutor Han.
- Prosecutor Han.
- Prosecutor Han!
- Hold on.
- Prosecutor Han.
- A comment, please!
Tell them to be on standby.
She's so annoying because she's always right.
You...
Hye Ryul, you know what?
I'm asking purely out of curiosity.
I would like to know the cause of all this.
This curiosity is killing me.
Okay? Go on.
Go on!
Oh, dear. I can only put up with you because I look after my health.
If I didn't,
I would have passed out. Okay.
Then answer for me this.
Has our agency become collateral damage for the fight between two sisters?
You can't get along with your sister?
Resolve your family issue at home. Why bring your family into my place of work?
You're making it very hard for me to do my job!
Are you pressuring me to stop investigating?
Look, Hye Ryul. How is this pressuring you?
Do you really think so?
I'm begging you right now, isn't it obvious?
Should I get on my knees?
I have to go see the Prosecutor General soon.
The prime minister and the staff from the Blue House are waiting.
Let's end the investigation against Jusung here.
This investigation is completely legal.
Why am I hearing about the higher-ups and the Blue House?
You really scare me.
After seeing you going after your sister's in-laws,
I'm scared that you might even go after your brother's in-laws.
Hye Ryul, you know that we'll be in-laws soon, right?
Your son and my daughter are dating, with marriage in mind.
You and I will be in-laws,
yet I'm down on my knees begging.
My gosh, Kang Baek never told me about that.
What? He didn't?
Come on in.
All right. Come on in, Won Kyung.
Sit.
Want it?
Okay.
I'm going to put an end to this nonsense today.
Clearly, you two still hold a grudge about your divorce,
but why are you trying to settle the grudge by making a mess at my place of work?
What are you doing right now?
I'm working right now.
Hye Ryul, hand over the Jusung case to Won Kyung.
- No.
Then there's only one other option.
Hye Ryul created this big mess,
and I need you to clean it up.
Back in the day, you used to clean up each other's mess at home.
Familiarity can be quite useful.
Better the devil you know. Don't you agree?
If you don't agree with this, I'll transfer you to an office in the countryside.
You have two options. Choose.
I'm going to sit in my own mess.
I'll cover myself in this mess even if it stinks.
Stay far away from me.
Sit back down!
So you're not going to let this go.
Don't tell me that you have the slightest hope that you will be the president. Is that it?
You must've liked all the attention you've been getting thanks to that pretty husband of yours,
so you're going to steal this opportunity?
Hye Ryul! Ms. In-law!
You need to fix this.
If you can't fix this and I don't get nominated or don't become an assemblyman,
I'm going to ruin your child's future first.
Why are you taking it out on me?
Must you ask?
I know you provoked her. You started this whole thing.
You asked if she could go after Jusung too!
That's because she acted as if she was the symbol of justice.
- I thought she was ridiculous.
- You'll find out how ridiculous...
I think of you.
Come on. Do you really think she started the investigation because of what I said?
We're talking about the Dragon.
Exactly, so you fix it! You gave her an excuse to do it!
Make that excuse non-binding!
You must know that crazy witch's weakness better than anyone, right?
Her weakness?
Her weakness...
Wait. Are you asking a father to give away his daughter's weakness?
I've done everything in my power to stop the Jusung investigation,
but she won't even budge.
You know what Jusung said?
They won't invest in new businesses or recruit any new employees.
They are even threatening us that they will restructure.
If I can't fix this, I'm going to be out of a job.
On top of everything, she is being discussed as a presidential candidate?
If Jusung does that, given how our economy is struggling,
the approval ratings will take a hit.
If it continues, peaceful change of administration becomes impossible.
Then if there were to be a bloodbath during that change,
will my daughter gain control over the administration?
Are you making jokes right now?
You're so sensitive.
By the way, you're not talking about my son-in-law whom you disapprove of.
Professor Na?
Well, he's all talk.
Once the game begins, I will just let him fall for all the traps he set up.
My job ends there with him.
They are in the same boat as they are married.
Why would you worry now?
It sounds like Hye Ryul's weakness is my son-in-law, Na Geun Woo.
Come on. Don't play that game.
Don't you know your own daughter?
If anyone was going to get in her way,
she would have gotten rid of them with the exception of her children.
Remember her divorce with Prosecutor Ko?
She already kicked her husband to the curb,
and it'll be easier to get rid of Na Geun Woo. Goodness.
My daughter is indeed extraordinary,
but still, her career is just taking off.
Why are you so worried about her?
Elections... are like the wind.
It's not a matter of Han Hye Ryul becoming the president.
The fact that she's bringing a new idea to my game is the problem.
Besides, does she think she can be the next president?
No. Or the one after that? Or will it be the one after that?
Even so.
It's only right to rid of any possibility from the get-go,
but you're her father, you can't trample on her yourself.
Let me sum up what you just told me.
Before my daughter poses a threat to the administration,
it sounds like you want to come after me, her father, first.
From olden times, the biggest threat to the throne was a smart heir.
I'm old and powerless now, so I have a humble dream
of living my life peacefully as a humble old man.
That humble dream is very hard to achieve.
I've never seen any former presidents achieve that dream. Not a single one.
My goodness. You're trying to scare me.
Oh, right. How is the Christmas Fund going?
Is it being handled nicely?
Pardon?
What did you just say?
If you don't know about it, that's a big relief.
That's the best news ever.
I'm truly relieved.
Hello, Prosecutor Han.
The two arraignment notices and three news articles, did you get them?
Yes. Right here.
All right.
I'll review them at home, wrap it up, and send it to you.
Tell Prosecutor Oh to check the inbox tonight.
Sure. I'll carry it to your car.
No, I can carry it.
- Work on tomorrow's investigation.
- Gosh, this is heavy.
I lift dumbbells to work out.
Goodness.
- See you tomorrow.
- Okay.
Come on, ma'am. You should take it easy.
Gosh.
Doors are closing.
Please let me.
Mom, I have something to discuss with you.
It's not easy to keep the investigation going.
You should talk to your husband regarding this case instead of me.
You should use him for cases like this. That tool.
The best skill a lawyer needs is reading the situation.
This skill of reading the situation can bring two different results.
Fight or flight?
Is the case worthy of your pursuit to take it all the way,
or should you admit defeat and focus on doing damage control?
You must be objective in reading these situations.
Of course, most lawyers...
deeply regret that they chose to fight.
However, even if you have to avoid fighting, you must be willing to learn how to take a punch.
So I plan to train you as fighters.
I will give you precedents to study. Write a report about defense strategies and have it ready by next Thursday.
You must fight for your client.
- Okay!
I'll prepare for next Thursday's class.
Oh, right. Hold on.
As for next Thursday,
I might have to attend a seminar,
so let's move it to next Tuesday.
- Okay!
- Yes!
- Nice.
As for the criminal code study group,
I just want the four of us to be in the study group.
Come on. Why would we form two separate groups?
This can help other students.
We should let the criminal lawsuit study group join us.
That way, we don't have to schedule sessions or rent rooms separately.
- It's more convenient.
- Right.
I want a smaller study group with top students.
Are you here to study or are you here to separate students based on grades?
Listen to yourself. Do you think this is a club?
Be objective.
It's true that we need to be on the same level to help each other when we study,
but we can't tell the other study group
that only the four of us will study the criminal code cases together.
Are you looking out for the whole group or just Nan Hee?
I wasn't going to say anything,
but why did you bring her to the concert?
What do you mean?
Why are you bringing up the concert?
Hold on.
I just don't get this.
Were you trying to get rid of Nan Hee?
If this is about Nan Hee, you can't kick her out.
Ji Yi, it should be you, if anyone.
- What?
- Why drag her into this?
Yoo Hyun, I can see right through you.
You want her to stay, but not Nan Hee,
and it's not about grades.
Forget about it! I don't need this study group.
You're all here. Shouldn't we go and study?
Let's study more later.
Wait.
What's this about?
Well, the thing is...
I...
Can I... I mean to say...
Can we...
I wanted to join your study group!
Our group?
I'm sorry, we already got pretty far with the curriculum.
I'm really sorry.
I see.
- But I have a bit more experience than...
- Let's go.
If you want, I can give you a summary note I put together.
Nan Hee.
That's from our study session.
No.
I put that together on my own and shared it with the group.
Right. You can do that.
I'll make a copy of that and give it to you later.
Can I really accept that?
You must have spent a lot of time on that.
It's no big deal.
I'll be happy if other people can find it helpful too.
We're not here to compete. We're here to learn.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
My aces! Where are you going? To study?
Do you need any help?
We're good. Thank you.
Wait.
I have some notes on the admissibility of evidence...
You can do it!
What are you looking at?
Seeking asylum in the 2020 bar exam.
Infectious Disease Control and Prevention Act in the 2021 bar exam.
Trends are reflected in the questions of the bar exams.
In my opinion, there will be a question about cryptocurrency.
Then we should definitely review leading cases of people who invested in Bitcoin.
We should review the revised act on reporting and using specified financial transactions too.
Yes. Did you read the article?
A while ago, the national treasury converted impounded Bitcoin to cash.
The amount increased by 45 times compared to three years ago.
It was 12.2 million dollars.
The price must have skyrocketed.
I should have bought some Bitcoin.
Seeing how you're studying the law, you've invested in the safest asset.
Is that so?
All right. Let's go back to our case.
When you look at the leading case, you must pay attention to this.
Unlike the existing precedents, they charged an additional fine
based on the market price when it was converted to cash.
So I listed relevant scholarly articles and added annotations on the last page.
- You should definitely read that.
- Okay.
A package?
Sorry. I need to make a call.
Hello?
Yes. Where are you?
I see. Okay. Enter the building and turn right.
Let me open it.
How beautiful.
I love it.
- Do you like it?
- Yes. Totally, I love it.
I mean it. You're the best.
Thank you.
I'm happy that you like it.
I do agree you have good eyes.
You look great in a suit too.
Is that so? Do you think I'll look pretty cool while training in the field?
Of course,
but you look much better naked.
Do I look like a fierce prosecutor?
Yes. If you're the prosecutor, I must plead guilty.
As fierce as Han Hye Ryul?
I guess she is one fierce woman indeed.
Then I'll be a sweet woman to you.
They were just here. Where did they go?
Hey!
It seemed this big to us.
How...
Goodness, this is crazy.
- Gosh.
- What?
What is going on?
Over there.
Someone...
Christmas Fund...
Christmas Fund, darn it!
What are you doing?
- Why are you bringing that up here?
- What do you mean?
You're making me anxious.
You can see this is just a suicide case.
No, it's not.
This is a murder case related to Christmas Fund!
Oh, come on.
What?
What is wrong with you?
Christmas Fund
safely passed through the eyes of the FSS  (Financial Supervisory Service) and prosecution.
Every single person in Yeouido
has heard the rumor that the Blue House has their back,
so why keep calling for trouble?
Didn't you read his dying note?
He lost all his money due to Christmas Fund.
He apologized to his family and wrote that he deserved to die!
All his life, he was a diligent and good man,
and he had to write that dying note.
How can you tell me to disregard it?
No, I can't do that.
Then what will you do?
I'll get whoever is at the top of that fund.
Even if you try, that person will slip through.
Hey!
- Me too.
- Gosh!
What are you doing here?
You go after murderers and drag them in handcuffs,
yet you got startled seeing me?
Murderers never prey on me.
Gosh.
Ms. Yoon, anything to drink?
That punk is a detective and he ran his mouth about my location
without any sense of privacy protection!
If others hear it, they might think you're a celebrity or something.
Wait. You have to pay first.
Oh, excuse me.
Here.
Come on. Pay for it.
These too.
- Now!
- Goodness.
- Did you scan this? I'll take it.
- Yes.
Darn it.
Aren't you going home?
Do your parents not care about their only daughter at all?
I need to get a result before next month.
Then go somewhere with a higher chance,
instead of chasing us around.
Your close friend works in the Information Division.
Could there be any info about Han Hye Ryul?
You told us about her internal investigation,
why ask me that?
Snap out of it.
She's the new presidential candidate and Na Geun Woo's woman,
but the office wants me to cook something
out of that info about the internal investigation.
Reporters are supposed to report what's true,
so why keep trying to make things up?
Was your dream to be a novelist, perhaps?
Be honest. Aren't you curious?
Am I the only piece of trash?
- I'm curious too.
- See?
Honestly, it can be a good story.
Whether or not, we're just dregs.
We live in a totally different world from people so high up.
What can we know?
You got the wrong person this time.
Finish your food, and hurry off.
Get lost.
You know Dolphin, right?
In the future, I want to run a convenience store,
so I can eat as much convenience food as I want.
And the store will be located in my own building.
You wicked girl.
Stop testing the waters!
Dolphin is the actual owner of Christmas Fund,
which recently became an issue.
Fund or whatever,
because of him, the victims are suffering and taking their lives.
Yet you're trying to bargain with this incident!
Tell me everything you know.
Darn you!
Get me what I want from your friend in the Information Division,
and I'll get you everything about Dolphin.
Where did they say Dolphin was today?
If arrested, he should be behind bars,
but he frequents the prosecutors' office instead.
Oh, really?
Keep going.
Are you treating your team to a meal today?
As if.
It smelled like tangsuyuk  (fried pork or beef)  and yusanseul  (seafood stir-fry)  too.
Let me join in.
Later. Much later.
What are you doing here? Go!
What are you doing?
You even ordered a drink?
What's gotten into you?
I'll sober up soon. Don't you worry.
Their yusanseul is very good.
I love their food.
Kaoliang liquor  (fermented sorghum wine)  is a must to have with Chinese food.
Come join me.
Should I throw you
someone not too small, not too big?
Let me start with someone as high as a chief...
from an office in Gangnam.
- How much?
- It's 60,000 dollars.
I even have a voice recording.
A voice recording too?
Goodness, take your time.
It's only the first trial yet.
I'm too frustrated to be in jail.
We have a lot of time left, so let's take it slow.
Mr. Ko.
How nice is it?
This is what you call catching two birds with one stone.
I help you make results and give you intel for your future career.
Right, I like it too.
I get to enjoy some fresh air thanks to you.
Darn it, I love it when it goes down my throat!
One hand washes the other.
It's what we call a win-win situation.
Why aren't you drinking?
What were you thinking that you got that surprised?
No, it's just that you suddenly showed up.
Gosh.
You don't have to check yourself. You're already cool and handsome,
so please look at me.
You're always cool too.
Look.
Ta-da! What do you think?
What's wrong?
No, it just seems new to me,
and you rarely wear a formal skirt.
Today's a special day,
so I asked Butler Yang to shop for an outfit for me.
I'll be showing off my beautiful legs, you see.
I'm giving a special speech to law school students today.
It's to look pretty for Kang Baek.
His friends will be there too, and I want him to feel proud.
Do I look like a charismatic prosecutor?
As you become a rising presidential candidate,
you're now rivals with Candidate Na, your husband.
Rumor says you have requested a warrant
against the vice chairman of Jusung. Is it true?
Is it true that there has been
outside pressure that you could be reappointed if you continue?
You usually enjoy wearing designer clothes,
and your outfit today seems expensive too,
won't you narrow down the gap between you and the people
by putting up a typical civilian act as politicians do?
Ms. Han!
She is posing!
Ms. Han, over here!
- Please look here.
- Ms. Han, here too!
Ms. Han!
Please say a word!
- Ms. Han!
- Tell us what you think!
- Ms. Han.
- Wait!
- Ma'am!
- Ms. Han!
Come in.
You came, son.
Hurry here and sit down.
Here.
When did you prepare all these?
I need to leave soon.
It's fine. It's just a cup of tea.
What would you like to drink? What do you like?
This is coffee,
and this is green tea.
I try my best not to run into Mom at the Prosecutors' Office.
I already go to where my grandma and dad...
Well... It's okay.
Feel free.
A lot of people find it unpleasant
that I'm a student where Professor Na teaches.
It's sort of a privilege.
As if.
You passed the exam and got admitted like everyone else did.
You're always too conscientious.
Like me.
Kang Baek.
Now that you're an adult,
let's meet up more often.
When you get married, I won't be able to see you anyway.
At least, before then...
I'm not going to get married.
What?
Why?
Because your mom and I got divorced?
No, this has nothing to do with it.
I just... have no intention of getting married yet.
Well, you're only 26. It's too soon to discuss marriage.
- I need to go now.
- What?
Already?
Okay.
Take these and eat them later.
I bought enough,
so share them with your friends.
Thank you.
Kang Baek.
Yes?
You're on good terms...
with Professor Na,
and that's a good thing.
Let your family love you and love them back.
That's only natural.
Don't mind anyone. Anyone at all, okay?
Okay, thank you.
Yes.
- Sir.
- Yes.
That's right.
What?
Your son will be coming to do the intensive prosecution training?
Wow, time flies.
Do you remember?
When you...
When your son got into SNU  (Seoul National University),
you ditched your afternoon trial so we could have a drink.
You were totally wasted and got naked.
Those waiting for the trial must've been frustrated.
I mean, no matter how much they waited, the judge didn't show up!
Of course, it was the Seoul National University, the trial didn't matter.
We couldn't care less about it.
When he comes to train, I'll make sure to dote on him.
Don't worry. Oh, right.
Look.
You still remember my daughter's internship at your law firm, right?
Okay, thank you.
This is how life works, right? Helping each other...
Wait, hold on. Ms. Han!
I'm almost done.
Hello? Yes.
Gosh, there's too much going on with the position I've been after.
Let's meet up for a drink soon.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Darn, do people think my office is for public service?
Why do they have so much business with me?
Gosh!
You can sit closer.
Just stick to the point.
Okay.
From now on, I'll be talking about Jusung.
No, wait!
I love your outfit today.
- That's sexual harassment.
- Okay.
Look at me. I'm on my knees. That was to butter you up.
Sorry.
I'll begin then.
If you hear this, you'll be tempted too.
I couldn't believe it at first.
Aren't you curious? Don't you want to hear it?
Jusung has offered CEO Yoo.
You know him, right? The right-hand man of Jusung's head.
They even helped him evade the hearing, their most favored guy.
What are you trying to pull here?
Plea bargaining, don't you know it?
That system is not accepted in Korea.
Don't be an amateur.
Ms. Han, without this source, the Narcotics Team can't take him down.
You want to try working there?
Look, that's about a criminal cooperating with an investigation
to reduce their sentence,
but in this case, it's just sacrificing CEO Yoo
to avoid getting arrested.
Look, they're family.
Family members do that to each other.
Getting arrested on each other's behalves.
Pushing one another to be arrested first.
That's what families do.
Has it never happened to your family?
You don't think it will ever happen?
Think wisely.
I'm giving you a chance.
Has it never happened to your family?
You don't think it will ever happen?
How could you do this to me?
How could you possibly do this?
Aunt, please calm down.
How do you expect me to calm down?
I'm about to go to prison!
This house. This building.
Part of all those is mine.
Taking it away from me wasn't enough
that you're trying to put me in jail now!
Father is still alive, so how could you do this to your older sister?
Older sister, my foot.
You were born out of wedlock, but I treated you with respect,
and you ungratefully siphoned off the money.
No.
I know nothing of it.
I'm telling you.
I only handled the taxes as your law firm told me to.
I really don't know anything. I...
Gun Do, say something!
Grandpa!
Is Grandaunt going to prison?
Can't you help her?
She's our family.
If she goes to prison, she'll be scared alone.
Please!
Grandpa, please help her.
Hye Ryul!
Take the girl upstairs!
Don't let her come downstairs until we settle everything here.
- Hye Ryul!
- Grandaunt!
- Mom!
Grandpa. Mom!
Spare me.
Help me. Please spare me!
You look graceful
in your outfit.
Why don't you look around some other brand stores
at the department store today?
Butler Yang.
You don't know what I'll be checking out today.
I'll be seeing some jewelry.
Just head to the exclusive shop as scheduled.
Do I have a place to run off from here?
Are you following me because I might hit it off with some other man?
Why don't you put an electronic anklet on me?
Madam, shall I bring your usual drink?
Yes, thank you.
There was another party tailing "A".
I think they are exclusively digging on "A" meeting "B".
Who is that?
I'm looking into it at the moment.
With so many bread crumbs,
it's not strange for others to trace the tracks.
But the schedule seems to be delayed than planned,
have you changed your mind by any chance?
Stop with the nonsense.
I'm the one who desperately wants to end this daily routine.
I apologize if I have offended you, Ms. Young Sun.
I think I told you not to call me by that name.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
I'll be back.
Thank you. Goodbye.
Here's your tea.
No, thank you.
I'm getting fed up with this.
I'm sorry. Shall I get you another drink?
Did we upset you by any chance?
Judge!
To save 6,000 dollars,
I endured only with pain relief patches,
without going to the hospital even when my body ached.
It's precious money that I've made in order to pay
for my grandson's college tuition fee.
I really believed that it would only take one month.
- Plaintiff.
- Yes?
Stop telling me this and submit it according to the right format.
Under the order of correction, if you do not correct this
by the next trial date, I will dismiss the case.
Gosh, Judge.
What do you mean by correction and dismissing the case?
I'm not smart and only learned how to read and write!
We will proceed with the next trial. Number 21-G-S-392015.
Darn it. All that for 6,000 dollars?
What is your sister doing?
She wants me to make an appearance, or else she'll apply for a warrant!
Han Hye Ryul, that wench!
Okay, you asked for it.
You came.
The students are waiting.
Are you handling the whistle-blower?
Yes, I'm being extra careful.
You need to make sure of it or they'll strike us.
Knock it out.
I heard that today is a special day,
so this was a favor I asked Professor Na.
It is a bit serious to lecture in front of students, isn't it?
Especially when we don't even have a suspect to fight with.
Then...
Here. How's this?
You look great!
Thank you.
Then, shall we start?
Many people think that prosecutors are people who beat up others.
It is correct.
"To beat up."
It sounds like something that is indecent and crude,
but I was surprised.
I thought it would be something close to cursing,
but it was a word in the dictionary.
Go ahead, search the word.
"To beat up."
First, "to tighten up so that the structure is not loose."
Yes.
A prosecutor must be someone like that.
Investigation and the safety of the vice chairman of Jusung
depends on whether or not we secure the evidence
to definitely prove it.
Did you check the internal documents on the plans for listing the stocks?
Yes, I have finished the investigation
by calling all the presidents of the subsidiary companies of Jusung.
The selected date fits perfectly with the announced date
of the listing plan considering the stock purchase claim period
and the period when the favorable factor has its effects.
We will subpoena the Vice Chairman.
Second,
"firmly supervise so that the job or words don't become careless."
The most important data shouldn't be saved on the computer or cloud.
Save it separately on a flash drive.
The facilities team came to fix some facilities in the afternoon,
and I don't have a good feeling about it.
Please check for wiretaps in my room tomorrow.
[Han Hye Ryul
Not being careless.
This is the biggest virtue that a prosecutor should have.
The most important thing when investigating a case
is to break down the case in detail and go through it one by one
without being careless.
You need to beat it up.
Now, third.
"To beat up furiously. To strike severely."
Only if we could,
everyone has someone that you want to beat up, right?
Right? Don't you?
Now, those people will never open their mouths without pressure,
apart from physical violence.
They must be furiously and severely taught a lesson!
So, you mean to say, you don't remember how this document was made?
No, I can't remember it at all.
Wait. Are you saying that you didn't get involved
in choosing this very important date of stock listing?
Are you telling me to believe this?
Then, how did this date come about?
We must have chosen an auspicious date.
Hey, knock him out.
On his daughter getting early acceptance from college,
on his son going to an Ivy League school,
on him getting funding from Christmas Fund.
Knock him out on everything.
Of course, there are things we must keep in mind.
If you beat someone up like this,
you should never approach it with self-conviction or emotion.
If you don't back it up with reasonable grounds
and objective yet solid legal justification,
you will also beat yourself up
as stated in the fourth meaning.
I have a question.
Yes, go ahead.
What do you think of those who ignore all circumstances
that are reasonable and objective, but have a conclusion ready
in favor of one side?
To be exact, the side that has money and power?
What is your opinion on those who fail to have an unbiased view
and fail justice?
Well, I can't deny that there are legal bodies like that.
They should bear the responsibility and pay the price for what they did.
According to your expression,
it is right for such legal bodies to have their lives beaten up.
Isn't that what it means?
You're truly great.
I know.
I really...
respect you.
Thank you.
I hope today will be a good opportunity for you
to experience the field work.
Thank you.
It must be nice to have someone like her as your mom.
Jusung would like to meet you.
Not now.
Even if they get prosecuted, the prosecutor in charge is my daughter.
That will cause a conflict.
Why would I step out when I can't handle it?
That will only cause a misunderstanding.
You see, if people misunderstand me after sleeping with someone,
I wouldn't be so upset.
But if people misunderstand me even before I sleep with them,
it drives me crazy.
That would drive anyone crazy to death.
You can't even appeal to the law.
Right. Things that we can't appeal to the law, that's most resentful.
All I have is money and law.
I'll buy time.
Yes. Time is money.
When one suffocates up to here, "If I die now,
all that money is worthless."
Then one finally realizes.
Yes.
Until Jusung is suffocated enough to show the whites of their eyes,
I will wait on it.
Hey.
You should've joined my family.
You'd make a perfect son-in-law.
Who would've known he was sly enough to steal my spot?
So you should've knocked her up first.
Because her grandpa is a fanatic,
this family never allows abortion or gay.
When he was in Supreme Court,
we couldn't even talk about anything against the abortion regulation.
What's so wrong with me being a fanatic?
Father, you should've told me you were coming.
Are you expecting me to worry about you in my own office?
I told you to watch your mouth at all times.
I will get going now.
What brings you here?
Because you weren't reliable.
Don't even think about calling Jusung.
Of course. I'd never do that considering the current situation.
Don't think it'll get you more money over time.
Is that how it works?
Now that I think about it, it makes sense.
You think I don't know you?
Jusung knows you too.
I turned them down when they called.
I can't take their case.
Father, they're still my in-laws. What will that make of Hye Ryul?
It's Hye Ryul's job!
Then think what's best for Hye Ryul.
Gwang Jeon is regretting her whole life for marrying you.
I can never let that happen again.
Only if Gwang Jeon wasn't a woman.
You never age.
Skincare technology is improving every day.
Your elegant speech is still the same.
Now that you have verified I haven't changed, tell me why you're here.
Yes.
I don't dare to be calculative in front of you.
I will be straightforward.
Please stop Senior Prosecutor Han Hye Ryul.
You're the only person who can persuade her.
Someone must've promised you a title.
A major anchor of a broadcasting station
gives up on staying neutral and volunteers to be a pigeon.
I'm not just a pigeon.
I'm also a blackmailer.
She should stop now.
That's best for her.
Director Yoon. This is purely my work habit,
but let me correct you because it bugs me.
There is a legal difference between threat and blackmail.
People often use "threat" and "blackmail" together to scare the other.
Blackmailing legally means an illegal act to gain wealth.
Money must be involved.
Unless you're here to extort money today, you're only threatening me.
When your greed to remain the same is too excessive,
it becomes an elder's greed.
I see.
An elder's greed?
That's defamation and an insult.
What are you doing here? You should've called me.
You're not happy to see me?
Because I wasn't expecting you...
What is this dress?
Are you a pervert,
or were you too lazy?
- That's not it.
- Then?
What were you thinking? Did you want to compare me?
That's really not what I meant.
Rip it.
If that's not it, rip it!
Piece of trash. Forget it!
It's trash!
- Nan Hee.
- I hate it!
Nan Hee!
Do you know how terrible it was?
What is this?
I'm sorry, Nan Hee.
This is wrong.
Yes. You're right.
You love me, right?
Of course.
No.
Say you love me.
I love you.
- You cannot enter.
- Move back.
- No photos are allowed.
Move back. It's dangerous.
- Is that the body?
- No pictures.
- Don't take pictures.
Stop taking pictures.
Hey, hey!
I told you to collect evidence, not damage the scene!
This is no sight to see. What are you doing?
- Stop taking pictures!
- No pictures please.
Before you get arrested
for defamation of the dead and obstruction of justice!
- Seriously.
- Please go down.
Yes. This way.
You're really determined to spread the word.
What is it that you really want?
Yes, we are all burning on the tide
Look, we are all burning on the tide
Who will be left in the end?
Yes, we are all burning on the tide
It's a game of the tongue
My heart is already on the floor
Who will laugh at the end?
On the shoulders of the giants like a blooming flower
Push the Christmas Fund case.
Investigate everyone, even the VIPs.
I'll make you pay for this.
The game has changed.
How dare you let them in here?
They're giving me shudders too!
Is this possible?
A scandal like this tends to go rampant behind the back of those involved.
I need Professor Na.
Are you by yourself?
Stop Prosecutor Han Hye Ryul.
Was the goal of your actions him all along?
You're the cause of all problems in this family.
Yes, we are all burning on the tide