Don't answer it.
Sorry, it's an internal phone call.
I'm telling you to not answer it.
People might show up at my office if I don't answer.
Let them.
Give me a second.
Yes, this is Na Geun Woo.
Yes, I know.
Yes, Mother. I mean, Director Ham.
Are you alone?
Yes, I'm alone.
I have new guidelines for your lectures.
Since I'm on my way out, I'll bring them to you now.
Right now?
Why are you so surprised?
Is there a reason I shouldn't be at your office?
No. I'm not surprised.
I can go to your office, but you offered to come here.
Okay.
Hey, you have to leave right now.
What do we do with this?
Do you want to stop here?
Nan Hee, let's talk later. We can talk about this another time.
What should we do with your clothes?
Get a hotel room tonight.
Nan Hee.
I won't leave unless you answer me.
Please, stop goofing around!
Nan Hee, please do something about your clothes first!
Get a hotel room.
Okay.
See you later.
You're here.
You've been coming home late quite often these days.
Am I giving you too much work?
No. It's just that I've been falling behind on work these days.
Is that so?
You should call it a day. Let's go home together.
I have some work left. I'll be home after I finish.
How much time will it take?
It will take some time. I'll be working until dawn.
I see.
Goodnight.
But make sure to finish it before coming home.
Don't drag it into our house and make a mess.
Come on. What is this?
Oh my.
How could anyone park like that? Come on.
What... Oh goodness!
Gosh. Hello, there.
What?
Darn it, you scared me! Goodness.
Gosh. You've been pushing papers at the Intelligence Division.
Look at you. You turned into a coward.
Hey, what are you doing?
I hear you guys spy on each other at the Intelligence Division.
That's because people are trying to dig out information from us,
so they are watching us.
I'm one of them.
I'm here to dig out information.
What?
Han Hye Ryul.
Senior Prosecutor at Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office.
You've been digging into her, right?
Why do you want information on her?
Give me something good about her.
So you can investigate Christmas Fund?
How do you know about that?
How do I know?
Because Han Hye Ryul has been investigating VIP's circle.
People connected to Christmas Fund.
I'll take responsibility for it. Push the Christmas Fund case.
No one is above the law.
Investigate everyone, even the VIPs.
So you have an exclusive report to give to us today.
You had reliable information. Correct?
Yes, that's right.
A board member of Christmas Fund
instructed someone to talk to the press and the prosecution
in the recording file I obtained.
The board member bribed someone from the Blue House
and asked to favor Jusung according to the recording file.
The recording file confirmed that the board member had received
a huge sum of money from Jusung and banks.
The public believed it was a good investment
and put their precious savings in this fund,
so they're facing a lot of damage.
What on earth have the FSS and the prosecution been doing all this time?
-  That's the biggest problem.
- Hey.
Were you behind this?
Was it you again?
You must have lost your mind.
Are you handing over your case files to the press now?
Why don't you set up a camera for a live broadcast in your office?
No. You know what? You're better off live-streaming.
"This is what I did today, and I'm doing this today."
"Here's what I'll do tomorrow."
Hey, get this. The tip came from the Special Department.
When did you have the time to investigate  Christmas Fund?
You're challenging me, aren't you?
This is a targeted investigation.
I should report you for violating the guidelines.
How dare you conduct an investigation with a target?
You're a mere senior prosecutor!
I'm investigating Christmas Fund because it's connected to Jusung,
and I didn't leak it to the press.
Are you telling me I did it?
I'm certain that the board member in question is Dolphin for sure,
but I haven't even listened to that recording yet!
You treated him to some Chinese liquor in your office,
but you failed to get some intel. You shouldn't say that out so loud.
What?
Are you seriously provoking me right now?
Darn it!
Do I have to watch a divorced couple argue now?
Han Hye Ryul, I'll make you pay for this.
Do you think you have the world at your feet?
You just watch.
Was it you?
Pardon?
That did come from our case file. Did you leak it?
No.
Prosecutor Oh,
I can't go out on a limb for you if I can't trust you.
Well,
the thing is,
I heard that the Intelligence Division of the Police Agency was doing an internal investigation on you.
I didn't want anything to happen to you.
I had to tell them something to get information.
I'm really sorry.
Hey, are you my brother or dad?
Even if you were my brother or dad, you shouldn't have done that.
Even if you were my husband, you had no right.
Everyone has their own part to play.
There are things you can't do for other people.
When I decided to follow your lead,
I was determined to risk everything I had.
Right. We might lose everything we have.
I appreciate that like crazy,
but only you can walk that path.
Do you know what that means?
I may be so grateful that you jumped in
but I can't walk that path for your sake, which I feel really awful about.
So leave it to me to walk my path.
But Hye Ryul, it's easier said than done.
Nothing is easy in life.
Let's be more careful, so this doesn't happen again.
And...
it's a bit uncomfortable for me to bring this up
because it feels like I'm intervening in your personal life.
That reporter. She's charming.
She's cute, smart, and passionate about her work.
She's an ambitious one too,
so she gets on my nerves a lot.
Prosecutor Oh, I trust that you can separate pleasure from work.
Seong Hyun, I'm so disappointed.
It's been a month.
How is this possible?
Are you the only prosecutor at your branch?
I'm a busy woman too, you know?
Gosh. I know that you're busy, Eun Mi.
I'm sorry.
Is it because of Christmas Fund?
- What are you talking about?
- You heard me.
Senior Prosecutor Han Hye Ryul is digging Christmas Fund.
Who told you that?
There's a detective going after Christmas Fund with laser focus.
A mere detective is digging the Christmas Fund case?
I thought even a mere prosecutor couldn't get to the bottom of it.
She's not just a mere prosecutor.
So she's different?
Hey, I'm sorry.
I have a report I haven't submitted yet.
I have to go.
There's an internal investigation
on Senior Prosecutor Han. It's from the Intelligence Division.
They're digging into her.
They must want to nip her in the bud.
Are you sure?
They are the most concerned that she's being discussed as a presidential candidate.
She's not like Na Geun Woo.
She's still a prosecutor. She has got the authority.
She's even willing to prosecute her in-laws.
It wouldn't stop her from going after politicians.
They can try all they want, but they won't find anything on her.
I know that for sure.
She's the cleanest prosecutor.
Do you really believe that?
Then what about Ham &amp; Lee law corporation?
They've got more problems than they can handle.
Being surrounded by minefields means she's standing on one.
Why are you following her lead? There's so much that can blow up in her face.
Seong Hyun.
I'm worried about you.
I'm happy that you want to follow a great prosecutor,
but things have changed. It's a different ball game now.
Don't you know how scary those politicians are?
This will only end when one of them is done for.
Let's be honest. She's got everything she needs,
but...
what about you?
Prosecutor Oh,
I trust that you can separate pleasure from work.
Gosh. It's so dry.
Seriously. We should have gotten cup noodles.
The hot broth will steam up the glass.
Are you trying to tell the world that we're on a stakeout here?
Having brothy food on a stakeout is a bit iffy,
or you should go out and have decent food. We'll wait here.
"Go out and have decent food. We'll wait here."
Do you think we're tour guides?
Why did you let her tag along, to begin with?
I can't let her wait outside on this cold day. She goes on TV.
I don't want you to catch a cold.
Fine. I don't want cup noodles. Okay?
I'm good.
I have a missed call.
Don't talk. I have to make this call.
Sweetie!
I didn't know you called.
You didn't tell me you would put it on the news like that.
No, I'm not in trouble.
She's in a tight spot now.
We have no definitive proof or any confessions yet.
Now that the cat's out of the bag,
there will be roadblocks for us.
Sweetie,
do you know how hard I thought about this?
This was the best scenario for you and Senior Prosecutor Han.
She needs to show people what she can do. That way, they can't come after her.
You guys are already going for it.
If you guys don't show it, people can come after you.
Sweetie,
did you think I would do something that could hurt your career?
Did you?
I'll keep checking on this.
Just give me information on Dolphin.
If you decide to go with Senior Prosecutor Han,
I'll root for you. That's a no-brainer.
Don't think about anything else. Just go home and get some sleep.
I'll call you again.
Okay.
I love you!
Senior, you've never seen a girl in a relationship before?
Relationship, my foot! You're totally using him.
Hold on a second, I should check your record.
This isn't your first time. You've done this before.
So what? Should I give up on getting intel on Dolphin?
Now, you're threatening me.
Your rap sheet seems to be quite complicated.
Aren't you hungry?
You must have been shaken up.
Did you watch the news?
Things are pretty bad, right?
The information leak was quite sloppy.
Now that the Blue House is mentioned, those in the power circle must have been shocked.
They will counteract now that they've seen your hand.
I wonder what they'll do.
They won't have a lot of options,
but among them,
they will find an option that can hurt us both.
Us both...
We're getting on their nerves.
We're too perfect.
Don't you agree?
All right. We're at your favorite tteokbokki  (spicey stir-fried rice cakes)  restaurant.
Let's think after we have had some food.
Let's get fritters and sundae. My treat!
What? Do you need more food?
Fishcakes too?
Honey, what about desserts?
Of course, we must have ice cream after tteokbokki.
Gosh. You're going to empty my wallet today.
All right.
Thank you.
Professor Na, I'm a huge fan! Can I get a photo with you?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Can you take a photo for me?
Okay.
Isn't it good?
It hasn't changed.
It's tasty.
Na Geun Woo.
No way!
What are you reading?
I really don't think this is right.
Nan Hee,
this is wrong.
Na Geun Woo?
He may look cool, but you can't do that to Kang Baek.
Not to a friend.
Maybe I shouldn't have told you this.
Forget what I showed you before.
How can I?
What you're doing is wrecking a family,
and what if the rumor spreads?
You'll suffer the most. You know that.
Na Geun Woo is a man,
so people might say he mistakenly got tempted by a female student,
but what about you?
What will you do?
Don't you want to become a prosecutor?
Ah Jeong.
You can easily find a decent guy.
Oh Seok Hoon, the hospital director's son.
I heard he had a crush on you.
Ji Eui Seong too.
The son of Law Firm Seungri's CEO. You know him, right?
I mean,
whoever you date,
it's better than dating your college friend's dad.
Ah Jeong,
you see,
I need Professor Na.
You need him?
Nan Hee, you...
Are you receiving
money from him or something?
Well...
Look. If it's urgent,
I'll get a credit line if I must lend you the money.
So stop this
before you get into serious trouble.
Or will you ruin your life for a few bucks even before you got to spread your wings?
It's not just about a few bucks.
Then just how much is it?
It's not about money.
I was keeping it from you in case you'd face harm for nothing,
but I guess I should explain.
Instead, don't get involved no matter what happens.
I'll take care of it all.
Pretend you don't know anything.
Okay?
Hey.
You're scaring me.
Promise me.
Okay.
It's a long story to tell.
If you look over there... Let me show you around.
Hello.
Why I need Na Geun Woo.
Why I must jump into that pit of fire.
Why I can never forgive.
Gosh, it doesn't taste good.
Ms. Yang, please take the dishes away.
Are you done eating already?
You heard me.
Yes, ma'am.
I ended up eating more because of them.
I already had 1,100 calories today!
Oh, my!
What... Come in!
Hey, hurry! Clean this up
and change the bedding.
I suddenly craved tteokbokki because of these kids,
but it wasn't as good when I actually had it.
By the way, if they put up a show with such an article in mind,
I must say they're impressive.
They're like celebrities being followed by the paparazzi.
Why won't you answer me?
You must find me easy to deal with.
Yes, that's right.
The others tiptoe around me and fake how they treat me
because my husband and their interests are on the line,
but you look down on me out in the face.
That's why I find you easy.
I don't have to fake my behavior either.
I'm trying my best,
but I guess it shows.
It shows so much that it's very offensive.
I'm worried you might end up feeling attached to me
while treating me at ease.
Go ahead and act up as much as you want.
Let's wait and see how long it will last.
Older Mi Ja and Younger Mi Ja will have to come up for the bedding.
Tidy yourself to act a bit coy.
You're so annoying!
Hello?
It's me. Just when will you come?
I know I shouldn't call you, but you have to understand me.
I can't stand it anymore.
It feels like a prison. No, even worse than that.
I know how it is to be in prison, and this is definitely worse.
I understand.
Okay.
Yes.
Hurry here.
Well...
Hello?
Oh, hello. How have you been?
It's always the same for me.
I'm sorry that I call you only when I need your help.
This time, I'm calling to inquire
about the Sentencing Commission's revision plan
to extend the limit and increase the sentence
regarding the industrial safety and health act's violation.
Excuse me. Someone's here.
Come in!
Sorry about that.
The Serious Disaster Punishment Act is to be enforced soon,
and I'd like to compare the sentencing.
It'd be of great help if I could have the organized minutes
of the General Conference.
Yes.
Thank you so much. Goodbye.
Moo Ryul, what brought you here unnoticed?
You're even going to meddle with the Serious Disaster Punishment Act?
What? Do companies seem to have things easy now?
Two laborers died again while working yesterday,
but the companies won't be punished as they have less than 50 workers.
The problem is, such companies
are the affiliates of big companies,
and plutocrats own 100 percent of their shares.
The law is too loose.
If executives receive a criminal punishment for a simple accident,
no one will be willing to run a business.
Moo Ryul, I believe you're saying this
as a member of the Jusung family,
but it sounds very dangerous for a judge's remark.
Look, Professor Na Geun Woo,
I'm saying this because I find it ridiculous to hear you
criticize businesspeople's sense of shame and responsibility
by mentioning this Serious Accidents Punishment Act.
You are not in a place to question if I'm qualified to be a judge.
It's not like we've been close in-laws,
and my sister is trying to trample on me for her intentions.
I doubt we need to keep manners,
so let me just stick to the point.
Your wife, Prosecutor Han Hye Ryul,
stop her.
You better not even try to decline.
Stop her no matter what.
Since you're a former judge, you must know from experience.
A conclusion comes first, and then you come up with grounds.
Tell her to stop investigating Jusung,
and use your skilled tongue to persuade her.
If she doesn't stop,
you'll be sharing this picture with the entire country.
Don't be too shocked.
A scandal like this tends to go rampant
behind the back of those involved.
I used to be quite close to Prosecutor Ko.
He didn't get paid much for his job, but he was nice enough
to give his sister-in-law allowances.
So when they wanted to get divorced, I came up to stop them.
Things were handled without much trouble,
so I didn't get why they still wanted a divorce.
Guess what Hye Ryul told me.
"Now isn't the problem."
"I don't want to have any future problems."
That's what she is like.
She never hesitates to cut off possible problems.
If this becomes an issue, you will get cut off right away.
Moo Ryul.
A professor's affair with his student?
You are not in the place to talk about ethics to others.
That's ridiculous!
- Honey.
- What is it?
- I'm sad.
- Why?
- You see...
- Hold on.
It's me.
I told you not to call me unless it was urgent.
What?
What are you talking about?
They are...
going after where?
Those people are unbelievable.
Prosecutor Ko, have you been planning this search and seizure?
Will you be searching and seizing through Mr. Han Gun Do's office too?
Aren't you burdened to go against your ex-wife's family?
- Please say a word about it.
- Let us through.
- Sir!
- Wait a minute!
- Please say a word!
- Tell us what you think!
- Mr. Ko!
- Prosecutor Ko!
What?
What did you just say?
How dare they try to raid here
when I'm right here?
Where is Gun Do? How dare these people...
Let me grasp the situation first. We're a little flustered too.
This means the court issued a warrant against us,
then the detailed charge or suspicion...
No one saw this coming?
Throughout the process of the prosecution's request and the court granting the warrant,
how could we have no idea?
I think they deliberately kept it from us.
Find out what happened and how.
Where is Gun Do, that punk?
Look. What are you doing in an empty office?
Please cooperate.
Look who this is.
He's my ex-son-in-law.
You shouldn't be this disrespectful in your ex-father-in-law's office.
The prosecution is not as powerful these days.
We only follow orders.
This is all thanks to your overly know-it-all eldest daughter.
No way.
She only acts up, thinking she knows it all. You know her very well.
No, I absolutely don't.
We'll take that desktop.
The desktop itself?
Are you sure you aren't unfairly targeting us to take revenge?
That's what the prosecution does.
This isn't even new.
- That's how you make money.
- Darn, that's not true.
I just slack off these days.
What happened has happened, so we'll stick to the standard tactics.
Do whatever it takes to arrest those runaway executives related to Christmas Fund,
and interrogate Dolphin to make a statement
about those mentioned in the recording.
I doubt we will even get to see Dolphin.
Mr. Ko is practically keeping him in his office.
I'll try talking to Mr. Ko.
Ms. Han, we have a big problem!
Take a look at this.
Today, the prosecution pushed ahead with their sudden search and seizure against Ham &amp; Lee law corporation,
the country's biggest law firm.
Being safe and unharmed under every former regime,
Ham &amp; Lee law corporation is said to be more powerful than the Blue House.
A lot of attorneys in Ham &amp; Lee law corporation are former prosecutors and high government officials,
and a lot of their former attorneys are high government officials.
Thus, it has helped them create a tight cartel with the government parties, prosecution, and legal circles.
That's why this search and seizure is considered an unprecedented act.
But behind the search and seizure, the eldest daughter of Han Gun Do, the current CEO of Ham &amp; Lee law corporation...
Most assume that this is intended to suppress Senior Prosecutor Han Hye Ryul of the Seoul Prosecutors' Office.
Also, her husband, Professor Na Geun Woo of Minguk University Law School,
is still an associate attorney of Ham &amp; Lee.
As this couple is being mentioned as presidential candidates, we can predict that this incident is a  signal
to go against both of them.
A card to go against both of us.
Pardon?
No, I'm just getting curious
about what they have found.
I'm just as clueless.
Prosecutor Han Hye Ryul's husband, Professor Na Geun Woo,
is still a part of Ham &amp; Lee law corporation.
It's assumed to be outside pressure against Prosecutor Han.
Honey, what is... What is going on?
I'm so astonished.
Honey, are you all right?
Don't be on edge. It's not good for your health.
How could they do this to Ham &amp; Lee? Is this possible?
Honey, I'm so scared.
Hurry home.
I need you by my side.
Yes.
Okay.
This is amusing.
Did they leave?
Did you defend yourselves with what the warrant stated?
They just left. Don't get me started.
As if they had installed cameras in my office,
they took everything that seemed necessary.
They came determined.
According to the warrant, there are suspicious circumstances in which the law firm takes on cases
within restrictive periods of former prosecutor lawyers, and that you handle such cases privately.
Do you perhaps have slush funds?
As if.
Your grandpa purposely opened an office to have influence over me.
He would never let me do such a thing. You know what he's like.
You idiot! You knew it, didn't you?
It was you, wasn't it?
Father, what are you talking about?
I'm their target. I didn't do anything!
How dare you let them in here?
They are giving me shudders too!
After what I did to the prosecution,
I had no idea they'd stab me in the back like this!
I don't know what you have up your sleeve,
but if it harms Hye Ryul even a slight bit, I will make you pay the price!
I will never let someone like you mess with Hye Ryul!
Hye Ryul is my daughter, Father!
Hye Ryul is my daughter!
If you think you can do something, you're deluding yourself.
Who are you to take care of her?
I meant that I wouldn't cause her any harm.
That's a given.
If they find anything about you during this search and seizure,
that will just be your problem. Got it?
Yes.
How dare you even speak of taking care of her, you stupid fool?
The problem is that you seduced my daughter into marrying you.
Mother,
this incident has nothing to do with our marriage—
Yes, it does!
It does.
I know exactly what you're like.
You're the cause of all problems in this family.
Order in some food.
We'll get started as soon as we finish eating.
- Yes, sir.
I'm sorry, but have dinner at the cafeteria.
I'll skip it.
Didn't you see what was written outside the office?
Only those involved are allowed in for security reasons.
I think I'm directly involved.
You're right about that.
You're way too directly involved
that coming into this office itself is worth a punishment.
What are you trying to pull?
That's my question for you.
Are you intending to violate every rule of investigation?
I thought you loved following rules.
Investigations take place closed-door. That's the rule.
If an investigation's security is intervened,
even before the indictment,
it could mean the suspect is trying to tamper with the evidence.
You know that.
Are you patronizing me about criminal law?
No way.
I could never dare to lecture you.
You are always placed first in everything.
I know how competent you are.
Stop with the gibberish.
Are you going to be unfair like this?
You talk about being unfair?
Then, were you fair yourself?
Are you saying that you were being fair and I wasn't?
Is that why you direct the investigation to beat up, knock up,
and batter based on facts of suspected crime?
Is that fair?
That's exactly why the prosecution goes through a reformation.
Hey, Han Hye Ryul.
You think you're the only fair one
since the world runs according to your thoughts and will, right?
What did you tell me when we got divorced?
Are you acting this way out of spite of our divorce?
Holding a grudge like this?
Do I look like a child to you?
Do you think I'd stick my neck out of spite?
You know, I put my neck on the line for this.
You and I have different paths,
but we have the same goal!
But if we have different paths, one of us has to fall out.
So, I'm trying my best not to fall.
What did I say during our divorce for you to act this way?
You don't even remember, do you?
Do you think I was entertained because I couldn't pay for my drinks?
I was there inevitably since those people gathered up like that.
What did you say when disciplinary action was being discussed?
I said I'd try to take care of it no matter what,
and you said you didn't want it to become a problem later,
so you wanted me to submit to the disciplinary measure
or quit myself, didn't you?
I mean, there would be no problem if you followed the rules.
So that you can succeed and I give up my job?
Well, you didn't do as I told you and idled your way until now.
You got what you wanted then, didn't you?
Sure.
That's why we got divorced.
Right. So, you're telling me
that divorcing me is what you didn't want.
Because you regret it?
Stop playing games with me.
Don't delude yourself.
You think you're so charming that men are helpless around you.
It's just that they don't want to fight a person with a bad temper,
and they are shaking over your background.
They just want to leech off on the amazing background of your family.
That's why I
became a fool trying to leech off on you.
Do you know that?
That tag is still dangling on me, darn it!
So you're acting this way to get rid of that tag?
This is disclosing the facts of a suspected crime
and leaking of investigation secrets,
but I'll tell you especially because you're my ex-wife.
You got rid of me, the father of your child,
shaking and worrying that the smallest things would go wrong.
How clean do you think
Na Geun Woo, the face of your family, is?
We'll find out.
Was the goal of your actions
him all along?
Then, do you think I went all the way there myself
just to lure out some old men?
Sounds like a good target.
Now, you look like a real prosecutor.
Yes, an investigation should be sexy like this.
That's how you get people's attention.
He is a bit sexy, isn't he?
And let me straighten this up.
I didn't divorce you because there could be a problem.
You were so unattractive as a person
that I couldn't live with you anymore.
You're so foolish.
But I must talk business before I leave.
I will leak how frequently Dolphin came to the prosecution service.
You won't be able to have Dolphin around anymore.
Now, it's under my jurisdiction.
What brings you here?
I was worried.
Are you all right?
It's embarrassing.
Is there a need to provoke him like that in this situation?
He will gradually be more offended.
I want him to be offended.
Excuse me?
He needs to lose his reasoning so that his judgment is blurred,
and his judgment needs to be blurred so that he will overdo himself.
And he needs to overdo himself so that there will be a weakness.
Even if I became an old man standing aside,
you got rid of my stay area without a word when I'm well and alive.
We don't have to work alongside together,
but it is a courtesy to give a word about these things.
This old man has become so useless.
Gosh. How could you say such a thing, Mr. Ham?
I came here straight away at your word
and am sitting here under your hands
like a puppy.
So, please do not be so upset,
and...
I have never forgotten being polite
in any situation in my life, so far.
How dare I
get rid of the stay area of the former Supreme Court Justice,
who had a leading role in the Korean Judicature?
I mean, how could I step foot without your approval?
Are you trying to drive a wedge between your family members?
Well, I'm not sure... where I saw it at the moment.
Maybe it was Sun Tzu's "The Art of War," or...
Sima Qian's "Record of the Grand Historian."
"Counter measures."
This is a great strategy
to destroy the enemy with no energy.
So, you're saying it's that jerk who brought you in?
Attack me.
Why are you all thinking of this in a difficult and complicated way?
Just attack me!
I think you need to say that more simply for us to understand.
Attack me. What's so difficult about that?
When you prepare for the news,
you pick up the most attractive one, don't you?
Ham Min Heon's son-in-law, Han Hye Ryul's father,
and Na Geun Woo's father-in-law. What better picture do you need?
Hey, Mr. Jang, work me up.
If you work me up, everything will be revealed!
When that jerk Na Geun Woo was a judge,
we brought him and used him as a butler and an attorney
when he cried over his father's debt. He used to clear up the dirt.
That dirt is still there.
I'll package that up on paper and hand it over. Take it all.
Who is he to nitpick about the illegal succession of Jusung?
If you want to be precise, he's the one who planned it.
That dirt probably is decayed and has maggots all over.
I'll organize it all on the computer and give it to you. Take it.
Search warrants exist to be used in these moments.
Gosh, how can I repay you for this?
He thinks the winning odds are with us.
Don't you think so?
Winning odds or what-not, I just don't like him.
Those nothing guys talk of culture and justice, my foot.
Who are they to discuss justice?
They must experience anxiety to know where they stand.
Bravo! Gosh, that's great!
Are you claiming that you didn't go there that day?
Prosecutor, it's not a claim. I really didn't go.
There are people who saw you that day.
Do you think that makes sense?
Somebody saw me?
Who are they? Bring them over right now.
I'm saying that I didn't go.
Who's saying that they saw me there?
Yes, Senior Prosecutor.
That's a bit difficult for me.
I just know how to handle computers a bit, that's all.
How can a virus spread all of a sudden?
Prosecutor.
Just a moment.
I know how to handle computers.
Yes, she's right.
If she digressed, she would have been a scary criminal.
- Hey.
- I'm right, though.
Yes.
Let's eat.
I might sound a bit old-fashioned,
but my heart flutters and I feel nervous sitting here.
Actually, I feel the same way.
Kyung Yoon, have you changed your mind to become a prosecutor?
What about the law firm?
Well, I'm still thinking about it.
Why isn't Nan Hee coming down?
She hasn't answered the text either.
She's working right now.
What work?
Well, there is a virus on my mom's computer suddenly.
She went to check on that.
Your mother?
How is your mother? Is she all right?
She first told me it was nothing and I shouldn't be surprised.
She called me to say it's no big deal,
though it sounds like a big deal.
She's amazing.
I was surprised to see the news.
I would've been scared to death.
You need guts to be a prosecutor.
I have my dad.
There he is.
Where's my princess?
Dad!
Hi!
- Let's go say hello.
- Okay.
There she is.
My princess.
I should think about working as a prosecutor.
I have no guts or a dad like hers.
Hey.
Professor Hwang!
Professor Hwang, do you need help?
No! I'm okay.
No. I happen to
have a class. I can help you.
Seriously. I said, no!
I just called you for some tea.
Relax and enjoy it.
And what happened today is up to the grown-ups to deal with.
You don't need to worry about it.
Still, you shouldn't have done that.
You should've told us. You knew it all along.
Why are you blaming me?
Prosecutor Ko was in charge of Ham &amp; Lee's search and seizure.
Uncle Won Kyung?
Yes. The chief prosecutor doesn't investigate himself.
The chief prosecutor only gets reported in his office,
and things like this must not be leaked
no matter how close we are or even if we were once a family.
You'll eventually become a prosecutor, so keep that in mind.
I can't believe Uncle Won Kyung.
Kang Baek, are you okay?
Yes.
What did Senior Prosecutor Han say?
- Did she tell you not to worry?
- Yes.
Right.
I know her from experience.
She's probably busy working
as if nothing ever happened.
You majored in computer engineering.
How did you come to law school?
There are people who deserve to die.
Becoming a prosecutor was the only way to beat them up legally.
I wonder how you're going to beat them up.
Are you like Senior Prosecutor Han Hye Ryul?
I'm going to finish them off.
I'm not sure what Senior Prosecutor Han is like.
You're more aggressive than you look.
Prosecutor Han may look tough outside, but is soft at heart.
- She's soft?
- Totally.
The juniors love her.
She's reliable and warm.
She's like a sweet big sister.
She looks different from how she actually appears.
Prosecutors are different from judges.
We don't just share joy and sorrow.
We literally live together.
Besides, an investigation shows who you are.
It shows your belief, perspective, and temper.
Senior Prosecutor Han is full of charms.
Professor Na Geun Woo must be very happy.
Prosecutor Han!
Yes, come in.
There's one student who didn't come back to the dorm last night,
and no one has heard from her since.
She goes to law school. A female student.
Collect the fingerprints.
When you identify the body, check if she's a student here.
♫  Take off the mask  ♫
♫  Why are you trying to hide it?  ♫
♫  Sing out your voice as sharp as an awl  ♫
♫  Reveal yourself  ♫
♫  Get out into the world  ♫
♫  Why do you want to hide?  ♫
♫  Tell me why  ♫
I can't let these jokers bring down Jusung or Ham &amp; Lee law corporation.
Go down alone.
I can't go down alone.
If we miss them this time, there won't be another chance.
Do you think it's prudent of us to go after Christmas Fund too?
Who are the higher-ups you're suspecting to be guilty?
Did you give her any advice on the Blue House search and seizure?
You are the only one who's there to comfort and care for me.
Reveal how many times Dolphin visited the prosecution service.
What do you think they found on the computer?
What if we don't disclose it and keep it to ourselves?
Should I hand it over to that crazy woman?
That won't work on the crazy woman.