Episode 5
I hear you still go around beating people up. Kang Soo told me everything!
Why did you want to see me? We would have seen each other at the hospital tomorrow anyway.
Something kept bothering me, so I wanted to first resolve it right away.
What is it?
Why do you keep on marrying me off?
I didn't marry you off. You're the one who did.
You've changed. Why do you listen to others and make judgments? I didn't get married!
Okay. You didn't. I want to leave now.
This girl.
I became determined, you see. At least to never get hit by you.
In a dangerous situation, the body reacts first according to how it was taught, by its habits, and how it practiced.
The body's daily habits are learned in your childhood.
Once those childhood years pass, nothing can replace them.
I give up! I give up!
Is this the mount position?
Yes. Could you get off now?
Yeah, sure. I'm sorry.
I was only thinking about winning. You aren't hurt?
I'm not hurt.
That's a relief.
You brat. If only you hadn't attacked, the mood would have been really pleasant and nice.
I'm not going to grapple with you anymore.
I'm not going to do it with you either. But why not?
Just because.
Ah, seriously.
Are you okay?
Wow, you've become way too strong.
Have you regained your consciousness?
As soon as she regained consciousness, I removed the intubation tube.
Why are you here?
I feel responsible for this woman.
What's your name?
That b*tch...
Can you understand me? What's your name?
Tell us your name first.
Oh... Young... Mi.
She's in a mental-drowsy state. It's okay.
Lift your right hand.
Lift your legs.
She can obey (follow directions).
You need absolute rest.
Administer 100mL of mannitol every 6 hours.
If her blood pressure is too low, there might be a risk of cerebral vasospasm and other damage.
- Approximate her systolic pressure to be around 180 rather than 160.
- Yes.
An aneurysm won't burst again, so don't be scared.
Maintain her stable condition using nimodipine.
If she says her head hurts a lot, then administer NSAIDs via intramuscular injection (IM).
If it still hurts, then half an ampoule of morphine.
I like you.
What?
In the end, this is how I confess... It's a bit of a downer, but I still want to do it.
What are you talking about?
I liked you when you were dating someone else, and I liked you when you broke up.
Of course, I'm not saying I fell in love with you at first sight.
- Why?
- You know what kind of girls I like.
I know. But it's time you stop getting hurt.
I don't think I got hurt. As much as I got hurt while I loved them, I grew.
Grow, my ass. Who took care of you when you got drunk and whined?
Why do you like a woman with a past?
I know. Seriously... Why do I like a woman with a past?
I'm bright with a good family and background, and a pretty face—
That's enough. Go and do well with another man.
You really have weird taste.
That's right, I have weird taste. Why are you getting upset about my preferences? Is it because of Yoo Hye Jeong?
Why are you mentioning Yoo Hye Jeong right now?
You know you get really bothered about Doctor Yoo. You said you went to the same school. Were you rivals?
- Why am I rivals with her?
- See this?
It seems like Yoo Hye Jeong has a story.
- Are you interested in her?
- Of course, I am.
Did you fall in love with her at first sight? Do you know the kind of person she is?
You don't like Yoo Hye Jeong, right? Even though I can't accept your confession, I will kick Yoo Hye Jeong out.
- For me?
- As if... It's for me.
I don't like her. She's not skilled, but she always gets involved. She's rude, too. On top of that, she talks back.
But how can you kick her out because of that when the supervisor is here?
We just need a brain aneurysm case.
Have you seen reality surpass imagination?
I have. You!
I knew you were going to be living well, but I couldn't have imagined you being a doctor.
It means the world is still worth living since I could raise my social status through education.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Do you want me to teach you how to place a catheter without navigation?
I would like that!
Then come work under me starting next week.
I'll be at work tomorrow but not officially. I'm just going to check up on patients.
Okay.
Go in now.
Go first. I can go by myself.
Do you know what you really need to learn, besides how to place a catheter?
What is it?
Accepting protection from others.
This doesn't seem like much to you, right? Since you can do everything by yourself.
I can protect myself.
People who grow up being assured that they are protected trust themselves and society. That's a basic rule in life.
Basics protect you when life gets unsteady.
Receiving protection is a childhood luxury.
- The past cannot be altered or secured. You can only accept it.
- Wow!
You still don't listen to others.
I learned this after paying a ton of tuition fees.
You can't change circumstances, but you can change hearts.
Where do I start with you and what should I teach you first? I should make a curriculum when I get home.
Why?
- Why?
- Just because.
Go in now. I'll watch you go in. Don't look back and go straight ahead.
See? You're not listening again.
Teacher!
Oh, Soon Hee!
Congratulations on your marriage!
- No, that's not it.
- Omo.
Sorry! Then did you get divorced?
I said that's not it!
You've changed. Your mouth has gotten cheap (have a big mouth).
Oh you don't know. Hye Jeong's mouth is worth only 10 cents (quick to divulge) to someone she likes.
That's right.
Yeah.
Hurry! Hurry!
You drop it every day!
With whose permission? Did you just wake up?
No, I didn't.
Come close.
Why are you lying? You just woke up.
I didn't.
Put your eyes downward.
Well, you can button up wrong, but how is this evidence that I woke up just now?
This jerk, seriously. Do you think I'm an idiot?
I told you that if you make a mistake, acknowledge your mistakes!
We woke up and dozed off a bit. Then we got your call!
Why did you doze off? Why? Why?
England. Where's Yeong Gook (Korean name for England)?
Neurosurgery Dog
Patient Lee Gi Cheol's lab values are normal.
We've changed his medication from injections to oral medication.
- He became better. How about his hematoma?
- It declined to 20cc.
Am I your morning call (alarm) or something? You just woke up, didn't you?
That's not true. I checked on Patient Do Yeong Gyeong, before Professor Hong Ji Hong started rounds.
I'm upset. I was worried that you, Chief (Resident), would be in trouble if I messed up so I was over there working—
I got it, I got it. Acknowledged!
You, scan this book.
Youman's Neurological Surgery
This is my book that you borrowed yesterday.
It's because I have no money, no money to buy books!
Never mind, I'll just give it to you.
You, go to the Korea Meteorological Site, check the weather for the last couple of years, and organize the data.
Is it for your thesis paper, chief?
Why do you ask those things when you already know?
- Joong Dae, Joong Dae, Ahn Joong Dae!
- Yes?
He keeps following you because you keep asking useless questions!
That's not it. We're already busy enough as it is, but since you're making us run personal errands for you, I just asked.
- The upper years have to do well, so that the lower years can do well too.
- Ye.s
He doesn't understand any words that are said if they put him at a disadvantage.
Grandma Hwang Jeong, she's your patient, right?
That grandma had an intracranial aneurysm.
We couldn't even see it because it was too small,
but I think it burst 3 months ago because it was cold.
Look into it so that we can see if it can be included in the paper.
Chief, can't you make Hyung Yeong Gook print the relevant research?
I'm just sitting over here minding my own business. Why are you suddenly bringing me into this?
I just have too much work, really.
Then, do I have nothing to do?
This rascal, seriously. How is it you haven't been trained no matter how many times you have been hit?
Are you some kind of wild horse? Be docile, huh!
I'll do it. Those research papers, I'll get them for you.
You saw that, right? You need to take after him in aspects like this!
It's times like this that the merits of aging show.
- I'll do my best.
- Right on!
I live like this you know.
Yes, I understand.
As for me, I won't get involved like that.
What are you talking about? Are you done preparing for rounds?
Just see what happens if I hear that you were scolded by the professors.
Professor, Patient Do Hyeon Gyu's hematoma has increased in size a bit.
It hasn't increased by a lot, so administer urokinase irrigation (UK) every 6 hours.
Be careful not to do too much. If any cerebrospinal fluid comes out, close his head right away.
Yes.
- You came to work?
- I'm leaving soon.
- What about your afternoon rounds?
- I will come back.
I'd rather just stay if it were me.
It's been a while since I've earned a vacation. I'm going to use it to the full extent,
and Dr. Yoo Hye Jeong agreed to work under me.
When did you meet with her to decide that? Are you really someone who's on vacation?
I put dibs on her first just in case, Doctor Jeong Yoon Do would take her from me.
Ah, that attitude is good. Having something taken away and giving something away are really different.
Would you like a cup of tea?
I have to attend a meeting. I don't know why there are so many meetings.
Wait. You haven't seen the research labs yet, right? I'll show them to you.
Yeah.
June Earnings Report for Guk Il Medical Center
This month's highest profiting department, as expected, is the general surgery department. You worked hard, Professor Baek.
Director Jin Myeong Hoon
I'll increase the credit card limit on the business account.
If you have good results, then I surely must give you the appropriate treatment.
Don't you think that's the benefit of living in a capitalist market society?
Thank you.
Neurosurgery Department Professor Kim Tae Ho, and our vice-director,
the general surgery's earnings last month came close to 10 million ₩.
What is 46 million ₩, neurosurgery department?
Is it good for him to be the only one doing well?
Do you have a plan for increasing the department's earnings?
I have hired a new talent. I've scouted John Hopkins' professor Hong Ji Hong. It will get better.
Will sales rise just because you employ someone new?
You! You're the vice-director of this hospital but you oppose the hospital management initiatives.
Why are you against it when I said we would build a geriatrics center?
Rather than a geriatrics center, having a transplant center is more beneficial for the advancement of medical—
If you're going to spout such b*llshit, then resign from your position as vice-director.
We need to survive in order for there to be progress. Last year there was a loss of 253 million ₩.
But our additional profit exceeded 1 billion ₩ didn't it?
That kind of progress is an apt example of the cart coming before the horse.
A hospital has to live off of its profits made from the hospital; would it live off of the profits made from a restaurant?
Return the entire neurosurgery department's vacation days this month.
There has to be at least one more patient and you need to do one more surgery. What do you mean vacation?
Nice putting.
Is your condition just not good today or have you gotten old?
My condition isn't good.
Since we're old, there are more days in which we're not in the best condition.
Isn't it about time for us to retire?
We have to. We should secure the basics and leave it to our children.
You know, Myeong Hoon? Not just because he's my kid, but he's excellent at hospital management.
He's pretty good, but we should change it up a bit.
Why change when it's going well?
We have to help him grow.
If an entire organization only relies on one person, it will stagnate.
Are you leaning towards Neurosurgery Department's Vice-Director Kim Tae Ho, or if not, Ji Hong?
Isn't it enough to have him promoted to a director?
There's no need to shake the leadership at the top. We can have them controlled from the bottom up.
Myeong Heon already has a subsidiary.
With that he doesn't need to work a day in his life. He likes money, correct?
Let's not talk about that anymore. I'm busy.
Are you looking down on me right now?
Are you thinking that my child is pathetic as a doctor and all he does is show off his desire for money?
Guk Il Medical Center's Revenue Chart for June
Cardiothoracic Surgery, General Surgery, Neurosurgery
- Father, you're here.
- Yes.
The general hospital department's earnings are the highest,
but why is the bed turnover rate for the Neurosurgery Department so bad?
I shook down the Neurosurgery Department over that, today.
Good job.
Give this to Chairman Jeong when you see him later.
What is it?
It's time we send Doo Sik home.
Don't pick it up! Don't pick it up! One, two, three, four, five...
Hello, Hyung-nim.
Why are you like this? If someone saw, they would think I'm your boss.
- One bite?
- No it's okay.
It's grape flavored.
Don't lower your guard, and stay as quiet as a dead mouse.
Yes, I understand, Hyungnim.
- How do you feel?
- I'm fine.
You need absolute rest. Do you need to have all those people posted outside?
I have lots of enemies.
If the rumor gets out that I've gotten weak, there will be many people who'll be out to get me.
Although it would be nice avoiding things that can be avoided,
things that are meant to find you will find you. I've learned that in life.
You finished checking his vitals, right?
Yes, there are no problems.
Rest up.
Be safe on your way back, Doctor.
Be safe!
- Are there anymore canned peaches?
- We ate them all.
Continue to check that the surgical wound is healing well.
Should I continue changing his wound dressing?
Of course. We're going to monitor him for a week and discharge him next week.
- Where are you going to go?
- The ICU. What about you?
ER General Surgery's Sun
Yoon!
Yoon, wake up, please. Yoon!
Please move him here.
Hey, where is the patient in a semicomatose state?
Yoon, wake up.
I'll check on him.
He went out for school and then suddenly collapsed. Please save him, Doctor.
Mother, Mother, please calm down. I'll take a look.
- Please move him.
- Yes.
Yoon, Yoon...
Ah, I'm about to get irritated.
Hey! He's not semicomatose, he's in a stupor (near-unconsciousness, insensible).
Whatever. He's going to be a neurosurgery patient anyway.
I was scared! Wow, I'm the crazy one.
I came down listening to a dirty general surgeon kid who can't even determine a mental state property. I'm really going to ***—
Where are you going? Where, where, where? You were the one that said the Emergency Room can't operate without the help of the Neurosurgery Department.
So, just stay down here, you kiddo!
You're not letting go? Let go of me. Let go.
- Should I lay a hand on you? Call me hyung, I'm your hyung!
- Let go, let go! I'm telling Mom. Hurry and let go.
Do you know today's date?
I want to see that b*tch.
Exactly who is that "b*tch"?
If she wants to see her that much, why won't you call her?
You can meet her once you move down to a regular patient room.
Seeing as how you're calling her a b*tch, I don't think you have nice feelings towards her.
It would be nice to see her when you're healthy.
As expected, you're a smart miss— Uh, doctor.
Given your condition, you'll be able to move down to a regular patient room soon.
Patient, cheer up.
You're taking such attentive care of that patient.
You always follow me in even though she's not your patient.
I guess you have lots of free time these days. I should make you run around more.
Anyway, you're a psycho. You can't stand to see me be comfortable.
Choi Kang Soo
Yeah, what?
Male, 15 years old. He suddenly collapsed on his way to school.
His right pupil is dilated about 5 mm. His motor reflexes are a bit depressed.
I'll be right there.
- What's wrong?
- Kyeong Joon, follow me.
Ah, yes.
The daughter sac (irregular protrusion on aneurysm wall) burst. This might be complicated.
Prepare for surgery, and call Doctor Yoo Hye Jeong.
Not Doctor Jin Seo Woo?
From now on in my surgeries, Doctor Yoo Hye Jeong is going to come in.
W-W-Why?
Finally the war has started.
Where are you going?
To prep for Dr.Jeong Yoon Do's aneurysm surgery.
Really? Then why didn't you notify me?
Doctor Jeong Yoon Do changed his assistant. Finally, the war has started with the two of them.
War?
For me, I put in my vote that Doctor Yoo Hye Jeong will get kicked out. What about you?
Did you not hear my instructions to prepare and come in for surgery?
I heard.
But what is up with your outfit?
I know that Doctor Jin Seo Woo is your assistant.
Starting today, you are going to come to train under me.
What training do I have to receive from you?
I'm not interested in learning the aneurysm operation through craniotomy (surgical opening into the skull).
Also, I've done plenty already.
So you're only going to do coiling? As long as I'm here, that won't happen.
I told you this once before, but I'm not the right major assistant to work under you.
You won't work under me? Then you should do it yourself. I'll acknowledge you then.
If I succeed?
I'll do whatever you want.
I'll do it.
If you fail, you could get kicked out of the hospital.
I respect Chief Kim so I was going to just let things go, but you act too much like a gangster.
You don't have any regard for your superiors, nor do you have respect.
Your skills are terrible, yet you still don't have the correct attitude to learn.
Then shouldn't you leave?
How is it?
It's seems nice. Is there anywhere in the hospital where I can work out?
There is. Our chairman thinks of those types of things as important. Amenities have been set up well.
That doesn't sound like a positive.
Because it's not free.
What is free in the world? Is he really picky in real life?
He's a pigeon. He's really picky.
But still, people like our chairman are very practical.
They can read the flow well. When people are busy arguing about the old liberalism and conservatism, he takes the money.
Well, that's the same in America, too.
That's what I'm saying.
This month the entire neurosurgery department has no break.
Our profits were worse than the general hospital department.
To get more profit, we need to discharge patients fast and raise the turnover, but
I really don't want to make our kids do that!
Then you deal with it and don't release your stress on us.
Hey, how can I receive all this stress by myself? You need to share it with me!
In the past you said, for sure, that as long as you can distinguish between good and evil in people, things are easy.
"There's nothing that can beat the value of eating and living."
But we're still human.
There are always people who do what they want no matter what, even if it means death.
That's the same for you and me, right?
Are you giving me pain and then medicine?
Just a moment.
Neurosurgeon Jin Seo Woo
Yes, Seo Woo?
Yeah. What is the problem?
This surgery, can a fellow do it?
This looks very serious.
A regular aneurysm surgery is complicated enough but this case has a ruptured daughter sac.
A fellow can't do this. Are you going to do it?
No, Hye Jeong said she would do it.
Says who? Who decides on the operating surgeon for this type of operation?
Doctor Yoo Hye Jeong is supposed to be under my training.
You shouldn't take her without my permission.
I am under the impression that you officially start next week. Doesn't that apply starting then?
I'll let you know the updated news. I start working today.
There wasn't an agreement with the fellowship, so it's invalid.
In this surgery, Doctor Yoo Hye Jeong isn't an assistant but the lead surgeon, so that doesn't matter.
Then I'll go in.
A fellow cannot perform a surgery of this level.
It's my patient.
You said it was Doctor Yoo Hye Jeong's surgery a little while ago. Then it must be her patient.
It is my patient.
I won't give you my permission.
I start with you next week. I'm still free. I will do what I want.
Why are you like this? Can you handle it?
I'm confident.
This person always goes beyond herself like this.
Still nothing changes. I'm going in.
Then do that. I'll be the referee.
I'll do it.
It's my fight. I don't avoid fights that come to me.
Don't worry. I only get into fights that I can win.
Don't forget that I'll always be next to you...
And that I'm always ready to help you.
I'll do the assist. Come out.
Ah, yes.
Irrigation.
Hand me the dissector.
Diatherm (electrosrgical cautery tool).
Please give me the surgical cottonoids.
I think they found it.
They won't be able to find it easily.
Clip.
They found it.
It burst.
Suction.
Raise the suction.
I'll do it.
I can do it.
Doctor Yoo Hye Jeong. Pass it to Doctor Hong Ji Hong.
Hye Jeong.
Blood pressure's falling. Bring more blood.
Doctor Yoo Hye Jeong, are you planning to kill the patient? Doctor Hong Ji Hong!
Concentrate.
Clip.
Ah, it's done.
What a relief.
Will you do it?
It's your surgery. Finish it too.
Suction.
Lower the suction.
Doctor Yoo Hye Jeong.
I'm sorry.
If you apologize this easily, I'll lose my fighting spirit.
If I lose, I immediately put my tail down.
I'm going to respect your decision now, whatever that decision is.
Everything I do is like a gangster, I don't have respect for anyone, and my skills are crap.
And I don't have the correct attitude to learn, so what could I do?
I... apologized just a moment ago.
You really hold grudges.
- You're quite strange.
- I am a bit strange.
You're quick to accept. It's good that you're simple-minded.
My grandmother was like this, too.
She'd scold me like crazy but got happy as soon I gave her something she wanted.
That's a compliment, right? I am quite simple.
You like it even now.
Doctor Hong Ji Hong seems to have excessive affection for his students.
When you were in school, he must have favored you over Seo Woo.
No. He probably shared the feeling of a parent who is kinder to the troublemaker child.
I was expelled from high school.
You're scared, right? I was expelled and everything.
Ah, seriously! What's scary about that?
I played around a bit in school, too.
You probably played around at the arcade.
What are you doing?
Oh, Uncle.
It's good that I ran into you. Let me sleep at your place tonight.
Why would you sleep at my house instead of your house with a slim model in it?
- I don't want to go because of that slim model.
- You loved her to death.
She wants to get married. When I said we should break up, she stuck herself to the house like a built-in closet and won't leave.
Take this opportunity and get settled.
You know my father, your grandfather.
He married three times and between those marriages, he dated.
Even during his marriages, he dated other women.
Also, your father, my big brother.
He swore that he would never turn out like my father but he's preparing for his second divorce.
There is no such thing as "long-lasting" in our family.
I'm going to change my DNA.
I was like that, too, when I first got married, but genes don't change, no matter how much you try to change them.
- Are you going to let me sleep at your place or not?
- I can't give you my password.
Why are you so inflexible? You can change it after you tell me.
Oh, that's true.
You've been looking dazed since before. Do you perhaps like that girl who went by earlier?
- What are you saying?
- It's bull****.
Hey. Next week Doctor Hong Ji Hong is transferring to your department, right?
You should get along well with him. He's a close friend of mine.
That ship has sailed.
What? Did you meet Ji Hong already?
I bought yours too. Do you want some coffee?
Instead of coffee, I'd like some water.
I'll give it to you.
Here.
I want to drink coffee too.
I'll give you that too.
- Did you meet the guardians?
- Yes, I reassured them.
You're being good to me because I assisted your surgery well, right?
With this, you're saying that I'm being good to you?
Hye Jeong.
Are you going to keep living like this?
How am I living?
Your competitive spirit is too strong.
You succeeded, so you should enjoy it. You should know how to play, too.
How many hours do you sleep a day?
I sleep ten hours a week. It's become a habit.
If I slept and played like others, there wouldn't be the me that there is now.
Are you happy right now?
I have nothing to be happy about.
Why?
When I first told you that I wanted to live differently ...
You said you wanted to allow your grandmother to live in extravagance.
I'm living differently and I succeeded, but my grandmother isn't here anymore.
I can't help you with that. Accept it.
Why do you keep saying you'll help me?
Do you still see me as your disciple?
Although I may still look like the 18-year-old who caused trouble everywhere—
To you,
do I look like I'm doing this because I'm your teacher?
If you think like that, you're really an idiot.
Or should I be happy about it?
You became a doctor before you could date anyone,
so your dating cells have died. You can't recognize the gaze a man gives to a woman.
If I think about you,
the scene where we met for the last time always comes to mind.
♫  The first time I saw you. ♫
I should have grabbed you at that time.
♫ You seemed as anxious as a child. ♫
Are you rejecting me like this?
♫  One day when you were standing beside me ♫
Oh, no, no.
Then are we dating?
♫  You had changed to be so lovely.♫
- No.
- Are you rejecting me?
Oh.
No.
What is this? You say no to everything. Your habit is to respond first with no to everything, right?
It is.
I'll ask you again next time.
It's because I feel more awkward.
Weirdly,
when I meet you it's serious at first but the ending is always comical. Whose fault is this?
What was that reaction?
♫  If love is needing my comfort ♫
You're weird. You've become weirder
Bad brat.
♫  Take a step closer. ♫
I'm going to ask you again next time.
At that time, no matter what I ask, it's an unconditional yes.
♫  I think it' probably now is our love. ♫
Thank you for coming here even though you are busy.
It's been a while.
While I'm here can I see my child?
Yoon Doo is currently in surgery.
After leaving to go live on his own, I have to look for him in order for him to barely show me his face.
Both men and women must get married to understand their parents' heart. Am I right?
Would I be able to see Seo Woo?
From what I hear, she is also in surgery.
That's good. Working together is really good.
Let's go in.
President Hong holds a lot of the Medical Care company stocks,
but will this be enough for his impeachment?
If we say that he bought the stocks with the sole purpose of making money, it'll change the whole story,
since he has a high regard for honor.
Are you saying he will resign on his own?
That is what I am hoping for. But we shall wait and see.
What does the Ministry of Health say? Will it get approved at the upcoming national assembly?
The public is refusing because it's an investor-owned hospital,
and the civic group is rebutting.
Until when do doctors need to be dragged around?
Just like in the US, the hospitals need to be privatized, and
the hospitals need to be commercialized to for fair competition.
We need to ban public health insurance, and let people see doctors when they want.
A privatized hospital has been approved at Jeju Island, so our plan will work out.
In the end, the hospitals will have no choice but to be commercialized.
Next week I will be meeting with Assemblyman Nam. Let's meet him together.
Release it to the press. Something like, "The hospital has a dire need to earn money".
Yes, I understand.
Ahn Joong Dae.
- Why?
- Patient Lee Gi Chan is complaining that he can't sleep at night.
Should I prescribe him sleeping pills or not? His mental state seems fine.
What's the problem? You said he's sane.
Hey, you bastard! Do you prescribe pills based on what could happen in the future?!
What did I tell you?
Please give Patient Yoo Gi Cheol the sleeping pills.
Yes.
Hey, you're more hateful.
Hyungnim, why do you have no sense? Why do you keep asking about everything?
Do I ask because I want to ask? Who said that I'm going to die if I don't notify correctly?
He said correctly, not frequently.
His words are true.
Hyung, Doctor Jin Seo Woo was looking for you.
She always looks for someone, but I don't always answer,
because I'm expensive (valuable).
What is he saying?
Hey! Do you want to die! Why are you in my room!
Missed Call
Teacher Hong Ji Hong
What?
Doctor! Patient Ji Min Gyo is yelling!
Why are you notifying me? Is it serious?
Aigoo. Aigoo, aigoo, aigoo.
Hello.
He kept trying to jump off the bed so we tied him down.
We have the prescriptions we received after the consult with the psychiatry department, right?
Yes. We took the same steps, and they gave us the same prescriptions.
Then why did you call me?
I didn't call you.
Tell Gyeong Joon to come here. Where is he and what is he doing?
Yes, Doctor.
What are you doing?
There's nothing special so why did you notify me?
- I'm sorry.
- Why are you so disorganized?
Ah, take it easy, Doctor.
Where were you earlier, not even picking up your phone?
Do you think I couldn't pick up my phone because I went somewhere? I couldn't pick up because I was busy.
Good for you.
You've been working here for a while already. Can't you listen when your underling's got something to report?
He said he notified me because he was scared he would get scolded if he notified you.
- You—
- I'm sorry.
I'll talk to him about this
to make sure this doesn't happen in the future.
Joon Dae.
Yes.
Come with me for a minute. I have something to tell you.
- Can you not tell me here?
- No, I can't. Let's go together.
- Um, please ...
- Go.
Then Doctor, I'll see you later.
Ah yes.
Why did you call?
I got a call from Doctor Hong Ji Hong, but I ignored it.
- Why?
- Right, why?
- What should I do?
- Did you do something wrong?
That couldn't be it. You wouldn't do something wrong.
Call him back instead of being restless and imagining what he could have called about.
Do I seem restless?
Call him. My answer is only this.
Because of what happened today, I wanted to clear the air with you, so I called you.
Clear the air about what?
In the past, too, 13 years ago,
we suffered a lot of emotional indignity because of useless misunderstandings.
I don't think we should step back onto that train again.
I don't think it was a misunderstanding.
Okay. If you think of it like that, then I'll respect your thoughts.
Let me make a correction then.
I need to make sure that in the future no more misunderstandings happen.
Are you like this because I told you about Hye Jeong's surgery earlier?
That included. I still like Hye Jeong.
Why are you telling me these things? You should tell Hye Jeong.
Do you think I would tell you first without telling Hye Jeong already?
That's good. I was uneasy when she appeared in my life again.
What is she going to take away from me this time? I guess at least it won't be a man.
I'm starting to like Doctor Jeong Yoon Do.
He's a college senior of mine and he's from a respected family so we can understand each other.
I just want you two to get along. Can't I ask you a favor to get along with her?
I didn't mess with her first. She's always the one that messes with me first.
She's the one that approached me first to teach her how to study, and from then on my life was ruined.
I miss Unni In Joo since she's a victim of Hye Jeong, as well.
I shouldn't have brought this up. We can't seem to clarify this issue.
Hong Ji Hong!
Uncle.
Do you two know each other?
I asked first, but I'll answer first. We do. We're best friends.
Him, me, and In Joo. We always went around together in college, right?
Must you confirm it?
Why wouldn't I confirm it?
Ugh, you rascal! If you came, you should have come to me first! How could you make me look for you?
I'll leave first. Go ahead and speak with each other.
Yeah, we don't have anything to talk about. We're just going to drink. Right Ji Hong?
Hey you rascal, look at the time!
Why? Daytime drinking is good!
- Let's go quickly.
- Hey, wait!
Are you married?
No.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Then that's all.
♫  I tried hard, yes. ♫
♫  Feels like ♫
Do you know what else you need to know other than learning to place catheters?
What is it?
♫ Things don't work out as I wished  ♫
Accepting being protected.
♫  Myself, ♫
♫  am I pitiful? ♫
♫  This world,
Do I hate it? ♫
♫ Perhaps you might be lonely?  ♫
I'll be finished quickly so don't sit around anxiously here. Go and eat something.
♫  I don't know if I can comfort you.  ♫
♫ These words may not be enough to comfort you.  ♫
♫  But, it's always like this. ♫
♫ It will be okay  ♫
Calling: Hong Ji Hong
Where are you right now?
Hey. Stay outside. I'm going to talk with a junior of mine for a minute.
Hey. Can't we be together? You said it's just a junior.
Ah, just stay outside.
Uh, hey, I saw that woman before. Hey, introduce me. I saw her twice.
Hey, leave already!
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
Do you not remember me? I remember you, though.
Ah, really!
We will meet again. At our third meeting we'll be dating.
Who is he?
A crazy person. He's a friend. He's a staff member in general surgery.
What did you have to say? You want me to ask you a second time already?
No, please don't do it yet.
You're being so serious that it's making me feel awkward.
I'm sorry. I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Doctor, if you're the chairman's son and a doctor on staff here,
you can access all the information in this hospital, right? Even the top tier ones?
Top tier information?
In Guk Il Medical Center, you can access different amounts of information based on your level.
I'm only temporarily here so—
You're saying that the information you can access is restricted because you're just temporarily here?
What are you saying right now? Are you asking me to access something you can't—
Doctor, let's talk about it again later.
- Why? What...
- I saw a strange person.
- What? But—
Ah, you scared me.
You came in without a sound.
Where are all your underlings who were protecting you?
I sent them all back.
Why?
Because you told me to.
You listened to me? Do you expect me to believe that?
Well, from now on, I'm planning on listen to a woman's words, too.
Why are you here, Doctor?
Does a doctor need a reason to see her patient?
Rest.
Yeah, what?
The aneurysm patient's blood pressure is under 90. I prescribed dopamine and an IV, but it's still not going up.
What should I do?
I'll come.
Did you eat yet?
Not yet. I had an emergency patient and couldn't even sit down.
- Go and eat.
- There's so much to do.
I need to prepare for surgery and do the dressing for Boss.
I'll do the dressing for Boss. Then you'll have time to eat.
- You are too happy.
- Thank you.
But why are you so good to me? Do you like me?
Stop fooling around. Get off.
- How about you?
- I'm going back up to Boss.
Thank you.
Should I put it in deep?
You bastard, bring my younger brother back from the dead.
Then, I'll let you live.
She's becoming stable.
- Yes.
- Call her.
She's not answering.
Do I have to leave her to you?
Can I trust you?
Yes, you can.
Okay. I will trust you once.
What's going on?
Here is the drink you ordered. Enjoy.
Where should I put this?
O-Over there by the kitchen.
It's already summer. How's it going with Su Jin, the girl you are dating?
Kang Su Jin, Park Su Jin ? Which one?
It's Kim, you punk. Wait.
Yes, Soon Hee. I'm on my way to your place to grab some drinks.
Doctor, Hye Jeong is not answering her phone. I have important news to tell her.
She may not answer her phone. Try again later.
Doctor, you don't know Hye Jeong. No matter what, Hye Jeong always calls back.
If she can't answer she always sends back a text message.
This is the first time I'm here. Can you recheck this?
Anyway, can you please recheck? Otherwise I will go to the hospital.
- Looks like the delivery ahjussi has changed.
- Yes.
Doesn't it seem like we met before?
Do you know me?
No. No, no. How much...?
She doesn't answer?
That's strange. Isn't she the doctor on call?
Doctor. Let's talk later. I saw a strange person.
- You go ahead first.
- Hey!
Hey! Ah, that guy!
Hello.
Where is Doctor Hye Jeong?
She went to change the wound dressing for the gangster boss.
Why is Doctor Yoo Hye Jeong doing that?
She told me to eat so she...
You didn't eat yet?
Finding food in between, while working, is a skill. Increase your survival skills.
Yes.
Call Doctor Hye Jeong.
I can't leave and entrust the patients to you guys.
She's not answering. Should I go and take a look?
Tell her to check the cerebral aneurysm patient.
Yes.
No, go and eat.
-,No, no, no, I can go—
- Go eat.
- Don't make me tell you twice.
- Yes, thank you.
Do you know what type of person he is? If you do, you'll regret saving him.
He's not even human. Should I tell you how he killed my younger brother?
Should I tell you how he ruined my family? What he did to me?
I'll show you.
I've been waiting... for this day to come.
You can't have good luck forever.
Why? Do you have something to say?
- Your brother came to find me with his own two feet. The one who came to find me first was that guy.
- So?
You role-played the good brother, and now that he has no value to you, you buried him, you sh*t-faced dog.
You can't hit the head.
Sit down, or else he dies.
If I can't hit the head, is this okay?
Please don't do that. It hasn't been long since his surgery, something could go wrong.
If something happens to him, you'll have to be punished by the law.
Don't try to convince me.
Why are you in pain because of trash like him?
If you get arrested on charges of murder, you'll have to rot in jail forever, and his gang members
won't leave you alone in jail.
It's enough that you threatened him.
He's scared. He's scared that he'll die.
As long as he's alive, people like you will keep visiting him.
Don't get blood on your hands. Give me the knife.
It's quite complicated here. I don't want to get involved. I'm going to go out.
Stop! Come next to the woman
or else this bastard dies.
Take him and leave.
I'll do it. Doctor Yoo, take him and leave.
Get out!
Kong Byeong Joo. Kong Byeong Joo!
People say this.
Forgiving isn't done for others, but for yourself.
You shouldn't say things like that. Forgiveness isn't as light as it sounds.
♫  Don't say you're sorry. ♫
♫  No way.  ♫
♫  Don't leave me, no way. ♫