We got it.
Let's move on to the next step.
Next step?
We need to find out
who killed the Chief and why.
This place is not for just anyone to come in.
Prosecutor General, congratulations.
- Congratulations.
Congratulations.
I just saw the announcement.
- Congratulations, Prosecutor General.
- Thank you.
Investigator, now is not a good time.
- I look forward to working with you.
- Thank you.
Pardon?
Prosecutor Jin Jung, you're under arrest for the murder of Chief Lee Jang Won.
The record of vehicles in and out of the legal complex at the time of the incident.
This is the testimonial of the eyewitness who saw you at the scene.
What I'm wondering is this.
Why on earth did you murder the Chief, Prosecutor Jin?
The Chief was probably not so fond of you
for suspecting him as the culprit of a murder case.
Did you two have a fight?
The Chief's last phone call was made to you, Prosecutor Jin.
He said there was something he needed to tell me.
There's no way to confirm that.
There's a suspect for the murder.
But you don't have any evidence.
I could say the same to you.
Present a concrete evidence that I'm the murderer.
This was found at your house.
The blood on the needle was confirmed to be the victim's.
Your fingerprints were found on the syringe.
Hey. What are you doing?
Who put you up to this?
What do you mean?
I'm saying, whose behind this?
Gosh. Think as you'd like.
Give up, Prosecutor Jin.
You can't get out of this.
I thought you only lacked conscience,
but you also lack brains.
I told you last time, right?
That I'll bring people like you down.
I wouldn't have even started if this was all it took to stop me.
Listen carefully to what I'm about to say right now.
I'm going to dig and find out
who's trying to frame me and why
to the smallest detail...
and get all of you locked up.
What brings you here?
Nonsense.
If you're done looking, can you leave?
I have to prepare for prosecution.
Are you going to prosecute as written here?
Is there a reason not to?
I don't know who the author is,
but they went the extra mile to make Prosecutor Jin the main character.
It doesn't make sense! Why would he—
Does it make sense for you to do this to me?
This is also an obstruction of the investigation, Prosecutor Shin.
Get out.
I know that you treasure Prosecutor Jin.
But you should still... be cautious this time.
I'm telling you this for your sake.
You'd better be careful yourself.
Who the hell do you think you are to order me around?
Prosecutor! Are you okay?
Yes.
You know the situation, right?
As things are, you're going to go down alone for sure.
Prosecutor Jin doesn't have a motive for murder.
His movements after the incident are also far from that of a suspect.
I think these points will give us some advantages.
At trials, evidence take priority before testimonies.
They'll be useless.
For now, you keep your mouth shut.
We still have time until they press charges. I'll find a way somehow.
Based on what we know about Oh Do Hawn...
this isn't something he planned by himself.
There's clearly someone behind him.
What about Deputy Chief Kim Tae Ho?
He became the Prosecutor General, right?
Deputy Chief?
Try then.
If it's suspicious, it's right to investigate until the end.
I'll take responsibility for whatever the outcome is...
so you two do your best and focus on the investigation.
Deputy Chief always helped us, though.
He's probably related to the Chief's case.
The guy who wanted his death to stay as a suicide.
And that person framed you
so that you can't look into the case anymore?
There's probably the intention to cover up the case like this.
If I'm found guilty in court,
there would be no reason to continue the investigation anyway.
Just like Kim Hyo Jun... of the Seocho-dong murder case?
Are you on your way out?
What is this?
I would like to confirm your claim
that you'll do anything, Prosecutor Oh.
I'll look into who's behind Oh Do Hwan.
Thank you, but I'll keep your words only, not your help.
I'll look into it myself.
You'll do it, Prosecutor?
There's an ox bone soup place near the market, right?
Order me one ox bone soup, please.
A thick one for tomorrow morning.
Okay.
Come on, please undo the cuffs.
I need to eat.
Gosh...
The broth is thick.
That's true.
You wouldn't know even if something's hidden inside.
What do you mean?
Something like a handcuff key?
Look.
You can't see it at all.
Why bother...
Please enjoy your meal.
What the heck?
Gosh, you're finally here.
What's this?
Where are the handcuffs?
Didn't you hear from Prosecutor Oh?
There was a misunderstanding.
- Please take care.
- One moment, Prosecutor.
We'll give one confirmation call first.
Why bother with a confirmation call? Go ahead.
What is this sound?
What's this? Hey.
Yes.
No!
Take care now.
- Wait, wait. My hand.
- The key!
The key... Give me the key...
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Okay, understood.
Excuse me, excuse me!
Thank you.
I'll open it for you next time.
Stop!
Geez, he scared me.
Stop right there!
Get him!
Get him! Stop there!
There he goes!
Corner him!
What are you doing?
Stop!
Don't let him go!
Follow him!
Lee Chul Ki speaking.
Oh, no... Are you okay?
Yes.
I'll be right there.
- Is it Prosecutor Jin?
- No!
How could that be?
It's definitely not Prosecutor Jin.
Are you a robot?
Act properly if you're going to act or
answer the phone outside, man.
That one has some loose gears.
Get out.
It's distracting.
Get out, I said. You're distracting me!
Thank you.
Please come with us.
The police had already searched Prosecutor Jin's house...
You never know, though.
Perhaps something beneficial for Prosecutor Jin will come out.
Let's head on over first.
Hello, Manager.
They said Prosecutor Jin disappeared.
Sorry?
Hello?
Yes, Prosecutor.
Are you on the way?
I'm sorry, Prosecutor.
I don't think I can come.
Prosecutor Oh Do Hwan is next to me! Please run away!
Prosecutor Jin.
You're only adding years to your sentence. Stop now and turn yourself in.
I need to see the end of what I started.
You're going to be caught anyway.
You'll be the one getting caught, Prosecutor Oh.
Wait for me.
I'll come see you very soon.
Investigations will continue without restraint.
Leave your phone on at all times.
Focus on arresting Prosecutor Jin for a while.
Prosecutor General!
- But Prosecutor Jin is—
- I know what you're going to say.
I'm on the same page as you.
However, Prosecutor Shin...
you're a prosecutor, and I'm a prosecutor, too.
Sometimes there's a need to trust and follow the organization's decision.
Prioritize the organization's decision before the innocent person.
Is that what you're saying?
It's for Prosecutor Jin's own good.
I don't understand what it is that's good for Prosecutor Jin!
The press started to catch on.
For now, I'm holding off the press for him.
Further down the road, no one knows what they're going to say about him.
It's right to solve a problem within, not outside, right?
Follow my orders on this one.
Also... when Prosecutor Jin contacts you, persuade him to return.
I'll do my best on my end as well.
Prosecutor General...
You may leave.
Hyeon Gyu.
Tae Ho.
Yes.
I understand you're busy after becoming the Prosecutor General,
but you still need to clean up your home.
Let's do a good job, okay?
Yes, CEO.
I've been thinking as to how I can help you.
These are some guys who are good to use,
so give them some seats and use them well.
The Anti-Corruption and the Public Investigation.
Those guys are exceptionally good with those things. They'll be helpful to you.
CEO, this is still a little...
Is there a need for you to go this far?
I'm on your side, so why...
You just want me as a figurehead?
Damn...
What about our internal and external CCTVs? Did they catch anything?
Nothing at all.
What about the reports from the police agency?
Even something like a card transaction history.
Nothing from them yet.
Since things like cards are sure to be tracked down.
Investigator Park, there are people who work with Prosecutor Jin. A man and a woman.
Please do a background check on them and find their personal information.
- As soon as possible.
- Okay.
See you later.
Miss... Come on, what the heck is this? It's so unspeakable.
The Big Boss is going to cry if he sees this.
It's fine. They're my brothers.
Ms. Baek Eun Ji?
I'm from the Prosecution. Please come with us.
Come on! Let go of this!
Let go of me and talk to me!
You need to tell me what's going on first!
Prosecutor Jin told you to do this, didn't he?
I-I'll walk on my own feet.
Hey, get him!
W-Wait, wait a minute. No...
You're here because of that, right? Last week...
T-The text messages that I hacked!
I apologize for using rough means.
The summons takes a long time, so...
Also, you two are not the type to come, even if I send the summons.
Let me introduce myself formally.
I'm Prosecutor Shin Ah Ra of Central District Prosecutors' Office Criminal Division 3.
Baek Eun Ji.
I'm Go Joong Do.
Okay.
Why did you need us?
Let me be brief and cut to the chase.
Prosecutor Jin has been cornered as the suspected murderer of Chief Lee Jang Won.
- What?
- What the...?
I told you that I'll come see you soon.
Who's the bastard that framed me?
Answer me.
If you knew... What could you do if you knew?
A criminal being chased for murder allegations. That's who you are right now.
Also, didn't I tell you already?
You're going to be caught anyway.
Who is it?
Step on it.
Step on it if you don't want to die.
What's going on?
Step on it, punk!
He escaped from the Prosecutors' Office while being interrogated.
So we're now searching for Prosecutor Jin.
At this rate, Prosecutor Jin will be expelled and
there will even be public wanted orders.
Have you been contacted by him, perhaps?
Or is there any way to locate him?
I-I don't know.
Prosecutor Jin has been located!
Let's go, Buddy.
Come here.
What's wrong?
What—
Have you eaten?
Hey.
Yes?
Eat slowly. I'm getting indigestion from just watching you.
Look how happy you are. With a hole in your head.
The kimchi tastes good.
What?
- It tastes good?
- Yes.
Is that so?
Eat up, then.
The pickled radish doesn't taste good.
Framed?
That's that, then.
What are you going to do now?
I'm going to find it and show them.
That they messed with the wrong person
regardless of who they are.
Your fighting spirit is there.
Your son is handsome...
and your wife is also a beauty.
Where are your family members?
It looks like you live here alone.
- A wild goose.
- Sorry?
I'm a wild goose dad, you punk.
(T/N: Dad who lives alone to support family living overseas)
Both my son and my wife...
are abroad.
I'm letting you stay only for tonight.
You're on your own starting tomorrow.
I'm curious about one thing.
Why are you at the Civil Service Division, Director?
Because I was living like you-know-who.
- Director!
- Can't you ask everything at once? What?
It's something important.
Thank you.
Sleep.
Coco! Have you been well?
I'm sorry. Daddy hasn't been taking care of you.
Let's sleep with Daddy, okay?
Come here.
Snowball, come in.
- Prosecutor.
- Yes?
The two of them... Why did you let them go?
We can't exactly keep holding innocent citizens hostage.
It's not like they're helping Prosecutor Jin with his escape.
I believe it's better to let them go for now.
Aren't you telling them to help Prosecutor Jin?
Stop saying weird stuff, and go home.
Okay, I'll be going ahead.
This is Shin Ah Ra.
It's me, Senior.
Where are you right now?
I'm at a safe place. How are things at the office?
Are you asking when you know already?
- I've also been ordered to arrest you.
- That's a little upsetting.
You said you met Oh Do Hwan.
Did you find out who schemed it?
It's not easy.
How great would it be to have you next to me at a time like this.
No. It's a "no, thanks" from me.
Go Joong Do and Baek Eun Ji have been sent home.
Call them or not, do as you please.
Thank you.
Forget it.
From now on, I'm going to catch you.
I'm going to catch you and get a promotion, so don't be caught
by anyone else. Absolutely never.
I'll keep that in mind.
♫  It feels like my blurry vision has become a little more blurred  ♫
♫  After all, the world is always unkind  ♫
Take care of yourself.
♫  It was a huge illusion, it hurts quite a bit  ♫
♫  It's miserable, miserable  ♫
♫  I believed that something would be a little
different from yesterday  ♫
♫  Mistake, mistake, my bad  ♫
♫  I just close my eyes indifferently  ♫
♫  I want you to be quiet, but it's not easy this time  ♫
♫  Look carefully, look at me  ♫
There's something I need to tell you.
♫  I need just one bite, yeah, just one bite  ♫
♫  Now you gotta know, yeah you gotta know  ♫
♫  Somewhere in the dark corner  ♫
♫  Take a bite before the dawn right now  ♫
♫  One bite, need just one bite  ♫
♫  Now you gotta know, yeah you gotta know  ♫
Didn't you sleep?
Do you want some ramen?
This doesn't make sense at all.
I clearly asked you if you wanted.
Don't steal from my plate later.
Oh, yay! Here we go.
Gosh, it's looking good.
Whoa, ramen?
Where's mine?
How can you eat by yourself?
Come on, let's eat together.
Is something not working out?
I just don't understand it, no matter how many times I look at it.
This part right here.
I didn't say I would take a look.
All right.
What about this?
Methamphetamine is a stimulant, not a sedative.
On top of that, it also causes extreme pleasure along with side effects.
Philopon?
(T/N: 1940s brand name of methamphetamine)
If they were going to make him commit suicide, shouldn't they have used a sedative instead?
They need to make him docile first to drop him from a height.
Why did the culprit bother using philopon...
instead of an anesthetic, which is the easier way?
Read me the effects of philopon.
Pleasure, hallucinations,
increase in sexual arousal, bodily vigor,
increase in brain activity,
anxiety, sense of happiness,
confidence...
and increase in hostility. That's what I know about the drug.
There's one more in addition.
It's a truth serum.
A truth serum?
At the moment of injection,
your memories and emotions rush in here.
What do you think will happen then?
Your mind is so overwhelmed that it is like it's going to explode,
but there's no way to relieve it.
From then on, you start running your mouth.
You're feeling good anyway, so until the drug wears off. Blah, blah, blah.
Is that possible?
Spilling secrets from being drugged up?
You see it happen all the time.
People get talkative while under the influence.
Of alcohol?
Even alcohol... can be a truth serum.
Then the killer... was trying to find something out from the Chief?
Sometimes, going back to where you started might be the answer.
Instead of looking for the person who framed you like that,
looking for the person who killed the Chief could be faster.
Today's lesson ends here.
The rest is up to you to find out yourself. Dismissed.
What is he telling me to find out?
Even the same black bean noodles...
differ in taste depending on who makes them.
Why am I telling you this?
As you know, our country isn't a drug-free country anymore.
China, Japan, and the Philippines...
All kinds of drugs from around the world—
I'm sorry.
- Come on.
- Sorry?
Your hands.
Anyhow, since things got competitive in our country,
these guys started using their heads.
Signature.
It's a way to appeal to your customers.
By adding or removing certain ingredients, they create uniqueness in their drugs.
"This drug was created by me."
"You can buy this only from me."
Just like black bean noodles made by a new chef.
Then if you analyze the ingredients of a drug,
you can also find the manufacturer?
Gosh, don't forget about the customer list.
All right...
- Did you have fun today?
- Gosh...
What now? I've been interrogated and released already.
I already told everything to Prosecutor Oh.
It's about a different matter today.
What's this?
Autopsy Analysis? What?
S-So... this guy was murdered?
Don't ask. Just answer.
Who's the one that made this?
I know you've got your hands on distribution and
that you can find the manufacturer with the recipe.
Stop shaking your pupils.
Well, I think I might remember...
You've got golf clubs in your car, right?
- Open up the trunk real quick.
- W-Wait, P-Prosecutor!
My goodness. Are you a thug or a prosecutor?
It's owned by the Gangnam gang.
They're notorious for mixing in tons of pseudoephedrine.
The cold medicine ingredient.
Describe him and tell me where he hangs.
I wouldn't know that.
I heard he's got a dragon tattoo on the neck.
They party every Friday at the club, so try going there.
I'm borrowing this.
Don't make me come find you, and answer my call promptly.
We're not done yet.
Geez, why did he have to take the most expensive one?
He left. I'll start trailing him.
- What's wrong?
- What the heck is this?
- What's going on?
- Gosh!
My goodness!
Why are you driving like that?
Gosh, my lower back.
- Yes, where are you?
- We're at Joong Do's store.
What about the tail?
We dropped them... thanks to Eun Ji.
Okay, listen up.
I think we can find out... who killed Chief Lee Jang Won.
The keyword is Gangnam Club. A dragon tattoo on the neck.
- Go Joong Do—
- This one is worth two big bills.
Find the location and text it to me. I'll see you there.
How do you plan to get there, Prosecutor?
Oh, you're here?
- Shall we go now?
- Yes.
- Hang on tight!
- Okay.
Son.
Geez! What the heck!
What do you mean? It's your mom.
Holly crap...
The police came by earlier.
Did you get in trouble or something?
Either eat cucumber or do the face pack. Choose one.
Why would you have that on out here right now?
- Should I take it off?
- Please!
I just put it on, though.
Tell me now. What did you do?
It's nothing like that.
Is this my first day with you?
Tell me honestly.
I won't hit you.
I-It's nothing like that, M-Mother.
Okay.
It's fine as long as you didn't kill a person.
- What about food?
- I'm eating well.
Seeing anyone?
I'm still looking.
What about Coco?
He's Snowball now.
- What?
- It just happened that way.
You took good care of it.
You hated it when dad would ride it.
I want to throw it out, but I have no time to go to the District Office.
Son... you know I trust you, right?
Also, I've been to my friend's grandson's first birthday—
Wait a second.
Why am I... working so hard right now?
I need to tell Prosecutor Jin about this.
Two bills aren't enough for this.
Focus, all right?
It's out, yeah?
There.
Club Vertigo!
Wow, this place...
This place is the bomb...
It's nice, right?
Let's move.
A drug ring is a sporadically networked group.
It means we can't reach the higher-ups regardless of however many underlings we catch.
It's game over if we can't get them here.
We have to get them today.
What the heck are you doing?
- I'm sorry.
- What's this?
What's your problem?
I-I'm sorry.
If you find one, talk to me right away, and don't make it obvious.
The VIP table upstairs.
Let's not cause a scene.
Stand your grounds and get them all at once when they-
We're from the Drug Investigation Unit.
Please stay put, and we ask for your cooperation.
Hey, sit down!
- Who the hell are you?
- Hey, sit down! Sit!
What the heck? What's going on?
Why does the Drug Investigation Unit come out of nowhere?
I think they're here for a crackdown.
Hey, you punk!
Damn it!
Stay still!
What? Where did he go?
- What are we going to ride?
- Hubby...
Hey, hurry up and run!
Hurry up and pack our stuff!
- W-What?
- I said pack our stuff!
Shit...
Hurry up and move, you punks.
Hey.
- What the hell are you?
- Me?
A prosecutor.
A prosecutor?
Yes.
Bast—
M-My bone, my bone!
Gosh!
This one's all right.
Oh, no!
- My bone, my bone!
- Stop being a wuss.
- You wuss!
- It hurts.
I told you I'm a prosecutor, but you kept acting up.
Hello.
Gosh, Prosecutor.
Hey.
I'm spent.
How was the stay at the temple?
It was lame. The food was bad, too.
Lee Seung Joon embezzled the company funds.
Who's Lee Seung Joon?
Jung Il group's oldest son?
If he's going to play with money, he shouldn't get caught.
If he's going to get caught, he shouldn't play with money.
How much is all this?
Fifty billion won?
The heir of a group tries this hard
to steal a couple of bucks? Gosh.
Yes, Chairman!
Yes, of course, I have your back.
It won't be in the newspaper,
so tell your son he can stand up straight.
Yes. Yes, yes.
Where's the jurisdiction for the case?
The Southern District Prosecutors' Office.
Arrange a visit to the southern district attorney.
And record Lee Seung Joon's story and put it in the archive.
Yes, Father.
What about Jin Jung?
The intelligence team says he's tracking down drug dealers.
He went all the way there in this situation?
He's quite something, all right.
What am I to do with him?
What's this guy doing that he's not calling me?
Prosecutor Jin?
Senior!
Are you hurt anywhere? Are you okay?
Yes, I'm all right.
Please do me a favor.
This is a ledger with the list of drug buyers.
They're all usernames.
The culprit is in there. The one who killed Chief Prosecutor.
From two weeks before Chief Prosecutor's death until the day of the incident,
there were a total of five drug buyers.
Please confirm their identities.
All right. I'll look into it.
It's important, so please get this done as-
I think someone was on your tail.
Damn it!
Hey, you bastard!
Go down, go down! Go down!
Hey, punk, get in here!
Go back up!
Damn it.
That little!
- Hey, you!
- Stop!
Oh, God.
That crazy nut!
Hey, come.
You can't come, can you?
- You can do it!
- Hold on, hold on.
- I'm coming for you!
- You're coming?
Don't. Don't do it. It's dangerous.
Are you okay?
Don't do it! Don't do it!
I said, don't come!
Hey, get him!
- Hey, stop!
- Hey!
Hey, bastard! Stop right there!
Get him!
Hey, stop right there!
Hey, stop!
Hey! Catch him, catch him!
Whoa! God.
Stop!
Shit...
Hey...
Man!
Hey! Come here!
What the hell?