(Child actors were accompanied
by a guardian...)
(and filmed in a safe,
supervised environment.)
(Episode 7)
But I'm full.
See you later.
Did you know
your wife is cheating on you?
It looks like she left with a man.
She completely stole my heart...
and acted like
she'd love me forever.
- She could've at least said bye.
- Don't look.
Then all of a sudden, poof.
If she just up and runs away...
How could she do that?
- What are you talking about?
- Hui Gyeong cheated on me.
She had an affair
and ran off behind my back.
She was cheating on me.
She just up and left.
Just like my father...
- She just...
- Dae Han.
Seong Mi, wait. Seong Mi...
I have a favor to ask.
Promise not to tell Mom
and Jeong Han. Okay?
If Mom and Jeong Han find out,
they'll be heartbroken...
Mom might collapse again,
so please just keep it a secret.
Collapse over what?
- Mother.
- Mom.
Collapse?
Why on earth would I collapse?
In your eyes,
do I really seem that weak?
Mom.
- Mom...
- Oh, my.
- Dae Han.
- Dae Han!
- Dae Han, are you okay?
- Mom, I was so...
- Dae Han.
- Hey.
- I'm sorry, Mom...
- Dae Han.
- I'm sorry.
- My gosh. Dae Han.
- Mom, Grandma.
What's wrong with Uncle?
- Woo Jae, help me with him.
- Yes, let me...
- I'm sorry, Mom.
- Here.
Hold him up.
I'm sorry, Mom.
- Here, careful.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, Mom.
- Mom, what's wrong with Uncle?
I'm sorry, Mom!
Uncle, how did you get this drunk?
Woo Jae.
Sorry, your uncle is such a fool.
Seong Mi, Mom... I'm sorry.
It's all my fault
that Hui Gyeong ran away.
What... What's he saying?
Let's step out, okay?
Mom.
Yes.
I'm your mother.
When things are this hard,
you should've come to me first.
Why are you facing this alone? Why?
Why are you hurting all by yourself?
Why?
Mom.
What do I do?
Mom, what am I going to do?
It's okay.
It's going to be okay.
Mom.
What do I do, Mom?
I don't get it.
She was packing to move yesterday.
How did Aunt Hui Gyeong run away?
What's going on?
I'm not really sure either.
Grandma must be so devastated.
Grandfather left the same way,
you know.
I know. If your dad finds out,
it'll be hard.
It'll bring up the past.
I'll just pretend
I didn't hear anything.
Okay. Go on upstairs.
- Good night, Grandma.
- Okay, you too.
Just leave him be. He'll be okay.
Okay, Mother.
What could Dae Han have done wrong?
Or was it...
something I did? Did I upset her?
No.
Of course not.
Don't even think that, Mother.
Oh, dear.
I never thought I'd live
to see a day like this again.
I'll try and take care of it.
Don't be silly.
You're too busy for that.
- Forget it.
- I can't let her get away with it.
I'll find her, get the story,
get our money and an apology.
It's the only way
we can all move on.
- I'm home.
- You're back?
Is Dae Han back?
Mom, how's Hui Gyeong's aunt?
Your brother's asleep,
- and they said her aunt is fine.
- I see.
You two go on in.
I'll head to bed soon, too.
But wait, Mom, you look upset.
Is something wrong?
Hey, come on. Let's go to our room.
Good night, Mother.
Go on. Let's go.
Let's postpone next week's filming.
- Why?
- Something came up at home.
Something at home?
Why? What's going on at home?
With your family, that is.
What is it?
Is there something I don't know?
Of course, there is.
There always is.
You're not interested anyway,
so I'll just handle it myself.
So just stay out of it
and focus on your work like always.
I'm calling Director Song, okay?
Hold on, just sit down.
I have a really funny story for you.
Forget it. I'm not in the mood.
No, but you have to hear this.
Bucket was so funny today.
I was laughing so hard
I almost died.
Why? What did he do this time?
Get this. The guy who begged me
on his knees to be Vice President...
is already skipping
morning workouts,
claiming he's sick.
So I sent him
that video of him kneeling.
And he came running
like his life depended on it.
- It was priceless!
- You recorded it?
No, from the security camera
at the clinic.
- I downloaded the footage.
- That guy is something else.
And that's not all. Check this out.
Here are the accounting ledgers
for the past three years...
and the event summary reports.
Organize them by category.
- Right now?
- Yes. When you're done with that,
run the night market survey.
Get it done this week.
By the end of this week?
Right. And you need to fill out
a daily work log,
report it to me,
and then you can clock out.
A work log?
Why can't I just tell you...
That's not going to work.
It's important to keep a record.
Yes, sir.
(Onjeong Market
Merchants' Association)
Pardon?
The toilet in Building A's restroom
is clogged?
That's a problem.
The maintenance staff have all left.
So there's no one here right now.
I guess I'll have to do it myself...
Wait. I've got someone right here.
Right, yes.
Yes. I'll send someone right over.
Don't mention it.
Just doing my job as president.
All right.
You heard that, right?
Building A's restroom.
So what?
Go unclog it.
Hey! These are a doctor's hands,
meant for taking pulses.
I was awarded "Golden Hands"
at the Korean medicine conference!
Goodness. There's a title
for everything, isn't there?
Who told you to use your bare hands?
That's what tools are for.
Come on,
you know I have a weak stomach.
I know. I hear
you can't use public toilets...
and have to run home
just to use the bathroom.
You know that,
and you still want me to unclog it?
Fine, if you don't want to,
you don't have to.
Now, where did I put that video?
Hey, you petty jerk.
This is so low and dirty.
Fine, I'll do it...
Hey, make sure you get that thing
good and clear, okay?
So? Don't tell me you quit
just because you felt...
it was gross and beneath you.
No.
Gosh, really.
Dr. Gong is going way too far.
That jerk humiliated me.
Should I really...
keep putting up
with this humiliation?
Of course.
This is all for your own good,
so you have to endure it.
How is any of this for me?
Look, honey.
Your valuable labor
got that toilet unclogged, right?
You solved someone's problem,
and their gratitude
will eventually...
turn into another vote
in your favor.
All this humiliation
just for one lousy vote?
We learned the hard way
how precious one vote is, honey.
Back then...
If only we'd gotten one more vote...
Honey, I heard Mr. Hwang...
was thrilled about you
becoming the Vice President.
Let's get some sun and enjoy
a round of golf this weekend, okay?
Come on, go get cleaned up.
I'll even put your body lotion on
for you tonight.
I love you.
Hurry. Go on now.
You think
that'll get rid of the smell?
Auntie!
Oh, boy...
He's not there.
Not at the gaming cafe,
not at the pool hall,
- or the sauna, Ji Hu.
- Hey, Dong Suk.
Ji Hu, could you give us a minute?
It's okay. I know what's going on.
My dad took your things, didn't he?
You think that's all he did?
He stole everything from the store
where he worked, too.
He even cleaned out
the bank account...
where he was saving his paychecks
and disappeared.
This is juicy! I must tell Grandpa.
- Yang Eun Bin!
- What?
If Grandfather finds out about this,
he'll call the police.
- Of course, he should. Grandpa...
- Come here.
Hey! If the neighborhood finds out,
it'll be a disgrace to our family!
The market gossip can be so vicious.
Forget about your dad's future.
It could reflect badly on you
and your brother, too.
I'm going to handle this quietly.
Nod if you understand.
Don't you forget
that this is a secret.
Then get me a spa membership!
- Deal!
- Sweet!
Yes.
Are you done yet? They say to hurry.
We're going to get some good food.
I'm not sure if I should use this
for my presentation.
What's wrong now? What?
Is it something about the Director?
Yes.
If I use this,
he'll figure out that I know...
that he's Yang Hyun Bin.
Isn't it time he knew you know?
Please, just tell him already.
How can I?
The Vice President is even here.
(Seohae Garden)
I wonder why the Vice President
and the Director aren't coming in.
You don't think they're fighting,
do you?
- This is all your fault.
- I know.
- I'm the traitor, the spy. Happy?
- Jerk...
Hey.
The Director might dump the VP
and switch over to you.
Gosh, you really need to stop
watching those dating shows.
Come on, it's not like the VP
isn't allowed to be here.
If you barge in and ignore my plans,
where does that leave me?
Is treating the employees to a meal
really worth getting so angry about?
And you're making them suffer
just to copy some reality show.
No! This is how they earn a reward
and pride that money can't buy. See?
That's the priceless experience
I'm trying to give them.
As Vice President,
I'm also looking out for the staff.
That is a bold-faced lie.
Just be honest with me,
and I'll forgive you.
The company is suffocating me,
and caring for my father
is too much.
I can't do anything I want,
let alone have a relationship.
But...
watching you and Ms. Gong Ju Ah
is so exciting and fun,
so I came here to live vicariously
through you two.
Fine. Then you only get to watch.
But you have to tell her
you're Yang Hyun Bin today.
Or I'll tell her myself.
Unbelievable.
Please, eat!
You must all be starving.
- Thank you for the food.
- Enjoy your meal.
So...
Am I making everyone uncomfortable?
- No, not at all.
- Of course not.
Not at all!
Not at all. You came all this way
and are even buying us dinner.
We're incredibly grateful.
Thank you. I'm glad you understand,
Mr. Park.
- Everyone, dig in.
- Enjoy your meal.
As you all know,
our Taehan Group began in fashion.
The Chairman has a soft spot
for the Fashion Division.
So I need you all
to win this competition...
and prove your talent
and your worth!
- We'll do our best!
- Yes.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thanks for the food.
The Chairman says our designers
illuminate our company's future...
Give it a rest!
Oh, right.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
Goodness...
- Eat up. Please, eat.
- Yes, let's eat.
- Yes, thank you for the food.
- Yes, enjoy.
I told you not to be so obvious,
didn't I?
- What? I didn't do anything.
- Whatever! Just hurry up and eat.
Pacu Nacho.
Looking at you up close...
You kind of look like an anteater.
You look like a sunfish.
Hey, sunfish are cute.
- Sure.
- Seriously. You just wait.
It's a good thing I came.
Without me,
the pairs would've been uneven,
right?
You're right. It's an honor
to have you draw me, Vice President.
Don't get your hopes up.
What's the point of this, Director?
This is...
To observe each other's faces
to bridge the psychological gap...
and communicate without words.
That's the purpose, Vice President.
After this,
we'll discuss the first creation,
and we'll share our motivations
to build a sense of unity.
No interruptions are allowed.
Got it?
That sounds boring.
Maybe we should have switched
your partners.
- Why is that?
- Since you two are a couple...
- Come on!
- My gosh!
Pacu Nacho and I are just friends.
That's all.
Really?
The rumor going around the office
is that you two are a couple.
The VP has a sick sense of humor,
lying to the executives.
Ms. Gong Ju Ah.
Do you have a boyfriend,
by any chance?
Excuse me, VP.
We're here for the workshop.
- Please save personal questions...
- She doesn't have one.
About three years ago, I think?
Her last one lasted
about 7 to 8 months.
- What are you doing?
- What?
Come to think of it,
why isn't our Pacu Nacho dating?
Now that I think about it,
he never dated in Argentina either.
Is there an unforgettable first love
you're hung up on?
Maybe a girl you liked
before you went abroad?
Right, Ms. Gong?
Shoot!
How did my eraser fly over there?
How weird.
Weird indeed.
When I was in elementary school,
I made this apron for my mom,
who used to run a restaurant.
When the nearby shop owners saw it,
they placed orders too,
and as I kept making things,
I ended up becoming the designer,
Jo Seong Min.
This scarf was...
the first birthday gift
I ever gave my dad.
This is an outfit
I made for my dog, Gamja.
Gamja passed away a while ago,
but she'll forever be my muse.
I was born and raised
without a father.
To this day,
I still don't know who he is.
What some might call
a child born out of wedlock.
When I was in high school,
I didn't know what to do in life,
so I was lost for a while.
But then,
my mother told me something.
She said my father had been
a clothing designer.
So I started studying hard
and made this. And with it,
I won the Taehan Design Contest.
If I ever get to meet
my father someday,
I want him to acknowledge me
as a designer in my own right.
Well, I...
What is it? Do you recognize that?
Well...
This handkerchief. When I was young,
a childhood friend was going abroad,
- so I made it as a farewell gift.
- Oh, my!
Make sure you come back happy.
Okay?
You crybaby. It's a farewell gift.
I made it myself.
This...
You really made this?
Yes.
Whenever you feel like crying,
look at this handkerchief.
Remember me calling you a crybaby,
and your tears will stop.
You know something?
You have a gift
for making people happy.
But to be honest,
I ended up using it more myself.
While I was in med school,
which I had no passion for,
I felt lost and kept wondering
if I was on the right path.
Every time I felt that way,
I cried into this handkerchief.
And every time I looked
at this handkerchief,
I'd remember my friend's words
and his bright smile.
"You have a gift
for making people happy."
So I made up my mind.
To become someone
who creates happiness.
But wait, why do you have it?
Did he give it back to you?
My friend doesn't know this, but...
I actually made two
so we could each have one.
Wow, so it was a matching set.
That's so romantic.
So was he your first love,
by any chance?
I'd say he means much more to me
than that.
He opened up my world
so I could live as a designer.
Yes.
The Chairman?
Sorry, everyone,
but I have to leave now.
Is the Chairman
in critical condition?
I won't know until I get there.
I'll call you when I arrive.
I'm coming with you.
Sorry, everyone.
We'll call you when we get there.
Mr. Park, I'm leaving you in charge.
Got it.
All right, then. Let's go.
What timing.
Sorry for ruining the moment.
This isn't my only chance.
For today, this is more than enough.
See? I told you.
I'm telling you, Ju Ah knew
you were Pacu Nacho all along.
I guess so.
My head's spinning,
wondering when she figured it out.
You two have a deeper connection
than I realized.
I was a little envious.
Even though you were apart,
your shared memories kept you going.
That's all in the past.
The Chairman will be all right,
won't he?
He has to be.
It's scary being an only child
at times like this.
If I had any siblings,
I'd have someone to lean on.
Why are you so antsy?
Are you that worried
about the Chairman?
Of course, I am.
It's natural to worry when you hear
an elder is sick, isn't it?
You're right. I'm worried, too.
Then why take it out on the fire?
Are you upset
that the Director left?
Upset? Of course, he had to go.
He's an executive, after all.
Look, if you ask me...
I think he and the Vice President
have already talked about you.
No matter how you slice it,
this was one heck of a workshop.
One day the Director confesses,
the next day you do.
What confession?
It's all just ancient history.
- Still, things will be different.
- Different? Whatever.
Our families are still enemies,
you know.
It's the Director.
Yes, Director.
Mr. Park, his breathing
was a bit unstable for a moment,
but I waited until he was stable
before I left.
It'd be awkward to go back,
so just carry on without me.
Understood. I'll send you photos.
Yes. See you at the office
in a couple of days.
Wait. Hello?
Gong Ju Ah is right here...
He hung up.
Is the Chairman okay?
Yes, thankfully.
But I wonder
why he didn't ask about you.
Why do you always have to
make things so weird?
Gosh, I'm going to bed.
And every time I looked
at this handkerchief,
I'd remember my friend's words
and his bright smile.
So I made up my mind.
To become someone
who creates happiness.
So was he your first love,
by any chance?
I'd say he means much more to me
than that.
He opened up my world
so I could live as a designer.
Wow, this pollack soup is great.
Dae Han.
When is your wife getting back?
She'll be back before the move?
She's at her aunt's place.
She said she's going to stay
a few more days.
So that's why you're so down?
Because your wife's away.
Goodness.
- I guess so.
- Woo Jae.
Can you order some supplies
for the pharmacy later?
Sure, but I have an online class
today,
so I'll get it done for you
tomorrow morning.
- Hurry up, you said you were late.
- What?
Yes.
By the way, Dae Han.
That new place you're moving into,
how big is it?
You should be thinking about
when you have kids,
so you should've looked
for something bigger...
Gosh, what's gotten into you today?
What? What did I do?
Why are you asking about family
you never cared about before?
Unbelievable. One minute you're mad
I don't care about family matters,
and the next you're mad that I do.
I can't win with you, seriously.
Gong Dae Han, finish up.
We need to go.
- Let's go. Time for our workout.
- Yes.
Unbelievable.
So what are we going to do?
What can we do? We should just wait.
He'll be back when his money's gone,
won't he?
Are you crazy?
You'd really take him back?
Hello, sir.
Have you heard from Ji Hu's Dad?
Heard from him?
I should be asking you that.
He has until the end of the day
to return the items or pay for them.
If he doesn't pay up,
I'm reporting him
to the police for theft.
Wait, how much is it in total?
Thirty thousand dollars?
How are we supposed to come up
with that kind of money right now?
Gosh, I can't deal with this!
This is driving me crazy!
What's to go crazy about?
Let him get reported and caught.
I'll give you back
the money you gave me,
so you can pay for the items first.
But what about the money
for your designer rentals?
That... I'll figure something out.
And how are you going to do that?
Exactly. How will you manage
without my father's permission...
to spend money?
Well, I'm sure there's a way.
What a waste of that Cabanel bag.
I never even got to use it.
Auntie, why on earth
did you marry a guy like that?
When your dad was pushing me
to get married,
he was the only man
who was interested in me.
- Divorce him. Find a good man.
- Hey.
What decent man would be...
crazy enough to date me?
(Pharmacy)
Mom, it's about Hui Gyeong.
She got her certification
a few months ago.
So she got it and still went out,
saying she was studying?
Yes.
It looked like she was checking out
properties in Ganghwa,
so I went to check it out.
But Ganghwa is so close.
Unbelievable. She's got some nerve.
And the fact that
she's seeing another man...
How did you find out?
I just... I happened to overhear it.
So, what now?
Mom.
What about you?
Why didn't you ever look for Dad?
I figured, what good would it do
to see that mess with my own eyes?
But...
now I regret it.
If only
I had gotten closure back then.
If I'd seen it for myself
and just cut him out of my heart.
For all those years,
I wouldn't have spent all that time
waiting and hoping he'd come back.
You need to get a divorce.
You can't go on living like this.
Okay.
It's a number I don't recognize.
Hello? Who is this?
It's a friend. Just a friend.
Bring you what?
How much is it?
Hey, forget it.
Is this why you called?
Because the other pharmacies
are too far?
No, that's not it.
I went to the clinic to see you,
but they said
you were at the pharmacy.
So I got your number.
So why were you looking for me?
To tell me not to spread
rumors about you?
That's right.
I won't talk if you don't.
Okay, fine. Deal.
Everyone at the market knows
why I'm living with my family.
If they find out
that jerk is in money trouble again,
I'll be too humiliated
to even show my face.
How much did he run off with?
All the money we've saved up,
plus the stolen designer goods...
It must be at least 100,000 dollars.
A hundred thousand dollars?
I have to go. Thanks for the drink.
Hey.
Gosh, you startled me.
Did you hear all that?
Please pretend
you didn't hear anything.
I didn't hear a thing.
(Warm and Reliable Police)
Thank you so much
for your help yesterday.
I'll be sure to repay this favor.
Please. It was nothing.
No, really. You were a huge help.
Chief, sorry about the other day.
I apologize.
Don't worry about it.
Well, then.
Mr. Gong.
I...
- I have the license plate number.
- Sorry?
Yes, I saw it on the store's CCTV
and jotted down the number.
- Really?
- But...
we can't give you the number
or run a check on it.
If you file an official report,
then we can help.
- Can't you just tell me the number?
- We can't.
(We're here to help with anything.)
Right.
No, that's okay.
Never mind.
Oh, wait...
Oh, man. You were right, Chief.
See?
Sometimes, ignorance is bliss.
He might change his mind,
- so I'll hang on to it.
- Good idea.
(License Plate: 314 J9542)
(Onjeong Market
Merchants' Association)
Darn it.
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
Hey, for plastic bottles,
peel the label and crush them flat.
And sort the glass bottles by color.
Brown, green, and clear.
Separate them.
- Seriously.
- What do you want from me?
- Have you ever recycled before?
- Yes... What?
Keep that up,
and you'll get divorced again.
Hey, no need to make it personal.
You need to learn to do this right.
And do some housework for a change.
Sort white and colored Styrofoam.
Clean plastic bags get recycled,
and dirty plastic goes
in the regular trash.
Gosh, honestly.
This is some disgusting trash,
and there's so much of it.
Gosh, this guy doesn't get
that these bags cost money!
Stomp it down to pack it tight!
Seriously...
Hey, I already stuffed it full!
You can fit more if you stomp on it!
Hurry, stomp it down! Stomp!
Hurry! Come on!
Are you even thinking? Seriously.
- Just a second.
- For crying out loud.
Would you stop fooling around?
Just stomp on it! Hurry!
- Just like this?
- Yes, it's open. Now stomp it down!
- Pack it tight. Yes.
- Do we really have to do this?
Harder! Push down harder! Go on.
Come on!
You have to stomp on it harder!
- You're a big guy, use your weight!
- Goodness.
Tighter! That's it!
There you go! Good job, Dr. Yang.
- Great job! Way to go!
- Gosh!
Hold on.
What?
Food waste must be separated! Hey!
Over here! The food waste goes here!
Darn it...
Gosh, so embarrassing. Seriously.
And of all things,
I was wearing white pants.
Will this stain come out?
Oh, my, Doctor!
At this hour,
what brings you here?
I took some time off.
Don't say you lost all your patients
because of that rumor I started.
Back then...
I was so terribly sorry.
Gosh, I must've been out of my mind.
Anyway, congratulations.
On Dr. Yang becoming Vice President
of the Merchants' Association.
Thank you.
I appreciate that, but...
Dr. Gong is just so mean.
He torments and bullies my husband
like a bratty little kid.
He says it's hard?
And to think he got on his knees
and begged for any work at all.
Oh, my.
Dr. Gong must've been bluffing
in front of you, Doctor.
My husband did not get on his knees.
Oh, come on. Dong Ik must have been
embarrassed, so he lied to his wife.
He got down on his knees.
That's impossible.
Do you have proof?
I do.
I learned from someone recently.
The importance of having proof.
Well, then...
Gong Jeong Han, that jerk.
I knew it.
I knew he'd go running to Seong Mi.
That jerk!
Honey.
- Is that what's important now?
- It's humiliating!
You think that's the problem here?
Then what is?
If that video ever gets out,
it'll definitely be an obstacle
when you run for city council.
Then what do we do?
(Gong Myeong Jeong Dae Han Clinic)
You must get your hands
on Dr. Gong's phone.
What good will that do?
I don't know the password.
It's definitely a backwards L.
Or maybe just an L.
Whatever it takes,
find out the password first.
What the...
Why show your face
to the phone like that?
Oh, this? It's facial recognition.
It's easy to use with one hand. Why?
Oh, I see. I was just curious.
What's this? Did you text me?
- What?
- Oh, I...
"You're working so hard?"
That's just how I feel.
You're ridiculous. Seriously.
Once you figure out the password,
think of Muhammad Ali.
- Who?
- Muhammad...
Ali.
Float like a butterfly,
sting like a bee.
Hey, Jeong Han.
What?
Jeong Han.
Gosh, what is it?
- What the... What are you doing?
- Unlocking it.
- What?
- There. Mission complete.
Hey, you! You little punk!
Hey! You...
Hey, Bucket! You little punk!
You little jerk!
Hey, you! Get back here!
Are you crazy? You little jerk!
Hey, you jerk! You punk!
- Hey! Bucket!
- Stop chasing me, darn it.
Stop right there! Hey!
(Grandma's Home-Style Gukbap)
Bucket! You're dead if I catch you!
Come on, where is it?
Why won't this work?
Gosh, where is it? Come on, please.
- This isn't it. That's not me.
- Bucket.
Oh, man.
Looking for the video?
You think you'd find it there?
- Then where is it?
- Do your homework.
- It's saved forever on the cloud.
- Darn... So why did you chase me?
Because it was fun. Come on.
Man, you're fast when you run away.
- Darn you...
- See you in the morning.
You slippery eel.
You rotten jerk!
Ouch, it hurts.
Somebody help me.
Man, It really hurts.
My gosh, honey.
- What's with this mess?
- Oh, no. What happened?
Oh, my goodness.
Look at all this sweat.
Dad, your foot is bleeding.
Gosh, Father.
I'll go get a bandage from the room.
- Oh, no.
- What were you doing out there?
Does he work for the association
with his fists? Right, Grandpa?
His medical bills will cost more
than he earns.
Quiet!
A freeloader like you has no right
to worry about his medical bills.
I was just saying...
Gosh, unbelievable.
There's no one on my side
in this house. Is there?
The clinic.
(Gong Myeong Jeong Dae Han Clinic,
Yang Seon Chul)
(Date Dispensed: February 14, 2026)
Why is this...
My gosh.
Father.
- Did you get treatment from here?
- What?
Yes.
Dad, don't we have an unspoken rule
that we don't go to that clinic?
Quiet! Give that here.
But what's wrong, Father?
Where are you feeling sick?
You should have told me.
It's nothing serious.
Just give it here.
Wait, hold on a second, Father.
But the fill date...
is the day before
the Association President Election.
So what about it?
Dad, don't tell me...
Dad, don't tell me
you voted for Jeong Han.
- You didn't, right?
- I said, quiet!
Dad, why didn't you answer me
back then?
Answer what?
Father.
In exchange for the treatment,
did they ask you for your vote?
No. Jeong Han's not
that kind of person.
He was just doing
his duty as a doctor.
So you did vote for him.
You voted for that jerk
and not for me.
Father.
Please tell us the truth.
Fine, I voted for him.
I voted for Gong Jeong Han.
So what? It's my choice.
Father!
Get out!
So was he...
your first love, by any chance?
I'd say he means much more to me
than that.
He opened up my world
so I could live as a designer.
Why did I say that?
I'm cringing so hard right now.
Seriously.
What was it like seeing her again?
Do you still have feelings for her?
I do.
He still likes me? Good grief.
But now, what do I do?
Should I pretend I don't know?
I acted like I recognized him,
but he just pretended not to.
So should I still pretend
I don't know?
What is going on?
Yes, Director.
Gong Ju Ah.
Gong Ju Ah?
That's right. Ju Ah.
It's me.
Yang Hyun Bin.
I'm back.
Yes. Hyun Bin.
If you have a minute,
could you come out?
Right now? Where are you?
The last place we saw each other.
So you're really back,
Yang Hyun Bin.
Yes.
Have you been well?
What about you?
Did you find your happiness?
I made up my mind right then.
I had to be happy, no matter what,
and I would never cry again.
So that if I ever met her again
someday...
I wanted her to be proud
of the life I'd lived.
You did well.
You've lived a very good life,
Yang Hyun Bin.
Thanks to you.
It's good to see you again,
Yang Hyun Bin.
I've missed you,
Gong Ju Ah.
I wish we could have met like this
from the very beginning.
Tell me about it.
We took the long way around
to get here.
I'm sorry I had to leave yesterday
without a chance to talk.
We were at a workshop,
so it felt wrong
to talk in front of the staff.
Of course, I understand.
So when did you figure out
it was me?
At that chicken soup restaurant?
No, Gaetdari Samhap.
When you were drunk and sang for me.
- Why didn't you say anything then?
- You're the one who ran off.
- I did?
- And you treated me like a creep.
Sorry.
Waiting for you to recognize me
was torture.
How was I supposed to recognize you?
You've changed so much.
That's a relief.
I worked really hard to change,
you know.
But then why didn't you say anything
after you knew it was me?
I mean, come on.
You're the director.
Let's just be casual
outside of work.
Okay.
Then you have to treat me
like your big sister.
What? No, thanks.
My gosh.
Ju Ah?
- Hey, brother.
- What?
- Is that your brother?
- Yes.
Woo Jae... You remember the director
from my company, right?
Yang Hyun Bin.
Hello.
Hey, Woo Jae. Long time no see.
I almost
wouldn't have recognized you.
By the way, Eun Bin,
what are you doing here?
We have a date tomorrow, so
I gave Woo Jae the matching shirts.
Then he offered to walk me home,
so we were on our way...
- And then we saw you.
- Wait, hang on. What? A date?
Matching shirts?
Hey, let's talk at home.
Right, let's go home, Eun Bin.
Hey, you'll be in huge trouble
if anyone sees you together.
Right? If my stepmom saw
the four of us together,
she'd totally flip out,
wouldn't she?
I'm so happy.
I think my wish is coming true.
- What wish?
- Double in-laws.
Hey, let's go.
- Ms. Gong, I'll see you at work.
- Yes, Director. Get home safe.
Woo Jae, see you tomorrow.
And I'll see you again!
Or should I say sister-in-law?
Hey, let's go. Come on. Bye.
We're going the same way,
so let's go. See you, sister-in-law!
Why, you...
I'm telling you,
we're not really dating.
Explain the date
and the matching shirts.
Spit it out. Five, four, three...
Eun Bin told me it was her stepmom
who spread the rumor...
that our mom was having an affair.
So?
She said I owe her. Because of her,
our dad won the election.
So I just agreed
to go out with her once.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
You're one to talk. What about you?
You said you'd ignore him,
so why were you so cozy at the cafe?
What if our parents find out?
Who do you think
you're talking back to?
Eyes down!
I am looking down!
You're just shorter than me.
Quiet!
Enough with the constant back talk.
So, nothing happened at home, right?
Yes, nothing.
What was that? You hesitated.
Something happened, didn't it?
Eyes front. What is it? Spill it.
- Hey. Headlock for old time's sake?
- No.
It's about Uncle.
What about Uncle?
Uncle.
Ju Ah.
- How was your workshop?
- It was fine.
What are you watching, Uncle?
Just flipping through channels.
- Can I have a beer?
- Of course.
This is nice. Here, cheers.
Cheers.
Goodness.
Uncle...
Gong Jeong Han, that jerk.
Are you that upset, honey?
Ever since we were kids,
they always compared us.
It was always, "Jeong Han this,
Jeong Han that."
But still.
How could he not vote for me?
Honey.
This is really depressing.
Grandpa, you really went too far
this time.
Exactly, Dad.
After seeing how hard he worked,
how could you vote
for the other guy?
Dad's so petty, he'll sulk forever.
He's even skipping breakfast.
You all can go ahead and eat.
I don't really have
an appetite either.
It was all for Dong Ik's sake.
Jeong Han has no political ambition,
so he would do a proper job.
Dong Ik, on the other hand...
His only goal was getting elected,
so he would've ignored his duties.
I guess you're right.
If that happened, he would've
lost his run for council.
He must win people over for votes,
just like he's doing now.
You're absolutely right, Father.
Then please, enjoy the food.
How much do you want?
I'll give it to you as an apology.
How much will it take
to make things right?
Forty thousand dollars, Father.
Done.
Forty thousand?
Dad always takes your side.
Forty thousand dollars,
just like that.
Isn't this what they call
a blessing in disguise?
Such is life.
I'm going to get ready.
Could you do the dishes first?
Of course.
You think I'd only do the dishes?
I'll do anything.
Where are you off to?
A lady I met in a class
at the community center told me...
about a private detective agency
great for finding runaway husbands.
A private detective agency?
- A lawyer?
- Yes. I know a family lawyer.
I'm going to go talk to them
about our realistic options.
Okay.
I thought you were heading out
today.
I'm just going to buy some supplies
for the pharmacy before I go.
By the way, about this laptop...
Aunt used this sometimes too, right?
Yes, she did. Why?
It's automatically logged in
to a web portal with her email.
- What?
I thought it was my account,
but it has a new order and address.
Wait, Cabanel?
Cabanel. It's Cabanel.
Cabanel... Stepmom.
Stepmom!
- The Cabanel bag's been listed.
- What?
I think Uncle listed it
on a resale app to sell it!
- Really?
- Yes, really! Where's Aunt?
Excuse me, Chief.
By any chance, can you do location
or vehicle tracking?
(Warm and Reliable Police)
That's a hot request these days.
Location and vehicle tracking.
Is this about a family member?
If you file a missing person report,
we can help you with that.
No, it's not like that.
I couldn't just sit around,
so I thought I'd come and ask.
- I see.
- Right.
Excuse me.
Can't you just run the license plate
through the system?
- Can't you do it for me?
- I can't do that.
- Please, sir. I'm begging you.
- What?
Can't you just find out where he is?
The plate is 314 J9542.
- I can't.
- Wait, 314 J9542?
- Chief, please. Just this once.
- We can't.
- Chief, please. Just once...
- Auntie! I know where Uncle is!
- What?
- That Cabanel bag! For real! Hurry!
- Where is he?
- Quick!
- Chief?
- What?
The person
that lady is looking for...
I think it's this guy.
What?
Mom, I think that's the place.
(Hui Gyeong Hair Salon)
Hurry up and come out, honey.
That's Hui Gyeong.
Honey, just a second.
(Hui Gyeong Hair Salon)
Hey, that guy.
Oh, my. Wait.
Isn't he the son-in-law
from the Korean medicine clinic?
No way.
- Honey, wait just a second.
- Okay.
- Mom, Grandma.
- I can't believe it.
What is it?
Look.
- This is it, right?
- Dong Suk, over here!
- What now?
- If you go this way...
It's close by.
(Recipe For Love)
Are you protesting or something?
- Gong Ju Ah and I are just friends.
- Friends?
We're old friends.
Then why the long face?
Are you sure you're just friends?
Men and women can't be just friends.
Well...
What about my place?
But apparently, their parents
have also been my patients.
I wonder who they are.
How about a blind date
with my brother?
A blind date?
We truly love each other.
Loving someone's no crime, is it?
Hey!