(Child actors were accompanied
by a guardian...)
(and filmed in a safe,
supervised environment.)
(Episode 47)
I'm going to walk away.
Listen carefully, Gong Ju Ah.
If you let me go now,
we're really over.
Don't go.
Don't go, Yang Hyun Bin.
Don't turn your back on me.
Gosh.
What's taking those two so long?
- Are they fighting again?
- Again? Did they fight often?
- Often? More like every day.
- Gosh, it was so awkward.
They were at each other's throats
any chance they got.
Really?
Gosh,
since they were always together,
I thought a romance might blossom.
Romance? More like a thriller.
By any chance...
- Interested in marrying Hyun Bin?
- Excuse me?
Mother!
I really got ahead of myself.
Have you talked to Hyun Bin
about it?
Father.
At this rate,
Hyun Bin is going to disown me.
Be prepared for that,
and push forward.
Father.
If you can't, I will.
No, wait...
Why is he suddenly being like this?
But this is strange.
See? You still liked me
even after we broke up.
Look who's talking. You said
you had no personal feelings.
You kept being so touchy.
I should have known
when you kissed me as a dare.
So what now? Want to start over?
You told me not to go.
Not to turn my back on you.
No, that's different.
So you have feelings for me
but no confidence?
It's just that nothing has changed
since we broke up.
But the feud between our families
is over.
Instead,
our families became in-laws.
Do you even love me?
Why all of a sudden?
You can't answer, can you?
Honestly, I don't know
if I have the right to say it.
Because I don't know
what we are anymore.
Then think about it.
Think about what our relationship
should be from now on,
and let's talk tomorrow
when we're sober.
- Tomorrow?
- Why? Do you need more time?
No, that's fine. Tomorrow.
We'll talk tomorrow.
- She should really tone it down.
- I'm home.
- Yes.
- You're back.
You're back?
You're pretty late today.
- We had a dinner at my aunt's.
- I see.
Ju Ah, I heard you're going back
to work at Taehan?
Yes, the brand I launched
got absorbed into Taehan Fashion.
Hey, Gong Ju Ah.
You aren't, by any chance,
seeing Director Yang again, are you?
No, Dad.
Who's Director Yang?
The grandson
from the herbal medicine clinic.
Remember,
we saw him at the hospital.
- Seon Chul's grandson?
- Yes.
She was dating him?
- We almost had double in-laws.
- Well, that is...
- They broke up before that, Father.
- Right.
That's a relief.
- I'm going to head upstairs, then.
- Okay, sure.
- Turn it on.
- Okay.
To Stylist Yang,
who has finally made a name
for herself.
- Cheers.
Are you that happy just because
the CEO said your name?
Her saying my name...
wasn't just part of the process.
It was the result.
Until then,
I was a complete nobody.
Just like Yang Eun Bin
to Gong Woo Jae.
Hey, what do you mean
you're a nobody to me?
I said "before." In the past.
Anyway, for someone like me
who felt invisible,
to become someone who is wanted...
is such a special thing, is it not?
Like Yang Eun Bin to Gong Woo Jae?
Me?
What are you talking about?
If you don't get it, never mind.
- Then let's toast again.
- Cheers.
But I knew you could do it.
Ever since you were a kid,
once you set your mind to something,
you always saw it through.
Remember in elementary school,
when you tried...
to collect all the stickers
from that character bread?
Do you remember eating
only that bread for months?
To be honest,
I was not collecting the stickers.
- What?
- Since you were collecting, I did.
Why?
I was creating something
to talk about.
So you would say
at least one more word to me.
I...
I really liked you a lot.
Not anymore?
What?
Of course not.
Not anymore.
What should I do?
I have only just started
to like you.
What did you say?
I said I have only just started
to like you.
I am sorry. Am I too late?
I am kidding.
- You were so surprised.
- Gosh.
What? I cannot believe
I did not know it was a joke.
How embarrassing. Gosh.
Well...
Our CEO is going on an overseas
business trip,
and she asked me if I had
a passport. I was so thrilled.
Hey.
I mean, how did she know
I just renewed it?
Is she going to take me with her?
Hey.
- You scared me. What a surprise.
- Hey, Min Ji Hu.
You have been drinking.
Yes, it was my treat.
Since Ji Hu is here,
I will get going.
Yes, you should go. Get out of here.
I will go. I am going.
You do not have to tell me to go.
Okay, get home safe, Woo Jae.
- Hey. Let's go inside.
- Hey.
- What?
- Do you still like Woo Jae?
- Hey, of course not.
- Then stop hanging out with him.
He likes you.
What does a little kid
like you know?
Hey, you do not know anything.
We are just in-laws.
Is that so?
You are the one
who does not know anything.
Wow.
Outstanding store owner
Cha Se Ri. What?
Wow, how is Se Ri so capable
at everything she does?
Oh, stop it, you.
Right, what happened with
Councilor Hwang?
That?
He said he is giving up
the nomination.
I am sorry, Se Ri.
No. You did well.
Really?
Did I really do the right thing?
Honestly,
I was getting sick and tired of...
having to please
Councilor Hwang's wife.
Gosh, you went through so much.
I am sorry.
You are the one who had it rough.
Anyway, honey. About your father...
I mean, why is he suddenly
pushing us so hard?
After Mom passed away
the way she did,
I think it might be guilt.
He probably feels
he has to do better...
by his remaining children.
I think he's stressed
about that, too.
I know, but still,
him pushing us
to get Yang Hyun Bin married...
it's just so exhausting.
Can't he marry Jeong Han's daughter?
Honey.
No, I mean, honestly,
becoming double in-laws,
it's not that big of a deal
nowadays.
I'm sure I can convince Father.
Right?
No, I can't do it. I can't.
Didn't you see
at the formal family meeting,
how she looked me right in the eye
and talked back to me.
Come on,
she had good reason to back then.
Fine. Okay.
I know I was in the wrong,
so I'd understand
if other people did it.
Like Dr. Han Seong Mi
or your sister.
If Ms. Na had done it,
I'd honestly be fine.
But Gong Ju Ah, she has no right
to treat me like that.
No matter if they broke up,
I'm her ex-boyfriend's mother.
- I guess so?
- Honestly, no one in our family...
knew they were dating
until they broke up.
But our Yang Hyun Bin went over
to their house...
and it seems he did all he could
to get their blessing.
It looked like only our
Yang Hyun Bin was madly in love,
- and that made me even more upset.
- That's true, isn't it?
Do you even love me?
You can't answer, can you?
Why couldn't I answer him?
Wait, you want to go back
to being a doctor?
Yes.
Why? You don't think I can do it?
I can.
Who said you couldn't?
But isn't your medical license
suspended?
I'll have to go to
the Medical Association.
Why?
Did you remember something again?
No. You were always
tripping over stones...
and about to fall.
Right.
You'd tell me to watch my step,
and you'd nag me so much about it.
So don't just look ahead.
Watch where you're walking.
It was nice you lost your memory
and stopped nagging.
I guess the good old days are over.
Take my hand.
What's this?
You're running for city council
as an independent?
Yes.
The idea of
tearing down Onjeong Market...
was something
I just couldn't stand for.
And you think you can win?
I have to try.
- Jeong Han agreed to help.
- Do your best.
- You have to win this election.
- Yes, Father.
Sweetie.
A lady shouldn't eat like that.
Yes, she can. You should try eating
like this too, Mom.
Goodness, so unrefined.
I was in a beauty pageant, you know.
- Pageant contestants aren't people.
- Why you little...
That's right.
You're always watching your figure,
eating like a bird,
- that's why you're always anemic.
- All right.
By the way,
who were you drinking with...
that you came home
so late last night?
It was a work dinner.
But Grandfather, what's wrong with
being double in-laws?
I heard
there's no legal issue with it.
What do you mean,
"what's wrong with it?"
Think how tangled
the family tree would get.
How will our ancestors even receive
their proper memorial rites?
How could I face our ancestors
in the afterlife?
My goodness, Father.
Why do you keep talking about dying?
Father, are you feeling unwell?
It's nothing. Just eat.
So, you're really running
as an independent?
Yes. Father said we should do
what you suggested.
What I suggested?
But our brilliant daughter-in-law
said it herself.
We didn't believe in rumors.
We believed in people.
But if we start hating people now
and get rid of the market,
it won't be Jo Mi Hyang
who took 30 years from us.
We will have lost who we are.
- Did he really say that?
- He really did.
Dae Han and I got persuaded
just like that.
When Yang Dong Ik heard that,
he became determined
to run as an independent.
It's great having Father around.
Goodness, why do the women here
hide when they struggle?
Oh, is that so?
I'm telling you.
You and your mother-in-law
are both the same,
always acting so tough.
- Honey.
- Yes?
It's just...
Where I had my radiation therapy,
it stings a lot.
- Could you take a look?
- Really?
Let me see.
What is this? My goodness.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I know. I don't know why I keep
hiding things from you.
This must have stung so much,
even with your clothes
brushing against it.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Come on,
let's get you to the hospital
right away.
I'll dress the wound for you.
- Nice. Should've done this sooner.
- I know.
- Come on.
- You silly. Honestly.
It's all right.
What was that?
- You did well.
- Mom, Father, it's time to eat.
Okay.
Wow, this looks delicious.
Yes, please have a seat.
Honey, you should sit here today.
Me?
- This was always your seat.
- Was it?
Mom, that was your seat
for 30 years.
Are you giving your seat to Father?
I want to now.
Well then, shall I?
Didn't this used to be
a low table we sat at,
not a dining table like this?
- Do you remember, Father?
- I remember it vaguely.
Yes. We replaced it with this table
not long ago.
And we also got a bed
for Mother's room.
I see.
- Why'd you get such a small one?
- Pardon?
Well...
Well, since you sleep on the floor,
isn’t it uncomfortable?
There's that,
but sleeping separately
doesn't feel right, does it?
Father, we'll get a bigger one.
- Let's do that.
- Of course. Of course we should.
Yes, we should.
I guess Father wants to sleep
with Mother.
Of course,
a married couple should share a bed.
You'll say anything
in front of the grandchildren.
Grandma,
we're all grown up, you know.
Grandma, your face is turning red.
This kid...
Why are you kids acting like this?
Just eat your dinner.
- Yes, let's eat. Woo Jae, you...
- Let's eat. Eat up.
Mom, your ears are really red.
Look, they're so red.
- Her ears are red.
- They're so red.
(Taehan)
It's been a while
since we all had a meeting together.
I've missed this. The unique energy
of the Design Office.
But what are you doing here?
I'm always here, so I guess
I've just gotten used to it...
Is there anything for me to do?
Vice President?
Please have some dignity.
You're one to talk.
I can't even go outside.
I'm afraid Director Baek
will beat me up.
Okay, now that
Pelliv is successfully...
established in the online market,
we now need to expand
our customer contact points offline.
How about we open a pop-up store?
If the response is good,
we can look into opening
an official store.
Good. FG should focus on
brand reorganization.
Please share your ideas
and suggestions...
on how we can win back
our customers' trust.
How about we invite
our VIP customers for a golf event?
I agree.
It's a charity event,
so it'll help improve our image,
and it's a perfect way to show
that the brand is still strong.
Okay. Since this is
the first official event...
since Taehan Fashion's founding,
I need everyone to put special care
into the preparations.
Ms. Gong.
Can I see you for a minute?
So, have you thought about
what we discussed yesterday?
What? Yes, I did think about it,
but not really...
Then can I go first?
Go first with what?
(Yang Hyun Bin's Strategy
For Gong Ju Ah)
To convey my feelings
more accurately,
I prepared a presentation.
- You didn't have to do all this.
- I'll get to the conclusion.
My ultimate goal is...
(Yang Hyun Bin's Strategy
To Marry Gong Ju Ah)
to marry you.
To achieve that goal,
I will take responsibility...
for removing all obstacles
in advance.
There are two main obstacles. First.
My mother.
As a stressor for Dr. Han Seong Mi,
who is currently ill,
the risk of conflict
with her mother-in-law...
and living with in-laws' hardships
have been identified as concerns.
I will counter my mother
with a strategy...
- of blocking and controlling.
- Blocking and controlling?
Mother, from now on,
you must maintain...
physical distance from
my wife and me.
What? Physical distancing?
What's that?
The location of our newlywed home
will not be disclosed,
and during family events
such as holidays and birthdays,
we will schedule overseas trips
and other external events...
to completely block
any possible contact...
between Mother and Ju Ah.
Mother, that aggressive stare
is also strictly forbidden...
- from now on.
- Hey, Yang Hyun Bin!
Second.
My grandfather, who is against us
becoming double in-laws.
Since he values
traditional family views...
and customs,
I will persuade him with sound logic
and evidence.
What? What did you just say?
Considering double in-laws taboo
is just an outdated way of thinking.
Furthermore, it is not grounds
for prohibiting marriage...
under civil law,
so there are no legal problems
at all.
But if the two families...
If the two families are intertwined,
you're worried that a small conflict
could escalate, aren't you?
That's not true. On the contrary,
it will maximize the bond
between our families,
creating the optimal structure
for an even stronger relationship.
So what happens after you solve
both of those issues?
Then, I'll go to your house.
- My house?
- Yes.
A strategy I'm benchmarking
from Dae Han.
I'm here, Father, Mother.
What is all this?
I, Yang Hyun Bin, want to spend
the rest of my life with Gong Ju Ah.
Please give us your permission
to marry.
What's going on?
Please give me your permission,
Father, Mother!
- Hey, but...
- Why? You don't think I can do it?
You saw me protect
the Fashion Division.
When I say I'll do something,
I do it.
Okay, I get it. But...
About us.
What if we just date?
So you mean we date
and then get married?
No, does marriage have to be
the end goal?
What do you mean?
To be honest, I'm not sure if I want
to get married.
If I get married,
my life will change,
and I'll have more responsibilities.
It's not just about being a wife.
- I'd have to become a mother soon.
- Of course.
Hyun Bin, I really like you.
You're so important to me.
But you don't want to get married?
It's not about forcing the marriage
against our families' wishes.
How can we live like this
our whole lives? They're our family.
So?
Well, instead of marriage...
What about moving in together?
I think of living together
as a trial run for marriage.
If we live together,
I'll still want to get married.
No, why does marriage have to be
our future?
Can't we just have our relationship
on our own terms?
What are you really trying to say?
I'm saying it's too soon for me.
There's still so much I want to do,
and I don't want to get married
and settle down.
So the reason we broke up wasn't
because our families are enemies.
You...
You just weren't ready
to share a future with me.
What do you want to do then?
I don't want to be strangers.
Okay, so what do you want to do?
Can we just be friends?
Fine. Okay. Let's be friends.
But I can't be your friend
while I'm still in love with you.
I'll try to be a real friend to you.
Okay. Thank you.
Hey, you...
You never planned on marrying
Director Yang?
Wait, so then the thing about
Dr. Han being sick...
and you not liking
Director Yang's mother,
that was all just an excuse?
- Was it an excuse?
- You weren't head over heels.
I like him a lot too.
If you really did,
you would've never broken up. Right?
You would've been determined
to overcome anything...
and found a way through it.
No, I mean, seriously.
Hey, have you ever told
Director Yang that you love him?
- So I haven't.
- Come on.
I mean, I just wanted to date more,
try living together,
and take things slowly...
Take things slowly? Give me a break.
Director Yang is putting
his entire life on the line for you.
Don't lead him on
if you have no intention...
of marrying him.
- Lead him on?
- Yes, lead him on. Get it?
Think about it.
Honestly, how devoted...
has Director Yang been to you?
He confessed his feelings
so many times.
But you just kept playing
with his heart...
and rejected him over and over.
I guess that's true.
I guess we were on different pages.
Well, to be honest...
you were the only one
putting in the effort.
I see.
But...
they do say it's better
for the marriage...
when the man is more in love.
So what? I should beg her some more?
No, why would you beg her?
Just a little...
I'm just saying you should
push her a little more.
If she loved me so much that
she couldn't break up with me,
and was willing
to overcome anything,
then I'd try harder too.
But she's so unsure and hesitant.
How can I force her into it?
That's true...
Marriage isn't something
you can make happen on your own.
If we both wanted it,
we would've gotten married
before my aunt did.
Gosh, this herbal medicine
is so bitter.
Should I complain to your dad?
All herbal medicine is bitter.
Here, have a piece of candy.
Gosh. Dolphin should have one, too.
Here you go.
I'll have one.
Here, you finish this.
What is this? Looks like you two
already claimed this spot.
I'm sorry.
So you two are
an official couple now,
out in the open.
- Yes, well, he proposed to me.
- My goodness.
Really?
- So the proposal was a success.
- Yes.
We're moving on from just dating
to marriage.
- Wonderful. Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Why are you drinking medicine?
- This?
We're trying for a baby.
A mini Mr. Gong?
Just imagining it is so cute.
I know, right?
It's not easy at our age,
but we're going to try our best.
I hope we hear good news soon.
We will.
Should I add promoting childbirth
to my platform? Go, go, go.
- Go for it.
Mr. Gong.
Hey, so did you submit the papers
to leave the party?
Yes. They processed it right away,
as if they had been waiting for it.
To run as an independent,
you need signatures...
from over 100 supporters, you know?
Do you think
I'll even be able to get them?
Hey, come on.
Where'd that confident Bucket
I used to know go?
- What? Getting cold feet?
- Hey, I even lost to you.
What chance do I have
against Councilor Hwang?
I'm also worried
I'll run for nothing,
only to fade into obscurity.
This guy. Hey, I'm Gong Jeong Han.
Hey, you. Get up. Get up.
Let's go to
the Merchants' Association Hall.
- The Merchants' Association Hall?
- Yes.
Why there?
The merchant executives
are gathering...
to plan your campaign strategy.
- Really?
- Yes.
Excuse me. Excuse me, Doctors.
- Yes?
- Hello.
Is it true that...
Councilor Hwang is tearing down
our market?
Is it true?
Excuse me, where did you hear that?
Yesterday,
Councilor Hwang met separately...
with just the landlords...
and talked about some landmark
or whatever.
That son of a...
He's acting just like I used to.
The market isn't going anywhere.
Don't you worry.
- Is that right?
- Yes, yes. Of course.
- Don't worry.
- My goodness.
Dr. Yang, Dr. Gong.
Councilor Hwang,
did you meet with the landlords
separately?
I'm just doing my job.
How could you tell them
you're getting rid of the market?
I'm not getting rid of the market.
I'm creating a landmark.
Dr. Yang,
my campaign is going to run a poll.
- A poll?
- With you an independent candidate.
We'll see how you do.
I'm very much looking forward
to the results.
I checked with
the Medical Association.
They said you need to submit
an explanation...
for why you didn't get
continuing education...
or report your license for 30 years.
Honey, just in case, you should go
to the university hospital...
and get a checkup.
It would be good to have
a doctor's note...
saying you're fit
to practice medicine.
My dear is as smart
and sharp as ever.
Honey, let's make this work.
You and Jeong Han,
working side-by-side...
at the hospital...
I really want to see that.
I'll make sure you do.
Is there any more of this?
You're going back to being a doctor?
And I was just thinking
about retiring.
What are you talking about,
retiring?
You're still in your prime.
My prime?
I'm old enough to die any day now.
Hey, I was locked up for 30 years
and just got out.
Is that what you should be
saying to me?
People live to be 100.
I'm going to live
for another 30 years.
Sure, whatever.
You can go ahead and live happily
ever after with your wife.
I'll just go to the afterlife
and see In Ok.
Hey, why do you keep acting like
you have one foot in the grave?
Gi Cheol.
Everyone has to die.
Life is just a brief event...
that happens before you die.
Gosh. What are you talking about?
I'm just saying it's a brief event.
Gosh.
(Sunhwa Real Estate)
Don't tell anyone
I'm liquidating my assets.
Yes, sir. Goodbye.
So Hye, I'm at a real estate office
about Pelliv's office.
Mr. Yang. So Hye, hold on.
Hello.
Who...
Sorry?
I'm the granddaughter
from the clinic, sir.
Sir, sir.
- My gosh.
- Are you okay?
Someone call 911.
- Are you all right?
- No.
Call 911...
Yes, an elderly man collapsed.
(Emergency Medical Center)
Is he unconscious?
No, he just fell asleep
a moment ago.
But why the blood transfusion?
Can you step outside for a second?
(Family Waiting Room)
- Acute Myeloid Leukemia?
- Yes.
I think he knew.
- What?
- He came in for a bone marrow test.
So what's his condition?
Can he survive...
with just a bone marrow transplant?
The hospital wanted to start
with chemotherapy...
and then consider a transplant
depending on his progress,
but your grandfather refused.
- Why?
- At his age, with a transplant,
it might be difficult.
So that's why...
he didn't tell anyone
and kept it to himself...
So that's why...
he was in such a hurry
for me to get married.
Thank you. Gi Cheol's granddaughter.
- It's nothing.
- You're not dating Hyun Bin again?
No, of course not.
Don't worry. We're just friends.
I have a favor to ask.
Don't tell Gi Cheol that I'm sick.
Okay.
I'm not getting the transplant.
- Grandfather.
- I might die even if I get it.
Don't tell the rest of the family.
Then at least get chemotherapy.
Then what are you going to do?
What if you collapse
on a street again?
Make a decision.
Should I tell the family?
Or will you get Chemotherapy?
You...
Hey, Yang Hyun Bin.
Are you serious?
Yes.
I'm signing up
with a matchmaking agency.
If you're going to be a devil,
act like one.
- Are you sick...
- Quiet.
Just set me up on blind dates,
matchmaking meetings, anything.
I've decided to do
as Grandfather says.
Wait, Hyun Bin.
Father.
He's finally grown up.
He's finally matured.
I'm worried sick.
What's the big deal?
We're just friends.
Director Yang is putting
his entire life on the line for you.
Don't lead him on
if you have no intention...
of marrying him.
Oh my, Hyun Bin.
Are you really going on blind dates
with Ju Ah still in the picture?
Forget it.
Labellin is also signing
a partnership deal...
with Taehan Fashion.
Never mind that.
The CEO already told me.
Are you really going to marry
someone else?
- What's it to you?
- But even after you broke up,
you were devoted to Ju Ah,
weren't you?
You acted like you would never marry
anyone but her.
This is really strange.
- What's strange?
- Hyun Bin is.
He swore he'd never get married.
What did Father say to him...
to make him change his mind
like that?
I guess he had a change of heart.
But the fact that he agreed
to go on blind dates...
must mean he's completely given up
on Jeong Han's daughter, right?
Of course he should, dear.
But something's strange.
You need to be admitted right away
and start chemotherapy.
The doctor said...
there are patients older than you,
Grandfather,
who have had successful
bone marrow transplants...
and are now living healthy lives.
And I'll sign up with
the matchmaking agency.
I'll even go on the blind dates.
But you can't tell
the rest of the family.
You'll be the only one
visiting me at the hospital.
But you have to be admitted.
What excuse are you going to use?
Don't worry. I have a plan.
You're going on a trip?
Yes.
Here and there,
wherever my feet take me.
I'm going to wander aimlessly.
With who? A woman?
A man.
An old friend, an acupuncturist
who retired this spring.
A friend?
A closer friend than me?
Why, are you jealous?
Yes.
Hey, who just up and retires
like this?
It wasn't sudden.
After what happened to In Ok,
I've been thinking
about it constantly.
So you want me to be
responsible for your kids?
Yes.
Make sure Dong Ik wins
the city council election.
And take care of things
when Dong Suk gives birth.
All right?
Thank you for coming back,
my friend.
Yes, thank you for coming
all the way to my office for this.
It's quite common.
Everyone's so busy these days.
Here.
This is my certificate
of marital status...
and all the documents you asked for.
Thank you.
Okay, then. Shall we start with...
what you're looking for
in a partner?
Someone with a darker complexion,
and I prefer a short bob.
- So, the exact opposite of her?
- Yes.
Okay.
As long as she's not in my industry.
I can't stand the thought
of working together.
Whether she's religious or not
doesn't matter,
and for personality,
I'd like someone...
who is kind and gentle.
I especially want to avoid anyone
who's overly opinionated...
and stubborn. That's a deal-breaker.
Unbelievable.
All right.
What kind of views on marriage
would you want her to have?
Someone who's willing
to compromise on their goals,
for the sake of the relationship.
Someone who doesn't run
away from challenges,
but works to overcome them together.
(Matchmaker, Kang Yu Mi)
Why on earth are you meeting
with a matchmaking agency here?
Didn't you hear?
I'm busy, and she said
she could come to me.
What, are you trying to win me back,
by making me jealous?
Don't you think
you're being a little...
self-centered, my friend?
My grandfather is sick,
so I'm trying to get married
quickly.
You have no consideration
for the people you work with.
Then go work in the Design Office.
Why are you working here?
This is ridiculous.
Fine. I'll go to the Design Office
starting tomorrow.
Get up.
I said I'll go tomorrow.
I have so much stuff right now.
No, I mean let's go
to the outstanding store.
We were supposed to get
gift recommendations...
for the VIPs coming to the store.
What kind of items
can I recommend for you?
These are for a VIP event,
so please recommend items
that have been popular recently.
This line here has products
that customers...
have been looking for lately.
I thought they'd prefer
a more classic style,
but there are more flashy items
than I expected.
These days,
rather than subdued items,
people are definitely looking for...
colors or materials
that make a statement.
We also need some accessories
to go with them.
What's been selling well?
Practical items like these
are very popular.
Yes.
In that case,
let's make the accessories
a standard set for everyone,
and for the clothes, we can research
our clients' tastes,
and prepare customized options.
What do you think?
Excellent. Let's proceed with that.
Oh my.
Since the event gift package is set,
let's finalize
the VIP invitation list...
by our next meeting.
Okay, you're going to the office,
right?
No, I'm going straight home.
I have to go to the office.
Ms. Shim wanted to see me.
I see.
Then I'll drop you
at the subway station, my friend.
You're so petty, my friend.
Wow, they've already sent
a potential match's profile.
If she was born in 1999,
isn't that too young?
How old is she?
Is that a real question?
Can you not do simple math?
Works in research and development
at a global beauty brand.
Studied abroad in Buenos Aires.
Oh my, awesome.
It says her hobby is
going on food tours.
What do you think?
Why are you asking me?
As my friend and my ex,
you can tell me that much, right?
(Yoon Seo Ah)
She's nothing special.
Really?
I think she's pretty.
You have terrible taste.
(Groom Choi Se Hyun,
Bride Shin Bo Mi)
Wait, you two are getting married
already?
Yes, in a month. You'll come, right?
Wow, so we're finally
getting our first...
in-office married couple
on the team?
But you're both so young
to be getting married.
Our parents were actually
against it, but we insisted.
Why?
Do you have good news?
- No, that's not it.
- Then why?
Why?
Did we need a reason?
Because we're in love.
Because we hate being apart.
That's the spirit.
Right? Hey, you two.
- I'm back.
- Hey.
Look at this.
For doctors who've opened
their own clinics,
there are so many training courses.
You're right. Wow,
Korea University Hospital...
offers a lot of good ones.
Going to a big hospital
might jog my memory.
- Want to go together?
- Sure. Let's go together.
- Gosh, this really hurts inside.
- I'm home.
- Hey.
How does it feel?
The breeze from the fan
feels much better.
Before you go to sleep,
I'll put a cold compress on it
and apply your ointment.
Thank you. You're the best.
- What? You have something to say?
- No, it's nothing.
- The rehab program looks good.
- This would be good to take too.
What about this one?
You all seem so happy.
You startled me.
Of course I'm happy.
Right. Gong Ju Ah. Officer Jeong
and Nurse Oh will marry.
Really?
That was surprising, wasn't it?
Why aren't you sleeping?
Why'd you call?
I saw. Did you tell Dad everything?
Yes, I'm not going to hide
anything from your dad.
I was thinking
I should tell him everything.
Why all of a sudden?
It's not all of a sudden.
I just felt like it was time.
So, why did you want to see me?
- For some counseling.
- Counseling?
Sounds good.
- What is it?
- Counselor mode, not mom mode.
Okay. Go on.
Dr. Han,
why do you think
I broke up with Hyun Bin?
Why all of a sudden?
Did something happen?
- Counselor mode.
- Right, right.
I just...
I want to figure out
what my problem is.
Everyone's rushing to get married,
and all the couples
are so lovey-dovey,
and it makes me wonder
what will happen to me.
I want to learn from my past
so I can move forward.
Why you broke up with
Director Yang...
You ask
because you really don't know?
Maybe because
there were too many obstacles?
Gong Ju Ah, who always gets her way
no matter what?
Weren't they huge obstacles?
Our families are enemies,
and you and Hyun Bin's mother
don't get along.
Plus, you were sick,
so it was hard for me
to bring it up.
What did your uncle and aunt do
in the same situation?
They never gave up.
Hey, honestly,
Director Yang gave it his all.
He was so good to me
and your grandmother.
But what did you do?
Wait, you did do something.
You gave up.
Are you saying
I wasn't committed enough?
That's for you to know.
So what does it take to get married?
When you can't imagine living
without that person?
No matter what obstacles you face,
when giving up is never an option.
What bombshell
is he planning to drop...
that made him gather all of us?
Grandfather...
is leaving on a cross-country trip
starting tomorrow.
- What?
What? A cross-country trip?
I'm sending him on the trip.
Wait. Why a cross-country trip
all of a sudden?
Father, why?
Father, then what about...
the clinic?
I'm going to retire.
You figure it out.
Grandfather, what do you mean
you're retiring?
You're still going strong.
Father, I'm going to be busy
with the election.
Hire someone
or figure it out yourself.
Father, why are you being like this
all of a sudden?
Did we do something
to disappoint you?
He wants to spend the rest of his
life doing what he wants,
so why is everyone
trying to stop him?
I know, but still,
Father needs to be here...
- for important family matters.
- For important matters,
get Hyun Bin's permission.
What is this...
(Taehan)
Come in.
Did your grandfather agree
to be hospitalized?
He already has been.
I'm on my way back
from admitting him.
I see.
Well, then, take this with you
when you leave work.
I packed some things for him
for his hospital stay.
Infection control is critical
for leukemia patients,
so they need a lot of things.
When he starts chemotherapy,
he'll lose his hair,
so I bought him a hat.
I appreciate the thought.
What? Why?
When my mom was in the hospital,
you did the same for her.
That was when we were dating.
Come on,
friends can do this much, right?
If I say you gave them to me,
Grandfather will worry
unnecessarily.
He's already sick,
and I don't want to stress him out.
I mean...
Pacu Nacho.
A rumor's going around the office
that you're going on blind dates.
Why are you suddenly in a rush
to get married?
What, are you trying
to make someone jealous?
My grandfather has leukemia.
I think he wants me to get married
before he passes away.
That's why he was putting pressure
on my mother.
No, but still. You're
going to rush into marriage...
with someone you meet
on a blind date?
And leave Ms. Gong,
who you love so much?
Well, what else am I supposed to do?
She said she's not interested.
Didn't she get jealous
when she heard...
- you were going on blind dates?
- It seemed like she did.
What does she want,
asking to be friends?
What if...
it's not that your feelings
are different,
but that you're moving
at different speeds?
Come on, stop giving me hope.
Some people are slow to warm up.
You're impulsive,
and Ms. Gong is cautious.
You've been chasing her
with a one-sided crush...
since you were young,
but that's not the case
for Ms. Gong.
- So what? Telling me to wait?
- Forget waiting.
You need to speed things up.
With a booster.
A booster?
Hey, my sister and Director Yang
are getting married.
Are you okay?
What?
Hey, you said you weren't going to
marry Director Yang anyway, right?
Hey, isn't this our chance
to lock Pacu Nacho...
in Taehan forever?
- This is great.
- Marriage isn't a business deal.
Well, it's similar. Marriage is...
ultimately about
managing life together...
- forming a strategic partnership.
- Snap out of it.
You marry the person you love.
Stop your sister.
Hey, why stop her?
This is a jackpot for my sister.
Didn't you know
my sister had a crush...
on Pacu Nacho
when she was studying abroad?
Besides, Pacu Nacho's family
will love her.
- Darn it.
- Hey, Director Yang is in a hurry,
so rather than having him
go on a blind date...
with a total stranger,
this is a thousand times better.
Don't you think?
This is crazy.
- Nacho, Pacu Nacho.
- Yes, my dear.
- Where should we have our wedding?
- Do whatever you want.
Excuse me.
- Buenos Aires for our honeymoon?
- I'd love that.
I'd love that too.
Are you okay?
Are you jealous?
Hey, you're not in a position
to act like this.
Hey, Ju Ah.
(Hanguk University Hospital)
Wow. It's really changed
since I was a resident here.
You remember?
I used to bring you lunch here
all the time back then.
Since Dr. Yang is going on a trip,
I think I'll hang out here
and reminisce.
You're sad that Dr. Yang
is going on a trip, aren't you?
Of course, I am.
Hold on. Which way do we go?
My goodness.
Goodness.
What?
Wait, hey.
Your Father is suddenly retiring?
Apparently.
He just up and left
for a trip this morning.
Jeong Han.
Dong Ik, you're here too?
Yes. Why? What is it?
Well, it is...
Is it about me?
Well...
Councilor Hwang's campaign ran
a poll, and the results are out.
Is that so?
How much did our Dong Ik get?
Why? What was the percentage?
Tell me. It's fine.
I'm not getting my hopes up.
Yes.
No way. Was it 30?
It was not 30, was it?
Then in that case, three percent?
Just three percent.
But it's too early
to be disappointed.
There's a zero in front of it,
so it's zero point three percent.
What?
Jeong Han.
I'm going home.
I don't think I'll run.
Hey, what are you doing?
We haven't even started yet.
He's right. Don't be discouraged.
- We're here for you. We'll help.
- Of course.
Right.
Zero point three.
I wish that was the interest rate
on a loan.
Zero point three percent?
(3H Acupressure Bed)
Honey, don't be so disappointed.
If we campaign hard,
we can definitely turn
the polls around.
Okay, talk to you later. All right.
I'm sorry, something came up.
About what you mentioned,
- know-how and practical materials.
- Okay.
My goodness,
you've organized this so well.
As the owner
of an outstanding store,
it's the least I can do.
(Certified Medical Device Bed)
By the way,
we're gathering people...
who are interested in
running a center,
and we're planning to hold
a business briefing.
How would you feel about leading it?
Me?
I don't have any experience.
Do you think I can do a good job?
Of course.
We'll be there to support you,
so don't worry.
Well then, since you're putting
your trust in me,
I'll make sure
to prepare thoroughly.
Oh my, here you go.
Thanks, Dong Suk.
You haven't gone to work
because of me?
It's fine.
Woo Jae is watching the store.
I'm really making you
take care of me.
Don't say that. It's upsetting.
Who could that be?
- Who is it?
- It's me.
It's Cha Se Ri.
What brings you here so early
without calling?
- Just open the door.
- Well...
What should I do?
Let her in.
I'm a mess. I'll go inside and rest.
Okay.
Father is suddenly retiring
to travel?
Yes.
It seems he's had a change of heart
after Mother passed away.
I was hoping he could get
some counseling...
if Dr. Han was here.
Is she in her room?
She's not in her room. She went out.
Did she go far?
Should I try calling her?
It's fine.
I'll tell her when she gets back.
Then don't forget
to pass on the message.
Yes, I will.
But why are you here at this hour?
What about your store?
I've been so busy going
to the main office...
that I left the store
to a part-timer.
Hey, my store was chosen
as an outstanding store this time.
And can you believe it?
They even asked me to lead
the business briefing.
Wow, you're so cool.
Right? I'm pretty amazing, aren't I?
My husband is thrilled about it too.
I mean, it's not like
Dr. Han Seong Mi is the only one...
who can be successful.
Who says I'm successful?
Han Seong Mi is finished.
I've been calling you.
Have you been busy?
I got some tickets to a play.
Want to go with me, Eun Bin?
Eun Bin?
Well, it's just...
So, should we go
to my place tonight?
Should we? It's been a while.
Ready for a match?
Yes, why not? Let's go all out.
I'm ready for whatever you've got.
- I'm feeling good today.
- Me too.
Wow, this looks so delicious.
- You haven't changed a bit.
- Let's get this too. Now...
- You still love your snacks.
- This looks delicious too.
Honestly.
- Wait. I have something in my eye.
- Let me see.
What's going on?
Did I get it?
How is it? Yes. It's out.
- Honestly.
- Then leave it.
Pacu Nacho, you're hilarious.
Why are you like this?
What should I do?
- I said it's out.
- Just let me see.
I'm so hungry right now.
Pacu Nacho, I'm exhausted.
Why am I...
Why am I being like this?
You're crazy, Gong Ju Ah.
No...
You are so dead.
- Are your skills still sharp?
- I'm on fire.
Same here. You'd better watch out.
- We'll see about that.
- Yes.
- I'm suddenly getting nervous.
- I knew you would be.
Gosh, my hands are sweating.
- Come in.
- Okay.
How long has it been?
I'm so excited and nervous.
My love.
- I love you.
- Ready for a game? Been a while.
I'd love to.
No. Open the door. No.
No, wait a minute. No, please stop.
No.
Ms. Gong.
What brings you here?
I was just...
We were just playing a game
from the old days.
It's one we used to play
a lot in Argentina.
Do you want to join us?
I'm sorry.
I just thought that you two were...
Looks like our little push worked.
Well then, I guess I should...
give you two some space.
- I'll get going then.
- Okay.
Why are you here?
- I don't like it.
- What don't you like?
I don't like you
being with another woman.
You said you wanted
to be just friends.
I can't.
I can't just be friends with you.
- So what now? You asked for this.
- Marry me.
- Forget it.
- Why? You wanted to get married.
You're only doing this
because of my grandfather.
I love you.
I love you too, you idiot.
So don't you dare
see any other women.
Don't even look at other women.
Only look at me. Got it?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry it took me so long.
It's okay.
Thank you for coming.
I'm sorry for making you wait.
If you don't want to get married,
you don't have to.
It's enough for me
that you're here now.
No.
I'm not going to run away anymore.
And I'm not giving up on you.
From now on,
no matter what challenges we face,
I won't lose you.
So marry me.
Marry me, Yang Hyun Bin.
Marry me...
Okay, I get it.
Stop talking.
(Recipe For Love)
Did you see Ju Ah
come home yesterday?
You know Ju Ah.
When she likes someone,
she goes for it and never gives up.
It seems I've saved you
twice now, Mother.
Father, please.
- Daughters-in-law falling out...
- I really don't like Gong Ju Ah.
- was 100 percent your...
- I can't stand her.
daughter-in-law's fault.
So I'm going to set a condition too.