(This series is produced for entertainment purposes. The characters,
actions, locations, and events depicted are fictional
and do not allude to any real organization,
profession, or group of individuals.
This program may contain imagery, sounds, and contents that
are inappropriate in terms of behavior, violence, sex, and language.
Viewers under 18 should be advised.
Viewer discretion is advised.)
Can I call you "My Babe"? Because my whole heart I give to you
Can I call you "My Babe"? Because my whole heart I dedicate to you
Whenever I turn, I see you
Because you are the answer
And I won't give the word "love" to anyone else…
Can I call you "My Babe"? Because my whole heart I give to you
Can I call you "My Babe"? Because my whole heart I dedicate to you
Whenever I turn, I see you
Because you are the answer
And I won't give the word "love" to anyone else, except for you
Can I call you "My Babe"? Love, love, love
Can I call you "My Babe"?
"Doctor's Mine"
(Episode 7)
Doc!!
Where will you run away from me?
I'm busy. I'll going to work.
What's wrong?
I said I'm going to work, Per!!
Doc, wait. Let's talk first.
I want to introduce you to my friends as my boyfriend.
There's no need to do that anymore.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
This isn't your fault, Per.
Then why are you like this?
Don't you like me?
Do you know?
Not long ago, someone confessed their feelings to me.
Who?
Do you like them?
No, I don't.
And I don't ever plan to.
When I rejected her,
it just reinforced that my heart already belongs to someone.
Doc!
I don't want to start over with anyone, Per.
I've always lied to myself like that.
But in the end, I can't stop my feelings.
Have you ever had a really good dream and then been woken up?
It's time for you to wake up, Per.
Wait, Doctor!
Doctor Kan!!
Kan, let's talk first.
Doc, I'm hurting.
Come and heal my wounds.
I'm here.
Hey... look at this, it's damn delicious.
I'm a real genius.
Alright, I'll let the host open it first.
You eat first.
F*ck! That hurts.
Hey... I'm asking you seriously.
Are you really happy in this kind of relationship?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Dude, don't you even realize that
before you started dating her.
You used to smile more often,
You looked so much happier.
I mean... you don't have to believe me,
but even when you were still trying to win her over,
you seemed happier than you are now.
I... I was like that?
Yeah, you were.
Now you look like you're under magic.
Are you even dating her
or just some idealized version of her?
Is this relationship making you happy at all?
I don't get it.
You ass! You're still dumb.
Does she even match a single thing
you thought she would?
Does she make you genuinely happy?
I'm happy with my life.
Happy? My ass! You're happy?
Look at you, you've called her a hundred times
and he still won't pick up.
Ask yourself honestly,
are you really happy with what you're doing?
Ugh, never mind. Let's eat first.
Maybe eating something will nourish your brain a bit.
But sorry, it's all just sodium.
Sure, I'll eat.
I put a lot of effort into this, you know.
Mmm, this is so good!
Is it good?
Thanks.
You've had enough. It's my turn.
Have you seen Dr. Kan?
Doc!
Can you open the door?
Oh! How did you get here?
I think we need to talk this through.
But I'll bringing coffee up for Tum and Klah.
Hello Tonklah, come down and get the coffee.
Mild's not free to bring it up anymore.
Hey hey, you're forced my hand!
I'll only listen to the truth,
and then I'm leaving.
Just hearing that makes me happy.
Are you going to talk or not?
If you don't, I'm leaving now.
I'll talk, Mild.
Can you stay with me a little longer?
The first day I met you...
I didn't meet you at your house that day.
What do you mean?
I wasn't drunk because I saw you lying there.
But because it had to be you.
The one who saved my life.
The one I've never forgotten.
When I was a kid, I liked to go read at the park.
And there was a child who liked to secretly watch me.
He seemed really shy, but I didn't mind.
I didn't want to startle him.
That child was cute.
It felt like I had a friend who was with me.
Until...
Help me!!
Help me!
After that day, I've been looking for you all this time,
but I couldn't find you.
You were looking for me
even though you didn't know who I was?
Yeah.
I want you to know that I've never forgotten you.
I never intended to hurt you either.
Please, just listen to me for a bit.
About what happened that day...
Hey, cheers!!!
Let's go all out today, my parents aren't coming back.
Let's do this!
Then I won't hold back anymore.
Just drink it all.
I have plenty more. I have a whole truckload.
Finish it all, finish it all!
Someone didn't cheers just now.
And he's quiet too.
What should we do?
Don't talk.
How?
Shove it in his mouth.
Be careful. I still have to go back home.
What are you talking about, go home?
You can just sleep here.
I have plenty of rooms.
Don't be a wimp. Drink it up!
Yeah, just drink it.
You know what happens when I get drunk.
- Bottoms up! Bottoms up!
- Drink it!
Bottoms up! Bottoms up! Bottoms up!
Hey, I'm gonna go to the rest room quickly.
I'll be right back.
Just a little bit more.
Are we friends or not?
I just finished mine.
Grab your glass.
Let's go!
Bottoms up, bottoms up!
That's my friend!
Oh, I can't take it anymore. I'm going to the rest room.
What's wrong with you? You can't even handle this?
Yeah, Don't make a mess down here.
Go upstairs to my room. Keng's using the one downstairs.
Go on up. My room is...
you walk and turn left, then turn right, then left,
then right again, then left one more time.
Ugh, stop it. I'll find it myself.
Alright, my friend.
Go on, go on. Let's keep drinking!
Your turn.
Oh, it's my turn?
Oh really?
Finish it all, finish it all!
Really finish?
Hey, you have it as a truckload, right?
Left, right,
left,
left.
Take it easy.
What the hell did you do to my brother?
Calm down.
What the hell did you do to my brother, huh?
I didn't do anything. I didn't...
- What the hell did you do to my brother?
- I didn't do it.
Hey, calm down.
I saw it. You raped my brother.
Knight, that's your friend's brother. Why would you do that?
How could you do this to my brother?
I didn't do it.
If you don't believe me. It's up to you.
I'm begging you!
I've told everything.
It was my fault for almost stealing a kiss from Mild that day.
But I swear, I never meant to hurt you.
Since that day, I've never let myself get drunk again.
If you've heard everything and you want to hate me,
then I...
I'm angry.
More than that...
I'm angry that you acted cool for so long and didn't tell me.
I was scared because the image made it look that way.
Stop feeling guilty.
I'm not angry anymore.
How about this, let's change the subject.
What about... you and P' Per?
Per?
He's my brother, but we have different mothers.
My mom married into the family later.
As you see Per like that, but he's a great older brother.
When I was looking for you, he was always by my side.
He always encouraged me.
And now, finally, I'm brave enough to confess to Mild today.
Aw! I'm hurting.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
That's all.
Do you know how long you let me be confused?
I couldn't enjoy my food, and I couldn't sleep.
So, I'll get the other 50% left back now, right?
I'll only give you 30.
The other 20 is for my wasted time.
So what do I have to do to get the other 20% back?
I'm keeping this kiss and I'm not giving it back to you.
Then I'll just let go of the full 100%.
I should have used this method more often.
What are you doing, Mom? It smells so good.
What brings you to see me today?
Because I miss you, Mom Lek.
You're not going to pester doctors anymore?
Did Knight tell you, Mom?
You've never been like this before.
I really can't hide anything from you.
He broke me up, Mom.
I don't understand. Why did this happen all of a sudden?
Per, have you talked to Mom Yai recently?
Mom?
Mom,
Mom.
What did you say to Kan?
I did it for your future.
Did you ask me if I wanted it?
I already know what's best for you.
And what is it? What's best for me?
Dating a man makes you look bad.
And you'll lose business opportunities.
Even though it's more open now,
people will still look at you strangely.
I don't care, I just want to be with Kan.
Nonsense, Per.
If he really loved you, would he leave you
so easily just because I asked him to?
It's because he loves me, Mom. That's why he had to go.
Because he knows I love you.
Per! Per, come back and talk to me right now!
Come back and talk this through! Per!
I told you to come back!
Thank you so much, Mild.
You're so lovely, just as Knight raves about you
every morning and night.
Mom.
Well, it's true!
He's been raving about you since he was a kid.
Actually, I've been encouraging him
to date you for a long time.
Yes.
Normally, he doesn't talk much about his day.
Whenever he does, it's always about how cute Mild is.
Mom, that's enough.
How was it? I want to hear more!
Well, before, he never used to come home early.
But ever since he reconnected with you.
Now he comes home so fast.
And when he does, he's so happy... his face just lights up!
Huh? When you're with me, you don't act like this.
What do you mean? I compliment you all the time.
You're the one who never lets me.
I'm shy. Just eat.
Oh my, I forgot the dipping sauce.
I'll be right back.
It's okay, Mom. I'll bring it for you.
Just stay here and talk to him.
Mild.
Yes, mom.
Please take care of Knight.
Even though he seems quiet.
He's actually very lonely.
I feel good knowing he's with you.
Don't worry, mom.
I'll take the best possible care of Knight.
And if Knight bullies you too much...
Yes?
You can tell me.
I will! You'll be the first person I tell.
What were you guys talking about? Huh?
It's a secret.
You guys have secrets from me now?
We can't?
Eat, eat, it's here now.
Here you go, son.
These shrimp are delicious.
You're changing the subject, mom.
- We're not.
- You are changing the subject.
Here, you want some? I'll serve you some.
His favorite.
Here, I'll serve you some. Here...
Thanks.
And you eat some too, mom, so you can grow up.
I'll serve you some chicken then.
Thank you.
Hello, what's up, Mild?
Hello, P'Kan. How are you?
I'm okay, doing well.
Are you sure? You sound a bit down.
Um, someone wants to talk to you.
Who?
Hello, Dr. Kan. I'm Knight's mother.
Hello. I'm Kan.
You might be wondering why I want to talk to you.
I'm really worried about Per.
Per miss you a lot.
And how about you? How have you been?
I'm fine.
You can tell me anything.
Think of me as an elder who cares for you.
I think having me in Per's life...
made him worse.
And there's no way her mother will ever accept me.
Hello, mom. Are you here to see Per?
I'm here to see you, Dr. Kan.
Me?
Yes.
Can I talk with you?
Haven't you seen Per at all lately?
Yes.
Honestly, he's my only son,
And I don't want to see him go down the wrong path.
So, please, doctor, get out of my son's life.
He should be with a perfect and suitable woman.
If that's all you have to say to me, don't worry.
I promise that Per and I are not and will not be dating.
You can rest easy.
And...
next time, I have to ask you not to wait for me like this.
It wastes my study time.
Goodbye.
Doc!!
Let's talk for a bit.
Doc, I want to introduce you to my friends as my boyfriend.
It's no longer needed.
What's wrong with you?
You didn't do anything wrong.
Then why are you like this?
Don't you like me?
I understand.
How about this? Dr.Kan would you mind meeting with me?
We can fix any problems together.
Uh, it's okay.
Thank you for your concern,
but I can handle it.
But I think...
Really, thank you.
I'm sorry, but I have to take this call.
I'm so sorry on behalf of P'Kan.
That's okay. Sometimes these things can be difficult.
Wow... if P'Kan could talk to you,
he'd fall in love just like I did.
Oh my... fall in love, really?
If that's the case, Knight will be upset with me.
Just let him be mad then.
I've been annoyed with him for a long time.
If you see Doctor Kan, tell me, okay?
I know what I need to do.
Sure thing.
Doctor, which is more huggable, this doll or me?
I win by a landslide, right?
What's your mood?
You don't even realize it.
That right now, you're in a terrible state.
That's why you need someone
to take care of you and put you to bed.
Are you Dr. Kan?
You're Knight's mom, right?
What a coincidence, I was just looking
for someone to have dinner with.
You're available, right?
Yes.
Hello.
Thank you.
What would you like to eat, Dr. Kan?
I'll have the salmon steak and garlic bread.
We'll have that, then.
Alright. May I take the menus.
How are you?
I... I think I'm okay.
I can handle everything in my life.
But why is it that with this one, I just can't...
Listen to me, Dr. Kan.
Sometimes, you don't have to handle everything all by yourself.
Per that I know is willing to fight the whole world
just to be with the one he loves.
To be honest, I'm not feeling well about this.
Per doesn't smile, laugh, or feel cheerful like he used to.
He also comes home drunk every day.
He says he's been looking for you everywhere,
but he can't find you.
Per that I know is a very steady
and committed person when he loves.
If I'm with Per and he has to choose
between me and her mother,
How can he be happy?
Listen to me.
Sometimes, it might not be necessary to choose.
Yesterday, I saw Per arguing loudly with her mother at home.
He insisted that he would be with Dr. Kan no matter what.
I'm still worried about him.
How about Per?
I think it's better if you go see it by yourself.
Why are you coming here?
You weren't home for dinner,
so Mom told me to bring you some food.
Thanks.
You can go now.
What's wrong with you?
I think he wants to break up with me.
Wait. You and him don't have any problems.
It's your mom who has the problem.
Then why doesn't he argue with my mom
and tell her we love each other?
Are you crazy? That's your mom.
If he argues with her, you, the one in the middle,
will be the one who ends up hurt the most.
You're right.
You're so smart when it comes to my problems.
But when it's about your own, you're so dumb.
Knight, just go back.
Last time, you stayed to comfort me.
Are you going to let me just leave you alone like this?
I really can't find him.
Do you remember what you told me?
Just keep trying.
Even if I have to apologize to Mild
for the rest of my life, I have to do it.
If I want to get Mild back.
Yeah.
It's the same this time.
If you think Dr. Kan is the right person.
You have to do it,
even if it takes you your whole life to find him.
You have me. I'll help you.
When did you get so grown up?
Hey... you jerk.
I'm not cussing you out because I see you're sad.
Knight.
What?
I won't give up.
No matter how long it takes.
I'm going to find him.
That's the spirit!
But for now, eat your food first.
You won't have the energy to look for him if you don't eat.
Yeah, thanks.
Sure thing, bro.
Is Mild going out anywhere today?
He's going to watch a movie with his boyfriend.
He still hasn't brought him to meet us.
Hello, Mom and Dad.
Hello, Night.
Hey.
We finally meet.
Yes.
Have a seat.
I know what happened back then.
It's good that it was all a misunderstanding.
Yes, Mom.
Mild's an adult now. If he chooses someone he loves,
we wouldn't think of getting in the way.
But let's take it slow and see how things go first.
Yes, I'm happy to prove to you both
How serious I am about Mild.
No matter how long it takes.
Thank you for understanding.
Yes, Mom.
And now is also the time
I'm giving Mild to make his decision.
I'm just waiting for Mild to be ready.
If Mild feels bad or no longer wants to love me,
I'll respect his decision.
I promise.
Good. Make sure you do what you say.
Yes.
What were you two talking about?
It's nothing, dear. Just a casual greeting.
Oh, Dad!! I won't be handsome anymore.
Go on, you'll be late.
Okay.
Take him and go now, Knight.
And don't bring him back too late.
Yes.
I'm not a kid anymore, mom.
Oh really? I still see you as a 5 year old.
Oh dad, what 5 year old? Mom, look at dad.
That's just how he is. Go ahead, hurry up.
I'm leaving. Goodbye.
-Okay
-Bye mom, bye dad.
Hey, P' Night.
Yes?
Is there something you're hiding from me?
Nothing.
I was just talking to your parents about you.
Is there anything I need to know?
All you need to know is that if you still love me,
There's nothing to worry about.
Okay.
Then I guess there won't be any problems.
Let's go.
Please, Kan..
Are you just waiting for your NL Step 3 exam results?
You don't have any classes anyway,
so please, please come help out at the camp.
Oh teacher, but… I...
It's a volunteer camp to help
develop a community up in the mountains, Kan.
We need a 6th-year medical student
to help with health checkups for the villagers.
Oh, okay.
A bus will be waiting to pick you up
at the university on Friday.
Okay?
What's up? What's she got for you to do now?
She wants us to go to a volunteer camp this Friday.
Is it that university camp?
What camp?
The community development volunteer camp.
The one where a bunch of faculties go together.
But... engineering is going too.
Really?
Are you sure you'll be okay?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
We might not even see each other.
Hey, come on.
I think it would be good for you to get a change of environment.
You look stressed out lately.
Yeah.
Whaooooo!
Ahhhhh.
Please stay with me. I'm afraid.
Did you secretly drug me?
I didn't drug you, but I put my heart into it.
I'm going to let the ghost in your room deal with you...
I really want to date you.
I'm serious about you, Doctor.
Please give me a chance.
The gear is the heart for an engineer.
Can I leave mine with you?
I miss you so much.
Guide, you need to load these onto the bus right away.
And be careful.
Doc!!
I've missed you, Doc.
Please Doc, don't run away again.
I'm begging you.
I don't have time for this, Per.
Per, let me go! Per! Per!
Mild.
Huh?
Per is probably taking Dr. Kan to the car.
Yeah.
The car is probably full.
You and I can go together, right?
No, we can't.
You want me to walk alone?
No way.
Let's go together.
Per, Per, let me go!
Per, I'm going to get in the car! Per!
Why are you avoiding me?
I'm not.
Doctor, let's talk nicely.
What happened?
Your mom... she doesn't like me.
She wants me to get out of your life.
And you have to believe her?
But that's your mom, Per!
Are you dating me or my mom?
Do you have to care what she thinks?
Answer me, are you dating me or my mom?
I'm dating you.
Now I'm shy.
You said it first, and you're even wearing the necklace.
Hey, I wasn't planning on wearing this, you know!
Doc, can we not do this again?
Let's just talk things out,
and please don't run away again.
I'm going crazy.
Yeah,
me too.
Let this just be about us, no matter how it ends.
Let the outcome be based on our own decisions.
Let's give it a try.
But you might not know that I liked you,
even before you knew who I was.
When?
But whether you knew or not doesn't matter anymore.
Because now I love you, and I won't lose you
so easily again, that's all that matters.
If you leave me, you're surely dead.