(This series is produced for entertainment purposes.
The characters, actions, locations, and events depicted are fictional
and do not allude to any real organization,
profession, or group of individuals.
This program may contain imagery, sounds, and contents
that are inappropriate in terms of behavior, violence, sex, and language.
Viewers under 18 should be advised.
Viewer discretion is advised.)
Can I call you "My Babe"? Because my whole heart I give to you
Can I call you "My Babe"? Because my whole heart I dedicate to you
Whenever I turn, I see you
Because you are the answer
And I won't give the word "love" to anyone else…
Can I call you "My Babe"? Because my whole heart I give to you
Can I call you "My Babe"? Because my whole heart I dedicate to you
Whenever I turn, I see you
Because you are the answer
And I won't give the word "love" to anyone else, except for you
Can I call you "My Babe"? Love, love, love
Can I call you "My Babe"?
"Doctor's Mine"
(Episode 5)
I like you.
I've always liked you.
My feelings have never changed.
Let's start over with me.
Thank you.
What kind of mood are you in?
Just thanking you for giving me a chance.
We've only just started counting to one,
we might not even make it to two.
Oh... Mild, that's too much.
Am I really that bad?
If you do well, then it'll be ok.
But if you don't do well, then I have to say goodbye.
It's not that difficult.
Of course... You're above me now.
But just give in to me.
Oh!
- Are you ticklish?
- P'Knight!
Are you ticklish?
P'Knight, Stop it!
P'Knight P'Knight! You're not going to stop,
Oh!!
P'Knight! No!
P'Knight!
Come on, that's enough!
Are you giving up yet? Are you giving up yet?
That's enough, no more.
Come on, come on!
That's enough.
You're awake? Want some?
Isn't this too early?
Have you been awake long?
Why didn't I know?
For a while.
Or should I say, I haven't slept yet.
Hey! You still haven't slept?
Ahh! I guess I must have been tired.
Oh... I guess I must have been tired.
My bad.
No...
The reason I couldn't sleep was just
that I wanted to look at your face for a long time.
You're a pervert!
Did you stare at my face all night?
Are you crazy! Who would do that?
I slept some, woke up some.
That's creepy.
Hey, but I didn't do anything to you.
When morning came, I rushed to prepare breakfast for you.
Can I really believe that?
Believe me, if I looked at your face any longer,
I might...
Hey!
Stop it!
Hello?
Hello, P'Mud?
Oh...
no signal at all.
It's a dead zone around here.
Can't make calls, no signal.
Does a place like this still exist on Earth?
Oh, but why did you choose this place?
Huh?
I figured no one would be able to contact you.
You're so scary.
Want some? I'll make it for you.
Hmm.
Are you going to eat it yourself
or do you want me to feed you?
I can eat it myself.
Okay.
Here.
Thank you.
Yes.
How is it? Good?
Yeah, I feel really good.
I've never been anywhere like this before.
Normally, I'm just in a classroom. Thank you so much, P'Knight!
So, it means I picked the right place, right?
Huh, but it's also a bit scary.
I can't contact anyone.
I thought you were bringing me here to kill me.
I just wanted you to relax.
Seeing you smile makes me happy.
Because your happiness is my happiness.
I'm really happy!
Thank you so much, P'Knight!
Hey, what are you eating? That looks delicious as hell!
Oh...
so you're not even going to let me try some?
Hey... are you going to move that much and you fall off your chair?
Yeah, I'm just kidding around.
Just in case you get a girlfriend and forget about me.
Nonsense.
I'll always be the same with you.
Are you serious?
Hey, get out! I'm hot.
Hey, what's wrong with you, Tum!
I'm going to eat.
- Tum! You ass!
- Hmmm.
My egg!
Do you know how hard it was for me to queue up and buy this?
Oh, I'll buy you a new one.
But seriously... This is really delicious!
You're still not realized yet,
but I can remember what you said about buying me a new one.
Yeah, I'll really buy you a new one.
If you don't buy me a new one, I hope you turn into a dog.
I'll tease you until your kids become monks!
Uh, Yesss, okay.
Damn, I didn't even get to eat any.
Hurry up and eat so we can go to class.
Tum, It's mine.
Hey, you have your own!
I don't mind.
Hm, yours is good too.
You don't eat vegetables anyway.
How did you know?
That's why I didn't bring any vegetables.
Hmm, eat some or you'll get hungry.
Um, keep it to eat, haven't you eaten yet?
No, just keep it to eat.
Um.
Okay.
See you this evening, then.
I'm leaving now!
Bye!
Come here!
Where did you take my brother to?
Mild and I are dating, Mud.
Huh!?
Mild and I are dating.
Mud, let me take care of your brother.
What the hell are you talking about?!
What?! My brother's gone and I can't reach him!
You're so damn bad!
You're going to take care of my brother?
Then why did you do that, huh?!
I told you that I really like your brother.
You don't even have the right to say that, you ass!
If you won't listen, then don't listen, damn!
You act like you're confident,
I'm telling you that soft-boiled egg,
the queue line to buy was so long.
I'll be waiting to see someone here howl.
If I howl, you'll howl with me!
Hey... I'm not involved?
Oh, so you don't really love me?
Bark bark bark bark!
Damn it!
Hey! Go check it out!
P' Mud!
Hey, calm down first.
P' Mud, calm down. Calm down.
Let me go!
Hey Klah,
are you okay?!
My nose...
Dammmm!
You wouldn't let him go when he told you to,
now you got it.
Look, it's all blood.
Hey,
what's wrong, Klah?
Your brother, just hit him.
Huh? What happened?
I don't know neither.
But I feel like there's something
they both know just between them.
Why do you think that?
Because they have some unresolved issues.
Something that's really... not okay between them.
Oh,
Mild!
Only you can find out what it is!
Hey, no way.
I'd rather him feel okay and telling me himself.
Hey, otherwise, either your brother or your boyfriend
is going to end up dead, seriously.
Yeah, it might not be anything serious.
But if you know, it might help to fix it.
Think about it.
But I'm hurt.
Take it all.
Uh, Doctor, I...
It's okay, just a little bit.
Don't be afraid.
It's done.
Are you worried?
I got a stick jabbed in my butt..,
I wasn't careful and accidentally sat on it.
So... I'm a bit worried.
Are you here for an HIV test, right?
How did you know, Doctor?
Is there anything you'd like to tell me?
I...
I accidentally had sex for the first time with an male senior.
And he was very violence.
So... I'm scared.
It's okay. I'll examine you,
and we'll do a blood test today,
then you can come back for the results.
For today, I'll give you a one-month course of
PEP (Post-Exposure Prophylaxis) antiretroviral medication.
Am I not overthinking, right?
I'm just really worried, so I wanted to get checked.
That's good you came to get checked out.
There's no need to be ashamed.
At first, I was really stressed and scared,
I didn't dare talk to anyone about it.
But... after talking to you, Doctor, I feel much better.
You can tell me anything, I'm happy to listen.
Talking to you made me feel a lot better.
This morning, after you dropped me off,
did you make it to class on time?
Oh! I'm Chill.
Really?
So are you fight with P'Mud again?
P'Knight, is there anything you want to tell me about you and P'Mud?
What exactly is going on with you two?
Why does it never end?
It's hard to end it, Mild.
It's something I need to sort out myself.
I just need you to keep supporting me like this, that's all.
So what?
Are you going to apologize for disappearing and being unreachable?
Do you even know how worried our family was?
Yeah I'm sorry, but I'm an adult now, not a kid anymore.
Exactly because you're an adult!
You should have left a message to me.
Oh, what about when you disappeared with a girl?
I haven't said anything yet.
Hey you!!
But anyway, you and P'Knight don't have to fight?
I already told you, Don't get involved with him!
You just keep saying "don't get involved, don't get involved."
So what's the problem between you two?
Why won't you tell me so I know?
You don't need to know.
I'm your brother, just trust me.
So you want me to just believe you like this?
Hey! You're my older brother, you should be more reasonable!
What's so hard about just telling me?
Oh, did you fail again?
I think it must be about you, Mild.
I'm gonna need you guys' help.
Can I call you My Babe? Because my whole heart I give to you
Can I call you My Babe? Because my whole heart I dedicate to you
Whenever I turn, I see you
Because you are the answer
And I won't give the word "love" to anyone else, except for you
Can I call you My Babe? Because my whole heart I give to you
Can I call you My Babe? Because my whole heart I dedicate to you
Whenever I turn, I see you
Because you are the answer
And I won't give the word "love" to anyone else, except for you
Can I call you My Babe? Love Love Love
Can I call you My Babe?
Is it delicious?
- Can I call you My Babe? Love Love Love
- Yes, delicious.
It looks good on you, actually.
Per, Even if we buy it, I won't wear it anyway.
You would wear for sure,
Here, a couple hats!
Let's take a photo first.
No, Per! No! No way!
Per! No!
You might not like it, but I do.
Per, stop!
How did we end up at a market anyway?
We met at a pub and now we're at a market?
But it often ends up elsewhere too.
Damn it, Per!
Hey, Per, today I met a patient.
He was so pitiful, he got bullied by his seniors.
Wait!
You saying that doesn't mean you like him, right?
No way, I'm possessive!
Oh, Per! Are you crazy?
I genuinely feel pity for him!
You can't even feel pity for anyone else.
You can only feel sorry for me..
And I definitely won't make you sad.
Per, I'm embarrassed!
You won't regret it, but you will lose...
Per! Per, stop it! Just take mine to wear.
It looks cute.
Did you see? Look!
Per! I'm embarrassed!
Why would you be embarrassed?
No one's looking at us anyway.
Here...
Ahh, the traffic is terrible, I can't take it anymore!
What did you buy so much, Per?
You can pick whatever you like.
Then why did you buy so much?
My mom gave them to me.
Your mom really takes good care of you.
Too much, She likes to bring me this
and that until the house is full.
Sometimes it just piles up in the fridge until it expires.
Then I have to throw away what's expired.
Hey Per, I want to play this!
Wanna play?
Sure! I'm super pro at this.
Damn!
Hey, which dog said super pro?
It was Per the dog,
The dog really wanted it too.
Hey!
Are you in heat lately?
I'm just so damn addicted to you.
My ass!
And what if I say I'm so damn addicted to you,
will you accept me?
Why should I accept you?
For you, what am I?
Brother, a friend, a boyfriend,
or just a one-night stand?
I don't know.
If I find out, I'll tell you.
Then I'll prove it to you,
that you have to be my boyfriend.
I'll be waiting to see if you get that "boyfriend" status.
You're really challenging me.
The person next to Khun Per is Khun Kan.
He's a 6th-year extern doctor
who recently broke up with his girlfriend.
A woman or a man?
She's a woman.
She was caught secretly dating another man, which led to their breakup.
There are many posts and comments online saying that they are a couple.
And it seems that Khun Per is the one trying to pursue Khun Kan.
Will it work, Klah?
It has to work, even if it doesn't.
Is there any other way?
But I have to pretend to call P'Mud and P'Knight's high school friends.
Also, to hold a party in my house.
Does my house might get wrecked before anything even happens?
It's not that hard.
Oh! Do I really have to do this?
Come on.
Where is it?
Here.
Hello.
Hi, is this P'Yiwa, P'Mud's friend?
Oh yes, Who is this?
Oh, I'm Mild. Mud's younger brother.
Oh, Mild! Has Mud died?
Which temple is the funeral at? Send me the location.
No, not at all...
P'Mud is actually having a party on Friday. He wanted to invite you.
Hey Mud! Been gone for so long,
and then he sends his brother to invite me to drink.
When I see him, I'm going to punch him.
So... Can you come to the party?
I can go. Same house, right?
And I need to go, uh... I...
Hey Mild, Let's eat.
Just a moment.
Okay, Friday at 4 PM at P' Mud's house.
Oh, Nong Mild, Nong...
Hey Mild, Let's eat! I'm hungry! Hurry!
Come down now!
Yeah, I know. Just a moment.
Damn P' Mud!
What's wrong with you, huh?
Why can't you stay still? Got hemorrhoids?
No, my legs just hurt. I was standing for too long today.
You're acting suspicious.
Nothing.
It's clear. Just tell me what's going on.
I noticed it since you rushed down here.
Oh, I've been studying so hard lately,
and then there's the stage plays rehearsing too.
I'm exhausted every day.
Well, you brought it on yourself.
Oh Look, my muscles are so weak.
I just dropped my phone when I picked it up.
What are you so weak?
Alright, Let me hear what my little brother has to say.
How about this, should we have a party at home?
I really want to relax.
Oh, I thought it was something serious. Yeah, sure!
Then I'll invite Tum and Klah.
Sure.
Your high school friends.
Even better.
And also P'Knight.
Sure, No way, that's crazy!
Why would you get involved with that jerk?
I told you to stay away from him.
But you and P'Knight are friends.
I just want that fun and lots of people kind of vibe,
Come on,
just one night, please?
Or do you want me to go party outside
with P'Knight just the two of us?
Stop! We'll have a party here. Is that okay?
Deal.
Hey, Mild! I'm here.
Hi, friends!
Hey, what did you buy?
We bought a lot of snacks!
Here Oh, Hi P'Mud!
Hi, bro! Hi!
This is in case we watch a movie.
Okay! Wow, popcorn! Oh, perfect!
Peanuts, peanuts!
I have peanuts too.
This is for watching movies.
Wow! That's a lot!
Well, you picked it up. What'd you get?
Why is there so much?
I guess it's a plate.
Really?
Mild.
Hi, P'Knight.
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
Hey, What's up!
Hi.
Wow! Everyone's here!
Get out, I wanna sit here.
I thought you're dead! You don't reply to my LINE messages.
You even let your brother call to invite me?
What's wrong with you?
Hey, calm down. Don't ask all at once.
I can't answer that fast.
Hey, is that P'Yihwa and P'Por?
Yeah, it is.
Oh, the legendary couple!
So you can't avoid it for sure.
What do I have to avoid?
Well, P'Yihwa's an engineering student, and P'Por's a doctor.
Um.
You definitely can't avoid it.
Nonsense, you ass!
Engineering students are meant to be with doctors!
But I totally forgot about that.
By the way, my house used to have parties often.
This is their house, not yours.
Oh, my friend's house is like my own!
Yeah.
A friend's stuff is like our own.
This was smooth.
Your brother's gang seems really close.
Yeah, they used to be like this.
But I don't know why my brother and P'Knight are like this now.
I don't know too.
You'll definitely find out soon. Tonight.
Hello everyone!
Keep an eye on him.
Have you all eaten anything yet?
What will we eat? Do we have food?
Would you like anything to drink?
I'll just take this bottle.
- Are you sure?
- I'm so thirsty.
Okay, then, go get 3 bottles.
3 bottles?
Just like this one.
- The same kind.
- 4 for sure.
Give me 4 too!
Yeah.
Want some?
Sure.
He served.
Let's drink!!
Hey, spin again.
I got you!
In Som Sri class, you didn't wear underwear to school, right?
Shit! How did you know that?
Hey, I saw it, I saw it! He forgot to zip up!
The girls saw it and got shy and ran away.
They aren't shy, they're disgusting!
At that time, I went to the restroom
and the tissue was out, so I had to use it to wipe.
Besides, it also helps with ventilation.
That's disgusting.
Dr. Por, but the tissue was gone.
If I just put it on top,
It wouldn't be hygienic, right?
Normally, Yihwa doesn't like to wash underwear.
Hey, you!
It's because Yihwa likes to wear it inside out...
Por!
Enough! Just hearing it makes me sick.
Let's clink glasses,
come on, Cheers!
Cheers!
Ah, it's my turn.
I want to ask P'Yihwa...
why aren't P'Mud and P'Knight friends anymore?
Can you tell me? I really want to know.
So…
Don't tell him.
Just tell him!
He definitely can't handle it.
So, this is what happened.
That day, we were out drinking just like today.
Yeah.
And Knight excused himself to go to the restroom.
Bottoms up! Bottoms up!
Just like that, my friend.
Oh, I can't take it anymore, I'm going to the restroom now.
What's wrong with you?
Can't even handle this?
Don't make a mess here.
Go on, up to my room.
Good job my friend.
Let's keep drinking!
He's gone. It's your turn now!
Mild, listen to me first.
See? Didn't I tell you not to get involved with him?
He's so damn bad!
It's been a long time.
We've never heard the truth from his mouth.
Besides, you guys used to be good friends before.
Can't you start over?
Fine, let's just start here then.
Hey!
Calm down! Let's talk first.
Mild, trust me.
How can you dare to say that?
It's obvious you raped my brother.
Hey Mud.
Calm down, calm down first.
Can you just listen to him first?
Mild!!
Mud.
Mild, Mild.
Mild, Hold on!
Hey Mild!
Hey Mild! Wait for us!
Would you like to try? In my world
Where it's just us, having fun all day
If you dare to step in and compete
I'll shower you with so much love
you won't be able to take it all
If you dare, I'll take care of you
Even if it's hard, I don't care
Just open your heart to a new world
I promise you won't regret it
Do you dare? Uh uh oh oh
To walk together
Are you scared? Uh uh oh oh
Will you agree? Uh uh oh oh
To love me every day
Just hold my hand and we'll go together
Do you dare? Uh uh oh oh, Uh uh oh oh