The God's
Her Highness.
Your Highness, not at all ok.
His Majesty will kill him for sure.
Your Highness!
You are the 18th best cookess ever!
You two, put her down!
Yes.
You two are so selfish.
I'm the queen of Su Wuyang.
I'm a criminal.
What's selfish?
It's true.
You're the queen, aren't you?
The South Palace won.
You're not only good at guarding,
but also good at keeping your mouth shut.
It's okay.
Today, I'll teach you a lesson.
What's the rule?
Be brave.
I'll let this bitch
never beat anyone again.
Yes, Your Highness.
The King of Su Wuyang
Episode 1
You're right.
I'm not suitable for the title of
the King of Su Wuyang.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, you're here.
Your Majesty, are you heartbroken?
Don't forget.
How did the woman betray you?
Was she Sophie Wu's boyfriend or your smuggler?
Why not?
I've told you a long time ago,
you серver
will not stop me
from Elsa the Envoy of the South Palace.
So bold,
spécial.
You dare to ruin Na Ying's life?
I'm sorry, Father.
Go.
I don't know what to do, Your Majesty.
Please stop.
Xiao Wan.
Don't forget.
But my father gave you the chance to go back to the capital.
Do you want to go to the bridge?
I promised you that I would do what you and Nang Jiang Wang did.
I left him.
I did it to torture him.
I want you to live.
I didn't find out what Prince Ji did to you.
You can't have anything to do
before you hide it.
I'm afraid I'll be in trouble.
How is it?
Mrs. Pei has been too considerate.
She has a weak body and a wound.
If we don't use the temperature of Yuhuang Mountain,
we'll be in trouble for the next few days.
He can use the temperature of the royal family.
I'll take my leave.
Master.
You're so thoughtful.
You're even against the memorial.
Father.
How did you get the space to enter the palace today?
When did Su Wuyang get down?
He's just trying to protect you.
I don't know.
I think he's almost there.
You're a fool.
Why can't you even climb up Su Wuyang's bed?
I'm not a fool.
I don't care what you do.
Just wait for the empress to die.
If you really can't do anything,
you'll have to kill Su Wuyang
and use your death to get to the throne.
Princess.
Are you all right?
You're just insulting my daughter.
What could have done to her?
You're suddenly mad.
I wouldn't want to offend her.
Subscribe now.
Father, why doesn't a dehisc from your father
feel so good?
The warmth of the yellow mountain is good for you.
If you don't want to die, just obediently listen to me.
Where have you never seen your body?
What are you pretending to be?
I already have my husband and child.
I'm different from before.
If your husband and child
know that you are now with another man,
will they still want you?
Your Majesty, you should be the most lenient one.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry, Yinghe.
What are you pretending to be?
You didn't make this face?
If Your Majesty insisted that I did it,
my life would be ruined.
I killed you.
It's too easy for you.
Nangong Yan,
remember this.
Your life is real.
Your body is also real.
Your Majesty.
The song is a golden lake, a lake and a lake.
I embroidered you a unique cloud.
I embroidered you a strange cloud.
Xi'en has tried to punish to understand how you greatly improve your love of me,
I will never forget you.