[Bad Memory Eraser]
[We followed the production guidelines
when filming child actors and animals.]
First, promise to never see me as a woman.
Second, you must respect my
privacy outside of working hours.
Third, you should undergo a brainwave
test and detailed consultation once a week.
Fourth, you don't have to provide
the four major insurances and salary.
Just provide room and board
for exactly three months.
Please read the rest as well.
I'm making a big decision by accepting
the offer to be the team doctor.
Normally, I should just write a standard
contract, negotiate, and just get it done.
I just have written it down briefly.
Why…
If there's a part of the terms you don't like,
we can make concessions and modify it.
There's no need for modifications.
Because I'm not going to sign the contract.
If you're done talking, please leave.
Just a moment.
Why?
You introduced me as the team
doctor in front of the investors,
and now you're saying
you won't sign the contract?
Because my mindset has changed since then.
Back then, I liked you,
but not anymore.
That's good, then.
You shouldn't have feelings for
someone you met through work.
I'm so relieved.
Now I can focus only on work.
Since I have a lot to do.
Please leave.
But you said the team needed a doctor.
I got permission to take
time off from the hospital.
Please leave.
You're kicking me out at this
hour? My phone battery is dead.
I can't leave now.
Please understand that this is
skinship due to a home invasion.
Oh my.
Since I drank a glass of wine earlier,
I can't even give you a ride now.
No, I have no reason to take you home.
Charge your phone in the guest
room and go home on your own.
Then could I charge this…
Do it yourself.
Oh, yes, I will.
The test subject has been discharged.
Discharged?
But the hospital director said
that even outside the hospital,
I should observe the test subject and
gave me time off from my hospital duties.
Thanks to that, the work is
going on without any hitches.
So, it would be better to
observe his everyday behavior
naturally outside rather than in a hospital.
Yes.
It's quite scary, isn't it?
That pufferfish poison.
It's said to be about ten
times as potent as cyanide.
They're born without poison,
and are weak with tiny fins when they're born.
But they eat poisonous food
to protect themselves
and to survive in the jungle.
That's frightening.
Don't worry, and just drink.
If we want to protect the subject,
we have to become even stronger.
Gosh, that startled me.
This darn weather.
Oh my, I'm freezing.
[Episode 6, Love Game]
I love myself.
All the people in the world love me.
The universe revolves around me.
Now, let's start the day fresh today as well.
Concentrate on the breath coming in,
and concentrate on the breath going out.
Three, two, one.
You are awake?
What's this…
I ordered delivery.
I thought you left at dawn,
but you are even having breakfast?
This is my true self.
This is what I always look like at
home, except when I go to work.
Why are you doing this?
You just have to not fall for me.
You said I was firm with
men, right? That's right.
Just think of me as wearing
a suit thicker than Iron Man's.
I will ask you once again.
What is your intention behind this?
The intent.
Because you are my patient.
To take your side,
to be responsible till the end.
Oh, you little cutie.
Why are you calling at this hour?
What?
What happened? Tell me properly.
Alright, I'll go to the rehab center now.
Did something happen to
one of the affiliated players?
Is that so?
I'm out. Let's go together.
Let's go together.
Oh my.
Oh my, where is he?
Something happened to the player, right?
This is when you need a team doctor.
Let's go together.
Oh my.
What are you doing?
Seriously, are you really going to do this?
Are you really leaving?
Mr. Lee Goon! Mr. Lee Goon!
Hey!
Thank you.
Oh, you startled me.
Ma'am.
Why are you out here so early in the morning?
It's still cold outside.
Well, Ju Yeon hasn't come back yet.
Oh, l envy her.
She must be relieved to have
her mom so worried about her.
Are you jealous of her?
Should I treat you like Ju Yeon?
Really?
Then that'd be so good.
This is the Korean style. It's affection.
Then I would feel relieved too.
Seung Hyun, go inside.
Hurry up.
Yes.
I treated you well because
you are my friend's daughter.
You stayed out all night
without saying anything?
Oh my, oh my, ma'am.
Do you think here is a guesthouse?
Coming in and leaving when you want!
If you're going to do that, leave right now!
- Why are you doing this? Please calm down.
- What?
Yesterday, you brought sweet potatoes,
and today you brought potatoes?
What are you doing outside?
You.
When I called your mom, she
didn't even know you were here.
Did you contact my mom?
You came to Korea and stayed out
all night without saying anything?
If you stay out once more!
I'll kick you out immediately.
I'm sorry.
Darn it.
I wonder if my mom told dad.
Are you surprised? Don't
you know taxis are fast?
Okay, I'll leave.
But, if I lose the bet, I'll leave.
- A bet?
- Let the player have the deciding power.
If the affiliated player
says she doesn't like me,
I won't bother you any further and will leave.
I never lost a bet.
Then, you will bet?
What if the player says no?
I'll leave without saying anything.
But, never change…
Deal is a deal.
Who is the affiliated player?
I said I wouldn't do it. I said
I wouldn't do rehab or anything.
I'm a psychiatrist, Kyung
Ju Yeon from the agency.
I came to help you.
Player Si On.
Shall we sit down calmly and talk?
[Lee Goon]
This is Lee Gun. You are Si On's mother, right?
Little cutie is…
I was late in greeting you because
Si On said you were overseas.
Does it make any sense to be excluded
from the national team candidacy?
You said you were a former player.
Don't you know better than anyone
that it's not often that you get the chance
to go to an international competition
as a national representative
in an international competition?
Since the knee injury won't be problems
by the end of the national team game,
if she wants, I'll appeal to
the association and get tested.
I already made her take all the tests. Oh my.
Please don't worry too much
and just trust me and wait.
I will resolve things well
with the association.
Let's go.
Oh, Si On's mother.
You know that a contract without
the guardian's consent is void, right?
Let's go.
Have a drink of something nice.
What kind of business card is this?
Could you tell me about your
emotion that's making you cry now?
Why?
Think of me as a human diary,
and if you tell me everything,
you'll feel relieved.
A human diary?
Shall I tell you about the last diary I wrote?
Title, love game.
I made an unforced error by missing
a down-the-line shot at a break point one.
After that, I only missed passing
shots, angle shots, and drop shots,
but then I lost the set
and started to collapse,
breaking the history of my love game.
I was in the top tier in the ITF,
but then started to fall behind in the KTA,
and now, I could not make
it to the national team.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
You're upset because you couldn't
make it to the national team, right?
You know what a love game is, right?
That's what they say when couples play tennis.
Right, that love game.
Yeah, I guess you're more upset
because you lost to your boyfriend.
From talking about boyfriends
to fighting between players.
Well, there can be discord within the team too.
I'll help you get through whatever it is.
So, shall we start the consultation?
But I don't have much time.
Maybe we can talk about it while
we're rehabilitating together.
Okay, well… What rehabilitation
should we receive first?
Excuse me, player Si On.
Player Cha Si On!
You didn't leave, right?
I thought you left, Player Si On.
Did you become closer with player Si On?
This is just the beginning.
Could you please put me down for now?
Do you know what this position is called?
To me, it looks like a Superman pose.
Stop talking nonsense and put me down now.
I've never seen this before
either. How do you do it?
I don't know how to use it.
Is it done like this?
I feel dizzy, stop it, just stop.
Put me down now, and stop joking around.
Professor Han.
What brings you here
at a non-consultation time?
Oh, it's good that you're here.
Could you and your family
please persuade your brother?
It's an emergency because
he got discharged overnight.
He doesn't listen to anyone.
And I can't exactly say that he's
in the middle of a clinical trial…
Fortunately, he doesn't seem
to dwell on the lost memories.
If memories of the past were to surface,
we don't know what effect it
might have on his brain circuits.
If even a small memory comes to
mind, it will come back like dominoes.
Will he remember everything?
I guess so.
Are you anxious?
Are you anxious about your brother
returning to his former self?
Everyone is satisfied with the present.
You've been taking
the medication regularly, right?
For panic disorder.
Yes.
It's not that I take medication
because it's become a routine,
but I get anxious when I don't take it.
But more importantly,
it seems like today is
Dr. Kyung Ju Yeon's day off?
She is busy, so there'll be a temporary
suspension of medical services.
Huh? Why, why?
Just give me her contact information.
- I have something to talk to her.
- Huh?
What are you going to do with it?
Why do you need the medical staff's contact?
I just thought we could grab a meal together.
Then would you like to
eat with me? That's great.
Today, I mean, actually today…
Goodbye, I'll get going.
He's so clueless. I don't know how
he can figure out what I'm thinking.
Ah, I should've asked for
her number beforehand.
I know her neighborhood, though.
The neighborhood?
The neighborhood!
It has been reported stolen.
Mom told it to Dad.
Ms. Sae Yan, I'll just give you one of these.
It's on the house!
You're totally the country grandmother
type. I mean you're full of affection.
Ma'am, seriously!
Thank you so much.
Oh my, drink it slowly.
Wow, you're really gulping it down.
Is that a special skill?
Hey, you.
You, Lee Shin!
Are you a stalker? You followed me, right?
No, I came here because I have stuff to do.
Maybe you are the one who knew I'd come here,
and came here in advance.
Why are you drinking a beer
with my picture displayed on it?
Well, that's because,
after I finish drinking it,
there is even this kind of fun.
I wondered how you found me.
Did you come here after seeing the address
I told you to send the bracelet to?
Why? Because I rejected you,
do you still have feelings for me?
We went on three dates and drank
beer all the time, and then again?
All I remember is the beer tour
during the Italian game tour.
Wow, you seem to remember it all so vividly.
Give it up.
Since you hit me, this molar
over here really hurts.
That must be a wisdom tooth.
So, can you stop your unrequited love for me?
If you keep doing this,
I'll report it to the reporter.
No.
Now that my dad knows I'm in Korea,
there might be someone following me.
It would be better to be careful.
Unless you want to be quietly buried
under the artificial turf of the tennis court.
Since you'll never see me again,
look whenever you want.
Let's never see each other again.
I want that too.
Oh my, they are exactly the same.
Both the athlete and the CEO.
You have had a hard time.
Well… you had an argument
with the hospital director too?
I heard you didn't go against it, either.
Well…
That… I found out late too.
The hospital director and Te O
colluded and to our subject…
It's not that I couldn't refute because
I was afraid of the hospital director.
It's the test data examined by the neurosurgery
department without our knowledge. Take a look.
By erasing bad memories,
the medial prefrontal cortex was overactivated.
Whenever questions related
to the first love are asked,
the results are inconsistent.
Does that mean his self-esteem
went down every time I rejected him?
I'll keep an eye on the hospital.
You manage the subject well.
Does this mean they are going
to do something to the subject?
No, of course, they won't go that far.
Under the pretext of a new surgical
method rather than a simple clinical trial,
how can we know what experiments
the neurosurgery department will do?
I will protect my patient.
Oh my.
Oh?
Now that I think about it, it's already…
Wow, time flies.
Professor, do you have time today?
Huh? Oh, yes, I do.
I mean, I don't have a wife or kids, so…
I have time!
That's good.
Then, please tell me some
tips for counseling athletes.
Like a know-how.
- What?
- Yes.
Figure it out yourself.
I was startled.
- It's today, right?
- Yes.
Why are you giving her money?
Are you planning to buy something?
That's…
Actually,
I feel a bit strange saying this to you.
Oh my, alright, enough.
That's not even necessary.
We also need to take care of camaraderie.
We decided to pool the money.
Because today is the day
for the money pool payout.
Oh my, why are you gathering it at this hour?
Go and do your work!
Ah, camaraderie?
I bluntly wrote that it's my birthday on SNS.
Dr. Song, do you have a phone charger?
Ah, I don't have a charger.
Dr. Te O.
Dr. Te O, do you have a phone charger…
No, it's okay.
Be quiet, be quiet.
I said be quiet.
Sit down, no, that's lying down.
Sit, like this, sit like this.
Turn around, turn around.
Like this, turn around like this.
Can't you do this? Show me your hand.
Huh? You did it…
Why do you keep stressing out
the one who doesn't understand anything?
He understood everything, but
he's just pretending not to hear.
Cola, you don't have to do such things.
You can live freely the way you want to.
Oh, you startled me.
Should I also tell you that you're cute?
Why do you keep sitting on my lap?
Oh.
Okay, today's menu is boiled pork.
I don't eat meat that's been boiled in water.
Even now?
What?
No, I know, I know.
I knew that already, so I prepared pork belly.
Let's eat pork belly.
Okay, Dad.
- Alright.
Alright, let's eat, let's eat.
Thank you for the meal.
- It's delicious, right?
- Yes.
You shouldn't stare when someone
else is counting money or eating.
Cola.
You have gained too much weight recently.
Eat diet feed later, okay?
Shin, did you hear about
the national team coach?
Ah, they said he's a foreigner.
A foreigner?
Let's meet him together when
you meet the general director.
Why?
Because you'll gain weight as soon
as you enter the athletes' village.
You should tell them in advance
that you're managing your diet.
I can't go chasing after you and keep watch.
Ah, I know the experts would take care of it.
But I'll contact the agency
and tell them to do it right.
Have your meal.
Okay, I got it.
I'll eat the broccoli.
Yes, eat the spinach too.
You said you wouldn't eat meat that was boiled.
You're eating well.
I think I should go now.
It's good that you are doing business,
but do you really have to live there too?
Would it be better if you worked from home?
Yeah, someone might think you've
got a woman hidden in your office.
Ah, what are you talking about right now?
Is now the time for me to fall for a woman?
Why? Oh dear.
In front of your first love then,
you used to say, "Isn't she eating so lovely?"
First love? What first love?
Did you have a woman you liked too?
Lee Goon has a first love?
I was mistaken.
Now that I look, the way
she eats isn't lovely at all.
He got dumped.
Is she pretty?
Yes.
First love is just a thing of the past.
I'd rather you not mention
my first love anymore.
Fine, let's say you got dumped.
- He got dumped.
- Did he really get dumped?
Ah, right, where's my suitcase?
- I threw it out.
- I sent it for service.
Ah, I sent it for service
and then threw it out.
You threw it away?
Oh, they said it couldn't be serviced.
But that was something I cherished.
Just buy a new one. It doesn't cost that much.
I got it.
Enjoy your meal.
Goon, you've got to finish
your meal before you go.
Why is he…
Is your first love pretty?
How did you get rejected?
Lee Goon really got rejected.
We're now just acquaintances who met
through work, so it's not a first love thing.
You brought your first love into the workplace?
It's so heartbreaking.
Would you like me to tell you
a secret to change her mind?
I can help you.
Oh, right.
That day, the day I had the accident,
did I just stay at home that day?
You said I fell down the stairs.
Well, you slept all day at home and fell
down the stairs because you weren't awake.
The accident happened when the family was
all together, so you were discovered quickly.
But why are you asking that?
It's not like you're remembering
old memories or anything, right?
Not yet.
Yes.
Get regular medical check-ups.
Professor Han is worried about you.
[Alumni reunion location, J Hotel]
[Recent search, J Hotel]
[J Hotel]
[You are invited to the alumni reunion]
That night, I went to the alumni reunion,
but why is he lying?
Why is the black box memory card missing?
I was wrong. It was all my fault.
It's for everyone's good, after all.
Unit 2001!
Yes.
She didn't come yet?
Understood, carry on with your work.
Yes, all is normal during duty!
Safety!
The phone is powered off,
connecting to voicemail…
She still hasn't charged it yet.
[Dad]
Oh, I should call you 'Ms. Man'
instead of 'Ms. Sae Yan'.
Did you drink all of this by yourself?
Ju Yeon, just lend me ten thousand won
to buy four cans of these beers.
This works much better
than a sleeping pill at night.
That's alcohol dependency.
It'd be nice to have something to depend
on when there's no one to rely on, right?
When I feel suffocated, if I gulp this down,
I get this feeling as if my
insides are getting cleared out.
Does alcohol really clear that out?
Ju Yeon.
Ta-da, don't you remember this?
You made this to me.
Did I?
Yes.
This is a wish bracelet.
You said if I wear this and then
it breaks, my wishes come true.
You said to wear it when I
have a wish I want to make.
Do you still believe that?
You're not a kid anymore.
I saved it without using it
for just any wish, and then,
I took it out with a big decision.
It's not about making a wish,
but about making an effort.
If you don't make an effort
but only make wishes, who will…
Well, there are things that don't
come true even with effort.
Oh, my.
Will drinking this really
make me feel refreshed?
Yes.
A dog? Why is there a dog here?
Bark at me, doggie! Woof!
So cute, it's so fluffy.
Let's go for the third round.
We are already at the fourth round.
Where would we even go?
Ah, this is why you don't usually drink much.
I had just one wish in my life.
So I studied to death to achieve it
and I devoted six years to do the research.
Far from having my wish come true,
I feel so empty inside, just like this.
What? Is the glass leaking?
Still, you are doing well for yourself,
given all the studying you did.
Wasn't that your wish?
It's all about the process
for the wish, the process.
Do you know how lonely
that process is?
How precisely must a wish be crafted.
Because I pursued perfection,
even my coworkers don't
want to have lunch with me.
The man I trusted…
I was taken advantage of by a senior I trusted.
And then,
I was abandoned by the only patient
I was wholeheartedly committed to.
I'm envious of you.
It would be nice if we
were born swapped, right?
I envy you, Jeon Sae Yan.
Everyone likes you.
Grew up without the twists and turns of life,
and grew up with plenty of
love without any worries,
without concerns…
I envy you.
You really don't remember anything, right?
What you see isn't everything.
I can't see anything.
I'm not going. I won't go!
The boss told me to bring you back.
Tell them I'll return after work.
I don't have options.
I said I'm not going!
- You rascal!
- Oh, you startled me.
Come over here.
If you came here for a trip, you
should have fun and then go.
Get lost! Go! You little brat, go.
- Interpret it.
- Uh, well…
Interpret it now!
I'll call my dad myself.
If you don't keep the promise, next
time I'll take you no matter what.
He said he's sorry and asked you to forgive
him just once. He said he would go right now.
- He got scared.
- Yes.
Go!
The self-defense you taught
me in Italy, I did it well, right?
If you touch her, I won't stay still!
I'll keep an eye on it.
Are you okay?
Of course.
- We have to go.
- Where are we going?
- We should go to the fourth round.
- No.
What are you talking about?
This is the fourth round now.
That's wrong.
That man knows me.
Can't go in, can't go in.
I can't help but wait here.
Ju Yeon.
I want to go back again.
[Assigned Parking for Unit 2001]
There's no van.
He hasn't come back yet.
I'll have to wait here until he arrives.
Ju Yeon, it's too late now.
Let's come here again early
tomorrow morning, okay?
Ju Yeon, you're drunk now.
Drunk?
Me?
Me? I'm not drunk. I'm totally sober now.
Go ahead.
Really? But how can you leave like this?
If you don't go, I won't go, either.
Huh?
Mom had spread out the blankets like this.
Ah, good.
What are you doing? Get up now, please.
It's okay. I'll sleep without
washing up, just like this.
What are you talking about? Get up now!
Jeon Sae Yan.
Lie down next to me.
What are you…
It's been a while since we lay down together.
Okay, I will protect you.
The pillow is hard.
Of course.
Your neck won't be able to turn tomorrow.
If I try hard, will my wish come true?
Of course, whose wish is it?
Right, it's the stubborn
Kyung Ju Yeon's wishes.
I'm my dad's daughter.
Dad.
It's been nearly half a century
for me to devote only to research.
I treat the loneliness of the patients.
But who treats my loneliness?
Professor Han.
Oh, why?
I called you several times,
but you didn't answer.
Gosh, this is heavy.
This is kimchi.
We made this kimchi at home and
also made some for you, professor.
Dr. Song, why are you giving this
to me? Your family should eat this.
Colleagues are like family too.
You can't eat without kimchi, right?
I'm not sure if it'll suit your taste though.
Make sure to have it with your meals.
What else do we have
at our age? Health is the best.
I'll get going then. See you tomorrow.
I'm like her family?
Does she want to be family with me?
She even knows my taste.
Does she…
Does she like me?
Yes, sir.
Oh, is that so?
Yes, I'll come down right away.
[Designated Parking for Unit 2001]
Ju Yeon, Ju Yeon.
Oh my.
Hey, hey.
Oh, my head hurts.
Ah, a cramp! I have a cramp! What should I do?
Oh my, oh my.
What are you doing in someone
else's room? You must be crazy.
What are you doing here right now?
I thought I slept at home.
Oh, smell of alcohol.
Your drinking habits are also the worst.
If it's a way to get rid of
affection, it's very successful.
That's fortunate.
Since our investor is coming,
so please move aside.
Only if you give me the card key.
Haven't you already lost the bet?
It's not over yet.
We won't know until the national team test.
Now, quickly.
Enough, leave now.
Jeez.
Just a moment, wait.
I should meet the investor first too.
Oh, smell of alcohol.
How do I look now?
As a team doctor personally selected
by the CEO, I should give a greeting.
Ah, this is driving me crazy.
Ah, yes, yes.
Here's the key. Leave now.
Go for it!
Have you arrived?
Thank you for coming in person.
Please come in.
You should drink some
herbal remedy to sober up.
I almost took the wrong
way while going to buy this.
I don't need things like this.
But I'm loyal to you, right?
I slept with you so you wouldn't feel
embarrassed sleeping there alone.
Yes, I'm extremely grateful.
And you even covered me with the blanket.
Well, it was not quite hotel-grade,
but it was like the hotel parking lot.
What aren't you coming in?
You go ahead.
What is this smell?
Did you drink and stay out last night?
You must have braced
yourself to get in big trouble.
- You've lost your mind.
- Mom.
I had a really hard time.
- Get out.
- No.
You little rascal, come here now.
If you want to get an investment,
you'll need the contract of a star player.
The player Cha Si On has some issues,
so we plan to finalize the contract
by the end of this week.
I heard that you're
the player Lee Shin's brother.
Ah, yes.
He's at the Big Picture Agency,
which you have invested in.
I heard he's about to renew his contract.
It's hard to gauge whether he'll
go to CEO Hong or to his brother.
If you're going to take
a picture, take a good one.
What's with this face?
At least do some editing.
Just took a picture without
the sender's info and sent it.
Would he or she have sent it to
the reporters without a message?
If it was sent, the reporters
would have contacted us first.
There's no need to worry.
You've become more lenient with
scandals, but will the sponsors be too?
There's nothing to worry
about because I'm honest.
Oh, I met her by chance…
And if she was going to send it to
reporters, she wouldn't send it to me.
Who? Who sent it?
She did.
Her family is pretty influential.
Her family is a gangster, so they warned me.
A warning?
I just need to make sure
not to run into her again.
Shred it without missing a single page.
I came here all nervous for
nothing when I'm busy.
I'm going to the practice room.
When are you going to
sign the renewal contract?
You have to speak up if you need something.
Traitor.
Where are you going?
To work, I can't give up.
My wish is also desperately needed by someone.
Your hand.
Why are you giving this to me?
Let's make a wish with reverent hearts.
Ah, it's fine. I'm not
a child. Take it off now.
Oh, you shouldn't say that.
What's this in Korea?
Take that back now.
Take that back.
Please make her works go well.
What about your wishes?
You are more important to me than myself.
What was your wish?
I…
I'll put aside my wish for a moment.
If you need anything, whether it's
love or work, tell me everything.
I'll help you with everything.
Even pufferfish have natural predators.
Only humans eat pufferfish
knowing the lethal dose of its poison.
Uniquely.
That's how venomous people
are, more than pufferfish venom.
If there are no flaws, you have to find them.
Isn't that so?
It seems like this patient,
Lee Goon, likes me too.
After seeing us dating,
saying don't mess with his things.
He even punched you and
discharged himself from the hospital.
That's about Kyung Ju Yeon.
He said Kyung Ju Yeon was his first love.
He may want to challenge you.
You should be nervous. Why do
you always come to this snack bar?
I didn't realize it before, but
patient Lee Goon is handsome.
Is it really confidence that
makes someone attractive?
Before? You've seen that patient before?
Yeah.
That… that's the person from back then.
The person who killed mouse number
107 with a car at the hospital.
- What?
- Oh.
You weren't here, right?
Back then, Dr. Kyung and that patient
seemed to be sworn enemies.
And she suddenly became his first
love after he got the brain surgery.
That's so nice.
I'm jealous of her.
[Tennis Training]
'Love Game.'
'A scenario in a tennis match where
one player fails to score any points'
'and it means zero?'
Wasn't a love game a couples game?
Ah, how embarrassing.
- Please, charge this as well.
- Yes.
Ju Yeon.
I didn't intend to interrupt.
Did you come to see me? I went to see you too.
Ah, that…
I'm trying to learn about
tennis for the consultation.
Are you perhaps offering to counsel me?
Player Cha Si On.
Cha Si On.
I read that book and kept
watching tennis broadcasts
but I studied in a rush, so no matter how much
I read, I can't understand the rules well.
I did memorize quite a few words though.
Do you know what dating
and sports have in common?
It's not done with the head, but with the body.
You remember it by doing it yourself.
Otherwise, you might forget by tomorrow.
I've never tried it before.
Wait a minute, just a moment.
Now.
How do I do it?
Like this, like this.
- Try holding it again.
- Okay, again.
Now, look.
I'll count one, two, three.
One, two, three.
- Like this.
- Ah.
Okay, let's try again, just like this.
One, two, three.
Is this right?
Well done.
Ah, then shall we try a backhand too?
- Good.
- The backhand is the opposite way.
Okay, just like that.
- One, two, hit.
- Hit.
- Your arm comes up like this.
- Ah.
Okay, I'll try it.
One, two, three.
Is this right?
It was perfect.
Now I get it.
Alright, then let's try one forehand,
one backhand, in succession.
- In succession?
- Yes.
- But…
- One, two, three.
How was it? Was it correct?
It was perfect.
Ah, now I understand.
This is fun.
Why are you here at this hour?
Surprise!
My friend.
The time is… Hey, slippers, slippers!
Wow.
Hey, look at this place.
What? Why is this place so good?
'Agency Goon.'
It's tremendous.
This is totally a hotel, a hotel.
Whose room is this?
Hey, this isn't a house, it's a company.
A bedroom.
But why are you here without contacting?
Hey, I don't have to call before coming, right?
Here it is.
I'm going to look around a bit.
So this is my room.
- Why are you lying there?
- It's good, I like it.
Ta-da.
Ah, come out, come out.
Somehow I thought it was strange.
What?
You worked all night at the sports agency?
What is this? What is this?
Huh? What's this?
Give it back to me. This belongs to our team
doctor. No, it's the candidate team doctor's.
A team doctor?
There's a team doctor in the agency?
But it seems the team doctor is a woman, right?
Well, I'll re-hire the team doctor.
A man I have no interest in at all.
Interest? Interest?
That means you have some interest in her.
No, that's not it.
It's that person you met
at the hospital before… that…
First…
First love.
It's her, but it's not working.
Even if I've sorted out my emotions now,
it could suddenly pop out like a virus carrier.
So I'm trying to block it from the start.
Hey, that's a good thought.
Send her out right now.
But why are you telling me to send her out?
What?
Well, I mean… There's no chance it'll go well.
Why would you insist on keeping
your first love by your side?
Hey, well. I'll have to keep an eye on you.
I'm going to take a shower,
so please get me a towel.
Hey, hey, why are you going there?
I'm going to sleep over.
What are you planning to
do after sending me away?
Hey, hey, hey.
I said I'm going to sleep over.
You are banned from visiting after 7 P.M.
Oh, and,
I heard you're a candidate for the national
coach, you're getting closer to success.
Congratulations, do it well.
That…
Wait, first love?
In the past, she had something with Shin.
I can't even tell him about this.
Shall I go?
[Reserved]
Ah, yes, let's set off.
- Isn't that player Lee Shin?
- Player Lee Shin.
Where is this place?
Did you move?
No, there's a place I need to drop by.
I'll go on my own from here.
The expert even gave a one-on-one lesson.
I'll treat you to a meal next time.
Tomorrow, I have to go to the hospital
to consult with the player Cha Si On.
Medical test.
Just by chance!
I'm going tomorrow too. How about tomorrow?
What?
You said, "Let's have a meal together."
Was that just a passing remark?
Why is everyone like that?
Promises must be kept.
Yes, yes, let's have lunch tomorrow.
Here.
Mine's out of battery, but…
I'll go.
Is that bracelet in fashion?
Next lesson, we will play a game.
A game with an active player?
It's obvious it will be a love game.
Let's do that.
Love game.
Okay.
A very intense love game.
Yes.
Respect solely for the benefactor of life.
No, no.
Welfare for the prospective
employee candidate, yes.
Oh, I'm a good person.
Oh my, what's going on?
What's going on?
Oh my, oh my.
What's so good about that kind of woman?
Look at that, look at that.
She keeps behaving indiscreetly like that.
It's driving me crazy.
I want to
keep helping her.
Do you need some help?
No, it's okay. I can do it myself.
Oh my, oh my.
I'll help you.
I said it's okay.
Ah, yes.
But she is firm to all men, not just me.
Geez.
Geez, oh my.
She has strong pride and bad drinking habits.
Ugh, she's the worst.
Oh right, battery.
Who are you?
Hey!
Oh?
You are the lady back then.
Why are you here again?
Right, here…
I came because I couldn't
properly apologize to Ju Yeon.
Sneaking up on her like
a cat burglar to apologize?
Ah, nosebleed.
We made a deal that we'd date
once Ju Yeon returned from the U.K.
But I ended up dating another researcher.
Ju Yeon firmly believes
she will go out with me.
My girlfriend has no idea about this situation.
I also had such a hard time
between the two women.
Even if it looks like I'm playing
a double game, isn't it a good thing?
Explain directly to
the person who was hurt by you.
Why are you explaining all the details to me?
Since Ju Yeon is your first love,
so it seems like you have animosity towards me.
And you're suddenly discharged after that day.
Well…
If you are uncomfortable with me being your
primary doctor, I'll recommend another doctor.
Surely, the primary doctor
knows my body the best.
I will get the test done on time.
By the way,
you said Ju Yeon was your first love.
Do you remember how you met
Ju Yeon when you were young?
I was embarrassed because you
suddenly said that she was your first love.
I'm not sure why that's curious to you.
I don't want to take up my busy
time to play nostalgia with you.
Are you sure?
That Ju Yeon is your first love?
Why is he ringing the bell?
He can just come in without doing that.
Ta-da!
Why are you here?
Then you are
my brother's
first love?
Yes, she's my first love.
[CEO's Office]
[Bad Memory Eraser]
Nice to meet you for the first time.
Is he mad because I didn't tell him about it?
Are you scared that I'm
joining as the team doctor?
It's just that I feel uncomfortable.
It's not like I'm working naked.
Shin, do you want to live like everyone
else? Are you the only one sacrificing?
Player Lee Shin, is there
really something going on?
Who exactly are you looking for?
The person I love.
That person used to live here when I was young.
Have you fallen for me?
Then, I might end up really liking you again.
That's all I can do for you.
I've brought an interpreter,
and where should I take her?
This was the place in that memory.
You can't be by his side.
Please don't give Goon trouble
anymore and just leave.