Where are you going?
The coffee Smell of you
The music of love is very beautiful.
Xin Yue,
so many years,
what did you listen to?
You're thin again.
I didn't see you.
Do you always eat instant noodles?
I told you many times,
don't eat instant noodles.
I don't have nutrition.
I don't think
I can cook well.
By the way,
I have a big surprise for you.
Next week,
I can go to the theater.
This time, I'll be alone.
How about it?
Am I really good?
I also left you
the best place
in the middle of the street.
Did Xiang Xiang grow up?
Don't you know me?
Xin Yue,
how about you?
I have a big hiccup.
How did you get married?
I was crazy about you.
But I still have far more that I have.
But you sure I raise him very well.
You look so pretty.
Even though I'm not pretty.
You're so annoying.
Watch your hands.
Oh.
You look so grumpy.
No need to be nervous.
Tomorrow is the first day of the game.
Let's play for a while.
Just one hour.
Who can relax and play well?
Right?
You can just throw your ball out of the net.
I really didn't expect that.
How can you enter the finals?
The coach is very important this time.
Or else, he won't let me accompany you.
Right?
Mr. Fan.
If I don't think about it,
will you be disappointed?
If you are the most talented person in my team,
really.
Mr. Fan.
What time is it?
Looks like we'll be late together.
Seriously.
I'll call Jiao.
Hello.
Hello, Uncle Jiu.
Why haven't you left yet?
I'm at home.
Didn't we say that we'd meet at 10 a.m.
and watch a movie together?
I forgot!
You're so good.
You're angry.
No, I forgot.
Wang Di asked me to tell you.
He can't go today.
He's going to watch basketball match with Gao Lei.
He called me yesterday.
When did he forget?
I'm sorry, Uncle Jiu.
Don't leave.
How about this?
Forget it. It's okay.
Please say sorry to Qing Ling.
Bye.
Uncle Jiu said that Wang Di...
I heard it.
It's your turn.
Qing Ling.
Please say sorry to him.
Why are you angry with him?
Qing Ling.
Don't be so rude.
I'm here for you.
I won't let you call them.
Next time, you can call them yourself.
He said you're angry.
Before the class,
I'll announce two things.
The first thing is...
The new idea of the first season is to play the game.
Everyone knows that
I personally led Wang Di to the first Beijing Championship.
Right?
The other members of the group
called us and informed us.
Wang Di won the prize.
Wang Di,
guess the first prize.
I don't know.
Let's give the first prize to the national team.
Come on.
You don't have to say anything.
Say something.
Come on.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you, teacher.
Oh, no.
Xi Zi is not your style now.
Okay.
Next class,
come to my office.
You tell me alone.
Wang Di, I'm so proud of you.
You...
You have to celebrate this time.
Tell me the second big thing.
You can't go crazy.
The school leader decided
to restore the autumn oil for our senior year.
Wow.
What's the second prize?
This time,
it's for the senior year.
The prize is the water fountain.
Yes.
Hey, what are you doing?
It's not bad to have fun in the senior year.
The old rule is
to be free and willing.
The beauty will be free.
If you want to go,
go to Fang Liu's place to report your name.
I'll go.
I want to go back
and discuss with the parents.
Don't report your name.
If the parents don't agree,
go to my place.
Teacher, I don't care about that.
Qiu You, you must go.
Qing Li, Qiu You, let's go together.
If uncle Huang is here,
we won't have fun together.
Right?
Are you going?
Okay, no more discussion.
I'm done.
I'll talk to you later.
One more big thing.
Today afternoon,
the principal of the school will come to our school to check.
You guys are all old.
The school uniform is all dressed up.
Who's going to do the thing?
Do you hear me?
Yes.
Coach Chang,
Don't think much about that.
Meow.
Don't run.
Go.
What rubbish is this?
Just pick it up and sweep it.
Mr. Chen,
the leader is not fit to go to the safe zone.
What if?
Don't be careless.
Hurry up.
Go.
Where are you from?
Isn't he a wild cat?
Is he here?
Manager,
why are you here again?
Who asked you to pick up the cat?
Hurry up.
I'm talking to you.
Do you hear me?
Hurry up.
I'm...
I heard...
What's wrong?
You still want to hit me?
Mr. Chen,
the leader is coming.
If you let me hear the cat,
you'll be dead.
Hurry up.
Did you hear that?
What is going on?
What's the situation?
The sound of the sound is so loud.
Meow.
What are you looking at?
Here.
Meow.
Move aside.
Qing Ling.
Open the door.
Here.
Meow.
You scared me.
Qing Ling, be careful.
You...
Get down.
The owner is here.
What are you looking at?
Get down.
Move aside.
Look at him.
You have a good influence.
You listen to the owner.
Get down.
Fang Di.
Go.
Get the key.
I'll go.
Go if you want.
I won't.
You still want to go, right?
Go.
Qing Ling.
Come down.
Go.
Fang Di.
What are you looking at?
Go.
Let's go.
Is there
She's scaring you
Why are you letting go
Cover my face
Qi Ling, what are you doing?
Don't try to change seats!
If you do this, I'll tell Teacher Fan.
I'm sorry.
He wants to interview you!
Teacher Fan, you're his classmate.
You have to recommend him.
Yes.
Do you know how much he needs to use now?
Don't be angry.
But I heard that he's a teaching leader.
What do you mean? I thought too much.
No, that's not what I meant.
Then what do you mean?
Don't be angry.
This kid in the group, he has a problem.
But based on my understanding of this kid,
if no one makes him like that,
he won't be like this.
You mean I'm making him like that?
No, no, no.
I didn't mean that.
I just think that you're a kid.
You're a cat in the group.
You're not worthy of your title.
Your school doesn't have a name.
I've seen that.
You're pitiful.
You just let him go, right?
No wonder he's like this today.
Teacher Fan,
I just want to remind you.
You're his classmate.
If he makes any mistakes in the future, you won't be responsible.
For him, whether it's worth it or not, you should think about it.
If you keep following Aik's orders,
even if you're being held responsible, can you still make it?
Let me tell you,
even if you don't care about him,
I'll tell him sooner or later.
Qing Ling.
Teacher Fan is calling you to work.
I've already asked the head of the math team.
There are five famous students in the competition this time.
I have to help you to win this competition.
What can I do?
Who told you to play two games last time?
I thought that if you didn't go to the Olympics,
you would only have to make it.
If you keep doing this,
who will be the best for you?
Right? You're not the best.
Can you not laugh? Be serious.
I'm talking to you. What's wrong with you?
I know that you've suffered a lot this year.
I've suffered a lot of grievances.
I can manage some of those. I can't manage some of those.
I'm still saying that I'm doing this for your own good.
I can't just watch you destroy yourself.
Do you understand what I mean?
If you feel uncomfortable,
don't be uncomfortable.
If you want to talk to me, I can go to work.
If you don't want to talk to me,
you can talk to a friend who can speak.
You can't do anything.
You're uncomfortable.
You'll be hurt.
You're so old.
You're so young.
You're so cute.
I wanted to have a cat when I was young.
My mom didn't let me have it.
She's really so cute.
Is it good?
It's good.
By the way, I heard that you're going to have a fall trip.
You'll go there too.
No.
Go. It's great to play with everyone.
Professor Jiang and Wang Di will go there.
I won't.
It's because you're going to pay. I'll go too.
I don't want you to pay.
You want to know so clearly about me?
Fine.
This isn't my place.
I'll go.
Why can't you go?
What's the point of going there?
Why are you yourself?
Don't you go to the play with Wang Di?
It's good to stay for two days.
It's not good.
Are you still not good with Wang Di?
I think it's different from before.
You're talking to Wang Di now.
I think it's the same.
Do you think
people really want to separate?
Wang Di said that.
I've always wanted to say that I don't agree with him.
Maybe people can separate.
But they can't.
They can't even recall.
Because people can't control themselves.
Really?
Yes.
Because we're all the same.
It's noodles.
What are you looking at?
My son wrote it.
I got it.
I'm back.
Do you need help?
No need.
I'll take your order.
I'm so angry.
I'm really angry with my parents.
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
I'm happy.
Fine.
Your mom is so angry.
Who said that
we should learn to be polite
and be polite.
You know that.
I'm not afraid of being rude.
You're not being polite.
I'm not.
How can I be polite?
This is my son's
national award-winning work.
I can do it.
I'll show it to my sister-in-law.
Right?
Dad.
You're in the competition.
It's not my award.
Hurry up.
You should win the award.
I'll put it there.
Pull me.
Don't put it there.
You should put it there.
Yes.
Put it on.
I'm happy.
I can do it.
I'm sorry.
I'll give you the award
if you need something.
Mom.
I want to go out with my classmates
for 300 yuan.
300?
Okay.
Is that enough?
Yes.
How much do you want?
I'll give you.
If I give you,
I'll give you 500.
Then you can give me 200.
People's eternal life.
But
because
the fight between the soul
with a experiments
has taken places
которой
in the times past.
It happens.
People who ever witnessed like this
are human
since the day
the живites
came to life.
Zhengcla Enc prototypes
Whether that's true...
I can't take all your blaming down on me.
But I still have killing concern.
I didn't want Kuning.
This is what I want.
Do you want to get done this.
Sorry, I'm a little clumsy.
It's okay.
We're just sleeping at home.
Fang Di.
I want to tell you something.
What is it?
Feng Xue Xiao?
Wang Di?
Gao Lei.
Why are you here?
My wife is on the upstairs.
It's dad.
I don't dare to admit it.
Why are you two together?
Are you...
No, no, no.
My dad is in the hospital.
I'm here to get a job.
I thought you two...
Wang Di, you're so nice.
You've been in the school for years.
You never attend the school.
You don't have to ask anyone to call you.
Come on.
Just let me know.
How many years has it been?
Last week, Fang Liu said
he wanted to hold a big gathering.
I'll tell you when the time comes.
Okay.
I'm here.
I'll tell you when the time comes.
Call me.
Call me when you get back.
What a coincidence.
What did you just tell me?
Just tell me when you get back.
Your doctor asked me to stay at home for a few more days.
Your dad is in a hurry.
What's wrong with him?
He's so nice.
He's in a fresh air.
He's almost going to kill me.
Sit here for a while.
Okay.
Just sit here.
I'll push you.
Help me.
Slowly.
Are you okay?
I'm a little bit sleepy.
Jiajia,
thank you for coming to see me.
It's my pleasure.
I'm glad to have you.
I can't live for long.
I'll be happy.
You're a good boy.
I can't live for long.
I just hope
I can leave them alone.
I can get a baby
as long as I can marry Wang Di.
Dad, what are you talking about?
Your dad is...
Can you talk?
Did you hear me, Wang Di?
Hurry up.
Uncle is in a hurry.
What are you doing?
You take Jiajia to the playground.
Go to the ice.
Yes.
I'm fine.
You two go to the ice.
You see so many people.
Go.
I'll sit here with your dad.
We'll stay here for a while.
Okay.
We'll go first.
Where's your mom?
She's in the U.S.
I was in the second year.
Li Wangsun passed away.
Do you know what I thought
at that time?
I thought I could finally understand
Huang Shiyu and Qin Yi.
But it's too late.
I never used to be a good friend.
I remember you came to my house
and said something to me.
Uncle Huang said something.
He said
I was the happiest person.
I didn't understand.
Wang Di.
Do you think we are bad people?
Do you think there are
people who are not selfish in this world?
If there are,
we are all bad people.
If there are no,
we are just ordinary people.
Really?
What did you say?
We found the reason for ourselves.
How are they?
As if you just want to cooperate with me.
It's not fun to play.
You will regret it.
Why don't you get something
from Phuong Dian?
You should care about him.
Did you say that you're wronged again?
Why should I care about him?
Do I have this kind of obligation?
It's not just him who's wronged.
What's wrong with you?
You two are not normal these days.
I am me. He is him.
Let's talk less later.
Is this the one?
No.
Go and get this one.
Go and care about him.
Yes.
Is there a car?
Let's go.
No need. Thank you.
You're still so considerate.
Can we be like before?
You said before.
What did you say?
Before you met Gao Li?
Before you met Uncle Hong?
Are you not impressed by me?
Your bloomingotive?
Impossible.
You can't even see it.
Who are you talking about?
I'm talking about you.
You're a coward.
The Chief Chen scared you.
So you're relieved.
Qilin.
I owe you.
Do you think the whole world owes you?
You're the one who's in the wrong.
You're the one who's in trouble.
The thing that happened to your family
is not someone who's lying on your head.
It's not like no one's going to force your father to kill him.
You think it's unfair.
You can't just leave.
You had a chance to take the exam.
You didn't hold back.
You can't blame others.
You can't blame me either.
You'll be angry at me.
Why do I have to endure you every time?
Because no one can bear you.
No.
You have Uncle Huang.
If you have Uncle Huang, you don't need others.
You don't need me either.
Fine. It's good.
Now I'm completely relieved.
Do you know how much pressure I put on you as a friend?
You think I'm willing to do it?
Qilin.
You're so selfish.
You'll have to apologize to him.
It's okay.
I promise.
You really have better know how I feel about you.
Everyone is exposed to the mist.
So you think too much?
Yes.
Posted...
Take it out.
What?
Take it out. I'll take a look.
Take out the wallet.
Take it out.
Is it this?
This is the one.
Are you satisfied with this?
Are you satisfied?
It's late, Wang Di.
It's late!
You lost your pride.
You're a despicable man.
You're always despicable.
You're going to die for me!
I'm sorry.
Wang Di!
Where's Qin Li?
I don't know.
I heard that no one wants to be with him.
It's your fault.
What did you say?
It's none of your business.
Come here.
What's this?
Take a look.
No, Teacher Fan is a dog.
I'll just take this and look.
Okay?
You owe me a lot.
This is my house.
This is good.
It's none of your business.
Okay.
Don't talk about money.
Okay, okay, okay.
What are you doing?
Let him look at it.
I don't have anything to eat.
Let's go.
I don't understand.
Are you afraid that you won't be able to eat?
I don't know if you have any complaints.
I know.
Do you want to hear the truth?
Nonsense.
My mom is on business with everyone.
Just because of this?
No way.
My mom asked me
to ask her dad for a business.
I don't know.
I have to ask her dad for a business.
We often eat together.
Brother Rong,
do you want to scold me?
I'm not scolding you.
I just remembered
that my mom told me a story.
What story?
People can't be poor.
People
can't be poor.
You're talking about me?
You're talking about yourself?
Boss,
I'm coming to the wedding.
Okay.
Is it good?
It's okay.
My father said
that we should eat less.
Then you should eat less.
I'm not eating.
You want to order?
I'll eat with you.
It's not interesting
to use this time.
It's not fun at all.
I won't come here in the morning.
Is it because of
Boss Gao that he's playing with me?
Maybe.
He won't come again.
Your wonton.
Thank you.
Try it.
Is it good?
It's good.
Sir,
what's wrong with Wang Di lately?
You should ask Wang Di later.
You let me ask him.
He let me ask you.
You two are the same.
What's wrong with you?
I can't say it.
You're not good at it.
You think you can't read
the words
on the paper?
I've read them.
Do you know
which one is the most similar to Wang Di?
The heart is different.
The mouth is different.
It's not uncomfortable to write it yourself.
Eat something and don't talk.
It's good.
Sir,
do you think
you can be a good friend
without Wang Di?
It's not meaningful.
By the way,
in two months,
it's your birthday.
You're 18 years old.
You should live well.
It's nonsense.
You have to live with me.
You can't live alone.
You have to come.
I'll go wherever I want.
I'll eat whatever I want.
You have to buy the bill.
Do you hear me?
Okay.
You can't finish it.
I'll reward you two.
Stop playing.
Get some rest.
Okay, I'll sleep right away.
What time is it?
I'm also...
Close the door.
Go to bed early.
Okay, sir.
Okay.
Who's there?
Open the door.
What's wrong, Mr. Chen?
I don't know who's running away.
This...
He's...
He's too unreasonable.
Who is he?
Mr. Chen,
why don't you take a rest?
I'll handle this.
I'll see who it is.
You're back.
You ran quite fast.
Whose is this yellow sticker?
It's not mine.
It wasn't you who ran from the window just now.
It's not me.
I said it's okay.
It's just your mouth, right?
Come in.
You're all back.
Why are you two here again?
You really don't have any surprises or surprises.
You two live in this room, right?
The one who ran from the window just now
wasn't you.
It was him.
I'm sure it's him.
Tell me.
Who?
Say something.
You two are still in the same room.
What's the matter?
Do you have any evidence?
Isn't this evidence?
Get out. I'm going to sleep.
Qin Li,
how can you talk to me?
I told you to get out.
Say it again.
Qin Li.
Qin Li, you can't do this to Mr. Chen.
You can't do this to me.
No.
Qin Li.
Go to sleep.
Go to sleep, Qin Li.
You have to go back to school.
I'll talk to you properly.
You're so annoying.
You can't go to sleep.
Have a rest.
You're annoying.
No.
Wait.
Let them think about it.
Yes.
Mr. Chen.
Hello.
Okay.
Don't worry.
Wang Di.
Your dad called.
He said you'll go to the hospital
after you arrive.
What happened to my mom?
No, it's your mom.
She said she was hit by a car.
Don't worry.
She'll be fine.
What's wrong?
Wang Di.
What's wrong with your mom?
Does it hurt?
It's okay.
It doesn't hurt.
My mom hit him on the road
in the morning.
She was lucky.
She didn't have a big accident.
She was a little stubborn.
The doctor said she should be fine.
Where's my mom?
She ran away.
She didn't have a bright day.
She didn't see the car.
What's so funny?
What's this?
What are you doing?
You're sleeping.
When did my mom lie down?
The doctor said
she had to lie down for half a month
before she could be cured.
She had to be cured after she was cured.
It's okay, son.
Look at you.
Why are you so anxious?
I just...
I just wanted to be a part of the family.
I was making money.
Mom,
don't worry about money.
I won a prize
for the competition.
I gave you a prize money.
You gave me a gift in the house.
If you have the news,
I'll be satisfied.
This is the first gift you made.
I'll keep it for you.
I'll give it to you.
You should study hard.
Don't be upset.
It'll be delicious.
You know?
Go back now.
You're going to school tomorrow.
I'll go to school tomorrow.
I'll stay here with you.
Hello?
I'm Wang Di.
Wait a minute.
Tell me.
I'll call your boss.
Tell him the truth.
Mom, I'm begging you.
You can't call him.
My parents know
I'm going to be beaten to death.
And the school
has to give me a hard time.
Maybe you'll be fired.
What do you mean?
You want me
to be fired from the front line, right?
That's not what I mean.
As long as you don't admit it,
there's only one result.
I can't be beaten for you.
Don't say nonsense.
Wang Di, don't worry.
How about this?
Give me a few days.
Let me think about it.
I'll think of a good one.
I'm begging you, Wang Di.
I'll give you two days.
I'll call my boss
when I have time.
I'm begging you.
I'll call my boss.
I'll be fired from the front line, right?
atzui
Qinli
it's OK. Come in.
Hetoo
You guys are not hot water again.
I haven't washed my hair for two days.
It's dirty.
But you should wash your hair.
Let me do it.
I'll help you.
Okay.
Can I use the water temperature?
Yes.
The water temperature is right.
By the way,
how are you guys playing in the autumn?
Are you happy?
I shouldn't go.
It's not a big deal.
It's boring.
I regret it anyway.
Okay.
Thank you.
Hello, Xiao Xiao.
I'm still in the dorm. What are you doing?
I'm fine.
I'm staying here.
I called Wang Di and Qing Li.
They haven't been home since morning.
What's wrong?
Are you with Qing Li?
I need to talk to her.
I saw Qing Li.
I'll call her.
Call her.
Hello?
Qing Li, did you see Wang Di?
No.
I'm begging you.
What's wrong?
I'm the one who's been on the line.
But I'm really in a bad mood today.
I can't stand up.
I didn't call Wang Di and Qing Li.
I don't know if you can help me.
I'll go with you.
Qing Li, you're so nice.
Thank you.
We'll have fun together in a few days.
I'll treat you to a meal.
Okay.
I'll hang up now.
Bye.
Bye, Uncle Huang.
Alright.
I am off with a clean week at the dorm.
Guess it's a tough job for you.
Qing Li.
Yell to the living room.
Sure.
Baozi, take the way.
Okay.
Let's go.
["Academia ją ge"]
Bai歡迎 a matchmaker's wife at Top 3 MIE.
Did the teacher tell you that?
No.
Wait a minute.
Let me show you what row he's worth.
You go up to the main building first.
Then, you should go to the rock tower.
At last, you go to the chariot.
Then sign here.
Okay.
This is as He Last
ashaiamientos,
like that place the most.
Had a short trip to N qia şen and got back in love with her.
I watched all of those worlds of sea lights and Par ruthes and aren't nice combination.
It was a fifteen year old gang of stairs to The world
it was like I was,
to find out about the story
I'm afraid the Gibro
move from emotions
to do something
very warn men
for little things
I'm sorry
my love has become 뭐
I'm willing to give you some
I like to see you smile and call me a little girl
Your expression is the love of a friend
Lonely become sweet color
And unique and unique
I like to see you smile and call me a little girl
My mood is like a lover
Weird intuition, wrong positioning
I love you, I'm a little worried
I like to see you smile and call me a little girl
Your expression is the love of a friend
Lonely become sweet color
And unique and unique
I like to see you smile and call me a little girl
My mood is like a lover