♪The spring breeze blows through the world♪
♪Blowing across the willow bank
and the peach blossoms are brilliant♪
♪The legend spreads♪
♪There is always an amazing heartbeat♪
♪Who picks up the pen and writes
that it's not too late to meet♪
♪Looking back to see someone smiling happily♪
♪Adding a touch of intensity
to the depth of love♪
♪Being with you in the world of mortals♪
♪Whether it is a hustle or plain life♪
♪There will be no regrets in my life♪
♪See you in the next hundred years♪
♪Don't forget the current youth♪
♪I wish to stay and live up to the passing years♪
♪Every morning and every night we are together♪
♪It turned out we've known each other
since the beginning♪
♪A thought at a certain moment♪
♪He sent me a thousand words♪
♪She left a story♪
♪The sound of guqin is like water and
the shadow of the light is like a dream♪
♪Everything is tactful♪
♪Looking at the scenery and mountains with you♪
♪The rest of my life will last in perfection♪
♪Wait until the spring breeze blows♪
♪That's when I know your deepest love,
and I'll miss♪
(Imperial College)
=A Female Student Arrives
at the Imperial College=
=Episode 30=
As per His Majesty's order,
search this place!
Yes!
(Taoist scriptures)
(Contract)
Sir, I found something.
Sir, the snitch in the Prefecture Court
has been identified.
How?
It's...
Speak. Don't hesitate.
I'm sure I saw it clearly,
but this is impossible.
Young Master.
Our spies didn't report back
on time.
Which ones?
All three of them.
What?
The ones in the Prefecture Court,
in the warehouse,
and in the Imperial College
are all missing.
What...
Who did this?
Who can be this capable
and capture all my spies like this?
Young Master.
My spies in the Imperial College
said
they saw Yan San Lang.
What? He's awake?
Oh, no. It's a trap.
Yan San Lang didn't just regain consciousness.
He must have woken up much earlier.
He has even cleared Yan Yun Zhi's name.
Yan Yun Zhi's surrender
was just an act!
I thought
the death of Sang Qi would destroy his morale.
It seems like he won't go down without a fight.
Young Master,
we're not sure what His Majesty thinks of this.
I think it's better to lay low.
I can gather everyone
and...
It's not time to admit defeat!
Tell everyone
to burn all invoices here.
Arm ourselves before heading out.
If it's just a false alarm,
we can then tell everyone
that we're on a hunting trip.
If Yan Yun Zhi is planning to catch me red-handed,
then I'll also fight back.
I can take his life easily
under the name of treason.
And this time, I'll make sure he's dead.
Yes.
Then about your wife and your in-laws...
I was ready to sacrifice Xizhao,
let alone Grand Tutor Song.
Someone
has to be the scapegoat after all.
Noted.
I'll get it done now.
(Grand Tutor's Residence)
As per the order of Yan Hua
from the Prefecture Court,
we're here to arrest Grand Tutor Song
to assist us in our investigation.
The Governor of the Prefecture Court?
Why should my father entertain him?
Due to the serious nature of the matter,
we await Grand Tutor Song's cooperation.
Can my father
come back alive then?
Is he going to be
the scapegoat for everything?
I will not
allow you to arrest anyone
from the Song family as you wish.
Then you are forcing my hands.
We were classmates in the Imperial College.
We fought many times,
so there's no use to play nice now.
We were just bickering
and we never drew weapons.
Yan Yan.
I knew we would face off each other eventually,
but I didn't know it would be like this.
I see no point in discussing further.
This is our destiny.
Is this your final decision then?
You would be in my way?
All right.
I have always wanted
to fight you for real anyway.
This is between us.
Do not intervene.
Yes!
You guys too.
No one moves an inch.
Today
is the day Yan Xiao Lang and I settle our score.
Yes!
(Grand Tutor's Residence)
Song Luo Tian!
Song Luo Tian.
Am I dying?
I feel cold.
I'm going to die, aren't I?
Just stop talking.
No, if I don't say it now,
I will miss my chance forever.
Yan Yan, we might have crossed each other a lot
in the Imperial College,
but those times
are fun and unforgettable.
I didn't want things
to turn out this way.
I merely wanted to protect my parents.
If I die today,
then I guess I'll die the proper way.
I'll be free.
Wait, I'm about to draw my last breath.
Why are you so cold-hearted?
It didn't even land on the lethal area.
The heart is at this side.
It was just a graze.
You won't die from it.
You're overly pampered
and rarely got injured,
so you thought this was a fatal wound.
I won't die?
Then what I said...
What I said...
It's okay. I heard nothing.
I will
protect your family.
If they did something wrong,
they should bear the consequences.
But if it's not related to them,
then I won't let them die without reasons
like Qian Jiu did.
Take him away.
Yes.
Let's go.
You're late.
Yan Yun Zhi, you're one tenacious bug.
Seems like Yan Sang Lang
regained consciousness.
You surrendered yourself
and begged for a swift death
so that I'd let my guard down.
You finally got it.
But it's too late.
You haven't defeated me yet.
Why are you fleeing the city
in a rush then?
I'm on a hunting trip.
What a coincidence.
Me too.
And I just found my prey.
Yan Yun Zhi.
You really think you can
stop me?
Don't underestimate me.
It's quite obvious
who's outnumbered here.
Why? You want to create a scene on your way
back to Bianjing?
I can always kill you
and then deal with your cronies
later.
I'll still be hailed as the patriotic
Official Zhuo.
Yan Yun Zhi.
You only have your meddlesome self to blame
in the first place.
If you didn't insist on investigating
the death of Sang Yu,
you wouldn't find out everything.
The salt route will operate as usual
and my wealth will be accumulated slowly.
I could have been your brightest student
who would ace his exams
and lead a successful life.
And during Chinese New Year,
I might pay you a visit.
Isn't this wonderful?
But you just had to be nosy.
You just had to dig out the truth
and force me to do this.
You colluded with unscrupulous parties
to profiteer
from salt smuggling and tobacco trades.
Oh my, you sure gave fancy names
to what's essentially crimes.
It doesn't matter if you know now.
Yan Yun Zhi,
you shall die
with this secret.
So you asked for backup from the Sang family.
My father doesn't need to be here.
I'm more than enough.
Sang Qi, you're still alive.
(We already knew about the poisonous pouch.)
(We were just playing along.)
Take the medicine and you'll be fine.
Thanks, Physician.
Feeling better?
Miss.
Your lips are pale
and sweat gathers on your nostrils.
Those are the symptoms of deteriorating health.
Are you unwell?
Not necessarily.
But I've been feeling fatigued easily.
Come on, let me read your pulse.
What's the matter, Physician?
You've been poisoned.
Poisoned?
Miss, think hard.
Is there anything unusual
about your diet lately?
Nothing.
What about the things you keep
at close quarters all the time?
Unless...
This pouch was away from me once.
Miss, this is the poison powder from Xizhao.
In high concentrations too.
If you carry it every day,
you will feel nauseous
and lose the ability to taste.
Worst comes to worst, you'll be bedridden and die.
Noted, Physician. I'll take care of it.
Can you keep this a secret?
Sure.
Lian Pian. See the physician off.
Yes.
I'll take my leave.
There's only one possible explanation.
Zhuo Wen Yuan tinkered with my pouch.
But Qian Jiu is already dead.
Why go through such a hassle?
In a way, it still makes sense.
He definitely
has something to do with Qian Jiu.
But you found this pouch at the outskirt.
He can still wiggle his way out.
Then we'll play along.
Once he thinks he got everything figured out
and becomes complacent,
he'll make a mistake.
That will be
the opening for our retaliation.
Finally decided to show yourself?
Let me in.
(Funeral)
Let me see her for the last time.
I will follow you afterward.
(Thanks to the Pseudocide Pill from Miss Su,)
(I could fool Zhuo Wen Yuan)
(with my fake death.)
So itchy.
Young Lady.
Lian Pian.
Is your face very itchy?
Perhaps the side-effect of the Pseudocide Pill?
Let me see.
I'm fine. Let's go.
My death
would explain why Deputy Chief
surrendered himself.
And I provoked you in the cell
because I knew
you wouldn't kill me straight away.
You will keep me alive
until the day your plan comes to fruition.
And then,
we followed your new salt route
to find the rest of your people.
We also found where you stashed your fortune.
Sang Qi.
You lied to me again.
Why the poker face?
Did my intention to kill you
squash all hopes you had for me?
Zhuo Wen Yuan,
you kept mentioning our childhood.
But the current you
is so different from the one I grew up with
in the frontier fortress.
The current you
are just a stranger to me.
In that case,
let's submit ourselves to our destiny.
Qi, the final chapter of our story
is long overdue.
For the love and resentment all these years,
let's end it.
Qi, don't listen to him.
If you wish.
Don't worry.
Everything ends here.
Just come back with me.
Qi, I'm too far gone.
I'll return you
the life I owed you.
Young Master!
(Qi, I'm too far gone.)
(I'll return you)
(the life I owed you.)
♪You're the wind and the moon♪
♪That blows along my longing for you♪
♪Which is engraved in my heart
that forgets to wither♪
♪The eaves listen to the love
chimes for seasons♪
♪You're all over the world♪
♪With thousands of words hanging in the galaxy♪
♪Longing makes the rain falls♪
♪Da da da~~ da da da~~♪
♪I'm willing to wait for you all my life♪
♪To see each other at a distance
as we turn around♪
♪Can't bear to wake you up to
meet me the second time♪
♪Would you say yes?♪
♪I'm willing to wait for you all my life♪
♪To pick up the joy left in the old dream♪
♪By trading my life in exchange for love♪
♪Would you say yes?♪
(Imperial Study)
(Tian Ming Dong)
(Compilation of Zengzi's Teachings)
(Signee: Zhuo Wen Yuan)
(Report)
The case is crystal clear.
The culprit, Zhuo Wen Yuan, is now dead
and so are the rest of his cronies.
As for Noble Consort Zhuo...
In honor of our marital bond,
she will be spared.
However, as a noble consort,
she manipulated imperial ministers
and framed the loyal ones.
She will spend the rest of her life
in the cold palace.
Grand Tutor Song.
You will be stripped from your position
and exiled to the frontier fortress.
Song Luo Tian will be demoted to a commoner.
Thank you for your generosity, Your Majesty.
I volunteer to follow my father
and reflect upon ourselves
to turn over a new leaf.
I'm happy to hear that from you.
It means the Song family can still be redeemed.
Guards!
Yes!
Bring them away.
Yes.
Both of you worked really hard for this.
For your immense contribution,
feel free to tell me what you like as rewards.
Your Majesty, if you put it this way,
I'll be hard-pressed to say anything...
Such moral integrity. So be it then.
Wait, I mean
I'll be hard-pressed to refuse your kindness.
I actually have a small request.
Speak.
I wish to be the Manager of the Archive
in the Imperial College.
That's easy.
I also have another important request.
Deputy Chief and I
would like to recruit more students.
We want to establish Class Hualin
in the Imperial College
so that talented women who are
thirsty for knowledge
have a place to do so.
That way, everyone can use their talent
for the greater good of the nation.
Please consider this, Your Majesty.
I'll take note of it.
It's indeed a serious matter,
so I need to think it through.
Your Majesty, you allowed me to study
in the Imperial College.
That shows that you're someone
who appreciates talents.
I want everyone
to experience your tolerance and generosity.
All right. I understand.
What about you, Yan?
Just tell me.
I only have one request, Your Majesty.
Please retract your decree
and annul the marriage arrangement
between Su Jie Yu and me.
When you were being framed,
I already annulled the marriage arrangement.
Today,
I have another arrangement for you two.
You two finally got together
despite all the hardship.
That is a feat in itself.
I hope you two can get married soon
and be the role model of all Bianjing couples.
Duly noted.
(Cenotaph of the beloved son, Sang Yu)
Sang Yu,
are you watching us from above?
Your best friend, White,
did not forget about your will
and he takes good care of me.
So good that I have to live with him now.
Why do you make it sound like it's something bad?
I'm the victim, Yu.
I'm practically chained to the Sang family
from the get-go.
Yes, you're so right.
We really can't live without you now.
So be a dear and be the Sang family's son-in-law.
(Cenotaph of the beloved son, Sang Yu)
Sang Yu,
I finally understood why you worked so hard.
Don't worry.
We will make sure the Imperial College
will continue to flourish
to achieve your dream.
(Grand Tutor's Residence)
(Prefecture Court. No Entry)
Yan Yan,
even though you're dumb, boisterous,
straightforward, and stubborn,
you're still a good friend to have.
Song Luo Tian.
Even though you're spoiled,
reckless, tactless,
and self-centered,
I must admit
that my time in the Imperial College
and even in the Prefecture Court
was good because of you.
Is this how you two bid farewell?
Thanks to your help,
His Majesty was lenient on me
and merely demoted me
to a commoner,
but I still want to serve the sentence
with my family
and start over.
If possible,
I'll return to the Imperial College again.
And then,
I
will ace the exam on my own.
I'll wait for you then.
Wen Yuan.
Let's go home.
Let's go.
Mr. Zhuo...
He hated going back to the frontier fortress
the most.
But now that he's dead,
only Miss Song was willing to cremate his body
and brought the ashes with her.
Life is like a dream.
But with you by my side,
I never want to wake up.
Where did you learn this corny line from?
In Qingfeng Restaurant.
I knew it!
I really need to talk to Master Sang.
She keeps teaching her weird things.
That hurts.
Lian Pian!
♪The spring breeze blows through the world♪
♪Blowing across the willow bank
and the peach blossoms are brilliant♪
(Imperial College)
(Double Happiness)
♪The legend spreads♪
♪There is always an amazing heartbeat♪
♪Who picks up the pen
and writes that it's not too late to meet♪
♪Looking back to see someone smiling happily♪
♪Adding a touch of intensity
to the depth of love♪
♪Being with you in the world of mortals♪
♪Whether it is a hustle or plain life♪
♪There will be no regrets in my life♪
♪See you in the next hundred years.
Don't forget the current youth♪
(A Place for the Talented)
♪I wish to stay and live up to the passing years♪
♪Every morning and every night we are together♪
♪It turned out we've known
each other since the beginning♪
♪A thought at a certain moment♪
♪He sent me a thousand words♪
♪She left a story♪
♪The sound of guqin is like water
and the shadow of the light is like a dream♪
♪Everything is tactful♪
♪Looking at the scenery and mountains with you♪
(Imperial College)
♪The rest of my life will last in perfection♪
♪Wait until the spring breeze blows♪
(Imperial College)
♪That's when I know your deepest love, and I'll miss♪
♪The spring breeze blows through the world♪
♪Blowing across the willow bank
and the peach blossoms are brilliant♪
(Double Happiness)
♪The legend spreads♪
♪There is always an amazing heartbeat♪
♪Who picks up the pen
and writes that it's not too late to meet♪
♪Looking back to see someone smiling happily♪
♪Adding a touch of intensity
to the depth of love♪
♪Being with you in the world of mortals♪
♪Whether it is a hustle or plain life♪
♪There will be no regrets in my life♪
♪See you in the next hundred years.
Don't forget the current youth♪
♪I wish to stay and live up to the passing years♪
♪Every morning and every night we are together♪
♪It turned out we've known
each other since the beginning♪
♪A thought at a certain moment♪
♪He sent me a thousand words♪
♪She left a story♪
♪The sound of guqin is like water
and the shadow of the light is like a dream♪
♪Everything is tactful♪
♪Looking at the scenery and mountains with you.
The rest of my life will last in perfection♪
First bow to Heaven and Earth.
♪Wait until the spring breeze blows.
That's when I know your deepest love, and I'll miss♪
Second bow to the parents.
♪Every morning and every night we are together♪
♪It turned out we've known
each other since the beginning♪
♪A thought at a certain moment♪
♪He sent me a thousand words♪
♪She left a story♪
Third bow among yourself.
♪The sound of guqin is like water
and the shadow of the light is like a dream♪
♪Everything is tactful♪
♪I wish to stay and live up to the passing years♪
♪Every morning and every night we are together♪
♪It turned out we've known each other
since the beginning♪
♪A thought at a certain moment♪
♪He sent me a thousand words♪
♪She left a story♪
♪The sound of guqin is like water
and the shadow of the light is like a dream♪
End of ritual.
The couple may exchange gifts now.
A bamboo ruler?
What do you mean?
Are you planning to treat me
like a student in the future?
I dare not to.
A teacher uses a bamboo ruler
to discipline his student.
I gave it to you today
so that you can
discipline me as my wife.
No need to go easy on me.
I'll gladly take it then.
You'll love my gift too.
We crossed paths thanks to a pouch
and we also used it
to seal our relationship.
It's only befitting to use it
as a token of our marriage too.
I want to be by your side forever and ever
just like this pouch.
Here.
Thanks.
Sorry. I sullied your handkerchief.
I will return it to you after I wash it.
You're too kind.
The handkerchief is not expensive.
You can keep it.
Dummy.
That's why you're single forever.
Here comes the royal decree!
I came bearing gifts from His Majesty
for your wedding.
Sang Qi, come forth to accept the decree.
Yes.
(Double Happiness)
I,
who inherited knowledge
from many philosophers,
who sought words from the Six Classics,
penned this decree
so that the status of Scholar is granted upon you.
Thanks, Your Majesty.
His Majesty
gave me a promotion?
Am I the first female scholar
in the Imperial College?
Correct.
His Majesty has also given his verbal agreement
to the idea proposed by Deputy Chief Yan
and Scholar Sang.
The Imperial College can now have a Class Hualin
to accommodate the female students.
From now on, the recruitment process
shall not discriminate
people of any age, any sex,
and any social status.
Deputy Chief.
Our effort is not in vain.
We did it.
Darling.
A female student like you
managed to earn the trust of His Majesty.
That's why more people are allowed to study
in the Imperial College now.
Wait for me!
I have always wanted to study with you.
Hurry!
(Imperial College)
Quick.
You're here!
Let's go in.
Come on.
(Imperial College)
Quite the foresight you have.
♪The sun will be out soon♪
♪The sound of recitation wakes me up♪
♪Surrounded by a conducive environment♪
♪My pen never stops until the moon appears♪
♪A noble man keeps striving relentlessly♪
(Imperial College)
♪Seizing every moment throughout his life♪
♪For there is♪
♪A lot to learn in this world♪
♪The mountain of knowledge is intangible♪
(A Place for the Talented) (Imperial College)
♪Which he must work hard to scale♪
♪By studying each and every tome♪
♪Without faltering in his long journey♪
♪His penmanship♪
♪Is his true companion♪
♪Which trains him to uphold righteousness
at all times♪
♪Now do it♪
♪Seize this very moment in time♪
♪Put to practice what you've learned♪
Scholar Sang.
You might need
to behave appropriately now
and stop climbing to the rooftop.
The bell hasn't rung.
I still can do whatever I want.
Also,
I'm not Scholar Sang now.
And you're not Deputy Chief Yan.
Who am I then?
You are...
my husband.
♪Fly higher than the swans
with your lofty aspirations♪
♪You might even surpass heaven♪
♪Look at how beautiful our country is♪
♪As our generation♪
♪Rules the world♪
(Imperial College)
♪Your dainty figure is my muse♪
♪I put on an honest expression
to hide my bewitched heart♪
♪Though I might not say much♪
♪Every word is pronounced
with my most profound feeling♪
♪As our fate intertwined,
which life should we pick?♪
♪I'm willing to trade this life for a chance
to meet you in every life♪
♪Many woes and sorrows♪
♪Fill my existence♪
♪If persevering♪
♪Makes us fall in love with each other♪
♪That's how I come to this life♪
♪If not letting go of my past♪
♪Becomes my mistake♪
♪Then I shall not make that mistake♪
♪This beautiful story♪
♪Is like the way I look when I make up my mind♪
♪But my heart changed its mind♪
♪At the dawn♪
♪What an unexpected love♪
♪And so I wrote my words with joy♪
♪I have accepted this life I reincarnated in♪
♪May this budding romance♪
♪Develop into something unforgettable♪
♪As our fate intertwined,
which life should we pick?♪
♪I'm willing to trade this life for a chance
to meet you in every life♪
♪Many woes and sorrows♪
♪Fill my existence♪
♪If persevering♪
♪Makes us fall in love with each other♪
♪That's how I come to this life♪
♪If not letting go of my past♪
♪Becomes my mistake♪
♪Then I shall not make that mistake♪
♪This beautiful story♪
♪Is like the way I look when I make up my mind♪
♪But my heart changed its mind♪
♪At the dawn♪
♪What an unexpected love♪
♪And so I wrote my words with joy♪
♪I have accepted this life I reincarnated in♪
♪May this budding romance♪
♪Develop into something unforgettable♪
♪As our fate intertwined,
which life should we pick?♪
♪I'm willing to trade this life for a chance
to meet you in every life♪
♪Many woes and sorrows fill my existence♪
♪If persevering♪
♪Makes us fall in love with each other♪
♪That's how I come to this life♪
♪If not letting go of my past♪
♪Becomes my mistake♪
♪Then I shall not make that mistake♪
♪This beautiful story♪
♪Is like the way I look when I make up my mind♪
♪But my heart changed its mind♪
♪At the dawn♪
♪What an unexpected love♪
♪And so I wrote my words with joy♪
♪I have accepted this life I reincarnated in♪
♪May this budding romance♪
♪Develop into something unforgettable♪