♪The spring breeze blows through the world♪
♪Blows the willow bank
and the peach blossoms are brilliant♪
♪The legend spreads♪
♪There is always an amazing heartbeat♪
♪Who picks up the pen and writes
that it's not too late to meet♪
♪Looking back to see someone smiling happily♪
♪Adding a touch of intensity to the depth of love♪
♪With you in the world of mortals♪
♪Whether it is a hustle or plain life♪
♪There will be no regrets in my life♪
♪See you in the next hundred years♪
♪Don't forget the current youth♪
♪I wish to stay and live up to the passing years♪
♪Every morning and every night we are together♪
♪It turned out we've known each other
since the beginning♪
♪Just a thought at a certain moment♪
♪He sent me a thousand words♪
♪She left a story♪
♪The sound of the guqin is like water
and the shadow of the light is like a dream♪
♪Everything is tactful♪
♪Looking at the scenery and mountains with you♪
♪The rest of my life will last in perfection♪
♪Wait until the spring breeze blows♪
♪That's when I know your deepest love, and I'll miss♪
(Imperial College)
=A Female Student Arrives
at the Imperial College=
=Episode 16=
(Secretariat Chancellery)
Bai Shi.
Did you really inform Qing Xuan?
Why isn't he here yet?
I did inform Qing Xuan,
but...
(Su)
Yun Zhi.
I have talked to your mother.
Both of us will travel together.
She was happy to hear that.
We can leave now.
(Qingfeng Restaurant. Shuiyue Shop.
Peach Blossoms Bloom)
Sang Qi.
Focus on the bigger picture now.
It's no time for a relationship.
(The Wei family)
(was obviously just a puppet
in the tea plantation matter.)
(But there's no solid evidence)
(that indicates that they were
ordered by the Song family.)
(Everything was somehow related to Xizhao,)
(but my elder brother
had no ties with the Song family...)
The clues are like the holes on this lotus root.
All over the place.
I can't draw any conclusions.
Unless Deputy Chief is hiding
some info about my brother
from me.
The audacity!
You dare ask the Song family to wait?
I don't care.
Give me a room now so that I can dine!
What's happening?
What happened?
- No room left?
- I...
Song Luo Tian,
can you give everyone a break?
Are you alone?
Why?
Can you do me a favor?
Song Luo Tian,
both of us study in the Imperial College,
but we don't get along well.
You're willing to drink with me today.
I suppose you just want a listener.
Is that right?
Whatever.
Even if it's you, Sang Qi,
I don't care.
Get out then.
I just got hold of Wei Zhan Hong's whereabouts.
Wei Zhan Hong? How is he?
He was exiled! What do you think?
Before he left,
I even bribed the soldiers
escorting the Wei family
with some money
so that they could look after Wei Zhan Hong.
But I just received news from the stage station
that they're arriving at the border of Jingzhou.
Is Grand Tutor Song aware of this?
My...
My father prohibits any mention of Wei
in our residence.
He severed our ties completely
with the Wei family.
That's why I'm here alone,
drowning my sorrow away.
Song Luo Tian,
at first, I thought
Wei Zhan Hong was just a sidekick of yours.
But it seems like
you hold him dearly.
You changed my view of you.
However...
Speak.
While Wei Zhan Hong is someone loyal,
the Wei family is convicted now.
Is the good faith you have in Wei Zhan Hong
enough to exonerate the Wei family?
Yes, I always ordered him around,
but we have also known each other for years.
My dad is strict
and I am temperamental.
So I always ask Wei Zhan Hong
to do things for me.
By the way,
sorry.
Wake up!
You can't leave me hanging.
Finish your sentence.
What did you ask him to do?
I asked him to prank you,
but he botched the plan.
Don't hold any grudges.
Get off me.
Forgive me, please.
I forgive you.
But you need to tell me what he did.
Okay?
Remember when you were poisoned
in the Imperial College?
It was me who asked
Wei Zhan Hong to poison the dishes.
You insisted on cooking for Deputy Chief.
So I poisoned it.
What poison did you ask him to put?
Laxatives.
Look!
(No, I didn't consume any laxatives.)
(It was the poisonous powders from Xizhao.)
(It could kill.)
(This means)
(Wei Zhan Hong is related)
(to Xizhao too.)
(Oh, no.)
(It was a trap!)
Wait.
We agreed
to forget about the past after drinking.
Later.
I'll drink with you when I have the chance.
But... Wait.
Come back, Sang Qi!
I
don't have any friends at all.
Young Lady!
Young Lady, why are you going to Jingzhou?
Qi.
(Agarwood)
Great timing, Mr. Zhuo.
Please stop her.
Why are you going to Jingzhou?
Deputy Chief might be trapped.
I need to save him.
But is he worth risking your life for?
Yes.
Young Lady!
Wait. I'll come with you.
(Prisoner)
Young Master!
There is quite some distance
away from the station.
Why aren't they here?
Did something happen on their trip?
Escorting prisoners is a tough
and laborious job. They can't be so fast.
Move.
Help! Help!
Young Master, there's a ruckus in front.
Save them, Bai Shi.
Help!
Help me.
Deputy Chief.
(Prisoner)
Run.
Run, Official Wei.
Are you okay?
Why are you here?
I won't let any harm come to you.
Deputy Chief.
(Prisoner)
Deputy Chief Yan.
We are here on Official Yan's order.
Forget about me. Chase after them!
Follow me.
Yes!
Bai Shi, carry your Young Master.
Zhuo Wen Yuan.
Find Wei Zhan Hong with the others.
I'll chase after Official Wei.
Be cautious.
Qi!
Young Master! Young Master!
Sang Qi!
(Prisoner)
We're too late.
Official, can you clean up?
I need to travel back to the main path.
Noted.
Better now, Young Master?
Deputy Chief.
What's the situation?
I was late. Official Wei was killed.
Bai Shi.
Deputy Chief is gravely wounded.
We need to bring him back to the city for treatment.
We can't let him bleed like this.
Let's go.
Qi, go back first. Don't worry about me.
What if the assassins come back here?
I want you to be safe.
Yan Yun Zhi, we're not in the Imperial College.
I don't have to follow your orders.
Should we wait for Mr. Zhuo?
He should be fine.
The assassins are not after him
so they won't do anything.
Besides, he has many soldiers with him.
Let's go.
Careful.
Come.
I'll carry you, Young Master.
No.
I don't want to ride with you.
But...
You should have told me earlier.
Your wound, Young Master.
Young Master Zhuo.
Wei Zhan Hong won't probably survive the fall.
It's fine.
Our plan failed.
He serves no purpose anymore.
According to our original plan,
after Yan San Lang
received the news that the Wei family
is close to Jingzhou,
Yan Yun Zhi would definitely follow us.
We didn't expect
Sang Qi to appear suddenly.
Forget about the plan then.
I took into account
the possibility of failure
and has stationed assassins on their way back.
Just in case the plan fails.
Do not harm Sang Qi.
I know that, Young Master Zhuo.
I already told them
not to hurt your Sang Qi.
Aren't you injured?
Yet you're holding me so tightly.
Didn't I ask you to stay put?
Why came here?
The Wei family is fishy.
Following them will put you at risk.
How do you know?
Song Luo Tian told me
that he asked Wei Zhan Hong
to poison me with laxatives.
However, I got the poisonous powders instead.
The Wei family is hiding something.
Deputy Chief, here.
Lean on me.
Xizhao again, unsurprisingly.
They want to leave no survivors.
Their infamy is real.
Get up now.
Young Master.
What happened?
Young Master,
we only have one horse left.
It might be too challenging to travel together...
Qi, you should head back first.
It's dangerous here.
Bring a physician and a carriage.
We'll wait for you here.
I'm staying.
Bai Shi, can you do that?
I...
Okay.
I'll leave him to you, Miss Sang.
Stay alert.
Qi, stop looking at me like that.
I'm fine. I know myself.
You're gravely wounded.
Rest well. Don't speak.
But I want to.
If you want to speak,
then you should tell me
what my brother had to do with Xizhao.
Yu.
To celebrate your recovery,
I stole my dad's best wine.
What's the matter, Yu?
You were so happy during the day.
Did something bad happen
at the frontier fortress?
With one wrong move,
everything falls apart.
With one wrong move, everything falls apart.
What did he mean by that?
I pondered about it for a while too.
Yu died abruptly in front of me the next day.
The coroner said
that it was a sudden cardiac arrest.
But he just told me
that he was recovering.
When I tried to look for clues
to uncover the truth,
someone had already erased all traces of Yu
in the Imperial College.
Perhaps...
Perhaps he found
a crucial
secret.
What are you guys doing?
(Sang Yu, Imperial College)
Who asked you to burn Yu's belongings?
No idea.
Someone claimed he's from the imperial court
and talked to Scholar.
Scholar then asked us to burn it,
saying it was to get rid of rubbish.
So you couldn't find those
who burned his clothes. Is that right?
Yu's case concluded very quickly.
Everyone from the Imperial College
to the Grand Commandant's Residence
assumed that he died from his sickness.
But I know very well
that someone was behind
his death.
The culprit was very well hidden
and I was just a student back then.
I couldn't investigate
nor fight against the dark forces.
Thanks to your perseverance,
the death of my brother
was not swept under the rug.
However,
how did you latch onto Xizhao?
After I was appointed as the Deputy Chief,
I've been conducting my own investigation.
I use Yan San Lang's position
to investigate in secret
any death that's similar to Yu's.
After you enrolled in the Imperial College,
we found
another crime scene
that bore a striking resemblance.
We discovered the powders
from Xizhao on the scene.
How is that so coincidental?
All clues point towards the Song and Wei families.
Our enemy may be hidden,
but I know that they are powerful.
When I enrolled in the Imperial College,
you were extra harsh on me.
You even sent me to the Lingwu Mountain
to find a master.
All that was just to...
Protect you.
To protect you.
Who are they?
I just hope
that after you undergo training,
you could be able to fend for yourself.
It's all in preparation for an ambush
like this.
Deputy Chief.
This...
Are you okay?
Qi, I want
to rest.
No, you can't sleep.
Yan Yun Zhi!
Look at me.
Open your eyes and look at me.
If you do this,
how are we supposed to get together?
Will you really
abandon me despite knowing my feelings?
When will we get together then?
Don't you know already?
Young Master!
Bai Shi!
Young Master! Young Master!
Hurry up, Bai Shi.
The carriage and the physician are here.
Young Master,
what happened to your lips?
Did someone hurt you again?
Bring him to the carriage now.
Don't ask him.
Qi, I want you to carry me.
But Young Master...
Come.
My sword, Bai Shi.
Okay.
Your Majesty.
(Official Document)
Yan San Lang.
How's the investigation?
Your Majesty,
Official Wei is confirmed dead.
The coroner has determined
a Xizhao tattoo on Official Wei's shoulder.
Wei Zhan Hong is still missing.
No idea if he's dead or alive.
The Wei family was found guilty,
but the crime scene had been tampered with.
We don't know who the Wei family was contacting.
Yan Yun Zhi was investigating the Wei family.
How is he now?
Deputy Chief Yan
was gravely wounded during his investigation.
Morning, Deputy Chief.
Morning.
Deputy Chief is back.
Morning, Deputy Chief.
Morning.
Deputy Chief.
(The wind blows and carries a beautiful poem)
Deputy Chief Yan?
Yun Zhi, you're here.
Everyone has been studying hard.
The imperial examination is around
the corner. It's just a practice test
so that they won't panic during the real one.
I brought some food for everyone.
Bai Shi.
Bring some water after you place down the food.
Careful.
Wash your hands before you eat.
Thanks, Deputy Chief!
Now you're all spirited.
Tell me why all of you looked so defeated
when you were writing the essay.
I missed all of you dearly
during my absence.
Yan Yan, I wanted
to drink with you, but it seems like
Scholar Feng would never let you go.
What a pity.
It's okay.
Several glasses can raise morale.
It's my treat next time.
Scholar Feng wants all of you to study hard
for your own future.
Show him some results,
okay?
Yes.
Look at
your handwriting, Guo Cheng.
I don't need
to read your text to know
you've improved.
Thanks, Deputy Chief.
The water is here.
Take a break, everyone.
Eat something.
Let's go.
Come.
Thanks, Deputy Chief.
Wash your hands.
- Hurry.
- Share it.
What is this? Let me see.
For you.
That's a lot.
Deputy Chief has been reborn.
Be patient. We'll share it.
Stop shoving. Pass it to me, please.
You have recovered?
What trick are you pulling this time?
Don't worry.
Play along.
Thank you, Deputy Chief.
It smells so good.
Come.
Give me some.
I want this.
Here, for you.
Qi, let's talk later.
There's some left. Here.
I can't finish it alone.
I feel like yours is more delicious.
We can swap later.
Can you pass this to him?
This is yummy.
Pass it to him. Try it.
Qi?
Master Sang.
Deputy Chief.
Qi.
Master Sang.
Why are you alone here?
What are you doing?
What are you reading?
Give it back to me!
Let me read it.
Why do you want to read it?
You won't understand anyway.
Anything?
Nothing.
We thought you were bored.
Exactly.
I'm not bored.
You guys can head back.
(Yan)
(Grand Commandant's Residence)
(Grand Commandant's Residence. Great Aspiration)
Greetings, Deputy Chief.
Zhuo Wen Yuan is not here, right?
No. Mr. Zhuo is not here.
Master, Mr. Yan is here.
Grand Commandant Sang.
Pardon my unannounced
visit.
How can I help?
I'm here to talk about
Sang Qi's academic performance.
But I remember
you are no longer the Deputy Chief
of the Imperial College.
Is our private residence part of your duties now?
You're right, Grand Commandant.
I am indeed free now,
so I can
offer some private tuition.
I believe Sang Qi could use
some tutoring.
Yan Yun Zhi.
Just be frank.
As you wish, Grand Commandant.
I am old enough to find a wife now.
Sang Qi has long attracted me.
So I hope you can consider me
as your future son-in-law.
Lian Pian.
What's for dinner today?
The Third Young Master Li sent pork chops today.
Our chefs are working on them as we speak.
They keep giving us pork chops
as if we don't already have this dish.
I guess Qi is just very popular among the men.
I don't know what's in the mind
of girls in Bianjing.
Four Bachelors? Four Handsome Men?
None of them holds a candle
to how I looked when I was young.
They look so hideous
yet they managed to enchant so many women.
With all due respect, Grand Commandant, my Young...
My, my. I'm getting old.
I forgot you're here.
I humbly accept your remarks.
Also,
Yan and Sang families are
two prestigious families in Bianjing.
Our statuses match each other's,
but there are pros and cons to everything.
Our marriage
might draw unnecessary attention.
I understand your concerns, Grand Commandant Sang.
However, marriage is an important matter.
Sang Qi should have a say too.
Lian Pian.
Mr. Yan has been standing here for a while.
Where's his tea?
Did I not teach you anything?
Yes.
I'll prepare the tea now.
It's okay.
I shall wait until Sang Qi makes up her mind
before my next visit.
Thanks, Grand Commandant.
See you.
I knew it.
It's indeed a trial from God.
I heard that he's arrogant.
But now, he's all
humble and modest.
That's a bad sign.
Qi will be charmed sooner or later.
Master.
You just shooed him away.
You know nothing.
He will come back again.
Father.
Master.
Great timing.
Look at this.
(Recommended Candidates
for Vice-Magistrate of Chenliu County)
(Vacancy in Chenliu)
I heard there's a vacancy in Chenliu,
so I gave your name to the Ministry of Personnel.
(The candidate shall depart to Chenliu
as soon as possible)
Chenliu?
It's a small county but it's close to Bianjing.
It's a good job nonetheless.
(Recommended Candidates
for Vice-Magistrate of Chenliu County)
Think about it. The position is ready.
If you continue to waste your time,
you'll never find a wife.
Then I shall marry a crane as well.
(A Place for the Talented. Imperial College)
What's so urgent?
Deputy Chief Yan is really leaving.
Leaving?
Where to?
I got news from the Ministry of Personnel
that the Deputy Chief is
taking up a position in Chenliu.
He'll be inaugurated in a few days.
I thought he'd be back to host the vesting ceremony
for the top scorers in the imperial examination,
but it seems like our encounter
with him is short-lived.
I have an idea!
- What idea?
- Tell us.
During the test later,
don't answer properly.
Just write something random.
Are you saying
we should make Scholar Feng believe
the absence of Deputy Chief
is the reason why we can't study well?
You know me well, Master Sang.
Scholar Feng will be infuriated
and inform His Majesty.
The rest will solve itself.
You're right.
Yes.
Especially you, Zhuo.
Don't stand out.
We have to be in this together.
Isn't that right?
Yes.
I don't know why you guys are upset.
The Imperial College will operate as usual
regardless of Yan Yun Zhi.
Don't you want Deputy Chief Yan to return?
I'm here to study,
not to idolize him.
You guys are too young.
What does he mean by that?
Does he have to put it that way?
Right, what does he mean?
(The wind blows and carries a beautiful poem)
Stop writing.
Zhuo Wen Yuan.
Put it here.
(Grand Hall)
How insolent!
Let's head back and wait for the good news.
Sure.
Let's go.
Qi.
You really want Yan Yun Zhi to come back?
Not just me.
Every student wants him to come back.
Everyone might be afraid of Deputy Chief,
but deep down,
we all agree with his pedagogy.
They think Scholar Feng is way too conservative.
I'm asking for your opinion,
not theirs.
Never mind.
I'm not in a good mood today.
Let's hang out in Qingfeng restaurant.
But I have plans later.
You can go yourself.
(The one responsible for my brother's death
is nowhere to be seen.)
(The situation is risky now.)
(Is Deputy Chief seeking refuge in Chenliu?)
(Tomb of Sang Yu, Beloved Son)
(Someone was here.)
What a chance encounter!
We're meant to meet here.
You scared me.
Shouldn't you be afraid of my palm?
Let me remind you
that I'm your senior
when it comes to martial arts.
Also, you won't hurt me.
You're heading to Chenliu.
Why won't I hurt you?
You already knew?
Yes.
I learned it from someone else, instead of you.
We were so sweet together a few days ago,
but now, you wouldn't even tell me
something important like this.
I guess I'm still an outsider.
Qi, only by accepting that position
in Chenliu
can I have enough confidence
to ask your father for your hand.
What?
I haven't said yes to you yet.
Pinched!
If you're pinched by me, you have to be my wife.
I forgot you're still wounded.
Are you okay?
Qi,
if you don't want me to leave,
I won't leave.
My brother's will is not fulfilled yet,
and we still don't know the truth about Xizhao.
You can't...
I want your answer.
Go away! Go!
♪As our fate intertwined,
which life should we pick?♪
♪I would trade this life for a chance
to meet you in every life♪
♪Many woes and sorrows fill my existence♪
♪If persevering♪
♪Makes us fall in love with each other♪
♪That's how I come to this life♪
♪If not letting go of my past♪
♪Becomes my mistake♪
♪Then I shall not make that mistake♪
♪This beautiful story♪
♪Is like the way I look when I make up my mind♪
♪But my heart changed its mind♪
♪At the dawn♪
♪What an unexpected love♪
♪And so I wrote my words with joy♪
♪I have accepted this life I reincarnated in♪
♪May this budding romance♪
♪Develop into something unforgettable♪