♪The gentle breeze sweeps by♪
♪As the starlit sky shines bright♪
♪Our dreams glow with fiery light♪
♪In this world♪
♪We agree to take
the challenge together♪
♪Never looking back,
without letting us down♪
♪Stars fall into the endless ocean♪
♪We'll find the days gone by♪
♪Sharing joy alike♪
♪Standing strong through the strife♪
♪Vows, clear as day and bright♪
♪Every day, we laugh and bicker,
shout and fight♪
♪Running through the streets
and alleyways♪
♪Every time, you're there by my side♪
♪My shoulder's always there
to shield you from storms♪
♪If you cry and feel the sadness inside♪
♪I'll give it all to roam by your side♪
♪Like the closest friend in stride♪
♪But somehow, it feels more, undefined♪
♪Stars dream of returning to the sea♪
♪Fulfilling them,
like our promises alight♪
♪Riding on a white horse once more♪
♪Reappearing by your side♪
♪To be your guiding light♪
=You Are My Lover Friend=
=Episode 26=
=Failed Announcement=
- Let's go.
Peng Si.
Take it.
- Hello.
- Mr. Jiang, something's wrong.
There's negative news about Ms. Sheng,
and it's gone viral.
Mr. Feng wants to discuss it.
Okay. Let me see what happened.
I'll call you back.
It seems her private account
was found talking weird stuff
with another account,
and there are indecent photos.
(I knew she was not innocent.)
Well, go to your company.
Don't worry. I can go myself.
Sorry.
Don't be.
I'm leaving.
Then I'll stop here.
Don't worry.
Goodbye.
What happened?
You're finally back.
It's gone viral on Hot Topics.
Do you know that?
Go to my office.
(Mr. Jiang,)
(all the photos)
(are fake.)
(Someone hacked Nina's account.)
(We're drafting a statement.)
(We'll hold the hacker)
(and those who spread the rumors
accountable.)
Her agent Wang Xingyue
sent me this on my way here.
The screenshots of the chat
have been exposed for two hours.
Do you know how fast
rumors can escalate in social media?
As far as I know,
all the brands she cooperates with
have deleted her information
from their websites,
so I suggest that we delete the photo
of her being the Food Selector
of Yixiu Found of Food
from our homepage as soon as possible.
Cheng Hui, have you analyzed
the technical problem?
I need time to find the hacker,
but I've asked someone
to identify and analyze the pictures.
They're all composite images.
They're fake.
There's another problem.
In her channel, Sheng Nina
(Fake Photo Analysis)
always has wisdom and good taste,
but the negative news
are completely opposite
to her public persona.
Even if we can
solve this crisis,
we still need to consider
if we should renew her contract.
As long as we can prove
she didn't do this,
her public image won't collapse.
Anyway,
at this critical point,
the safest thing we can do
is to remove her from our homepage.
Since Cheng Hui has conformed
the falseness of the rumors,
Sheng Nina is very likely
to be the victim in this.
Her food live-broadcast
has helped us a lot
by bringing in many users for us
as a celebrity.
But we've established
our celebrity social media matrix.
She's not indispensable.
In terms of business interests,
she can only bring us
negative comments.
Regardless of business value,
I think we've built
a partnership with her
after all our cooperation.
Since Cheng Hui thinks
the photos are fake,
I think
we should keep her image.
What are you doing?
Didn't you decide to keep her image?
I have to prepare for a PR crisis.
Who else can be responsible for that?
Thanks, big lawyer.
Stop laughing, Jiang Shiyan.
My career as a lawyer
has long gone
since you got me
into this.
What are you doing?
I'll
visit a friend.
Visit a friend?
Okay.
We've sent the statement,
but based on the public's comments,
it didn't work well.
They said
they knew we'd claim
the account was hacked.
A PR company suggested
that you go live
and respond to this.
How should I respond?
Besides, even if I clarify it,
will they believe me?
It'll only lead to
more hot topics about me.
Mr. Cheng from Yixiu.
Why is he calling me
now?
Maybe
they want to terminate our contract.
Hello, Mr. Cheng.
(Xingyue,)
(are you with Ms. Sheng?)
(She didn't answer my video calls.)
(I'm downstairs,)
(but the guard wouldn't let me in)
(without her permission.)
Mr. Cheng.
Get in. I'll open the door.
(For Fine Food)
(In this press conference,)
(we'll focus on Yixiu Found of Food's)
(latest business.)
(I'm going to introduce)
(the core features
of the business platform)
(and give you a brand-new blueprint
of Yixiu's Food Map.)
Tell me the details
of the Yixiu's brand-new
Food Map Project.
It's the integration
of online and offline businesses.
They'll find
representative and historic
food specialties of an area
and open food collection stores there.
Eventually, they'll promote the brand
to other industries
via marketing strategies
of Yixiu Found of Food.
Do you mean
Jiujiang
should invest in this project?
Yes.
Jiujiang has large resorts
and shopping malls
in many areas.
I think
we can cooperate with them
with Jiujiang Property's
real estate assets.
We'll provide funding
and build offline stores,
and they'll select food products
and promote and publicize them.
Yixiu is very popular right now.
Are you sure
they'll cooperate with us?
They're in the Series C Round
of financing.
Considering their growth rate,
the financing
will be used
to expand their current business.
As for the offline brands,
they cannot make it
with their own funds.
If we cooperate with them,
we'll not only provide funds
but also solve the problem
of location selection.
It's a win-win situation.
After the Series C Round,
Yixiu will focus on going to market.
If we want to participate in it,
this is the best opportunity.
After that,
we'll cost ten times the price.
Yixiu's CEO Jiang Shiyan
and CBBC's branch leader Tang Yang
are very close.
If I talk to Yang Tang first,
we'll have a good chance of winning.
You've got a good plan.
The business model
and the path are both clear,
and it'll be very influential.
I think it'll work.
Just stick with the plan.
Okay, Ms. Wei.
Thanks.
The base is chicken soup.
I asked him to make dumplings and soup
separately.
Thanks.
Try it.
Mr. Cheng, leave it to me.
It's okay. I can wash the dishes.
No, no. Let me do it.
Let me do it.
Thanks.
No problem.
Is it good?
Very good.
I'll take you to the store.
It's even better.
However,
you owe me
four meals now.
Yes.
I owe you more and more meals,
but I'm starting to take it for granted.
Then I'm leaving.
I'll see you off.
I remember there was a time
when I went to Daxing'anling Prefecture
and lived in a mountain village,
but there was a blizzard,
and I was stuck there for a week.
There was no network
or cell phone signal.
During that week,
I didn't even know what was going on
outside the mountains.
After I left,
I realized
that all the messages
I missed in the week
didn't matter at all.
I had nothing to do with them.
Bye.
Why did he
come here?
Well...
Eat dumplings.
What about the hacker?
Anyway,
we've done everything we could.
We've sent a statement.
Whether they believe it or not
is not up to us.
So, what should we do now?
Now
I'm tired.
I'm going to sleep.
Thanks.
Who's this?
Why are you here?
I finished my work.
I knew you weren't sleeping,
so I came to see you.
Did you have dinner?
Yes,
but I only had a sandwich.
Only a sandwich?
It's not enough.
Are you hungry?
I can cook for you.
Cook for me?
Can you do that?
Don't look down on me.
It's not a big deal.
I can make
simple food.
Like instant noodles?
Of course I can do that.
I can even make more complicated food.
I can make dumplings
or something like that.
I'd like some small rice dumplings
with sweet fermented rice.
There are some
black sesame glutinous rice dumplings
in the fridge.
And the sweet fermented rice
hasn't expired.
I didn't know they were in the fridge.
Why do I feel
that you know my fridge
better than I do?
I just cleaned it in the morning
and threw away the expired ones.
What's this?
I went out in a hurry.
Maybe it got stained somehow.
Coffee?
Take it off. I'll wash it for you.
You don't have to.
It's okay. Not a big deal.
I'm going to do the laundry anyway.
With your clothes?
Why are you staring at
the washing machine?
I like to watch
our clothes
rolling around together.
♪Can't tell♪
♪Whether it's friendship or love♪
♪In the dark♪
♪You're my guiding star♪
♪It's becoming clear♪
♪My overwhelming emotions♪
What's wrong with this?
I think
we just spent too much time
doing laundry,
and it's overcooked.
We can only have
the sesame soup.
Was it long?
I don't think so.
♪I still can't forget the stars♪
♪Only want to travel around
the universe with you♪
♪Like twin stars in perfect harmony♪
♪Our meeting♪
♪Is a great miracle♪
♪We're meant to be together♪
♪Inseparable♪
♪When you care about me♪
♪Even if you're nagging♪
♪I'll bear it all in mind♪
Mr. Feng, this is
the consulting team of Liqin Consultant
hired by Ding Shen Capital.
- Hello.
- I'm Lisa.
I'm Feng Weiran.
This is the project leader,
Mr. Alex Song.
Song Jing?
The first two are samples.
We need to think carefully
about both the design plan
and the location.
Got it.
Go on with your work.
- Okay.
- Mr. Feng.
Why are you here?
Take a look.
The investment team is here.
Didn't you ask me to come at lunch?
Do you know
who the leader is?
Who?
Song...
Jing.
What are you looking at?
I'm not surprised.
They're here again,
those guys in dark suits
who eat the same takeout food
for every meal
and never leave our meeting room.
The cafeteria prepared lunch today.
Remember to come.
(Meeting Room)
I'm too busy.
As a co-founder,
you need to say hi to them.
I'm busy.
They made sweet and sour ribs
and Sichuan pepper chicken.
When?
12:00 p.m.
Okay.
Song Jing.
It's been a long time.
Jiang Shiyan,
it's really been a long time.
Alex,
are you guys
classmates?
I transferred to
Rongcheng First High School
in my senior year.
I had to come back to my hometown
(Project Director of Liqin Consultant)
for the college entrance examination,
(Song Jing)
so we three
were classmates for a semester.
Well, Mr. Jiang,
do you have any gossip
about Mr. Song's youth?
It's the senior year.
We spent all day
taking exams.
Time flew by so fast
as we took countless exams.
I remember we haven't seen each other
since we graduated
from high school, right?
That's not true.
In college, I went to your university
to visit...
visit a friend
and met you at the door
of the supermarket,
right?
Yes, I remember.
Liqin Consultant,
welcome and thank you.
We don't have much to offer,
but we have plenty of snacks.
Let me introduce them.
This is Xue Lei, our accountant.
- Hello.
- Zhang Le, the administrator.
- If you need anything, just ask them.
Get some fruit and coffee.
- Okay.
Well,
our cafeteria has made
some nice food for lunch.
I'll ask Zhang Le to send it to you.
- Okay. Thanks, Mr. Feng.
- Thanks, Mr. Feng.
My pleasure.
Go on with your work. We're leaving.
Okay.
- See you later.
- Okay.
(Meeting Room)
Do you think
(Tang Yang, Jiang Shiyan)
Song Jing knew
it was us
when he took over the case?
Why didn't he
tell us in advance?
Did he
(The consultant team came.)
want to surprise us?
It's more like a shock.
(Do you know who the leader is?)
That's right.
Listen,
Yang and he didn't end up well.
I'm pretty sure
it was his fault,
and he knows
we're close friends,
so I'm sure he has complicated feelings
towards us too.
Well,
do you think
we should tell Yang about him?
Forget it.
I don't think we should tell her.
Otherwise,
it'll remind her of the bad things.
Besides, they're
from two different worlds.
Liqin Consultant is based in Beijing.
He came here
only for a business trip.
When this is over,
he'll go back.
If we tell Yang,
it'll only bring trouble.
(The consultant team came.
Do you know who the leader is?)
This way.
Mr. Song, they've arrived.
What a feast.
I was going to have a salad.
Now I have to eat more.
It looks yummy.
Come on. Have a seat.
Have a seat.
Here, take a seat.
Let me introduce him.
This is Cheng Hui,
one of our co-founders
and the CTO.
Hello.
Well, let's eat.
It's just some
casual food.
- Suit yourself.
- Okay.
Eat more.
- Try this.
- Okay.
(Tang Yang)
(I'm in your office.)
Where are you guys?
You guys eat. I'm going downstairs.
Mr. Jiang, I'll come with you.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing. Don't worry,
Forget it. Let's eat.
Eat more. Don't waste food.
Why are you here?
Why am I here?
It's weird. Usually, you'd be
happy and surprised
to see me.
Why do you look
very nervous?
Did you make a mistake?
No.
The consulting team came,
but the leader is...
is Song Jing.
So what?
Are you afraid that he might
give you a hard time?
I don't think
you offended him before.
It's not like that. I'm not afraid. I...
Why are you here?
Cheng Hui told me
you were going to have
sweet and sour ribs
and Sichuan pepper chicken.
I still had some time,
so I came for a free lunch.
Is there a problem?
Of course not.
Let's go. There are many people today.
The cafeteria made lunch.
Let's go.
I think we were taking extra classes
during the summer.
Tang Yang, why are you here?
For the sweet and sore ribs
and the chicken.
Tang?
It... It's been a long time.
Yes. Song Jing, it's been a long time.
Take... Take a seat.
I'll get you a chair.
It's okay. No need.
I can sit here.
I'll sit here.
Then I'll move.
Are you working
in a bank?
Yes, in CBBC,
This is our uniform.
I need to go back to work later.
Yes.
Yang is the director
of CBBC Rongcheng Branch's
Credit Audit Division.
Deputy director.
Yes, deputy director.
The food looks really nice.
Let's eat.
Come on.
Eat more.
Don't worry about me.
Just eat.
Is coffee ready?
Yes.
- Let me take it.
- Be careful.
Okay.
Lanqing told me
she had a meal with you.
Yes, she came
with her mayor friend.
She also introduced
the brewery.
We need to work with different areas
for the Food Map project,
- so I invited them here
- Thanks.
to talk about it.
Thanks.
Well, do you like
the cafeteria's food?
It's good.
I think I can write in my report
that the most valuable thing about Yixiu
is their chef.
Mr. Song,
you're telling a bad joke again.
Tang.
Wipe it.
What?
Your mouth.
Mouth?
Oh, no need.
My boyfriend will help me.
Right?
Look at you.
He called your nickname from childhood,
and you think you're really a child.
Only the seniors would call me that.
I was surprised.
Cover it.
I'll put the tissue here.
What are you looking at?
Eat your food.
More rice for him.
It's so good.
Shiyan, you were so brave
and smart.
If I hadn't been married,
I would've said I was Yang's boyfriend.
He'd be pissed off.
Have you ever thought that maybe
Yang and I are really...
Best buddies forever.
You're such a good friend.
I've found that you two are closer
than we are.
Hello.
Did you check the email?
Check it and reply to me.
I just don't understand.
- What's wrong
- Okay.
with Song Jing?
(Tang Yang)
(Did we officially announce it)
(to the public?)
Tang!
That's so disgusting.
Yang was so clever,
or he would've found out
she's still single
- and thought
- (I think we just failed.)
she still can't get over him.
Shameless.
The sweet and sour ribs
are so good.
- What do you think?
- Really good.
Wish we could have it every day.
Alex.
This is the aging analysis
of the accounts receivable.
Alex?
Just send me a copy.
(Yu Minjia, Song Jing)
(I'm back in Rongcheng)
(for a project.)
(Do you have time for a meal?)
(Feng Weiran told me)
(what happened.)
(You're so clever.)
(Well, has Song Jing)
(ever reflected on his mistakes?)
Now he's trying
to be close to you.
What is wrong with him?
He's always like that,
feeling good about himself.
Whatever.
I wish I could be there.
If I were there,
I could've seen it
with my own eyes.
(But I have to say)
(Jiang Shiyan is a good friend)
(in the critical point.)
What did
Feng Weiran tell you?
Well, Feng Weiran
told me
Song Jing
still cared about you,
(and you immediately)
(pretended to be
Jiang Shiyan's girlfriend.)
(Jiang Shiyan was also smart.)
(He responded as your fake boyfriend)
and embarrassed Song Jing
in front of everyone.
Is that right?
It's...
not wrong.
That's right.
Not wrong?
It's the truth.
I think you did a good job.
(Mommy, come here.)
(Okay. I'm coming.)
(Okay. I need to go.)
(My son is going to sleep.)
(Okay?)
Okay. Bye.
(MU Plaza)
Ms. Sheng!
Ms. Sheng, I'm your fan.
Thanks.
Hello, Ms. Sheng,
I'm your fan!
You're gorgeous!
So pretty!
(Jiang Shiyan, Feng Weiran, Tang Yang)
(CBBC's coffee)
(is worse than ever.)
(I want to file a complaint
to the administrative department.)
(Moments, Sheng Nina)
(Fish or shrimp?)
(It's a question.)
Yes. Then
give me more details about this part.
Yes, and make sure
that our fresh foods
have long shelf lives.
No expired products.
- Okay.
- That's it.
Peng Si,
do we have any Thai lime sauce
we promoted last time?
Yes. Mr. Cheng, do you want it?
Get some for me.
- Okay.
- Is there any other deciduous food?
Dried fish. The crispy dried fish
is always one of the best sellers.
Okay. I'll take a few packs.
- Peng Si.
- Mr. Jiang.
Do we have more pour-over coffee
that we all liked last time?
I think so.
Mr. Jiang, do you want it?
I'll take a few boxes.
Pack them
and send them
to Ms. Tang in CBBC.
Okay.
Why are you smiling?
Nothing.
(Moments, Sheng Nina
Fish or shrimp? It's a question.)
(50 Minutes Ago, Cheng Hui)
I brought a bottle of sauce.
It suits both fish and shrimp well.
Mr. Zhou, do you mean
Jiujiang wants to invest in
Yixiu's Food Map project?
Yes.
Jiu Jiang
has business properties
all over the country.
Yixiu needs to open
offline food stores
for the Food Map,
which matches the resources
of Jiujiang.
We think
we can provide
stores and funds,
and Yixiu
will focus on branding,
product selection,
overall plans for publicity
and implementation.
We can integrate
offline and online resources.
Mr. Feng, are you interested?
I want to ask something.
Which cities
are Jiujiang's business properties
located in?
I can send you
the details,
including the locations, progress,
and the overall layout.
That'd be great.
We check it
and have a meeting.
- Okay.
- I'll tell you the results later.
Okay.
We don't have to decide on
the form of the investment now.
However, we're considering
setting up a joint venture with Yixiu.
We've got some plans
for this,
I'll make a memo
and send it to you,
okay?
No problem,
but
if it's a joint venture,
our board has to have a meeting
and talk about it.
I understand.
Your investors
in the previous rounds of financing
are also our long-term partners,
so I believe they'll
trust Jiujiang.
I've heard you're working on
the Series C Round.
If we can come up with
a cooperative package
at this point,
I believe it will benefit
your company's valuation.
♪Twinkle stars are shining,
lighting up the night sky♪
♪Every one of them
is talking to you in silence♪
I get it.
I get it!
♪Those lonely wanderers♪
♪And the interstellar adventurer♪
Closer.
I'm going to cut it.
Do it.
I'm really doing this.
Hurry up.
I'm really...
No, I can't.
You'll cut it.
- Do it yourself.
- You're up.
- Just do it.
- You'll do it.
- You cut it.
You cut it.
Never mind.
♪I understand the rules
of this chaotic world♪
♪Tried to play every role well♪
It's not ready.
♪I tried to satisfy everyone♪
♪Hid my sorrows and pains♪
♪But you'd understand me every time♪
(Rover No. 1)
♪You'd always be there cheering for me♪
♪Be brave♪
♪Be free♪
(Oort Cloud:)
(Made dumplings
with tom yum instant hotpot.)
(So delicious.)
♪That's the color of Van Gogh♪
♪I remember every tale
about the moon and the stars♪
♪They've lit up♪
♪The view along the way♪
♪Keep going♪
♪I know you'll always be there♪
I can feel
they're quite interested in
our proposal,
but the board will vote for
the establishment of the joint venture.
Voted by the board?
It's a good thing.
In that case, Yixiu's investors
will know we're going to
cooperate with them.
The investment circle
will find out very soon.
It will be more trustworthy
to let them talk about it
than doing it ourselves.
Ms. Wei,
this time, our goal...
At least 1.5 billion yuan.
Got it.
Come on.
- Cheers.
- Come on.
Cheers.
Sorry.
It feels so good.
So delicious.
It's good, right?
You know,
actually, I'm not sure
whether I should quit being an actress.
I thought it'd be fun,
but now
it seems to be much more complicated
than I expected.
I used to think
that by being an actress,
I can play different roles
and have different lives.
It must be interesting.
You know, most people
can only have
one life.
But actresses are different.
They can
experience different things.
However, sometimes, being an actress
can be very troublesome.
It seems like
everyone can judge you.
What clothes are you wearing?
Does it look good?
What haircut did you get?
Does it suit you?
Sometimes, I don't know
whether I should listen to them.
Come on. Have a shrimp.
Thanks.
Try the dipping sauce.
- Is it good?
- It's good.
If you change the sauce
to soy sauce and vinegar
in Cantonese style
or boil the shrimp
with beer,
it'll also be delicious.
It's up to you.
Sometimes,
you don't have to be
trapped by those labels.
You can eat whatever you like.
- Let's eat.
- Okay.
Try the food here.
Song Jing,
have you settled in Beijing?
Yes.
Liqin Consultant only has offices
in Beijing and Shanghai.
I remember your husband was in
the School of Economics and Management.
We were in the same grade.
Are you Guan Jingtang
and Ge Hui's
classmate?
And Tang Yang.
She was also their classmate.
Song Jing,
I remember...
Forget it. It's been many years.
I met Tang Yang
at Yixiu Found of Food the other day.
She's working
in...
a bank, right?
The deputy director
of CBBC Credit Audit Division.
She's amazing.
She's the youngest deputy director.
She's really impressive.
Is she
married now?
I don't think so. It seems she's been
single for many years.
I've heard her mom is very worried.
She sets up blind dates for her
every month.
Yes. When we had a reunion,
she was complaining
that her mother arranged
several blind dates for her
every day.
She was exhausted.
She's a successful woman.
I don't think she'll like
normal guys.
Isn't she
very close to Jiang Shiyan,
the CEO of Yixiu Found of Food?
A video of them
was once exposed.
Well, they're bros.
Jiang Shiyan
has a girlfriend.
It's that actress
Sheng Nina.
Really?
Of course.
Check out Yixiu's homepage.
Sheng Nina was in trouble,
but she was still on the homepage
of Yixiu.
What does it mean?
She's Mrs. Jiang.
Of course they didn't remove her.
- Mr. Chen.
- Thanks, Mr. Chen.
Tang Yang.
Tang Yang,
this is Song Jing.
He just transferred to our class.
Song Jing.
this is our deputy monitor
Tang Yang.
Hello.
Tang Yang,
take him to the classroom,
introduce him to everyone.
and arrange a seat for him.
I have a meeting
for the teaching and research group.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Okay, go back to the classroom.
Goodbye, Mr. Chen.
This way.
Is it heavy? I can help you.
It's okay. Don't worry.
Have you gotten your uniform?
You can get it
at the Academic Affairs Office
on the third floor of that building.
I'll only be here for a semester
to attend
the College Entrance Examination.
Most lessons
will be reviews
and mock exams.
I don't need a uniform.
♪When a beam of light♪
♪Falls gently on my shoulder♪
♪Guiding every step of the way♪
♪The wind sways my clothes♪
♪With trees rustling in sight♪
♪Even dreams have sprouted wings
to take flight♪
♪We've cried and laughed before♪
♪Yet you stayed by my side♪
♪With every turn I take♪
♪Your warmth remains sure♪
♪You said you'd join my adventure
in this vast world♪
♪Following the map
to grant my every small wish♪
♪Slowly healing every wound
I've ever bore♪
♪The seasons pass,
but your gentle touch soothes♪
♪The moments in my palm♪
♪You said you'd join my adventure
in this vast world♪
♪Following the map
to grant my every small wish♪
♪Slowly healing every wound
I've ever bore♪
♪The seasons pass,
but your gentle touch soothes♪
♪The moments in my palm♪
♪You said you'd join my adventure
in this vast world♪
♪Following the map
to grant my every small wish♪
♪Slowly healing every wound
I've ever bore♪
♪The seasons pass,
but your gentle touch soothes♪
♪The moments in my palm♪