♪The gentle breeze sweeps by♪
♪As the starlit sky shines bright♪
♪Our dreams glow with fiery light♪
♪In this world♪
♪We agree to take
the challenge together♪
♪Never looking back,
without letting us down♪
♪Stars fall into the endless ocean♪
♪We'll find the days gone by♪
♪Sharing joy alike♪
♪Standing strong through the strife♪
♪Vows, clear as day and bright♪
♪Every day, we laugh and bicker,
shout and fight♪
♪Running through the streets
and alleyways♪
♪Every time, you're there by my side♪
♪My shoulder's always there
to shield you from storms♪
♪If you cry and feel the sadness inside♪
♪I'll give it all to roam by your side♪
♪Like the closest friend in stride♪
♪But somehow, it feels more, undefined♪
♪Stars dream of returning to the sea♪
♪Fulfilling them,
like our promises alight♪
♪Riding on a white horse once more♪
♪Reappearing by your side♪
♪To be your guiding light♪
=You Are My Lover Friend=
=Episode 16=
=Reckless or Calm=
Deputy Director Tang.
Director Ying.
Why are you being so polite?
Director Ying?
You called me Deputy Director first.
Then...
I'll call you Tang Yang.
Miao.
Look how smart you are.
Hasn't Mr. Jiang arrived?
Is he coming?
Usually, Mr. Feng attends those events
on behalf of the company.
Mr. Feng seems to be busy,
so Mr. Jiang will come.
I haven't got a chance to meet him.
Can you please
introduce me to him today?
Of course. If Mr. Jiang is coming,
I'll let you guys know each other.
That would be great.
(WeChat, Now,
Jiang Shiyan: One Message Unread)
(Jiang Shiyan)
(I got stuck in a traffic jam
after the meeting.)
(I will arrive in a few minutes.)
Tang Yang.
Mr. Zhou.
Mr. Zhou?
Why are you so polite?
You're our client,
so I need to respect you.
I need to talk to some clients
over there.
Mr. Zhou
is also our partner.
Ms. Tang, please take care of him.
No problem. Go on with your work.
Take your time.
See you later.
I want to introduce you
to some friends.
Okay.
Good.
Director Gan's staff are all impressive.
They have a good teacher,
- right.
- Exactly.
Linlang,
how old are you?
I was born in 1996.
I didn't expect you
to be so young.
I thought
you just graduated from college.
With the help of Director Gan,
you'll have a bright future, right?
Absolutely.
Come on, to a bright future.
- Come on.
Okay.
Cheers.
Linlang,
thank Mr. Gan.
Mr. Guan and CBBC
are long-term partners.
You need to keep in touch
to deepen our partnership.
Please take care of Linlang.
No problem,
as long as Linlang doesn't mind.
Come on, cheers.
- Come on.
- Cheers.
- Finish it. Good.
That's inappropriate.
- Come on.
- Mr. Guan,
I can't drink anymore.
Mr. Guan really admires you.
You have to
finish it.
That's right.
Director Gan.
Sorry to interrupt you.
Linlang needs to help me
deal with some work.
I believe Director Gan
can take care of the guests.
Come on.
Director Gan, it seems
you still need to train your staff.
Here, Linlang.
Drink some orange juice to get sober.
You should go home.
I'll tell Mr. Gan
that you're not feeling well.
I'll call a taxi for you.
Thanks, Ms. Tang.
Linlang, listen,
no matter how sleepy you are,
you can't fall asleep on the way home,
okay?
Thanks, Ms. Tang.
Get in the car.
Tell me when you get home.
Goodbye, Ms. Tang.
Goodbye.
Mr. Jiang.
What a coincidence.
Are you waiting at the door
to welcome me?
Welcome you?
I didn't even know if you were coming.
So, have you been waiting for me?
I told you I was stuck
in a traffic jam.
Wait...
Waiting for you? I...
I...
This is so ridiculous.
Why would I wait for you?
Actually, it was
Ying Miao...
who asked about you a lot,
so I came out
to check it out.
Nice necklace.
Isn't it because I'm pretty?
It means I'm both sweet and cool.
I can be dressed in any style.
You know nothing.
You're Tang. Of course
[*Tang: Candy]
you're sweet.
You're also quite cool.
[*Cool: Homophone of his name Yan]
Why are you smiling?
You look weird.
You must be
up to no good and guilty.
Don't use that word, okay?
Then why are you smiling?
Mr. Jiang!
Mr. Jiang.
Right on time.
I recognized you from afar.
You're really here.
This is Mr. Ying.
This is Mr. Jiang.
Feng Weiran
talked about you a lot.
Thank you for giving Yixiu a chance
to cooperate with you.
I was in a rush last time.
I've wanted to talk with you
about our further cooperation.
No problem.
Ms. Tang.
President Zhou wants to see you.
Okay.
Take your time. I need to talk to them.
Okay. No problem.
Ms. Tang,
you told Linlang to go home.
It seems you have to
drink with us tonight.
Mr. Gan,
if you don't withdraw your hand,
my hand might slip
and accidentally
pour the wine
on your face.
Mr. Zhou is waiting for us.
Okay.
Distinguished leaders,
dear guests,
ladies and gentlemen,
- This way.
- good evening.
Welcome to...
Ms. Shen, I've watched
a lot of your lectures,
and I've been following
your legal awareness videos.
They're so educational.
Thanks.
Tang Yang,
where is Linlang?
A client just asked me about her.
We had a little situation.
I've told her to go home.
Is she drunk?
That little girl
has never seen anything like this.
She'd gotten drunk before we started.
Ms. Shen,
when I was in college,
my social ethics professor
recommended one of your lectures to me.
It was about
workplace harassment
and women's self-defense.
I learned a lot from it.
You mentioned
that many sexual assaults take place
after a woman drinks
with her bosses and clients.
I'm wondering
if you have time
to attend our discussion panel for women
and give us a lecture
about preventing workplace harassment.
No problem.
Indeed, many young girls
who just graduated from college
don't know how to refuse
the drinks from their male leaders
and prevent intentional physical contact.
Yes. That's great.
Well, I'll send you
the schedule after the meeting.
Okay.
Let's welcome
Ms. Shen and Ms. Tang
to draw the third prize for us.
There will be ten winners,
and each of them will get
a latest sweeping robot.
Let's welcome them.
Let's go.
You go first.
(Tang Yang, Branch Credit Audit Division,
CBBC Outstanding Employee of the Year)
(Shen Li,
Co-founder of Tiansheng Law Office)
Okay, Ms. Shen and Ms. Tang,
each of you will draw
five lucky winners for us.
Number 15.
Congratulations.
Number 76.
Number 83.
Number 56.
Number 8.
Congratulations.
Okay. Congratulations to you.
Let's find out who will be
the other five winners.
Number 82.
Number 39.
Number 5.
Number 71.
Number 182.
- Did you win?
- Okay.
- Congratulations to you.
- No?
Ms. Shen, Ms. Tang,
thank you for giving us
a good start.
Please go back to your seat
to take a break. Thanks.
(Let's welcome Zhou Zixing,)
(president)
(of CBBC Rongcheng Branch,)
(to help us draw)
(the biggest prize of tonight,)
(the grand price.)
(The winner will get a voucher)
(for four nights
at Six-star Qingcheng Resort.)
(As we know,)
(Qingcheng Resort)
(is located at the backside)
(of the 5A scenic area
Qingsecheng Mountains.)
(Everyone wants to win)
(the grand prize.)
(Let's welcome...)
Little kitten.
The more outstanding
a woman is,
the more a man wants to conquer her.
Mr. Gan, are you drunk?
In Credit Audit Division,
no one ever took over
a case from me
or
surpassed me
to get Outstanding Employee of the Year.
The more outstanding
and disobedient you are,
the more curious I am.
Do you think I'm afraid
to be your enemy?
For what?
Infighting in CBBC?
Deputy Director Tang,
do you want to lose the position?
Do you want other banks
to make fun of us?
Or
sexual harassment?
Are you uncomfortable
with the title of deputy director?
I just passed by
and brushed against you by accident.
Do you want to use this
to replace me?
I can take the risk.
Do you want to take the risk
too?
Threaten me?
You'll be sentenced to death for murder.
You can try and see if I dare.
After all, you'll die first.
Besides, this is a hotel
with cameras everywhere.
Okay.
Mr. Jiang.
(Elite Society)
Can you learn
to avoid hurting yourself
when beating someone else?
How could I notice that when I hit him?
I'm worried about crushed glass.
Tang.
Tang Yang.
Aunt Yi
always calls me Tang,
but it seems you never
did that before.
I want to tell you something.
Go ahead.
I called you bro
because you cross-dressed a male role
in The Merchant of Venice.
I thought it was funny.
Besides, do you remember
we used to spend time together
eating and doing homework?
Yes.
Because my mother
were always out.
Even if she was at home,
she would make
some weird food.
Therefore, Aunt Yi
would always ask you
to bring me some deciduous food.
Then they said
we were in a relationship.
I didn't want the teachers
to misunderstand us
or to get you into trouble,
so I called you bro.
Thanks.
Actually,
that wouldn't get me into trouble.
Back then, teachers
only cared about grades.
I always had good grades,
and your grades were improved.
All the teachers loved that.
I thought about it many years later.
Maybe I just didn't want
to be your burden.
After all, you could
raise the average
of the whole school,
whereas I might've
failed to get into a college...
if it weren't for your help.
You...
Aunt Yi and you
always say that,
but actually,
you couldn't keep up with others
in the first and second years
because you missed some remedial classes
and practices
when you had to help your mother
and had no time.
However, in the third year,
we didn't need to learn new stuff.
Everyone started to focus on exercises,
and you manage to keep up with them.
You're not a bad learner after all.
But you made me believe in myself.
Tang Yang.
I...
Hello, Mom.
- What's wrong?
Slow down. I can hear you.
Calm down. Take your time.
What?
How's that possible?
Okay.
I'm coming back right now.
Okay. I'm coming.
- Bye.
Well...
Let's go.
Come on.
First-aid kit.
Forget it!
(Jade Garden Property Management Center)
I said it was an accident.
Old women, you've lived for so long...
Old women?
Don't you dare hit me!
How could you call other old women?
So what?
How dare you blackmail me?
Sir, look.
They hit my head.
It really hurts.
You deserved it.
Don't you know what you've done?
Nasty trash.
I said it was an accident.
What accident?
Why did you take pictures?
Why did you
put your phone under her dress?
Do you know what this is?
It's indecent assault!
It's sexual harassment!
You insulted a woman, okay?
Indecent assault?
Harassment?
Come on, I'm a 20-year-old
handsome young man.
What about her?
She's just a middle-aged ugly woman.
Why would I harass her?
I'm not a psychopath!
Shut up!
Listen, don't try to blame the victim!
You're not only a psychopath
but a pervert!
Sir, the old woman insulted me!
I can defend myself
- by cursing her to die, right?
- Say that again!
Do you want a fight?
I'm scared, okay?
Hurry.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Come on.
Beat me. Come on!
Mom!
Mom, Mom, calm down.
- What happened?
Aunt Zhou and I
wanted to send some food to Tang
and saw
this pervert
taking pictures
of this girl
with his phone under her dress.
We caught him,
but he hit us
and asked us to pay compensation.
You saw it.
She was the one who hit me.
I didn't do anything.
You asked for it.
You gave her a cup.
Enough. Stop arguing with him.
We should call the police
and let them deal with it.
- Okay.
- What's the point?
There's no surveillance or evidence.
Yes, no surveillance.
Hello, I need to report
- How do you know?
- a suspected indecent assault
- or sexual harassment
- I get it.
- at Jade Garden Property Center.
- He must've done it before.
- Please come.
- The security cameras on the road
- have stopped working for a long time.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
- Yes.
So, there's no surveillance.
What's the point of calling the police?
Here's the thing. Well,
Room 301 in No. 2 Building,
the one that keeps pigeons,
has surveillance
in the dovecote.
We can ask them to give us
the footage.
I remember there are two cameras
at the south entrance.
They can also capture
the images of the corner.
Okay. We'll contact the owner.
- No problem.
- Okay.
Over there!
Are you still denying it?
Officers, I'm sorry!
I was out of my mind!
You can tell us at the police station.
You must be careful on the street.
Those perverts...
Thank you so much.
Thank you, officers.
If it weren't for you,
she would've suffered a lot
because she can't speak or call for help
when facing a pervert.
Thank you so much.
It's okay. We're neighbors.
It's not a big deal.
- Thank you.
- It's okay.
- Yes.
- As long as she's fine.
It's okay.
- Thanks.
- It's okay.
Here.
I always carry pepper spray.
Take this.
If you encounter a pervert,
use this to defend yourself.
Be careful! It's...
very spicy.
It's chili water.
Take it.
- Put it in your bag.
- Thanks.
It's okay.
If you have to walk alone at night,
choose the north entrance.
It's the main gate. It's safer.
- Thank you so much.
- Okay.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Okay. Goodbye.
- Bye.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Come on. Let's go home.
Luckily, we're fine.
If that man
had a knife...
was a desperado...
If he wanted to kill us,
how could two old ladies like us
defeat him?
We were too reckless.
Look,
you're family.
You threw a punch without hesitation,
whereas Jiang
remained calm.
He asked for the footage
and called the police.
Excellent work.
The pervert tried to hurt you.
You threw a punch first.
Yes. I was also reckless. I...
I must reflect on myself.
From now on, we must be smart
when helping others.
We can't resort to violence.
Oh no. Whatever happens,
we must stay calm
and come up with a plan.
Attack By Stratagem
in The Art of War is very useful.
"The highest form of generalship
is to balk the enemy's plans,"
that's what I'm talking about.
It means...
What's wrong?
The groceries we bought!
And the frozen food!
Wait!
Slow down.
Be careful.
Mr. Jiang, it seems you're
more mature and calm.
Wait. Why is your hand injured?
Is it because you hit someone?
Where are we going?
Ms. Wei is at the clubhouse.
It seems you know
my wife whereabouts
better than I do.
So, how do you know
there's surveillance at the dovecote?
I developed a habit
when I was living in Lancheng alone.
I don't walk on a road
without street lights or cameras
after 10:00 p.m.
I thought I was the only one doing this.
Then I found all my female colleagues
would do the same thing.
It seems
every single woman who lives alone
will become a great scout.
I was right.
About what?
You often called me
at 10:00 p.m.
when you were in Lancheng.
You would tell me
to work hard to survive the competition
or to rest well
and stay healthy.
I was wondering
if you were too scared
to walk alone at night.
Yes.
You used to go to sleep
at 5:00 or 6:00 p.m.
and get up at 1:00 or 2:00 a.m.,
but I forced you to go to sleep
at 1:00 or 2:00 a.m.
Cheng Hui told me it was hard for him
to get used to jet lag,
but it was never a problem
for me.
Tang,
where are the garbage bags?
In the closet.
The closet?
So, back then...
No. It's full of
your packages.
I'm coming.
Come on. Help me.
Why can't you find it?
They're in the closet.
At the bottom.
Look, it...
It's a mess. I can't find them.
Check it out.
- Mom, sit down.
- Where are they?
Did you run out of them?
Oh, I remember now. I bought it,
but I haven't unpacked it.
I remember I got a delivery.
Look how careless you are.
Listen,
you need to unpack the packages
once you get them
and put them in order,
- or you'll forget soon.
- Where are my scissors?
Now you've forgotten the scissors.
I put them right here.
Here.
- Let me do it.
- Here.
Listen,
when you get a package next time,
open it right away
and put it in order.
I've been busy,
so I forget to do it.
No matter how busy you are,
your house must be organized.
Don't embarrass me
in front of Mr. Jiang.
What? Jiang is our family.
Why are you embarrassed? Look at you.
- We're family.
- I got it. I got it.
I'm sorry, Ms. Zhou.
Be careful. Don't break it.
I...
Careful.
Look at you.
Remember to wash your hands.
I got it.
It's dirty.
Ms. Zhou, this is too much.
Look, a piece of cake.
One bag is enough.
First, it can prevent leakage.
Second,
you don't have to do it again.
Come on.
You're so smart.
It's easy to tell who can do housework
and who can't.
Can you please not be
so good at everything?
I want to save you some trouble.
You're making me look stupid.
I didn't finish my words.
Go ahead.
Tang, help me change the channel.
I can't figure it out.
Tang, hurry.
- Why isn't it working?
- I'll ask my driver
- to send them home.
- Tang, why isn't this working?
Be quick.
I'm coming.
What's wrong?
The controller is so advanced.
- How can we change channels?
- It's high-tech.
Aunt Yi, which channel?
Mr. Gan,
Ms. Wei
is still working.
You have to wait for a while.
What does she want?
Ms. Wei will come
after finishing her work.
Mr. Gan, would you like
something to eat?
Your uncle is Zhou Zixing.
You don't need her help.
There have been many men
around Wei Changqiu over the years.
However,
you're the youngest
and most handsome man.
I just can't figure out
what you want?
Mr. Gan, you're injured.
Can you still go to work tomorrow?
Tang.
The corns are cooked.
You just need to add some water
and put them in the microwave
for five minutes.
Okay.
I also bought some ready-to-eat carrots.
Just wash them before eating.
- Okay.
- Besides,
I prepared
some steamed breads.
Did you see them?
The shelf life is three months,
but once opened,
they'll be stale in three days.
Therefore, two breads a day,
and you'll finish all six of them
in three days.
I got it.
Thank you, Ms. Zhou,
you're the best.
Aunt Yi,
Jiang Shiyan,
thank you for today.
Stop pretending to be polite.
Aunt Zhou,
Mom,
I'm calling the driver
to send you home, okay?
I... I'll come back later.
Yes. I need to talk to Jiang Shiyan
about some stuff.
Yes.
Just suit yourself.
We'll watch TV.
We'll have nothing to do
when we get home.
Yes. Look at your father.
He plays chess
in the garden every night
and won't come back until 10:00 p.m.
Move.
Come on. I want to talk to you.
I'll get some snacks for you.
She has many good snacks.
Here, so many snacks.
Come, let's see what she's got.
This one.
I recommend this.
Try this.
The duck necks are so good.
Other brands
are only spicy.
These are spicy and yummy.
Try this.
Gloves.
No need. I've got this.
Try this. Do you like it?
- It's so good.
- Where can I buy it?
Tang, where did you buy it?
- What?
- Well,
where did you get the duck necks?
Jiang Shiyan brought it.
You can find it on Yixiu Found of Food.
Yixiu.
Why didn't you
bring some home?
- Well...
- It's okay. We've got plenty of them.
There are duck stomachs too.
Every time I come here,
I don't want to go back
after eating the snacks.
You can take them all later.
By the way,
our class monitor gave me a flash drive.
There are some videos
of our classmates in high school.
He wanted to make a short video
and play it at our class reunion.
Then I'll help you
to upload them to the server.
Okay.
Someone can edit it.
When's the reunion?
Why didn't I know it?
We haven't set a date.
The monitor said he needed
to count the people first.
We talked about it
at the reunion last time.
You didn't come.
Look at you.
Mr. Gan.
I can handle it.
Just go back.
Okay.
Have you finished?
It looks like
he's royal to you,
but he might be
up to something else.
He wants money,
just like you back then.
He...
He's not that simple.
Don't overestimate yourself.
He might set you up
one day.
Mind your own business first.
You'll be destroyed by women
sooner or later.
You already got me a long time ago.
I've done so much dirty work for you.
If it's exposed,
none of us can get away.
We're married.
We can never
get rid of each other.
Each of us
should have some fun.
What do you want from me?
Linjiang project
has a funding gap.
Zhou Mo
is working on CBBC.
I need you to figure out
something else for me.
When?
Within three months.
I've uploaded them.
I'll send it to you when it's finished,
- Okay.
- and you can send it to him.
I should've hidden the snacks.
Why are they still eating?
When will they stop?
Eating snacks is not a big deal.
It's holding things up.
I'll buy her plenty of snacks
so that she can eat them at home.
I remember
there was a time
when I couldn't finish
my computer homework
because I was busy
preparing for competitions,
and you'd finish my homework every time.
I've been wondering
why the teacher never found out
our assignments
were exactly the same.
Who told you they were the same?
I wrote different answers.
I never knew.
- Tang.
- So, you...
I'll sleep here tonight.
The cultural center said
the reading conference
at the library on Saturday
was rescheduled
to tomorrow.
It's more convenient to get there
from your apartment.
Convenient?
Jiang Shiyan,
when are we going back?
It's almost 10:00 p.m.
I'm a little tired.
Mom, you can stay.
Then I'm leaving.
Okay. Let's go.
I'll pack some snacks for you.
No need. Jiang Shiyan
will buy them for me.
Just take some home.
No need. We're leaving.
Okay.
I'll leave this to you.
- Remember to clean...
- No problem.
Then I won't walk you out.
- Let's go.
- Be safe.
- I'll get my shoes.
- Tang.
I'm going to take a shower.
Okay, I'll see them off.
We're leaving.
Goodbye, Tang.
Okay.
Goodbye, aunt.
Be safe.
(Is there anything else)
(Tang Yang)
(that I don't know?)
(Let me think about it.)
(Jiang Shiyan)
(You're doing this on purpose.)
(Tang Yang)
(You don't need to recall them.)
(Jiang Shiyan)
(Nothing important.)
(Tell me.)
(Tang Yang)
Stop playing with your phone.
Take a shower.
Okay, I'm coming.
Look at you.
You've worked all day.
Aren't you tired?
What?
- What's wrong?
- Why is it gone?
What's gone?
I just bought it. Why is it gone?
The orders.
Did you buy it on Yixiu?
Yes.
I saw Sheng Nina's streaming
and bought it immediately.
I also told Ms. Zhou about it.
That's right. Why haven't I received it?
Your platform is too slow.
I'll file a complaint.
What's wrong?
Stop playing. Take a shower.
Okay, I got it.
Hurry up.
Look what you did.
You only put it in the cart.
You never paid, okay?
Even if you're my mother,
they won't send you the product
(Instant Sweet Corns)
until you pay for it.
(Shopping Cart)
Did you do this?
Why would I do that?
(Tang Yang: Tell me.)
(WeChat, Now,
Jiang Shiyan: One Message Unread)
There's a coupon.
Jiang Shiyan. Jiang Shiyan,
how can I use the coupon?
Mom, stop doing it.
I'll buy it for you tomorrow.
Mr. Liu, drop me off
when you leave the overpass.
Send my mother home.
Where are you going?
Company.
Why are you
going to the company at this hour?
Buy duck necks for you.
You don't have to buy them now.
(It seems there are many things
I want to tell you,)
(but I don't know how to start.)
(Back then, I always felt
that you were nice to me.)
(I didn't know how to pay it back.)
(Jiang Shiyan)
(Actually...)
(Have you arrived?)
(Can I go to your place now?)
(Is it a little bit late?)
(Tang Yang)
(I'm going out now.)
(Can you go downstairs?)
What did you tell Aunt Yi?
I said I had to work.
Then go to the company.
Goodbye, then.
Don't go.
I won't.
Why did you
suddenly come back?
You asked me to tell you,
so I wanted to tell you.
But I hate typing,
so...
I'm here.
Then...
tell me.
I just remembered I forgot to tell you
something important.
Well...
I founded Yixiu Found of Food
because of you.
Where is Yang?
She's in the principal's office.
Is she okay?
Maybe they're rewarding her
for winning another competition.
I really envy the good students.
They can be praised every day.
Shiyan.
Is Yang crying?
Move.
Yang.
Shiyan.
Why are you crying so hard?
Did the principal scold you?
No.
Did someone bully you?
I'll beat him up.
What did the principal do?
My eyes hurt so badly.
When I went to the office,
a mosquito bit me on the leg.
I borrowed some cooling balm,
but I forgot I'd used it
and rubbed my eyes,
and I couldn't stop crying.
I can't open my eyes.
- Oh my god.
- It hurts.
Come on. Let me blow on your eyes.
Let me help you.
No, No.
- Are you feeling better?
- No. You blew too hard. No.
Stop blowing. Take her to wash her eyes.
Okay. Let's go.
Come on.
No, wait!
- Which way?
- Over there.
The restroom is over there.
How can we get into the ladies restroom?
Let's go to the water supply room.
Wait.
The wind is so strong!
Block the wind. Hang in there.
The... The wind!
- Are you better now?
- No!
Not at all!
Hang in there.
(History)
(Relations of Production,
Managerial Approaches)
Please turn to page 64.
With the rapid growth of productivity,
social structures
and the world situation...
Jiang Shiyan.
(Geography)
Is this a history textbook?
Where is it?
My textbook
was lost.
(History)
♪When a beam of light♪
♪Falls gently on my shoulder♪
♪Guiding every step of the way♪
♪The wind sways my clothes♪
♪With trees rustling in sight♪
♪Even dreams have sprouted wings
to take flight♪
♪We've cried and laughed before♪
♪Yet you stayed by my side♪
♪With every turn I take♪
♪Your warmth remains sure♪
♪You said you'd join my adventure
in this vast world♪
♪Following the map
to grant my every small wish♪
♪Slowly healing every wound
I've ever bore♪
♪The seasons pass,
but your gentle touch soothes♪
♪The moments in my palm♪
♪You said you'd join my adventure
in this vast world♪
♪Following the map
to grant my every small wish♪
♪Slowly healing every wound
I've ever bore♪
♪The seasons pass,
but your gentle touch soothes♪
♪The moments in my palm♪
♪You said you'd join my adventure
in this vast world♪
♪Following the map
to grant my every small wish♪
♪Slowly healing every wound
I've ever bore♪
♪The seasons pass,
but your gentle touch soothes♪
♪The moments in my palm♪