♪The gentle breeze sweeps by♪
♪As the starlit sky shines bright♪
♪Our dreams glow with fiery light♪
♪In this world♪
♪We agree to take
the challenge together♪
♪Never looking back,
without letting us down♪
♪Stars fall into the endless ocean♪
♪We'll find the days gone by♪
♪Sharing joy alike♪
♪Standing strong through the strife♪
♪Vows, clear as day and bright♪
♪Every day, we laugh and bicker,
shout and fight♪
♪Running through the streets
and alleyways♪
♪Every time, you're there by my side♪
♪My shoulder's always there
to shield you from storms♪
♪If you cry and feel the sadness inside♪
♪I'll give it all to roam by your side♪
♪Like the closest friend in stride♪
♪But somehow, it feels more, undefined♪
♪Stars dream of returning to the sea♪
♪Fulfilling them,
like our promises alight♪
♪Riding on a white horse once more♪
♪Reappearing by your side♪
♪To be your guiding light♪
=You Are My Lover Friend=
=Episode 18=
=Moonlight and Sunshine=
Only water?
Have some beer. Come on.
Okay. Thanks.
Cold Harbin Beer?
Of course.
Come on.
Jiang Shiyan.
You're a big boss now.
I wouldn't dare
drink the beer you serve.
Don't be ridiculous.
Ask Feng Weiran.
As co-founders,
we've never gotten
any dividends.
You work at a giant technology company,
so stop making fun of me.
Your job is much better than mine.
Feng Weiran.
Come on.
Everyone else is here
except for you two.
What took you so long?
Did you make a deal to come together?
No. I saw Sun Xiao
- by chance
- Have a seat.
when I passed the subway station,
so I picked her up.
Come on. Have a seat.
Boss.
It seems no one
is going to give a speech
at the conference today.
My mute spell
has finally worked.
You should thank me for using magic.
Why are you two always talking about
some weird
secret codes?
Jiang Shiyan.
You're a super busy boss right now.
How can you have time to come?
Stop mocking me.
Ask Yang about it.
I never missed any parties
or badminton games
on weekends.
That's true.
You only hang out with Yang.
You guys...
- Have some tea.
- Jiang Shiyan.
Stop talking.
Bring us some fruit.
Okay.
Yes,
my boss.
Boss, what about our salary?
Of course I'll pay your salary.
Don't you believe me?
Hello.
- It's been a long time.
- Have a seat.
Hello, hello. Have a seat.
Did you have a reunion
in Spring Festival?
I was traveling,
so I couldn't come.
Yes, we wanted
to have the reunion
on the monitor's birthday.
However, Cheng Xinyi suddenly came back,
and Feng Weiran said
she'd only stay for a few days.
She told him in advance
to gather everyone.
Wait. Why did Cheng Xinyi
call Feng Weiran?
She used to be
Jiang Shiyan's girlfriend,
right, Tang yang?
I didn't know that.
Aren't you best buddies
without any secrets?
Stop spoiling the fun.
When Chang Xinyi and Jiang Shiyan
were together,
Yang wasn't there.
She went to another city.
Besides, they were only together
for a short time.
A few months later,
Cheng Xinyi decided
to study abroad.
When she left,
Yang wasn't in Rongcheng.
Well...
There was a time
when my mother went to Beijing
for training
and left me with my father.
He was in Gansu at that time,
so I stayed there
for a while,
and we traveled to Dunhuang
for a few days.
When I came back,
I found Chang Xinyi had left.
Well, Jiang Shiyan must've told you
they were together.
Oh, he did.
He did.
It's not like that. I...
It's been too long,
and I didn't pay attention
to these things,
so I forgot he told me.
Then do you think
his first kiss
was also with Chang Xinyi?
Absolutely.
Yes.
To be honest,
there was a rumor in the class
that you and Jiang Shiyan were together.
However, he started to call you bro,
so we realized
that you were
best buddies.
It's brotherhood.
You haven't changed at all
over the ten years.
- Yes.
- To be honest,
if I have such a good male friend,
it won't matter
whether I have a boyfriend or not.
After all,
this friend can help you
whenever you need him,
and you won't be alone
when you're old.
That's not necessarily true.
After all, friendship
and love
are two different things.
They're both busy with work
and don't have time for a relationship.
When one of them
finds the other half,
no one will know
if they can still be friends,
especially for Jiang Shiyan.
Ruili.
I just... I'll talk to him for a minute.
I didn't see you.
It's been a long time.
- I heard you've been
- Over the years...
working on
robotic software development, right?
Yes.
All my long-term partners
are big robotics developers
in the country.
- Really?
- Yes.
I was introducing
hardware and software integration.
Really?
That's great.
I heard it's a fast-growing
and profitable market.
Not at all.
Just make a living.
Congratulations. It's impressive.
What are you so happy about?
Here, have some fruit.
Thank you so much.
Give it to me.
- Okay.
- Go get the call.
I need to take this.
Hello?
Have some fruit.
- Thanks.
- I think it's close.
What's close?
Many girls will fall for
an outstanding rich bachelor
like Jiang Shiyan, right?
Feng Weiran, you're his best friend.
You know him well.
Tell us how many girls he has.
Don't ask me.
I know nothing.
Why are you covering for him?
Feng Weiran,
did you also
like Chang Xinyi back then?
Everyone except me
pursued Chang Xinyi,
right?
You were the craziest pursuer.
However,
I think
Chang Xinyi and Jiang Shiyan
are a better match.
Feng Weiran,
Chang Xinyi called me
and said she went to the wrong door
and got lost.
Let's pick her up.
See?
That's what I'm talking about.
Chang Xinyi and Jiang Shiyan
are meant to be together.
She couldn't get through to Feng Weiran,
so she called me instead.
- Let's go.
- Stop making excuses.
I don't even have her WeChat.
You must've been
talking to each other a lot.
- Enough. No more gossip.
- We'll pick her up.
Something must be wrong.
Chang Xinyi is special.
They both went to pick her up.
They can't wait
to see their dream lover in high school.
I told her to wait by the lake.
She might fall into the water.
Hurry.
Maybe
- They have a thing.
- they're getting back together.
What did she tell you on the phone?
She said she came back
for her family this time.
She'll go back after meeting us.
Later this year,
she'll stay in the country for a while,
and we can hang out more often.
See? I told you
you're special
to her.
Stop talking nonsense.
If you say it again,
I'll tell Jiang Yanan.
What did I do?
You're acting like I made a mistake.
Chang Xinyi.
Good to see you.
Me too.
Come on, cheers.
Thank you, Mr. Feng.
Here's to you.
Take your time.
Guys, I want to say something.
Everyone is busy,
so it's hard to get together.
Enjoy yourselves today,
and I'll pay for everything.
Come on. Cheers!
- Okay.
- Cheers!
Thanks, Mr. Feng.
Cheers. Cheers.
- Come on.
- Cheers.
Tell me when you get home.
Goodbye. See you.
Be careful.
- Goodbye.
- Be safe.
- Watch out.
- Slow down.
Yang.
My driver is here. Let me send you home.
- It's okay.
- You can park your car here
and pick it up tomorrow morning.
I'll call a designated driver.
Shiyan.
Send Xinyi back.
She lives in the InterContinental Hotel.
You can send her back
on your way home.
I'll send Yang after Xinyi gets off.
It's okay. I'll take a cab.
I'm going to work tomorrow,
so I need my car.
I'll call a designated driver.
Don't worry.
I can pick you up tomorrow morning.
Stop.
What are you doing?
Why are you making it a big deal?
Stop wasting our time.
Just tell Wang
to drive Yang's car and send her back.
That's it.
If you're worried,
I'll go with them
and send her home, okay?
- Well...
- Okay.
It's a deal.
Wang will drive my car
to send me and Feng Weiran.
You'll send Xinyi back. That's it.
- Let's go.
- Let's go. Come on.
Xinyi, see you next time.
Can you do that?
Send her back. Tell me when you arrive.
(Leisure House)
My driver
will come in a while.
Wait a minute.
I'll talk to Feng Weiran later
about the thing
you told me.
Okay, I'll send the information
to you later.
Okay.
Thank you for believing in our company.
Of course I do.
After all,
you're Jiang Shiyan.
Yang,
something's wrong with you.
What's wrong?
I knew it right away
that you wanted
Jiang Shiyan and Chang Xinyi
to get back
together.
How... How did you know?
Come on.
We're best friends,
and I'm smart.
I knew what you meant
once I heard it,
so I insisted on
sending you back.
You would never get in their car
and interrupt their romantic moments.
I...
I'll tell you another top secret.
Say it.
Do you know
Jiang Shiyan was the first person
Chang Xinyi called when she came back?
No.
Do you know why Chang Xinyi
called Jiang Shiyan.
No, I don't.
Listen,
Chang Xinyi
has been working on
overseas listing of domestic companies
all these years,
so she contacted Jiang Shiyan
to ask him if Yixiu needs
to list overseas.
To be honest,
I don't think
Yixiu is ready
for going listed.
However, Jiang Xinyi said
many of her clients
are quite interested in
investing us.
She can help us
with the C round of financing.
Do you know
what it means
if Chang Xinyi takes over
Yixiu's case?
- No.
- It means
she'll spend a lot of time
staying here.
She'll go on business trips
have meetings, and visit clients
with Jiang Shiyan.
They'll spend a lot of time together.
It'll be perfect for them
to get back together.
What a wonderful love story.
It's amazing.
It's not amazing at all.
What did you say?
I said you're smart.
I'm so happy.
This is great.
Not great at all.
(Leisure House)
Is Tang Yang
still your friend and bro?
Okay.
She's my bro.
I didn't know she could drink so much.
I heard
she's doing credit work in a bank.
It's said that credit officers
have to drink a lot every day.
It seems
she's made a lot of progress.
Can she drink a lot?
Normal, she can only drink
two cans of beer.
But she drank a lot today,
at least five for six cans.
Really?
Get in.
Mr. Liu,
please send Ms. Chang
to the InterContinental Hotel.
Okay.
Sorry, I just remembered
I have something important to do.
I can't send you.
You're going to see Tang Yang, right?
Yes.
We've been talking about
my company,
so I didn't notice she drank so much.
I'm a little worried.
I need to check her out.
I really envy Tang Yang.
I used to,
and I still do.
Rest early.
Good night.
Bye.
(Hello. The door is unlocked.)
(The door is locked.)
Why are you here?
Since we're all here.
Let's keep drinking.
Come on.
Here's to you.
You...
Why are you
so upset?
If you're sad, just tell us,
understand?
What's the point of
sulking here?
You're not candid
or cute at all.
You're on your own.
No one cares about you.
Here's to you.
What are waiting for?
You didn't drink with me all night.
You only wanted to talk to her, right?
Drink...
Forget it. You can't drink.
You need to send her back.
I'll drink alone.
(Calling Tang Yang)
(Tang Yang, Awaiting response...)
(Calling Feng Weiran)
(Sorry,)
The subscriber you dialed
cannot be connected for the moment...
Yang.
You're here.
We've been waiting for you.
Hurry. Come in.
Yes.
We need a fourth player.
Yang, are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm drinking with my bros.
You're right on time.
After all, we're best buddies.
How about this?
I'll finish
this one first.
- Stop drinking. Stop.
- I'll finish it.
I'll finish it.
So cool.
Tang Yang.
You're drunk.
I'll get you some honey water.
- Wait a minute.
- Who's drunk?
Who?
No one is drunk.
You're not drunk.
Well, did you finish it?
How dare you judge me?
Did you drink it?
I'll drink. Come on.
Who told you to drink?
That's the only thing
that can make me happy.
Do you have to steal it from me?
Big bad bear!
I'll hit you. I'll hit you.
- Don't hit it. Stop.
- Tonight...
- I'm Mr. Bad Bear.
- Let me hit it.
Hit me. Your hand will get hurt.
Tang Yang!
Your hand is swollen.
How about this?
Let's have some honey water together,
okay?
Okay, I'll get you up.
Don't touch me.
I'll stop.
Let's hold hands
and have some honey water together,
okay?
Let's go.
Be careful.
The kitchen is over there.
Do you think I don't know
where the kitchen is?
Thank you, sir.
You're so kind.
It's cold outside. Let's get in.
Look.
What's this?
What?
Look at your Moonlight.
[*Moonlight: Crush hidden in your heart]
I don't have a Moonlight.
You do.
I don't.
- You do.
- I don't.
You do.
I really don't.
You do! Chang Xinyi is your Moonlight.
You do.
Okay.
I... I do.
If you say so.
Okay? It's up to you
whether I have a Moonlight or not,
okay?
I know you have a Moonlight.
Why didn't you admit it?
You have a Moonlight.
I really don't,
but you said I had one.
If she's your Moonlight,
what am I?
She's not my Moonlight,
but you're my Little Sunshine.
Little Sunshine?
Little Sunshine.
Come with me.
Be careful.
Come on.
Yang, what...?
Little Sunshine!
Technically speaking,
it's an overhead light.
Little Sunshine is the bathroom heater
we used to put in our bathroom.
It's a big lightbulb.
It's bright and warm.
So, you're calling me overhead light.
That's not what I mean.
- You're a bathroom heater.
- Bathroom heater?
No, you're Little Sunshine.
- You...
- I...
Shiyan,
why are you here?
Aren't you supposed to be
sending Xinyi back?
Be careful.
Tang Yang, are you mad at me
because you heard
I was going to
send Xinyi back?
But it was you who told me to do it.
She asked you to pick her up,
so you should
send her back.
Are you jealous?
Shut up. I'm not.
I'm not.
Then why are you mad?
I'm not mad. I...
I'm so happy right now.
(Mute Spell)
Okay.
Stop talking.
(Mute Spell)
I think
you look like
that ungrateful Jiang Shiyan.
Look, look at this.
The eyes,
the nose, and the mouth...
(Mute Spell)
It's yellow.
It's red again.
So, you got angry
when you heard I was going to
pick Chang Xinyi up.
I was angry.
Do you hate
that ungrateful Jiang Shiyan?
I do.
You don't want him
to talk to any other girls,
do you?
I can't answer.
The spell is broken.
Actually, I...
Your lips
are pink and soft.
It must feel nice when kissing.
Did you kiss Chang Xinyi?
How many times?
- I...
- Stop.
I can't accept it.
No.
A real hero
has the guts to face the cruel reality.
It's okay. Just tell me.
I can handle it.
Actually, I can't!
I'm a coward!
I can't accept it.
I don't want to know the answer.
I didn't kiss her.
We only had a meal once.
And I went shopping with her once
for the stuff
she needed for going abroad.
I really didn't kiss her.
I didn't even hold her hands.
You didn't?
Then let's kiss.
Just one kiss,
but you can't tell anyone.
Shiyan, how dare you?
I treat you like my bro.
How dare you try to kiss me?
I'll kill you!
♪Can't tell♪
♪Whether it's friendship or love♪
Forget it.
I can't take advantage of you.
♪You're my guiding star♪
♪It's becoming clear♪
♪My overwhelming emotions♪
♪Can you chase away my fear♪
♪Listen to all my desperation♪
♪You said♪
♪I've got your back from now on♪
♪Fried skewers, tofu skin,
and ice cream♪
♪It's raining,
we're a mess under the umbrella♪
♪Leaving traces of love with you♪
♪I still can't forget the stars♪
♪Only want to travel around
the universe with you♪
Shiyan?
You're awake.
Have breakfast.
What time is it? Why did you come here
early in the morning to make breakfast?
What do you mean I came early?
I didn't leave.
What?
You blacked out.
I...
I wasn't that drunk, was I?
I remember we ate dinner
and drank a lot,
and...
Then...
Feng Weiran was going to send me home,
and you were going to
send Chang Xinyi home, right?
Yes. Then you came back,
and I came and drank with you.
Do you remember what you said to me?
I didn't go too far,
did I?
I'm always rational.
You were quite rational.
Drink the honey water.
Shiyan!
My elephant bush came back to life.
Did you do that?
I didn't.
It was water with some kind of elixir
and came back to life.
Elixir?
What a miracle.
It came back to life overnight.
Let me see what you're making.
I made brown rice porridge,
spring rolls, pumpkin cakes,
and steamed breads.
You know me best.
I dreamed about
having brown rice porridge,
and here it is.
You're magical.
Go get cleaned up
I'll get the door.
Yang!
What are you doing here?
I... Where's Feng Weiran?
What happened?
Yang!
What's wrong?
It's okay. Don't cry.
What happened?
I don't know.
It's okay. It's okay.
Don't cry.
It's still early.
You haven't had breakfast, right?
Have some porridge.
Did you put sugar in it?
I thought you didn't eat sugar.
Yes.
Thanks.
It's so early. What happened?
Did you have a fight with Feng Weiran?
How's that possible?
Feng Weiran wouldn't dare to talk back
when she scolds him.
Feng Weiran kicked me out.
How's that possible?
No way.
Yes. He'll go on a business trip, right?
He's going on a business trip!
How could he kick me out?
Calm down.
He's got appointments
with three investment organizations
in Shenzhen this week.
He's catching an early flight now.
Should I find him?
I'll walk you out.
I'll see him off.
Calm down.
I'll be right back.
Okay. Wait a minute.
Thank you
for last night.
Well,
what will you do to thank me?
What do you want?
How about the way
you did it last night?
What did I do last night?
You hair.
Goodbye. Talk to you later.
Then...
Be safe on the road.
You...
Be safe when you go back inside.
Press the button.
Well,
remember to eat the porridge, and...
Jiang Yanan will be fine.
I'm leaving.
I'm going in.
Goodbye.
You're at the airport?
What did you do early in the morning?
I was going to...
You ruined everything.
What?
Sell your house?
Call me when you finished
the security check.
Feng Weiran went out
to catch a flight this morning,
and the housing agency called.
That's when you realized
he was going to sell
the two-bedroom apartment
at Rongcheng City Town.
Yes.
So, the agency called
because they needed to take someone
to see the apartment,
but Feng Weiran wasn't home,
so they wanted you to open the door.
Yes.
You're angry
because he decided
to sell the apartment
without asking for your opinion first.
However,
he thinks it's a great deal
to sell it and buy another apartment
in downtown.
Wrong.
It's not about a great deal or not.
It's our first apartment
and first home
we bought it when we got married.
I told him it meant a lot to us,
but he said
it was not profitable
and could only waste
our housing purchase quota.
Yes, I understand
what he meant,
but he should've told me
when he decided to sell it, right?
It's definitely his fault.
How could he not tell me
about selling the apartment?
Wait. I'll take this.
Don't.
It's Feng Weiran.
(Call, Feng Weiran)
It's really him.
I don't want to hear his voice.
I hung up. I won't answer it.
But I...
Don't!
It's Jiang Shiyan.
Jiang Shi...
(Call, Jiang Shiyan)
It's really him.
He wants to persuade me!
Then...
Okay. I hung up.
I won't answer it either.
On my way here,
I was thinking...
I shouldn't have become
a housewife when I was so young, right?
I should've learned from you.
Look at you two.
If Jiang Shiyan is going to
sell his apartment,
he'll ask for your opinion, right?
And you'll do the same
when you want to sell your apartment.
Why didn't Feng Weiran
ask for my opinion?
We're a married couple.
Are you a couple?
No.
But you can't deny everything.
You've been good
so far, right?
You're sweet and cheesy.
You're the perfect couple.
You only had a fight once in a while.
No.
We never fight.
We don't have time.
He's been so busy.
He doesn't have a choice, does he?
As you know, their company
is preparing for the C Round...
Wait a minute.
C Round?
I never heard of it.
Okay.
As the CEO and CFO,
he'll be
the most stressed person
when preparing for
the financing.
You get it,
right?
Besides, Jiang Shiyan told me
he's going to meet
a couple of big investors this time.
It's very stressful
and important,
right?
Okay.
Yes.
He doesn't even tell me
about his work now.
No. Yanan, that's not
what I meant.
Yang, don't persuade me.
I've made up my mind.
I'm not coming back.
I'll live here for a few days.
Live...
Okay. No problem.
But what about Qi?
He happened to go
to his grandmother's house.
Any more porridge?
Yes. Over there.
- I'll have more.
- Okay.
You've finished eating, right?
I'll finish it.
Hello.
Is Jiang Yanan still there?
Yes.
Yang!
Look!
So happy.
Is she still angry?
I don't think
she's angry at all.
On the contrary, she looks
so happy right now.
She said she was happy
to be single again.
She doesn't need to pick up her son
and send him to remedial classes
or read three story books
every night
and go to bed at 9:00 p.m.
She can go to sleep whenever she wants
and eat as many snacks as she wants.
I'll ask Feng Weiran tomorrow
if he can come back.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Are we broke?
What?
Cheng Hui...
Do you know how to speak properly?
If not, just shut up.
I just talked to Yunhe and Dingshen
about two funds,
and they were very interested.
They're even talking about
who's going to lead the investment.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
We won't be broke,
but why are you still unhappy?
I made a deal with some friends
to drive to the Arctic Circle together.
If we're broke, I can start my journey.
Jiang Shiyan,
I strongly suggest
you kick Cheng Hui out of the board.
I agree.
By the way,
I've set up the framework
for the cooperation platform
you talked about.
Check this out.
For real?
When will you release it?
Send me the timetable
and the introduction.
I'll add them to the file
for the meeting this afternoon.
You're quite efficient.
It's a direct
resource placement platform
for enterprises
and brands.
With this platform,
they can directly contact
influencers
and channels.
By the way, you can invite us
to a video conference in the afternoon,
and Cheng Hui
will introduce the features
and the framework.
I think the investors
will see the platform's potential
in business cooperation in the future.
Got it.
So, why are you staring at each other?
What happened?
My wife is angry at me.
She won't come home.
She's living with Yang.
I'm in another city
and can't come back.
I can't persuade her.
She's been sticking with Yang
like an octopus.
I haven't even gotten a chance
to have a meal with her.
Why don't you
bring Mrs. Feng too?
Or do you want to spend time
with Yang alone?
She's the one who wants
to occupy Yang
and exclude me.
Shiyan.
Shiyan!
Have a seat.
I'll serve the dishes.
Let me help you.
- Stop singing.
- Why did you kick me?
Watermelon juice.
It's hot. Do you want some?
I can't. I can't drink it today.
- I'll get a warm drink.
- Okay.
So cool.
Food is here.
It's too hot,
so I didn't use fire.
I only made some cold dishes.
Why did you suddenly
invite us to a meal?
The magazine paid me
this month.
Really? How much?
(Eight) hundred yuan.
That's a lot.
I heard
you were learning bartending in a bar.
I was working on
a special column of Bars in Rongcheng
at City Magazine,
so I went to a few bars with them
and learn some skills
from the bartenders.
I made Watermelon Mojito today.
Let's try it.
Only this little?
- I...
- Is this alcohol?
I made a whole bottle.
It's going to be
the most important year of your life.
The college entrance examination
was three years ago.
Get sober, okay?
What should we do?
What can I do?
She's drunk. I...
I can't persuade
or hit her.
Yang.
I'm begging you.
After the exam,
I returned all the physics I learned
to my teacher.
All my knowledge
is gone.
Yang,
I'm an art student.
I don't study physics.
Why are you laughing?
It's all because of your Mojito.
What should we do?
By the way, why would she bring
a physics paper?
She tutors in summer vacations.
Well...
She's got math, physics,
and chemistry papers.
Hurry up.
Okay.
One mistake, ten push-ups.
Okay. No problem.
You win.
I'll do push-ups right now, okay?
Come on.
Look. I'm doing it.
Keep an eye on him. Hurry.
Watch him.
Come on.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
She's like Ms. Zhou, isn't she?
Great!
- I really...
- Wait. Wait a minute.
Get Yang on the couch.
- Let's go.
- Is she okay?
- Come on.
- Let's go.
She's heavy.
Face! Face!
♪When a beam of light♪
♪Falls gently on my shoulder♪
♪Guiding every step of the way♪
♪The wind sways my clothes♪
♪With trees rustling in sight♪
♪Even dreams have sprouted wings
to take flight♪
♪We've cried and laughed before♪
♪Yet you stayed by my side♪
♪With every turn I take♪
♪Your warmth remains sure♪
♪You said you'd join my adventure
in this vast world♪
♪Following the map
to grant my every small wish♪
♪Slowly healing every wound
I've ever bore♪
♪The seasons pass,
but your gentle touch soothes♪
♪The moments in my palm♪
♪You said you'd join my adventure
in this vast world♪
♪Following the map
to grant my every small wish♪
♪Slowly healing every wound
I've ever bore♪
♪The seasons pass,
but your gentle touch soothes♪
♪The moments in my palm♪
♪You said you'd join my adventure
in this vast world♪
♪Following the map
to grant my every small wish♪
♪Slowly healing every wound
I've ever bore♪
♪The seasons pass,
but your gentle touch soothes♪
♪The moments in my palm♪