[English subtitles are available]
Do you think I can't find you
if you hide?
I just need some time.
What?
Instead of going to Harvard,
you're hiding in this small countryside.
What time do you need?
Does that make sense?
You loser.
Are you going let this chance go to waste in such an important time on impulse?
Go pack your things.
I'm not acting on impulse.
What?
After seeing you,
I've made up my mind further.
I quit.
Law school.
You punk.
You're not going to let go?
I didn't get hit
because I couldn't stop it all this while.
What?
I don't want to be interfered by you anymore.
From now on, I will be living my own life,
doing what I want to do.
Please stay out of my life.
Wooshik.
Bro will be fine, right?
I'm so worried I'm going to die.
That's right.
How would you know how I feel?
The atmosphere was so scary yesterday.
I can't stand it anymore.
Bro! Are you in there?
What's all this?
Brother!
Brother.
You're here.
What's all this?
The friend I met yesterday sent me the equipment.
They arrived this morning.
All of these?
Yes.
I said I'd do it so he sent it to me right away.
Wow.
So you're going to start music again?
Yes.
Good luck.
Your father
will understand in the future.
Bro!
Is there anything I can help with?
Well...
Just tell me.
I'll do my best to help you.
Oh. There is one thing.
Yes?
What is it?
I can't focus if you're here.
Bye.
You're too much.
Am I really that annoying?
You said you'd help me with anything.
That's true, but...
Go ahead.
I'll call you when I'm done.
Bro!
You didn't even say goodbye properly.
How heartless.
I don't have any appetite.
Son.
You've eaten a whole bowl of rice.
Even if I don't have an appetite, I should eat up.
What kind of nonsense is that?
I'm saying this because I feel empty.
Son...
Are you going crazy? I'm scared.
I'm already crazy.
Eat more if you're crazy.
Okay?
I'm going to eat more anyway.
Okay, let's start with the soup.
Yul, I miss you so much.
Bro, have you been well?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Isn't it heavy?
This is nothing. It's not heavy at all.
Yechan, I'm the one who finds it heavy.
Move it quickly.
Okay.
I thought my arm was going to break.
Bro,
I think my heart is going to break.
Lovesickness is scary.
Be quiet, Dongshik.
Dongshik, be quiet.
I'll just peek at your brother's hair and come out.
Okay?
I won't get in bro's way.
I'll just take a peek and come out.
Be quiet.
What's going on?
Bro?
Bro!
Are you okay?
You're not a normal stubborn.
You look so pale. Why aren't you going to the hospital?
I didn't sleep for a few days. What's there to go to the hospital for?
You're not eating either, are you?
Look at your skinny frame.
Are you an idiot?
Can't you eat and sleep?
Yechan, are you mad?
No, I'm not mad.
I'm just speechless.
Really?
Do you know how shocked I was when I saw you fainted there?
If I really listened to you and didn't come to see you, what would have happened?
You're really mad.
I'm not mad!
Seriously.
You're the only one who worries about me.
I'm glad you know.
Bro.
Can you take back telling me to go home?
Okay?
I know I'd be a hindrance to your work,
but I really...
Just like a TV,
I will be just be here quietly.
Just leave me at home.
TV?
Yes. Just take me as a TV.
I can't not see you.
It's about 60 inches, right?
What?
If you're a TV.
Does that mean I can stay here?
Yes.
Then why make say something so difficult to understand?
I almost couldn't understand.
Why are you laughing?
Seriously.
You know you're handsome when you smile.
At times like this...
Bro!
Let's eat first.
Thank you.
Giving a bracelet
means this person means a lot to me.
What?
That's what it means.
Hang in there, bro!
No!
I like you.
Bro.
Keep making music.
Okay?
Bro, please continue.
Bro!
What happened?
I'm done.
Whoa. It's been hard on you!
Congratulations, bro!
It's all thanks to you.
When did I...
I didn't do anything.
Thank you so much.
Come on. Do you want to see my heart explode?
Bro!
Can't you play that song for me?
What?
Can't you play it for me?
Whoa! Bro!
This song is really great.
This song will be a hit.
You don’t know the latest music, do you?
Of course I know.
I listen to the recent top 100 songs.
Yechan.
What?
Give me your arm.
Why?
What? You're giving me this?
You want me to do something so childish by myself?
This...
Then this is a couple bracelet with you?
Well...
Something like that...
Are we a couple?
You gave me a bracelet.
I...
From now on,
you're very important to me.
Couple?
Dongshik, let's eat.
Hello?
Hey.
What's with this song?
It's not your style.
Why? What's wrong?
You don't like it?
No.
I like it so much.
Hey, Seonyul, what's wrong with you? Did something good happen?
The song is exploding with sweetness.
Really?
Everyone in the company is going crazy. Everyone wants to see you immediately.
Let's finish the rest in Seoul. Okay?
What?
I found a studio for you.
In Seoul?
Yes. You just have to come. You know what I mean right?
We'll talk about the details when we meet.
When do I have to go?
Dongshik.
Will Yechan be okay
if I go to Seoul?
So nice.
The weather is nice too.
Aren't you riding too slowly?
Hey!
Hurry up.
Oh!
You're faster than I thought.
I'm going ahead.
You go first. I'll catch up.
Follow me.
That's cool.
Hurry up.
We just have to go this way.
Be careful.
This is it.
I've always wanted to show it to you.
Bro!
Isn't the scenery amazing?
Come down quickly.
The water is cold and nice.
Oh!
The 60-inch TV fell into the water.
What?
Are you going to continue treating me like a TV?
I'm sorry.
Do you want to see how strong TV is?
I said I'm sorry.
It's too late.
Wait!
Wait.
Wait. Wait.
What?
Gosh.
Wow.
It's suddenly raining.
It's a nice rain, though.
You're right.
I...
want to play with you every day.
Right?
Yes.
I had fun too.
Yechan.
-Right... -Bro!
Hm?
Can you
grant me a wish?
Before you go to Seoul.
Did you know?
No, how did you know?
Dongshik told me.
Dongshik.
Will Yechan be okay
if I go to Seoul?
Yechan, what's your wish?
Hold on.
What are you doing?
Pick it up!
Hello.
You're right next to me. What are you doing?
Look at your phone. Hurry.
Okay.
What did you do today?
It's been a while since I slept in.
I came to the stream.
What else?
Ah.
I saw a 60-inch TV swimming.
Seriously?
Goodness.
You told me to look at my phone.
This is practice.
Practice for when we are apart.
In this way,
we can see each other's face
even when we are far apart.
Bro.
Just go to Seoul.
Write lots of great songs there.
When you go to Seoul,
call me every day.
That's my wish.
Is it too much if it's every day?
Once every two days?
Or once every three days?
Bro!
Are you busy?
No.
Not at all.
I wrote a song today. Do you want to listen?
No.
Listen.
I put Dongshik's voice in.
It's been a month since he left.
We video call every day.
Dongshik looks like he got fatter.
I told you not to feed too much.
Come on.
It's just looking a little fatter on screen.
Yechan, have you eaten?
Yes.
I had two bowls.
Wait.
You don't have any appetite, do you?
It's all because you're not here.
Eat three bowls for dinner.
Okay.
What about the farm? Is it okay?
Though I'm looking at him, I'm still missing him.
Your dialect sounds weird.
I finally understand what the lyrics mean.
Sometimes,
when I miss you too much,
I want to rush to Seoul right away.
My God! What's wrong with you, Village Head Ma?
-You rascal. -I'm an adult after all.
I will be strong
and support bro's dream.
I miss you, Yul.
Dongshik, you miss Yul too, right?
My eyes are so swollen.
[Yul]
Is he busy?
What is he doing to be so busy?
Is that Yul?
Bro!
I really missed you.
I'm home.
I missed you too.
Strongly,
all the wait is worth it.