[English subtitles are available]
What are you doing?
I'm making a wish upon the meteor.
Making a wish?
I remember you don't believe
astrologers' interpretations of celestial events.
Why are you being so superstitious now?
It's not a superstition. It's about hope.
Hope?
People in my times made wishes upon a meteor
not because they believed meteors would make their wishes come true
but because meteors were rare.
The act of wishing upon a meteor represents the belief that miracles can happen.
Miracles can happen?
Then let me make wishes upon the meteor.
I hope the war will end soon,
and there will be no starvation in the world.
I also hope everyone is born equal
so that my mother
won't be looked down upon because of her family background.
What is this?
It's a meteor.
I believe your wishes
will come true someday.
Is this for me?
Yes.
It's done.
I can't believe it.
I have a house now.
I can't believe
you got a mortgage that will take you thirty years to pay off
and bought a house in such a remote area.
Jin Xia, are you going to build a resort in the suburb?
Congratulations.
You're a mortgage slave now.
Thank you.
But it doesn't matter.
My house is so big.
I can rent a room to someone
and use the rent the tenant pays to pay for the mortgage.
I'm not that worried about the mortgage.
I'm more worried that with the house,
you'll gradually stay away from city life.
Your house is more than 50 kilometers away from the city.
It's a bit far,
but I have a car.
Most of the time, I work at home.
Making clothes
and working on my designs.
I don't have to go to the company every day.
Besides, if there's something urgent I need to deal with at the company,
I'll stay and sleep at the company for a couple days.
It's not safe for a girl to live alone now.
If something bad happens to you,
I won't be able to come to help you quickly.
The house is located in a seaside town where residents there are nice.
You don't have to worry about me.
Well, that's not true.
Are you okay?
It's you.
I've finally found you.
What should I do?
No.
Though I don't know if you're a ghost or not,
it would be unkind of me
if I just leave you here.
You win.
What should I do?
Got it.
Wait for me. Be good.
Your legs.
You must be very tall.
I've given you all my quilts.
You should feel warm enough.
You'll be fine, right?
Smells good.
Where am I?
The ghost.
The meteor.
Was it my dream?
It's you.
I've finally found you.
Why did it happen on the first day after I moved in?
I'm so tired, Yellow.
Why am I on the bed?
All my quilts were...
Darn it.
That ghost saved me
and covered me with this quilt.
Fine.
I should be nice to him.
Smells good.
Morning.
I made you breakfast.
Time was limited so I just made a simple one.
Just make do with it.
Thank you for what you did last night.
You're welcome.
Without you,
I would have become a ghost like you.
Is the food cooked by a ghost really edible?
Take a look at these.
What are they?
They're the draft design and the quotation. I've got them ready.
I thought they wouldn't be ready until next week.
Actually, I got them ready long ago.
I didn't tell you because I didn't want you to feel suspicious.
But now...
I see.
You're a scheming ghost.
Are you going to make a historical drama here?
Why do you want to decorate the house this way?
[Total Renovation Fee: 2,000,000 RMB]
200,000 RMB?
That is too much.
Do you have a cheaper plan
of a decoration with a modern style?
Miss Jin, it's not 200,000.
It's 2 million.
[Total Renovation Fee: 2,000,000 RMB]
One, two, three, four, five...Seven digits.
Two million?
Are you kidding me?
I'm not.
Taiping is so beautiful.
To renovate it,
you must use top-class materials and hire the best decorators.
You want me to spend so much money
renovating this shabby house?
I didn't even spend so much buying it.
Taiping is not a shabby house.
It just hasn't been renovated for a long time.
Its beauty remains.
It's definitely a shabby and cheap house.
Why do you think
I bought a house in this remote area?
You bought it because you like the peace and tranquility of the suburb.
The house is near the sea and faces the sun.
It's a pleasure to live here.
I bought this house because I'm afraid I'll
have no money for the food and shelter when I'm old.
Let me tell you.
Women in my family
will all live a long life.
My grandma is 80 years old.
She's very healthy now.
I'll probably live a long life, too.
And it's very likely that nobody will marry me.
I'll have to live alone when I'm old.
This house
gives me protection and a sense of security.
Now I can keep making money
and save it to pay off the mortgage.
After I retire,
in my own yard,
I'll grow vegetables and raise chickens.
It's good to be self-sufficient.
Nobody will marry you?
But with your appearance and talent,
you'll be chased by men introduced by matchmakers.
You've been away from the real world for too long.
Do you know how high the divorce rate is
for people born in the 1990s in this year's census report?
It's 49.3 percent.
Do you know what it means?
It means almost half of the married couples
got divorced.
So?
Getting married is like a gamble with a 50-50 chance of winning.
Instead of trying to get married, I'd rather buy a house.
Instead of expecting others to bring me happiness,
I'd rather rely on myself.
I don't agree with you,
but I understand.
Miss, what was your original budget?
What budget?
The budget for renovating the house.
50,000 RMB.
50,000 RMB?
That's too little for my Taiping.
It's not your Taiping.
I bought this house.
I've been living here for over a thousand years.
It's understandable that I hope to spend more renovating it.
It's understandable.
But I won't increase the budget.
50,000 RMB.
That's too little.
The bathroom can only be a bath module.
Isn't that good?
Taiping shouldn't be made
into a cookie-cutter condo.
How can you say it's cookie-cutter?
It's the beauty of minimalism.
Here, take a look.
This kind of ancient bathroom is old-fashioned.
Nobody likes it.
Nobody uses this kind of large carved bathtub nowadays.
It's old-fashioned?
The classical design is always the most beautiful.
Miss Jin.
You're a designer.
Your understanding of beauty is too shallow.
I'm afraid you won't be a good designer.
Shallow?
At the company, I have to overwork.
At home, I get criticized by a ghost.
Sorry about my words.
I need to go to the real estate agency.
Why?
I'm selling the house.
I'll find you a buyer
who would like to spend 2 million decorating the house.
I'm leaving.
What's wrong?
I feel a little dizzy.
Have a good rest.
We'll talk later.
What's going on? The withered tree comes to life again?
Yesterday it was...
Forget it.
Whoever encounters this strange happening,
will need some time to understand it.
She didn't eat a bite.
It's been so long since I got along with someone last time.
I should be careful with my attitude from now on.
What happened?
My car!
Oh, no.
How could it be hit by the meteor?
Can I claim for the loss on my insurance?
Forget it. I'll deal with it when I get back.
Ms. Jin.
Who are you?
Did you call the police and say there was a peeper in your house?
You're the officer from yesterday.
Yes, what a coincidence.
You began to patrol so early.
No.
My house is next to yours.
Your car...
You live here?
Ms. Chen is...
My mom.
Oh.
Hello.
By the way,
I went home too late last night.
So I didn't bother you.
Have you solved the problem?
What problem?
Well,
about that ghost.
Oh, that thing.
Actually, I had a nightmare.
It was a vivid nightmare.
I made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. I'm glad you're fine.
But you should be more careful
since you're a girl who lives alone.
Can I have your WeChat?
Yes.
If you need my help,
you can call me anytime.
Officer, what's your name?
My name is Ding Yanhai.
But I'm not a police officer yet.
I'm a student at the police academy.
I'll graduate in a year.
Now I'm an intern auxiliary officer.
Oh, I see.
Officer Ding, you're so hard-working and responsible.
You'll be a good cop in the future.
Thank you.
We're neighbors.
Just call me Ding.
I'll call you Jin Xia.
No problem, Officer Ding.
Sorry, Ding.
I have something else to do. I should go now.
Let's talk later.
Okay, go ahead.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
[You Shu Housing Agency]
Are you sure you want to sell it?
[You Shu Real Estate Company]
Yes.
But didn't you buy the house not long ago?
Is it difficult to sell it?
Miss Jin.
I remember you were quite satisfied with this house.
It took you a lot of time and effort to get the mortgage
and buy the house.
Why are you selling it?
Because...
Wait. I cannot say it's a haunted house.
He won't believe it.
Even if he believes it,
it's even harder to get the haunted house sold.
Because I'm going to work in Paris soon.
I won't be able to live in that house anymore.
Besides,
I'll need lots of money to cover my expenses abroad.
That's a bit tricky.
How about this?
I'll post your house on my website.
Maybe you'll be lucky
that a buyer would like to pay the full price to buy the house.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[You Shu Real Estate Company]
Bye.
Hello, Xiaochuan.
Can I sleep at your place tonight?
It's a long story.
I'll talk to you in person later.
Bye.
What I said is true.
So you mean
you met a handsome ghost
who is good at cooking
and very gentle.
He offered to make a plan for decorating your house for free.
So you were excited.
No, you were scared.
So you wanted to run away.
When you were running away,
a meteor fell from the sky.
And it almost hit you.
At the critical moment,
he jumped,
broke that meteor with magic,
and saved you.
Bingo.
But my car got hit by the meteor.
Baby.
Is it possible that you watched too many dramas
and thought too much? You can't be so lucky.
How would such a good thing
happen to you?
First of all, I don't know why
you think it was a good thing
that I met a ghost and was almost killed my a meteor.
Second,
what do you mean by saying I can't be that lucky?
It was the first day after you moved into that old house.
I guess it was because you were not used to the new place and had a nightmare.
That was impossible.
The ghost talked with me this morning.
What did you talk about?
About renovating the house.
Unbelievable.
It's so romantic.
Romantic?
He saved your life first
and then decided to build a home of love with you.
Isn't it romantic?
Is it because I didn't say it clearly
or because there is something with you?
I'm telling you a horror story.
But you think it is a love story between a ghost and a person.
You are thinking too much.
He didn't do anything to you.
Instead, he saved you.
He may be a ghost, but he is a good ghost.
He may be an alien like Do Min-joon.
Aliens can be bad.
Have you watched the Alien films?
The movies you like
are so different from those I like.
It's not important.
Let's stop chatting.
I came to ask you to help me.
Can you give me
some useful advice?
Useful advice?
As you said,
it's no use calling the police.
It's no use selling the house.
How about
you do everything he asks you to do?
I'd rather find a ghost hunter to deal with him.
It's late.
Are you going back home now?
My teacher will be back in two days.
I've only finished half of the designs.
My drawing board and my materials
are all at home.
The designs I finished are also at home.
My goodness, Jin Xia.
If I can't finish my work,
I won't get paid.
If I can't get paid, I won't have money to pay the mortgage.
If I can't pay off the mortgage,
my life
will be ruined.
Then go back.
I should get my draft designs and come back?
Let's go.
Wait, it'll be at night when we arrive.
I'm busy tomorrow.
You either go home with me tonight
or go home on your own tomorrow.
No.
Xiaochuan, you can't leave me alone.
You are my best friend.
Please, go with me.
Go with me.
Jin Xia.
You're embarrassing yourself.
Let's go.
Okay.
Let me get changed.
We've arrived. I'm so nervous.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Wait.
What's wrong?
Didn't you say
your car had been hit by the meteor?
Yes.
The roof of the car was damaged. I saw it.
What happened?
Good question.
In my yard,
these is a pit caused by that meteor.
The pit must still be there.
When did the light get fixed?
Yesterday it was...
What?
Nothing. Lower your voice.
What's that sound?
What sound?
Didn't you hear it?
I heard nothing, but I can feel you're heavy.
Let's go home first.
You open the door.
I don't know the password.
Where is the pit?
Where is that pit?
Where is that pit as big as an adult?
What a big pit.
The car is not damaged and there's no pit.
Was everything just my illusion?
It's fine. If you're ill, go see a doctor.
Let's go into the room.
I see nobody.
You scared me.
He's here. I'm not lying.
He's this tall.
Tell me.
Why did you trick me into coming here?
I'm not lying.
This is his decoration plan.
A luxurious haunted room.
It's all true.
Welcome home.
You're so handsome.
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
It's not true that ghosts are afraid of millet.
The millet cannot hurt him.
Let's try with dog blood.
No. He's so handsome.
He is a...
Miss Jin.
How many more times do I have to repeat?
I'm not a ghost.
The light was flashing just now.
That's because, first,
the wires are aging.
Second, when I'm emotional,
my spiritual energy overflows and it disturbs the electrical current.
Just turn the light off and turn it on again.
That makes you more like a ghost.
When you're fighting,
you're like a couple.
Are you okay? He's a ghost.
He said he was not a ghost.
You believe him?
If he said so...
Miss Jin.
After you left today,
I thought about what you said.
You're willing to leave?
No.
I would like to
pay the mortgage with you.
What?
I'll pay the mortgage with you.
Of course, the house is still yours.
I'll also pay
for the renovation.
Is that okay?
Okay, okay.
What are you doing?
This is such a good offer.
Why are you hesitating?
He'll pay half of the mortgage.
He'll also pay for the renovation.
Accept his offer.
Even if you don't,
I can't leave.
You asked me why I stayed here before.
I didn't tell you the truth.
It was because I didn't want to scare you.
Actually, I'm not just staying here and waiting for someone.
I stay here
because this is the only place where I can collect spiritual energy.
What is spiritual energy?
In short,
by collecting spiritual energy which is the energy in nature,
I'll gain life energy.
Gain life energy?
That makes you more like a ghost.
It's hard to explain.
But I am indeed trapped here.
Poor thing.
Let him stay.
Accept his offer.
What offer?
You're so kind.
How about I sell this house to you?
Okay, I'll buy the house.
I disagree.
He disagrees.
Why?
Because Miss Jin,
I think
you're the one I've been waiting for.
Is this your draft design?
Yes.
Sorry I took it without telling you.
Wait a moment.
These are meteor-like gemstone earrings.
They belong to me.
Although I don't remember where they came from,
I think
it has something to do with the person I've been waiting for.
The earrings you drew
are quite similar to them.
They're antiques.
This...
This must be a coincidence.
Coincidence?
They're too similar.
Yes, they're almost the same.
Come on, tell us.
How did you get the inspiration for this design?
Inspiration?
I remember last night,
I smelled the scent of Chinese medicine.
And then I got the inspiration.
The smell of Chinese medicine?
What kind of Chinese medicine's smell could give you inspiration?
The smell had multiple layers.
And it also smelled like mint.
Mint?
Is this it?
I think so.
This sachet was made by me and no one else knows how to make it.
It has been with me for many years.
It can refresh people
and help people remember what happened in the past.
Why are you wearing this?
To help me remember my past.
Your past?
I see.
The smell of it
helped you remember your previous life
so you could draw this pair of earrings.
So you're the one he's been waiting for.
Stop joking.
I remember you don't believe anything about ghosts.
Now you believe in reincarnation?
I got it.
He saw my draft
and made a pair of earrings
according to the draft.
You want to fool me?
I...
Why does he need to fool you?
What can he get from you?
Your money?
He is going to pay half of your mortgage.
Your love?
He's out of your league.
Miss Jin, I'm not a liar.
You may think the earring thing is a coincidence.
But there's one thing that is by no means a coincidence.
What is it?
The meteor.
That day, the meteor fell from the sky.
At that time, I didn't have enough spiritual energy
to stop the meteor.
But somehow,
I got charged more spiritual energy
because of you.
Got charged?
Do you remember that day,
we accidentally
got very close to each other?
How close?
Because you helped me get charged spiritual energy,
I regained my long-lost extraordinary energy
and stopped the meteor.
Regained your extraordinary energy?
Before that,
due to a lack of spiritual energy,
my extraordinary energy had almost disappeared.
I only had some basic energies left.
After I met you,
I regained my high-level extraordinary energy.
This can't be a coincidence.
So romantic.
It's like
you're his power bank.
It's more like
my energy was absorbed by him.
Ghosts in movies all did that.
Miss Jin, I will never hurt you.
If you're really the person I've been waiting for,
I will also take care of you, protect you,
and try my best to fulfill all your wishes.
Please trust me.
Let's call it a day.
I need time to digest it.
Let's talk tomorrow.
Sir.
Which room do you live in?
I'm scared to sleep alone.
Can you protect me? Let's sleep in the same room.
You can sleep in my room.
Wait.
Bye.
It hasn't sprouted for decades.
Will it wither again soon?
When did the light get fixed?
-What?
-Nothing.
She's back.
I knew you would come back.
Ouch! I was so excited that I forgot to use magic to go through the wall.
Didn't you hear it?
I heard nothing, but I can feel you're heavy.
Let's go home first.
You open the door.