Hello, subscribers.
It's a wonderful morning.
It's so cold right now.
The weather has definitely gotten
much colder since my last video.
It's freezing.
Can you guys see my breath? Maybe not.
Ta-da!
Wow.
What a view, right?
It's too cold right now,
so I'll quickly get ready to head down.
See you guys in a bit.
All righty, let's start packing.
All right.
I'm all packed up now.
Let's make our way down together.
Mt. Chowol is known for its rough terrain,
so not many hikers come here.
That means it's quiet,
so you can get a good night's sleep.
If you come here, I suggest that you bring
at least one mini carton of soju.
What was that?
Hold on, guys.
Guys, there's a dog here.
Can you see it?
That scared me.
What is that?
What was that dog eating?
A body?
Hello?
I'm on Mt. Chowol right now.
There's a dead body here.
No, it's a dead human body!
KARMA
When was the last time
I ever felt this way?
My life has been quite eventful,
but I've never felt
such a great sense of accomplishment.
I remember snorting at a friend
who said men make money
to get the women they want.
I finally get it now.
CHAPTER 2
THE MAN WHO DISPOSED OF THE BODY
Hi, babe. Sorry I'm late.
You're earlier than I expected.
You're cold. Take a seat.
I was almost here,
but the traffic just outside was terrible.
I had the taxi driver pull over
and walked here.
The traffic's bad because it's Friday.
You must be so tired.
I looked this place up. It's super famous.
I made the reservation two months ago.
The head chef is actually French,
and the restaurant is Michelin-starred.
Nice, so it's the place to be.
So, what did you order?
I was waiting for you to get here
so we can order what you like.
You still don't know what I like?
I thought I should ask you,
just to be sure.
Your face is red because you're flustered.
Is it really?
Yeah, it's cute.
"Cute"? Come on, stop it.
-I'm going to the ladies' room.
-Of course.
-Please hurry.
-Yes, sir.
Where to next?
There's a good dessert place nearby.
I saw it on TV recently and made a note.
Why? Don't you feel like something sweet?
Right now,
I'm in the mood for something else.
What?
Gosh, seriously.
Come here.
I want to spend the night with you.
But it's Friday night.
I wonder if they'd have rooms available.
Let's go somewhere quiet.
It'll be romantic, just the two of us.
Sure, sounds good.
Get in.
Careful.
What do you think?
-Isn't it nice and quiet here?
-Yes.
Who'd expect to find a lodge
in such a remote area?
How did you find it?
I've been here before.
You've been here?
Why?
Well, I came hiking with my friends
to Mt. Chowol and stayed the night here.
You know I like hiking.
My gosh, you're so timid.
Ta-da!
A friend brought back
this delicious wine from France.
I brought a bottle
so we could have it together.
If I drink,
we'll probably have to sleep here tonight.
Tomorrow's Saturday anyway.
You're not working tomorrow, are you?
No, I'm not, but…
What's with you?
Are you going to keep ruining the mood?
You want to just do it sober?
No, that's not what I meant.
I'm on this medication.
I took it earlier.
For three hours, I can't--
One glass can't hurt.
What? When?
Seriously.
All right, then.
I'll leave now.
What?
What is it?
Did something happen?
I have to go somewhere now.
Now?
Where? It's past midnight.
My close friend's father passed away.
Really?
It's so annoying
after coming all this way.
But your friend's father passed away.
You should be there.
I wonder if I can find
a designated driver at this time.
It's late, and we're in the middle
of nowhere, so I doubt it.
But I drank,
so I probably shouldn't drive.
Fine. I'll just get myself a taxi.
It stopped raining, so it should be fine.
Just go back to bed.
No.
It's late, so I doubt we'll run into cops.
I'll drive you to the funeral home.
Let's go.
I'M ON MY WAY NOW
Texting your friends?
Yeah. It is urgent,
so I'm texting everyone to let them know.
Sorry it's such a rough night.
You must be tired.
You should've slept more. It's my fault.
It's fine.
It's better to go before traffic.
I'm sorry I snapped at you earlier.
Don't worry about it.
Your friend's father passed…
You're just kind.
You snapped because you're too kind.
Thanks, babe.
By the way, it was really nice.
It's been a while since I came.
Really? I guess
taking the herbal medicine paid off.
You're adorable.
Oh dear, looks like someone's sleepy.
I'll wake you up.
Hold on, Yu-jeong.
Don't you want to?
I think this guy down here likes it.
No, it's not that I don't want to.
We're on a foggy mountain road,
so it's dangerous.
Dozing off while driving
is even more dangerous.
Yu-jeong, there's a rest stop coming up.
Let's do it there.
But I want to do it now.
What was that?
What did we hit?
A water deer?
No.
Then what was it?
I think…
we hit a person.
What?
Fuck.
Shit.
Don't tell me he's…
He's not dead, is he?
He's dead.
No, he can't be. Let's call 911.
When they get here,
they'll be able to save him.
What are you doing?
-We should call it in.
-You know that I drank.
-I know that, but--
-Make that call, and I'll be arrested.
-My life would be over.
-We can't just leave him--
I drank and drove.
I hit a person who's now dead.
But what? You want to call it in?
Don't raise your voice.
Someone might hear you.
Right, I'm sorry.
I can't think straight right now.
This is why I didn't want to drink.
What do we do now?
What should we do? I'm totally fucked!
I told you I didn't want to drink.
Why did you make me?
Why did you force me to fucking drink?
I'm fucking screwed.
Why did you make me drink?!
-Babe.
-If only I hadn't drunk!
Babe, look!
Did you have an accident?
Yes.
My car skidded on that turn.
Oh dear.
Well, do you need any help?
I already called insurance,
so it's all right.
I'm good with cars.
I think I should take a look at your car.
That's all right.
I called my insurance company.
Insurance company?
I think there have been
several accidents due to the fog.
I guess so.
It's cold. You should get going.
I'm really okay.
Your girlfriend's waiting.
You should get going.
All right, then.
Right.
Hold up.
Do you know a place around here
where we could stop for a rest?
Come on, let me ask him.
I see.
There's Oasis Stay.
You can find it with your GPS.
It's nice and clean.
Oasis, huh? Okay.
You must have been in a rush.
You should zip up your fly.
Right. Thank you.
Fuck.
You didn't take a photo, did you?
It was too awkward.
There was a woman in the car too.
-It's all right.
-Damn.
We have confirmation, so it's fine.
What happened?
Don't tell me we've been busted.
What are you doing?
I asked you what you're doing.
Can't you hear me?
Holy fuck.
Babe!
What the hell are you planning to do?
Let's bury him.
-What?
-Think about it.
On this cold night,
this old, disheveled man was jaywalking.
There's probably no one who'd miss him
if he disappeared.
Have you gone totally insane?
That's nonsense!
What's truly insane
is the situation we're in.
Babe, hold on.
Let's try to think rationally.
You're not in your right mind now!
He's already dead anyway.
It doesn't matter how he died.
Don't you think it's important
to do our best with what we're given?
-What do you even mean?
-Let's just go into the mountains.
We'll talk on the way, Yu-jeong.
What's with you today? Snap out of it!
Why did this fall?
Babe?
What do we do now?
For fuck's sake.
-That son of a…
-Babe!
Fuck.
Who is this guy?
Why are you putting him in there too?
What's your plan, huh?
I have no idea.
In any case,
we can't leave a witness here.
Just get in.
Do you want me to end up in jail?
Stay here, then.
Thanks.
I'll take care of the rest.
Don't worry.
Buckle up.
MT. CHOWOL HIKING TRAIL MAP
What happened to the man
under the overpass?
Is he dead too?
He's alive.
Then why did you bring him here?
What are you going to do?
He's the only witness.
What do you think?
Babe.
You wouldn't.
Would you?
You're not that kind of person, are you?
Please help!
-Fuck.
-Help!
Wait. Where are you going?
Somebody please help me!
Get me out of here!
Help me out! Get me out of here!
Damn this prick.
Please save me!
Fucking idiot.
Just shut the fuck up.
Damn.
I really saw nothing.
I swear I won't say a word.
Please let me go.
If you saw nothing,
what do you mean you won't say a word?
I mean that I really know nothing,
so please let me go.
Somebody, help!
Shut up!
You fucking idiot,
I told you to shut the fuck up.
You got that?
Please don't kill me.
Killing one person or two
makes no difference.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Your bank details?
Sorry?
Fucking earmuffs.
Don't make me repeat myself.
I don't give a shit anymore.
What's your bank account number?
Hanjin Bank.
-Three, four, nine…
-Hanjin Bank.
It's three, four, nine… three, two,
one, three, eight, two, six, four.
Check your account.
NOVEMBER 11, 1:55 A.M.
10,000,000 WON DEPOSIT
Listen carefully.
We're accomplices now.
"Accomplices"?
That's right.
If I left you here like this,
you would die anyway.
You kept your life and made some money,
so be grateful.
Get out.
I said, get the fuck out!
Okay.
Thank you, sir.
Where are you going?
Sorry?
I'm going home.
I paid you, so you need to do some work.
Work?
What work…
Follow me.
Hurry up.
Shit.
Wait for me.
Wait, my ass. This is not a picnic.
Get over here!
Shit.
What are you waiting for?
Come here and dig!
Put that down, will you?
Fuck me for giving ten million
to such an idiot.
Are you all right?
What do we do?
Just dig. We must finish before sunrise.
Shit.
Fuck.
Frozen ground makes it tough, doesn't it?
What…
Don't you think…
it's a little too shallow?
I think we should dig deeper.
Keep your useless opinions to yourself.
There's no time. We must bury him fast.
Fucking whining and mumbling nonstop.
You should've left some.
Excuse me…
I…
kept thinking while digging the ground.
I just can't stop thinking…
that ten million is too little.
What?
Please give me another ten million.
That's only fair.
-What are we going to do?
-Shit.
I'll give you 20 million more.
End of discussion. Sound good?
Yes, let's do that.
Sounds good. Thank you.
Babe, are you sure about this?
Let's just go home, please.
Put on your seat belt.
Okay.
Yu-jeong.
Take a shower and get some sleep.
I'll call you later.
It'll be okay, right?
I don't know.
Don't worry, though.
I'll head in, then.
Fuck.
Sir.
I'd also like to go home now.
Yeah, you can go.
Jesus Christ.
I still need you to transfer the money.
NOVEMBER 11, 7:30 A.M.
20,000,000 WON DEPOSIT
PAYMENT SENT
BALANCE: 3,021,064 WON
Really, thank you.
From this moment on,
we bury what happened today forever.
Put your worries to rest, sir.
Take care.
Fucking hell.
I'm really sorry to ask,
but I don't have money for a taxi.
I'm really sorry.
I didn't bring my wallet.
Sorry.
Sorry about that. Drive safe.
What a lunatic.
For fuck's sake.
Here's your invoice. Take a look.
Thank you.
AUTO INSPECTION AND REPAIR INVOICE
4.8 million won?
Shit.
BODY BURIED ON MT. CHOWOL
FAMILY CAMPING TRIPS TO MT. CHOWOL
Take photos of him entering the building.
-Got it.
-Great.
EXAMINATION ROOM 1
I'M SORRY TO EVEN ASK YOU THIS
YOU'RE NOT SICK, ARE YOU?
PLEASE TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF AND CALL ME
I HAD TO FIX THE CAR AND STUFF
SO MONEY'S A LITTLE TIGHT
COULD YOU CHIP IN?
Ever since I slipped
and fell in the kitchen,
I get terrible back pain
even if I just move around a little.
Another doctor told me to do
warm compresses,
so I do them all the time,
but they haven't helped.
Excuse me, Doctor?
Yes.
You're listening, right?
Of course. Once you start getting
back pain at your age,
it doesn't go away easily.
I'll prescribe you
a week's worth of medicine for now.
But the medicine is so expensive.
You seem to charge more than others.
That's not true.
All right, I understand.
Let's see how you get on for now,
and then I'll give you…
LEE YU-JEONG:
CALL ME WHEN YOU HAVE A MOMENT
The nurse will see you out.
Hey. I'm sorry I forgot to text you back.
I had a lot going on too.
I get it.
You must be stressed too.
I'm sorry for even asking.
I had to take out a loan
to move to this new clinic.
Don't be sorry.
I should chip in too.
I'll try to get the money this week.
Thanks.
God, this is embarrassing.
One more thing. I don't think
we should contact each other for a while.
You know, just in case.
You understand, right?
Yeah. I understand.
All right. Thanks for understanding.
Get some rest.
All right.
I refuse to pay all of it. No way.
It's her fault I was drunk.
Fuck.
I'll start seeing patients in 30 minutes.
Don't let anyone in.
Yes, sir.
Fuck.
I told you not to…
I told you not to let anyone in.
Did you manage to get some rest, sir?
Subtitle translation by: Jimin Choi