Pang.
Hurry up. What are you doing?
Coming, coming!
Everyone,
to some extent,
is enthusiastic about dress-up and role-playing games.
That's because these types of games
can satisfy many subconscious needs.
Perhaps these needs
are ones they themselves aren't even aware of,
nor would they admit to having.
Who says games are all fake?
Sometimes,
they are more honest than you are,
and they help you see yourself more clearly.
At the same time,
they also make you understand
that these are ultimately
just human delusions.
Wake up.
[Falling into your smile]
[Episode 13]
Tong Yao!
What were you thinking?
You're here for the match,
not for romance.
You promised yourself not to date esports players.
Have you forgotten the goal you set for yourself?
You mustn't let Jinyang's words affect you.
You mustn't!
Idiot.
Quadra kill!
Guang, Team KING's jungler, has secured a quadra kill!
Once again, we are amazed by
the excellence of this talented esports boy.
Although he's in a secondary league team,
his mechanical skills
can be said to be
on par with any jungler in the national league.
Tong Yao.
What are you doing?
You wrote this?
You've taken notes of the habits
of all the players on Team KING, our rival?
As the saying goes, "Know yourself and your enemy, and you can fight a hundred battles without defeat."
Let me see.
Not bad.
We should all learn from you.
This...
Good work.
This kind of work
should have been done by the data analysts.
But since the qualifiers have just started,
and we're facing a newly promoted team like Team KING,
we didn't think it was necessary to pay much attention.
And considering you were all tired from yesterday's game,
we planned to let everyone relax a bit.
The term "newly promoted team" refers to
a team that has moved up
from a lower category to a higher one.
But we shouldn't look down on them
just because they were newly promoted.
It's not that we're looking down on them.
It's just we have stronger teams to face.
Just facing the completely transformed Team YQCB alone
requires a lot of analysis and habit-tracking.
You were up late organizing materials last night too, weren't you?
Keep it up.
Let's go.
Good luck.
Hey.
If they reach level 3 first,
the probability of the ADC going in to apply strong pressure is
85.37%.
Why did you snatch my notebook?
What if it was a girl's diary?
Where did you get that percentage from?
I calculated it from the dozens of matches I watched,
of course.
You watched dozens of matches of the newly promoted team?
Yes.
You have a lot of free time, don't you?
Why are you guys so arrogant?
Be careful not to lose to them today.
Is your abdominal pain better?
Not really.
You still have abdominal pain, and you're not wearing slippers.
No woman has dysmenorrhea for four or five days, okay?
If that were the case, how are women supposed to live?
If it doesn't hurt much, have some breakfast.
Why are you acting like a breakfast butler?
Put on your slippers before eating.
I'll wait for you outside.
Shorty.
Lend me your girl's diary.
Why do you want to read my girl's diary?
I want to see Team KING's data analysis.
Didn't you say you didn't need to see it because they're not a strong team?
You've already written it, so I might as well take a look.
K.
What's up?
Come take a look at this.
Starting by clearing their own jungle until level 4,
they'll then invade the enemy jungle to steal small camps.
After clearing the first set of camps,
there's a high chance they'll gank mid lane.
They'll try their luck there,
and if they fail to gank mid lane, they'll poke and harass
the enemy mid laner a bit, and then recall.
There should be a counter-gank here.
What the hell?
She's teaching you how to counter-gank. Don't you get it?
I don't.
Why did she write so many of her own thoughts
in the tactical analysis?
Because she's a born actress.
A drama queen.
To the audience here and those watching at home,
hello, everyone.
Welcome to the 2020 National League
of Onmyoji Arena.
I'm Dudou.
And I'm Qiu.
Now, everyone,
please look in this direction.
What's appearing on the screen
is the introduction of Team KING's players.
The first to appear on the screen
is Team KING's captain, Guang, who's a jungler.
It was he who single-handedly
carried Team KING
from the qualifiers into the National League.
With bare hands,
we climbed up from the secondary league.
We thirst for victory
like a dying person
craving for the last drop of water.
This is a battle for survival.
We will give it our all.
So,
veterans of Team ZGDX,
get ready to be trampled underfoot by us.
[Guang, KING_Guang
Gaming Position: Jungler
Keyword: Jungler full of youthful vigor]
Player Guang is really full of youthful vigor.
-Just a rookie.
-But his youthful vigor
is not unfounded.
His confidence is quite well-grounded.
After all, he has just reached the age
required by national regulations to participate in professional leagues,
and he's already led Team KING
all the way from the qualifiers into the National League.
As for himself,
he's the team's most powerful driving force
and the tempo engine.
That's right.
It was also because in the finals of the qualifiers,
Guang forcefully snatched Orochi and turned the tables
that he led Team KING
into
the OPL.
So we're really looking forward to seeing
if this newly promoted team
can give Team ZGDX a surprise.
Speaking of this, although...
They want to target me.
Tong Yao, I'll pick Ootengu for you.
Okay.
-Okay.
-I think it's still pretty hard.
Well, it's hard to say.
There's an old Chinese saying
that goes, "Newborn calves aren't afraid of tigers."
Let's wait and see.
As we can see,
both sides are ready now.
Let's see their final lineup choices.
Alright, let's see.
Now, as for Team ZGDX,
top laner Cat picked Ibaraki Doji,
jungler K picked Yoto Hime,
mid laner Smiling picked Ootengu,
ADC Chessman
will play Dodomeki,
and Pang as support picked Ichimokuren.
Now, let's take a look at Team KING.
They picked Shuten Doji for top lane,
Guang as jungler picked Mannendake,
mid laner Jung picked Menreiki,
and bot laners SKY and YC picked the combo
of Hakuro and Kuro.
Don't forget, everyone,
focus on ganking the jungler.
Our strategy is top, mid, and jungle coordination.
-Got it.
Good luck, everyone.
This game is yours, guys.
Cheng and I will just be supporting.
Alright.
We'll carry Cheng to victory today.
Sis.
Do you want to carry the whole team?
Do your job, top and jungle.
Don't count on me.
I'm just an invisible mid laner,
trembling in fear of the enemy jungler.
It's the enemy jungler who should be trembling.
So, the ten players
have all picked their shikigami.
What kind of audiovisual feast
will these ten shikigami
bring us?
Let's enter the game right away.
God Ming.
Do you think Tong Yao's strategy will work?
Let's have confidence in Smiling's girl's diary.
This is strange.
K left a camp untouched
and went straight into the bush.
What's this supposed to mean?
Smiling has also come to the top lane and jungle area.
Could it be that K wants to
leave this camp for Smiling to kill?
But he's already falling behind in levels.
It doesn't make sense to give up any more economy.
Moreover, at this point,
the opponent's level is already high enough for a push.
Team ZGDX's decision this round
is a bit puzzling.
It really is.
This is truly bizarre.
Is the bush really that attractive?
Not just K, but Smiling has also gone into the bush.
Support, help me take a look.
I'll go invade their jungle.
As we can see,
Guang is already in position to invade the enemy's jungle.
So, K and Smiling
are planning to kill Guang in the jungle.
Guang is here. K, let's go!
Okay.
Here it comes, here it comes!
Yoto Hime and Ootengu
are surrounding and chasing Guang relentlessly!
Kill him. Don't let him get away.
Ootengu used his blink
and instantly killed Mannendake with his first skill!
Nice! First blood secured!
Nice!
That was brilliant!
Mid lane and jungle coordination.
K and Smiling worked together in the mid lane and jungle.
-What's going on?
-What happened?
Why didn't you tell me their mid laner was missing?
How was I supposed to know?
I saw her push the minion wave
and retreat, so I thought she recalled.
How did she know
you would invade their jungle at this time?
Shouldn't K normally
clear the top lane jungle first and then go clear the bottom jungle?
They must be cheating.
Talking big, saying they'll dominate us.
Cat, keep it low-key.
But our skills don't allow us to be low-key.
But here's the question.
How did the two of them
know that Guang was coming to invade their jungle
without any vision of the enemy?
From my point of view,
Team ZGDX must have studied their enemy team thoroughly.
Whether it's the regular qualifier match, or...
Tong Yao.
The things you wrote in your little notebook
are quite effective, huh?
Of course they are.
Sis, awesome!
If that's really the case,
it's incredibly professional and impressive.
As a veteran top team,
to be able to study a new team
so thoroughly,
they've really got something.
And if Team ZGDX has really figured out
Team KING's strategies,
Team King is in a very dangerous situation
in this match.
Come on, K.
Let's wipe the floor with them today.
As we can see,
K is already lying in wait for Guang in the bush.
It seems that the enemy jungler's strategy
has been completely figured out by Team ZGDX.
Bring it on!
At this moment, Team KING's support is on his way!
Kill.
K's Yoto Hime beautifully landed against the wall
and used her third ability to dash away!
Even though the enemy's support arrived in time...
Nice!
It was still too late.
What were you thinking, my friend? See ya.
that Team KING's mid laner will fight head-on with the enemy.]
[When fighting one-on-one, if the HP and economic gaps are not big, there's a 72% chance
Now let's look at Ootengu's core ability.
This ability
relies entirely on predicting the timing of the opponent's skill release.
The shikigami Ootengu
is a bit overwhelmingly strong
played by Smiling.
In this match,
Guang, as the jungler, is almost completely...
I'll cover you, I'll cover you.
Indeed.
Wait for me to farm, wait for me to farm.
He hasn't fed any kills,
but his economy is still significantly behind the opponent's.
That's right.
This fight is really smooth.
What's wrong with the enemy jungler?
He's just been farming and doesn't dare to show up.
K, Guang is in their jungle.
Follow me.
Okay.
We can't fight them. Let's retreat immediately.
K, attack!
Roger that.
They seized the timing with great accuracy.
Guang doesn't have his ultimate,
and Team KING's overall economy is being crushed.
Nice!
Tong Yao has completely figured out Guang's jungle tempo.
Let's take a look at the bottom lane.
Chessman is already leading the team to push the tower.
Tong Yao, come here quickly for the team fight.
Be right there.
Can Team KING withstand the pressure and defend their high ground?
Pang, watch your positioning.
Roger that.
Since Team KING
lacks the damage from the core jungle position...
Retreat, retreat. Let's not fight for now.
Chase, chase!
Shoot him, shoot him!
And look.
After Chessman pushed down the second bottom tower...
Here we go. K. I'm going in. Follow up.
Go, go, go. I'm right behind you.
Good, good. Let's go, let's go!
Good to go. Good to go!
I'm coming!
Another team fight. Another team fight! Do they have a chance?
They've pushed to the high ground in the top lane.
Smiling is also constantly destroying the high ground in the mid lane.
Keep going.
Stay steady.
Watch this fight.
-Team KING can't take it anymore.
-Retreat!
After the team fight, their HP was critically low,
and Chessman scored multiple kills.
Shoot the tower, shoot the tower!
Go, go, go. Good to go.
While relentlessly chasing Hakuro,
Ootengu managed to take down Hakuro.
-So exciting!
-Team kill!
This fight was truly breathtaking.
Congratulations to Team ZGDX for winning the first game.
Congratulations to Team ZGDX for winning the second game.
Now, the first match of Group A
of 2020 National OPL
between Team ZGDX and Team KING is over.
Team ZGDX secured another victory,
currently ranking first in the group standings.
Bro!
♫We will be your hero♫
It was a breeze. I didn't even break a sweat.
Let's go.
It was too easy.
Sis, you were amazing.
So, judging from the past two matches,
when facing our veteran powerhouse of OPL,
Team ZGDX,
the newly promoted
Team King
[Defeat]
still has a noticeable gap in strength.
Indeed.
If we look at the first game,
the jungler, Guang, was marked and defended against during the entire game.
In the second game, he was just farming the jungle.
What the hell? What kind of performance was that?
Let's go.
Let's go. I'm done watching.
Moreover, Team ZGDX
has thoroughly figured out Team KING's strategies.
They've got them down pat.
It can be said that
for a veteran powerhouse,
to be able to study a newly promoted team's strategies
so thoroughly
is very professional.
-It doesn't happen a lot.
-Yes.
So, it's only reasonable for Team ZGDX
to win this match.
Yes.
Let's congratulate Team ZGDX again
for winning their second match in the National League.
Congratulations.
Cheng.
I didn't expect your team
would even study the teams promoted through the qualifiers.
It was truly impressive.
It was an exciting match.
It's just our mid laner gets nervous no matter who she faces.
Don't overthink it.
Congratulations.
ZGDX!
What?
Did you just say something bad about me to them?
Do you have paranoia or something?
Then what were you just saying to Guang...
Cheng.
The MVP interview is about to start.
Please come to the interview area.
Okay.
Pang, help me pack my things.
No problem.
There are always people trying to hurt me.
Congratulations to Team ZGDX.
Congratulations to you, Chessman, for successfully winning
the first match
of OPL National League qualifiers.
Is there anything
you'd like to say to your fans right now?
Thank you to all the fans for your support.
We'll give our all in the National League.
It seems you
really understand what the fans are expecting, Cheng.
I'd also like to ask,
in today's match,
you were up against
the newly promoted team
from the OPL qualifiers, right?
As a traditional powerhouse,
Team ZGDX obviously made thorough preparations.
It was a bit surprising.
So why did you do that?
Was that your secret to victory?
No.
It's just that our mid laner gets nervous no matter who she faces.
If we slack off against any team, she'd say we're getting cocky.
Before we left this morning,
she was loudly announcing at the training base
that we'd lose this match.
It seems you
are getting along well with your team's new mid laner, Cheng.
Well, we're not that close.
But she's very skillful.
She's also very diligent.
As the captain,
I'm very happy to have such a teammate.
With her joining,
this summer,
Team ZGDX will be stronger than ever before.
Do you feel the same way?
You know what?
I saw a beauty blogger
apply a new lipstick the other day.
The lipstick on her lips
looked like fairies dancing on her mouth.
Why are you so slow?
My computer cable and mouse cord got tangled.
It took me a while to untangle them.
-Guys.
-Good for you.
Team DQ.Five that will be using this lounge
is already on their way.
Let's tidy up a bit.
I'll finish eating in a minute.
We should take these away too.
I almost forgot.
You're like the queen of manners in the esports industry.
Good job.
That's how classy our team is.
Strong, and classy.
Perfect.
Hello?
I also said we should clean up just now, but did anyone listen to me?
Why did everyone listen when she said we should clean up?
That's gender discrimination.
You guys.
I'm going to report you
to the esports industry committee later.
Go ahead.
You'll be the first one I report.
Go, go.
-I'm not afraid at all.
-Good.
I won't let you off the hook.
Tong Yao.
When is Cheng coming back?
I don't know.
You came in so late. Didn't you see him?
I didn't.
I'm telling you, with Cheng's performance today,
he's going to receive so much admiration.
Looks like we'll have to wait until the cows come home.
You guys, check out the Douban special discussion group.
The Esports Farm is bombarded with comments.
Judging from the current situation,
I'm afraid it's not Esports Farm that's bombarded,
but Team KING.
Look at these headlines.
"As expected from a newly promoted team."
"So what if they were champions in the qualifiers?"
-"Headshot by Team ZGDX."
-Look at this.
"So tragic. I'm speechless."
"Team KING's jungler is killing me."
"The gap is still huge."
"Their tactics in the qualifiers were too simple.
Even though they successfully got into the OPL,
they're going to get destroyed."
Why isn't anyone praising my performance today?
They have no time to do that.
Everyone's busy
trying to divide the blame among the five members of Team KING.
Divide?
Divide what blame?
This comment.
Someone said, "In the 10 seconds of the teamfight,
the ADC spent 9 seconds just dodging around like a snake."
"The Support was invisible the whole game.
Couldn't even cast a shield."
Anyway, every one of them is getting criticized. No one's spared.
Although everyone's being criticized,
I think
their team's jungler, Guang, is getting the worst of it.
Yeah, he's really in a tough spot.
Starting from the first fight of the first game,
when he wanted to invade our jungle and steal camps
but got caught by Tong Yao and K,
and ended up giving first blood.
Why didn't you tell me their mid laner was missing?
He's been exposed to our vision
almost the entire game.
A jungler needs to be elusive,
making unexpected attacks
to give teammates early lane advantages.
A jungler who only farms in the early game
and disappears in the jungle like a coward
will definitely be
criticized by the audience until they're blue in the face.
Unfortunately,
Guang did it again in the second game.
He disappeared in the jungle early on,
and during that crucial Orochi teamfight,
he failed to provide timely support.
He only showed up after the 4v5 fight when all his teammates were dead.
By the time he arrived,
they'd almost lost the game.
He even fed us the last kill when he arrived.
After the first game ended,
they must have known there was a problem.
But at that moment,
it was difficult to come up with a solution.
So in the second game,
having known he couldn't ambush anyone,
Guang could only focus on farming the jungle
and try to find chances for teamfight.
What else could he have done?
You think the spectators would care about that?
All they can see is that
in the first game,
Guang failed to counter-jungle and couldn't ambush anyone,
feeding first blood,
and in the second game,
Guang focused on farming the jungle,
had no impact, and was practically invisible the entire game.
It was like Team KING was playing 4v5.
These are the most obvious things.
That's why they're most critical of Guang,
saying all kinds of nasty things.
Who's to blame? So tragic.
Don't make it sound like Team ZGDX
won easily.
Where are you going?
To the restroom.
Come back quickly.
We'll leave when Cheng returns.
Trash.
The queen of manners has retired.
Exactly.
Quick to come online, quick to go offline.
This is totally unacceptable.
Pang, go.
Why me?
Just go.
Or I'll report you.
-Collect the trash.
-Go.
Go, go.
Collect it.
Good boy.
You go throw it away.
Let me finish eating first.
I heard some noise,
so I came in to check.
Sorry you had to see me like this.
Why are you hiding here, crying alone?
You already know why.
Is it because you lost the match?
We fought for this spot against secondary league players
who were like a pack of wolf cubs in the qualifiers.
We came to the venue full of joy,
but little did we know
we'd lose so badly.
Losing the match was bad enough,
but then I saw the Esports Farm
filled with such harsh insults.
It's not like I haven't seen things like this before,
the esports forums praising winners and trashing losers.
I had prepared myself
mentally for the criticism if we lost.
But when it actually happened to me,
I still couldn't take it.
I wanted to tell everyone
that we really had no choice at the time.
We could only farm and wait for chances of teamfights.
We couldn't ambush because it was truly impossible.
Next time, with preparation, we'll do better.
But there won't be a next time.
So many people.
So many posts.
So many insults.
It's impossible to respond to them all.
You already know those people always praise winners and trash losers,
so why do you care so much?
Because they used to say I could lead the team to victory,
and that I was the best at creating opportunities for my teammates.
Although it might seem
that I was the only one chasing opportunities,
what they didn't know is
every single person in our team
longed for such an opportunity.
Everyone worked incredibly hard,
dreaming of entering
OPL
and proving ourselves
in front of the national audience.
I knew Team ZGDX was strong,
and we probably couldn't beat you.
I originally thought that even if we lost,
it wouldn't be this embarrassing.
At least we'd have some chance.
Deep down inside,
what we'd always longed for
was a chance to win, just like this.
I understand.
How could you possibly understand?
You started playing in the professional league in such a strong team,
and you're skillful yourself.
No one would criticize you.
The only one who wouldn't get criticized
is probably our captain.
If Team ZGDX loses a match one day,
they'll definitely criticize us like crazy.
Do you think they'd spare me?
Actually, the reason you're feeling this
is because when you won the games,
you were praised too highly.
So now that you've lost, it hurts more.
This feeling
is actually also quite familiar to me.
When I first joined the team,
I was like a fearless newborn calf.
I was on cloud nine after winning just one practice match.
Later,
we had a match with Team TAT from Korea.
You know about that, right?
That time, I lost to Tai so badly that I almost developed a fear of Korean players.
Even now, when I occasionally see that ID
in ranked matches,
my palms still get sweaty from fear.
I still haven't found a way to fully recover from that.
But starting from the National League,
you've been playing very well.
You don't seem nervous
or uncomfortable at all.
You and your team work together perfectly.
I can see that your teammates also trust you a lot.
Your team is great too.
Besides, this is just the beginning.
Your professional careers have just started.
As a newly promoted team from the qualifiers,
after you see more professional teams' strategies
and tactics,
you'll have a lot of room for improvement.
The next time we meet on the battlefield,
you'll become stronger.
But in the end, we were still
easily crushed by you guys.
Easily?
Esports Farm says it was easy,
but was it really that easy?
What's with getting misled by the special discussion group?
If you want to know if it was really easy,
why don't you ask me?
I have the most say in this.
To study your jungling routes
and team strategies,
I watched all the videos
of Team KING's matches.
I only came to
all these conclusions
after watching dozens of matches.
Before today's match,
I was still watching your qualifier finals.
Look at my dark circles.
So don't cry.
What's to cry for?
Having a clear goal
and working hard towards it,
isn't that a good thing?
Isn't that the whole point of the qualifiers?
No team can easily defeat
another team.
So don't belittle yourself like this.
You've earned
a position in OPL.
So hold onto it.
You're being a bit too nice.
I just don't like being mindlessly praised.
Isn't it good,
having all other teams fear you?
How is that good?
I stay up late every night reviewing matches.
My eyes are nearly blind from watching them.
Do you think it was for getting mindlessly praised?
You watched dozens of the newly promoted team's matches?
Yeah.
You must have a lot of free time.
Jian Yang.
You need to do homework to beat your ex-boyfriend?
As the saying goes, "Know yourself and your enemy, and you'll win every battle."
So, in that case,
when I lost to Tai...
Why did you stop talking?
What are you thinking about?
While I'm trying to comfort you,
I've also realized something.
What's that?
Before someone seemingly effortlessly defeats you,
who knows how much work he's done behind the scenes?
We're all human.
How could there be a person
as strong as an alien?
So,
never underestimate your opponent.
Don't fight a battle you're not prepared for.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Cheng.
I called you so many times, and you didn't answer.
So this is where you've been hiding.
[Missed calls: 4 calls from Long-legged Ice King]
I...
What were you playing?
Hide and seek?
The place you chose is really unexpected.
Not bad. Quite clever.
What do you mean?
Can't you talk properly?
Thank you. I'll leave now.
Goodbye, Cheng.
Hello. I found her.
Be right there.
You made the jungler from the other team
cry in the safe passage?
What do you mean?
Exactly what I said.
Why did he look at you with
that sorrowful gaze?
He was indeed in the safe passage just now,
and so was I.
He did cry,
but...
How should I put this...
Can't you talk properly?
What do you mean by "I made the other team's jungler cry"?
You can't use the word "make" so carelessly.
Then why did he look at you with
that sorrowful gaze?
How was that a sorrowful gaze?
Then tell me, what kind of look was it?
Don't you think it was a look of admiration?
That was a tamed look.
Where are they?
You did this kind of thing, and expected them to wait for you?
Tell me, do you have some grudge
against the title of team captain?
Two matches, two team captains collected.
Collecting them like stamps?
Is this some kind of
2020 OPL Limited Edition Stamps?
Shut up. You're a team captain too, okay?
Sorry I'm back late.
Where have you been?
Collecting stamps.
Cheng came back and saw you weren't here.
He risked being surrounded by fans again
to go look for you.
You didn't answer your phone either.
We thought you'd been kidnapped.
Why would anyone kidnap me?
To make me jungle for them?
-Sis.
-I won't lose anything.
Tell me the truth. Where did you go?
Only those who suffer losses know that.
I went to the restroom.
Why did our captain say you like collecting stamps?
I ran into Team KING's jungler
on my way to the restroom.
He was secretly crying in the safe passage.
So I comforted him a bit.
But the special discussion group's criticism is really harsh.
And they're praising us like crazy.
It makes me feel uneasy.
He dared to check the special discussion group after losing a match?
The day we lost the spring finals,
Rui uninstalled the Douban special discussion group
from our phones, one by one.
After all, he's a newcomer who's just started his career.
Besides,
Team KING was very strong in the qualifiers.
They've been praised all along.
And what's with you comforting him?
He's not just anyone,
but our enemy.
What if your comfort makes him soar?
What then?
No matter how much they soar, they can't beat us.
Because we're soaring too.
That's true.
While I'm comforting you,
I've also realized something.
Before someone seems to defeat you effortlessly,
who knows how much work he's done behind the scenes?
We're all human.
How could there be a person
as strong as an alien?
Cheng.
What?
Collecting stamps again?
I refuse.
No, that's not it.
Spit it out.
I want to challenge Tai again.
You're not afraid anymore?
Yes.
Okay.
When do you want to do it?
No way.
I don't agree.
You can't.
Why don't you agree?
Go.
I've got your back.
No. We have two matches next week.
What if it's like last time?
Mental breakdown.
Shut up.
Then for the remaining matches,
I'll play.
You'll lose.
Cheng,
I...
You've really made up your mind?
Yes.
Cheng, are you crazy?
Even if I don't help her arrange it,
she'll find a way to arrange it with them.
It's arranged.
Tomorrow afternoon.
Tomorrow? So soon?
If you get ready today, it's not too late.
Good luck.
Come on!