According to Beijing time,
it's now 8:58 and 30 seconds.
What's your answer?
Excuse me?
Keep it down.
Others don't know yet.
Can't you two date
normally?
Oh my god.
How did the fire spread to Jinyang?
From now on,
whether it's a sea of flames
or a bottomless abyss,
I won't ever look back.
Did YQCB's mid laner sleep with a fan
or did the fan sleep with him?
[Falling into your smile]
[Episode 22]
In this match,
YQCB's top laner Rong Rong chose Aobozu,
[2020 OPL National League Group B Round-Robin, Match 7]
jungler Xbang chose Itsumade,
mid laner Ai Jia chose Higanbana,
ADC Pope chose his signature Youko,
while Support Liang Sheng chose Ebisu.
-Pope! Pope! Pope!
At this point in the match,
YQCB has already
destroyed Alpha's bottom lane tower!
Liang Sheng, come over.
Come to me.
Fighting so soon?
Well said.
Look! They're fighting as expected!
They're really fighting!
Look!
They're team-fighting!
Liang Sheng, use your ult!
I'm using it!
But Alpha's ADC and Support
have come to assist!
Look!
Liang Sheng activated his ult
to shield Pope!
I'm here.
Yes! Look, Ai Jia's also come to support!
Before Mannendake could attack Pope,
Ai Jia made the first move!
Nice, nice.
He directly stunned Mannendake!
Pope successfully escaped!
If Higanbana's Support had been a bit later,
Pope would've been in deep trouble.
Ai Jia's play in this team-fight was really awesome!
Why's the cameraman zooming in
on Ai Jia so much?
These days,
he's been so anxious
that he's got a big forehead pimple.
Fine, awesome!
Babe, Ai Jia's play just now
even made me sweat.
Can't you be a little more nervous?
If we lose this match,
you'll be the one to blame.
But I don't understand it.
Then why are you sitting here?
Hengheng, look.
Overall, YQCB's team members
are very relaxed,
like they have a foolproof plan.
Yes, that's right.
Right now, the odds still look to be in YQCB's favor.
Higanbana is coming. Retreat.
Let's go for it.
Ai Jia's Higanbana
first baited out the enemy support Yamausagi's shield,
then Liang Sheng's Ebisu went in to stun.
Impressive!
This move was so unexpected!
Alpha's ADC couldn't react at all!
Pope's first kill is really boosting morale!
Yeah, yeah!
YQCB seized the opportunity with this one move!
Pope's strategy is so profound!
Pope!
Nice, nice, nice.
-Ai Jia!
I don't know if you've noticed...
Hurry up.
After Pope joined YQCB,
he has changed the team's playstyle.
Want to leave?
They're here.
We can fight.
YQCB is very likely to win the championship this year.
Don't fight yet.
-We can fight.
Come on, one push.
Make space for the damage dealer.
Nice!
Pope is signaling again.
Looks like this tower is going to be pushed.
Ai Jia's Higanbana team-fight
is really well played.
Look, they're about to push the base!
They hit the base!
It'll be a one-push!
One push, one push!
It's really a one-push!
It's too late.
-Boom!
-Nice, nice.
It's destroyed!
Congrats to YQCB for winning this match!
Nice!
That was brilliant! Congrats!
Brilliant, brilliant.
This push was really awesome.
YQCB's really charging forward
with great momentum this season.
Yes, it seems that in just a few months,
they already have great chemistry.
Not only has Pope found a suitable support,
but even mid-laner Ai Jia's playstyle
is also changing.
Yes.
Ai Jia really dominated this entire round.
The rhythm of this round was spot on.
Can you take it more seriously?
This is your boyfriend's highlight of his life.
Look how excited the fans next to you are.
What highlight?
You know that
when I met this kid,
he was still just a little boy.
It's not like I'm with him because...
I'm sorry.
It was an accident.
What are you doing?
Did I do anything wrong?
Some people are just ridiculous.
They don't understand
or know how to play the game,
but got with the player
because he's famous.
Yet they're so smug about it.
Keep it down.
His girlfriend isn't...
I'm not talking about her.
Isn't it because of those people
that female fans are catching flak?
Like that, what's his name, Xu Tailun
and that Guoguo?
If they like a player,
just be content with watching their matches.
Why must they go and seduce them?
You're right.
We'll talk after the match.
Look at that fool.
He's playing on stage optimistically.
If I were down here arguing with his fans,
would it be appropriate?
But we can't let them talk about you like that.
It's fine, don't overthink it.
Let the second round begin.
The current score is 1-0,
with YQCB in the lead.
The ban and pick phase for this round is now complete.
Both teams have confirmed their shikigamis.
We can see that
Alpha picked Ryomen,
Kosode no te,
Higanbana, Youko, and Ebisu.
For this round,
they aren't using the jungle-support roaming strategy?
YQCB has chosen Yamausagi, Tanuki,
and Ibaraki Doji for jungle,
and Ai Jia is using Yuki Onna.
It's clear that
this "Protect the Carry" strategy is for Pope's Hakuro.
They might be trying out a new tactic.
But I think
they're not entirely familiar
with "Protect the Carry".
Besides,
Alpha's jungler is using Kosode no te.
He's no pushover.
Once he figures out the opponent's intention...
The bottom lane will suffer.
Alpha's jungler
can't do much when behind,
but when ahead,
his skills are world-class.
The push is happening quickly.
Look, we can see
Alpha's jungler, Zero,
preparing to gank the bottom lane
as a surprise attack!
That's right, but look,
Ai Jia's Yuki Onna doesn't seem to have noticed!
He hasn't gone to support!
-We can fight!
-Go, go, go!
-Keep up!
By the current confrontation,
Pope's Hakuro seems to be in danger!
His life is hanging by a thread!
Yes, we can clearly see
YQCB using a "Protect the Carry" strategy.
Pope has been taken out first!
What a huge blow to their morale!
Instead of returning to the jungle,
Kosode no te headed straight for mid lane!
Is he planning to cut off their retreat?
Ai Jia, careful!
Just as I'd predicted!
Quick, look!
Ai Jia was completely caught off guard by this move!
Instead, Xbang came to support
and got caught too!
YQCB's change in strategy
shows zero chemistry!
Ai Jia's play is just painful to watch!
It's like Ai Jia reverted
to his old playstyle!
It's almost the same opening as the last round,
freeing up the support to gank mid together,
catching YQCB's mid-jungle duo.
The next step should be to target top lane
and gank the top laner,
or wait for Octopus to respawn and take it.
Based on the data,
it's more likely that they'd gank the top lane.
Rong Rong's Tanuki is already intercepted
by the enemy jungler
-on the way...
-Chase them!
to support Ai Jia!
Chase them down!
Five minutes.
Five kills in just five minutes.
Neither of the bottom laners has reached level six.
YQCB's rhythm has gone haywire this round.
It seems that in this season,
"Protect the Carry" isn't quite viable.
But Cheng and Pope
are really cut from the same cloth.
They always charge in for a fight, regardless of the lineup.
But
Pope is a bit more aggressive than Cheng.
Now that Pope's down, they have no way of winning.
How can you deal damage with Yuki Onna in mid lane?
To be honest,
I really don't get
why he chose Yuki Onna.
Any damage-oriented shikigami
would've been better.
Exactly.
Sometimes we really can't
ignore the meta.
If you go for a "Protect the Carry,"
your opponents will have counter-strategies.
Ai Jia's performance
is really off-rhythm this round.
Pope has no room to deal damage at all,
and he's far behind on gold.
We can fight! Go, go!
Come here, protect me.
Protect the damage dealer.
-We can fight.
-Come on!
-Hurry up!
-Chase them!
-Keep up!
They're low on HP!
Retreat. Retreat now.
-Let's go!
Alpha completely saw through
YQCB's "Protect the Carry."
After the ADC was taken out,
the other members are
like fish on a chopping board, ready to be slaughtered.
They can't keep up with damage output either.
They're totally getting stomped, aren't they?
That's right.
But changing strategies now
might be too late!
After a beautiful team wipe,
Alpha has pushed to the high ground.
Pope has respawned.
But I think it's hopeless.
Hakuro, who didn't get to farm early on,
is utterly helpless!
He died in his own base
without killing a single minion!
It's destroyed!
Congrats to Team Alpha for winning this round!
Congrats to Alpha!
Congrats!
Didn't I tell you we shouldn't play like that?
It's okay. Next round.
Ai Jia didn't perform well this round.
It's in stark contrast to the previous round.
Your boyfriend lost the round.
What's the big deal? It's just one round.
It's not like I've never seen him lose before.
He barely won during the entire spring season.
And now he can't accept this loss?
It doesn't matter.
It's not over yet.
They can just win the next round.
What are you doing?
What does she mean?
What doesn't matter?
Why shouldn't it matter?
Exactly!
It's because of people like you
that players end up underperforming!
We came all this way
just to watch them win.
Please don't say such
irritating things.
Ai Jia!
My friend didn't mean
that...
Let's go.
-What are you doing?
-Let’s go.
Why bother with people like that?
Wait, "people like that"?
I'm your fan, you know.
Yes, you heard right.
I wouldn't ever speak to my own girlfriend like that.
What gives you the right to?
How I play has nothing to do with her.
If you have a problem,
come at me.
Let's go.
So cool!
That's so crazy!
I've never seen anything like it.
So cool!
Not bad!
Nice, nice.
-So cool!
-He's such a star!
That was so cool!
Put me down.
Are you crazy?
Why did you jump off the stage?
Should I've done nothing?
Of course.
For your competition, I can tolerate anything.
Why do you have to?
Listen.
I've been furious for days.
Playing esports is my business.
Dating is my business.
Winning or losing is also my business.
I just can't stand
them slandering you.
If they want to criticize,
they should criticize me too.
I won't indulge them.
Why should my girlfriend,
whom I cherish and protect,
be bullied
by those who don't even know us?
Also,
they're doing this in the name
of protecting me.
Should I tolerate it?
And why should you?
Do we owe them anything?
What right do they have?
Are you a fool?
That chatter's nothing to me.
Silly, how childish are you?
I'm childish?
I've told you before,
as long as I'm with you,
whether it's a sea of flames or a bottomless abyss,
I'll trudge through it even with my eyes closed.
At first,
I didn't understand your esports dream.
But since I came back to China,
from the opening match,
I've watched you fight your way to where you are now.
Though I still don't understand those operations,
like tower breaking or whatever.
It's tower diving.
Whatever it is,
I know that
at least for the first half of your life,
you won't leave the esports stage.
I also know
that you can't live without me for your entire life.
So,
I won't do
anything melodramatic like
forcing you to choose between esports and me.
I've made up my mind,
so I won't regret it.
if I can't handle that minor chatter,
how can I even date you?
Isn't being with people like you
about accepting this attention and criticism?
It's all because my boyfriend is so capable,
a rising star in esports.
Whether they bless us or not,
our future
has nothing to do with them.
I'm not joking.
Whether it's a sea of flames or a bottomless abyss,
I will...
It's so tough.
Jinyang does have it tough.
Those haters are at it again.
What's the deal with Ai Jia?
Is he an esports player or a drama actor?
-I know!
-Now I believe...
that girl's family is rich.
Ai Jia must be using his status as an esports player
to latch onto power.
What's on your mind?
Ai Jia didn't do anything.
He just spoke a bit loudly.
Will he be banned from competing
or be punished?
Jinyang didn't do anything either.
She usually can't stand being wronged.
But today, for Ai Jia's competition,
she took it all without retaliation.
What more do they want?
They're just simply dating.
What's with all these reasons
and weird conspiracies?
If you truly like someone,
who cares if they are
an impressive player or star?
It's just pure love, that's all.
Players are human too.
They also have people they like
and people they want to be with.
What's wrong with that?
Or is it that
having such thoughts is wrong in itself?
Because as public figures,
you don't have
complete autonomy.
Players exist
to win competitions,
please fans,
and serve the team.
So you should do anything
to achieve these goals.
These ideas seem right,
and of course, many people agree with them,
but if even the players
think this way,
then it's a disaster.
Yes, winning is important.
But compared to
the fans' appraisal of our results,
we're the ones directly impacted by the results.
So, selfishly speaking,
it is our business.
"Thank you for your love and support,
but the match results
really has nothing to do with you."
This is the right way of thinking.
You're too rational.
But I can't be like that.
I'm easily affected.
I have mental breakdowns
and get upset.
Everyone does.
But you seem immune.
Cheng.
Are you really so invincible that you fear nothing?
Yes.
Because I still need to protect you all.
Forget it.
Let's just hug first.
Why are you making it sound like the world
is about to end?
Tomorrow,
these great pecs and abs
might not be mine anymore.
It is the end of the world.
It's such a pity that they lost this round.
Luckily, they won it back later.
After all this commotion,
what strategy should we use next?
God Ming.
I have an immature idea.
Why don't we use "Protect the Carry" again?
"Protect the Carry"?
Why?
No particular reason.
It's a very controversial strategy now.
Everyone says
teams that rely on it this season
are bound to lose.
But when we played against DQ Five,
we used it in the second round
and it worked quite well.
So I want to test it again
to see if it works.
Don't they say
application is the sole criterion for testing truth?
You want to use Yuki Onna?
Yuki Onna?
Didn't Ai Jia just use Yuki Onna?
And they lost.
Their loss in the last match
wasn't because Ai Jia used Yuki Onna.
The key of the strategy is the ADC.
Tong Yao.
You seem to have an ulterior motive.
You've been rambling on and on
just to
vindicate your good friend,
to prove that their loss
had nothing to do with Ai Jia's girlfriend.
Alright then.
Pope never gets flak.
No matter how he plays,
people will always defend him.
Pope was the biggest reason
their team lost their last match.
Let's show him what
"Protect the Carry" really is.
This will really frustrate him,
which I'm on board with.
So,
I agree.
Okay, okay, sure.
I'll take Ibaraki Doji later.
Let's relive the spring season.
Using outdated shikigamis and tactics
regardless of the current meta.
You guys are really cocky.
How did I end up in such a chaotic team?
Join the chaos too.
Why don't you take Ichimokuren?
Cat is right.
Take Ichimokuren later.
Go support Cat, and I'll solo bottom.
Reliving the spring season, huh?
Let's go.
Relive the spring season.
[2020 OPL National League Group A Round-Robin, Match 8]
Tong Yao.
Are you sure?
Okay, now the ten players on the field
have chosen their shikigamis.
Let's check out the final shikigami lineup.
On ZGDX's side, the top laner Cat
chose Kuroko.
Jungler K chose Ibaraki Doji.
Mid laner Smiling chose Yuki Onna.
ADC Chessman chose Hakuro.
Support Pang chose Ichimokuren.
On Doomsday Orcs' side, the top laner is Shuten Doji,
the jungler is Yoto Hime,
the mid laner is Menreiki,
the bottom laner is Dodomeki, and the support is Higanbana.
Qiu, what's your opinion
on these ten shikigamis?
I think ZGDX seems to be
up to something here today.
Smiling actually chose Yuki Onna?
What's the deal with today's matches?
Well, maybe Smiling
was influenced by YQCB's last game,
thinking, "Didn't you screw up
with Yuki Onna?
Then I'll pick Yuki Onna
to show you how to really play her."
With such a functional mid-lane shikigami,
Smiling's not as good as Ai Jia.
If that's really what she thinks,
she might be getting a bit cocky.
I'm just... I'm just kidding around.
This round, ZGDX is even going for the "Protect the Carry" strategy.
What's wrong with "Protect the Carry"?
Are you asking what's wrong?
Didn't you
see YQCB losing after using it
with the Pope?
That was the Pope.
He's on par with Cheng.
All the best, guys.
Alright, let's go!
Don't say I didn't warn you about saying such provocative stuff.
After the match is over,
go check your Weibo
and you'll see what's up.
Okay, let the match begin.
Shikigamis from both sides
have arrived in their respective lanes.
In the mid lane, Yuki Onna will be facing
Menreiki.
Five, let's go to the bottom lane.
Menreiki and Yoto Hime
have started moving down
to join Dodomeki and Higanbana
to face Pang and Chessman...
Wait for me.
-Pang, retreat.
-Okay.
They're trying to trap ZGDX's bot duo
so they can't escape.
Look, Pang and Chessman
can only cower under the tower.
Dive the tower. Don't let them escape.
We can fight.
As expected of Higanbana, going straight in to tank the tower!
These three from Doomsday Orcs
dove the tower and secured the kill!
That was some extraordinary teamwork.
-Nice!
-Brilliant.
Menreiki and Higanbana
unleashed their ult moves at Chessman at the same time!
K's Ibaraki Doji
controlled the incoming Dodomeki!
I can handle it. No problem!
I'm going in, I'm going in.
The enemy jungler is coming!
-Nice!
-That was well done.
-Not bad, bro.
-Very good.
The odds are really not in ZGDX's favor for this round.
If this were me in a regular ranked game,
I might've already given up.
But clearly, ZGDX hasn't given up.
Cat, you go too.
Let's go, we're going too.
Orochi pit!
Is the Orochi pit about to witness a big team-fight?
Come quick.
Menreiki has activated her ult and has been dealing damage.
K and Cat are both low on HP.
Will they engage in this fight?
Use your ult!
Shuten Doji has entered the battle!
-Attack him!
They're going for a push!
The Doomsday Orcs are so well-coordinated in this push!
They've taken out Cat and K!
-Nice!
-That was good!
Not bad, not bad at all.
Pang, Tong Yao, lead the momentum.
Give me time to farm.
Okay.
Pang, follow me.
Here I come.
Smiling... Smiling used her ult,
taking out the low-HP Menreiki and Higanbana!
Fight back! Go!
-Chase them!
-Keep chasing!
Pang speeds up, blinks, and knocks out enemies airborne.
Menreiki and Higanbana are down!
Nice!
ZGDX pulled off a brilliant two-for-none exchange!
So worth it!
This push was so worth it.
So brilliant!
That was really impressive.
Smiling's timing and rhythm
just now was excellent.
And Pang was very in sync.
You can clearly see
Yuki Onna is still a viable shikigami.
We can see that
Chessman's really seizing this opportunity well.
He's already frantically farming.
Yes, that's right.
Why? Because Chessman
is the "carry" in ZGDX's "Protect the Carry" strategy,
the core damage dealer.
As they're behind on gold,
he can only let Smiling lead
in small skirmishes
to ensure his farming time.
But Doomsday Orcs has noticed this.
We can fight!
I'll flank them.
I'll go to the bottom.
Yoto Hime has taken position!
Chessman's Hakuro is in danger again!
Yoto Hime used her mobility skill to attack Hakuro!
Chessman quickly reacted and dodged!
Yes, he turned back and attacked!
Chessman's operations are so ferocious!
Counter-kill!
What's with Chessman?
He actually managed to solo kill Yoto Hime with Hakuro!
That was amazing!
-Cool!
-Cheng's showing off!
Now we see the Doomsday Orcs
teleporting to the Orochi pit.
Looks like they want to stabilize their gold first.
The mid laner is missing.
The top duo is also missing.
Trying to get Orochi to get rich?
Cheng, shall we ambush them?
Okay, go set up the ambush.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
Over here,
Doomsday Orcs are already fighting Orochi.
We can fight.
ZGDX is also rushing over,
preparing to ambush near the Orochi pit.
Are they planning to steal the gold?
I'm in position.
Me too.
My skills are off cooldown.
Chessman's still clearing minions in mid?
What about this team-fight?
They don't want this Orochi?
Chessman is still in mid?
Cheng, if you don't come now, we'll lose the Orochi.
Giving up this Orochi
is basically handing this victory to the opponent
on a silver platter!
Cheng, we're out of time.
Cheng, get over here!
This determines if we can turn the tables.
Cheng, come now!
Wait a bit longer.
There's still time.
Orochi's HP is critically low,
but Chessman's still in mid.
W-What is he waiting for?
At this point, Doomsday Orcs' far ahead on gold.
If they take down this Orochi,
once the minion waves arrive,
it'll be tough for ZGDX to make a comeback.
-Cheng!
-Come now!
Wait, I'll reach max level in three seconds.
What was that?
Chessman's Hakuro is almost at max level!
Then they might have a chance at this Orochi pit.
The shikigami Hakuro
has a very long attack range at level 18,
and its high burst damage makes it hard to catch.
They might turn the tables soon.
Three.
Just one more minion!
-Can he make it?
Two.
One!
Initiate! Go!
-Watch my position.
-Okay.
-Go!
-K, get ready for suppression.
Pang, charge in with me.
-I'm here!
-Tong Yao, use your ult!
-Let's wait and see.
Cheng, I'll shield you. Go!
Careful, Cheng.
I'm here.
It's destroyed!
Congrats to ZGDX for winning this match!
-Nice!
-Yeah!
Congrats to ZGDX for successfully turning the tables!
Yes.
So in this match,
Chessman successfully utilized Hakuro
to its fullest potential, showcasing its terrifying burst damage
near the end of the game,
and leading ZGDX to victory.
Of course, Smiling also shone
in this round.
She proved that her Yuki Onna
is viable for competitive play.
So, who says
we must blindly follow the meta, right?
Listen.
"Protect the Carry"
is still valid!
[Onmyoji Arena]
First, congrats to Team ZGDX for maintaining
their undefeated streak.
Thank you.
We're also very surprised that Team YQCB
hasn't left the venue after the match ended,
joining us in this special
post-match group interview.
We wanted to leave,
but the coach wouldn't let us.
He kept us in the lounge,
insisting that we watch them play "Protect the Carry."
Because it's a newly attempted strategy,
we're not very familiar with it.
Hello, I've a question for Team ZGDX.
"Protect the Carry"
isn't that suitable in the current meta
where the bot lane is weak.
So why did you
insist on using it
when YQCB failed with it?
Our mid laner said
she also wanted to try the strategy
with Yuki Onna.
I thought it sounded fine.
It was a good chance
to teach other ADCs how to play it well.
So we played two rounds with it.
Okay, thank you.
He said he wanted to teach you how to play it.
I've a question for YQCB.
After the second round today,
there was a small incident.
In the third round,
Ai Jia didn't appear in the starting lineup.
May I ask if you were suspended?
The fans really want to know.
Actually, it's like this.
Letting a sub play in the third round
was a decision made jointly
by the coaching staff and team members.
I know
there are many people online stirring up trouble,
saying Ai Jia was being a diva by refusing to play.
That's not true at all.
Please stop with these rumors.
Actually, at that time,
Ai Jia wasn't in a good mood.
So we thought it'd be better
for a sub to go on.
That's why.
May I ask
why he wasn't in a good mood?
Didn't you see what happened?
Ai Jia.
Enough.
Recently,
there've been
constant rumors
about players' personal lives.
As professional players,
what are your views on this?
Just let nature take its course.
We don't think much about that.
We spend most of our time training.
We rarely have time to interact with others outside.
So most of us are still single.
Hey, hey.
This doesn't mean we've sworn off love.
It's not that we can't find someone,
but it's also not that we don't want to.
It's not that we can't find someone either.
Anyway, you need to understand what's going on here.
But many fans still hope that players
can focus on matches
and strive to win the world championship,
instead of thinking about other stuff.
Like when streaming qualifiers for practice,
just look at match info.
During qualifiers,
don't play other strange games.
Aren't there many
online forums discussing these things?
Fans hope you can play seriously,
win the world championship,
and strive for good results.
Let me repeat what you just said.
See if it's reasonable.
Don't stir up trouble.
Many parents
hope their children can study hard,
strive to ace exams,
and get top universities,
so they shouldn't think about other stuff.
It's like how they always hope
that during breaks between classes,
you'd memorize more English words
instead of playing
those so-called strange games.
Parents often discuss this topic.
But their intention
is also so that you can focus on studying,
achieve good results,
and live your life well.
This sounds quite reasonable.
But usually,
the fans who make such suggestions
are mostly around this age
or are working adults.
Yet they demand
professional players, fellow humans, to do this.
I won't even mention those
who constantly mock players for wasting time
on dating,
or playing other games during their off time.
Don't you ever check your phones
during class or work
to browse forums and waste time?
I just hope
everyone can put themselves in our shoes.
We're all young.
Who hasn't been distracted in class,
fallen asleep during class,
or peeked at the class beauty?
I don't have similar experiences,
but I want to ask, how are pro players any different?
Why should they be flawless like saints?
Nobody's perfect.
People fussing about players
playing Tetris today,
playing Snake tomorrow,
and dating the day after
is really pointless.
We spend most of our time training.
In fact, our training hours
are even longer than some people's study hours.
Many people in school break up
because of
distance or graduation.
But for us pro players,
we get dumped mid-game.
Why?
Who do you think Cheng is talking about?
Why is that?
I suggest you interview
God Yang, the jungler from Team CK.
He'll tell you why.
He's talking about Tong Yao's ex.
Cheng.
You seem to have a lot of insights on this.
I'm not
considered young in this circle.
I've been a pro player for years
and have seen quite a lot.
So, in that case,
you don't actually oppose
players dating?
If it's within
reasonable limits.
Haven't we all
heard of people acing their exams
because of love?
Cheng, do you want that too?
I already have someone I like.
Who does Cheng like?
Cheng has someone he likes too?
This is big news!
What a scoop!
He has someone he likes?
Oh my god!
He has someone he likes!
He didn't say anything.
You didn't hear anything.
Don't blush. Relax.
Don't breathe heavily.
Stay calm. Stay calm!
To fans with overly high expectations,
do you have anything to say?
I'm very grateful for your support and love.
I'll work hard in future matches.
If possible,
please come often to support us in person.
And I want to say,
if you're a true fan of a pro player,
stay close to his game stage,
but keep a distance from his personal life.
Thank you.
You realized your mistakes, right?
When you're free, I'll teach you.
Gosh, enough already.
Shorty, let's go.
Let go.
Come on.
If it weren't for my brilliant performance
with the "Protect the Carry" strategy in these two rounds,
Ai Jia wouldn't have cleared his name.
How will you thank me?
I'll kowtow to you.
No, don't brush me off again.
I'm not.
You are.
Because I want to protect you all.
Someone once said
that the meaning of love is probably
that there's suddenly a person in the world
who can give you everything you want.
He does everything within his power,
fearless,
ready to act without hesitation anytime, anywhere.