What's the use of doing well in the qualifying season?
We still didn't make it to the finals
because of someone.
In the end, we handed over the trophy to others.
Who was responsible for God Ming's
severe hand injury?
Not all mistakes
can be covered up by time.
Lu Yue won't be in the starting lineup.
Anyway,
it must be an inside job.
I posted the video.
Pang?
Why did you fight?
Why did you drag God Ming down?
Why did you have to implicate the team?
You're just a coward who always runs away!
Say that again!
I'll say it again!
You're a coward!
Pang, enough!
-Shut up!
-Say it again!
You're a coward!
-Alright, Pang, that's enough.
-Let's go.
Let's go cool off.
Pang, you've got it wrong.
Lu Yue didn't fight for no reason.
It's clearly Lu Yue's fault!
Why do you keep defending him?
The truth is often not on the surface.
Do you want to hear it?
What exactly happened a year ago?
[Falling into your smile]
[Episode 8]
Hey, yeah, I know.
Yao, don't hang up yet.
Go watch Ai Jia's livestream.
He's clearing Lu Yue's name.
It was quite a coincidence.
I happened to be in the restroom with an upset stomach at that time.
You have no idea
how despicable those guys from Team JK are.
Who does ZGDX think they are?
Why are they so arrogant?
They're too cocky!
Exactly.
Especially that Lu Yue.
He didn't show up for his buddy's party tonight,
and yet he still dared to talk big.
He's clearly disrespecting A.
A spent a fortune.
He did it
just to promote before the match.
And what happened?
It was all livestreamed,
yet they beat us 2-0.
Wasn't it a deal?
It's an exhibition match.
A 2-1 would've been enough.
It's one thing to not go along with it,
but they're even cocky.
The audacity!
Come to think of it,
if A hadn't been off his game today,
would we've lost?
Yeah!
They just got a free pass to the finals.
What are they cocky about?
Exactly!
They want to go to the national finals?
Dream on.
Since they dared to disrespect me,
I'll make sure
they get what they bargained for.
Hello?
Come over later.
Yeah,
bring more people.
Take care of those
uncooperative ZGDX guys for me.
Cripple all their hands.
Oh, and
be careful when you do it.
Don't hurt the second young master of the Lu family.
Wait, A,
why not cripple Lu's hands too?
We can't mess me
the Lu family.
About this fight,
A's side started it first.
His exact words were,
"Get people
to cripple those pro players' hands."
Who are those pro players?
It's ZGDX.
Guys,
they wanted to
cripple the hands of all ZGDX members.
And they weren't joking.
They'd already called for backup at that time.
If it were you,
in such a situation,
would you just sit back and do nothing?
And if they really brought people over,
it would've been too late.
Yes, that's the whole course of events.
I'm only stating the facts,
without making judgments.
Take your time to process this.
Bye bye.
Lu Yue.
We're all buddies in the same team.
You shouldn't have kept it a secret
that you got into a fight to protect us.
There's one thing they're right about.
Your hand
was injured because of my fight after all.
Lu Yue.
Alright.
Now that everything's clear,
let's not dwell on the past anymore.
But your hand is injured.
I'm still responsible after all.
So even if I'd spoken up,
nothing would've changed.
Pang was right.
I did hold you back
and hold the team back.
No matter what,
Lu Yue was impulsive for this.
Then it seems
we can't just blame everything
on Lu Yue.
In the end,
it's all because of the despicable A from Team JK.
Yeah! If I heard someone
was going to beat up my buddy,
I'd call for backup too.
Right?
So Lu Yue
can't be entirely blamed for this.
How can you think like that?
In such situations, we should call the police.
Yeah.
We should sue him until he's ruined!
Now that the truth is out,
K,
Pang,
are you two...
good now?
Lu Yue.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
I misunderstood you.
It's okay.
Cheng.
I think we should
officially release the truth first.
Even if we can't reverse public opinion,
we must at least let them know
that we didn't start the trouble.
I'll make a call to PR for help
to resolve this.
Lu Yue.
I'm sorry you were wronged.
I don't feel wronged.
I did take
the worst possible approach.
Gosh, bro.
You should've
contacted me immediately.
If I'd been there,
God Ming's hand would've been fine.
If you'd called me,
I would've gone there and—
And called the police right away.
Yeah?
Okay, all's good now.
Yo! Cheng's here!
I've finally made it to a ZGDX livestream!
I'm dying from curiosity.
Cheng, can you explain the fight incident?
Why did Lu Yue throw the first punch?
It's true that Lu Yue struck first.
As for why he did it,
you can watch Ai Jia's livestream.
You withdrew from the competition because of God Ming's injury.
That's why the fight happened, right?
Let's have a moment of silence for God Ming.
God Ming's injury was an accident.
You're right.
It is related to this.
But God Ming's hand was injured before.
This is common for pro gamers.
Tendon tears
are common for core players.
No matter what, Lu Yue was impulsive.
Cheng.
If it were you,
what would you've done?
I wouldn't have hit someone.
But I'd have made sure
that those who bullied my teammates
regret their actions.
Look.
My contract renewal with the club.
If you have time to show off,
you might as well expand your shikigami pool.
Speaking of which, shouldn't I get a fixed seat?
I can't keep fighting with this fool for the computer.
Am I right, God Ming?
It just shows
the difference in our status.
I meant adding a computer desk for you.
Pang has been busy in the kitchen since morning.
It's making me nervous.
What's he up to?
I bet
he's making dinner for everyone
to apologize.
Pang.
I didn't know you were a good cook.
I've never been treated so well
all this time I've been in the team.
What do you need? I'll help you.
No need, no need.
Stay in your seats.
Rui.
I heard Pang was fined three months' salary this time.
That's harsh.
This means that for the next three months,
he might ask to borrow money from me anytime.
Can I choose not to eat this sadfishing meal?
I'll pass too.
Keep up with the sarcasm
and I'll dock your salaries.
-Okay, I'll eat.
-I'll eat.
I deserve it.
I deserve this.
Pang.
Even though you were fined,
if you're treating,
you could've at least bought more meat.
There's nothing here!
Yeah, where's the meat?
Then I'll have it.
No, no, no.
I'll eat. I'll eat.
Let me look again.
Do you want some of mine?
Do you have meat?
A little bit.
What are you doing?
No way, Pang.
Hiding meat at the bottom of the bowl
for your favorite child?
I thought this went out of style
in my mom's generation.
I...
Look,
you made him mad.
Lu Yue, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have accused you
without clarifying the situation.
I'm sorry.
Pang will break his room door down sooner or later.
That's settled then.
Back to the point.
Everyone's okay with Lu Yue
rejoining the team, right?
Yeah.
Then I'll submit the roster for the new season tomorrow.
Wait, what?
No objections?
How's everyone suddenly okay with this?
What about me?
I object.
New members always start as substitutes.
Really?
I've never played professionally. Don't try to fool me.
Lu Yue is right.
Back then, Cheng also started
as a substitute.
But it took him just a year
to make that player
tremble on the substitute bench.
Let me correct that.
That person didn't actually tremble.
If you want to make me tremble,
that's impossible.
Oh, shut up, will you?
Who exactly was pushed to the substitute bench
and made to tremble?
The Pope.
The Pope?
From TAT?
My brother and the Pope
were once substitutes for each other.
The strongest light and shadow in OCK history.
Let's eat.
Are you trying to convince me or what?
It's to tell you
that true talent will always shine.
Look at Cheng and the Pope,
right?
They're equally respected,
each dominating a league.
You know,
all damage dealers
have to cower and tremble under
their dominance.
The shadow that rolls on the ground after being defeated by Tai once.
I don't want that.
Watch your words.
Say that again.
I won't.
Then you say it.
Say what?
Your brother's trying to walk all over me.
First come, first served.
Who told you to rejoin the team so late?
Besides, her shikigami pool
is much deeper than yours.
You'd better behave.
Why are you speaking up for her?
None of your business.
Did you hear that, huh?
First come, first served.
My shikigami pool is deep.
And you're just a noob!
You keep quiet too.
Both of you
haven't been in any official matches.
Just in case,
isn't it normal to have a substitute?
If you two want starting positions,
earn them with your skills.
Great! That's wonderful.
I really respect Cheng's suggestion this time.
Come to think of it,
this is truly
the fairest treatment I've ever seen.
Really.
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four.
Three, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Four, two, three, four.
Five, two...
Cheng.
As the team captain, you should set a good example.
I have near-perfect vision.
From here, I can see
which episode of what Korean drama
the opposing team is watching.
With my excellent eyesight,
do I need to do that?
Seven, two, three, four.
While I was away,
ZGDX's really transformed so much.
A family should be neat and tidy.
Is this the new computer the club sent for you?
Yup!
I no longer have to fight with that fool.
What era are we in?
You're still doing eye exercises?
I bought everyone eye protection lamps.
Now, no matter how long you stare at the computer,
you won't have to worry about eye strain.
One for everyone,
so use it.
That's quite thoughtful.
Of course.
Fool!
Come over here.
Moron.
You come over.
Shorty, how long are you going to practice?
I'll stop
when you stop.
Why are you copying me?
Hey, how are things with you and Ai Jia?
Looks like you've made up?
I've put him on my probationary boyfriend list.
Let's see how he performs.
You've been together for six years,
and he's been on probation six times
and never been kicked off.
I'll shut up.
The new season's promo photos and schedule are out.
Check it out.
What is it?
The National League needs promo photos.
National League?
The one you're going to host.
That National League.
Hey.
Shouldn't you
know a little about your part-time job?
Don't I just need to look stunning for it?
I don't need to know all that.
Your No.1 fan has decided to host
to support you.
Why are you still sighing?
Because Lu Yue is also there.
Our team hasn't decided on the starting lineup yet.
It must be you!
You're so awesome.
Not necessarily.
Cheng said it needs to be fair.
I'm thinking
about how
I can tip the balance to my favor.
Don't worry.
Girls should be confident.
Let's go pick out your battle clothes.
Battle clothes?
What battle clothes?
Our team's just chosen our uniforms.
It's different.
These are different battle clothes.
This...
This is the battle...
Go try it on.
A perfect woman
should always be ready to show her sexy side
to handle any unexpected situation.
I'm going to take promo photos,
not wedding photos.
Well said.
Tomorrow will be your first photo together with Cheng.
For your next
photo together, I hope it'll be on
your marriage certificate.
You're overthinking it.
I'm sending you my best wishes.
My silly bestie snagging the esports heartthrob.
If that day really comes,
I could brag about it for a lifetime.
How did I end up with a friend like you?
This black one will show through my clothes.
How'd I go on stage to compete?
It's the allure of mystery, get it?
Then go try this one.
Hurry.
Go on.
This one's so cute.
Even underage girls
don't dress this childishly.
But I like it.
Fine.
Go try on these two pieces then.
Do I really need to?
Alright.
Since they haven't decided who's starting yet,
there's no use worrying about it.
Anyway, you need to take photos tomorrow.
Be in your best condition
to show your captain
that you're his best partner.
Once your couple photos with Cheng come out,
if fans' voices grow louder,
the club might make you the starter.
Alright, go on.
Please, please.
Go, go, go!
We're at a spa.
Why are you like a fish on a chopping board,
sighing and groaning?
Jinyang.
Since Lu Yue is back,
am I going to
lose my chance to be a starter in the new season?
You've said this
a million times today.
Don't fixate on it.
What's meant to be, will be.
If it's not, there's no use fighting for it.
Is it okay?
We're done.
Jinyang.
Since Lu Yue is back,
does that mean I won't be in the starting lineup?
Say something.
Jinyang.
Do you think I'm going to...
You won't be in the starting lineup?
Bye.
Go ahead.
Good luck, Tong Yao.
-Bye bye.
Look at how they're fighting this team battle.
Why are they hesitating?
We must gank them!
Look at their situation!
Honey! Honey!
Honey!
Honey.
Why don't you come and check on me?
Put on makeup?
Even styled your hair?
Too bad there's no camera by the water cooler.
Lu Yue, don't go overboard.
Why are you sitting in my seat
and eating my snacks?
Give them to me.
It's fattening.
I'm helping you share the burden.
This is healthy.
What do you know?
It doesn't make you fat.
Tong Yao.
Come with me.
What's wrong, Cheng?
Do you want some dried mango?
It's very sweet.
What is this?
How can you use the keyboard with all that stuff on your nails?
And don't those long eyelashes
obstruct your vision?
Such a strong perfume scent.
Are you trying to choke your teammates
and lose the game?
If you want to be a starter,
just focus on practicing hard.
Don't waste time on useless things.
Caught you in the act of favoritism, huh?
Delete it.
I won't!
If you dare tell Mom again,
I'll kill you.
Bro, you've changed!
Yao.
I forgot to gossip with you.
Guess who I ran into two days ago?
Did you see a ghost?
What ghost?
I ran into our third roommate.
She's actually dating our class monitor now.
That thick-skinned and heartless girl
was blushing and shy in front of our class monitor.
It was like her heart
was about to jump out of her throat.
Her heart was about to jump out of her throat?
How's that different from seeing a ghost?
Don't interrupt.
Tong Yao.
What is it?
Where are the manicure and eyelashes I got for you?
Did Pancake eat them?
Cheng didn't approve.
Hey.
I've realized
only Cheng can keep you in check now.
How did the topic shift to Cheng again?
Remember the bar incident?
You were so frustrated.
But after Cheng took you home,
you were back to normal the next day.
Tell me,
did Cheng do something to you?
Be honest.
Now, when you think of Cheng,
do you feel over the moon, your heart racing,
your face turning red, and out of control?
I'll give you three seconds.
Answer quickly.
If you don't answer, I'll take it as a yes.
Do you like Cheng?
I...
Do you?
Come on, tell me.
Hey.
You're in love.
Pancake!
Why didn't you knock?
Why didn't you lock the door?
I forgot.
I was too lazy to knock.
I thought you'd rolled off the bed.
Oh my god, it's Cheng!
You two are really together?
Everyone went to bed quite early today.
We have a promo shoot soon,
so I told everyone to rest early.
You're such a team captain.
Cheng.
Why did you come out from there?
She just rolled off the bed.
I went to help her up.
I also saw something funny.
Heard that?
She rolled off again.
Aren't you going back in to help her?
Forget it.
People need to learn to grow on their own.
You mocked me again.
I heard that.
I won't help you win tomorrow.
Remember to take your medicine before bed
for your insanity.
Did the sun rise from the west?
That night owl
actually got up early to read?
Here.
[Strange Pilgrims: Twelve Stories]
The title sounds so profound.
I don't get it.
Hey.
You're in love.
Go away!
Cheng, you're up so early.
Team CK had mid-season tournament match.
So I got up to watch.
Did they win?
They crushed Red Arrow and Obsidian.
As usual, they were thrashed by Alpha.
Do you feel over the moon, your heart racing,
-your face turning red...
-Shut up!
What?
Nothing, nothing.
What are you doing?
There's fur stuck on your head.
It's Pancake's fur.
I'm working on my core today.
Yao, want to work out?
Let's go, let's go.
-Let's go.
-Let's work out.
Healthy nuts.
Healthy living.
Not bad.
Muscles.
You're not even starting in the National League.
Why are you training so hard?
You're not starting either.
Why are you so serious?
It's already a done deal.
Don't make your delusions sound so real.
You can't afford to scare me to death.
I'm definitely starting.
You're definitely not starting.
Why are you copying me?
I'm not copying you.
Childish.
Cat.
What's up?
Have you ever seen a living moron?
Moron?
Where?
Over there.
What's wrong with them?
And you too.
What's that smell?
Moron...
You're so dramatic...
The new team uniforms are here!
The uniforms are here. Take a look.
How are they?
This one looks the best.
Didn't you insist
that black would make you look slimmer and better?
It's just right.
It's called making the best of what you have.
Do you understand?
Didn't you say you were afraid of looking fat?
I fell for your nonsense.
It's not even half the size of my uniform.
Never trust a girl when they say
they're fat.
It's not about whether she's fat or not.
She just looks like a kid no matter what she wears.
What are you saying?
Where are your manners?
Who looks like a kid?
A perfect woman
should always be ready to show her sexy side
to handle any unexpected situations.