La la la la Jesus
I know that you're a bad guy, but I still have to say that when Brother Cheng said the last sentence, his right hand was put under the table.
At the same time, the left hand was also under the table. Brother Cheng's hand is shaking.
So what did you guys do?
I already have someone I like.
I'm sorry, but I'm not sure if I'm right.
What's wrong?
Are you shy?
Look at this.
Look at the details of the singer.
He's so rich. He's so rich.
He's so rich.
What the hell are you doing?
He's going to find out the truth.
I...
I'm sorry.
No.
Why are you so nervous?
I was standing on the rock when I was playing the white snake.
He's a spy in the police.
I was scared that he'd be in charge of the show.
I didn't care. I didn't agree.
If he's with me, I don't care what kind of game he'll play.
Now you know why I'm so strict.
Once I'm exposed, Your Majesty,
you'll lose your half-dead spirit.
Do you know why I agreed to be strict with you?
Because of your half-dead spirit.
How dare you say that?
I don't.
I was afraid that the lunatic would pour dirty water on you.
He said that you can't play the game well because of his love.
He only cares about your career.
I don't care.
I care.
Yes, although it won't happen,
even if it happens,
I'm confident to hit their face with a gun.
But I don't want you to think about that.
You're a person who likes to gossip.
You'll definitely get affected.
It's also because of this matter.
Do you want to be with me?
After all, if other teams are looking for you,
I'll definitely be the first to stand up and fight.
I'll warn that person not to harass him.
He'll be a good player.
And then?
Why are you laughing?
Don't mind me. And then?
I'll be the first to stand up.
To celebrate the silver medal,
I'll be the first to get a reward tomorrow.
Eat whatever you like.
I want to eat the food.
I'm afraid of the mud.
I want to eat the chicken.
I'm afraid of mud.
I want a bowl of soy milk.
I want a piece of raw beef.
Thank you.
Brother Cheng, what do you want?
I'm not eating. I'm a little sleepy.
Go upstairs and rest.
Why am I feeling a little hungry now?
Tong Yao,
did you have something spicy in my room these days?
No.
Add me some more tea. Thank you.
You're really good at eating.
Are you sure there's nothing spicy here?
I think there's something spicy in Brother Cheng's room.
It should be the electrician.
Don't worry about the electrician.
Where is he?
Brother Cheng,
do you want breakfast?
I can order for you.
I'm afraid you'll get a stomachache.
I want to eat you.
Captain,
the meat is not enough.
The waist is broken.
What are you hiding from?
I won't do anything to you.
You're dangerous.
Do we have to keep this kind of posture?
You can also lie down.
You're so stupid.
I just want to thank you.
You worked so hard to cooperate with the Four Seasons' Hospital,
to show the style of the Ni Feng Bureau's textbook.
And to thank you
in front of the whole country,
to show that you already have a new talent.
You're so sincere.
You're so grateful.
Then,
do you have time tomorrow?
Yes.
Then,
let's go to the date.
Okay.
But,
before we go to the date,
should we kiss first?
See you tomorrow.
Fatty,
I'll give you a panini.
In less than three seconds,
Brother Cheng will definitely appear.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the date.
I have a breakfast ready for you on the table.
You guys eat.
I'm going out to buy something.
I'll go out with you.
Why do you guys
always go out to play
and go to the famous bureau?
I'm like this every day.
Me too.
Forget it.
You too.
Last time I saw you
playing hard to get out,
or when you went to the fish market with my brother
to buy goldfish,
I didn't even think about it.
What's wrong?
The blinds are going in.
You're just going to play.
How's that?
When did you two go out together?
I'm so tired.
I'm so tired that
my AD is actually abandoned.
I'm going to the middle.
I'm just kidding.
I can't accept
my brother's future son
being like his mother.
And then being laughed at.
Shut up.
I don't want to.
I'm leaving.
This normal person like us
can only be lonely.
What's wrong?
You're not happy?
Lu Si Cheng,
why didn't you react to him?
Do you think
he's right?
I'm so angry.
Your record-breaking perfect memory
is about to be turned into a powerhouse
by my sister's sixth sister.
Your powerhouse?
She's kidding.
You're as tall as my mother.
You can't see who's in the group.
You're in the group.
When our son
gets in the group,
he'll be taller.
Don't worry.
Who's with you?
My son.
Your daughter is also good.
Just like your mother.
And then you can
be a tall boy.
Perfect.
I actually like girls.
She's so naughty.
Shut up.
You can't even imagine.
No.
Can you imagine
something normal?
I feel like
your voice is smiling.
I'm not.
Captain,
do you think
you've been breaking up recently?
What do you mean?
In my opinion,
Chessman is a calm,
calm,
and thoughtful person.
I didn't expect
to be a shameless,
old-fashioned,
and old-fashioned.
I'm very sad.
Do you remember
when we first met?
I treated you as a
rotten wheat.
I threw the door
on your face.
What did you think?
The license.
I thought
you were far away.
But the license
doesn't mean Chessman.
I'm a gentleman
in front of other girls.
Isn't that great?
You can enjoy
my inner self
with your own thoughts.
Chessman.
Let's go.
I'm so tired.
You're so silly.
That...
Forget it.
I don't want to play with this.
I have money to buy
here.
I bought a pair of the same ones.
That's right.
This is so cute.
I want to buy it.
I want to buy ten.
I want this color.
I also confirmed
that it's a pair of the same.
It's so cute.
So cute.
Which one do you want?
I think there's one.
This is a different hat.
That rabbit is hard to catch.
Yes.
We haven't caught it for a long time.
It's too hard.
My god.
It's so amazing.
My mom is coming.
So cool.
I want to play with this one too.
Which one?
It's so cute.
The one in the middle.
Really?
It's okay.
It's so amazing.
I was thinking about
the fact that there were
so many different types of caravans
in the amusement park.
In the future,
I will find a man who can do it
and come back
to avoid all of them.
You did it.
What?
There's a man who can do it.
Which amusement park?
Go and buy tickets.
I will go and get them.
Dongqing is your enemy, Luo Yan.
What do you want to eat in the future?
The ice cream shop
was good just now.
What ice cream do you want to eat?
Why can't I eat ice cream?
You are a three-year-old child.
In your heart,
am I not a three-year-old child?
You must love me forever.
Don't lie to me.
Next time, we will go there.
You go there.
Bye.
We will go together.
You go first.
I will go to the cinema later.
Let's go.
Bye.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Why didn't you go to the cinema?
Why did you wait for me?
Why did you run away?
I saw our fans
at the gate of the dormitory.
I left it there.
Okay.
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you wearing a mask?
I can't see you.
Lu Si Cheng,
speak.
What's wrong?
Because you look ugly.
You don't deserve to be bald.
Lu Si Cheng,
don't be angry.
I didn't mean that.
What?
Okay, okay.
I was wrong.
Can you let me go?
Where are the fans?
Did you see us
walking on the street?
Do you remember
the comments I showed you?
They don't accept you as a girlfriend.
They don't accept you.
I don't care.
Give me your pants.
I care.
I'm not afraid of them
being like Chen Jing Yang.
saying I'm not good at my job.
I just know how to seduce them.
I just know
that since you started your job,
no one has ever said
you're not good.
Even if it's a professional
professional nutritionist.
So?
So I don't allow myself
to be
the one who's going to break your mouth.
You're right.
Everyone has their own weakness.
I have one too.
It's you.
I don't care what others say.
If it's true to me,
I'm happy.
But my behavior
won't be at the house
because of this.
My behavior is because
of my product.
Not because I'm
your friend.
I just like
a little girl.
I'm not doing anything wrong.
Why are you
always so nervous?
Let's go.
I'm so happy.
I didn't react.
Let's go again.
I'm so happy.
What are you doing?
I'm expressing my disappointment.
I'm so happy.
I told you,
the summer is really good.
There's a lot of fun.
I told you,
there's less time to work.
There's a big beach over there.
The gym.
The photo is really good.
There's a swimming pool.
It's really good.
Did you two
go to the Las Vegas
to get married?
You only came back this late?
Brother Cheng.
Since you're back,
I'll tell you something.
The club is not
allowing us to participate in the event.
It's really simple.
I'm going to tell you
that it's really simple.
It's a fan meeting.
I'll take it as a joke.
Just be fun.
Since Brother Cheng doesn't want to go,
I'll just go to the basement.
The basement?
What?
Where?
The basement.
If we don't go,
we'll miss the chance
to meet the food.
We'll miss the chance
to meet the beautiful city.
What a pity.
Don't...
Don't.
Is our hotel
far from the night market?
Has the activity been canceled?
What time is the meeting?
What time is the work?
If we can get it,
it's bad if we can't get it.
Don't take it off at that time.
You said it's a million.
Then we have to
tell Brother Cheng.
Brother Cheng.
Are you going?
Yes.
Yes!
It's so good.
Yes.
I'm not going.
Okay.
Hurry up.
I know how to play.
You're playing with the vegetables.
I don't have your vegetables.
Stop.
My list.
The order of the club
is a problem.
We can clean the room at 8 p.m.
Let's go.
I just saw the screen.
The hotel's
table is very high.
How about we go for dinner?
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Brother Cheng.
Help me bring the luggage.
I'll go and hug my mom.
Okay.
Hello, mom.
Yes.
We're already at the basement.
It's nice.
It's raining a little.
Don't worry.
I'll hang up.
Big sister.
Are you Smiling?
You are...
It's really you.
I'm your fan.
Fan.
Before you quit your job,
I really like to watch your live broadcast.
I also play mid-term.
I've learned a lot from you.
I can play the team now.
I can play a little more online.
Maybe I'll meet you.
My dream is to play a game with you.
Big sister.
Can you sign a name for me?
Okay.
Yang Yang.
You're running around again.
Why are you talking to strangers?
Can you make people feel better?
I'm not running around.
I didn't talk to strangers.
This little sister is my favorite computer player.
What player?
Computer.
Okay, okay.
What computer?
Isn't it playing games?
You kids.
You're playing games.
You're not slow at learning something.
You're looking for some excuse for being cowardly.
Let's go.
Sister Smalone.
I also want to get a job.
I also want to win a title.
I will be a champion in the national finals this year.
I'm begging you!
Goodbye, Sister Smalone.
Okay, see you.
Okay.
Stop running around in the future.
Why are you here?
You've disappeared for 30 minutes.
I thought you were kidnapped.
I don't have money.
I just got a job for three months,
and I was deducted from three months.
The assets are paid.
I have money.
If you were to tie up a family,
what would you do with me?
I have to give you 50,000 yuan.
Who was that little ghost?
A little fan.
What did you say?
He wanted to sign.
He said he also wanted to get a job.
But the career path was done by my mom.
Let me ask you a question.
Have I used up my money?
I don't have money.
Money is in etcetera's name.
I am a confidant.
What is it?
You want to get rid of it?
Actually, I don't have anything to ask.
How long have you been like this?
Just a short time.
It's a good hiding place.
No one found it.
Who broke the famous Yuyi first?
Me?
I threatened him.
If he didn't do it, I would throw him away.
So he did it.
Are you satisfied with my answer?
You are wrong.
There is only one girl in the team.
We are bragging and protecting each other.
As the captain,
you are the captain.
We are not good at talking.
So you are the one who is bragging.
I am not bragging.
Then I will keep it for you.
I am the captain, not Lei Feng.
And you, Tong Yao.
You said you would do well in the career.
You didn't talk to the professional players.
The professional players are all in the team.
You are so self-centered.
Captain is not a good guy.
He won't lie.
He usually watches the game.
I feel more and more empty now.
I feel more and more
the smell of the mysterious dog food in the air.
Why are you two so quiet?
I don't know.
I just scolded him.
I scolded him.
Did you hear the Sider's brother's voice?
The game was so cute when I was playing in the supermarket.
It was so cute when I was playing the game.
I was defeated by Ata's early morning money.
I was alone in the room.
I cried all night.
I practiced all night.
It was so cute.
I won the game.
I didn't know what to say to the sun.
I didn't have the time to be polite.
So cute.
When Solo won the game,
I felt more cute.
I just asked.
I can still say a lot.
You stay in the school hall and talk to your wife.
Don't you want to hear it?
The last question.
Where are you two?
You only saw that.
There's nothing else.
What else do you want to ask?
I'll tell you everything.
No, no, no.
You two let me play quietly.
Go, go, go.
You two go first.
Walk far away.
Oh, right.
I used the spray.
I'm going to buy a spray.
No.
Tell me what you want to say directly.
I'll go and spray you.
I've been a assistant for two years.
You didn't even buy me a washbasin.
Don't move tomorrow morning.
Don't move.
Bye bye.
After the V-log,
where are we going tomorrow?
Where do you want to go?
Go eat something delicious.
Okay.
Miss,
how are you going to sleep tonight?
What's up?
What are you doing?
I just finished my face mask.
I woke up early that day.
I'm so sleepy.
I think I can sleep anytime.
Close the door.
Put a stool in front of me.
Close the door?
Do you want to lock the thief or lock you?
Lock me.
Okay, I won't talk about it.
I'll hang up.
Bye bye.
My private life
has been filled with your doggy days.
I'm still my assistant.
Have you finished?
I remember
the excitement of
the young lady
in the hotel hall today.
I can't calm down
for a long time.
I just want to beat you up.
I'm a teammate of Tong Yao.
But you want to commit a crime.
Brother Cheng,
Tong Yao is very good.
Look at God Yang,
look at Guang,
look at Li Hengshuo.
They are all like our family.
If we didn't win the game,
they would probably not come to do it.
If you have any problems,
please contact me.
The OPL team
is half of the team.
You have to be careful.
Don't forget
that Xia Lu has a big me.
You are so lucky.
What do you want to say?
Brother Cheng,
your competitor
is quite a lot.
Don't think that you are a man.
Just keep it.
I didn't keep it.
When I was with him,
I wanted to tell the whole world.
There was someone behind me,
but he didn't let me.
Why didn't you let him?
At first, I didn't think it was good.
I was afraid that he would lose.
But then I found out
that he has already got the recognition.
Now, if we want to jump out again,
he can't do this, that can't.
That's just hitting his own face.
The OPL team has all won the record.
It means that Tong Yao has perfectly recognized
our position in the middle
and followed our rhythm.
But then,
when I was at my doorstep,
how did I tell this thing?
The OPL team
and Qingyang had a fight.
It was a big deal.
My fans
were also
very enthusiastic about this competition.
They were even more impressed by him.
He always thinks that
if I don't show him my true colors,
he will lose his fans.
Little girl,
you are so thoughtful.
Is the new one useful?
Yes.
You are so thoughtful.
I am not the one who is giving you the gift.
Brother Cheng,
what do you like about Tong Yao?
To be honest,
Tong Yao
is just a normal girl.
I think
she is a girl
who can pull out
and support
her fans
who are not as good as you.
Because she is very strong,
she is very eyes-catching.
She is also very cute.
She is a pervert.
She is also very handsome.
She is also very beautiful.
Is there anything else?
I will try my best.
So, can I call you Brother Cheng?
Who will you miss again?
This is the one.
I don't know what to do.
I will sleep here.
Your man is judging your voice.
Listen to it.
It is noisy.
Hurry up.
Thank you.
I don't know what to do.
You are really angry?
Give me back your room.
Let me see if there are any others.
No, no.
I am the only one.
Then why are you
so naughty?
Do you have any work to do?
What?
I was wearing a mask last night,
okay?
Love is the main character.
You are going to kill me?
Aren't you going out with Ai Jia today?
Why haven't you answered the phone?
I am not going.
Why?
Actually,
I have thought about this question carefully these days.
I think they are right.
Which one?
Who do you want to attack?
No.
I am serious.
I am not like you.
I am not as good as the other players.
In the fans' eyes,
I am not a person
who can help Ai Jia.
I am not as good as the other players.
You are playing a game.
You are not as good as the other players.
I can play a game.
But I can do something else.
For example,
for example,
I bought her a team.
I bought her a company.
When she saw the fans,
she would think,
wow, such a handsome man.
Every hair color
is the one
that the woman who hates
bought her a company.
But I can't let her not want a company.
What should I do?
I can't.
I am so angry.
I am happy to have a rich man.
I don't deserve Yong Yong.
I like them.
They hate me.
They don't want to kill me.
Are you serious?
Maybe.
By the way,
don't you know that you are going to Vlog today?
Go and dress up
for me.
Don't be embarrassed.
Okay.
Bye.
We just finished the meeting.
The fans in the next room
are really enthusiastic.
Now,
we are going to have dinner
in the small world.
I don't know
where they are going.
I will find
your favorite brother.
Where is brother Cheng?
Hu Xiao.
What is this smell?
It's pork.
Xiaobang is taking a photo.
What should we do?
It's not a live broadcast.
Don't worry.
I will delete it later.
Delete it.
What do you mean?
I can't keep it on my mind?
Tell me.
How are you going to get married?
What do you want to do?
I think
it's not going to be a good thing
without the pig's stomach.
Welcome to the shop.
We have a lot of snacks.
You can choose.
What would you like?
We can choose.
Okay.
This is a harvest.
harvest.
We are here to buy snacks for Xiao Pang.
Aren't you afraid of the fat man?
Don't worry.
Our snacks are all good ingredients.
They are delicious and not fat.
Do you hear me?
Please take two pieces of pork belly for us.
Thank you.
Okay.
Mango.
I want to eat.
You are like a rabbit.
Give it to me.
I won't give it to you.
You are so arrogant.
You are bullying me.
You are so jealous.
Give it to me.
I won't give it to you.
This is two pieces of pork belly.
Thank you.
You can take your time.
If you need anything, you can ask me.
Okay.
Give it to me.
You are so jealous.
Li Kai.
Come out.
Hello.
Who are you looking for?
Where are you from?
You little brat.
Come over here!
If you don't answer my call,
I won't answer your call.
Come on.
I've been here so many times.
Where are you from?
You are a bastard!
Come here, I'll tell you everything.
Don't go.
Come here.
Go! Go!
Go to final
Get out of here
Go
Hurry!
Love never needs a girlfriend
I want to get close to you, a little bit closer to you
A face without a face, a calm smile
Heart beats are always at home
Never want to be addicted to the light, the information
The world is me and you, the first and the last
You think I'm a good person, I'm thinking about you
I want to get close to you, a little bit closer to you
A face without a face, a calm smile
Heart beats are always at home
Never want to be addicted to the light, the information
The world is me and you, the first and the last
You think I'm a good person, I'm thinking about you
I want to get close to you, a little bit closer to you
The world is me and you, the first and the last
You like me, I'm going to take your hand
Love never needs a girlfriend
I want to get close to you, a little bit closer to you
A face without a face, a calm smile