(Presented by WeTV)
♪I'm thinking of you again somehow♪
♪The happiness and sorrow♪
♪Keep replaying in my mind♪
♪I thought I could love you
until eternity♪
♪I have never stopped♪
♪Missing you♪
♪I can't stop♪
♪Missing your tenderness♪
♪I'll always be waiting♪
♪I'll be there waiting for you♪
♪For no reason at all♪
♪I only want us to be together♪
♪I'll be there waiting for you♪
♪Until the end of my life♪
♪All I need is you♪
♪I'm always missing you♪
=Accidentally Meow On You=
=Episode 19=
Well,
you did something, actually.
Do you remember
that I logged
into your Weibo account
and replied to your fans?
A few days ago,
I received a message.
It's from a little girl, named Song.
She is ill in hospital.
She needs to receive
plenty of treatments every day.
Most of the time,
she is confined to bed.
She said
that she repeatedly read your book,
feeling that the treatments
were less tormenting.
Read this.
It's her message.
(I don't know what the illness is.)
(Song: Dear Qiao Yi,)
(Mom refused to tell me.)
(Hi,)
(My hair dropped a lot today.)
(my name is Song.)
(But I'm not afraid. I have your books.)
(I have been your fan for three years.)
(They are pumping me up.)
(Thank you)
(Thank you, Qiao Yi!)
(for giving me the courage)
(at my worst moment.)
(So that I can bravely face my illness.)
(Let me tell you a secret.)
I think
you can go to the hospital
to visit this girl.
Yeah.
I'll go visit her now.
Now it's not a good time.
We have to work later.
Maybe after we finish the interview?
I'll accompany you.
OK.
Yi.
Qiao Yi,
about your future work plan,
do you have anything to say?
Sorry.
I don't think
I can't face my fans on the stage
in my current state.
So,
I'll cancel the book launch
and do charity.
- Cancel?
- Cancel?
Why?
But your readers are expecting!
(Extreme Impala Incident)
(I can't face my fans)
(or face anyone who supports me.)
(So,)
(I'll cancel the book launch.)
What is Zhou Tian doing?
Can't she even handle such trivia?
The situation is messy enough.
She's making it worse.
Enough.
I heard it.
(Zhou Tian)
Hello?
Mr. Ji, Qiao Yi...
I know.
Sorry, Mr. Ji.
After so many things have happened,
I should have learned
and prepared a plan
for this situation.
I failed in my duty.
This is who he is.
A self-willed man.
To be honest,
he's not really self-willed this time.
(I can see him blaming himself)
(for the Extreme Impala thing.)
Li Ang said
he has never seen
Qiao Yi this sad before.
So,
keep him calm now.
(Don't make more trouble.)
(Leave)
(the rest to me.)
These two
are actually one thing.
When the Extreme Impala thing
results clearly,
he will figure it out.
Got it.
Yi...
Hi,
have you seen
Qiao Yi?
He's gone.
Thanks.
Hello, Zhou Tian?
He hasn't come back.
He doesn't even know
how to book a car.
Where can he go?
Yeah.
Let's go find him.
Qiao Yi,
where are you?
Zhou Tian is looking for you.
Do you know how negative
the cancellation
of the book launch is at this time?
Can you be less childish?
How old are you?
(Twenty-five years old.)
(But,)
(I want you to accompany me to a place.)
Rooftop?
I can take pictures of your dead body.
(No.)
(It's the hospital.)
You are back.
We're having a meeting soon.
I'm in a hurry.
Gotta go first.
Go.
How's Yi?
Mr. Ji has to arrange future work.
The announcement has been released.
The lawyer has gone
to the police station
to meet with the relevant officers.
Qiao Yi left the launch on the spot.
He didn't even tell me.
Li Ang told me
that he was with Qiao Yi.
And I didn't have to worry.
He said he would talk to Qiao Yi
about the concert thing.
So I came back.
Do you want to go home to rest?
I can tell them
you haven't come back.
No need.
I'll join you at the meeting.
Let's go.
I have read your report.
(Xing Yi Media)
You're working really hard. Very good.
But the biggest problem
is how we should tell the truth
to the public.
We have released
an official announcement,
yet the situation is not getting better.
That's how public opinion
flows now.
We have to take out solid evidence.
Yeah.
We need enough evidence
to prove that
we took the initiative to cut off
from Extreme Impala
before the incident happened.
Like
a lawyer's letter to them or whatnot.
A lawyer's letter?
Tian, what's wrong?
When I checked the gifts and letters
to Qiao Yi from his fans,
I saw Extreme Impala
using Yi's photos
as their publicity picture.
So I forwarded it to our attorney.
Did you seriously read
those letters from fans?
Yeah.
As his executive agent,
checking his fan letters,
choosing some to reply,
and collecting opinions,
these are what I should do, right?
You have done a good job!
Kevin,
call our attorney
to see if we have sent any letters
or released any announcements
about that picture.
OK. I'll call him right away.
OK.
Mr. Ji,
the attorney said
we released an announcement,
but he suggested
we find out the original letter.
Original letter.
Original.
I'll go find it.
You continue this meeting.
Zhou Tian.
What are you waiting for?
There are over ten thousand
fan letters.
Join her to find it.
You're not leaving until it's found.
This is so difficult.
I don't think I can do this
in my whole life.
Yi,
how can you write
such excellent stories?
Because I like it.
You can only achieve
when you like what you're doing.
That's also what my mom said.
Yi,
since you like writing so much,
why do you refuse
to launch the new book?
It's too complicated.
I don't think I can explain this
to you in a few words.
If you like my book,
I'll bring my new book
to you later.
But
I am not the only one
who's expecting your new book.
Every time
when you launch a new book,
your stories warm me
and so many others up.
Your stories
even moved my mom.
Am I right, Ang?
Totally.
Qiao Yi's story
can always bring light
to people
at their saddest
or worst moments.
The sunshine on a winter night?
Am I?
I didn't tell you
for fear that you might get too cocky.
When am I even cocky?
Totally nonsense.
I get it now.
I was being so self-willed
that I easily canceled the book launch.
Song,
you're right.
I will write
as long as there is one person
who can feel the warmth and sunshine
from the joys and sorrows of my books.
Which means you still will
launch the new book?
Of course.
And I'm turning the royalties
for copyright into a charity fund.
Thank you, Yi.
Thank you.
(Eat this after you wake up.)
Why did he join me in finding it?
(Xing Yi Media)
(I didn't expect this crocodile)
(would look)
(this innocent one day.)
(Why do I feel)
(he's kinda cute?)
(He has long eyelashes.)
(Did he lengthen them?)
(His nose, ear, and mouth.)
(He's actually cute)
(if I look at him carefully.)
(Not inferior to Qiao Yi at all.)
(Wait. His lips are too thin.)
What were you doing?
I was not doing anything.
Were you trying to steal a kiss?
Who would try to kiss you?
Nonsense.
We were so close.
You would have kissed me
if I opened my eyes one second later.
Y-You are not very clear
since you just woke up.
Go back to sleep.
♪Baby sleep, gently sleep♪
Stop.
I now know
why Qiuqiu can't sleep
at night.
Stop.
I have found it.
Then...
Where are the others?
It's basically settled.
They all went home.
So why are you here?
You were sleeping.
Where is Ms. Jiang?
Did she leave?
You seem
to care about her a lot.
What? Why?
It's just that
you two are really close.
You always come
and leave together.
It's just a question
out of curiosity.
Are you
jealous of her?
I said you are not clear.
Wait.
Jiang Hanyi and I
have known each other since childhood.
After my parents died,
half of my life
was spent at her home.
She
and her parents
treat Nian and me
like family.
So to me,
she is also a family.
She's like my other sister
besides Nian.
W-Why did you say these to me?
It has nothing to do with me.
Sounds so ridiculous.
Zhou Tian,
I did make mistakes.
I want to apologize to you.
Apologize?
Too late!
Can we
restart this?
I'll prove to you
that I have learned
from my mistakes.
Nite.
(I did make mistakes.)
(I want to apologize to you.)
(Apologize?)
(Too late!)
(Can we)
(restart this?)
(I'll prove to you)
(that I have learned)
(from my mistakes.)
I'm so sleepy,
but why can't I fall asleep?
It's all his fault.
This is my second
sleepless night these days.
(New Friends, 1003, Start Again?)
(He appears when I think of him.)
(Should I accept his friend request?)
(New Friends, 1003, Start Again?)
(Miss you.)
(So corny.)
(Fine.)
(I'm not being soft-hearted.)
(It's for the sake of Qiuqiu.)
(Go Confirm Done)
(Sunday, Add to Contacts)
(Send Message Voice or Video Call)
Did you order
SSSVVVIP-only breakfast
from Kitties' Fairyland?
Yeah.
Aren't you Ji Chen's little sister?
Ji Chen has a little sister?
Why wasn't I aware of this?
When have you ever cared about him?
Are you studying
at the Juilliard School?
So you graduated?
No. I'm still a student.
Perfect.
We are looking
for a guest performer for the concert.
Why don't you give us some advice?
Me?
Really?
But I'm not professional
in the band.
You think Li Ang is?
He's not professional, either.
Music
is a matter of joy.
Come in.
♪It was raining that day♪
♪When you held me♪
♪A shooting star♪
♪Fell in my heart secretly♪
♪It found a place in your eyes♪
♪And witnessed my promise to you♪
♪Eventually♪
♪It brightened my whole universe♪
(Xia)
Hello?
(Quick! Check the trending!)
Hold on.
(Xing Yi is accused of being involved
in the scandal of Extreme Impala.)
(Reverse: Qiao Yi is also a victim.)
What's going on?
It's said that
Extreme Impala's developers
once invested in Xing Yi's project.
(What?)
(Xing Yi is accused of being involved
in the scandal of Extreme Impala.)
(Xing Yi Media)
(This news is spreading quickly.)
(Now, it has affected)
(the share price of our company.)
(Do you have any solution?)
I have asked someone to investigate
all of our external
cooperation contracts.
There isn't
any business contract
between Xing Yi and Extreme Impala.
Everything on the Internet
is a rumor.
I have asked the Legal Department
to handle this matter.
(There are many people)
(who want you to resign.)
(This rumor spreads too quickly.)
(And the comments on the Internet)
(are to your disadvantage.)
(Mr. Ji,)
(you have to respond to this matter.)
(I don't think so.)
(Before the truth comes out,)
(Mr. Ji shouldn't give any explanation)
(because very few
would believe his words.)
(Xing Yi is accused of being involved
in the scandal.)
Don't worry.
Mr. Ji can handle this matter.
If I were you,
I wouldn't be so positive.
This scandal
has a huge social effect.
It's completely different
from those showbiz affairs.
Shut up!
After I came to Xing Yi,
I changed the process
of signing the contract.
All the contracts must be signed
by the agent,
the director of department,
the CFO,
the legal personnel and me.
After signing the contract,
the Financial Department
will keep a copy of it
before it takes effect.
These are
all the contracts that I signed
after I came to Xing Yi.
Take a look at these.
You will know
whether I have anything
to do with this matter.
(But you are)
(the CEO.)
(You can follow the rules.)
(But if you want to break them,)
(I think nobody will dare to object.)
(It's said)
(that Mr. Ji is very decisive)
(in the company.)
(Now,)
(the rumors are too strong.)
(We must)
(give everyone an explanation.)
(How about this?)
(We'll select)
(an acting CEO)
(from the directors)
(before we solve this matter.)
(Mr. Chen,)
(I think you're very suitable)
(for this position.)
(Mr. Chen,)
(I agree.)
(Jiang. Just in time.)
(We're discussing)
(how to deal with Extreme Impala.)
I agree with you.
Since you all believe
that Ji Chen is the one to blame,
then he can rest for some time.
From now on,
I'll be the acting CEO
of Xing Yi.
(You?)
(Jiang,)
(you have just returned from abroad.)
(You're not familiar)
(with the domestic market
and businesses.)
I'm also a director of the company.
As the CEO,
I don't have to be good at everything.
All the professional matters
will be handled
by more professional employees.
Mr. Chen,
are you professional enough
to deal with everything?
Ji Chen.
Any objection?
Since this is the group's decision,
I won't have any objection.
It is a group's decision, of course.
Okay. That's settled, then.
The meeting is over.
Please continue your work.
Thank you.
Are you serious?
It's better for me to become the CEO
than the others.
You're acting as if this company
is yours.
I...
You...
I help with your relationship,
and now I even have to worry
about your career.
How can you even say that?
You're so ungrateful.
I'm sad.
But, seriously,
how should we deal with this?
We should talk about it.
I do have
a plan.
But I need to borrow your authority.
I love it when you have a plan.
Please tell us, Mr. Ji.
Well, this incident
is not that complicated.
We can...
Mr. Ji is suspended!
The announcement is just released.
What?
(Ji Chen will be suspended.
A director will take his position.)
How could it be?
(Kevin:
The announcement of the temporary.)
(The announcement
of the temporary meeting.)
(Ji Chen has been suspended.)
(Director Jiang Hanyi
has become the new CEO of Xing Yi.)
(Xing Yi Media)
Have you read the email?
I hold this temporary meeting
to officially explain the situation
and arrange the following work
for everyone.
We...
Ms. Jiang,
I have a question
about the company's decision.
When the Extreme Impala thing
just started,
Mr. Ji hadn't become the CEO yet.
Why does he have to be suspended
when this incident broke out?
Now, I am
the CEO of Xing Yi.
I'm your superior.
I don't have to explain
any of my decisions to you.
If you have any objections,
you're free to resign anytime.
Zhou Tian,
sit down.
I'm trying to...
I know.
Thank you. Please sit down.
(Seriously?)
(I'm trying to help you,)
(but you're in favor of her?)
(Nevermind.)
(I'm nobody to you.)
Let's continue.
The group wants us
to minimize the negative effect.
The share price can't be affected.
Now, I'll talk about the strategy.
The plan for crisis management...
(Xing Yi Media)
(Meeting Room)
That's all for today's meeting.
You are dismissed.
Mr. Ji.
I think
you shouldn't leave the company
before the truth comes out.
I have been suspended.
But this matter
has nothing to do with you.
It had nothing to do with me.
But now,
I'm the CEO of Xing Yi.
I have to be responsible
for all the projects of Xing Yi,
including this one.
I have to bear the consequence.
That's why
we have to find out the truth!
Even if you're leaving,
you can't leave like this.
I know you worry about me,
but Jiang Hanyi
is handling this matter now.
Worry?
I only seek justice.
Do you remember
what I told you
when Qiao Yi was in trouble?
You have to be responsible
for your position.
I don't care. You can't leave.
(She's so cute)
(when she worries about me.)
All right.
Actually, this matter...
Kindly reminder.
This is my office now.
Ms. Jiang,
you are just in time.
Didn't you say during the meeting
that Mr. Ji still needs to assist
with your daily work?
So, I think
he shouldn't leave for now.
But
this office belongs to the CEO.
He has no authority
to stay here anymore.
Ji Chen,
I have to follow the rules.
I hope you will understand.
Zhou Tian,
let's get out of here.
Besides,
it's not allowed to gossip
during working hours.
This rule also applies
to suspended employees.
How was it?
She was so protective of you.
Did you enjoy it?
You're welcome!
Where are you going?
Here.
Here?
From now on,
I'll be seated here.
This is my desk.
Excuse me!
Excuse me. Put it here.
Mr. Ji,
are you joking?
Do I look joking?
By the way,
I have just been suspended.
You don't need to call me Mr. Ji.
Call me Ji Chen.
Ji... Chen.
If you feel weird
about calling me by my full name,
you can also call me
Chen.
I can't believe you're
still in the mood for jokes.
Ji Chen!
Yi!
Ji Chen.
Ji Chen? Have you transformed?
Yi.
Are you looking for Ji Chen?
But now,
I am the CEO.
It's not a joke.
Ji Chen has indeed been replaced.
I don't know you.
Bye.
Zhou Tian,
I read the announcement.
Ji Chen
has indeed been suspended.
You...
W-Why are you sitting here?
What's wrong?
What do you want?
I do want something.
I want to add a program
about my new book
to Li Ang's concert.
We decided to do charity together.
No problem.
But...
but you're not
the CEO anymore.
You're still my agent, though.
I can count on you, right?
Li Ang also works in our company.
It will benefit both of you
if you can attend his concert.
The company won't reject your request
even though I'm not the CEO.
Okay. That's settled, then.
Zhou Tian,
keep an eye on him.
Ji Chen
had a rather successful career.
He has never suffered
so much.
He might seem
very calm right now,
but his heart
is badly injured.
I know this kind of man
the best.
He does seem weird.
Bye.
Ji...
Ji Chen.
Do you want to go home and rest?
Remember what you said?
I need to stay here
before the truth comes out.
I can't leave.
Then go to investigate.
Don't just sit here
and throw paper airplanes.
I'm not
the CEO anymore.
How can I find out the truth?
Besides,
I have never been this free
ever since I lied for a few months
as a baby after I was born.
Since you don't want to see me,
I'll leave right away.
I...
I didn't mean that.
What?
Chen is suspended?
Jiang Hanyi did this to him?
Huh! Jiang Hanyi!
I treated her as my family!
How could she do this to Chen?
I thought
she could be my sister-in-law!
I mean... in the past.
That's not important.
The point is,
Chen is so proud.
And this is so huge a blow.
Where is he?
This morning, I asked him
whether he wanted to go home and rest,
and I said he had nothing to do.
Then, he went home.
He must feel depressed
after you talked to him.
Chen is always a busy guy,
and he never allows himself to be free.
Yet you said he had nothing to do.
Will he commit suicide?
I don't think so.
He tries so hard to live a healthy life,
so he must be afraid of death.
But,
I think he's quite weird.
He seems
very normal,
but in fact,
he's deeply injured.
Nian called me just now.
She asked me
why I suspended you.
Zhou Tian must have told her.
That's exactly what I expected.
You're a professional in toying
with women's hearts.
You are the wise one.
You used me to suspend you,
so the mastermind behind it
will be off guard.
Then, you can clear them all.
As for me,
I can help improve your relationship
with Zhou Tian.
Impressive!
♪It was raining that day
when you held me♪
♪A shooting star
fell in my heart secretly♪
♪It found a place in your eyes
and witnessed my promise to you♪
♪Eventually,
it brightened my whole universe♪
♪And you walked into my life♪
♪But we've missed out on so much♪
♪We tried so hard
to engrave each other's face♪
♪I made up my mind
to drift with you all my life♪
♪But you remained deadly silent♪
♪You weren't sure about our life♪
♪No worries.
I decided to be your support♪
♪I'll make the future ahead
more promising♪
♪It was raining that day
when you held me♪
♪A shooting star
fell in my heart secretly♪
♪It found a place in your eyes
and witnessed my promise to you♪
♪Eventually,
it brightened my whole universe♪
♪I've spent my entire life to find you♪
♪I've never been in deep love before♪
♪Love you made me a better self♪
♪I'll be a shooting star
and shine for you forever♪
♪Shine♪
♪It was raining that day
when you held me♪
♪A shooting star
fell in my heart secretly♪
♪It found a place in your eyes
and witnessed my promise to you♪
♪Eventually,
it brightened my whole universe♪
♪I've spent my entire life to find you♪
♪I've never been in deep love before♪
♪Love you made me a better self♪
♪I'll be a shooting star
and shine for you forever♪
♪Shine♪