(Presented by WeTV)
♪I'm thinking of you again somehow♪
♪The happiness and sorrow♪
♪Keep replaying in my mind♪
♪I thought I could love you
until eternity♪
♪I have never stopped♪
♪Missing you♪
♪I can't stop♪
♪Missing your tenderness♪
♪I'll always be waiting♪
♪I'll be there waiting for you♪
♪For no reason at all♪
♪I only want us to be together♪
♪I'll be there waiting for you♪
♪Until the end of my life♪
♪All I need is you♪
♪I'm always missing you♪
=Accidentally Meow On You=
=Episode 9=
Ji Chen, I've decided.
You don't have to go with me.
I will be a little more comfortable.
Hello, Hao?
(Hello, Tian.)
I've got the training center
you asked for.
It's the one we used to visit
every year.
You mean the one on the coast?
(Yeah.)
That one is really nice.
But about the date,
their schedule is tight.
Only five days of vacancy this month.
If we miss it,
you'll have to wait until next month.
Hang on.
I'll ask about it.
Mr. Ji,
the training center
has only five days of the vacancy.
About our work schedule...
It fits.
Hao,
please book the center for me.
Yeah.
You wanna go with us?
Of course, yes.
You can be our coach.
Remember to give us a discount.
OK.
Bye.
(He was asking)
(about the confession things.)
(And now he is booking
the training center for Tian?)
(What on earth is going on?)
Mr. Ji,
Yi,
I'll go contact
and prepare for the training center.
I'll excuse myself then.
Hold on.
On second thought,
I should go with you
to experience the athlete's life.
But you said you wouldn't go.
I'm your agent.
Of course, I should go with you.
You're the president of Xing Yi.
And you're the pillar of Xing Yi.
Xing Yi has more than one pillar.
They have their agents.
They don't need me.
But they don't make such requests
to their agents.
Someone has to try tomato first.
That someone doesn't have to.
You're not used to being turned down.
I'm starting to get used to it.
Anyway, I've made up my mind.
It's settled.
I'll go with you.
If you have any requests, shoot.
(How can I make him less annoying?)
(Oh!)
(I heard he hates sports)
(and never chooses to exercise himself.)
(Got it.)
I have only one request.
You have to experience
whatever I experience.
If you can't make it,
then I don't have to do it.
Hao,
thank you for specially coming
and setting out with us.
You can wait
at the training center, actually.
It's OK.
You don't have to thank me.
You haven't gone there for a while.
I'm afraid you have forgotten the route.
How is it possible?
We've been going there
every year since we were kids.
I can get there with my eyes closed.
Zhou Tian,
check the schedule with me.
Mr. Ji,
I've sent the schedule
to your phone.
Double check, double insurance.
You two look cute
in lovers' clothes.
Not lovers' clothes.
It's the sportswear
from my old sports team.
It's about time. Get in the car.
Then Yi and Mr. Ji share a ride.
I'll share a ride with Hao.
Qiao Yi,
you stay with Zhang Hao.
You can talk about his experience
on the way there.
Let's go.
Sir, we can set out now.
(Please look after Qiuqiu these days.)
(Mute Mode)
(Sunday: Please look after Qiuqiu
these days. Thanks.)
(1003:
Rest assured. I've got it all set up.)
(Your priority these days)
(is to look after the cat.)
(Don't worry, Mr. Ji.)
(Kevin: Don't worry, Mr. Ji.)
(I'll look after her)
(just as I look after you.)
These two, please.
Here we are.
When Zhou Tian and I
trained here when we were young,
the conditions here were much worse.
The whole resort was built
in recent years.
For example, this villa.
One single room on the first floor.
Two rooms on the second floor.
The third floor has a wide view.
And you can see the sea there.
How will you allocate rooms?
I'll take the third floor.
That room
is meant for you.
I-I surely know.
I was just trying
to emphasize our tacit understanding.
Tian, which room do you want?
I'll take a room on the second floor.
It's close
to both the first and third floors.
I'll also stay on the second floor.
(Is there anything special
about the second floor?)
(They both want it.)
You both want a second-floor room?
Then you two stay on the second floor.
I'll stay on the first floor.
You choose first.
It's OK. After you.
This one, then.
By the way,
all who enter the center
must have a physical examination.
A nurse will come later.
Now the training center that
everyone must have
a physical examination.
Why do I need a blood test?
It's to check your body's indicators.
Very simple.
Look how poised Mr. Ji is.
Mr. Ji!
(I didn't expect)
(such a strong person)
(to have such a weakness.)
(Somehow,)
(I feel him cute.)
He should be fine.
I'll go prepare lunch.
I thought
he was acting,
but it turned out
to be his needle sickness.
So fragile.
That is not correct.
Needle sickness
is a common physiological phenomenon,
just like car sickness and seasickness.
It's not because of being fragile.
Mr. Ji,
you're awake.
You are being too loud.
Even a dead will wake up.
Mr. Ji,
do you know about your needle sickness?
I do. So what?
You do?
Why didn't you tell us?
You don't have to be embarrassed.
Today,
if it weren't for Hao,
you would have hit your head
on the ground.
Who can take the blame?
My needle sickness
doesn't attack every time.
It depends on my mood.
Sounds creepy.
I'm too full.
Let's go for a walk.
What about you, Mr. Ji and Yi?
The blood's concentration in the stomach
after eating aids digestion.
Why do you have to make it spread
to your limbs?
Ji Chen stays, so I stay.
(Tian,)
(do you remember this tree?)
It's what used
to record our heights.
Yeah.
You remember it.
These are mine.
And these are yours.
You haven't come for a long time.
About four or five years.
Wanna record your new height?
Yeah.
Stand straight.
Seems you're shorter.
How is it possible?
See?
Hand away.
You clearly faked this mark just now.
Hao,
since when did you be scheming?
Silly girl.
I was just joking with you.
Mr. Ji,
what are you doing?
This tree
is embracing its death.
The outlet in my room
doesn't work well.
Can I try yours?
(I will have)
(at most 20 rounds every day)
(and 16 sets of training.)
(In June 2016,)
(in order to adapt to)
(the climate in Europe early,)
(he went back and forth between Dali)
(in Yunnan and Three Gorges in Hubei)
(for cross-country training.)
(The daily overload of training)
(on the high-altitude track in Dali)
(made Yu Lei feel...)
Thank you.
Thank me?
I fainted
at the blood test.
She said you caught me.
Just a lift of the finger.
So, you two have known each other
since childhood?
Yeah.
We were neighbors.
Our fathers worked together.
I entered the Youth Sports School
two years earlier than her.
And we came here together.
During these years,
she spent more time with me
than with her parents.
You've been training there
since you were kids?
Yep.
We came to train here every year.
Closed training.
So rough.
I remember it
when we came here the first time.
Tian ran out at night
because of being homesick.
We looked everywhere for her.
I found her on a nearby beach,
crying there alone.
(She saw me)
(and jumped into my arms.)
(My shirt got soaked that night.)
Oh, right.
One more thing.
She refused to get up every winter.
I had to drag her out of bed every time.
I would dress her,
and she would nod
for another while.
You were always this close?
I said it.
She spent more time with me
than with her parents.
No one knows each other better
than we do.
Yeah.
You are like siblings.
Completely real siblings.
Sort of.
My mom always believes
she is my family.
I also believe so.
We'll never be separated in this life.
(Sunday:
Are you awake?)
(I miss Qiuqiu a bit.)
(Can I see her now?)
(Mr. Ji)
Hello, Mr. Ji.
OK.
No problem.
I'll get it now.
Qiuqiu?
I can just take a random track.
Do you have to do it this seriously?
You have to experience it
to know the character.
There are a lot of rough trails
in cross-country running.
We'll climb obstacles,
run through jungles, cross ditches,
and even cross a single-plank bridge.
(This looks like an easy route.)
(Is it really)
(a normal training route?)
You are a beginner.
You have to start at the junior track.
Take your time.
The environment is complicated here.
Be careful, everyone.
Don't get hurt.
Zhou Tian,
take a GoPro.
Record Qiao Yi some writing material.
OK.
Qiao Yi,
take one with you.
Zhou Tian is never tired from running.
How does she make it?
She was an athlete after all.
Look.
How beautiful.
A perfect couple.
Right, Mr. Ji?
No.
They grew up together
and fit each other
perfectly in sports.
I heard eighty percent
of childhood sweethearts
turn into couples in the end.
That's nonsense.
Perhaps,
they don't see each other now,
but they will approach
each other eventually.
This is the magic of love.
Intimacy, see?
I don't understand Zhou Tian.
She doesn't have to work
as an assistant in Xing Yi.
Zhang Hao's assistant is a better job.
She can look after him
and run with him during training.
What a happy family.
So beautiful.
Xing Yi is a subsidiary
of Ansheng Group,
one of the top ten in the world,
and has the strongest
cultural brokerage business in China.
We...
I didn't say Xing Yi was not good.
Zhou Tian
is the most promising employee.
How can she be Zhang Hao's assistant?
I was just saying.
You don't have to be triggered.
Hurry up.
Or we won't finish it before dark.
Ji Chen!
Zhou Tian, watch out.
Thanks for your helping hand.
It's OK.
Zhou Tian,
the rest stop is just ahead.
Let's sprint for it.
All right.
(Mountain Trail Running Rest Stop)
I'm drained.
I can't run anymore.
Let's take a break.
OK.
Thank you, Hao.
Mr. Ji, keep it to yourself.
You are still fast
though you haven't run in a long time.
Come on. You slowed down for me.
I promise I didn't.
You're all hungry, right?
I'll get us some supplies
to regain strength.
Where's Qiao Yi?
I didn't see him.
I thought he was with you
running behind?
I'm not his attendant.
He...
It could't be that he ran alone
and got lost, right?
Hao, phone.
The terrain in the mountains is complex.
Not easy to navigate here.
No answer.
Calm down.
Let's go find him.
OK.
Qiao Yi.
- Qiao Yi.
- Yi.
Qiao Yi.
Yi.
Hi.
Excuse me.
Have you
seen a guy
who doesn't look like an athlete
in a rose jacket
instead of a straitjacket?
No.
Thanks, anyway.
We're in the mountains.
The passing players all said
they hadn't seen Qiao Yi.
I think we need to split up.
Then let's split up.
We two will go east.
And you go west.
I mean, I'm a stranger here.
If
you are not worried I may get lost,
I can go alone.
OK.
Let's split up.
No matter whether we find him or not,
we have to get out of here before dark.
After that, we can call the police.
OK.
Yi.
Qiao Yi.
Mr. Ji,
can you please speed up?
Easy.
There's a GPS on Qiao Yi's GoPro.
I can just check it.
Why didn't you say this earlier?
I forgot it.
My boss has short memories.
Let me see.
(Device, Qiao Yi's GoPro)
Not far away from us.
He should be...
He should be over there.
Left or right?
Right or left?
Whatever.
I'll take the left.
The ancients respected the left.
Yeah. To the left.
Qiao Yi.
But he should be here.
Where?
Qiao Yi's hat!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
So weird.
He should be here.
GoPro.
He lost it halfway.
It's a large forest.
And so many forks here.
He can be lost in the forest.
Let's go find him.
Easy.
Qiao Yi.
Yi.
I must be a genius.
Cross-country race.
Outdoor positioning ability.
I'm completely a human GPS myself.
Qiao Yi.
Yi.
Mr. Ji,
did you plan this?
What did I plan?
I got it.
You are making use of this incident
to teach Qiao Yi a lesson.
Am I right?
Why would I make use of danger
which threatens his life?
I believe you.
But we really need to find him
as soon as possible.
He'll be in danger
when it gets dark.
Let's find shelter first.
Over there.
What should I do?
It's a cliff.
Rain in the mountains comes heavily,
but it won't last long.
I'm fine with it.
I'm not fine with it.
If you get sick,
I'll have to...
We'll have to take care of you.
I haven't listened for rain
in the mountains for a long time.
Did you often leave
for the mountain when raining
instead of staying at home?
When I was young,
my parents ran a farm
in the mountains.
When I was back home on vacation,
I would stay a few days
in the mountains.
I would run up the mountain
even though it rained.
When it rains in summer,
the stream will rise.
The dragonflies are not afraid
of getting their wings soaked.
They linger on the water's surface.
Like everything slows down.
Sounds quite interesting.
I never needed an air conditioner
before I joined
the Youth Sports School.
It was pleasantly cool in the summer
when living in the mountains.
Open my window,
and the wind would blow in.
The longan tree from the next yard
reached into our yard.
I could pick some to eat
if I opened the second-floor window.
That kind of life is something
that people like you who live in cities
will never experience.
Not everyone can survive hardships
as you do.
Exquisite life is also needed.
In case that accident may happen.
Mr. Ji,
you cherish your body so much.
And you take so many pills.
Are you born
with some terminal illness?
Your phone is ringing.
Hello, Hao?
OK.
I see.
Got it.
We'll be right back.
He found Qiao Yi.
Great.
It stops.
Keep it.
It's cold after the rain.
I don't need it.
You have a terminal illness.
You keep it.
You have it.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just sprained my ankle.
Sit down. Let me check it.
You don't have to. I'm OK.
Just a sprain. Not serious.
Yeah, I said it.
Just a minor injury.
I got a lot of that
when I was under training.
What's the story of this scar?
I was injured
and had surgery.
So I couldn't do
long-distance running again.
Let's go.
Stay still.
Mr. Ji,
are you Doraemon?
There are so many things in your bag.
Just my habit.
To prevent from incident coming.
And to get myself braced.
Will you get tired?
My parents died young.
And I had to take care of my sister.
So I have to take more
into my consideration.
When I'm needed,
I can offer more help to people I love.
Thank you, Mr. Ji.
I'll carry you back.
No, no.
No need.
I can walk by myself.
Let's hurry back.
Maybe
it will rain again.
You sprained your ankle.
You shouldn't walk.
I'll carry you on my back.
Come.
On my back.
Be careful.
I will.
(Be careful.)
(Training Center)
Zhou Tian,
where have you been?
It's so late now.
We...
Went to find you.
Where did you go?
I was lost.
I stopped
to catch the beautiful scenery.
You were gone when I resumed.
Thank goodness Zhang Hao found me.
What about you two?
We were looking for you.
Can you please
be less self-centered?
Do you know she got hurt
when looking for you?
Who got hurt?
It's OK.
I just accidentally sprained my ankle.
It can be serious.
How is it now? Let me see.
I-I can do...
Don't move.
Zhou Tian,
sorry.
I didn't mean to get lost.
Sorry.
It's OK. I'm fine.
It's a work injury.
I'll be paid for that.
You're fine?
Look at your ankle.
How swollen it is.
Not that swollen.
Ji Chen,
I think
you're being overstrained.
Zhou Tian,
why are you blushing?
You two couldn't have...
I blame the lights.
Leave me alone.
I can make it myself.
Do you think
they are weird?
♪It was raining that day
when you held me♪
♪A shooting star
fell in my heart secretly♪
♪It found a place in your eyes
and witnessed my promise to you♪
♪Eventually,
it brightened my whole universe♪
♪And you walked into my life♪
♪But we've missed out on so much♪
♪We tried so hard
to engrave each other's face♪
♪I made up my mind
to drift with you all my life♪
♪But you remained deadly silent♪
♪You weren't sure about our life♪
♪No worries.
I decided to be your support♪
♪I'll make the future ahead
more promising♪
♪It was raining that day
when you held me♪
♪A shooting star
fell in my heart secretly♪
♪It found a place in your eyes
and witnessed my promise to you♪
♪Eventually,
it brightened my whole universe♪
♪I've spent my entire life to find you♪
♪I've never been in deep love before♪
♪Love you made me a better self♪
♪I'll be a shooting star
and shine for you forever♪
♪Shine♪
♪It was raining that day
when you held me♪
♪A shooting star
fell in my heart secretly♪
♪It found a place in your eyes
and witnessed my promise to you♪
♪Eventually,
it brightened my whole universe♪
♪I've spent my entire life to find you♪
♪I've never been in deep love before♪
♪Love you made me a better self♪
♪I'll be a shooting star
and shine for you forever♪
♪Shine♪