I like you.
I like you with him.
I hope it won't be
a bad relationship this time.
I mean it.
Thanks.
Later.
Mr. On is outside.
You go first.
Bye.
You held me back
to push me away even farther.
Did you hurt your foot?
It's nothing. I wore new shoes...
Those shoes are so open.
How did they hurt your heel?
Right?
Did the shoot go well?
Yes. We have just the last shoot left.
I wish it would end quickly.
Why?
So you'd stop calling me "Mr. On."
How long will I be "Mr. On"?
What do you want me to call you?
I don't know.
I haven't really thought about it.
Since you call me "Woo-yeon."
should I do the same
and call you "Joon-soo"?
Or "sweetie," for simplicity sake?
Or should I call you my prince?
You seem to like that a lot.
Why are guys always so into titles?
We like it because the person
we like is calling us that.
You say you don't want to be "Mr. On."
You're full of contradictions.
Go inside. It's late.
Look at you changing the subject.
Good night.
Bye.
Mom.
Did you hang this up here?
That's right. Clean up a little.
Stop shoving them in a corner
and buying more.
I came here to give you this.
I don't need this.
I lost the other side too.
I was going to throw it out.
It took a lot to get back to you,
so don't throw it out.
Who knows? The other side
might be somewhere too.
It really came back to me.
(All these photos were telling me)
(that I had countless opportunities.)
(That all of those opportunities)
(turned into regrets.)
=Episode 8: Opportunities Lost
Become Regrets=
(Prosecutor Han Jin-ju)
(Victim)
(I went to the hospital.)
(Send me the receipt.)
(Send me your account number.)
(Can't you pay me in person?)
What's his problem?
Are you a fugitive?
Do you have bad credit?
Do you not have a bank account?
This is my ID,
my school ID,
and my driver's license.
You can check with the police
if you don't trust me.
Then why did you want it in person?
That way
I can see you.
I really didn't get hurt,
but you said to contact you
after I go to the hospital.
That's why I went and got a check-up.
I wondered what I should say
so that I could see you again.
I thought long and hard about it.
Ever since I first saw you,
I thought about you
for an entire month.
May I
keep contacting you?
A Seoul University student? He's younger?
Is he cute?
Yes.
He's in!
How is he in so quickly?
Young, handsome, and smart.
Someone like that is always a good catch.
Stop being so loud.
Are you sure he's not a swindler?
Just look at her. How can this face
be on his mind for a month?
Her face isn't something that would
glimmer in someone's eyes.
Are you sure it's not a pyramid scheme
or a religious group?
All right, all right.
I just find it strange.
But if he's still a student,
I guess you might feel pressured.
Why? What?
I didn't do anything yet.
Why would he feel pressured?
You're a prosecutor.
Do men find women who have
better jobs hard to approach?
Do you?
It's not about men or women.
If the other person is distinguished,
anyone would feel discouraged and small.
It's the same for everyone.
He doesn't know.
- Did you say I don't know?
- No.
Hey.
- Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
It was a mistake, right?
I wouldn't say it was a mistake.
I was only trying to tell you
that this seat isn't for you.
- Gosh. Hello.
- Hello.
You're here, Mr. On.
Are you all well? Are you okay?
Are you a gambler?
Why couldn't you just tell me?
Why are your hands faster than your mouth?
I'm sorry.
But you just said it's okay.
Why do you always build up to anger?
Hey, just accept it.
He's always angry.
Be quiet.
He's so scary.
Sit here.
What were you talking about?
Just this and that.
A Seoul National University student
who is young and handsome
is chasing her around saying he likes her.
That's good news.
(Tonight)
- Thank you. Please visit again.
- Bye.
Take care.
Right. Do you guys remember
our teacher, Ki-an?
- The teacher who managed our club.
- What about him?
I met him recently.
His wife is the director of an orphanage.
He retired and is managing
the orphanage with her.
He says he needs volunteers,
so I decided to go help him on Saturday.
I see. That's pretty cool.
Right? That's why I was going
to ask you guys to join.
Do you see this?
There's not a drop of moisture,
so it's dry, tough, and hard.
This is what I'm like.
An office-worker has no humanity
left in them.
I think I kind of understand
since you look like a squid.
- Hey.
- What?
Why are all of you always ready
to throw things at me?
- Anyway, I'm not going.
- No, no.
I already told him, so you all have to go.
- Hey!
- What?
Would you like to join us too?
Don't bother Joon-soo.
I'll go too.
Amazing.
It's okay. You don't have to go.
I'm going because I want to.
I want to see you.
How sweet.
- We're all going together, okay?
- Okay.
What time on Saturday?
I think we can meet at around 11 a.m.
I look good
although you see me often, right?
Even guys think I'm handsome.
You're right.
We're seeing each other too often.
Whenever I try to see Woo-yeon,
you're always there too.
Kind of like an unwanted free gift.
I believe you're the unwanted free gift
that came
with my relationship with Woo-yeon.
Do you know why people
categorize relationships?
So that you act
within the boundaries of that category.
Just be her friend.
Her boyfriend's position is taken.
- What if I don't want to?
- If you don't want that either,
you can become nothing.
Her boyfriend's position is taken,
and if you don't want to be her friend,
there isn't anything else you can do.
So just disappear from her sight.
I guess you're not confident.
- Of course, I am.
- It looks like you're not.
If you're so confident,
why are you telling me to disappear?
Because you're shameless.
What?
You made her stand
behind your back for ten years,
and now you're idling around her
because you have feelings for her.
Isn't that shameless of you?
I didn't have the right until now,
so I kept it in,
but I won't let it go anymore.
I have the right.
Woo-yeon is the best drinker.
No, she can't drink well.
- I already know.
- What do you know?
Right.
I should return that to you.
The thing you took off in my car.
Are you trying to make trouble?
What did I take off in your car?
It's nothing like that.
I'm talking about the shoes.
The shoes from Mr. On.
Mr. On. Please don't misunderstand.
I won't misunderstand.
My glass is empty.
- Should I pour you some?
- Yes, thank you.
Okay.
Did you have to talk about
the shoes there?
(Tonight)
And in that way?
No matter how many times you reject me
and embarrass me in front of others,
I'm okay with it.
But don't turn him into a fool too.
Who are you to hurt him?
Is he that great?
Is he that precious to you?
More than yourself?
Yes. He's precious to me.
- You're too easy.
- What? "Easy"?
How could you cherish something else
more than yourself so fast?
Sure. I'm easy.
I'm an easy person.
That's why I clung onto someone like you
for ten years.
Did you want to bring that up this badly?
- I didn't mean that.
- You asked if you're bad, right?
Yes, you're bad.
You're nasty to your bones.
You ignore everyone else's feelings,
and you don't know how to be considerate.
You're a selfish jerk.
That's why
you're always so lonely.
You must be upset.
We had to walk a lot to shoot,
and the shoes were new
so they were hurting my feet...
You don't have to explain.
I know you didn't do it on purpose.
I don't want to do anything
to be sorry about,
but I keep on having to apologize.
Everything is fine
because it's you.
Thank you.
No, not the big street.
There's an alley beside it.
Just stay there. I'll come.
- Just leave.
- You should stop acting pitiful and leave.
Go home and sleep.
When you wake up, stop bothering Woo-yeon.
Ten years out of 28.
She liked you
for over a third of her life.
When she got over those feelings,
she had to be strong.
It would've been difficult.
Don't ignore that.
(Tonight)
(Choi Won-jung's Solo Exhibition)
As for this piece,
I was focusing on the volume in this part.
- Especially with the leaves.
- Yes.
Do you see it?
This time, your artwork has changed.
Yes, it has.
There's so much depth to it.
Son.
What happened to your hand?
Did you get hurt?
- Yes.
- You should be careful.
Is everything going well?
Yes.
Are you seeing anyone?
No?
- No.
- Why not?
Do you not like anyone?
You do.
Mom.
Are you just friends with Dad now?
I heard you used to love each other a lot.
He still...
likes you.
Son.
Do you know what's most important
in long-term relationships?
Memories.
We have many good memories,
but the painful memories are deeper.
I don't think I can
overcome those memories.
What a coincidence running into you here.
I know.
What a coincidence.
Hey.
- About that day...
- You're sorry?
No, I...
Sorry for being so harsh?
What does your cochlea look like,
that you hear me so well?
I told you, it's pretty.
For the final shoot, I wanted to capture
being loved even after being abandoned.
A train track on which
the train doesn't go.
An amusement park that has been shut down.
Things for which time has stopped.
I don't know.
That's from the perspective of the ones
who abandoned them.
For those locations,
it's neglect and abandonment.
There was a reason.
They were no longer useful.
There is always a reason for abandonment.
They consider it to be useless,
they got sick of it,
or it hurt them.
Beautifying abandonment,
calling it fond memories,
is a right belonging solely
to the abandoner.
The ones that were abandoned
probably still hurt.
Was that memory nice for you?
To me, that memory
hurts.
What?
Sorry.
For what?
For hurting you.
For mistreating you.
Everything.
Out of nowhere?
Have you finally matured?
Right?
If I were going to mature
out of nowhere like this,
I should've matured sooner.
They say people suddenly mature
right before they die.
But I'm not worried about you.
They say you live long
if people curse at you.
So you'll live a long life for sure.
Don't fall from now on.
(Prosecutor Han Jin-ju)
(Do you want to watch a movie tonight?)
What's wrong?
He wants to watch a movie.
Sorry?
He asked me to watch a movie.
What movie is it, that you're so jumpy?
Hello?
Yes. I was going to send you the proposal.
No. There's no need anymore.
Pardon?
I'd like to know
why I suddenly lost the opportunity.
The person who will be
working on it in your place
is Calligrapher Han Jin Suk.
You got someone famous.
I assume that answered your question
as to why you lost the project.
He has a lot of experience,
and he is very close to the director.
I had no reason to insist we go with you.
You'll get more opportunities.
Connections create experience,
and that experience adds up
and brings fame.
And that turns around
to create connections.
That's how the world will run.
It's a never-ending cycle.
There's no room for a small chick like me
to break in.
But you're still young,
so don't be too anxious.
It's not about age.
Moving forward is hope
and stopping is despair.
I believe anxious hope
is better than comfortable despair.
That's why I can't stop
my anxiety.
(Wind Films)
Cry. I won't look.
I'm not crying.
I'm not a child.
I'm glad.
Sure. This is how I live.
Mock if you want.
Why would I mock you?
You must really think I'm a demon.
Here.
Why are you giving me that?
You must really think I'm a child.
When life is bitter,
you should eat something sweet.
Come pick up your shoes later.
Okay.
Come at night. In time for dinner.
Do you have any ideas
for Lee Do Kyung's new book event?
It's a trend on social media
to show pictures of their rooms
or their house right now.
Following that line of thought,
what if people share pictures
of their study or bookcase and we pick...
Just be her friend.
Her boyfriend's position is taken.
I guess you're not confident.
I like it.
It'll be good marketing for the new book.
I agree. That's not bad.
What do you think, Mr. On?
Mr. On. What do you think
about the event
for Lee Do Kyung's new book?
Sharing bookcases. It sounds good.
Let's go with that.
He's good looking.
Did you wait long?
No.
Actually, I did wait a little.
I was excited, so I came early.
(He was excited?)
I'm wearing contacts for the first time,
and I bought new clothes
since it's our first date.
(Date?)
Let's go.
(Oh my gosh.)
Would candles be overdoing it?
- Eat before you go.
- That's okay.
I wasn't giving you a choice.
I didn't say, "Do you want to eat?"
I said, "Eat before you go."
You always do whatever you want.
I'm trying to grab onto you
so you won't fall ten floors down.
What will you make for me?
Seafood ramyeon.
Put in lots of seafood.
What about the noodles?
Do you like them chewy?
- Add lots of chilies.
- Take a seat.
Hello?
I see.
Okay.
I need to go down for a moment.
Someone scratched my car.
Okay.
It's past 6 p.m.
I'm your friend right now.
(CEO On Joon-soo)
I didn't say anything.
Hey. Something happened to you, didn't it?
Don't try to hide it.
You finally started dating the one
you were head over heels for...
and work is going well.
You should look like you're happy
beyond belief.
Why are you spacing out
so often these days?
Did I do that?
Yes, you did that.
You've been doing that constantly,
so just tell me. Come on.
It's normal to be nervous when I'm
holding onto something precious, right?
Yes.
Right.
But if you're always nervous,
when will you become happy?
If you're too nervous, just let it go.
It must not be yours.
I'd rather stay nervous.
You're so stubborn.
Why isn't he back?
Gosh, this won't do.
Was this the washroom?
(So if I ever take a photo of someone,)
(it would mean...)
(I like that person a lot.)
(Joon-soo)
Ouch.
Darn it.
Where did she put the band aids?
I'm home.
Why did you go through my stuff?
- Is that important right now?
- Yes, it is.
I know you gave birth to me,
but we're different.
So is my private life.
So the private life
you wanted me to respect
was this?
You're an unmarried woman.
Mom. I'm 29.
I have a boyfriend I dated for ten years.
- You're overreacting.
- I'm overreacting?
You're not like other people.
Do you know how hard I had to work
so that people
wouldn't look down on you
for being fatherless?
What if you suddenly get pregnant?
What will Hyun-jae's family think?
Can you stop talking about
me being fatherless?
Is it my fault I don't have a dad?
Did I kill him?
Who cares about that?
Why should I cower
when I didn't do anything wrong?
Mom, I want to live normally
like other people.
If you wanted to meddle,
you should've been more responsible.
Why did you let her find them?
You should've hidden them.
No, you should've swallowed them.
How can I swallow 100 of them?
You sure are a big spender.
Do I have to fight with my mom
about condoms at my age?
We'll forever be kids to our parents.
My dad still nags at me and tells me
to chew more when I eat.
I went to Grandma's on Lunar New Year's,
and she was saying that to Dad.
She told him to chew more.
Isn't it something similar?
Like a baby filter on a phone app,
our parents must have a baby filter
on their eyes
when they look at us.
I wish that were true.
What about you?
Why are you acting pitiful?
What?
There's something
Soo said to me before.
So if I ever take a photo of someone,
it would mean...
I like that person a lot.
Why were there my pictures
in his darkroom?
- Woo-yeon.
- Yes?
On your birthday,
Soo went to you.
He got into an accident.
He lost consciousness for an hour.
Why did you tell me?
It's not like I can do anything now.
Not Soo.
I'm talking about you and Mr. On.
You know this, don't you?
If you truly love someone,
you'd never falter no matter what happens.
(The person you have reached
is not available.)
(Lee Soo)
Why would you come back like that?
Who said you could?
- Hello.
Are you all well?
- Yes.
- Of course.
Sir, you should dye your hair.
You have so much grey hair.
Yes, I should.
Have you been well?
Yes. You two should get married soon.
Pardon?
It's too early for marriage.
We'll date as much as we want.
It's not good to date too long.
What's gotten into you?
You always talk about getting married.
You changed. He changed, didn't he?
He changed.
It'll be hard on Young-hee
when we get married.
I have three older sisters.
You got him under your thumb.
They say getting married is like
getting a husband and his family.
Nice to see you again.
Are you going to ignore me?
Hello.
Hey.
Sir.
You're here.
- You're here.
- Hello.
Are you well?
Of course.
It's nothing big.
I brought some school supplies.
Amazing.
You didn't have to prepare anything.
Soo, you look competent.
You're looking cool, Soo.
Yes. It's all about money.
You need to spend money to look cool.
You bought a good mix of items.
Yes. The kids are going to love it.
Hello.
- Hello.
(Eunyu Publishing Company)
What are all these?
Our CEO of Eunyu Publishing
would like to donate two sets
of the complete series
of world literature,
three sets of children's books,
and 100 must-read books
carefully selected for youths.
- Amazing!
That's crazy.
They're refurbished books,
so you don't have to feel pressured.
You were Woo-yeon's teacher.
I should help with what I can.
This is my boyfriend.
Gosh. Nice to meet you.
It's going to take half a day
to just organize.
We'll do the organizing as well,
so you don't have to worry.
Should we move them?
Yes.
- Put it on top.
- What?
Please put some more on top.
There's no need to overdo yourself.
I understand.
Put more books on top for me.
This is too light.
It looks heavy to me.
More.
What?
- More.
- One more?
One more.
More?
Carry just a bit at a time.
Your back is precious.
I know.
Those people don't know what's precious.
- More.
- This looks dangerous.
Let's stop.
Why? Is it too much for you?
It's
super light for me.
Are you okay?
- What do we do?
- Are you okay?
I knew you were overdoing it.
These are heavy.
Are you okay?
You can't just send books.
Organizing takes effort too.
I never planned you in the picture.
Were you planning to do this
with Woo-yeon?
Were you going to make her
breathe in all the dust?
You're so inconsiderate.
Why are you talking casually?
You started it.
I'm much older than you.
Yes, sir.
I'll make sure to speak to you formally.
"Sir"?
Did something happen to them?
Gosh. I was going to ask you that.
What's wrong with them?
Are you in touch with that guy?
Yes.
You're smiling so big.
I'm so excited these days.
It's so nice to see his text
when I wake up in the morning
asking me if I slept well.
I love it that someone's asking me
what I did,
what I ate, and what I'm going to do.
That's nothing special.
It's because this is the first time
someone likes me.
Scrub it properly all the way.
Okay.
Why did you lie earlier?
I didn't lie.
You said you like dating more.
You said it's too early for marriage.
I gave it a thought,
and I thought my dream was to become
your husband.
And?
And
my dream is just Kim Young-hee.
To have Kim Young-hee full,
to have Kim Young-hee smile,
and to have Kim Young-hee happy.
Anything that starts with Kim Young-hee.
What a humble dream.
I'll just live as a man who has
a humble dream.
Kyung Woo-yeon.
Young-hee.
Is there anything I can help with?
Woo-yeon, can you take this over there?
Okay.
- Here. Enjoy your food.
- Thank you.
Enjoy.
Here you go.
It's time to eat now.
Do you want more?
Are you okay?
You don't want to eat it?
Enjoy your food.
Now you're running away to dreamland.
I thought I told you
not to cross the line.
I know my hands are beautiful,
but you shouldn't just grab it
whenever you please.
Don't try to talk your way out of this.
What are you two doing?
Woo-yeon.
Now that you're up, let's talk.
Do it here.
- I have nothing to say.
- Then listen to what I have to say.
- I don't want to.
- Listen anyway.
Just once.
Are you always this rude?
She said no, but you won't stop.
I know you're friends, but this is wrong.
Woo-yeon!
What, Jin-ju? You need me?
No, I can do it myself!
Okay! I'm coming!
I said not to grab my hand.
I said not to cross the line.
Soo.
Woo-yeon waited for you that day.
She waited...
She waited and waited,
and then finally left.
Did Soo and Mr. On get into a fight?
- Of course not.
- True, why would they fight?
It's not like Soo likes you.
- What?
- Then why do I see rage in their eyes
whenever they see each other?
What is that?
There's no rage.
I'm sure you were mistaken.
I was not.
Sorry, I have to run to the bathroom.
She's so observant.
She surprisingly has a good eye.
- Sweetie.
- What did you do wrong?
What is it?
Well, it wasn't anything wrong.
- I think...
- Okay.
Misunderstandings
cause bigger misunderstandings...
You told Soo, didn't you?
Can you read minds?
Why did you tell him? It's useless.
Woo-yeon knows he went that day.
But she's going to pretend she doesn't.
It's over for her.
I see.
- How did Woo-yeon find out?
- I told her.
You saw the photos, didn't you?
You waited for me that day, didn't you?
I went too.
I went, but I was in an accident.
I said it was nothing
so that you wouldn't worry.
Soo.
That doesn't change anything.
Why not? You went, and so did I.
This happened to us because of bad timing.
Do you think it was timing?
You had thousands of chances
over the past ten years.
You lost all those chances.
People always resent the last chance
that they missed out on.
Go somewhere.
Leave for a while like you always do.
Please.
Get lost forever and stop confusing me.
Are you confused?
Do you think that's all?
Everything is a total mess because of you.
I'm livid right now.
What? You like me? Now? Finally?
That isn't love. That's a misconception.
You don't want me, but you don't want
anyone else to have me. That's greed.
You thought I'd like you forever,
but now that I like someone else,
you're jealous.
Don't talk like that.
What should I say then?
That's the only way
it makes any sense to me.
I liked you for ten years,
but now of all times?
Now, when I'm with Joon-soo?
This is about you and me.
Don't drag him into our relationship.
No. You stay out of
my relationship with him.
For me, "us" and "we" refer to me
and Joon-soo, not you.
So...
let's end this. Please.
It's exhausting.
Why aren't you eating? Do you not like it?
Yes, I do. It tastes good.
You can't eat chicken feet, can you?
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I only found out today.
I only said I couldn't eat it,
but it's my first time trying.
I found out today.
I can't eat chicken feet.
This is about you, you know.
I'll get used to it.
What else do you like?
I'll practice ahead of time.
Why? You shouldn't eat things
you don't like.
I want to like things that you like.
I should match you.
Just be moved. Don't feel bad.
An egg souffle please.
(Let's finish our shoots.)
What is it? Is something wrong?
No.
We'll be finishing the shoots soon.
Thank goodness.
- For what?
- Just because.
That the shoots will be finished
without a hitch.
I agree.
(Woo-yeon)
(Sure.)
Is it supposed to rain today?
They said it will, but I don't know.
If it starts to rain while we're working,
- let's...
- Let's finish it today.
Okay, let's do that.
This is so nice, isn't it?
Yes.
Why did they shut down a place like this?
Let's go on the carousel.
Okay.
People are terrible.
They threw it away saying it was useless,
but now,
they want it back.
I'm always doing wrong by you.
That won't happen again.
I'll get lost forever.
Are you really leaving?
Where are you going?
Anywhere.
When?
Anytime. Soon.
So play with me one last time
and smile for me.
Whatever.
We should work.
Soo is leaving again.
It's not the first time.
I think he likes someone.
I guess it didn't work out.
He likes someone?
He won't say, but I think so.
I see.
He runs away when things get tough
just like you.
You're the one who ran away.
You threw divorce papers at me
and lived in the US for years.
I left. I didn't run away.
How is that different?
It's different.
I left because you kept running away.
If I tried to talk to you,
you worked late and on weekends.
You ran away through work.
That's because...
You don't have to go far away physically
to be running away.
It was able to start anew
because it was abandoned.
If it wasn't abandoned,
it would've remained the same.
If trains kept running
on that abandoned train track,
if this amusement park wasn't shut down,
they would've been a bland train track
and a typical amusement park.
"I'm glad I was able to start anew
although I was abandoned."
They may think that.
One, two, three.
("I'm glad I was able to start anew
although I was abandoned.")
(Joon-soo)
(What time should we meet later?)
(We're still shooting.)
(I'll let you know when we're done.)
(I'll be waiting.)
I've never seen a carousel
that doesn't move.
Why are you so careless?
You won't let me let go.
I never asked you to hold me.
Exactly.
That's the one thing I'm waiting for,
but you won't.
You found out anyway,
so I don't want to hide it.
The fact that I like you.
I told you, you don't like me.
I do too. Why don't you believe me?
I can't because it's you.
I was fooled too many times.
There you go again, being hurtful.
I'm going to go take more pictures
before I get hurt even more.
Excuse me.
You dropped this.
That's not mine.
Then it must be your boyfriend's.
Look.
Okay, then.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but do you mind giving it to him
when he leaves later?
Don't tell him you showed it to me.
Please.
Sure.
It didn't rain.
The shoot finished without a hitch.
It did.
Excuse me.
I think you dropped this.
It's yours, right?
Yes. Thank you.
Aren't we going?
I think I lost something. Wait in the car.
- If it isn't important...
- It is important.
I'll be right back. Wait for me.
What is wrong with him?
Why isn't he back yet? It's raining.
Looking for this?
What's your problem? What are you doing?
Give it to me. It's mine.
- It's my face.
- I took the picture.
Are you kidding me?
Do I look like I'm kidding?
I wish you were kidding.
If you were going to be pathetic
like this, why did you lie to me?
You should've said you couldn't go
because you got hurt,
not that you didn't go.
You keep acting like it's sincere.
That's why I keep going back to that day.
Why do you keep...
Why do you keep acting sincere
and confusing me?
(Opportunities lost become regrets.)
(If there are no more opportunities
for me to lose,)
(I can just create them on my own.)
I'll be the one
in an unrequited love this time.
Just as you liked me...
No. Much longer than that.
I'll like you much more.
I'll act like you now.
You act like me.
Then, just as I liked you,
like me back.
If this is our cycle,
I'll wait.