(The exhausted and thirsty fox came across a vineyard.)
("I'm very lucky. I found such delicious-looking grapes.)
(The fox jumped with all his might
to pick some grapes,)
(but they were too high.)
(After jumping for a while,
the fox gave up on the grapes,)
(and turned away.)
("Those grapes are probably
too sour anyway.")
("That's why they're still there.")
=Episode 15: The Reason for Walking Away=
(Woo-yeon Calligraphy)
Hi,
Woo-yeon.
Do you want some tea?
How have you been?
(A heart meant for that one person)
(I cried every day,)
(and I couldn't even remember
to close my umbrella.)
But you ask...
how I've been.
Good.
I've been well.
You?
I see, you have.
I'm glad.
Time heals all wounds.
I've been busy.
I hardly ate or slept.
All I did was take pictures...
to come back to you.
I told you, time has passed.
It's too late.
Woo-yeon.
You're with a guest.
He's leaving.
If you're done...
No, I'm not.
With anything.
Then another time.
I have plans for tonight.
I'll call you.
(Woo-yeon Calligraphy)
Thank you.
I came to bring you this.
Did I come at a bad time?
No.
What is this?
Our company's merchandise
that you worked on.
They sent you a set.
I could've picked them up.
Thank you.
Should I lend you an ear,
or should I change the subject?
You seem down
and nervous.
You always
catch me.
I told you. We're alike, you and I.
Please change the subject.
Let me think of something else.
That movie that you worked on
was based on a book
owned by Eunyu.
I'm going to the premier.
Go with me
if you have no one else to go with.
Okay.
Don't act like you're fine
in front of me if it's too hard.
You know I see right through you.
Okay.
(Crossing the ocean between us)
(Your photography project finished
earlier than I expected.)
You didn't eat or sleep
while working on it.
Because I have to go back to Woo-yeon.
It's the first time your photographs
had a different goal.
It's the first time I regretted something
because of photography too.
Every day since I came here,
I regretted coming.
I should've stayed beside Woo-yeon.
I guess I'm regretting things again.
Why did you break up with Woo-yeon?
I thought we'd never break up
since it took a long time
for us to be together.
I'm used to being lonely
since I was always alone,
but it wouldn't be the same for Woo-yeon.
How can I beg her to stay
when she says it's too hard on her?
I thought you were selfish,
but you're stupid.
Once you let go, it's over.
Too much time has passed.
It's different for us.
We're different.
(Crossing the ocean between us)
(My Woo-yeon)
(My Soo)
Is she busy?
(My Woo-yeon)
She's probably asleep, right?
What is it?
Ms. Kyung and I met today because of work.
Did you call to tell me that?
Yes.
There's nothing between us,
so don't get us wrong.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I don't want her
to be misunderstood because of me.
If I misunderstand,
wouldn't that give you a chance?
I don't want to catch a cheap chance.
I need...
to catch whatever I can.
(Hyun-jae.)
Yes. Go ahead.
You can take Young-hee.
Don't worry about me,
and take just Young-hee with you.
If you stay beside her,
I'll be able to close my eyes in peace.
You shouldn't close your eyes.
Young-hee is going to be really beautiful.
You should open them wide to see her.
We're going to have an American wedding,
so you have to wear a dress too.
What color would you like?
Pick me out something bold.
Something with a very low back.
Sure. I got it.
(General Ward A)
Hyun-jae.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mother.
(Woo-yeon Calligraphy)
Woo-yeon, you should go on a blind date.
I know a prosecutor who is a great catch.
Forget it. I'm sick of dating.
What? You're sick of dating?
Are you still not over him yet?
Are you never going to date again?
Oh, right. Soo's back.
(Woo-yeon Calligraphy)
- Is he back in Korea?
- Did he call you?
He came here.
How are you okay?
Should I be crying my eyes out, then?
Work is the most important thing to me
right now,
and I don't want to fall in love again.
I don't want to waste my emotions
on stuff like that.
In just one year, the person to whom love
was the most important thing
is gone.
What are you doing just sitting here?
Let's go out.
I feel full and it's cool outside.
This is paradise.
It gets rid of all my trivial thoughts.
I'm happy since you two are happy.
It was worthwhile.
I'm thankful to both of you
for staying beside me.
I love you.
I love you too.
You make me cringe.
Why don't we just stop dating
and forget about getting married?
Should the three of us
live together forever?
Sorry. I already have my date set.
My gosh. Are you going to be like this?
- Gosh.
- What's the matter with you?
- Here you go. Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- One more soju, please.
-  Okay.
- Can you take our order?
- Okay.
- Hey, can you take their order?
- Sure.
Enjoy.
Welcome.
What? Long time no see, brother.
You have a lot of customers now.
This is a hot place now.
Take a seat.
When did you come to Korea?
- Today.
- Then you should be resting.
Did you come straight to see me?
I didn't come straight here.
You're the third person I'm seeing.
Who did you see so fast?
Woo-yeon.
Did you see her?
Why are you being awkward?
You two broke up.
You probably went to see her
because you still have feelings for her.
If you're here to drink alone,
it probably didn't work out well.
You changed a lot in the meantime.
A year has gone by already.
Is a year a long time?
The time going by is one thing.
The situation has changed a lot too.
I'm getting married.
What?
Hey, Kitty Cat.
Hey, Puppy Dog. Are you working hard?
I missed you so much
that I thought I might die.
How much?
Me too.
Did you hear the story
of how they got engaged?
Yes. I thought it was
a scene from a sitcom.
What do I do?
Puppy Dog, you look so cute today.
- How do I look? Do I look okay?
- Totally. You look so hot. I'm in love.
What happened to your finger?
Dong-sik did this.
Dong-sik should get scolded.
Don't do that.
He's the most powerful member
of our family.
He thinks everything is a chew toy
besides my mom.
My dad and my brothers are all scared.
I better get on Dong-sik's good side too.
Just don't let him see you.
That'll be the best.
Okay.
Let's go.
Okay. Let's go.
I know
I'm not good enough for Jin-ju.
But
I
really
love Jin-ju.
Whatever I lack, I promise
to fill them as we live together.
It's not that you lack something.
You and Jin-ju aren't right
for each other.
By that, I mean one of you
will end up exhausted.
You'll likely become that person.
Mom.
I won't stop you two from dating.
But as for marriage...
What's with him today?
Gosh, my dear Dong-sik. You're so cute.
What's wrong? Gosh.
My goodness.
Dong-sik.
What?
(Sure, the dog is picky with people.)
(But is it normal to give them permission
to marry because the dog likes him?)
Her mom even went to a fortune-teller.
Apparently, they're a perfect match.
Wait just a little.
I'll be right there. Okay.
Gosh. How sweet.
Vomit.
What do you want to drink?
Black sugar milk tea.
- We'll get two black sugar milk teas.
- Okay.
- Please charge this card.
It's sweet. Drinking something sweet
makes me feel good.
Sugar is the best when things are tough.
Are things tough for me?
Why are you giving me sweets?
In case you're low on sugar.
Pretending to be something you're not
is the hardest.
Are you talking about yourself?
Yes.
Are you going home?
No. I'm stopping by the hospital first.
How's your mother doing?
She's the same.
Didn't Woo-yeon talk about me?
No.
Is it really over for her?
Why do you two make dating so difficult?
Why is it always so hard?
Both of you are too considerate,
which ends up hurting the other person.
I was always alone,
so I don't know how to treat other people.
I didn't even know that was a fault.
You normally don't talk about this stuff.
I keep regretting things.
I think I ruined our relationship.
And despite that,
I don't know how to turn it back.
I feel lost.
Gosh. You and Woo-yeon are the same.
You're both so foolish.
Why are you watching me? It's unsightly.
Are you going to make me remember
only what your back looks like?
Don't even remember my back.
Don't remember anything.
The backside is always sadder.
And I made you
see that backside
too many times.
Exactly.
Show me your face.
I don't want to forget your face.
I'm going to sleep. Leave.
Puppy Dog.
You're here.
- Did you have fun?
- Yes. How was work?
Good.
You're here too.
Aren't you going to ask me why I'm here?
Why should I?
You must be at a bar to drink.
You must be at your friend's bar
to see your friend.
What is this?
I thought you'd yell at me to go away.
There's no need.
I don't hate you anymore. I really don't.
Why not?
Emotions can wear out.
I hated you so much
that I don't feel anything anymore.
Now I just assume
you're someone like that.
You'll start to hate me again.
I saw Woo-yeon today.
I intend on asking her to come back to me.
Go ahead,
but I have no direct connections to you.
All of my emotions towards you
were built through her.
I was only a bystander,
and this is how I feel.
Wouldn't Woo-yeon's emotions
be even more worn out than mine?
She said she'll call me.
She said she would,
so she will.
Are you back in Korea for good now?
Maybe.
Are you going to leave again?
You'll make your girlfriend upset.
Why didn't you bring your girlfriend
with you today?
I want to buy her a meal.
Next time.
It's mine.
Yes, sir.
Soo.
Did something happen?
No.
If something happened...
If you feel troubled or lonely,
won't you tell me?
Parents are people you can always rely on.
We were never able to tell you,
so I thought you might not know.
I'll tell you if anything happens.
(It looks like)
something happened between Soo
and his girlfriend, doesn't it?
Did they break up?
Then again, who would put up with a guy
who makes her lonely?
Did you just diss me?
Why? Did that strike a chord?
I thought he took after me,
but he takes after you.
- I'm so upset.
- Why are you blaming me?
Never mind. We made him that way.
Just blame me.
I'm the root cause.
What?
Did I mess up again?
I'm amused because you keep growing up.
Was that a compliment?
It was.
We were planning to only display
the nature scenes
from World Airlines' departure points,
but we didn't want to miss
your first portraits.
(Open PDF file)
That's why things got much bigger than anticipated.
I see.
(World Space Gallery Portrait Exhibit Adjustments)
(Import image)
(Copy, paste)
(Important)
(Save as PDF)
I sent you the revised layout.
The photo that I attached
is very important.
Let's display it by itself.
Yes, sir.
Anyway, how did you take
so many pictures in a year?
It's like you didn't even sleep.
I didn't sleep.
So that I could come back.
I see.
Hello.
She'll be conducting the interview
to be included
in our pamphlet.
Hello. I'm Yoon Da-un.
Hello, I'm Lee Soo.
The title of the exhibit
is "The Door at the End of the World."
Is there a special reason for that?
I appreciated that the world was round
during my trip
because whereas nations have borders,
the world does not.
A new world opens, that's all.
Whether it's the door to a plane
or airport,
you must open the door
to reach the new world.
I think people are the same.
(They say every person
possesses their own world.)
(So if a person enters yours,)
(it means an entire world is entering.)
(If I open my heart,
I can see a whole new world.)
(It was an unexpected discovery.)
(I think the title encompasses
both subjects, landscape and people.)
You're more famous
as a landscape photographer,
but there were many photos of people
in this exhibit.
Is there a special reason why
you took pictures of people?
I had never looked at anyone
with love before.
Generally, I tend to be very cold,
but it was also my belief
that things like love
were but a mirage, which lasts briefly,
then disappears.
However, that belief was shattered
because of someone.
Most of the people in the exhibit
are people in love.
Only recently did I realize
that people and their love
were lovely.
Which is your favorite photograph
among all that you've taken?
The self-portrait.
My philosophy of not photographing
things I didn't love
applied to myself as well.
So I had never taken a picture of myself.
When I think back,
I don't think I had ever loved myself.
I think I had the courage
to take that picture
because I was finally ready
to love myself.
As I lay here,
I tried to remember just one time
I was good to you,
but I couldn't.
At least you won't cry for too long
since I wasn't a good mom.
I'm glad.
Don't talk, Mom.
It's too hard for you.
I...
never received love from my own mom,
so I couldn't love you properly.
I'm sorry.
I said to stop talking.
My daughter.
Yes?
My pretty daughter.
Don't cry.
I'm sorry for making you
be born as my daughter.
I will...
stop being your mom now.
In your next life, don't...
Don't be born as my daughter.
Be born to a good mom
and receive lots of love,
and throw tantrums as much as you want.
Be a spoiled brat
with good parents.
I was too ashamed to tell you, but...
I love you,
my baby.
I love you too, Mom.
I love you.
Is Cheol Soo not coming?
I wish I could see him before I go.
Mom.
Please don't go.
Please stay with me.
You never did anything I ever asked.
Mom.
I won't stop you for long.
Please stay just a little while longer.
Please?
I'm sorry, my baby.
Mom.
I'm good now.
(Rest in Peace)
Hey.
Thanks for coming.
Don't act strong.
Yes, don't act strong.
Watch how you talk to your elder.
Cry.
We'll cover you, so cry.
We'll hold you, so just cry.
You don't have to wear
mourning clothes too.
I'm an only child
and don't have an older sister.
Pretend you have a younger sister.
I only have two older brothers
and not an older sister.
You have another younger sister.
I feel so reassured.
Mom would be
so pleased to see you.
(Rest in Peace)
It's okay to cry, Young-hee.
Will crying change anything?
It will if you don't cry.
If you keep your tears in,
it'll dampen your spirits.
And once you get too wet,
you'll sink alone.
So it's okay to cry, Young-hee.
You won't crumble even if you do.
If you crumble,
I will hold you up.
You can lean on me.
As a friend is fine.
Or if not, consider me a chair, a rock,
or a tree.
Anything you can lean on.
Consider me something like that.
(Was it because I was used to
seeing my mom's back?)
(Or was it like she said,)
(and that she wasn't a good mom?)
(I seemed to be getting over)
(my mom's death pretty easily.)
(Closed)
Forget it. Pour me a drink.
I need liquid courage to say
something so cringe-worthy.
Your existence alone comforts me.
I thought that
I'd crumble if I cried.
I thought leaning on others
would make me feel small.
But I didn't crumble even when I cried.
Because you were there to hold me up.
I leaned on you as much as I wanted
and I didn't feel small at all.
I knew that you wouldn't
shed tears so easily.
I never held you up.
Why should I take shared credit
for what they did?
That would be shameless of me.
I can't take credit,
so I'll just fill your glass.
You're cute, punk.
Don't abuse it. I'm not your waiter.
Don't worry.
I hate you and very much at that.
Hate me at least.
Just don't pretend I don't exist.
Shall we clink glasses?
Okay.
Ready? Kim Young-hee, be happy.
- Be happy!
- Be happy.
- We love you.
Since when?
Hi, Mom.
I'm at Tonight with the guys.
Yes.
She looks okay.
Okay, then. I'll see you soon, sir.
Bye.
Hey.
If you talk to your mom,
do you think I'll cry and go, "Mommy"?
I dislike that even more.
I'm sorry.
Why are you always apologizing?
Are you Hyun-jae?
I didn't think you'd invite him too.
I owe him a lot, and I'm very grateful.
Anyway, do you feel uncomfortable
because I invited Soo?
It's fine. He's your guest.
What'll you do about him now?
He still seems to have
lots of feelings for you.
He wouldn't stop looking at you.
I don't want to whine at you
even on a day like this.
Please whine at me, will you?
I really need an excuse
to think about something else.
So what? What'll you do about Soo?
I didn't throw out anything he gave me.
I look at them
and keep thinking of what we did.
The bad memories, the hurtful feelings.
The days I cried.
Must you do that?
They say that fear comes from memories.
That fear is what keeps me wary.
I must be wary.
It's like armor.
Well...
I guess it is.
Am I pathetic?
Who can say that when it's your life?
Find and put on
the thickest suit of armor that you can.
Then it's one or the other.
The armor will crush you,
or you'll take it off.
I'm glad to see that Young-hee seems okay.
I'm not sure if she's really okay,
or if she's just pretending to be okay,
but it was good to see her smile.
Yes.
What's up with Soo and Woo-yeon anyway?
Thanks for taking me home.
Get home safely.
Woo-yeon.
Yes?
We have some talking to do.
Yes.
Let's wrap it up today.
I was hoping to start.
But you ended it.
The only thing we can start
is a friendship.
Is that what you want?
I can't be friends with you.
Not anymore.
Then we'll have no reason to meet again.
I really hate myself for doing this.
But you owe me a wish.
Do you want to bet?
The one who asks to break up
has to grant the other a wish.
Okay, I'll keep my word.
What do you want me to do?
For just one day,
can we go back to before we broke up?
Okay.
What's the point of all that
when we're breaking up?
That's why we shouldn't break up.
Okay.
You liar.
You said we shouldn't break up.
You're here early.
Yes. I got ready early.
Do you not like that?
Shall I order you something else?
It's tasty.
(Late Night Snack Cart)
You should've waited until
the noodles came out.
Why are you downing soju
after being away so long?
I feel like drinking today.
You evil brat.
How could you stop coming
just because you broke up?
You broke up with him, not with me.
How did you find out?
Hyun-jae comes by sometimes.
My gosh. Just when I mentioned you.
(Late Night Snack Cart)
My glass is empty too.
You should've taken that off long ago.
Young-hee.
I'm still the same.
I haven't changed.
Yes.
You're right.
Nothing has changed.
I'm still miserable.
And
I still don't want to share my misery
with you.
You know
how you told me to get out of your misery?
Do you know where I'm living now
after being kicked out?
I'm living within my misery.
Can't you
let me back into your misery?
My misery...
hurts way too much.
Consider me your cart.
Why do you keep trying to do so much?
Because I want to do anything I can.
Hop on.
- Hurry back.
- Okay.
(Mom constantly walked away from me,)
(so all I remembered)
(was her back.)
If you're poor, at least be nice.
It's the worst.
(I thought she was turning her back to me
to shun me.)
(I realized over time,)
(that it was to feed her child
a little more.)
I'm going to sleep.
(To cry alone.)
(To hurt alone.
Her back was actually the face of a mom.)
What should I bring you on my way home?
Cookies.
Okay. I'll finish work quickly
and buy you cookies.
Come home quickly.
Okay.
(Late Night Snack Cart)
You're showing me your back
in order to carry me.
I'm having an exhibit this Saturday.
Will you come?
Soo.
Let's drop the act.
It's over between us.
Can't we
start over?
I'm not someone you can drop and pick up
whenever you feel like it.
You're the one who dropped me.
Did I really?
You called multiple times a day,
then it became once morning and night.
Then once a day.
Some days, we only exchanged
brief messages.
You're the one who changed.
There was the time difference.
If I called right before falling asleep
after working all day,
you'd be busy working.
If I woke up in the morning,
you were ready for bed.
It was only natural that I called less
as the time difference grew.
You said you were okay with it.
You said
you understood.
I had to understand, to feel less pathetic
because of your indifference.
I understood in order to be loved,
but you kept growing
more and more distant.
You agreed and simply let go
when I said let's break up.
How could I stop you?
It wasn't like I could fly back.
You said it was too hard for you.
How could I stop you?
You should've told me then
to try harder.
You should've said all this back then.
Soo.
I was insecure
the entire time I was with you.
I wondered whether you truly liked me.
Maybe I mistook fleeting jealousy
for love.
Someone who's insecure...
can't say what's in their heart.
For fear of losing the other person.
You always doubt me and think by yourself.
You love alone and break up alone.
I thought we loved each other,
but it was always an unrequited love.
You dealt with it
because you didn't trust me,
and I dealt with it because I felt bad.
We both just dealt with it until it ended.
You're right.
That's a failed relationship.
Don't hold onto a failed relationship.
Let's really end it this time.
Eat well,
sleep well,
and be well.
You're home.
I stopped by because I thought
you'd have nothing to eat...
Son.
What's wrong?
I thought I could see her again
if I came back, but...
I was wrong again.
(There is a reason
why someone shows their back.)
(I realized that reason)
(too late.)
(No one knew of the fox's wounds.)
(The fox's efforts.)
(If he fell just one more time,
the fox would've died.)
(The fox showed his back
in order to live.)