[The Legends]
[Episode 5]
Lu Zhaoyao! You are a wicked woman. You must die today!
Where is the Sect Leader?
Inside the Sword Tomb.
Wanjun Sword.
The Sword Tomb.
Sect Leader!
- Wanjun Sword is coming into the world.
- The ancient enchanted sword has immense power.
It must not fall into their hands. Fight for a quick win!
- Revered Lady Changyu!
The Demoness was heavily injured by the miasma from the sword pedestal. Today, she can't escape here.
She must be put to the sword today and pay for the evil from these few years.
I was careless! I fell into the Immortal Sect's ambush.
Sect Leader,
your wound is serious.
Why are you here?
Your wounds need tending immediately.
The wounds don't matter.
Wanjun Sword is emerging today. I must get it!
But your wounds...
Little monster... Did I use to call you that?
This look he has... is it...
Mo Qing,
do you love me?
Sure enough.
This Silver Mirror is my personal belonging.
I forgot who gave it to me. But it should be a precious item.
Today,
if you help me leave here unscathed,
I promise to set you above and rule over the masses in Jianghu.
This silver mirror
is yours, as a token.
No.
You don't need to give me anything.
Keep it.
Just keep it for yourself.
He's is a romantic.
Mo Qing,
draw those Immortal Sect followers away from me, can you?
Sect Leader,
I would give up everything for you,
as long as you're safe.
You can give up everything for me.
Isn't that just because you have nothing?
A moment ago Baishui Jianxin Sword detected a thread of magic power. It seems Lu Zhaoyao is close.
I won't let anything happen to you.
A man from the Wan Lu Sect?
Wanjun Sword is coming into the world.
Wanjun Sword.
Zhaoyao can finally fulfill her wish.
This sword's voice is calling out to me.
Can't touch it!
The sword belongs to Zhaoyao.
Let go!
Let go now!
Let go! Wanjun Sword can only know one master!
Let go!
Why? For what reason?
Why am I unable to let go?
You little monster!
You really are the son of the Demon King!
Enduring hardships for years,
guarding the gate, it was just to use me!
You rascal... What a schemer!
I'm an infamous demoness.
The day I died,
it was when the ancient magic artifact, Wanjun Sword, reappeared in the world.
I gave my all and suffered every sort of pain
to get Wanjun Sword, to ascend to the highest position in Jianghu.
I'd never thought that in the end
it would become a gift for someone else.
Thinking of all my efforts throughout this life,
I really can't accept it.
[Five years later]
North Hills Chief, we've dug to the bottom of this Sword Tomb.
All right. You can go back.
Yes, sir.
Sect Leader, if you could see today's Wan Lu Sect,
you would be filled with anger, too.
Today's Wan Lu Sect
has long since lost the way it was.
Father...
Don't come here!
Sect Leader!
The Sword Tomb has been dug out.
We haven't found the Previous Sect Leader's body.
To think that the Previous Leader had such an illustrious name,
and in the end, not even her body can be found.
Sect Leader, this time you'll finally be at ease.
If the North Hills Chief is so nostalgic about the Previous Leader,
why don't you follow her to the underworld, to uphold your loyalty?
What do you think you are?
Without the Previous Leader,
could you have risen to Captain of the Dark Guards?
I would have surely followed the Previous Leader and treaded all over the world.
Even down to the Underworld, I'd have gone unwavering.
When that time comes,
I will definitely drag you down with me.
- You!
- Enough.
North Hills Chief, please withdraw.
Sect Leader, the North Hills Chief contradicts you again and again. I–
No need to follow me.
It is the taste you liked.
I'm not going back. I want to leave the Thousand Dust Pavilion.
Since not one of you believes me, I'll seek vengeance for my father on my own.
Miss Zhiyan, your father's death still contains many suspicions.
The Pavillion Leader will certainly clarify the truth in the name of justice.
Miss Zhiyan, he's your father's biological brother, you should believe in him.
He's the one who doesn't believe me!
Senior Suyu, what should we do now?
You people don't believe me so I can only rely on myself. I must leave.
I'm not scared!
This Sushan maze you have here... how...
Hey! Are you people still there?
Hey! Are you all still there?
Leader Qin, it pains me that Brother Qin Yu encountered such terrible tragedy.
It shocks me even more that Zhiyan mistook me for the killer.
I am glad that Leader Qin could personally come here today.
I want to work with you to find the real murderer. Not only to clear the misunderstanding.
Even more, it is to avenge Brother Qin Yu.
Since Sect Leader Liu speaks thusly, then I will get to the point.
I came today to verify your whereabouts on the day of the event.
That day I was at Phoenix Mountain, sharing drinks with their Deacon Chi Tianming.
After a few cups, I was slightly drunk. When I woke up, I returned home.
Later, I heard that Brother Qin Yu had been attacked in the Xuanyu Hall
and Zhiyuan had escaped in the commotion. Leader Qin,
the most pressing matter at present is to find Brother Qin Yu.
Dead or alive, there has to be an answer. Not to mention, Xuanyu Hall is currently unattended.
We need to find someone to manage the Hall's affairs posthaste.
Pavillion Leader. Sect Leader Liu.
Miss Zhiyan wouldn't listen. She ran into the Sushan Maze.
Sect Leader Liu, in the Pavillion there are some matters that need my attention,
so for today, I won't keep you any longer.
Leader Qin, as you please.
Revered One...
Has Qin Qianxian left?
Yes.
Did his expression show anything unusual?
Nothing unusual. I suppose Liu Wei did not raise any suspicion.
Of course.
I will withdraw.
Mingxuan, Lu Zhaoyao died. It's such a pity
that she died so easily.
What in the world is this place? I've been walking all day.
So this is what the Netherworld looks like.
What Netherworld? Who are you?
Who are you?
I... I'm not telling you. You tell me who you are first.
Fine. Listen well.
My last name is Lu, first name is Qiong, called by Zhaoyao, [Ancient Chinese have a formal first name and a casual first name. ]
founder of the Wan Lu Sect at Chenji Mountain...
D-D-Demoness!
Right. I'm that Demoness.
A-A-Aren't you already dead?
Right.
Wasn't I already dead?
- Let's try.
- Try wha–
Ouch! Why did you hit me?
Why-Why do you look like me in the mirror?
In the mirror, I look like you? So, in your eyes, I don't look like you?
N-N-No. In the mirror you have my face,
but the one I see is you.
I'm also curious about why it's different.
God! It's scary!
This place is actually a maze spell.
How did I come back here?
It's the end! I can't get out.
Come here.
Little sister, what are you afraid of?
Leaving this trivial maze is no problem for me. I can take you out.
But before I do, answer some of my questions. All right?
Wh-What questions?
First, where is this place?
This is Mount Su's Thousand Dust Pavillion.
Thousand Dust Pavillion...
Second, where do you want to go?
W-W-Wan Lu Sect.
Your body is showing Immortal Sect's energy, you're clearly from there. But you say you want to go to Wan Lu Sect. Why?
Th-The Immortal Sect is crooked. I want to become strong.
And then... seek vengeance.
Vengeance? For what?
Liu Wei, from the Jian Xin Sect, killed my father.
I want to avenge my father and kill Liu Wei.
Liu Wei...
What a coincidence. I want to go back to Wan Lu Sect, too.
I can take you out of the Sushan Maze and take you to Wan Lu Sect. How about it?
You-You'd be so good?
Because I'm generous.
But it was said...
Can you believe the rumors? They said that in Wan Lu Sect everyone was a follower of evil.
Now you, too, want to go to Wan Lu Sect. Do you think you are a follower of evil?
I...I... It seems you're right.
Also, you're not so much like they said.
Is that prettier or uglier?
It's... It's...
It-It's pre-prettier. Prettier.
Rubbish.
I am really a good person.
So... Demoness,
I'm curious. Why are you in the Sushan Maze?
- I don't know.
- This maze is very close to the Thousand Dust Pavillion.
Does my uncle know that you're here?
Don't know.
Why do I always get hurt?
We've been walking for so long. How come this doesn't look any different than the place we just went through?
Did we go back again?
Your eyes can't tell the difference. But mine can.
We finally got out!
This maze is a nuisance; of course, you can't get out without a Sect Leader's skills.
But who am I?
Little girl, you should rejoice that you've found big shoulders to climb on.
Miss Zhiyan, you did come out.
Miss Zhiyan, come back with me first.
I'm not going back. Since none of you believes me, I'll avenge my father by myself.
How can there be two Miss Zhiyans?
Don't blame me! Don't blame me! I must go.
Cut this rubbish. Let's leave quickly while nobody is onto us, lest anything else should happen.
Sect Leader, as of late in Jianghu, there's a rebel group that calls itself "New Mountain."
They run wild, clashing with our Wan Lu followers every now and again.
I think we should dispose of them as soon as possible, to defend our Sect's prestige.
Sect Leader, I think that subduing the enemy without a fight is the best strategy.
If we can induce them to submit willingly to our sect, that will be a defense of our prestige.
Ridiculous. Subdue the enemy without a fight?
Captain Lin, you make it sound easy.
Are you going to send a team of women to pillow-talk them into idiocy?
These past few years, the North Hills Chief has been fighting here and there. It was hard work on you.
Do you mean that in a battle of wits
you'd do no better than sending a team of unskilled women?
Captain Lin, you're good at banter.
Then please, Captain Lin, take a trip in person
and chat them into submission.
Enough!
Where is this New Mountain? Who is the Sect Leader?
The Sect Leader is a coarse man swaying a broadsword.
The disciples call him Tuying, "Bald Eagle." The Sect is located near Fengmo Mountain.
Near Fengmo Mountain.
Yes.
Then we can't allow him.
- As a subordinate, I'm willing-
- Lu Gang!
Here, sir!
Within three days, clear off this sect. Spare those who flee. Put down those who resist.
I shall accept the order.
Sect Leader, I don't understand.
These few years your conduct has never resembled the Previous Leader's fierce ways.
If we could make them surrender to us this time,
though it'd take longer, there would be no need to obliterate them. Sect Leader, why...
In the vicinity of Fengmo Mountain, there can be no-one disturbing the peace.
♫ If you don't personally seal that dream ♫
♫ you'll have the mark of being born a demon  ♫
♫ Cliffs of carnage blood like mountains and rivers  ♫
♫ Step into a fiery sea, to become a god  ♫
♫ The wind's rising; Nirvana comes from arrogant pride ♫
♫ On the remote road I'll always be there ♫
♫ to trample the troubled times ♫
♫ To slash away fate's ♫
♫ shackles  ♫
♫ To battle nature, breaking  ♫
♫ the swirl of gratitude and grudge  ♫
♫ This uproar  ♫
♫ hasn't settled ♫
♫ so what?  ♫
♫  If love is a thunderbolt's crushing roughness ♫
♫ Just stagger to the end of the world  ♫
♫ With no inscription, who would understand?  ♫
♫ Let feeling carve your heart  ♫
♫ Unbreakable, is the wild wave in the hands  ♫
♫ On the remote road I'll always be there ♫
♫ to trample the troubled times ♫
♫ To slash away fate's ♫
♫ shackles  ♫
♫ To battle nature, breaking  ♫
♫ the swirl of gratitude and grudge  ♫
♫ This uproar.  ♫
♫ hasn't settled.  ♫
♫ On the remote road, desolate, ♫
♫ Heaven and Earth are shaken  ♫
♫ Drinking cold snow, majestically,  ♫
♫ come back to me  ♫
♫ After the thorn's pain,  ♫
♫ a tender flower blossoms  ♫
♫ I'll go with you, to die  ♫
♫ and forget ♫
♫ forever together  ♫