[The Legends]
[Episode 2]
Take care.
Luo Mingxuan!
Wait for me!
I will definitely come and find you. Wait for me!
I will definitely leave this place.
Old Man, what are you doing?
I heard from the clansmen who returned from the outside
that there are members from a Southern Moon Sect outside who can make living people out of wood.
Don't you want one?
I will make a living creature for you to play with for your entire life.
How can something made from wood be considered a living creature?
Old Man, I don't want anyone to keep me company anymore. I want to leave Fengmo Mountain.
- Leave?
- Yeah.
I secretly saw a glimpse of the outside world.
It's so beautiful!
Blue skies, fresh flowers, even the wind that blew over is fresh.
The trees outside are thick and strong, too!
They would definitely make a good walking cane. Much better than the one you have now.
I want to leave and go to a much bigger world.
See many more people!
I want to become a good person who brings prosperity to people.
If you want to leave Fengmo Mountain,
you must be able to personally break open the seal
and survive by yourself.
Of course, I will rely on my own ability to leave this place.
I am going to practice martial arts!
Sect Leader, this is the location where I was separated from Golden Immortal.
There's a seal here, we are unable to enter.
This is power from the ancient times; a defense spell.
Outsiders cannot enter, and those inside can't leave.
Looks like the creator of this magic spell didn't wish to meddle in worldly affairs.
Young Master Qian, do you have insight into what kind of spell this is?
This spell is quite esoteric. My ability alone is unable to break it.
What you mean, Young Master Qin, is that our trip today was pointless?
Mingxuan!
- Mingxuan!
- Suruo.
Why did the two of you come here?
We received no news of you these past several days. Deacon Chi and I were worried.
Therefore, we went to Thousand Dust Pavilion to ask Young Master Qin
to take us here to Fengmo Mountain, to search for the entrance to the seal.
I entered the seal of the mountain alone.
I indeed saw the Demon Master's son who was sealed inside.
Unfortunately, I was careless and was wounded by the seal,
allowing the Demon Master's son to escape.
Mingxuan, how is your wound?
It's fine. I only need some time to recuperate.
But we must not delay in searching for Demon Master's son.
If he grows to adulthood, he will threaten all of Jianghu.
We must capture and eliminate him.
We, of immortal sects, shall not shirk from the duty of killing the Demon King's son.
We just don't know what appearance this Demon King's son has. What are his characteristics?
The lot of us don't know how to identify him.
A young man who has horrible blue markings on his face.
All right. I shall immediately return to the immortal sects and dispatch people to search.
When my master comes out of training seclusion, I will definitely report this matter to him.
I've caused trouble for the two of you.
Let me take you back to Phoenix Mountain to heal your injuries.
What is it?
Nothing. Let's go.
This sealed place has been peaceful for a thousand years.
Not even a fart has been released before.
I never thought that after all this holding back such a big one would appear.
Since the Demon King's son is no longer here,
Zhaoyao and I do not have any reason
to continue staying on Fengmo Mountain.
But the dazzling world outside isn't that much safer than this Fengmo Mountain full of marsh gas.
I strongly do not wish for Zhaoyao to leave.
Zhaoyao resembles her mother too much:
passionate, impulsive.
I’m really afraid this child will be just like her mother back then.
But if I am too forceful,
I'm afraid I'll lose my only granddaughter.
The kid has grown up; just let her fly.
Up there! Get him!
He’s up ahead! Hurry and keep chasing!
Surrender yourself! Surrender yourself!
Stop!
Don't run!
Hurry and keep chasing.
Stop!
Don't run!
- It is him.
- Take him.
Sect Leader.
Deacon Chi has urgent news to report.
- You may go now.
- Yes.
Zhang Yu Sect leader.
Deacon Chi, what urgent news are you reporting?
My disciples have caught a teenage boy who is suspected to be the Demon King's son.
The Golden Immortal has been meditating to recover from grave injuries since he returned.
I will deliver this news to him in awhile.
How is the Demon King's son?
Golden Immortal.
Yesterday in the forests near Fengmo Mountain, my disciples captured a teenage boy.
Age, appearance, and body size;
also, the blue scar on his face all match what Golden Immortal described.
Bring the teenage boy in front of the Thousand Li Mirror.
Yes.
It is him.
Then... will you still be making another trip to Fengmo Mountain?
Golden Immortal is now cultivating his energy and healing.
He shall soon advance to the next level. He can not travel now.
How about waiting until Golden Immortal completes his advancement then handling this matter?
You must dispatch people to watch over this youth.
No need.
The Demon King's son is the son of our Immortal Sect's nemesis. Everyone wishes to eliminate him.
We only need to gather all the factions of our sects together and execute him where he stands. There's no need to wait for me.
This important task will have to rest on your shoulders, Deacon Chi.
It will be my honor to complete this task faithfully.
In that case, we shall trouble you then, Deacon Chi.
Yes.
Mingxuan, why are you in such a hurry?
Isn't it better to hold the execution until you're are fully recuperated?
The Demon King was treacherous and sinister when he was alive.
His son probably is not far from that.
Better to make the move sooner rather than later.
What you said makes sense.
Help me to notify all the factions in the Immortal Sect.
They must all be present to spread our sect's glory.
Sect Leader.
Golden Immortal is still wounded, make sure his tea is not too strong.
The incense in the room will be lit for an hour, then extinguish it for two hours.
Be alert for any situations.
Remember not to be careless.
Yes.
Mingxuan seems strangely restless.
Did he encounter something on Fengmo Mountain?
Old Man, I won.
Since I've beaten you, this time I can surely crack open the seal spell.
If you can open it,
then you should go.
I'll go and try it right now!
Nothing. I can't believe that. Again.
It's opened.
So beautiful!
Old man, I'm going.
Grandfather, once I've explored enough, I will bring you back a cane.
Everyone, a few days ago, Deacon Chi captured Demon King's son on Fengmo Mountain.
He shall be executed soon.
Golden Immortal wishes that everyone here and the rest of the sect leaders,
will assist Deacon Chi in raising the reputation of the legitimate sects.
Golden Immortal will not be coming?
Golden Immortal's power will be advancing to the next level in the next few days. He can not travel around.
We should all share some of Golden Immortal's burden to eliminate evil from Jianghu.
All right. Eliminate evil from Jianghu.
Eldest Brother, what are your intentions?
It's Golden Immortal's directive. It's natural that we shall obey.
Young Master Qin?
I wonder what your thoughts are.
As the younger generation of Thousand Dust Pavilion, I don't dare decide for my master.
I shall report this development to my master today.
Immortal Zi Dan is someone who cares for the world in his heart.
Surely, he shall respect Golden Immortal's decision. I appreciate your efforts, Young Master Qin.
Outside, it really is beautiful. Beautiful mountains and clear water.
And the scent of flowers, too. It's so nice!
Come have a look!
Watch! Come look! Breaking a rock slate with his chest!
Watch! Come have a look!
Such cute little monkeys!
Our sect leader captured the Son of the Demon King. Tomorrow, they'll execute him at Fengmo Mountain.
The Son of the Demon King?
Shouldn't we seize the chance to increase our reputation?
You're drunk, you!
Our Sect leader is looking forward to killing the Demon King's son in the name of justice.
- Kill him?
With your skills, just keep drinking, you.
What are you saying?
What of it? Huh?
Am I wrong?
What are you guys saying? The Son of the Demon King left the mountain?
Why does the Sect Leader want to kill him?
Girl, are you new in Jianghu?
As a big brother, I can only give you a word of advice: With matters of the legitimate sects, you better not join in the fun.
- Why?
The Sect Leader is determined to kill the Demon King's Son this time. If a little girl gets involved,
and the Sect Leader thinks you're going to save him,
- you're done for!
- Because he's done many wrong things, I shouldn't save him?
Little girl, I can't explain to you the details of this matter in a short time.
I'll advise you again, like an older brother.
When you mingle in Jianghu's matters, ponder well the situation. It's the only way to keep your life.
What's the point of living in surrender?
As long as you know good from evil and act as a good person, you can flaunt yourself a bit.
Where did you learn such foolish words?
Who are you calling a fool? When I say I'll do something, I'll do it at all costs.
In this fun, I'm going to take part for sure.
Wine– Where's the wine?
- Give it to me!
Son of the Demon King, wait. I'm coming to save you.
Master.
Your brow is furrowed. What matter troubles you?
Tomorrow, the sects will unite to put to death the son of the Demon King.
Has your heart been moved to compassion?
Those who have committed no evil, how can they be convicted of evil?
Good and evil are bound in cause and effect.
Tomorrow, you don't need to go to Fengmo Mountain.
Stay in your room and practice for your achievement.
Master, what is this for?
Lotus heart, caused by good intention,
a small carelessness will incite demons.
Former Master, forgive my selfish heart.
The pupil Qianxuan has extreme wisdom.
After Jinshen, he is the person who can most likely soar high.
I can't bear for him to be entrapped in the world of mortals.
If he does not meet that woman,
then this calamity can be kept from him.
Isn't he dying today?
Kill him
All convened sect fellows,
these have been troubled times in Jianghu.
After a long wait, I received Jin Xian's order
to arrest the son of the Demon King.
Today, he will be executed here
to deter evil in the world and return order to our Jianghu!
- Execute the son of the Demon King!
He should die, yes. He should
That's the son of the Demon King?
Yes.
Isn't he just a boy? Why is a crowd surrounding him demanding that he be killed?
He was born to evil magic. The son of the Demon King should just die.
This is also by Jin Xian's decree.
Who's Jin Xian?
You don't even know this?
Jin Xian Luo Mingxuan. He's a well-renowned great name in our sect.
Nonsense. How could Luo Mingxuan issue such a decree?
Then tell me. What did this boy do wrong?
Even if I don't know what wrong he did,
he's just evil. Evil should be killed.
This child's blood is an offer to our fellows.
- Offer to our fellows! Offer to our fellows!
There's so many of you bullying one boy, aren't you ashamed?
Where did this wench come from? What a brazen attitude!
And where did you come from, old man? What a bronze face!
(Note: "Bronze face" is an idiom that means that the person is bold or impudent)
Impudence!
Which sect and school are you from, girl? You must know that this act will make you an enemy of our sect.
I have no sect nor school. But if I want to make an enemy of you, what will you do?
Such a mad girl; daring to say that she will make an enemy of our sect?
Leaving alone all assembled masters, today,
if you can defeat me, you will be allowed to take him away.
Defeat you? Fine!
Don't be afraid. I'll take you away.
To deal with such a nameless pawn, there's no need for you to take action yourself.
Nameless pawn?
Here. Easy.
My name is Lu Qiong, styled Zhaoyao. Do not worry about forgetting it now.
In the future, the whole of Jianghu will make you remember me.
Wench, quell your arrogance!
You said if I win the fight, I can take him away.
I've fought everyone except you.
Are you fighting or not?
A girl with no sense of reality.
Who else?
To do what? Have you not been shamed enough?
Our sect holds true to its word. Since you defeated Deacon Chi,
we shall let the two of you leave as promised.
How rare. There's someone with reason here.
Only, after this day, each of our sects will spare no effort to hunt you down
along with this son of the Demon King.
Good and evil do not go hand in hand.
Girl, take heed for yourself.
My own road,
I'll walk myself. No need to worry.
How are you? I said I'll take you with me,
so I'll definitely take you.
You're the first person I have saved.
Let's go.
Go.
Th--
Master.
Every person has their mind. I have my own.
It's a good thing that you aren't deceived by vanity.
But the sect persists in its course,
the Thousand Dust Pavilion is in its midst.
What do you think we should do?
Demons are the enemy,
yet only those who sin are demons.
The orphan of the Demon King has done no evil.
At present, the sect persecuting him is not the right way, in truth.
The wise are afraid of the cause, the fools are afraid of the effect.
My opinion is that we should not corner and kill the son of the Demon King.
♫ If you don't personally seal that dream ♫
♫ you'll have the mark of being born a demon  ♫
♫ Cliffs of carnage blood like mountains and rivers  ♫
♫ Step into a fiery sea, to become a god  ♫
♫ The wind's rising; Nirvana comes from arrogant pride ♫
♫ On the remote road I'll always be there to trample the troubled times ♫
♫ To slash away fate's shackles  ♫
♫ To battle nature, breaking the swirl of gratitude and grudge  ♫
♫ This uproar hasn't settled, so what?  ♫
♫  If love is a thunderbolt's crushing roughness ♫
♫ Just stagger to the end of the world  ♫
♫ With no inscription, who would understand?  ♫
♫ Let feeling carve your heart  ♫
♫ Unbreakable, is the wild wave in the hands  ♫
♫ On the remote road I'll always be there to trample the troubled times ♫
♫ To slash away fate's shackles  ♫
♫ To battle nature, breaking the swirl of gratitude and grudge  ♫
♫ This uproar hasn't settled  ♫
♫ On the remote road, desolate, heaven and earth are shaken  ♫
♫ Drinking cold snow, majestically, come back to me  ♫
♫ After the thorn's pain, a tender flower blossoms  ♫
♫ I'll go with you, to die and forget, forever together  ♫