[The Legends]
[Episode 54]
Zhaoyao! Run!
Sect Leader!
Sect Leader...
A demon is a demon!
You all who were born as demons must be extinguished!
Brother Cangling.
We've been saved.
Yes.
Against all predictions, the time for some Immortal Sects to join hands again,
it was to face such a situation.
Obsession will turn a man into a demon.
This poor world! How many have perished again!
I'm not wrong.
The ones in the wrong are all of you.
Grandpa,
Gu Hanguang, Jiang Wu,
and every innocent soul that Luo Mingxuan killed,
I've avenged you all.
Mo Qing!
Mo Qing, what's happening to you?
Mo Qing! Wake up!
Mo Qing!
- Mo Qing!
- Don't touch me!
I won't let anything happen to you.
The same place.
In the end, we're still at sword's point.
As soon as you get out, you'll be killed by Liuhe Tianyi Sword.
If you die, you'll have nothing more.
Grasp it.
Join your mind and strength with me, we'll break the Liuhe Tianyi Sword.
From now on, you'll never fear death again.
There'll be nothing in the world you can't obtain.
Sect Leader.
Sect Leader!
You'll become the lord of the world.
If the price to become the lord is to plunge people in misery and suffering,
I won't have it.
What do the lives of the world have to do with you?
Millions of people are just millions of me and Zhaoyao.
I love her and love this world.
I don't want some great power,
nor do I want to become the lord of the world.
The only thing I want to control is my own fate.
Only power will allow you to control your own fate.
As for the people you love, their ruin or salvation will be a blink of thought for you.
The people never needed anyone to save them,
and I've never feared death.
If I lost myself, then I'd truly have nothing.
Foolhardy!
Mo Qing! Wake up!
Wake up, Mo Qing!
Zhaoyao...
Zhaoyao! Go out and cleave the Wanjun Sword!
Mo Qing!
- Mo Qing...
- Zhaoyao, help me!
Mo Qing!
♫  One night like a dream, there’s a curse inside my heart ♫
♫  One word flies past, suddenly forgetting past worries ♫
♫  One thought’s interval, pour out a bowl of wine ♫
♫  One glance, one life, no request ♫
♫ One frown, like magic, unhesitant to receive torture ♫
♫ One leaf makes Autumn, love and hate are groundless ♫
♫ One word, white hair, endless shallow waves, ♫
♫ One call, one life romance ♫
♫ One sentence, this life won't be changed; (I'll swagger through trials and tribulations) ♫
♫ Leaving me alone to go through joy and sorrow ♫
♫  If the years are too short  ♫
♫  I, Zhaoyao, will swagger through trials and tribulations ♫
♫ I'm fine with accompanying you for a lifetime ♫
♫  There's no need to make it difficult between the both of us ♫
♫ Gloomy in the brightest time ♫
♫  To love is common in life ♫
♫  There's even more happiness in dying ♫
Sect Leader,
I would give up everything for you,
as long as you're safe.
You cannot defeat me.
You cannot defeat us.
All who take Heaven's Sword must die by Heaven's Sword.
The importance of life is not in living or dying.
Beyond life and death, what can be of any importance?
I'm willing to perish for my madness, even if I'm burned to ashes.
I never thought that by extracting the sword I would actually meet you.
Mo Qing!
You already knew... didn't you?
Zhaoyao... this isn't destiny.
It's my choice.
Mo Qing!
Where are you...
Mo Qing! Don't be controlled by him!
Don't be controlled by him! Come back!
Don't be controlled by him!
I'm still waiting for you... to watch the stars together.
Don't be controlled by him...
Come back!
Mo Qing! Mo Qing!
In my lifetime,
many years were spent alone in the darkness.
My life and soul were still like dead water.
Until one person said
she saw a starry sky in my eyes.
Maybe she doesn't know
in my eyes there's only darkness
and she is all the shining things in my world.
Let's go back. To Wan Lu Sect.
Save me... I still have my wife, children, and parents.
I don't want to die. Save me!
Success or failure,
the people bear all the consequences.
[Phoenix's Song Hall]
This light...
Our master is comforting the souls of the dead.
So many people died in Mount Phoenix. He can't handle it alone.
Disciples of Thousand Dust Pavilion! Follow me and assist master!
Zhaoyao...
I'm here.
Demoness!
Rest for a bit more.
♫ If you don't personally seal that dream ♫
♫ you'll have the mark of being born a demon  ♫
♫ Cliffs of carnage blood like mountains and rivers  ♫
♫ Step into a fiery sea, to become a god  ♫
♫ The wind's rising; Nirvana comes from arrogant pride ♫
♫ On the remote road I'll always be there to trample the troubled times ♫
♫ To slash away fate's shackles  ♫
♫ To battle nature, breaking the swirl of gratitude and grudge  ♫
♫ This uproar hasn't settled, so what?  ♫
♫  If love is a thunderbolt's crushing roughness ♫
♫ Just stagger to the end of the world  ♫
♫ With no inscription, who would understand?  ♫
♫ Let feeling carve your heart  ♫
♫ Unbreakable, is the wild wave in the hands  ♫
♫ On the remote road I'll always be there to trample the troubled times ♫
♫ To slash away fate's shackles  ♫
♫ To battle nature, breaking the swirl of gratitude and grudge  ♫
♫ This uproar hasn't settled  ♫
♫ On the remote road, desolate, Heaven and Earth are shaken  ♫
♫ After the thorn's pain, a tender flower blossoms  ♫
♫ I'll go with you, to die and forget, forever together  ♫