Episode 1
Oh my god!
Lady Mozu, this is a mirror!
Oh my god! This is so beautiful!
There's such a beautiful place inside!
It's so incredible!
This is the whole mirror!
It's so beautiful!
Look! This is the Night Pearl!
So beautiful!
The Night Pearl is actually blinded by the 50 stars?
Oh my god!
Lady Mozu, this is so beautiful!
Lady Mozu, what are you looking at?
This should be the appearance of the sky in the
whole world!
Yes!
That's right! It's so amazing!
Come and help me out!
I want to see it!
Come on!
Slow down!
What's wrong?
There's a world here!
That's right!
Zhang Qi Ling, what are you doing here?
Why are you fighting for this?
What the hell are you doing?
Or why are you so calm in the valley?
What's the purpose of your wedding?
Sister Wen, what's going on?
I don't care.
Look.
There's nothing here.
'' fall here by fire ''
'' I'd like to cover them for you ''
'' You are afraid? ''
I think I've stopped there.
Then I'd rather become a woman.
You're coming home!
You've dreamt of becoming a woman.
So quite as to go on Return to heaven.
You go on. I'll deal with him.
How is it?
Golden Sword.
Don't be afraid.
What's going on?
Master!
Everyone, stay calm.
Don't move.
Go!
This is the shadow.
I'm glad to find this wall from a special angle.
The walls and the walls have formed this pattern.
That's right.
Everyone, don't panic.
This is a scientific phenomenon.
What is this drawing?
Xiao Zhang, what did you find?
It seems to be a painting of a master.
It looks like a play of the Celestial Palace.
Look.
This palace is actually built on a very steep hill.
The hill is misty.
It's surrounded by the whole palace.
It's like it's on the clouds.
Really?
It looks like a snow mountain.
Look!
Is that white snow on it?
The mountain is very high.
But I don't know which one.
It seems to be a high-rise.
The head is on my body.
These people are the ones who were buried, right?
So this is the Celestial Palace?
This is the tomb?
Who is the person who is in the coffin?
I don't think I've seen this historical record.
Me neither.
Who is it?
Why did you find the fire on this road?
It must be the Celestial Palace.
After the burial ceremony, they put the fire on it.
They destroyed the only road in the Celestial Palace.
If no one is there, the tomb will be safe.
But they can't even get out of here.
The Celestial Palace is surrounded by the dead bodies of the Celestial Palace.
The feudal society is too cruel.
Why did the Celestial Palace disappear?
Could it be that it's really on the sky?
This must be the Snow Mountain.
The Celestial Palace is surrounded by it.
Can't you see it?
No.
It's the whole mountain covered by the snow.
Then this whole mountain
will become the tomb of the Huozhen Stone?
It's not a new season.
It's a great honor to bring the human spirit to the palace.
It's all fate.
I think the Huozhen Stone is also a part of the Yu Huai.
It seems that even if we find the Celestial Palace,
it will be hard to get it out.
I'm not afraid.
I believe that technology will be more and more developed.
We will find the Celestial Palace one day.
Yes.
This one.
What's wrong?
Someone's inside!
What's going on?
Who's there? Come out!
It's Wu San Xing!
I saw his face!
Are you sure it's San Xing?
Can you see it clearly?
I... I only saw his face!
It's okay.
...
I'm scared.
What are you scared of? There are so many of us.
It's okay. Let's go together.
That old womangirl!
What are you doing here, woman?
Are you all right?
alien
Are you doing badly
Bubiblist
Don't make sound
and get inside
OK
Why is there water?
D buzzing
Whicion result will she get?
What such a weird response.
It's incredible
Suddenly you cry
And describe your drawing
It's beautiful
Not only about the dream, I don't even remember myself.
Until a few months later,
I've been thinking about some of Lin Cui's shortcomings.
And after a few years, I've found that I've got some problems.
I don't remember the reason.
But three months ago, I met your uncle.
I think he's very strict.
I wanted to know more about myself, so I married you guys to the Seven Stars Dragon Palace.
There, I found that your uncle had some problems.
No, Ping'er. You said that you lost your memory after you came out of the sea.
Maybe it's because of the smell of the organs here.
You've caused a hallucination.
So before you fainted, you didn't see my uncle.
It has nothing to do with my uncle.
The Golden Thread Embroidery you got from the Golden Thread Embroidery is fake.
It's true.
I'm not sure.
But the Golden Thread Embroidery you got from the Golden Thread Embroidery is fake.
It's true. You've already lost your memory.
Li Youping,
how do I remember that you lost your memory?
No, it's your uncle.
He and Da Kui.
They were able to hit the coffin directly from behind.
Why did Da Kui die?
The Golden Thread Embroidery
It's impossible.
It's a dream.
Think about it.
How many things did your uncle hide from you?
He lied to you.
You must know how many things your uncle didn't do right.
How about my uncle?
I know better than anyone else.
He can't have me killed.
If it's really your uncle,
he won't harm you.
But...
What do you mean?
You're talking about a fraud.
No matter who says it's true or not,
we have to wait until we get out.
You just want to stay here and stay here.
You can talk to the old lady in the office.
You can talk about the truth.
Yes.
Let Fatty dress up.
The Golden Thread Embroidery
Fatty, you're really blind.
You're a girl.
You know what?
This is called a man's harmony.
At this moment, I'm the beautiful woman.
The beautiful woman is me.
The door is open.
Open.
Okay.
Fatty, I'm asking you.
Shouldn't you go to the Palace of Heaven?
We can't just sit here and wait for the night pig.
It's good to have a few night pigs.
You're right.
I knew it.
When did you come to the Palace of Heaven?
You're wronged.
I have a plan for Fatty.
Didn't Yabozhang say that the stone is upper floor.
Plus, the room with the wall is very high.
Plus, the top floor is ten meters high.
How deep is the whole tomb?
If we want to go out, we have to go down from the top floor.
We have three ways to go out.
The first way is to go back the original way.
But we can't figure out the changes in the past.
I don't know if we can go back to the beginning.
The second way is to repair the tomb.
It will be a secret passage to prevent the burial.
But the secret passage is to the sea.
This is the problem before us.
The sea is so deep that there is no oxygen.
We can't go up there.
It's not like the cliff is also a hole.
So we can't go up there.
The third way is to go out.
It seems to be on the line.
When we just entered the tomb, I saw the water pressure.
At that time, our water level was only 13 meters.
The current water level is just above the tomb.
The water level is just above the tomb.
So we can't go up to 30 meters.
So...
The room with the sky-drying model is just below the sea level.
We can't go up to 10 meters.
We have a chance to go out.
Fatty, you can do it.
You finally said something.
I'm not going up there.
Stop pretending to be my mom.
Stop wasting time.
Fine.
I won't bother you anymore.
By the way, I'm warning you.
If you really go in there, don't run away.
If you have a chance to go out,
you can't just die and die.
That's a bad idea.
The last warning.
Don't touch the night table.
okolade
You mean it's not even open?
Don't you love me anymore?
Not even me.
Will you go and ask for it?
Absolutely not.
I have promised you
I'm going to kill you.
Sofia
Yan Ming Chu
I bet the owner's crush is low-χa-rib action.
It is?
I'm not shocked to see it.
The man is actually the local official.
Don't think he's the previous policeman.
St нужно
I guess it's a small town.
I guess it's not that big.
It's not certain.
He must have his reason for this.
After all, it's a shipyard.
There is a limit to space.
To make it more dangerous,
we have to save space here.
Besides,
if it's a child or a beast,
who can imagine a fat man?
Yes.
The ancient machine is a part of the modern world.
Fat man must be the first to talk about the body.
But that's money.
I'm not losing weight.
It's really...
No, this...
You're not losing weight.
Just now, you said you were stuck in the car.
No, this wall is a problem.
No, the wall is a temporary home.
Let's go back first.
Let's go.
No, you have to find a way.
Otherwise, the guys are here.
They'll get cold.
Let's go back.
Maybe there's a trap.
It's too late.
Go up.
Go!
Hurry up, fat man!
Wait for me!
Come on!
Go!
It's so dangerous.
I told you, I don't want to be killed by a snake.
I don't want to be a demon.
Thank you, Your Highness.
He's a big man.
Go and rest.
Don't hurt the dog.
No, no, don't.
Don't.
Look.
What?
Wu Sanxing killed me.
I was killed by him.
I'm a traitor.
Who killed Xie Lianhuan?
Why did he kill him?
Xie Lianhuan was also a reliable person.
He died in the stone bridge.
He was a traitor.
Is there a problem here?
Where could be a problem?
It's here, look.
It's not ready yet.
Let me see.
Give it to me.
What's wrong?
What's the problem?
He said it's not ready yet,
but he insisted on it.
He's so impulsive.
He's looking for a way out.
It's a chance to find a solution for you.
Don't you want to be a traitor?
I want to be your hero.
I want to see who is more capable than me.
You're so stupid. We're all old friends.
Let me do it.
Even I...
Enough, enough. Let's go to the store.
Why don't you give me a hug?
You can say it without a word.
Come over and take a look at this water tank.
There seems to be some problems.
I'm sorry.
I...
I'll pretend to be a pervert.
Impossible.
What if you pretend to be a pervert?
I'm sure you'll...
Enough, enough, enough.
Wenjing, leave me alone.
Nobody knows you then.
Get out of the way.
Everybody, hurry up.
Okay.
Everyone is here.
What a propaganda-major.
A special 1970s car diy.
How come you came?
I came here to see you.
I've been talking to you for a long time.
Can you take me out to have a look?
What do you mean?
What do you want to see?
You're going to travel to your own place.
Can you play with the team?
San, please help me tell Wenjing
that I don't need your salary.
I can help you.
I'm better than the students in his hands.
Tell me, what's your idea?
I...
I'm also a person...
Join us soon.
At the A-Memory Theatre, 994466.
Come.
Who?
What do you want?
A foreigner.
The foreigner who will go with you to the label?
San, how do you know?
How do I know?
I want to ask you.
How do you know that Xie Shi Mu?
I want to ask him to take me to the label.
The foreigner who will go with you to the label.
He lived in Changsha for a long time.
I know him.
I don't know how he knows that Xie Shi Mu.
But he doesn't know the situation there.
So he wants me to take him there.
San, you don't know that it's too dangerous there.
I almost got killed.
You're a bastard.
You dare to go with him to the label.
You don't want him to send you to the scene in the newspaper?
It's okay, San.
Now it's business society.
It's all about brains.
I want him to take me to the label to help him.
But it's too obvious there.
There's no permission to go to the label.
The boat is not allowed.
Well...
It's convenient to go with the label.
Don't worry. I promise.
It's not going to affect the document.
If it's not convenient, forget it.
I'll think of a way.
It's not convenient.
But I can't do it alone.
I have to discuss it with Wen Jing.
Of course you have to listen to him.
Wen Jing is the leader, right?
Come on, come on.
Brother, I'll toast you.
Bastard!
How can you treat Xie Lian Huan?
How can you treat Xie family?
durchaus
The Remark
Part II
I remember there was a check boy
in my shop
where he felt like everything was strange
It looked like he eyed very big
maybe the lift Heinander
i can't even jump
I need to use a small boat
I don't know why
I carry him
I'm sorry.
It seems that this Xie Lian Huan is a master.
This is a self-proclaimed move.
Even if this is a small accident,
it won't cause a lot of danger.
Under such a tense situation,
it's still possible to be so calm.
It's not easy.
Xing Xi,
can you kill the old man?
Yabuzhang,
you are in the team.
With the old man's master,
you are in trouble.
I don't remember.
You should remember how to leave.
You should leave the hospital.
Let me ask you.
You were doing well before.
Why did we have to be added to the meat?
Did you take the wrong way?
Unless it's just a signal from the door.
It's possible that we didn't leave the door.
But the door of death.
Who can do this?
Ning.
I tell you, this girl is real.
I...
Maybe she wants to help Yü Sidi.
But she can't.
She's been acting like a monster.
So it's your uncle.
But don't think too much.
She can't be your nephew.
She wants to be Xie Lian Huan.
How bad is your uncle's relationship with her?
It's impossible.
Xie Lian Huan is close to my family.
She's almost three years old.
And I saw her when I was little.
I had an impression on her.
Are you a fight?
No.
Brother.
How much do you remember about Xie Lian Huan?
I don't remember.
Look.
But I have an idea.
If Xie Lian Huan and your uncle knew each other,
they would be close.
They didn't show up when they entered the test team.
But when they entered the first time,
Xie Lian Huan found out about the underwater tomb.
And he found out about the entrance to the underwater tomb.
He didn't tell anyone.
But he told your uncle.
It's hard to give up this opportunity
with their birth.
So they found out about the underwater tomb
while the test team didn't pay attention.
They're both experts.
It's hard for them.
But they're both experts.
They're both experts.
So the Excel team found out about the entrance want to enter.
mange
And to run away and run away again for good.
Sorry, thanks.
Say goodbye to the talk you saw.
It's too late to go to Similarly Credits Bureau.
Open the door! What do you mean? Open the door!
I'm not in the mood! I'm not in the mood!
Open the door! Open the door!
The bridge and the river in the water are all money.
How much do you want to spend to make yourself die in the tomb?
Don't do anything.
We can't know the exact reason for their rebellion.
But we can be sure that when Xie Lian Huan was walking on the road,
there was blood on the wall.
But he suddenly found out that the wall was empty.
So he used his equipment to make a tunnel here,
and saved his life.
But he died in the tomb afterwards.
Maybe Xie Lian Huan wanted to find your uncle after he was born.
But your uncle killed him.
We can't be sure that when Xie Lian Huan was walking on the road,
there was blood on the wall.
But he died in the tomb afterwards.
Maybe Xie Lian Huan wanted to find your uncle after he was born.