Now the world needs you and now the world needs me
for all the world needs you
and if all is possible
human beings will stand by the holy head
I'm afraid of the stars in my heart.
I've been searching for the stories of the nightfall
that disappeared in the history of Chen'ai.
It's a great pleasure.
However, the facts are not as simple as I thought.
What are you doing? Go away!
What I've encountered in these ancient tombs
is a completely different story
from the stories of the ancient people's cunning and cunning.
I've found that in my life,
there are too many mysteries
that are related to these tombs.
When I was young,
Yangyang, don't move.
No one can predict the future.
I think that every time I see the truth,
I think that the reason is to persist.
Wu Xie,
I've found the old photo.
I'll take it back.
You gave me this photo.
From the internet,
there is only one result.
However, according to the IP address,
I can confirm that the person who posted it was in Beijing.
Who are these people in this photo?
This is a test team of decades ago.
I've been inside for three days.
But I've never seen such a detailed list of people.
Besides this list,
is there anything else that can be found?
I can try.
Look at it yourself.
At the station,
The Seventh Floor of the Sea? Can we find the exact location of this person?
The Seventh Floor of the Sea? This name
is not only used by him on the Internet.
Recently, it appeared in the company system of Terescom.
I translated this website. It seems to be a company with a computer science and technology.
They are always in Hangzhou.
Terescom.
The company with a computer science and technology
is still in the company.
What are you thinking about?
You are looking for a high-end computer company and you are still in the Seventh Floor?
The search engine has provided a clue that has been ignored by us.
What clue?
On July 20, I found the entrance of the Seventh Floor of the Sea.
After that, the Seventh Floor was left alone and was in the South.
There are still nine people left in the list.
But there are only eight people left in the list on July 24.
There is one missing.
Yes.
If he didn't go to the Seventh Floor,
then he wouldn't be in the South.
But why didn't he go to the Seventh Floor?
I will take the blame.
He might know that the Seventh Floor is dangerous.
So he left the Seventh Floor alone.
So you think that there is a problem with the people on the Seventh Floor, right?
If there is a problem, we will know.
Yes.
Fatty.
I have a question.
What question?
Why am I wearing this?
You are just pretending to be a bodyguard.
Remember, you are a big boss of a company.
I am a boss. I am a family member.
What is this?
I don't usually wear this kind of clothes.
I am wasting money.
What else can I do?
Remember, being an actor is the most important thing.
You are a actor.
All of us are actors.
I am so tired of acting.
I am dying.
Is it that important to be in the Seventh Floor?
Shouldn't we put the center of gravity on the sea and the sky?
You are right.
That is so ridiculous.
We can't go through the waves of peace.
What is that person called?
A smoker, right?
Hello.
We are here to see President Xiao.
President Xiao is having a meeting.
Do you have an appointment?
I called President Xiao's secretary yesterday.
We are here to talk about cooperation.
You are really a fish.
Of course not.
Let's talk about it later.
So hot.
President, are you up to anything?
What will happen now?
I have to go to the CPC English Association.
And your name, correct?
If you don't stop talking about it,
I will kill you.
You want us to go back to the audience?
Forget it.
Go.
Sit.
President Xiao, Hello
It's...
Our channel is not a garbage and isn't offered by human Дм ordinarily
It's from our boss, Director Wang
I'm the founder and our composer
Sit
First of all, I'd like to thank President Xiao
for giving me this opportunity to introduce my company.
Our next company is the first company
to develop the smart machine in China.
In fact, the smart machine
has already been developed by foreigners.
This must be the most promising
industry at the moment.
The high-tech information company wants to
move forward in the industry.
That's the best option.
Let me show you my idea.
As long as you give me your big data,
I can immediately give you a model.
The artificial intelligence machine
will definitely use your company
to make people believe in you.
I think you two should stop wasting your time
on me.
Maybe you have some misunderstandings
about my company.
I hope that in the future,
you can find the right partner
to fulfill your dream soon.
I have a meeting this afternoon.
I won't be here for a long time.
President Xiao,
I may not be able to express my opinion
clearly, but I know that the best
is the cloud data output.
Let me give you an example.
Just like the sea island,
once you have the opportunity to get the data,
you can send it to your big data
through the data storage in the cloud data storage.
If it is more and more,
I don't know what your real purpose is.
I have only one thing to say.
I can't provide anything you want.
We can't work together.
Send it to the big data storage.
Please.
You are not selling the cloud data here.
You don't have any information.
Why are you mentioning the sea island 701?
I did it on purpose.
I just want to see the information.
What is the reaction after hearing this name?
Why?
I have seen the pictures.
Look carefully.
The list mentioned in the sea island 701.
Chen Wenjing, Huo Lian, Li Sidi, Zhang Qilian.
Xiao Da?
Does Xiao Huo have anything to do with Xiao Da?
I don't know if he does,
but he must have something to do with sea island 701.
After hearing this name,
his reaction is clear.
Hello.
Why are you here?
I remember you.
You came here last time, right?
Yes.
I have a impression.
I dropped it.
Don't break it.
Time is running out.
Please let me have a look at the computer.
Be careful.
What?
I came here today to meet you,
Mr. Xiao.
In the past,
our staff was Xiao Xie.
What happened?
A black shell is in my computer.
You are sea island 701?
I can't.
What are you doing?
President Xiao, I really have no enemies on you.
Please tell me the truth about the
truth.
I promise I won't bother you again.
But I won't leave even if I die today.
Because I lost my uncle before one month.
The only one who knows the truth is you.
Only you.
Your uncle?
My uncle is Wu San Xing.
Sir, you can't go in.
President Xiao, sorry.
I didn't stop you.
One month ago,
I was told that someone used me
and went to the ADIM.
I went to the ADIM personally
and didn't find him.
If you're telling the truth,
I mean understanding and sympathy.
But I'm sorry.
I know what's going on.
It's useless to you.
As long as you give me the data of your cloud,
and help me,
I'll analyze it myself.
I've had nothing to do with what happened that year.
I didn't participate in any of the events.
Please understand me.
I don't want to be disturbed
by any of the events.
Okay.
I'll finish the job this morning.
I'll go to the ADIM.
Stop it.
I think he doesn't want to tell us
the reason for the accident.
What's the reason?
He's just a doctor.
He doesn't want to affect his family
because of this.
No matter what I say,
you're still a kid.
You're dead.
This is not the end.
Go back to Beijing.
Go back?
You're going back to Beijing?
I just arrived here this morning.
I'll go back.
You can go back to Beijing.
Stay here.
I'll pack the food.
I'll go find Ji Xiu Zhang.
No.
I...
I'm going to the ADIM.
I'll go to the ADIM.
Reinhard,
What?
Hello, hello.
Hello.
Dr. Li.
Right.
Do you know that you let my mom cure it?
Now, she's got the nerve.
She's so healthy and grateful to you.
Probably yes.
I'm so grateful to you.
I should.
Why did I come here today
to see Mr. Xiao Yu?
Mr. Xiao's wife.
Is she his mother?
Is he his mother?
His mother is in the lake.
She's in the sun.
Mr. Xiao is here, too.
Yes, his mother.
Okay, okay.
How can I go to the lake?
Do you want some water?
I'll get it for you.
This is a pond.
I can't drink it for a few days.
I'm so thirsty.
Mrs. Xiao Yu.
Are you Xiao Yu's mother?
I'm...
You're not my name?
My name is Wang.
Wang?
You're Wang's son, right?
Yes, yes.
I know your father.
I'm Wang's son.
Yes, yes.
I know your father.
Your father is Wang.
Wang.
Wang, Wang, Wang.
Dad.
Si.
Okay, okay.
To be honest,
I'm getting more and more
into this kind of physical and mental disorder.
We don't have a better way to do it.
You take the time to accompany him.
Go out and walk.
Try not to cause any sensitive problems.
Okay, I got it.
Mr. Xiao.
Why are you here?
Where's my mom?
Your friend came to see her.
She's talking to her.
What friend?
Mr. Xiao.
You're doing this together?
Yes, he's not just a company
with information about the Pugong Eagle.
And we're also doing a test.
Do you know what's going on?
The underwater tomb, the Seaside Island, the 701?
The underwater tomb?
Mom.
Who told you to go to the valley?
Tell us.
Mom.
Who told you to go to the valley?
I don't know who told you to go to the valley.
Mom, it's okay.
Xiao Yu's attitude is more determined than I thought.
And everything about the valley
is important to the management of the secret body.
All the troubles
are all gathered in the Seaside and the Seaside.
What kind of power
can make so many people go to the valley?
The three Seaside and the Seaside
are in the Luang Palace,
the Seaside and Seaside.
Where's the other one?
Is it the Cloud Sky Palace?
These three graves
are the Seaside and the Seaside.
The other one
is the Cloud Sky Palace
which can be used as a memorial service.
What's the connection between these three graves?
Where's the suit?
It's off.
What's wrong with this?
What's so strange?
What's that?
What do you want?
After being touched,
I didn't give up.
I went to the hospital.
After being touched, I gave up.
I was a child.
I envy you.
You have a mother.
I didn't have a wife.
I didn't have a family.
Mr. Xiao. Mr. Xiao.
I'm sorry.
returned.
OMG.
You guys look like each other.
They
went to the relative to find the relative.
You?
Mr. Zhao.
What's the situation?
Xiao Yu is cold blooded.
He's too strong to protect himself.
But he's not willing to do that.
If a family gets into a fight,
then no one will be able to handle it.
Is he Xiao Da?
Yes.
And I'm telling you,
Xiao Da is the only one who hasn't been to the bottom of the sea.
He's the one who's been to the bottom of the sea.
The archaeological team member.
My father and Wu San Xing, Chen Wen Jin and the others,
went to the Xisha Islands together.
On the day of the sunset, he sent a message to the team.
The archaeological team's teammates left him alone on the sea.
When he woke up, it's been three days.
Did he do it himself?
He didn't dare to do it.
I went to investigate the unit of the archaeological team.
I couldn't find anything.
Where did he go?
He went back to Beijing alone.
My father had to go to the Xisha Islands at least three times a year.
He's been going on for two to three years.
Until he found someone.
My uncle found him?
Yes.
Xiao Da was happy.
He's always been your uncle's fan.
Did my uncle mention anything else?
Did he mention anything else?
He wanted to...
He wanted to ask Xiao Da about Xiao Da's whereabouts.
My father has been following Wu San Xing's way.
Wu San Xing couldn't explain it.
He didn't ask.
My father asked Wu San Xing.
What happened in the bottom of the sea?
What did Wu San Xing say?
He said that no matter if they were dead or alive,
they would be dead or alive.
But I think he really wanted to find someone.
Not these people.
Fatty, there's a MP3 here.
This is Xiao Yi Lu.
Your uncle and Xiao Da fought with Lu.
Why didn't you go?
What are we looking for?
We're looking for a team of the anti-tank teams.
But they've already died half of China.
If I can get out of the bottom of the sea, they'll be...
It's different.
Even the West Union is dead.
How could they be alive?
They must be alive.
They have a key.
The secret is not always sealed.
There's always a day when we need to see the light.
We're in this situation.
We can't forget our real purpose.
Do you understand what I mean?
Fatty.
Who drew this?
I don't know. Xiao Yi didn't say anything.
Can I ask him?
It's all here.
You can just ask him.
If you don't find him, you can ask him.
I don't think it's good to see him.
Boss Xiao, it's late at night.
I'm sorry to bother you.
There's something else in here.
Can you tell me who drew it?
Please watch out.
It's late.
I don't know what it is.
This was the reason
for my father's справ finan 1954's peace assembly.
I don't know why my father got lost.
Hello.
Is Chinese Yives here?
They have been here.
The photo that the enemy left us was sent to you.
It was the same as the old photo you sent.
No.
I was sure that this photo had no signature on it.
I'm sure.
I've checked it.
It wasn't the photo you gave me.
Also,
there was a snake-mei-tong on this photo.
The snake-mei-tong is on his hand.
Besides, the enemy wants to see you.
I've checked it.
He's wearing a mask.
Do you want to see him?
Yes.
What do you need to do?
Put him on the boat.
Don't let him run away.
Got it.
The wind is blowing.
Why did you bring me here?
You want to see me?
Just take it as a reason.
Spring is not good.
You don't want to kiss me?
I said,
go now.
I'm not going.
I'll wait for you here.
Don't regret it.
I'll wait for you.
You're looking for me?
Someone wants to see you.
Have a seat.
Okay.
I'll wait for you here.
What do you want?
What's up, Wu?
Do you want a song?
I'm sorry, ladies.
I lost the game
because of the real-life adventure.
My friends
asked me to come here.
Please drink this bottle of wine.
Come on.
What's up?
Who's the winner?
Do you know who's the winner?
You're also the winner of the game.
You go first.
Okay.
Come on.
I have one of the same kind of fish.
I need to find two more.
How do you know there are three?
I'm going to find one.
What are you going to find?
This is the third question.
I'm going to find the third one.
Is this the third question?
I'm not asking you.
Are you still my friend?
I'm too anxious.
Because the same kind of fish is important to me.
Since you're also investigating the same kind of fish,
you should have seen that photo.
The Western Sands Valley team.
You should know
that my uncle Xie Lian Huan
is also in that photo.
Which one is your uncle?
This one.
This one?
Are you sure this is my uncle?
This photo is low-speed.
You admit it wrong and you don't have enough time to maintain it.
Besides, as far as I know,
when they were young, they really looked alike.
Even if someone said they were twins, they also had a personality.
And don't forget,
Xie Wu and I are related by marriage.
They were originally brothers.
So they look alike.
What's so strange about them?
They look alike.
I know.
My lord,
I'm here to talk to you.
Uncle,
you're back.
What have you been up to?
Yu Chen.
He's your uncle Wu Jia.
They look alike.
He's very Sociological.
So, I realized that they were in a group.
Four people decided not to see any other of them
even my Complex was corrupted from the mission.
So I didn't have enoughふふ.
Look.
Sorry.
What's your money?
You haven't told me how you came up with three of the same fish.
And you also know that the relationship between the fish and the archaeologist is not the same.
Are you investigating the archaeology too?
I went to the Western Desert to see the archaeologist before it was too late.
Wu Xie, you shouldn't have come in here.
Listen to me.
Keep it.
As long as I haven't found the clue,
I'll keep investigating this matter.
Before I came here, I was worried about something.
So I put the same fish in my house.
When I come back to Hangzhou, I'll send it to you.
Why give it to me?
There are three of the same fish.
If you can use two,
maybe I'll help you find another one.
I'm not interested in the secret behind the same fish.
The reason I found the clue is because
It's because I'm very likely to find out the reason why I was born.
Xiaohua,
it seems that we are doing the same thing.
So,
if you have any clues,
remember to tell me.
Okay.
You finished?
Do you want me to send you back?
No need.
I have a friendもう
What's going on?
Is it him?
You didn't tell me that.
If something happens, what will you do?
It's not like a flower.
Or you won't know how to die.
I didn't expect it to be a flower.
He scared me.
A flower is so mysterious.
It's so beautiful.
It's crazy.
So,
he was investigating the truth about the sea.
His purpose is to find out
the cause of Xie Lian Huan's death.
Then tell him the word.
This is what I'm most worried about.
Once he knows about the suicide,
he will think that it was me who killed Xie Lian Huan.
You also think it was me?
No.
You don't dare to do it.
So,
I must find out the truth.
Tell Xiaohua.
I can't let Xie Lian Huan die.
Right?
Turn left.
Enough.
I'm a good person.
I'm not a good person.
Xiaohua is a fool.
She doesn't know Xiaohua.
It's impossible.
She is so fat.
She must be so tired.
I just feel sorry for Xiaohua.
You are so important.
Drink something.
Don't forget anything.
Besides,
you can find out the cause of Xie Lian Huan's death.
You helped Xiaohua.
What do you think?
Do you have a good relationship?
We played together when we were young.
I was a good person when I was a kid.
I was married and had a good relationship.
But now I don't know anyone.
Fatty,
get ready to go abroad.
Where are you going?
I found a way to help Xiaohua.
O implemented
Xiaohua
odzi
Western
Bronze
gerne
Economy
I'm wondering the news striking is not new?
We need to go abroad already.
I don't know if you are crazy or I am.
Maybe we are all crazy.
This is not a romantic night.
People usually don't know this.
I tell you, this is abroad.
You don't know.
Just like this.
This place is not in our country.
It's abroad, right?
It's safe when you come back.
It's so dangerous.
Let's find someone to talk to.
And let him stay in our country.
It's safer when we are in our country.
You are right.
Of course.
Can we go?
Where should we go?
We can't go.
How?
Hurry up.
This is your car.
Don't you know my car?
Let's bet.
Let's bet on the first one.
What?
Let's bet.
We will say it later.
But first,
we will record it first.
Then send it to Weibo.
Don't deny it.
Ready, go!
Hello, I am Wu Xie.
I bet with Wang Pongzi.
I will go to the Hengdeli Museum first.
I will go there first.
I will make a video.
See?
Fatty is here.
What's wrong, Fatty?
You are not well.
I am fine.
What do you say?
What's wrong?
I haven't decided yet.
The museum is not big.
Well,
you owe me a wish.
When will I make a decision?
When will I return it?
How can you?
You are a real man.
Of course.
I can't take it.