[English subtitles are available]
[Beloved Life]
[Episode 15]
Fine, I lost.
Lip gloss, huh?
Come on.
But no girl in our department
carries a lipstick around, right?
No lipstick?
Well, that's not on me.
I have one.
I now announce
that Du Di won.
I'll fulfill my duty
by punishing the loser.
Don't worry, Dr. Lin.
I'll be very careful with your lips.
I promise it'll feel like your first kiss.
My baby girl.
It looks great.
So exotic.
Move, please.
My God.
So many people today.
Has everybody chosen this day to give birth?
Don't you know?
I see you don't know your job well.
It's not relevant,
is it?
What month is it?
August.
Yeah.
August is a peak month.
How come August is a peak month?
For what I can tell, many Chinese
are virgos or scorpios.
Because people have time
for weddings during the Spring Festival.
So October
and November are peak months.
It's because
there's a long national day holiday in October,
many people
hold their weddings in the holiday.
So the next year's August
is the peak month
for childbirth.
I totally forgot about
the national day holiday.
When do I get
to have a 7-day national day holiday?
In your dreams.
Unless all babies
decide to take a break, too.
I'm so tired.
I feel you. Look.
The parturients
have doubled in the last two years.
But there are only these beds
in the Obstetric and Gynecologic Department.
When the hallways are full,
we'll have to shove people in the staircases.
Short-staffed, insufficient beds.
This has been the toughest condition
for you residents so far.
I heard
Director Tian
grew gray hairs
in order to apply for more beds
for the Obstetric and Gynecologic Department.
Would the situation improve
when he becomes the deputy dean?
You just started your work here,
don't you
gossip about the director like others.
I'm not gossiping.
It's been posted
on the notice board.
Liu Zhenghua of the Neurosurgery Department
versus Tian Yunshan of the Obstetric and Gynecologic Department.
There will be a vote in a few days.
I'll vote for Director Tian.
It's none of your business.
It's a vote within the leadership.
Just get back to your work.
Stop taking naps.
If we don't deliver at least 8 babies a night,
then the government
has approved the long holiday for nothing.
I'm going to deliver babies.
Director Tian, you asked to see me?
Nianbai. Come. Sit.
I asked you to come here
to talk to you about
the sickbed scramble between the Obstetric and Gynecologic Department
and your father's Neurosurgery Department.
Look at the problem
Du Di had.
If we had enough beds
here in our department,
she wouldn't have rejected the family.
She would think before act.
It's the peak season for childbirth.
As you can see,
even the hallways are full.
Over the spare rooms in the old building,
your father and I
are also having a fight.
It is a real headache
for the leadership of our hospital.
They reconciled differences regardless of principles
and said whoever had a higher-level project
could get the beds.
So, is there any update
on your father?
I never care about him.
Well, you should.
He's your father, after all.
I don't want to speak to him.
By the way,
could your teacher
do his research here at Shengji?
Here's his suggestion.
He will work with you.
But the research funds
will be applied from both domestic and overseas channels.
This way,
the cash flow won't be a problem.
And both of your names
will be on the research achievement.
Great. Perfect.
Let's get it going.
I'll ask him
how we push this thing forward.
Once this is achieved,
I consider myself
live up to Director Zhang's expectations.
What was Director Zhang like?
How come every one of you
holds him in high esteem?
Director Zhang
was the last student
of the master obstetrician-gynecologist of Shengji Hospital,
as well as the shiniest rising star
in the academic community of obstetrics and gynecology.
He was a top-notch doctor
both academically and clinically.
If everything went in the right direction,
he would become
the youngest academician.
Many excellent students
and social resources
would follow Director Zhang.
Director Huang and I
also studied under his instructions.
Du Di was his
last doctoral student.
Director Zhang
wasn't going to recruit a doctoral student.
But why did he want Du Di?
Because he saw
the commitment in her
was the same as he had when he was young.
Director Zhang would only sleep
for 3 to 4 hours a day.
He was in poor health when he just reached 40.
For the good reputation
of the Obstetric and Gynecologic Department of Shengji,
he burned himself out.
He had no idea
that he had a late-stage cancer.
It was Shengji's greatest shame
that we failed to save his life.
I was wondering
why you keep giving Du Di chances
even though
you don't like her.
It's not that
we don't dislike her.
Du Di has the potential
to be a top-notch doctor.
However, the doctor-patient relationship
nowadays is complicated.
It takes more to be a good doctor
than using a scalpel well.
If she was half empathic
as Director Zhang,
I wouldn't have a second thought.
But maybe it's also my problem.
I'm not a good boss
for doctors like Du Di.
Director Zhang once said
the young people should have the chance
to decide their targets and positions
based on their characters.
Speaking of that,
Director Zhang was not only a academical master,
but also a good mentor.
I feel bad that I fail to put
what I learned from Director Zhang into practice.
Director Tian,
I will do whatever I can
to help the Obstetric and Gynecologic Department.
This is, after all, the department that my mother
used to work in.
Oh, speaking of your mother,
you'll receive a gift from me
some time later.
What gift?
Wang Ying, the head nurse
told me that
you were searching for your mother's medical record.
Yes.
I can give that to you.
Mrs. Wang Ying said
there was nothing special about the medical record.
Nothing special
in the record of the Obstetric and Gynecologic Department.
But your mother
also went to other departments.
I believe this is what you want.
Nianbai,
you are now
a member of our department.
Frankly,
I won't allow the Obstetric and Gynecologic Department
to go down
under my management.
I'll make it better.
But to do this,
I'll need you to join hands with me.
I see.
I'll do my best for our department.
Thank you.
Have you made up your mind?
When will you give me the thing?
Honestly, I have
nothing for you.
I only had a slip of the tongue
before the operation.
How about this?
You stop taking beds
from the Obstetric and Gynecologic Department.
I won't report you if you do that.
Did Tian Yunshan send you here?
It was my own choice.
I am also a member of the Obstetric and Gynecologic Department.
When did you
get the sense
of responsibility and honor?
I like working in the Obstetric and Gynecologic Department.
The girl I like also works
in the department.
And I sincerely
want to contribute to our department.
Well, I guess
I'll take your word for it.
But I can tell you this,
I'm not fighting him
over the beds and the deputy dean position
for my personal interest.
The Neurosurgery Department has recently
founded a state-level key laboratory.
It needs more resources.
I need more beds,
and I need to be the deputy dean.
Otherwise,
it will be difficult
for me to push the project forward, do you understand?
I understand.
But I don't accept it.
I thought
you've changed
and become sensible.
Well, I guess it was my delusion.
Listen,
I don't want Mom's legacy.
Give us the beds.
Not a chance.
Alright, I changed my mind.
I want the beds and the thing.
And I'll get them.
Let's wait and see.
The project that Nianbai
introduced should be
the most important one for me in this year.
Considering one head scientist
can only be in charge of one project
and follow two subjects,
I'd like each of you
to be in charge of one subject respectively.
No problem.
It's just my baby will be born.
That will take some of my time.
Well, I refuse.
Can you take off your mask?
Do I not deserve
your respect?
I'm cold.
It's summer, and you're telling me you're cold?
What is going on?
I lost a bet.
Can you be serious?
Can you please
think more about the department's future
and yours?
No.
Unbelievable.
He's hopeless.
It's not the first day
that we know he's not into academic research.
Calm down.
We're short of academic manpower.
I suggest you steal
some director-level doctors
from other hospitals,
and promote some of
the residents and attending physicians
to prepare and build
a scientific research team of our own.
I tried. It was hard.
Not long ago,
I participated in an academic meeting.
I only had a few words with the director
of the Obstetric and Gynecologic Department in Nanling Hospital
before their dean took him away in a hurry
as if I'm a pickpocket.
We'll take our time stealing directors.
But we can start building a talent team as soon as possible.
What do we do now?
On the basis of your research project,
organize an open competition for the young doctors.
They can choose their own subjects
that they're interested in and do a report.
We'll appraise their information-collecting ability,
analytical ability, and basic skills.
To put it simply, who does a good job
gets into the research team?
Yes.
Good. You go make the announcement.
I'll give them one night.
This is a rare opportunity.
Director Tian
will select members
for his project
based on your performance.
As we all know,
once you're in a project,
you'll have a chance
to discuss cutting-edgy academic subjects
with the big shots.
You'll have access to more knowledge.
You'll be making academic achievements
step by step
and eventually get your names on your thesis.
The quality of your thesis
and the impact factors
will determine your future.
The project is
Assisted Reproduction for Elderly Parturient Women.
You'll have one night.
You can choose
your own subjects,
collect information
and write an essay
on your ideas of the research direction.
I'll collect your essays tomorrow morning.
Got it.
What's for dinner?
Leave me alone.
Are you all possessed?
Are you going to take a test?
You passed your practitioner license test,
didn't you?
I'm more nervous than the time I had the test.
What makes my daughter
feel nervous?
I haven't seen you so tensed up
since the college entrance exam.
I don't want to lose.
It's my dream
to become
a top-notch doctor.
Your dream?
Bring babies to every
sterility and infertile families.
Am I great?
You're great.
Alright, don't stay up too late, though.
Remember to drink your milk.
Why do you give me a video call in the middle of night?
I want to know how it is going
with your report?
Thank you for your concern.
It's going well.
And if you'll leave me alone,
it'll go even better.
I have written
quite some directions.
How about I share one with you?
Are they even usable?
I directly took them
from my teacher's report.
I was helping him
in the laboratory anyway.
I appreciate it,
but I can't cheat.
You came early, too.
Sleeping a few minutes longer doesn't help.
I'd rather get up early for the subway
while it wasn't crowded.
I thought the same.
Du Di, do you know that
the one who gets in the project
will most likely be appointed
as the next chief resident by the leadership?
I do.
Are you aware
that academically, you won't necessarily get the better of me?
Your English is so good,
and you're expressive.
I'm very aware.
So let's bring out
our best.
Let's have a good match,
okay?
OK.
But after this,
we're still friends.
Sure.
Then I won't hold back.
And I won't care about your feelings then.
The comparison between
frozen single blastocyst implantation
under in vitro fertilization
and fresh single blastocyst transfer.
Du Di,
why did you choose this subject?
To verify the frozen eggs and cryo-embryos' influence
on reproduction.
So that the age problem
can no longer trouble women.
This is interesting.
Li Junxiao.
Age's effects on pregnancy outcome
and the offspring's health.
It looks like
you're going in different directions.
Yes, Director Tian.
I personally advocate
high-quality reproductions
at suitable ages.
In recent years,
bad pregnancy outcome
and risk of poor offspring health
are both increasing.
Because
there have been more and more elderly parturient women.
Not necessarily.
Director Tian, this is mine.
The technology upgrade for assisted reproduction.
My goal is
to cure sterility and infertility.
Nianbai, how come you didn't write yours?
My subject is
the screening and diagnosis
of single gene inheritance disease
before the embryo implantation.
Last night, my teacher told me
that he'd fly here
and talk with you about the collaboration.
Really? So soon?
Yeah.
Alright, you go back to your office.
When there's a result,
I'll let you know.
Nianbai, come to my office.
OK.
No matter how hard we work,
we can't compete with certain people with a background.
How do you know that he doesn't work hard?
Do you think it's so easy to get into
Johns Hopnews University?
Perhaps his family
sponsored a lot of money.
Li Junxiao,
you're already the attending physician.
Less jealous, more performance.
Could you stop
barking at me like a mad dog?
When will you two
make peace?
Not in this lifetime.
She's very close
to Nianbai.
Will Nianbai talk Director Tian
into choosing her?
That's possible, actually.
Don't you think it's unfair?
Well, we live in
an unfair world.
We do what we can, and let fate decide.
Zhang Zilu?
What is he doing here?
Hello, Zhang Ying.
When will you come and get your report?
I'm not very busy today.
I'll treat you to lunch.
Director Huang,
you seem troubled.
Are you tired
or is there something on your mind?
I'm okay.
It's about Zhang Ying.
I'm thinking about what I'm going to tell her.
You're worried
that it'll be bad for her emotions.
But it's not a small thing.
She has to be informed.
Yeah.
I can't believe
I have to deal with this.
Oh, you know.
You gotta work hard
on your subject.
Nowadays,
more and more women
choose to have babies at older ages.
Sterility and infertility
are more and more common.
Your subject
is a meaningful one.
If you ever
need my help,
just come to me at any time.
I will. Thank you, Director Huang.
Congrui,
you have become
more and more professional.
Director Tian and I
both think you can compete with Du Di.
Prepare yourself.
OK. I'll call the next number.
Sure.
Director Huang,
here's my Down's syndrome screening report.
What's wrong?
Is there something
wrong with the report?
It shows
that there's a high chance of Down's syndrome.
Is something wrong
with my baby?
Down's syndrome
is caused by conventional chromosome aberration.
It's a sporadic illness.
This screening
sampled your serum
to test the AFP,
HCG,
and your free estriol level.
The calculation
of the risk coefficient
takes your expected date, weight,
age, and your gestational week into consideration.
If it
suggests high risk,
you'll need
another confirmatory test.
Because the accuracy
of this test
is only 70% to 90%.
Currently, there are three types
of confirmatory tests.
Villus sampling, amniocentesis,
and umbilical cord puncture.
Are you telling me
that my child
may be a dummy?
We cannot be certain.
There is high risk.
This is awful.
I need to talk to my husband.
Can I ask him to come in?
Sure.
Her husband?
Weird.
What is he doing? Why doesn't he pick up my call?
What?
You didn't see the doctor's name
while you waited?
I see you're surprised to see me.
She's an old schoolmate of mine.
Long time no see.
I see you are a doctor now.
You know each other?
Tingting,
give me some time, please.
She used
to pursue me. It'll be awkward.
Give us a moment alone.
There's a misunderstanding
between us.
I need a quick chat with her.
Make it quick, then.
There's a problem with my report. I'm scared.
I'll be quick.
Just go.
I hope you don't
say a word to Zhang Ying about it.
If anything happens
to my child,
you're not going to get away with it.
Shouldn't you be
begging me?
Your wife is pregnant,
and you knocked up your mistress.
Now you're threatening me.
It's my family business.
It's none of your business.
I have both
their files with me.
And you're telling me it's none of my business?
Caiting?
Zhang Ying.
You're here for another check?
No.
My bestie is free,
and someone stood me up at noon,
so I thought
I could come here and surprise her.
Have you had lunch?
How about we go together?
You know my bestie.
Director Huang.
You, too, are seeing her, aren't you?
Great.
There's a problem with my Down's syndrome screening report.
I'm really worried.
I really didn't know
you were a director
in Shengji Hospital,
or else,
I wouldn't have allowed her to come here.
Alright, we'll go to another hospital.
Who is this guy?
What a jerk!
They lived a poor life.
In order to provide the family,
my bestie never thought about having a baby.
No.
He's not getting away with it.
Help me up.
Sure, we'll go together.
Tingting, let's go.
Honey?
Zhang Ying,
who are you calling "honey"?
Zhang Zilu. This is my husband.
Who's your husband?
Zhang Zilu.
What's going on, Zhang Zilu?
Listen, honey. I…
Let's talk somewhere else.
I'll explain everything to you.
OK?
-I'll explain.
-You'll explain right here.
From the moment I found myself pregnant,
you have never accompanied me
to any prenatal check.
You're coming to the hospital with another woman.
Zhang Zilu, you're good.
Zhang Zilu,
didn't you say
your wife was dead?
Wh... What is this?
Stop filming!
You keep making a scene here.
I'm embarrassed.
You're embarrassed?
When you cheated on me,
were you embarrassed?
You stand aside.
Now you're embarrassed?
Make way. Make way.
Stop it. Make way.
Stop, stop.
You're pregnant.
Be careful with me baby. Come with me.
Come on.
Stop filming.
Put your cell phones away.
Who allowed you to film this?
Zhang Zilu!
We'll talk in the car. Come on.
There, there.
Here.
Calm yourself down.
Or it'll be bad for the baby.
I don't want it anymore.
I want an abortion.
I'm going to divorce him.
No. The child did nothing wrong.
Congrui, go to the ward for now.
Some other patients are waiting to see you.
Shall I ask them to see another director?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You do that.
You make the arrangements.
You started to want a baby
more than a decade ago, right?
Just think it over.
Yes.
I was afraid to have a baby over the years,
now I'm finally pregnant,
I find my husband is cheating on me,
and his mistress is pregnant as well.
Ironically, we have become friends.
We agree to
give birth our babies together.
All these years…
All these years,
I sacrificed for the family.
I'm a joke.
Why?
Why do I get this
in return?
All right. All right.
Let it out. You let it out.
After that,
we'll work out a solution.
Let it all out.
Only us here. Go on, speak.
I have no feelings for her already.
You watched so many dramas
with me,
can't you come up with a better line?
How did she get pregnant then?
When you were poor,
she was afraid to have a baby.
She worked hard to provide your family.
You have no feelings for her?
Not only do you have no feelings,
but you also have no conscience.
Guo Caiting, how do you know my past?
You lied to me.
Your wife and I became friends.
What a joke.
When she told me how her husband
worked to become a successful entrepreneur
from a poor guy,
I felt lucky
that I found the right person
so I didn't need to go through her misery.
Now,
I think I'm a joke.
No, Tingting.
Please listen to me.
I really love you.
Right before I planned
to divorce her,
I found she was pregnant.
You know I
can't divorce a pregnant woman, right?
Yes, she did help me a lot,
but that's exactly why I can't stand her.
She always acts like
she's sacrificed for me.
The more she helps me,
the more pressured I feel.
I feel like I'm a complete loser
when I'm with her.
No matter how much money I make,
she has the credit.
I don't want to live
in her shadows anymore.
Stop finding excuses
for your cowardice and unfaithfulness.
It has nothing to do
with you lying to me
about your so-called dead wife.
You're a jerk. You're shameless.
Fine, fine. I'm a shameless jerk.
Tingting, this is enough.
Calm down.
Trust me, I will divorce her.
Just believe me.
As soon as the baby is born,
I'll divorce her.
You're such a bad man
that you don't deserve a healthy child.
I'm young and healthy.
I was wondering why my baby has a high risk of Down's syndrome
So it's because of your trash DNA.
It's impossible.
Think it through before you call him.
I haven't thought it through,
but my phone keeps buzzing.
Guo Caiting
sent a whole bunch of text messages to me.
What does she want? Ask you to divorce him?
Honey,
I'm sorry.
I…
I got drunk
and made a mistake,
and she wouldn't get off my back.
I knew it would be too much for you
during your pregnancy.
I was gonna…
I was gonna
end the relationship with her
and ask her to get an abortion.
Really?
Yes.
You were drunk?
Only one night?
Yes, only one night.
Only one night,
and you bought her so much stuff.
Honey,
I had no choice.
She's a greedy one.
She keeps threatening me with the baby.
I…
I didn't want to harm you,
so I kept it to myself.
What are you going to do?
I will break up
with Guo Caiting.
Honey, please don't get mad.
Be careful with the baby.
We grew up together
and have been with each other for over 20 years.
Over 20 years.
How can I have the heart
to harm you and the baby?
Fine.
How about we get it done right now?
Call her.
Break up with her now,
and ask her to get an abortion.
She won't get an abortion,
she's threatening me with the baby.
If you kill her delusion of marrying you,
she will
get that abortion.
My dear,
I'll take more time
to convince her.
But look,
if anything happens to her,
I'll be in trouble, right?
How thoughtful
and considerate you are!
You still don't want to break up with her.
Fine.
I'll get an abortion.
-No.
-I'll divorce you.
No, no, no.
I'll let you two
be together as a happy couple.
No.
You can wait for the divorce deal.
You should start thinking about
the division of property.
No, honey.
Yunling, thank you for your help.
I have to go.
Here.
Honey, please. Stay calm.
I'll drive you home. Come on.
No anger for baby.
No anger for mom.
It's alright. It is alright.
4 bottles of saline.
You wrote 40. What?
A saline bath for the patient?
How about
you give her a massage?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Director Huang
had a little bit of trouble.
So I
accidentally added a zero.
You're lucky that Li Fei found it out,
or else,
the patient would
report you to the dean
if she saw it, you know?
Things haven't been smooth in our department.
Can you please save trouble for the leadership?
I swear that I won't
make the same mistake again.
Director Huang doesn't know this, right?
She has no time for you.
Did her bestie fight against
the mistress in the hospital earlier?
Oh, yeah.
The mistress and the wife
found out that they were pregnant
with the same man's baby.
Director Huang was so mad
that she nearly gave birth on site.
There's no negotiation on this.
Keep the baby, get a divorce.
For the good of the child,
I don't suggest a divorce.
It's sad that a child grows up without the dad.
Fix it,
and cancel the wrong one.
Right away, ma'am.
Yes, that's tolerable
if it's for the child,
but the thing is,
the mistress is pregnant, too.
For the completion of the family,
she should forgive the man
and deal with
the mistress later.
Forgive him?
A man like him
cannot be forgiven
unless he proposes to kill himself.
If everybody is as extreme as you are,
most families in the world
will break apart.
Well,
is this your justification
for having an affair?
What the…
Alright, stop.
You both have a point.
I don't think so, extreme feminist.
You male chauvinist.
Du Di, you ordered
so much take out?
A high blood pressure primipara
secretly ordered
a lot of spicy crayfish for herself.
I found it under her bed.
What's her problem?
Which restaurant did she order from?
Is it that good?
I don't know if it's good,
but it's expensive, though.
When I confiscated the crayfish,
she nearly burst into tears.
She didn't even cry
when she was diagnosed
with preeclampsia.
Is the crayfish really worth it?
Where did you
get these?
Director Tian's office.
To thank his
excellent medical skills,
the patient gave him a whole bunch of sweet snacks.
But Director Tian doesn't like sweet snacks.
No wonder I didn't see you anywhere,
you were in Director Tian's office.
I went to fetch the snacks for you.
Fine.
I'm going to ask you a question.
If you pass my test,
I'll forgive you.
If the wife and the mistress are found pregnant at the same time,
what to do with the man?
That's exciting.
This is for my senior
and the head nurse.
Mocha flavor. Nice.
Director Huang wasn't working.
It's been a tough day for me.
Be nice to me as well.
The mistress is also a victim.
I'm told that she didn't know the man was married.
So
that man is a total scumbag.
It's so you, Du Di.
Only you would use this word.
I think
this is their privacy.
We shouldn't think about it.
You can have it.
Was I wrong?
No.
You have officially been
kicked out of the gossip association.
The gossip association? Who's in it?
Thank you
for spotting my mistake earlier.
"Always double check".
It's what we nurses do.
No need to thank me.
Always double check?
Double check when and what?
You, answer me.
Before, during, and after the action.
Double check the name, bed number,
drug name, dose, concentration,
time, way of use,
expiration date, nationality, marital status…
Wait a minute.
Nationality and marital status?
You caught me.
You failed.
Examination for your shift tomorrow.
If anyone makes a mistake,
you say goodbye to your bonuses.
You are good at imitating the head nurse.
I say
you can pair up with Liu Nianbai
for his stand-up.
Be honest with me.
Do you have a crush on Liu Nianbai?
I noticed that you took quite a lot of pictures of him.
I didn't.
Let me check your cell phone.
I don't like him.
I'm one of his fans.
I'm only
managing his fan group.
We are all his fans.
We're a large community.
How many people?
Let me see
what you chat about him?
Well,
a large community indeed.
16 people up till now.
He didn't
give away any pictures of his face,
so he hasn't
got many fans so far.
I'll suggest him to
pay attention to image management,
and
we will help promote him.
Since you don't intend to pursue him,
just stop
paying attention to him.
If he gets married one day,
your heart will break.
I don't mind.
I have no feelings for others.
You see, Dr. Li
is a good looker,
but I think
he's
way too direct.
Look.
Even his post about his date
is so embarrassing.
Who is he dating?
I don't know.
Look here.
"You like fish.
I wish I was fish".
Eesh.
How come I can't
see this post?
Perhaps,
he forgot to include me in the co-worker group?
Hey,
who is he dating
in our hospital?
He's been sneaky.
Send me a screenshot.
You want some gossips,
don't you?
Senior,
will you watch my stand-up
when you're off work?
No.
That's hurtful.
Director Huang isn't at work today. I'm busy.
We'll have lunch together.
No. I'm busy.
You are not going to skip lunch, are you?
It's Friday today.
Your favorite braised pork with potato
is on the menu.
Ah, yes.
Braised pork on Friday.
Come on. No pork for us if we're late.
Pack the lunch for me.
OK.
-Braised pork, please.
-Thank you for queuing for me.
Braised pork, please.
Hey,
you just cut the line
and took my pork.
I learned from you.
You got the last portion
of braised hairtail with your acting last time.
Swipe your own card.
More rice, please.
OK.
Mine.
I thought you didn't like braised pork.
My senior loves it.
Give me a break.
Love drives men crazy.
I can't believe someone like you
would cut the line for a girl.
Let me have a taste.
Not allowed.
I tell you what,
if Du Di was with us,
she would allow me to have one piece.
She would allow me to have all.
Do you believe me?
And even if
she knew you got it for her,
she would let me have it.
Weiwei.
How come she doesn't respond
to my wooing?
Does she not like me
and pretend she doesn't know what I'm doing?
You're pursuing her?
How come I didn't know?
Isn't that obvious?
You claimed
that you had a girlfriend abroad.
So it was a brag?
No, it wasn't.
I would just go to a bar,
make eye contact with a girl.
And she'd understand,
and we'd talk and go out on a date.
It never took me
so long to pursue a girl.
No matter how hard I tried,
how I made eye contact with her…
Hell, even my eyes are tired.
She won't respond to me.
I even doubt
if I'm a real man.
Does she take me as a woman?
Since when did you
have feelings for Du Di?
I don't know.
At first, I would get scared
at the thought of seeing her.
Yeah.
I would wonder
what traps she got for me.
And then, I started to feel a little bit down
if I didn't see her the whole day.
I started wanting to know her,
approach her, invite her to my apartment,
and dine with her.
But like I said, no response.
Maybe it's
a stereotype thing.
Maybe Du Di only
sees you as a dumb,
incapable returnee intern.
So everything you do
fits your image.
How do I
break the stereotype?
She beats you at intelligence,
physical strength, and expertise.
How do you
break the stereotype?
Am I that lame?
I was the best student at school.
I was admitted into Johns Hopnews University.
I was the youngest assistant researcher
in a top genetic science laboratory worldwide.
I was a top player on the university hockey team.
Yes, she's smarter than me,
and her clinic work is better than mine,
but I'm better than her physically.
You
have no idea how tough she is.
There'll be an operation this afternoon.
I think you should watch it.
Too much fat.
We have to open all layers of your fat
before the cut.
Your operation
will take longer than that of others.
Doctor, thank you.
I weighed
over 200 kilograms last night.
I was only 130 kilo before pregnancy.
Doctor,
how about you remove my fat
while doing the cesarean?
Good idea.
Maybe we can
do a joint
cesarean-fat management operation
with the plastic surgery department.
It may become
our hospital's featured project.
Congratulations, you're a mother now.
Out comes a little girl.
She's not big.
3.2 kilograms.
Only 3.2 kilograms?
Well, all the weight is on me.
You must be careful when you're out of the hospital.
There's a high chance
of fat liquefaction on the wound.
You may feel awful if that happens.
I guess I shouldn't listen
to the older generations' advice.
My mom
said that I couldn't bathe
within the first month after the birth.
If the fat liquefaction
causes an infection because you don't bathe,
that will be real trouble.
You mustn't follow her advice.
I won't.
Alright, the stitching is finished.
Now, we get her off the table.
Senior, let me.
Now, follow my command.
One, two, three. Up.