[English subtitles are available]
[Beloved Life]
[Episode 31]
If you weren't a female doctor,
you'd be a lady
who's elegant,
and knows how to enjoy life.
Well, I know
how to enjoy life.
I just don't want to waste my time.
The pressure
of becoming a top-notch doctor
is always on my shoulder.
Life is short.
If you see
a great goal
that you can potentially achieve,
you strive for it.
There's nothing wrong with an ordinary life,
but I want a different life
for myself.
Of course.
Being aspirational is a good thing.
A tough woman can live
a full and beautiful life, too.
Being tough
is just a life attitude.
I didn't expect
that a person
whom I thought little of
would understand me so well.
It's not that I understand you well,
it's just many people
are trapped in their own little world.
They don't understand themselves.
How do you expect them
to understand others?
Good.
You're saying something smart.
Why aren't you eating anything?
Haven't you heard of this before?
After making a full table of dishes,
the cook loses all the appetite.
I'll cook for you next time.
Are you serious? Can you cook?
I'm dead serious.
I lived abroad for so many years.
I have some basic
survival skills.
Omelette.
Spaghetti.
Steak.
I can make them all.
Impressive.
When are you going
to cook some dishes for me?
On your next day off,
okay?
OK.
You look so pretty
when you smile.
Your smile
has sweetened the air.
You are not
watching a video about obstetrics & gynecology?
Neurosurgery.
You must watch a video about neurosurgery?
I have watched enough
female organs already.
So I wanted to watch something else
to learn some new stuff.
You want to learn this?
What's wrong?
Nothing wrong.
Just learn from me.
You have such a nice body.
It would be much fun to dissect you.
Sorry.
I've been busy these days.
Really? What have you been doing?
My sister told me
that you let her have
the free examination chance.
Congrui.
I know
there's no such thing as
an annual free physical examination.
You paid for her examination, right?
How much was it?
I'll give you the money.
That's fine.
She told me
that for some reason,
she was never able
to get pregnant after she was married for several years.
So she wanted a check.
I thought it might be too much for her,
so I came up
with this idea.
It didn't cost me much.
Don't worry about it.
Thank you.
You don't have to do this.
If it wasn't for you,
-my sister wouldn't be…
-Oh, right.
How is her
result looking?
Everything's fine?
Yeah.
Everything's fine.
Glad to know.
You know,
there are many reasons
that a couple doesn't have a baby
after years of marriage.
Why does it
have to be the female's problem?
I think both
the husband and the wife should have a check.
That man,
he didn't get himself checked.
He just blamed it on Sister.
She's actually better off
without that guy.
Yeah.
Junxiao,
this is the operation fee.
Enjoyed working with you.
This is how you make a month
at Shengji, right?
Now, one operation
can pay you that much.
So,
don't feel
pressured.
Looking forward to working with you again.
Sister,
we had a deal, didn't we?
That you'd quit
and get some rest at home.
Why are you still at work?
Look at you.
You aren't willing to stay in the hospital,
but you still came to work.
Watch your health, will you?
I'm fine.
You know me.
I have to keep myself busy.
And once I'm not busy,
I'd have crazy thoughts.
So I might as well keep working.
I know that you want to make more money.
About the medical bill,
I'll work out a solution.
But a patient shouldn't
be making money.
What solution?
I wanted to ask you this.
Did you come home
after midnight last night
and went out before 5:00 AM this morning?
Don't overstrain yourself.
My disease doesn't have to be treated.
I don't want to be a liability.
What are you talking about?
You will quit immediately.
Go home and rest.
You hear me?
Fine.
I will do that.
Junxiao,
I just met with Congrui.
Does she know
about my disease?
I still haven't got time to tell her.
All right.
Don't let her know.
I don't want it to affect you.
I got it.
What are you doing?
I only want to hold my girlfriend's hand.
No. People can see us.
I want them to see us.
I don't.
I want compensation then.
Do you know
how much it hurts?
Bai.
You don't remember me?
I'm Li Qiao'er.
I played games
with you.
Li Qiao'er.
What a coincidence.
What are you doing here at the hospital again this time?
I came with her.
Qiao'er.
I have got my number.
Hey, Wang Lu.
He is Bai,
the one I often talked to you about.
He got a doctor's degree
at a foreign medical school.
He's very good.
How about you let him check on you later?
I'm only a trainee resident.
I'm not qualified to check on a patient.
The attending physician
will check on you.
Come on.
You've got your number. Just wait.
Let me take you there.
Ultrasound result.
Both ovaries are 11 centimeters in diameter.
Whereas the average diameter
of normal people's ovary is 3 to 4 centimeters.
There's a large amount of fluid
in the abdomen and chest.
Blood routine result suggests
severe hemoconcentration.
Hepatic injury.
Most importantly,
low blood protein.
You are both students at a nursing school.
You should know a little something about it.
I'll be straightforward.
You have
ovarian hyperstimulation syndrome.
It's a serious complication
caused by ovulation induction and ovum pick-up.
It may cause
eternal organic damage
or even death.
Ovum pick-up?
I suggest you be hospitalized first.
After hospitalization,
you'll get a blood protein transfusion
and volume expansion therapy.
After tonight,
you'll have an operation tomorrow.
How much will it cost?
We aren't sure about the cost.
Do you have medical insurance?
I guess the school covers our insurance.
I'll ask our counselor.
You mustn't let
the counselor know about it.
You need to be hospitalized first.
Your condition
cannot be delayed anymore, you know?
Come on.
We'll get the admission procedure done.
She's so young.
Why would she have an ovulation induction?
I think she sold her eggs.
What?
Isn't that illegal?
Yes.
Those illegal organizations
make dirty money
at the expense of these girls' health.
I think
she took a lot of ovulation induction shots.
And the unprofessional procedures
caused her serious
hydrothorax and ascites.
We received cases
like her before.
Mostly young girls
who mindlessly sold their eggs.
They got the money, but lost their precious health.
That poor girl.
Her ascites will take some time to be drawn.
It's lucky that she's not infected,
or she'd be dead.
Have some food.
Did you ask the counselor for leave?
I did.
I told her that you
needed a few days to deal with some family stuff.
She asked you
to make a confirmation call to her.
I'll call her later.
How did you
get this ovarian hyperstimulation syndrome?
You mustn't
tell anyone
about this.
I sold my eggs before.
You what?
Why would you…
I know.
I regret it.
But I needed
to pay off
a loan.
I had no choice.
I needed the money.
So I sold my eggs.
And they guaranteed that the doctor
was from a Grade A Class 3 hospital.
They said there would be no risk at all.
But after I went there,
they gave me
a whole bunch of shots,
and used a tube this long
to take my eggs.
It nearly killed me.
And after
they got my eggs,
my belly grew bigger and bigger.
It's bloated.
But the middleman told me
that it was normal.
And a few days later,
this is what I have become.
Qiao'er,
can I be cured?
Don't worry.
Shengji will cure you.
But
it will cost much, right?
You got paid
after you sold your eggs, didn't you?
Where's the money?
I paid off the loan.
I have no money left.
You made such a big mistake.
I know.
I'm so regretful right now.
Qiao'er,
I see you know Bai well,
don't you?
Can you please…
Don't worry.
I swear I will pay him back.
It's not that I don't want to help you,
but I borrowed money from him before.
And I still owe him money now.
If I borrowed more from him,
he'd look down on me.
I'll figure out
another way for you.
You like him, right?
Yeah, so?
He's out of my league.
Wang Lu. Hi.
I will be your bedside resident.
My name is Du Di.
Is your immediate family here?
I didn't let them know.
If there's anything,
tell me and Qiao'er.
It requires your
immediate family's signature.
Dr. Du,
must I have an operation?
You now have
severe hydrothorax and ascites,
causing your chest stiffness.
In the meantime,
the hemoconcentration in your blood vessel
may cause
serious thrombus in your organs,
resulting in organ damage,
electrolyte disturbance,
and other complications.
In the worst-case scenario,
you will die.
I see.
Thank you, doctor.
Stop crying.
They will cure you.
I thought about it,
and I still want you to know this.
Don't do silly things like this again.
The ovulation induction drugs
they gave you
must be overdosed,
and unprofessional puncture
has damaged your ovals
and affected your reproductive function.
You're still young.
Don't ever trust
those illegal organizations again.
And never make money
at the expense of your health.
I got it.
It was so stupid of me.
I fell for their tricks
the moment I was told the amount.
Doctor,
please save me.
I still want to get married.
I still want to have a baby.
We'll do our best.
[Kaiming Women's Hospital]
[Outpatient Building]
Junxiao,
you are here at last.
A 35-week expectant mother
is waiting for you to see her
at outpatient.
It may be a tricky problem.
[Congrui]
Any symptoms lately?
I've been feeling light-headed,
nauseous, and exhausted all the time.
I didn't feel like eating anything and kept vomiting.
At first,
I thought it was a late-stage pregnancy thing,
so I didn't pay too much attention.
I thought it was normal.
But
it feels like torment
these days.
So I had my husband
come with me to see a doctor.
From what we have right now,
I suspect
it is acute fatty liver of pregnancy.
Fatty liver?
She doesn't smoke or drink.
How did she get fatty liver?
Right.
Acute fatty liver of pregnancy
is not the fatty liver you know of.
It is a rare complication
in the late stage of pregnancy.
It normally doesn't start off
as a serious disease.
Just like your wife's symptoms.
Nausea and vomit.
Both the expectant mother and her family
think it's normal
during pregnancy,
so they generally don't pay attention.
But once it worsens,
it may cause
multiple organ failure
disseminated intravascular coagulation.
In more serious cases,
the lives of the mother
and the fetus
are endangered.
Doctor,
are you sure
my wife has this?
I cannot be 100% sure.
There's no specificity in the disease's
clinical signs and symptoms,
so it's difficult to diagnose.
But I suggest
you be admitted
to the hospital as quickly as possible.
Doctor,
a-are you
serious?
Dr. Li is serious.
Your condition
requires immediate hospitalization.
My dear,
what's wrong?
My dear, are you okay?
Honey,
my belly hurts.
Her pregnancy may need to be terminated.
Doctor,
quickly.
Save my wife.
Not in here.
You need to go to Shengji Hospital.
Shengji Hospital?
You go to the emergency department
at Shengji Hospital
and tell the doctor
that your wife
has acute fatty liver of pregnancy
and that she needs a cesarean section immediately.
A-a cesarean section? I-I mean…
Forget it.
I'll take you there.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, doctor.
Li Junxiao, what are you doing?
Her life is in danger.
I don't have time
to explain this.
Let's go.
Easy.
Can you still walk?
The patient has been pregnant for 35 weeks.
She vomits and has abdominal pain.
Her transaminase and bilirubin
are notably higher than regular values.
Also with coagulation disorder.
Low blood platelet.
It's my initial diagnosis
that this is AFLP.
You are a doctor?
Yes.
I'll get an O.B.
here to consult with her.
Thanks.
It's killing me.
Doctor.
A-Are you leaving?
You're now in Shengji.
Don't worry.
I have other stuff to do.
I can't stay here with you.
OK.
T-Thank you.
Junxiao?
From O.B. department?
The patient is over there.
The patient is diagnosed
with AFLP.
Director Wang,
it's a timely diagnosis.
A doctor sent her over.
He looked familiar.
He told us
that it might be AFLP,
so we diagnosed
her rather quickly.
Congrui, explain
AFLP's
therapeutic principle.
therapeutic principle
is prompt childbirth
and the maximum-level supportive treatment
to ensure euglycemia, and the balance of blood volume
and electrolytes.
Calibrate DIC.
The way of delivery
is to be a cesarean section.
But the coagulation disorder
can add risk to the operation.
Good.
How is her
coagulation function looking?
She now
has severe coagulation disorder.
A cesarean section
will quicken the delivery process,
but it may cause massive hemorrhage,
aggravating her coagulation disorder
and further damage
to her liver
and the other organs.
Indeed.
Congrui,
contact the blood bank.
She needs hemocyte and plasma.
Apply for fibrinogen
and prothrombin complex,
or the patient
will have a hemorrhagic shock.
After the childbirth,
watch the mother and the child closely
to see if
there's any LCHAD
symptom.
And hypoketotic hypoglycemia
and fatty liver.
Also, get the family's signature.
Specify the situation.
OK.
Are you going home or to Shengji?
Home.
How about I give you a ride?
No, thanks.
Ye Ying,
the reason why
I took the patient
to Shengji
is that…
I know. I don't blame you.
I admit
that at first,
I was a bit mad.
But later, I thought it over.
It's highly risky to treat
AFLP.
And her condition is serious.
It's better
that she's transferred to Shengji,
so there would
be no chance of medical dispute for me.
I'm glad you understand.
But I hope
this is the last time you do this.
Director Wang wasn't there,
so I acquiesced
in your action.
I hope you will be
handling operations
of higher levels of difficulty
so that we can make more money.
You told me
that my family
can receive free treatment
in this hospital.
Do you still mean what you said?
Of course.
Why? Is your family sick?
Just checking.
I'm leaving then.
Doctor, how is my wife doing?
The surgery was successful. You can rest assured.
But she'll still be under observation.
That's great. That's great.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
AFLP
is a rare and fatal complication that typically occurs
in the third trimester of pregnancy.
It's characterized by fast development.
It's an obstetric
acute and serious complication
with a mortality rate of 70%.
Your wife is lucky.
You brought her here
in time.
I got to go home to see my baby.
You need to pay attention to
her post-surgical condition.
Rest assured, Director.
Please take care.
Can you tell me about
the doctor
who just sent you here?
I don't remember his name.
I only know
he's a specialist
in Kaiming Women's Hospital.
He seems to be hired
from Shengji Hospital
with a high salary.
Kaiming Women's Hospital?
Yes.
[Kaiming Women's Hospital]
Hello?
Congrui.
Are you busy on the night shift?
Where are you now?
Where else could I be?
I'm at home.
Junxiao,
don't you really need a ride?
Tell me the truth.
Where are you now?
Well,
I'm coming to you right now
and explain it to you in person.
Let me give you a ride.
It's difficult to call a cab at this hour.
I'll drop you off
outside Shengji.
Congrui won't see me.
OK.
Congrui.
Where are you going at this late hour?
No,
I'm just walking around.
You're lying.
You've got rid of the habit of
nibbling your nails
when you feel anxious.
Why are you doing it again?
What happened?
Du Di,
can you follow me
to see Li Junxiao?
Where?
At the gate of the hospital.
Junxiao.
Here.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Li Junxiao,
who sent you here?
Was that Ye Ying?
Yes.
It was Ye Ying.
How did you know?
That's why I'm meeting him
in the middle of the night.
I want to hear your explanation.
Come on,
let's go somewhere else.
I'll explain everything to you.
We stay right here.
In front of Du Di,
let's get this straight.
It's the matter between you and me.
Why do we talk about it in front of her?
She is the witness.
I don't like people lying to me.
Ye Ying hired me
to work at her hospital.
It's been a month.
You've been saying that you're busy.
So, that's what you've been busy with.
Congrui,
there's nothing between Ye Ying and me.
Can you swear?
I swear that
I've never
had any feelings
for Ye Ying.
You're the only one in my heart.
Then can you not work
at Ye Ying's hospital?
I'm sorry.
I can't do it right now.
It seems that
I've taken myself too important.
Du Di, let's go.
Congrui.
Li Junxiao,
what do you mean?
Ye Ying told me
that as long as I work at her hospital
on a regular basis,
my sister
could receive free treatment
at her hospital.
Shengji is a Grade A Class 3 hospital.
Isn't it good enough for your sister?
You're an attending physician
but work as a specialist there.
Do you trust it for treating your sister?
I have no money.
They have the most advanced
equipment and medicine.
At least my sister could stay there
for the interval between surgeries.
Fine.
Since you said so,
I can't help you.
I've given you the chance
to explain it to her.
Don't be so sad.
I've been waiting for him to propose to me,
but he hasn't done it yet.
I thought he was too busy.
I didn't expect
that he is with Ye Ying.
Do you know about
his sister's illness?
What is it?
Ovarian cancer.
Was it found in the last physical examination?
I knew it by accident.
I tried to talk her into therapy,
but she wouldn't do it
and doesn't want to be hospitalized.
No wonder
she faltered
when I saw her.
Why doesn't Li Junxiao
tell me about it?
He's a proud man.
How would he tell you about it?
It turns out that
he's making money for his sister.
I was wrong about him.
Now that you've known the truth,
just stop making wild guesses.
Du Di,
I feel sad.
I feel really sad.
Bai, how is Wang Lu doing?
The surgery went well.
More than 3,000 ml of ascites
were drawn from her stomach.
It's about seven kilograms.
You can imagine
how much pain she had before.
Fortunately, she was treated in time
before having
serious consequences.
That's good. That's good.
Those organizations selling eggs
are so villainous.
Don't they have sisters?
How can they do this
to girls?
After going back,
you may work with some schoolmates
to print some relevant materials.
That could prevent more girls
from being cheated.
I will.
Bai,
you always think so thoroughly.
You're just like a protector of girls.
Without you,
I wouldn't be able to
be admitted to the nursing school
I haven't got a chance to thank you.
Besides,
I'll repay the money I owe you
as soon as possible.
Wait until you graduate and make money.
Wang Lu
is saved in time.
After she gets recovered,
I hope you can persuade her to call the police.
Girls shouldn't feel ashamed
to disclose such a thing.
Those vicious people
should be ashamed.
My girlfriend is right.
I'll persuade her to call the police,
just like
you persuaded me.
And
I'll study hard
and try to enter Shengji.
We'll be waiting for you.
You didn't drink before.
That's because I wanted to get pregnant.
But now I no longer have expectations
and can drink at will.
Haven't you cleared the air
with Li Junxiao?
If I didn't
find it out myself,
would he tell me that?
Now I find that
the two of us
are getting farther apart.
He doesn't tell me that his sister's sick
and he is working part time
at Ye Ying's hospital.
I thought
we're going to get married.
And I trusted him.
But now I realized
he doesn't tell me anything.
I feel really anxious.
Congrui,
Li Junxiao doesn't know
how to speak sweet words.
And he always feels inferior
due to his background.
Now
his sister is sick.
He certainly
won't propose to you
so easily.
Oh, I see.
He must be thinking of
solving the current difficulties
before talking about your future.
I've never expected
that you would speak for him.
I'm telling the truth.
Forget about me.
What about you?
When will you
marry Liu Nianbai?
We're not there yet.
Liu Nianbai
is an excellent man.
He is handsome and has a high IQ.
He has a good family background.
The most important thing is that
he loves you
and respects you.
So, you mustn't
let go of him.
Our feelings for each other
are very pure.
Why are you describing it
so worldly?
Am I?
It's not easy
to meet true love.
But when you meet the one,
you must cherish him.
Or it would be too late to regret it.
Understand?
Understood, Aunt Wu.
Who is it?
It's me. Du Di.
Liu Nianbai, what are you doing?
We're going to be late for work.
What are you doing?
What are you doing here?
Let's go to work together.
I brought you breakfast.
Let's go. Or we'll be late.
Have you washed up?
Look at your hair.
Oh, my hair.
Why are you looking so nervous?
Have you done anything wrong to me?
How is it possible?
Let's go.
-You need to have breakfast.
-Nianbai,
who is out there?
Du Di.
It tastes good.
Du Di, have some, too.
I have no appetite.
I don't want to eat.
You're very busy every day.
You should have breakfast.
You may just go by yourself later.
I'll go and see your mom
and come back alone.
You don't need to worry about me.
Why?
Are you planning to stay here for long?
No.
Your grandmother's condition
has become stabilized.
The doctor said
that she just needs
to stay at home for recuperation.
I come to take care of your mom.
But you can't
stay at Liu Nianbai's place.
I want to stay at your place.
But
your place
only has one room
and it's in the basement.
How could I live there?
You've made yourself at home.
His place is big and comfortable.
Why don't you ask who has a villa
for you to stay?
It's someone else's house no matter how big it is.
It's not your house.
How is it someone else's house?
Liu told me
that you're together now.
This is the house of my son-in-law.
There are
two bedrooms here.
Just let Uncle stay here for the moment.
-I'm okay with that.
-Shut up.
Do you think I want this?
Your grandmother is so angry with you
that her heart condition is worsening.
That has costed me a lot of money.
Your mom's medical bills
are due soon.
Where do I get the money to stay in a hotel?
We're really going to be late.
Let's go to work first
and talk about this later.
Let's go.
Come on.
I'll find him a place
as soon as possible.
We're family. Just let him stay there.
Family?
I'm ready
to be with you forever.
Tell me that
you're not thinking differently.
Why do you suddenly say that?
Nothing.
Don't take it as a burden.
Even as a friend,
it's the right thing
to share a place
and help you
when you're in trouble.
This has nothing to do with burden.
If my father
stays at your house and won't leave,
you would know the consequences.
I just don't want to get you into trouble.
You see,
she looks healthy.
But why couldn't she wake up?
Your mom
likes the baby, too.
Of course.
All mothers like their babies.
Only men
easily get a child,
but they are not satisfied
and don't cherish what they have.
I don't want to argue with you
in front of your mom.
Maybe she could hear us
and wake up
to stop us from fighting each other.
After all,
she doesn't want to see us arguing
and doesn't want me to hate you.
If you were not so self-willed,
this wouldn't have happened.
Now I just
want the baby
to be born soon.
Maybe she would wake up
when she hears the baby's cry.
Have a shrimp.
Come on,
have a fried chicken wing.
I've made up my mind.
I'll use my savings to pay for
the treatment of Li Junxiao's sister.
Sweetie,
do you have that many savings?
After divorcing Feng Yuanhang,
we sold the house
and each got half of the proceeds.
Congrui,
I'm not disapproving of you.
But if you spend the money
and Li becomes penniless,
where and how would you live
after getting married?
As long as you like him
and he is a good man and capable,
we don't worry about
your future life.
Right.
We are not snobbish.
We just don't want you to live a hard life.
You're about thirty
and haven't earned a title.
After getting married,
you can't get pregnant so soon.
As time goes fast,
you'd become an elderly parturient woman.
These are all inter-connected.
There would be many hard days ahead.
Father,
I'm no longer a kid.
I've thought about
all what you just said.
At the moment,
Li Junxiao is facing
the biggest obstacle in his life.
I'm his girlfriend.
If I don't help him, who would?
I've also realized
that I might live a hard life in the future.
Or maybe the two of us
would go our separate ways.
But you always told me
to do
what I should do.
If you were me,
what would you do?
What else would he do?
Your father would surely choose to help.
When your grandfather
got sick,
he would love to live in our house.
Then I have to believe
a good heart can earn good rewards.
Just do what you think is right.
In my opinion,
you could get married sooner.
When you're a couple,
you could be of one mind
and don't have to worry about others.
When you're free,
you bring him home.
Then we can discuss it.
You choose the wedding place
and we will cover the expenses.
You're so generous.
I'll work hard to make money.
And I'll no longer
buy so many clothes.
Okay, let's have the meal.
Hello, this is your takeout.
Thank you.
Please give me a positive comment.
Uncle, the takeout is here.
Yeah.
It's really good to live in a big city.
Home delivery is offered for everything.
Back in our time,
parents cared most about
whether their daughters-in-law
could cook.
They were most worried about
having a daughter-in-law
who couldn't cook for their son.
It's good now.
Hot meals can be delivered to your house.
There's no need to cook for yourself.
By the way, Liu,
do you have wine?
Just have a drink with me.
Uncle, I don't drink.
But if you like,
I can drink water
and have a toast with you.
Why don't you drink?
I'm allergic to wine.
There is only one bottle of alcohol,
and it's from a friend.
Uncle, cheers!
Cheers.
It's good.
It's been a long time
since I had such a good drink.
Liu,
thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you for buying me the underwear
and sleepers
as well as my necessities.
You are
taking good care of me.
Du Di is so lucky
to have you with her.
OK.
Uncle,
what was Du Di like
when she was a child?
Can you tell me about her?
Stubborn.
She's as stubborn as a cow.
Who would come at this late hour?
Could it be Du Di?
She is on a night shift.
What are you doing here?
I'm your father.
Can't I come?
I haven't come
since you're back.
I'm stopping by
to check on you.
What needs to be checked on me?
I'm doing fine.
Isn't this Director Liu?
What a surprise to see you here!
Come in, come in.
Come in, please.
You are…
I'm Du Di's father.
What are you doing here?
I'm living here.
You're living here?
Yes.
Come on, let's have a drink.
Come on.
My son has never
had a drink with me like this.
Well,
Nianbai
is really good to me.
He's taking good care of me.
You're taking good care of
someone else's father,
while giving your own father
the cold shoulder.
Have you had dinner?
Do you want to have it with us?
No.
I've got something to do. I got to go.
Are you leaving so soon?
He just arrived.
Why doesn't he stay for a while?
Did I
say any wrong words?
Don't care about him.
Dr. Feng.
Director Huang.
Thank you
for coming early in the morning for consultation.
Don't be so polite. That's what I should do.
I'm…
You used to say
that you're a family member.
Therefore,
you came more often
than other neonatologists.
It's all for Congrui.
She is careless
and I was worried about her.
But now I don't need to worry about her
since I'm no longer a family.
Did you tell her
about that?