Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
[Weaving a Tale of Love]
[Episode 22]
Young Master Pei.
You've come.
Didn't you say you were giving me something today?
It's something that I'll be very happy to see.
What is it? What is it? Hurry and give it. I'm so curious.
I have a friend who gave me some wine from the western region.
I knew that you'd like it and was going to give it to you.
But then I thought, you don't know how high the sky is nor how deep the earth is,  (being careless and rash)
I'm afraid that you'll get drunk and make a mistake. So, never mind.
You are just being stingy and don't want to give me the good wine,
even found an excuse!
Here.
Your favorite osmanthus cakes.
Someday you will understand
about what I'm doing today.
It's all for your safety.
So there is such a beautiful place in the palace!
If we have to talk about something in the future,
we can just come here, all right?
You are thinking too much.
This is an imperial garden.
We can't come whenever we want to.
From now on, we can arrange to meet at the Hall of the Thinking Heart.
Hall of the Thinking Heart?
I heard that a concubine died by hanging in the Hall of the Thinking Heart.
It's been vacant ever since.
They also say it was later haunted.
In the next few days, I will spread around
this haunted story.
Let people avoid that place all they can.
Why are you afraid?
You can always trust me.
Perhaps...
not just for today.
Maybe...
it even started a long time ago.
What are you talking about?
Heaven's secret. (Heaven's secret cannot be revealed)
[Hall of the Thinking Heart]
Let's walk faster. Every time I pass by this Hall of the Thinking Heart,
I also feel a chill down my back and my whole body gets cold.
Sister, quit talking about it.
They say the Hall of the Thinking Heart is haunted.
I was already afraid of walking by here.
Now you talk about that, I'm even more afraid.
Ever since this spring, my health hasn't been good.
To let me rest quietly, all the activities in the palace
have been reduced or simplied,
except for today's Feast of All Souls Festival that's held on the 15th day in the 7th month.
Not only that it's not skipped, but it's especially important.
Crown Prince, do you understand why?
Replying to Your Majesty. I think
the main theme of the Feast of All Souls Festival involves filial piety, taking care of parents, and helping the people.
Your Majesty pays such great attention to the Feast of All Souls Festival
and have set up a praying chamber in the palace.
It's also to set an example to all the people, and to all the royal princes and subjects.
You want us to always keep in mind, no matter when, where, or the situation,
we must always be filial and have compassion.
Crown Prince verbalized my thoughts exactly.
A'Quan, are all the Feast of All Souls Festival's ceremonies prepared?
Replying to Your Majesty. Everything is ready.
We are just waiting for the auspicious hour when Your Majesty will personally start the activities.
Why aren't Consort Yang and Meiniang here?
Replying to Your Majesty. The ceremonies involved in the Feast of All Souls Festival are complicated.
Mother is personally taking care of everything regardless of big or small
lest any mistake occurs.
My guess is that she is delayed by some miscellaneous matter,
so she is a little late in coming.
I apologize for her guilt on behalf of Mother to Your Majesty.
Your Mother is helping me
to take care of the Feast of All Souls Festival.
If she is a little late, there is no need to apologize for guilt.
Consort Yang, why don't we walk a little faster?
Prince of Cao has already sent someone to rush us twice.
He said everyone else had arrived,
and they were just waiting for you, Consort Yang.
Since I'm already prepared this time
to use the "One Hundred Birds Paying Homage to the Phoenix" that I'm wearing
to announce my status in the harem.
I should appear by myself
so that everyone can see clearly,
so as not waste this elegant dress
and not waste my effort.
Only this way will all those ingratiating appeasers in court and the harem
not take advantage of my Ming'er because he has no support behind him.
Consort Yang arrives!
So beautiful! She looks like a goddess.
That's right.
Consort Yang's beauty is unparalled in the harem.
This consort greets Your Majesty. I'm sorry for coming late.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
You may rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I haven't seen this dress on you before.
Is it custom-made for this Feast of All Souls Festival?
Your Majesty, a few days go, some foreign envoys brought in bird features as tribute,
because they had heard it was difficult to obtain bird feathers in Chang'an even with a high payment.
They thought this was a popular trend in Great Tang and found it inexplicable.
Now, I can see how it started.
Consort Yang has used many precious bird feathers to make the gown.
This is so ingenious.
It's so refreshing and impressive to see.
Your Majesty had ordered me that this Feast of All Souls Festival
must be held in grand style.
All the consorts and concubines haven't dared to slight it.
Everyone had an elegant gown made.
Talented Lady Wu even used golden silk thread for embroidery,
inlayed with Tian Mountain Jade,
for the design of peony flowers.
On such an important occasion,
why is Talented Lady Wu so late and making Your Majesty wait?
Your Majesty, it's so that Your Majesty not lose face
that I also had a new gown made.
Talented Lady Wu arrives!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
I heard that, in order to attend the Feast of All Souls Festival,
you used golden silk threads and Tian Mountain Jade to make an elegant gown.
If you regard the event so highly, why are you late?
Is there an explanation?
Your Majesty ordered Consort Yang to organize the Feast of All Souls Festival
and let me assist.
Sister is very capable, so I couldn't do much.
But I remembered Late Empress Zhangsun's virtues.
She worked hard in her whole life for the harem
and was truly a worthy example for all the consorts and concubines.
I dare not forget the virtues of Late Empress.
The Feast of All Souls Festival is dedicated to ancestors and the deceased.
The elegant grown that Your Majesty mentioned
is what I especially arranged to have Xiao Douzi of the Bureau of Imperial Attire
to make, according to what the late empress liked,
into a gown with the peony flowers in the design.
I took a bath and changed clothes, then personally
took the gown to offer as tribute to Empress Zhangsun's hall, that's why I came late.
Please mete out punishment, Your Majesty.
Meiniang, you are so pure-hearted and understanding.
You understand and obey proper etiquette.
You also understand why I want to hold the Feast of All Souls Festival in grand style.
I am very pleased.
You may rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Meiniang, I haven't seen the design of
the dress that you're wearing.
It doesn't appear to be the pleated skirt that is popular with Tang women, right?
Your Majesty's eyesight is like the blazing torch.
(Sharp eyesight)
The Feast of All Souls Festival is solemn and serious.
I thought that this gown should not look poor
but also not losing the imperial family's dignity.
Nor can it be extravagant and wasteful
and disobey Your Majesty's frugality and caring for the people
as well as the original goal for the Feast of All Souls Festival.
So, I jointly designed this gown with Xiao Douzi of the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
The craftsmanship isn't complex
and the fabric isn't opulent.
Simplifying the pleated skirt
can not only save some fabric
but also save handwork. It's sumptuous and exquisite,
and easy for the civilian women to imitate.
Meiniang is thoughtful.
It's my blessing that you can be so thoughtful for my sake.
Meiniang has skin that's fairer than snow.
It perfectly matches
this pleated skirt.
Your Majesty, the auspicious hour has arrived.
The ceremony can begin.
All the princes, consorts, and concubines,
follow me to go pay tribute together.
Your gown is improper for today's ceremony,
you should return to the Hall of Brilliant Joy and self-reflect.
[Hall of Immortal Nectar]
The summer heat is so strong.
Consort Yang, you have already kneeled for over two hours.
We are worried about your precious body.
That's right. His Majesty only told Consort Yang to go back and self-reflect.
He didn't say he would punish you.
Consort Yang, you don't need to suffer like this.
Our hearts ache for you, Consort Yang.
What do you two know?
His Majesty told me to go back to self-reflect.
It's so that he didn't have to see me and get annoyed.
If I can't appear frequently in front of His Majesty,
our feelings will reduce after a while.
I may as well kneel here so that His Majesty knows that I am remorseful.
It's heart-aching to see you like this.
If His Majesty will see me today
and hear my regrets in person,
and lecture me a few words, he will lose his anger.
That's how this page can be turned over.
Consort Yang is smart. So you are actually using the tactic of inflicting injury to yourself. (Tactic to win the enemy's confidence from the Book of War)
I originally thought I had inside help in the Hall of Sunset Pool
and I would win without any worry.
Who would have known that I still got trapped by Wu Meiniang.
This time, it's not only that I couldn't use the gown of "One Hundred Birds Paying Homage to the Phoenix"
to clearly affirm my status in the harem,
I actually helped Wu Meiniang
get ahead by stepping on me.
Consort Yang, His Majesty has asked you to go inside.
Consort Yang, you have kneeled for such a long time outside the hall,
His Majesty's anger has reduced quite a lot.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, I know I did wrong.
Please punish me, Your Majesty.
I told you to go back and self-reflect.
Why did you insist on kneeling outside to see me?
It's all my fault to make Your Majesty angry.
If I can't be forgiven by Your Majesty in person, I cannot be at ease.
When I was kneeling outside, I kept reflecting on my wrongdoing.
I know that I really did wrong.
Since you've reflected, then tell me,
what did you do wrong?
Your Majesty trusted me
and assigned me to organize the Feast of All Souls Festival.
But I disappointed Your Majesty's trust.
I reminded the Bureau of Imperial Attire
to make clothes that adhere to the rules of prosperity
so that the imperial family will not lose dignity.
But I didn't expect that Attire Expert Zhuo
didn't fully understand my intent.
Because I was busy with the event,
I didn't inspect the gown first.
I hurriedly changed into the gown right before the ceremony started.
Even though I thought it was inappropriate,
but it was already too late.
This is the result of your self-reflection?
It's to push off your wrongdoing?
You've misunderstood me, Your Majesty.
I am definitely guilty of oversight.
Let me tell you what you did wrong.
"One Hundred Birds Paying Homage to the Phoenix" is for the empress.
It's inappropriate for a consort or concubine to wear it. That's the first mistake.
Killing living things for the Feast of All Souls Festival disobeys Buddha's teachings. That's the second mistake.
To satisfy your personal need and be extremely wasteful, it goes against the need of the nation.
That's the third mistake.
Your Majesty, please allay your anger.
I know what I did wrong.
I don't think you really reflected.
You are only trying to push this mistake totally away from you.
Go back to your hall and continue to self-reflect. If you don't receive my summons,
do not appear in front of me.
Your Majesty!
I am willing to be punished for what I did wrong.
But there is one thing,
I beg that Your Majesty
won't deny my seeing you.
Escort Consort Yang back to her hall.
Yes.
[Memorial Table of Empress Zhangsun]
[Empress Zhangsun]
Today is the 15th day of the 7th month.
Among the civilians, they will light up lotus lamps to help light the way for the deceased.
I have especially brought two lotus lamps here today
in the hope of lighting Your Majesty's path to return to the palace.
His Majesty misses you greatly.
But since the start of this year,
His Majesty's health hasn't been good.
His Highness the Crown Prince has great aspirations as well as caring for the nation and the people.
His Majesty appreciates and likes him very well,
I hope Empress Zhangsun's spirit in Heaven
will bless His Majesty
and bless the crown prince.
Your Highness.
I came to light incense for my imperial mother
and unexpectedly ran into Talented Lady Wu.
I heard everything that Talented Lady Wu just said.
Talented Lady Wu is thoughtful.
In this inner palace, probably
the only ones who will sincerely come to pay respect to my mother,
other than His Majesty and me,
is only Talented Lady Wu then.
The late empress was virtuous.
I have always admired the late empress.
Today is the 15th day of the 7th month.
I am merely following the traditions among the civilians
to come to offer two lotus lamps
to the late empress and show a token of my thoughts.
You had the Bureau of Imperial Attire make the gown for imperial mother,
and defeated Consort Yang through this incident today.
To be honest, I have even more appreciation for Talented Lady's intelligence,
and I am in awe of your strategic thinking.
But tonight, you brought two lotus lamps for my imperial mother.
I am really touched.
I know that this has nothing to do with schemes or with the infighting in the harem.
There is no calculation to take advantage of.
This is your true sincerity to my imperial mother.
I will remember your kindness.
Your Highness is too serious.
Your Highness should hurry and light incense for the late empress.
I shall take my leave first.
Talented Lady Wu, walk slowly.
[Memorial Tablet for Empress Zhangsun]
[Autumn Comfort Gate]
Talented Lady, do you really believe that the lotus lamp will guide the dead souls to return to home?
The lotus lamps are lit for the living and to show those that are alive.
I purposely went this time
to show the crown prince.
The crown prince has a kind nature, but he is not stupid.
The talk about making a gown for the late empress today
could move His Majesty's heart, but not move the crown prince.
The crown prince is intelligent.
He knew it was just a ploy among the harem's infighting.
But these two lotus lamps,
although meager, could warm the crown prince's heart.
You are so smart, Talented Lady Wu.
I don't really want to scheme so much,
especially to scheme against a kind person like the crown prince,
but I have totally offended Prince of Cao and his mother.
If I can't win the crown prince's heart,
I won't be able to survive in the harem.
What you did really can't be considered a scheme against the crown prince.
In this inner palace,
who else, other than you, is truly sincere in helping the crown prince?
I used to be disgusted by scheming and plotting.
I had no idea that in order to stay alive,
I have become so calculating every step of the way.
I almost can't recognize myself now.
Don't be sad, Talented Lady Wu. You are forced by the circumstances.
If I didn't miscalculate, His Majesty will summon me very soon.
I will have to energize up by 200%.
Consort Yang has a secure position.
I can't knock her over in a short time.
It's only temporary that she loses favor.
I must grab the opportunity
to win His Majesty's heart.
Greetings, Consort Yang.
Attire Chief Lin. Attire Expert Zhuo. Do you acknowledge your crime?
- We deserve to die. Please allay your anger, Consort Yang.
-  We deserve to die. Please allay your anger, Consort Yang.
You actually know you deserve to die?
How dare you!
I was responsible for the Feast of All Souls Festival and was very busy with many miscellaneous tasks.
I repeatedly reminded you
that all the clothes worn by the consorts and concubines that day
must be treated with caution and care,
and no mistake could be made.
Who would have known that I took my eyes just slightly away,
you overstepped a boundary in making my gown and embroiled me in impropriety.
If I don't harshly punish you,
I would not be able to explain to His Majesty and, furthermore, would not be able to convince the entire harem.
Consort Yang, please be wise. The matter regarding your gown
was completely in Attire Expert Zhuo's charge.
This servant didn't know anything.
Attire Expert Zhuo is the ultimate culprit,
but you, Attire Chief Lin, are involved, too.
After all, you are the chief of the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
Consort Yang, please allay your anger. We do not shirk from our wrongdoing.
But the culprit is actually Physician Dou.
This Physician Dou, in order to appease Consort Yang,
he came up with the idea of "One Hundred Birds Paying Homage to the Phoenix," and even drew the design.
Physician Dou is scheming. I really cannot give him cover.
I hope Consort Yang will wisely judge.
Xiao Douzi is in big trouble.
[Lizheng Hall]
Your Highness! Your Highness!
You...
What's wrong, A'Sheng? You are in such a panic.
Your Highness, I was taking Xiao Douzi's favorite snacks to him.
But as soon as I arrived at the Bureau of Imperial Attire, I saw Consort Yang criticizing them for accountability.
Attire Chief Lin and Attire Expert Zhuo, in order to protect themselves,
pushed all the wrongdoing to Xiao Douzi.
I'm afraid Xiao Douzi is in big trouble.
- Follow me to the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
- Yes.
So you are Physician Dou.
Xiao Douzi greets Consort Yang.
I didn't know that there was such a talent like you in the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
I heard that you made the seven-fold skirt for Talented Lady Wu.
You also made the gown with peony flowers' design for the late empress.
My "One Hundred Birds Paying Homage to the Phoenix" was also your creation.
You are quite popular everywhere.
Replying to Consort Yang.
I saw that Attire Expert Zhuo was out of ideas for Consort Yang's gown.
To relieve her worries, I came up with the idea of "One Hundred Birds Paying Homage to the Phoenix."
Consort Yang, you have a supreme stature in the palace,
and you are deeply respected by all the other consorts and concubines.
You are also unparalleled in His Majesty's heart.
The design of "One Hundred Birds Paying Homage to the Phoenix" is most suitable for you, Consort Yang.
I was originally the sanitation medical officer at the Courtyard of Misfortune.
Attire Expert Zhuo temporarily borrowed me to help at the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
Naturally, I don't have much experience with the world.
I only told Attire Expert Zhuo of my immature ideas,
just as a suggestion.
Firstly, I wanted to express my affection and respect to Consort Yang.
Secondly, I wanted to relieve my master's worries. I thought, even if there was anything inappropriate,
Expert Attire Zhuo would know what not to do.
Attire Expert Zhou has served Consort Yang for many years, so she knows the best about propriety.
Xiao Douzi, shut up!
How dare you talk to Consort Yang?
You are the one who did wrong.
Why are you arguing to cover the truth
and falsely drag me in?
You're so clever with your mouth.
You say you are lowly, ignorant, and full of affection and respect for me.
It sounds really good.
If there weren't the seven-fold gown for Talented Lady Wu, nor the peony flower gown for the late empress,
I might have believed your sweet talk.
But now, however I look, I feel that you are framing me.
And you still dare to talk back? Watch out that I pull your tongue out!
Consort Yang is wise. Consort Yang judges wisely.
All of this trouble is caused by Physician Dou.
You, shut up!
You can't wait for me to deal with you?
Consort Yang, please allay your anger. It's all my ignorance.
I originally wanted to help Consort Yang but ended up making a mess.
Guards!
Take Xiao Douzi out for a beating. Keep beating him until I say stop.
Stop!
Greetings, Your Highness the Crown Prince.
Crown Prince, you are noble and also busy.
In a place like the Bureau of Imperial Attire,
there can't be much for Your Highness to personally sort out, is there?
I came to the Bureau of Imperial Attire to personally reward Physician Dou.
The gown he made for my imperial mother was based on Mother's favorite pattern when she was alive.
I think her spirit in Heaven should be very gratified.
Crown Prince, as the heir to the throne,
it seems that you are only busy with these trivial matters all day.
Wouldn't people criticize you if this were spread outside?
Filial piety is the top of 100 virtues. How is filial piety toward my imperial mother something trivial?
Besides, that Talented Lady Wu and Physician Dou together made the peony flower gown for Mother was also praised by His Majesty.
Have I heard wrong?
Why does Consort Yang want to punish by beating the person that His Majesty has praised
and that I am about to give a reward to?
The design of "One Hundred Birds Paying Homage to the Phoenix" was created by Physician Dou.
He harbors evil intentions and embroiled me in injustice! Shouldn't he be harshly punished?
Consort Yang, that doesn't sound right.
Physician Dou was transferred to the Bureau of Imperial Attire from the Courtyard of Misfortune
to provide temporary help here. Based on his experience,
even if his designs are inappropriate,
they should have followed the procedure to be checked.
If his superiors didn't give approval, the designs
wouldn't have been made into clothes
that offended His Majesty.
Consort Yang, you said you were too busy to affirm the propriety of the gown.
That's why you didn't know it was inappropriate and pushed the responsibility to the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
Consort Yang, do you think this kind of argument will convince His Majesty
and the entire palace from top to bottom?
You–
Crown Prince,
must you make it difficult for me today over a mere Physician Dou?
I am definitely protecting Physician Dou today.
Of course, I'm not only protecting him.
I'm protecting the word, "truth."
I advise Consort Yang.
If you insist on making a scene of this matter today at the Bureau of Imperial Attire,
you will be suspected by the people of covering up your own wrongdoing.
I remember that His Majesty told Consort Yang to return to your place to self-reflect,
instead of coming over to criticize the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
Guards!
Drag Zhuo Jinniang outside!
Cane her 50 times as a warning to everyone!
From now on, will anyone still dare to commit dereliction of duty at the Bureau of Imperial Attire?
Consort Yang, please allay your anger! Consort Yang, have mercy!
This servant was wholeheartedly working for you!
Consort Yang, have mercy! Consort Yang, have mercy!
I was really just doing work for you!
Consort Yang, have mercy!
[Hall of Immortal Dew]
I have been summoned here by decree. Greetings, Your Majesty.
Meiniang, I feel a little lonely today.
Come over and talk with me.
Yes.
Come here.
Meiniang, you know that after Empress Zhangsun departed,
within the harem,
my favorite has been Consort Yang.
If it weren't for the opposition from all the court officials back then,
she would be sitting in the empress's seat now.
I've remembered her suffering and given her extra affection and respect.
But during today's Feast of All Souls Festival,
she really disappointed me.
I was also self-reflecting today.
Has my special affection for her
turned her into how she was today:
arrogant, overstepping,
haughty because of the favor she's received?
She is no longer the gentle, virtuous,
humble Consort Yang from years ago.
Your Majesty, you don't need to worry.
I'm sure Consort Yang knows she's done wrong
and is feeling regretful.
I hope so.
But, Meining, today,
you really touched me.
I didn't expect that
you've been keeping respect and affection for Empress Zhangsun in your heart.
You don't know I've always missed her.
I'm very gratified.
Your Majesty has been missing Empress Zhangsun and feeling upset.
How about I sing a song for you
to relieve your yearning?
Meining, you want to sing a song for me?
Sure, sing for me.
Your edict is obeyed.
♪ The peach blossoms are radiant in the morning ♪
♪ A lovely lady feels the spring arriving  ♪
[Empress Wende]
♪ Her face is round and delicate like a peach blossom ♪
♪ Her slim figure like the willow tree branches ♪
♪ The butterflies dance among the flowers ♪
♪ The warblers chatter is overheard in the trees ♪
♪ A hermit doesn't need to travel far ♪
♪ To feel the free air of spring ♪
Your Majesty.
It's Empress Zhangsun's
"Song of Spring Tour."
I didn't know Meining would match it with a melody and sing it so beautifully.
I am stupid. Empress Zhangsun's poem is pure, elegant, joyful, and romantic.
I don't think I was able to sing the full flavor.
I just wanted to sing it
to allay Your Majesty's yearning feelings.
You sang well.
It made me suddenly go back to that year.
I still remember that day. The weather was lovely.
Empress Zhangsun and I came back from visiting the imperial garden.
Empress Zhangsun was in a great mood
and wrote this Song of Spring Tour.
I really liked it.
That was Empress Zhangsun's good time.
It was also a good time for me and Empress Zhangsun.
Consort Yang!
Consort Yang, don't worry about smashing things,
but it's not worth it to get angry and upset your body.
Have you forgotten Imperial Physician Zong's reminder?
Too much anger will upset your health. Don't be angry anymore.
His Majesty asked you to stay here and self-refect.
But if you make such a ruckus now,
what if it's spread outside and His Majesty finds out. Wouldn't he get more upset?
I suffered enough outside.
Why can't I vent a little in my own palace?
I just want to smash. Who dares to spread this outside?
Move aside!
Consort Yang, allay your anger. Consort Yang, allay your anger.
We are loyal to you until death,
and we won't ever spread any gossip against you, Consort Yang.
Do you think that I'm angry because
I lost to Talented Lady Wu and also got scolded by the crown prince?
I am feeling upset that I couldn't protect my son.
I see the crown prince getting stronger every day under Talented Lady Wu's support.
But I...
probably don't have much time left.
Consort Yang, you are in the prime of life. You can't say this about yourself.
That's right. Consort Yang, you are tired.
You should take a good rest.
After you've rested, then
make a long-term plan for you and for His Highness.
You are right.
The more urgent it is, the calmer I should be
and think of a good plan to fight the enemy.
After the incident at the Bureau of Imperial Attire today,
it seemed that I was defeated by Li Zhi on the surface,
but it's not so. That Xiao Douzi is only a little physician,
as lowly as an insect, but Crown Prince
is protecting him so much.
This is too abnormal.
Perhaps...
this is Crown Prince's weakness.
Dan Qing, order people to monitor Xiao Douzi.
Find out exactly what his relationship is with the crown prince.
Yes.
Yu'er.
You are right, this is really a good place.
Remote, quiet, and no one to disturb us.
This is a rare paradise within the inner palace.
It's the 15th day of the 7th month today.
According to folk traditions, people would release water lanterns
to guide the road home for their deceased family members and friends.
I heard you say previously that you hid your identity in the palace
so that you can hide from your enemy.
I know it's probably not easy to pay tribute to your mother.
This place is remote, so no one will notice.
You can release a water lantern, too, then.
It's so rare for you to still remember it. Thank you.
Mother, it's the 17th day of the 7th month today.
Have you returned to the mortal realm to take a look?
It's too bad that we don't have a home of our own.
I also don't know if you came back,
where would you return to?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
♫  Watching the flowers bloom and fall in the courtyard  ♫
♫  How many loves, regrets, entanglements, separations,
reunions must we go through together  ♫
♫  Uncover the vicious cycle of the past  ♫
♫  Fate has its uncertainties  ♫
♫  I've spent this life with brush and ink in hand  ♫
♫  Writing about what love is ♫
♫  Borrow from the relentless of the night  ♫
♫  To exchange for the certainty of a promise  ♫
♫  There are too many bumpy roads along the way  ♫
♫  The more twists, the deeper it is  ♫
♫  Breaking up and making up is like an illusion  ♫
♫  Resembles a traveler traveling through this life  ♫
♫  Time ignores everything including obsession  ♫
♫  With the candlelight flickering indefinitely  ♫
♫  After the fire, there was only one thing left  ♫
♫  A bright moon that makes one's heart tingle  ♫