Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
[Weaving a Tale of Love]
[Episode 34]
[Prince of Cao's Manor]
Your Highness, Pei Xingjian has arrived.
Greetings, Prince of Cao.
Ask Liuli to come here.
Yes.
Pei Xingjian, later when you two meet,
I hope you don't mind me here.
Frankly,
whether to you,
or to her, I am not at ease.
So, later, it is better to watch.
Please, Your Highness.
Consort Yang, Pei Xingjian has arrived.
His Highness has asked me to bring Liuli there.
- Go ahead.
- Yes.
Wait.
Where's the note you just wrote?
Bring it here and let me have a look again.
[Tomorrow at 11:00 a.m., Prince of Cao will raise troops at Black Tortoise Gate]
Remember.
This note, you have to find a chance to secretly give to Pei Xingjian.
The more you give it carefully,
the more he will believe it as the truth.
Liuli!
Liuli.
Your Highness has asked for me. I am not sure what you have asked me for?
Pei Xingjian is afraid for your safety and doesn't believe that you have followed me.
So... I arranged especially for you two to meet.
To help Imperial Guard Leader's lovesickness.
Also, for him to give up and follow me.
So in the future, you two will be enemies, harming your relationship.
Your Highness, you have spoken wrong. Imperial Guard Leader and I have no love.
He is he, I am me.
I am just a pitiful person who cannot save herself.
How would I have the strength to make Imperial Guard Leader switch?
If he follows Prince of Cao, it is not thanks to me.
If he continues to go on the dark path,
please don't involve me.
Liuli, I know you are still upset.
I also don't wish for your forgiveness.
You can resent me or get mad at me.
I have nothing to say. I really didn't think it would come to this.
I didn't think the medicine Physician Heng prescribed
was a poison that could take your life.
I never thought from the start,
the more I wanted to protect you, the more I could harm you.
You didn't think. Such simple 3 words.
You have done so many things in secret.
Eleven years ago, you changed my fortune.
Eleven years later, you gave my mother's golden needle to Zhuo Jinniang.
As Zhuo Jinniang wished, she got my mother's title, "Number One Needle in the World."
After, you still thought I wasn't pitiful enough,
yet you made the poison become a medical pill for Xiao Shunzi to make me eat!
Now, I am not human nor a ghost. Living is like hell.
I cannot face Mother after I die. This is all thanks to you!
In the end, who thought all you could say would be "I didn't think"!
Then, you so simply have moved on from it?
Liuli,
I know you feel wronged.
It is my fault.
Don't worry, no matter what,
even if it takes my life, I will cure you.
Pei Xingjian, you still don't understand!
I am not afraid of death, I am afraid that till death,
Mother's wronged case cannot be overturned.
Mother's title of Number One Needle in the World has been snatched by her murderer.
I hate so much...
hate that I was careless, and could not see clearly...
to see your true self.
Liuli.
Pei Xingjian,
remember what I just said.
Although you have saved me multiple times,
but you have also harmed me several times.
Now I don't owe you anything.
You and I are no longer associated.
Liuli.
Women's views.
You don't need to mind them.
A man's future is more important.
You saw Liuli, and I've also promised a great career for you.
When do you plan to give me an answer?
Future? Prosperity?
I don't need either.
I only want Liuli. Please tell me
if Liuli's poison can be cured.
Since I have the poison, I also have the cure.
As long as you follow me,
I will surely give the cure to Liuli.
Since you have the cure, why don't you cure Pu Banu?
I always reward based on their accomplishement.
If Pu Banu wants to get the cure,
then he has to let me see his value.
You and Liuli also.
I don't raise useless people and I don't do sales where I lose money.
As long as you have the cure,
then I will not disappoint you.
Okay.
Also, one more thing.
Liuli's real identity...
Her pretending to be a male cannot be revealed.
No matter what reason.
If Liuli dies,
I am a useless pawn.
I really didn't think you were a lovesick fellow who didn't care.
Please remember.
No problem! I agree to all.
I am not afraid of what you ask for, I am only afraid you have nothing to ask for.
[Prince of Cao Manor]
[Tomorrow at 11:00 a.m., Prince Cao will raise troops at Black Tortoise Gate]
It is such a shame you did not see yourself, Mother.
If it weren't that I already knew,
I might have been scared by her fierceness.
Pei Xingjian really loves you.
Devoted.
It makes me touched, too.
Pei Xingjian and Li Zhi really trust her.
He will surely believe the note's message.
Tomorrow, as long as the East Palace shifts its army to surround Black Tortoise Gate,
we will be totally justified to accuse the crown prince of revolt.
Then, search the East Palace
and find the dragon robe that Liuli custom-made for the crown prince.
Then Crown Prince's evidence of overthrowing will be the truth.
[Hall of Esteemed Virtues]
This note was given by Xiao Douzi secretly when the Prince of Cao wasn't looking.
It is Xiao Douzi's handwriting.
This note shouldn't be fake.
A'Sheng, how is His Majesty today?
His Majesty is still unconscious and shows no signs of waking.
His Majesty has been unconscious for many days.
If we make a choice after he wakes up, then it'll be too late.
It is urgent. Please take lead, Your Highness.
Prepare.
Tomorrow, shift the East Palace's army.
At noon we will surround the Black Tortoise Gate.
Yes.
- Consort Yang. Your Highness.
- It's late.
You better hurry and embroider the nine-dragon robe for the crown prince.
Consort Yang, even if I don't sleep and hurry to sew,
I still won't be able to finish the nine-dragon dragon robe in one night.
What do you mean by this?
Unless you want to find an excuse to not do it?
It's not that I won't do it.
It is that I have a better plan.
Say it.
The crown prince likes me.
Usually, I make all his clothing.
A few days ago, I made a new serpent robe for the crown prince. (A serpent robe is less in rank than the dragon robe)
I haven't had time to send it.
Now I only need to get that clothing,
and change the four-toed claw on the robe to a five-toed claw.
Then the serpent will become a dragon, and the serpent robe will become a dragon robe.
It can also show Crown Prince trying to overthrow the emperor.
There is another advantage to changing a serpent robe to a dragon robe.
Compared to the usual serpent robe that Crown Prince usually wears,
the dragon robe only has one more.
Ordinary people won't be able to detect.
If the crown prince wears this
in front of people, then it'll be hard evidence.
He cannot say anything.
Good idea.
Good.
We will do as you say.
[Adjutant's Bureau]
I have a lot of hate,
hate that I was careless
and could not see clearly.
To see your true self.
Pei Xingjian, remember what I just said.
Liuli probably wants me to see the note's true self.
[Embrace All to Carry Forward]
[Tomorrow at 11:00 a.m., Prince of Cao will raise troops at Black Tortoise Gate]
Either the candlelight is too dim, then the candlelight is too bright,
then there are too many bugs, and then you wanted to use the toilet. What do you want now?
Thirsty. Bring me tea.
Haven't you already finished embroidering? Can't you get it yourself?
The imperial robe is finished, but I have not finished my tasks.
Delaying progress, can you be responsible?
- What are you doing?
- Don't you see me sewing a secret message for Crown Prince?
You want to send a message to the crown prince?
Rather than suspecting I am secretly sending messages to Crown Prince,
then go tell Consort Yang.
Don't make a big ruckus and disturb me.
I have asked you to pour me water. Did you not hear?
Sign? What sign?
It is a Douzi, of Xiao Douzi.
It is the same color thread as the imperial robe. If you don't look carefully, you can't see it.
She said last time that Prince of Cao in front of Crown Prince
put poison on Crown Prince's clothes, so he keeps it in mind.
After, he only wears clothes sewn by her.
This clothing is with Douzi as a sign.
When she sewed the words, did she purposely avoid you?
No, she even told me to report to you.
Since she didn't take precautions with you, there won't be anything.
Consort Yang, then are you really going to let her send the imperial robe to the East Palace alone?
What if she has suspicions?
Won't she ruin your and His Highness's big matter?
We naturally cannot let her go alone.
Find a maid from the manor.
Make her seem like an embroidery maid from the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
Let her go with Liuli to the East Palace to send the dragon robe.
Remember, you have to find a smart one.
So that she watches carefully and won't leave her side for even a second.
There cannot be any carelessness at all.
Rest assured, Consort Yang.
- Eunuch Wang, how are you lately?
- Good, good, good.
I haven't seen you in many days.
I've heard a lot.
I heard you committed a big crime and suffered a lot.
How is your injury?
Thank you for worrying, Eunuch Wang.
My wound is already well.
These days, I have been recovering at the Courtyard of Misfortune.
The task to sew clothes for the crown prince has also been delayed.
I am really not at ease.
This is the serpent robe that I especially made for His Highness the Crown Prince.
I hope that he likes it.
Here.
I heard Pei Xingjian say you were captured by the Prince of Cao's men.
Are you fine now?
I am a low official. I am grateful for the crown prince's care,
but I have also been harmed because of this.
Now I am a drug addict. I am useless.
Not only can I not help the crown prince,
I might even be the crown prince's burden.
I feel really guilty and have nobody to thank.
I can only use threads to show my intentions.
I probably cannot live long.
I don't know in the future
whether or not I will be able to sew clothing for the crown prince.
It looks like the crown prince should almost be awake. How about you wait a bit?
If His Highness can you see, he would be happy.
Where's Xiao Douzi?
Your Highness, Xiao Douzi put the serpent robe down and left immediately.
He said he has no face to see you.
What does that mean? Xiao Douzi was harmed because of others causing him to be a drug addict.
It's because I'm respected that I'm hated.
This is obviously implicated by me.
Wasn't Xiao Douzi captured by the Prince of Cao?
How could she come here to deliver the serpent robe?
Did Xiao Douzi come alone?
There is a maid that came with Xiao Douzi.
She said she is from the Bureau of Imperial Attire, but I've never seen her before.
I boldly think
that maid may have been sent by the Prince of Cao.
If that is the case, for Xiao Douzi to deliver the serpent robe,
it must have been on the Prince of Cao's orders.
Last time, didn't the Prince of Cao do something to your clothing?
Unless they want to use my trust in Xiao Douzi to harm me?
A'Sheng, did Xiao Douzi leave any other signs?
Your Highness, I have looked carefully at this clothing, it is the same as before.
Xiao Douzi embroidered the word "Douzi" inside the clothing.
But this "Douzi" word this time looks messy.
It looks like 3 dots.
Let me see.
Xiao Douzi has just gotten well after being really sick. He just became addicted to drugs.
His hands were not as active as before.
It can be understood.
If it was forced by the Prince of Cao,
Xiao Douzi wouldn't leave a sign.
You're right.
This Douzi is your and Xiao Douzi's secret message.
It means for you to wear it without any worrying.
If Xiao Douzi was forced by someone,
he wouldn't sew this Douzi.
I haven't worn clothing sewn by Xiao Douzi in a long time.
Hurry up and let me try it on.
[Hall of Immortal Nectar]
Your Majesty, don't blame me for being ruthless.
Maybe it is that I have never thought to fight for power.
I only hoped you would treat me well.
I could ask for nothing for my whole life,
but what about our Ming'er?
Crown Prince and Ming'er are like fire and water now.
If it isn't you who dies, it is I who dies.
My lung disease cannot be cured.
Even if you wake up, you probably don't have many days.
In the future, if the crown prince reigns,
without you and I to protect Ming'er,
Ming'er will surely die.
I have no other choice.
Even if I die, I need to fight for my son once.
Consort Yang, His Majesty woke up a while last night.
He was more conscious than before.
Eunuch Pan, I have something I want to talk to you about.
[The Prince of Cao Li Ming is virtuous and brave. I now proclaim Li Ming as Crown Prince to succeed the throne.]
[Li Zhi is demoted from the crown prince's seat.]
Consort Yang,
making up this order will have nine generations killed.
His Majesty's death is today.
If you want to live, then listen and do what you should.
What do you want to do?
Today, there will be two big things happening.
The first is the crown prince surrounding the Black Tortoise Gate.
The Prince of Cao will catch him red-handed.
The second thing is His Majesty dying.
Director Pan Qinghai reading the verdict of His Majesty's will.
Reporting to disown Crown Prince, Li Zhi,
making Prince of Cao, Li Ming as emperor.
Consort Yang, this probably isn't that easy.
A few days ago, His Majesty just appointed the two ministers as regents.
He has already given protection to the crown prince.
If you say the crown prince is using his army to overthrow,
not only will the people not believe,
even the officials will be suspicious.
They will naturally be suspicious.
Then I will need you to prove it
so they believe it.
Me? What can I do?
Then, you have to speak with me,
be firm that your previous superior, Gao Quan,
was a spy placed by His Majesty's side.
Since the start, he has done something to his nourishment soup.
This is what caused His Majesty to be deeply ill, unable to be treated.
His Majesty knows Gao Quan poisoned him, so he asked for him to be killed.
To find out the mastermind,
His Majesty purposely didn't make it big,
telling the public Gao Quan accidentally died.
Just last night,
His Majesty had found out that Gao Quan is Li Zhi's man.
So he wants to disown Li Zhi and look highly at the Prince of Cao.
Gao Quan has been helping Crown Prince. This, everyone knows.
This way, isn't my plan flawless?
You are very daring! You two dare to block me?
Consort Yang has ordered that no one can leave or enter the Hall of Immortal Nectar.
[Hall of Immortal Nectar]
What do you two want?
Your manor has bought vegetables and asked for us to send it.
Are you the substitutes for Old Wang?
Yes, yes!  He asked us to come.
Who are you? You dare to pretend to be the vegetable person to enter the manor?!
Please spare us!  We are here to find someone.
Where is this?! Let us go!
Aren't you here to find him?
His Highness said to admit you guys.
Child, child!  Are you well?
Xiao Douzi, what happened to you?
Where are you unwell?
Foster father. Xiao Shunzi. Why are you guys here?
I heard Pei Xingjian say you were captured by the Prince of Cao.
We couldn't sleep the whole night. We thought to pretend to be vegetable people to save you.
But who thought once we entered, we were caught.
Child.
It is all my fault.
Now I am already someone useless.
Why did you two use your lives to save me?
Child, are you all right?
Is your drug addiction relapsing?
It is all my fault! I fed you. It is all my fault.
His Highness has ordered.
If your drug addiction relapses, then to give you one pill.
Child.
No. No.
- Child.
- What I need to do has already been finished.
In the future, I would rather die
than touch this drug again.
Child, hurry up and tell me
why Prince of Cao wants to capture you and poison you.
Because he wants to harm the crown prince.
No,
they have already harmed him.
Already harmed him?
Yes.
Consort Yang, right now the crown prince is wearing the serpent robe that Liuli embroidered.
Great! Liuli knows her stuff.
Your Highness, Prince of Cao can only move his own army.
They are just wearing the armor that was secretly shipped into Chang'an.
They intend to control the critical station at the Black Tortoise Gate.
Your Highness, rest assured, our East Palace's troops are sufficient to defend against them.
I have already prepared.
Please relay the order to go to the Black Tortoise Gate to catch the Prince of Cao.
Not only do we have to go to the Black Tortoise Gate,
we also have to meet the Prince of Cao
to not disappoint Xiao Douzi's hardship.
I will immediately mobilize the East Palace troops
to go with Crown Prince to the Black Tortoise Gate.
[Reform from the Source]
I understand then.
When you passed the message,
you hid a secret code.
But I don't know if the secret code
will be noticed by Crown Prince and Pei Xingjian.
Be good and stay there. When it gets dark,
you'll be taken to the Prince of Cao's Manor to see Pei Xingjian.
The extra dot that I sewed on the "Douzi" word is a dragon claw.
The embroidery method is different from the other two dots.
I wanted to remind the crown prince that there is an extra toe on the claw for the serpent robe,
so the serpent robe has become a dragon robe.
Even though your idea is ingenius,
but would it be too risky?
You are the person that Crown Prince and Pei Xingjian trust the most.
Foster Father, the Prince of Cao has repeatedly harmed the crown prince.
His scheming never stops. If I don't pretend to obey them,
they will definitely think of other schemes to harm the crown prince.
It will come again and again.
All the gods and immortals, please protect Crown Prince and Pei Xingjian
to be lucky and see through the Prince of Cao's insidious plot.
If Attire Expert An's spirit is listening in Heaven, please protect us to safely get through this danger.
[Prince of Cao Manor]
Your Highness, the soldiers have been trained for many days and are ready for their mission.
We're only waiting for Your Highness to issue the command.
Everything is ready. We're just waiting for the east wind.
(Just need one more thing)
All officers and soldiers, please wait patiently.
What time is it now?
Replying to Your Highness, it is 11:00 a.m.
Reporting!
Your Highness, the troops are moving from the East Palace.
Crown Prince and Pei Xingjian are personally leading them.
Your Highness, shall we start?
Wait a little longer.
There must not be any mistake in today's battle.
[Brightly Lit Gate]
Reporting!
Your Highness, Crown Prince and Pei Xingjian are leading the troops toward the Black Tortoise Gate.
Are Crown Prince's troops really going to the Black Tortoise Gate?
Crown Prince's troops went around Taiji Palace and kept going north to the Jian Fu Gate,
they then went westward, and the Black Tortoise Gate won't be far.
Your Highness, if we don't start now, it may be too late.
Crown Prince Li Zhi is planning to revolt.
He is raising troops at the Black Tortoise Gate. All officers and soldiers, listen to my order.
- Yes!
Follow me to rush to the Black Tortoise Gate to capture the rebels.
Once the mission succeeds, all the officers and soldiers
will be meritorious contributors to Great Tang. I will
definitely reward based on merits!
- Capture the rebels!
- Support Prince of Cao!
- Here, top it off.
- Come, drink.
Guards.
Guard Pu, why are you delivering the food today?
Where is Xiao Cui?
His Highness has something big to do today and took away most of the manor's troops.
He especially dispatched me to deliver food
and to also inspect the jail cells,
to prevent
any bandits taking advantage of the empty manor.
Guard Pu, you've worked hard.
It's a trivial matter. The two of you,
I'll deliver the food inside and also check around.
You can rest assured and enjoy the warm food.
- Yes.
What do you want?
I only see the three of you in this entire jail.
But there is food for a fourth person in this container.
I only want to know where this fourth person is jailed.
You are the Prince of Cao's dog.
You've helped him to commit many sinful wrongdoings.
You should know very well all of those unspeakable crimes.
Why did you come here to ask us?
We don't have to argue or discuss old accounts.
I came to find this person because Pei Xingjian asked me.
I came to help you.
It's also to help myself.
Liuli has already been harmed by you all like this.
Do you think we will still believe you?
Just save your strength. Don't try to lie to us with pretty words.
I am not lying to you. I don't need to either.
You can see.
Liuli is tormented by the poison. So am I.
Prince of Cao has been controlling me with this poison. My addiction
has pierced into the bone marrow.
Forget it, if you don't believe me.
I'll make the story short.
Pei Xingjing is suspecting that there is a poison master behind the Prince of Cao.
Usually whoever makes the poison can also detoxify it.
I've looked everywhere in the manor except this dungeon.
Pei Xingjian is speculating that if there really is such a poison master behind the Prince of Cao,
it's very likely that he is hidden somewhere in this dungeon.
You just said, there are only three of us jailed here,
but there is food for four people?
That's why he must be
hidden in a secret place.
These days, during the middle of the night,
I occasionally heard a knocking sound from the underground.
Really?
[Peace within the Four Seas]
Crown Prince Li Zhi intends to poison and kill His Majesty,
raise troops at the Black Tortoise Gate and rebel. The evidence is confirmed.
I will eliminate the wrongdoers and return things to normal
and arrest Li Zhi, the traitor who would commit regicide and patricide.
Li Zhi!
Come out now to face your charges!
[Inner Gate]
Why are Zhangsun Wuji and Zhu Suiliang here?
I wonder why the two of you are here?
Last night, this old minister and Minister Chu received a secret report,
which claimed that the Prince of Cao was secretly exercising troops and horses as well as hoarding armor
with the intent to rebel
and will raise troops at the Black Tortoise Gate today at 11:00 a.m.
What I see now concurs with the secret report
without a single difference.
Crown Prince is the one rebelling!
Are the two of you helping the crown prince to rebel?
The one raising troops at the Black Tortoise Gate to rebel
is actually you, Prince of Cao!
We were entrusted by the crown prince to lead troops to guard the Black Tortoise Gate.
Truth and lies are clearly seen.
You are Crown Prince's Ministers-Regent.
Of course, you will speak for the crown prince.
Tell Crown Prince to come out!
I want to question him in person!
Your Highness, it's men from the East Palace.
Shouldn't the East Palace's troops be inside the Black Tortoise Gate now?
I'm afraid we've been trapped by the crown prince.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
♫  Watching the flowers bloom and fall in the courtyard  ♫
♫  How many loves, regrets, entanglements, separations,
reunions must we go through together  ♫
♫  Uncover the vicious cycle of the past  ♫
♫  Fate has its uncertainties  ♫
♫  I've spent this life with brush and ink in hand  ♫
♫  Writing about what love is  ♫
♫  Borrow from the relentless of the night  ♫
♫  To exchange for the certainty of a promise  ♫
♫  There are too many bumpy roads along the way  ♫
♫  The more twists, the deeper it is  ♫
♫  Breaking up and making up is like an illusion  ♫
♫  Resembles a traveler traveling through this life  ♫
♫  Time ignores everything including obsession  ♫
♫  With the candlelight flickering indefinitely  ♫
♫  After the fire, there was only one thing left  ♫
♫  A bright moon that makes one's heart tingle  ♫