Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
[Weaving a Tale of Love]
[Episode 6]
Liuli, you can live here at ease.
If you're missing anything, just tell me and I'll get it for you.
A'Ni, can you lend me some money?
I am penniless now and it's inconvenient to go out.
I'm empty-headed.
I should have thought of this.
Liuli, take this money and use it.
I can't use that much.
This money isn't that much value.
I'm afraid it's not enough for you for a few days.
I have money. I can pay it back tomorrow.
If you have money, then where is it?
I'm not lying. I do have money and a fair amount.
It's just... it was picked up by a Simen student.  I'll go get it back.
[Simen College]
This man knows that Duke of Hedong's Heir Apparent.
I offended the heir that day.
If his friend recognizes me and deliberately makes it difficult for me
and doesn't give me the money back, what will I do?
Uncle Zhang, where is she?
The young lady was just here.
Why has she disappeared in an instant?
Forget it. You can go back.
Yes.
Wait!
This bag belongs to me.
How will you prove that this bag is yours?
Sir, you don't know this, but
my cousin works in the palace
and has unfortunately died of illness.
The family asked someone to transport my cousin's corpse out of the palace.
Unexpectedly, the horse cart carrying the coffin
got turned over in the market
when the horse got scared. Everything was in chaos.
After that, a kindhearted person
brought back my cousin's corpse,
but his belongings were lost.
I went to search for them in the market,
and that's how I discovered your message.
I should have come sooner to retrieve my cousin's belongings,
but it so happened that Simen College was closed for the internal exam.
That's why I've delayed until today.
So that person was your cousin?
This bag is his belonging?
Yes, yes, yes!
This is the one.
But you've never seen this bag.
How do you know it is the one I'm holding?
There are three small bags inside the big bag.
The colors of the three small bags
are separately green, red, and blue.
If you don't believe me, Sir, just check it.
That's right, this bag is yours.
The jade is returned in one piece to Zhao.
(T/N: The property is returned intact to the owner.)
Thank you. You do not keep a lost time and have a noble character, Sir.
You are indeed an exemplary scholar. I have nothing to repay you with,
so I can only wish you good health and fortune,
continued success in your career and many students.
Take care!
- Good! Good!
- Good!
- Awesome!
- Once more!
Good!
Come catch me!
Don't run! Give me back my candied haw!
Awesome!
You really are... you are indeed in the same ilk as that Duke of Hedong's heir.
- Stop, Miss, you can't go inside!
- Pei Xingjian!
- Miss, you can't go inside!
- Miss!
- Pei Xingjian!
Impudent!
This is Simen College, not the market. Who is barging in?
I'm looking for Pei Xingjian. Tell him to come out.
I told you that I already asked someone to find him.
Why are you so impatient, Miss?
He cheated me of my money. Why would he dare to come out to see me?
He must be hiding.
What?
You said Pei Xingjian cheated you out of your money?
That's right!
Pei Xingjian, I've caught you today.
It's like this, I am Pei Xingjian's superior.
My name is Xue Xu. I'll take you to find him
and uphold justice for you.
Thank you, Sir Xue.
Young Master Pei is coming.
Why are you here again?
Where is my cousin's money? Give it back to me!
Money? DIdn't I already give it to you?
Are you telling me that these are my cousin's belongs?
- The bag contained these things?
- That's right.
The bag only had rocks and tree branches.
No, no, no. I almost got sidetracked by you.
The bag originally had money, but you exchanged the content
and put these things in.
Pei Xingjian, stop! What is that attitude of yours?
You would believe such a crude scam?
This woman is clearly a cheat.
Or she took what was inside the bag and is still not content.
Now she wants to bite me back. (T/N: falsely accuse)
Anyway, I've already returned the bag's content to you.
If you continue to bother me, I'll report to the authorities.
I've never seen such a despicable person as you.
Pei Xingjian, stop!
Give me my things back.
Simen College's Pei Xingjian has taken a civilian woman's money by force.
You have shamed the Imperial Academy.
I am weak and alone,
orphaned without support. I ask everyone here
to carry out justice for me.
Who is this?
How could this happen?
What's the situation?
Young Miss, don't be anxious.
Regarding such a shameful action,
Simen College will definitely not condone it.
I'll take you to find the Director of Studies now to get justice for you.
Thank you, Sir Xue, for upholding justice.
Pei Xingjian, what are you doing?
If you are not guilty, why won't you let the victim talk?
I am the victim.
I did something good, and still got falsely accused.
This woman is talking nonsense and switching lies and truth. It's no use to talk more.
The easiest to do is to throw her out.
So heavy.
You still want to hit me?
After all, you are a woman.
If I abandon you here and you run into a lecherous person,
you'll probably be taken advantage of.
Forget it. Consider it as teaching you a lesson today.
Let me tell you! A gentleman likes money but will only obtain it through righteous ways. Understand?
Say it!  Where is your home?
You are a bad person. I'll cut you into pieces!
It's so difficiult to be a good person.
I was going to just let you go,
but I didn't know you would refuse to cooperate.
This evil person. He's stolen my money
and he would even play me.
In front of everyone,
will this evil person take advantage of a woman?
Help!
This woman looks familiar.
Why are you closing your eyes?
Your eyes can talk,
then use your eyes to show me the way then.
Either you use your ways to show me and
tell me where your home is or I'll leave you here.
You decide.
Let's go.
[An Residence]
If you dare to come make a ruckus at Simen College again,
- whenever I see you, I'll throw you out.
- Release me right now!
In another six hours, the acupoint will be released by itself.
You can stay here and reflect on your wrongdoing.
You big bad man, cheater... indeed, birds of a feather stick together.
You can't be anyone good if you follow behind that Duke of Hedong's heir.
I swear, however you took in those things today,
I will make you give them back in the future!
Why did I tell the truth as soon as I got anxious?
I'm doomed. It will be even more difficult
to get what Mother left me.
What do you want?
It's you.
You are that Hu woman that was copying the wall portrait in Da Ci'en Temple.
That's right, it was me. What do you plan to do with me?
I can't do anything to you, but the Duke of Hedong's heir can.
Are you threatening me?
Duke of Hedong's heir isn't as tolerant as I am.
He has already ordered people to inquire about your background.
I'm afraid he will soon come over to get you into trouble.
I can only help you this far. Best of luck.
You want to scare me by using the Duke of Hedong's heir? You are underestimating me.
Don't go!  Release my hand first!
Big bad man! Don't go!
My hand is sore.
Bad man!
Xiao Guizi, what are you looking for?
I'm looking for Xiao Shunzi's stuff.
What did Xiao Shunzi hide?
Xiao Shunzi was locked up for so long, Eunuch Sun ran around for so long that his legs became skinny.
But not only did he not save him,
he couldn't even see him.
But it's all right. Xiao Shunzi was selling fragrance sachets
and earned some money, but
who would know where this money is hidden?
Let me help you!
Hey, what are you doing?
Xiao Guizi! Xiao Guizi!
I finally found out! Xiao Guizi, come here.
Slow down, slow down.
I finally found out.
It turns out someone
quietly went to Deputy Director Pan to tattletale.
They said Xiao Shunzi illegally sold outside items in the palace and stole money.
Eunuch Pan is famous for his greed.
Once he heard this, of course he was curious.
If he doesn't get something good from Xiao Shunzi,
he definitely won't let him go easily.
Who would be so evil? If I find out, I'll fight him until he can't stand!
What use is talking about this?
Let's collect some money to save Xiao Shunzi.
Did you find Xiao Shunzi's money?
Oh, right!
I was looking everywhere.
But I couldn't find it at all. How about let's look for Eunuch Sun?
Maybe he has ideas?
Eunuch Sun also has his hands full right now.
People from the Bureau of Imperial Attire are looking for Physician Dou from him.
Eunuch Sun doesn't have the person, so they're fighting right now.
Really?
I haven't seen Physician Dou in many days. He didn't go to the Bureau of Imperial Attire?
That's right. Eunuch Sun said this, too, but
the Bureau of Imperial Attire doesn't believe him.
What a mess. Let's go take a look.
Your Highness, do you really intend to stay in the side hall for the long term?
The East Palace is too far, and His Majesty's health isn't stable.
Living here allows me to take care of His Majesty and puts me at ease.
[Imperial Examination]
Your Highness, you really intend to deliver Pei Xingjian's
Imperial Examination idea to His Majesty?
Of course.
Your Highness, His Majesty's health is not great.
He might be in a bad mood.
If you hand him this...
this "Determining government position through imperial examination" scroll,
it will be hard to guess how His Majesty will take it.
Please reconsider, Your Highness.
Pei Xingjian is just a scholar.
Yet he could see so far and think so brilliantly.
As Crown Prince, I have the idea to make the Tang Empire better.
How could I pretend to be mute and deaf for my own benefit?
Of course, I should deliver this to His Majesty at the earliest possible time.
Yes, but...
Are you worried about what Prince Cao said?
Yes.
The more he wants to stop this, the more I need to hurry.
Otherwise, the worries will pile up.
Liuli, you are so pretty.
It's because of your skillful hands. Growing up,
this is the first time someone did makeup and hair like this for me.
What are you laughing at?
I was thinking that liar from Simen College
probably has a head made from wood glue.
You are so beautiful, yet he treated you so poorly yesterday.
I get mad every time you mention that Pei Xingjian!
He really is a greedy bastard who swapped out contents, but he won't admit it!
Most despicable was how he turned it around and said I bit the hand that fed me!
That he helped me get the bag and then tried to accuse him of stealing.
How could he think of such an unthinkable tactic!
He's an evil liar!
Where are you going?
That was all the money I had.
It's stuff my grandpa and Xiao Shunzi toiled hard to collect for me.
I can't let some evil person take it!
Most importantly, my mom's stuff was in there, too.
I already lost mom's golden needle. I can't lose this, too!
I must get it back no matter what!
You are a citizen, he is an official. You have no power.
He has a sharp tongue and can fight well.
What can you do with him?
Besides, if he really wanted to return it to you,
would he swap it out from under you?
Then am I going to let this go?
To get justice, you must find a way that guarantees it.
Don't be in a hurry.
Your uncle said you can stay at Ruyi Resist Dye Shop as an artist.
Your pay and bonus will not be missed.
So you don't have to worry about money for now.
Once we find out a good plan,
we can find him and get your mother's stuff back.
How about it?
This is a pretty flower dress. Did you make it?
Liuli, your uncle's family are all nice.
They treat me as one of their own.
Not only did they let me stay in their ancestral home,
but also let me become the clerk of Ruyi Resist Dye Shop.
I have no way to repay them, but I want to use this flower dress
to get first place at this year's Hu Merchant Conference to help us gain recognition.
What is this Hu Merchant Conference?
The Hu Merchants hold a conference in Western Market every year.
A lot of people will come for it.
The one who wins will get the next year's orders from the Hu merchants.
They will also be known as the head of the field.
Why is their conference to determine bids hailed as the way to help Ruyi Resist Dye Shop gain recognition?
That is a long story.
Later when you meet your auntie,
you have to talk and act elegantly.
You need to find ways to make your auntie like you.
Understand?
Mother, as great as Auntie's family might be, it's only a concubine's position.
That Pei Yan was born from the first wife, so he is the eldest son.
Regarding him getting a concubine, can Auntie make the calls?
Have you guys looked too high on Auntie?
Pei Yan's biological mother is already dead.
Even though your auntie is his stepmother, she is still an elder to him.
Now that he is getting a concubine,
the elders recommend their own families' daughters.
He should at least pay a little respect, right?
They can't reject at once.
Once you enter the Commandant Manor and meet Pei Yan,
what happens next will depend on yourself. Understand?
Madam Cao, Fifth Madam Kudi is here. Master has asked you to hurry up.
Hurry up. Stop looking. Let's go.
Younger Sister, please have a seat.
You have called me to quickly come today.
What pressing matter is there?
- Hurry.
- Ever since you have married well, you have not come here in a long time.
I've missed you so much.
Fifth Madam is here!
Greetings, Auntie.
Shanhu is already so big.
This... You probably have a family-in-law, right?
Auntie is teasing me.
We asked you to come today to discuss Shanhu's marriage.
To tell you the truth,
getting a concubine isn't Pei Yan's idea.
But a suggestion from his first-wife, Cui Shi.
Cui Shi, after marrying into the Pei family for three years, has still never borne a child.
Though Pei Yan didn't utter even half a word of complaint,
but Cui Shi has a hard time confronting the rest of the Pei family.
So, she took the initiative in suggesting
to find a concubine for her husband.
This way, the Pei family's bloodline will go on.
I hear this Pei Yan was formidable at a young age,
and his appearance is first-tier as well.
He is already a First-Ranked Scholar in the Classics,
and he will soon climb up high.
Of course.
If she becomes the concubine and marries over,
she can go with him to his job. Then it's not too different from the official wife.
If her fate is good and she gives birth to a son,
then that would be the Pei family's first great-grandchild.
We cannot give up this type of good thing to others.
Fifth Madam, please help.
Have Shanhu marry into that family.
Not long after your mother was harmed,
Madam Cao's older brother opened next to Ruyi Resist Dye Shop
the Caoji Resist Dye Shop,
and brazenly used the name of "Number One Needle in the World" Attire Expert An to do business.
Madam Cao has been helping her older brother at Caoji.
She even publicly stated that your mother had completely passed on her dressmaking skills to her.
How can those customers who came because of the fame tell the difference?
Even many of Ruyi Resist Dye Shop's loyal customers have been scammed away.
Your uncle has often gotten so angry over this matter that he gets pain in his chest.
He says Cao Shi betrayed Madam An back in the day.
Yet now she has the nerve to pretend to be Madam An's successor and to use her name to make money?
So I swore to myself,
we must defeat Caoji at the Hu Merchants' Conference,
to vent for Attire Expert An and Ruyi Resist Dye Shop.
A'Ni, I take the place of my mother and thank your kind intentions.
Right, what about this?
You're the proper successor of Attire Expert An.
Then, as for this dress, help me finish it together. Okay?
If Shanhu can marry into Younger Sister's manor,
then it's good to have family on top of family relations.
My daughter understands to be grateful.
If this succeeds, she will definitely become Younger Sister's helping hand.
All right.
Since Shanhu is my own niece...
Thank you, Auntie.
Younger Sister, please have a seat.
Here, here!  Please.
Pei Yan is going to invite some talented scholars to his manor to
drink wine and write poetry.
I discussed this with Cui Shi.
We'll invite some well-suited daughters from good families to the manor in a Flower Pageant.
Under the excuse of the Flower Pageant,
let Pei Yan take a look and see. It's good if he likes you and selects you.
If it doesn't work out, nothing will be wrong.
Tomorrow? The timing is so tight.
Is there time to prepare?
How about this?
Tomorrow, I'll help Shanhu prepare a carriage.
Also, a high-quality peony flower for the Flower Pageant.
The only thing is...
Shanhu, your outfit and makeup needs
to take some effort.
Since she is my own niece,
she must not get looked down on by people.
Besides, Shanhu's uncle has shops upon shops selling shoes.
He wouldn't let Shanhu's dress lose, would he?
Mother.
Of course. Fifth Madam can rest assured.
Shanhu's dress will definitely be good tomorrow.
It definitely won't embarrass you.
Have you heard? A Talented Lady of the late emperor got a serious illness.
Abscesses grew on her body. She got stinky but no one took care of her.
She can only lie there and wait for death. It's so pitiable.
That's right. Not to mention it's the late emperor's Talented Lady,
Now that His Majesty is ill, even those ladies without children
are all feeling endangered.
I heard the Lady of Bright Deportment who Xiaolian serves has already lost sleep for three nights.
When her bedding was being sorted out in the morning, it was discovered that
even her pillowcase was wet.
You may all take your leave. I want to walk on my own.
Yes.
[Hopeful Cloud Pavilion]
Please take care.
Meiniang greets Your Highness, Crown Prince.
This baby bird fell down, just put it back into the nest then.
Talented Lady Wu doesn't need to be so sad.
Here, climb up the tree and put it back.
Your Highness may not know.
Once a baby bird is tainted with the human odor,
it will be abandoned by its parents.
Even if you put it back into the nest, it still won't work.
The love between parents and children exists among all living beings.
It's the same with flowers, birds, fish, and insects.
I don't believe the parents will be so cruel.
Climb up the tree. Go.
Yes.
Go.
How can you be so dumb?
Here, get up and give it to me.
Get up.
- Here.
- Your Highness, you...
What are you doing?
- Get up. Move aside.
- Your Highness.
Your Highness! Your Highness, what are you—
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Your Highness, take it easy. Be careful.
Your Highness. Your Highness, step over there.
Yes, yes, yes.
Your Highness, if you fall, I'll—
Your Highness! Your Highness, be careful!
Your Highness! Your Highness!
If something happens to you, what will I do?
[Proposal to reform Great Tang's imperial examination system]
Your Highness, be careful!
Be careful! Be careful!
You aren't hurt, are you?
- Are you all right, Your Highness?
- I'm fine.
Thank you, Talented Lady Wu.
Your hand is hurt.
It's fine.
Thank you, Talented Lady Wu.
I still have matters to attend to with His Majesty, so I'll take my leave.
Crown Prince.
While His Majesty is sick, his mood has naturally been unstable and irritable.
I hope Your Highness won't discuss too much about state affairs
and perform more acts in filial piety.
Thank you for your reminder, Talented Lady Wu.
[Ruyi Resist Dye Shop]
Come, everyone! Come!
Come take a look!
Come! Come take a look!
Great fabric! Come take a look!
[Caoji Resist Dye Shop]
[Number One Needle in the World]
[Only One Store in the World]
No problem.
You have nothing to do with my mother. So shameless!
Come take a look!
[Ruyi Resist Dye Shop]
Guests, please follow me.
Come take a look!
Be careful on your way back.
A'Ni greets Eighth Miss Pei and Miss Cui Yu.
Please come inside.
Yu’er!
This is the new artist in our shop, Yu’er.
Greetings, our esteemed guests.
These two esteems guests haven’t come over for a while.
Would you like to have a look around today, or are you looking for something in particular?
It is a little hard to explain today.
We are here to look for clothes for Sister-in-Law.
This dress is to be worn at the Flower Pagent tomorrow.
We need to finish it today.
I have never met the Pei family's madam.
I don't know anything about her looks,
height, or demeanor.
Is it possible to let the madam come into my small shop?
Or let me go and get the measurements from the madam herself?
I will just tell you directly then. My sister and brother-in-law have extremely good feelings for one another.
But she can't help but find a concubine for my brother-in-law.
The Flower Pageant tomorrow is specially being held for matchmaking.
At that time, all the young ladies who are there to have a look
will all be dressed very beautifully to capture the eye.
If my sister doesn’t dress up extravagantly,
then wouldn’t she seem like she is lonely and sad?
Miss Yu and I have asked Sister-in-Law to dress up, but she just doesn't want to.
She says something like "she doesn’t want to snatch away the light from others."
If she dressed too beautifully, then she is afraid that she will be laughed at by other people.
Laugh at that she doesn’t understand limits and doesn’t know how to be a good person.
That's why we want to get a new dress for Sister-in-Law tomorrow.
If the madam knew how much you cared for her, then she would definitely be very grateful.
I also want to help and make sure that good will happen.
But... this...
But we will only need for these two guests to wait a little.
Give me half a day to make the dress. It should be enough time.
- It will be just in time.
- Are you saying the truth?
What is hard in this?
I heard the two of you speak a lot, and the madam's own sister is here.
I have an idea of the measurements of the madam.
Is it possible for you two to explain a bit more in detail about the measurements of the madam?
Her height is similar to mine. Approximately, this tall.
She likes wearing blue and pink.
This one won't do!
Not this one, either!
This child!  Put it away.
This one isn't right, either!
Uncle!
Cao Wu!
Are there any more clothes? Bring them all down!
Let Auntie and Cousin take a look.
All right. I got it.
- Quickly tidy it up.
- Daughter, what about this one?
- Look at this one.
- Maybe this one will do.
Mother, Auntie's family is the commandant's family.
Their friends are all important people. So tomorrow,
it will mostly be daughters from renowned or noble families that go to the Pei Manor.
My background and family is already not high enough.
If I lose on how I dress, then there'll be no chance to win.
Coming! Coming!
I'm coming!
I'll help you. It's quite heavy.
I think that if Cousin doesn't like any of these clothes,
why don't we choose the fabric and make another one?
These clothes are for ordinary families.
How can they match up to the elegance at the Commandant Manor?
You-You-You... Hurry and pick it up!
-  What a brash temper.
- You—
Daughter.
[Caoji Resist Dye Shop]
What should I wear for the beauty pageant?
Shanhu, what do you think of this pleated skirt?
Combined with a pink-colored top, it should be very attractive.
Mother! Your taste—
Auntie, please have some tea.
Auntie, what about my affair?
What is your affair?
Aunt, you can't only think of Cousin's marital prospect
and forget about me.
Are you still thinking about A'Ni at the Ruyi Resist Dye Shop?
That won't succeed. Your father won't agree to it.
Aunt, my father always listens to you.
As long as you agree, it will definitely succeed.
- No way, no way.
- Just talk to Father, please.
- Hey, where are you going?
- I'm going out on the streets.
I'll take a look at how those girls from renowned families dress.
Auntie, please just talk to Father some more.
Awesome!
Miss, have a look.
Toys!
Awesome! Awesome!
Do it again!
Let's see it again!
Come on! That's awesome!
That's really good.
The new artist at Ruyi Resist Dye Shop is really good.
The dress she designed is rich but not trendy, elegant, and poised.
It'll be perfect for the Flower Pageant.
If that dress can be complimented so much by ladies from a renowned family,
then I can't go wrong by wearing it tomorrow.
[Ruyi Resist Dye Shop]
[Changshan's Spring Collection]
It's because this dress has a simple and clean style
that I can be sure of completing it today.
When the style is simple, then it needs to compete on colors and fabric texture.
I think this fabric will be perfect.
This silk fabric is good, but it's widely seen. Could it be too ordinary?
Of course, using one layer is ordinary.
But if you try three layers, or even five, it won't be so ordinary anymore.
When she walks, it will be like a wave of moving clouds, with every step looking lively.
Really? How come I've never thought of this?
Miss Kudi!
Why did you come to our Ruyi Resist Dye Shop?
It's you?
You are the one who was asking my father for directions the other day.
I am the artist at this shop.
So you are the new artist at Ruyi Resist Dye Shop.
I heard that you are pretty skilled.
Why don't you come to our Caoji shop.
My mother and I will treat you well.
Just with your mother and you,
how dare you put up a sign of "Number One Needle in the World, No other Store in the World"
to cheat people.
Even if I have no place to go, I would never go make a living at your mother's place.
Besides, the shopkeeper of Ruyi Resist Dye Shop treats me exceptionally well.
I was being nice.
You... don't need to be so rude.
You really don't know what's good for you.
This is not the time to count old scores. You should be patient and wait.
A'Yu, there isn't much time left. You should go inside to make the dress.
Miss Kudi, since you came to Ruyi Resist Dye Shop today, what do you want?
My older cousin really likes you.
He keeps clamoring to marry you.
That's why I came here today to inquire about your intention on behalf of my older cousin.
Oh?
I have no romantic feeling for Young Master Cao.
Please go back and tell him not to bother me anymore.
This is for the best.
My mother and uncle are very dissatisfied with you.
Everyone, do you still have any reports to submit?
Your Majesty, this son, and subordinate have an urgent matter to report.
Your Majesty, this son and subordinate recommend reforming Great Tang's imperial exam system.
Great Tang's imperial exam system inherited that of the previous dynasty.
It has groomed a batch of scholars who memorized old books and have no creativity. They cannot be entrusted with major responsibilities.
The Imperial Academy and Chongwen Hall, as the nation's institutions to develop pillars of the nation,
have mostly accepted students from aristocratic and noble families.
After a long time, they unavoidably form private cliques and factions for personal gains, resulting in corruption.
Your Highness the Crown Prince, excuse me for this old minister for speaking straightforward.
The imperial exam system is the foundation of the nation, providing an important method to select talents for the nation.
Furthermore, His Majesty is not feeling well now,
and he needs to rest quietly. I hope Your Highness won't get impatient.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
♫  Watching the flowers bloom and fall in the courtyard  ♫
♫  How many loves, regrets, entanglements, separations,
reunions must we go through together  ♫
♫  Uncover the vicious cycle of the past  ♫
♫  Fate has its uncertainties  ♫
♫  I've spent this life with brush and ink in hand  ♫
♫  Writing about what love is  ♫
♫  Borrow from the relentless of the night  ♫
♫  To exchange for the certainty of a promise  ♫
♫  There are too many bumpy roads along the way  ♫
♫  The more twists, the deeper it is  ♫
♫  Breaking up and making up is like an illusion  ♫
♫  Resembles a traveler traveling through this life  ♫
♫  Time ignores everything including obsession  ♫
♫  With the candlelight flickering indefinitely  ♫
♫  After the fire, there was only one thing left  ♫
♫  A bright moon that makes one's heart tingle  ♫