Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
[Weaving a Tale of Love]
[Episode 19]
Please rest assured, Talented Lady Wu.
I went to the Bureau of Imperial Attire a few days ago and made a big ruckus.
I told them Crown Prince's injury had worsened, so I asked them to make more clothes.
This is great.
Unless...
This is Bao'er?
This is the Bao'er you rescued the other day.
Bao'er is such a pretty bird.
It's often lonely in the palace.
Good thing Bao'er brought a lot of happiness.
I was thinking you were bored and angry every day at the palace,
so I brought Bao'er to ease some boredom.
Your Highness, the Bureau of Imperial Attire has just brought this here.
Let me have a look.
[Dou]
Xiao Douzi is caring.
How about... we ask Xiao Douzi to the East Palace to work?
I have been thinking that Xiao Douzi working at Courtyard of Misfortune is a shame.
I didn't think he would go to Bureau of Imperial Attire.
He has great needlework, too.
What do you think, Talented Lady Wu?
Xiao Douzi is smart, attentive, and kind.
He takes responsibility for his actions.
I also like him.
But... working at the Bureau of Imperial Attire is not a bad thing.
This way, you can have another person in the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
You also won't stop his skills.
It is just that it is too boring here.
If Xiao Douzi could come, he could make me happy.
I wouldn't need to look at A'Sheng's bitter face all day.
Please endure for a few more days.
Only when Prince Cao and Consort Yang think
that you have not gotten well, will we then have peace.
And they wouldn't do more tricks in tomorrow's competition.
As long as Pei Xingjian can beat Pu Banu and become Your Highness' personal guard,
then, in the future, your safety will be guaranteed.
You are right, Pei Xingjian is good at martial arts and is scholarly.
As long as he is by Crown Prince's side, we can feel safe.
If Prince of Cao's scheme succeeds and Pu Banu is placed next to Your Highness,
then wouldn't that be placing an assassin?
- What if...?
- A'Sheng. A'Sheng. A'Sheng!
Can you learn from Xiao Douzi?
Say less unlucky things.
He is also considerate of you.
Being more careful of everything is not a bad idea.
Tomorrow will be the Martial Arts competition.
I am thinking why don't you ask Pei Xingjian to come to the East Palace sooner.
This way you can look after one another and we can prevent outsiders.
You are right.
Then I will go meet up with him now.
Is there any news from the East Palace?
Crown Prince has been resting these days in his chamber.
Everyone in East Palace is staying quiet about the crown prince's condition.
There is actually a lot of movement in the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
Every other day or so, Attire Chief Lin will dispatch Cai Yue to pick up new fabrics,
saying that the daily change of clothes for the crown prince...
There is more and more each day.
It looks like the wound is bad.
This is a good thing.
Why are you uneasy instead?
Tomorrow is the martial arts competition.
If the crown prince is really deeply wounded,
he should have asked His Majesty to withdraw from the competition.
Right.
Crown Prince looks highly upon Pei Xingjian.
He even personally pleaded with His Majesty
to make an exception to the rule in order to keep Pei by his side.
It looks like he is not an ordinary person.
Martial arts are important. There cannot be any mistakes.
I have to go to the East Palace myself.
Greetings, Prince Cao.
I came specifically to visit Crown Prince.
This is...
I am Pei Xingjian. Greetings, Prince Cao.
Prince Cao is here to visit Crown Prince!
Greetings, Brother.
You have been injured for so many days, why are you still not well?
Reply to Prince Cao. It is not sure if it is because the Crown Prince's body is weak.
These days the wound doesn't get better.
Instead, it has gotten worse.
I know your body is weak.
That's why I've brought some high-quality deer antler and mountain ginseng
for you to nourish your body.
Thank you, Fourteenth Brother.
I am afraid about your health.
So I specifically asked people to invite Imperial Doctor Zhong from the Imperial Academy of Medicine.
Greetings, Crown Prince.
These couple of days are hot and dry. It is really easy to infect the wound.
Please let me check your wound. Afterward, I will prescribe you some good medicine.
No need.
Every time they change the medicine, it's like peeling the skin and cutting the muscle.
The pain is unbearable.
I have just changed the medicine. No need to check.
You are unwell.
How about we tell His Majesty to reschedule the competition?
The date was chosen by His Majesty.
I don't want to ruin his happiness.
Tomorrow, it is. Don't change it.
I have been bored these days resting.
I can go out for a walk tomorrow.
Pei Xingjian.
Yes.
I have praised you in front of His Majesty.
Tomorrow, you have to show some real skills.
Don't cause me to lose face.
I will try my best.
Pu Banu.
Yes.
I forgot to tell you earlier, this is the bodyguard I want to give you,
Pu Banu, the warrior I've recommended.
I have chosen him with much difficulty.
Pei XIngjian, if you want to become Crown Prince's bodyguard,
tomorrow, you have to go through him first.
Please.
Your body is unwell, so I will not bother you any longer.
A'She,
help me see off Fourteenth Brother.
Yes.
Seeing off Prince Cao.
- Pu Banu.
- Yes.
You were really great earlier.
I saw that you gave way to him, saving strength for tomorrow's competition.
It is great to let them be happy tonight.
Tomorrow, it will be great to finish him.
Your Highness is smart. I couldn't tell.
I almost thought that Pei Xingjian was capable of winning over Warrior Pu.
Pu Banu was only trying him out.
Where did he show off his strength?
My apologies, Your Highness.
I also showed my strength earlier.
Pei Xingjian's strength is above mine.
For tomorrow's fight, I cannot guarantee I will win completely,
but I will try my best for you.
Pu Banu,
I don't care what strategies you use tomorrow.
You have to beat Pei Xingjian!
Or else,
I cannot keep useless people by my side.
Yes.
[Bureau of Imperial Attire]
Qiniang! Qiniang! Qiniang!
Qiniang!
My stomach hurts terribly. Please help me ask Attire Expert Zhou
to give leave time. I really cannot endure it anymore.
Qiniang!
Last night, I caught a cold and I cannot endure my headache.
Also, help me request a leave.
Me, too!
You guys have all said the excuses,
then what should I say?
My throat hurts.
Your throat hurts and you're still speaking so loudly?
Don't think that I don't know what you are up to.
You are all taking leave to see
what... Pei... and what... Nu... competition?
Attire Expert Zhuo, it is not Nu.
It is Pei Xingjian and Pu Banu.
The person who wins will be Crown Prince's bodyguard.
I heard that His Majesty is encouraging soldiers, guards, and maids to watch.
So... we Bureau of Imperial Attire...
His Majesty is asking soldiers and guards to compete
to encourage them to be better.
And we Bureau of Imperial Attire...
The loyalty we have to His Majesty
is making great clothing!
You have all asked to take leave to watch.
Isn't it to be lazy?!
Feast of all Souls Festival is coming up soon.
The workload at the Bureau of Imperial Attire is a lot,
and you still have the thought to go play?
Today, who dares to leave this room,
I will punish them heavily!
Work hard!
Whenever there is a little bustle,
don't act like there's grass growing in your hearts.
(Get stirred up and can't concentrate)
I heard the personal maids at the East Palace say
that Pei Xingjian is really handsome.
If we are able to have him look at us once,
then our heart can jump out.
So all the palace maids are hoping that he wins.
This way, they can see him often.
Really? Is he really that handsome?
I want to see him.
Shouyue, Prince Cao must have come prepared.
You have to be careful in everything.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
This time's competition is within our palace.
I don't think Prince Cao can do anything.
Besides, I am confident in my martial arts.
I won't let Prince Cao's evil plan succeed, for sure,
for him to place his spy by your side.
If it was an open competition,
I am completely confident in your martial arts.
But I am afraid the enemy has some evil skills and we cannot prevent it.
Shouyue,
you and I are monarchs and friends.
I don't wish for you to get hurt.
Thank you for your care.
I will, for sure, fulfill our agreement
to help you win the competition.
- Pu Banu.
- Yes.
This competition is really important,
especially since His Majesty has set the location at the East Palace.
This is why you can only win and cannot lose.
Do you understand?
I will try my best.
Not "try my best,"
but you have to win.
Your Highness, this pill can instantly increase my strength,
but its after-effects are really bad.
Before, I have also had a few.
If I eat it, I'm afraid...
Your Highness, how about I talk to Pei Xingjian first?
If it is not successful, it is not too late to use it at the crucial moment.
Important moment?
It is the crucial moment now!
When you realize you cannot beat him, it'll be too late.
The chance to place a bodyguard at Crown Prince's side is so precious!
If we miss it, there won't be another one!
So, today, I won't allow you to have any mistakes.
Your Highness, I will follow your orders.
Hong An,
this is prepared for your hammer.
Make sure you get good rest.
Yes.
I want to go, too.
Why not let us go?
I want to go see, too.
That's right. I've been thinking of going.
Yes.
Qiniang,
the color to make the clothing is not right.
- I will choose some colored threads at the warehouse.
- Sure.
I will help Xiao Douzi.
Sit down, Shuang'er, keep doing your work.
Today, you all have to finish the work Attire Expert Zhuo gave you,
or else be careful of being punished.
Xiao Douzi, hurry up and go, and quickly return.
Yes. I will come and go quickly. I won't waste any time.
[Bright Moon Concentrated Light]
Look! Look!
Who do you think will win?
I don't know. They are all incredible.
It's not for sure.
I have prepared today's competition
to choose a bodyguard for Crown Prince.
So I have set the competition to be at the East Palace.
Through this competition, I want to appoint several guards.
Pei Xingjian. Pu Banu.
You are the warriors within the warriors of my country.
Today, show some real skills. Don't disappoint me.
- Yes!
I want to see how this goes.
Your Majesty's Literature ability can govern the nation and military ability can help us.
How literary skill and martial skills are both strange.
To be able to have Your Majesty's judgment and oversee this competition
is Pei Xingjian and Pu Banu's luck.
And is also everyone else who can watch this competition's luck.
Please start the competition, Your Majesty.
I cannot wait already.
Your Majesty is strong in both literary and martial skills.
There has been no king as great,
but what I admire even more is Your Majesty having a good eye to know using the right people
and observing the situation to decide what to do.
Please start the competition for Pei and Pu.
Great.
I will order Pei Xingjian and Pu Banu
to choose whichever weapon they like. Whoever wins,
I will appoint him as Imperial Guard Leader.
Thank you for Your Majesty's love!
- So handsome.
Qiniang,
why has Xiao Douzi been gone to the warehouse for so long?
Exactly. He has already been gone for 2 hours.
I think he for sure went to see the entertainment.
You are still protecting him.
You can only dare to tell us to work here stupidly.
Shuang'er, which eye of yours saw me protecting him?
Attire Expert Zhuo has assigned work for all of you.
Just take care of your own stuff.
If Xiao Douzi doesn't finish or doesn't do it well,
he will of course face punishment. Attire Expert Zhuo is a person of her word.
It's not your place to talk.
Great!
[Enbroidered Splender Blooming Flowers]
I have already established rules this morning.
Whoever breaks them,
then I will for sure punish them; no exceptions!
Work hard, don't chatter.
Qiniang, how long has Xiao Douzi been out?
For-For almost 2 hours, Master.
[Upstanding Virtues Gate]
Such an amazing move!
[Bright Moon Concentrated Light]
So awesome!
What poison did you just use?
You can't exert force anymore, right? Your sight is fuzzy.
I will tell you frankly, not only have I given you poison,
I've also taken a drug. I'm stronger and you are weaker.
I encourage you to quickly admit defeat,
so you don't lose your life.
[Bright Moon Concentrated Light]
[Left Spring Workshop]
What happened to Pei Xingjian? Why is he suddenly not right?
Why does he look really tired?
If I lose, Crown Prince's safety,
will be in danger by Prince Cao.
I need to calm down.
I need to have peace of mind.
I must remain clear-headed.
What is he doing?
What move is this?
This is too dangerous.
Pu Ba Nuo, you did it first,
so don't blame me for being ruthless.
If you don't want, then I will kill Prince Cao.
If I die, I have to find someone to be with me.
Protect His Majesty!
Pei Xingjian!
I concede. Don't hurt Prince of Cao.
Pei Xingjian, you dare to assassinate?
Guards!
Ming'er.
I, Pei Zingjian, ask Your Majesty to punish me.
Your Majesty, please allow Pei Xingjian to explain himself.
I don't think he really meant to hurt Fourteenth Brother.
I know Pei Xingjian's skills.
If he didn't stop, Fourteenth Brother would have been killed.
Crown Prince, Pei Xingjian is someone you recommended.
Is it because he has you as a backer
that he would have such guts?
He dares to rebel in front of His Majesty.
He intends to harm the Prince of Cao. He almost took his life!
Crown Prince would actually dare quibble for him, make guarantees for him.
This Pei Jingxian rebelled.
Crown Prince, are you rebelling, too?
I am willing to guarantee Pei Xingjian.
He is loyal and would never be insubordinate.
I ask Your Majesty to give him a chance to explain himself.
Okay.
Since Crown Prince pleads with me to give Pei Xingjian a chance to explain,
I also want to hear what Pei Xingjian will say.
Even if you don't have any intention to harm the Prince of Cao,
kidnapping a royal prince is also a high crime punishable by eliminating nine related clans.
I really would like to see how you will come up with a brilliant explanation.
May I report, Your Majesty, that when I decided to kidnap Prince of Cao just now,
I already disregarded my life.
I dueled with Pu Banu today to fight for the position of Crown Prince's personal guard.
As Crown Prince's personal guard,
the primary mission is to rescue the crown prince from peril.
Even if I fight to the last drop of my blood, I would safeguard the crown prince.
While sparring just then,
my old illness suddenly recurred and I couldn't continue to fight.
I could only quickly end the sparring.
If I was fighting for real, under my weakened condition,
the first thing to do was to protect Crown Prince.
Therefore, the best thing I could think of
was to capture the opponent's leader first.
Your Majesty, please don't listen to Pei Xingjian's chicanery.
In front of everyone, he almost harmed Ming'er.
He must not be tolerated and must be harshly punished.
Meiniang, what do you think?
Your Majesty, I'm just an ignorant woman in the palace. I dare not randomly talk.
I only know that Your Majesty is intelligent and wise. You've acquired talented people without being restrained by rules.
Our dynasty is full of talented people.
Your Majesty is kind and generous. Even women and children know about how you use competent people.
Your Majesty not only has gathered 24 famous officials in Lin Yan Pavilion, (Lin Yan Pavilion is like a Hall of Fame)
you also highly relied on the Wei Zheng and others who were knowledgeable, (People who worked for the emperor's older brother)
and it became an exemplary story for the millennium.
Talented Lady Wu, you said you were ignorant and didn't dare to talk randomly,
but you kept talking so much nonsense.
Pei Xingjian was arrogant and dared to offend royals.
How can you compare him to the 24 famous meritorious officials of Lin Yan Pavilion?
Older Sister is right to teach me.
I was only admiring His Majesty's kindness and tolerance that I temporarily got impudent.
All right.
I will make my own judgment.
What do you think, Crown Prince?
Since childhood, I've been learning from what I saw and heard by Your Majesty's side.
Even though I can't reach even one-thousandth of Your Majesty,
but I also understand the principle of trusting the people you use, and not using the people you doubt.
I highly regard Pei Xingjian's martial skills.
I also believe in his character and ethos, and furthermore, I admire his courage.
Pei Xingjian, even though your behavior was somewhat rude,
but you were sincerely thinking for Crown Prince's sake.
You didn't disappoint Crown Prince's trust in and support of you.
You are smart, courageous, and didn't panic when facing danger.
I quite admire you, too.
I judge that you won the duel.
You will stay by Crown Prince's side and protect him.
Thank you, Your Majesty, for your kindness. I will wholeheartedly protect Crown Prince.
Your Majesty!
Pu Banu, you are outstanding in martial skills.
You impressed me and all the imperial guards. You will continue to stay by Prince of Cao's side
- to protect the Prince of Cao.
- Yes.
- A'Quan.
- Present.
Bring the swords that were recently offered by Dragon Spring.
Each will be bestowed to Pei Xingjian and Pu Banu.
Yes.
Thank you, Your Majesty, for your bestowment.
Pei Xingjian! Pei Xingjian!
- A'Sheng, summon the imperial physician!
- Yes.
- Pei Xingjian.
Pei Xingjian!
Is His Majesty old and muddled?
We saw Pei Xingjian pointing his sword to kidnap,
just relying on a few cunning words of evasive retorts,
and the crown prince and Wu Meiniang
were talking nonsense to help him.
He got off so easily!
Mother, you should have realized Wu Meiniang's fierceness today.
She dared to retort what you said in front of everyone.
His Majesty even listened to her and totally disregarded any respect toward Mother.
If Talented Lady Wu becomes Crown Prince's insider in the palace,
then if the crown prince wants to kill me,
all that's missing is an opportunity.
From today on,
I will never stand by and compromise,
I will fight, for my sake
and also for Ming'er.
With me around,
no one will dare touch my son, Ming'er, even a little bit.
[Upstanding Virtues Gate]
How is it? I saw Sir Pei's condition
and knew to summon the imperial physician to help.
It's just that–
It's just that Prince of Cao's eyes and ears are in the Imperial Academy of Medicine.
It could be harmful to Young Master Pei.
This is also what I am worried about.
Earlier, Pei Xingjian was busy trying to win.
Something must have happened to him that we don't know of.
Anyone could see that his arm suddenly didn't listen to his actions.
It was as if it had been poisoned.
The East Palace is really protected.
The enemy can give poison in such a short amount of time.
How can I easily trust the Imperial Academy of Medicine?
It's all my fault. I never thought of
building my own power inside the palace.
Your Highness, you are kind and just, and you don't need to blame yourself.
Talented Lady Wu.
Your Highness, earlier at the competition,
I realized that Pei Xingjian's arm was not right.
So I dispatched people to go outside the palace to invite Physician Lu
as preparation just in case.
Now that Physician Lu has arrived, he can diagnosis Pei Xingjian.
Thank you, Talented Lady Wu. You got Physician Lu here
just in time to solve my urgent problem.
Young Master Pei is unconscious because he lost too much blood.
His arm suddenly lost strength because of poisoning.
Fortunately, the poison's effect has a time limit.
It will disappear automatically in a cup of tea's time. It's not a big problem. (about 15 minutes)
I will sanitize the wound and stop the bleeding now.
I will also prescribe a few orders of herbal medicine
for him to take. He only needs to rest quietly.
Thank you for your trouble, Physician Lu.
Xiao Douzi,
Qiniang said you went to the supply room to pick up threads.
What threads?
It took you four hours.
Where are the threads?
I was too eager to have fun. When I heard there was a martial competition in the palace,
I couldn't stand it, so I went there to watch the lively scene.
You are quite honest with your reply.
What did I say this morning?
The Bureau of Imperial Attire is not the Courtyard of Misfortune, and it does not tolerate your slacking off.
How dare you treat my words as the wind that blew by your ears.
I did wrong. Please punish me, Attire Expert Zhuo.
Punish? Of course, I will punish you!
I will even punish you very harshly.
I can't let you show a bad example and ruin the rules in the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
You sneaked away for four hours. So I'll punish you
to kneel four hours, and no dinner.
After you've kneeled, you must finish all the work that I assigned you today.
If you can't finish,
I'll double the punishment tomorrow.
Xiao Douzi is wrong. Xiao Douzi accepts the punishment.
Those that come from the Courtyard of Misfortune just don't follow rules.
As I see it, the punishment is too light.
A'Bi is right.
Let's see if he will still be snobbish in the future.
[Proclaim Brightness Gate]
Thank you for today at the competition's ground
with everything that you did for me, Talented Lady Wu,
as well, your finding the physician for Pei Xingjian.
I, Li Zhi, will deeply keep it to heart.
Crown Prince, you are too serious.
I have helped support you, Crown Prince, because of your kindness.
In the future, you will definitely make great achievements
and keep Great Tang in comfort and safety,
as well as a calm harem in the palace.
Talented Lady Wu, your intelligence has impressed me more and more.
Every time you have extended a helping hand today has helped us avoid peril,
it was also done with the right timing and appropriateness.
This takes great wisdom.
My mother, the empress, passed away too early. As Crown Prince,
I actually have many constraints in the palace.
I've never had anyone like Talented Lady Wu
who would generously advise me from the side without personal greed.
Crown Prince, you have great aspirations, and you are also at a vibrant, prime age.
Every time I see Your Highness,
I am reminded of myself when I first entered the palace.
It's too bad
that I won't be staying much longer in the palace.
I can't avoid eventually going to the Ganye Temple
to accompany Buddha for the rest of my lonely life.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
♫  Watching the flowers bloom and fall in the courtyard  ♫
♫  How many loves, regrets, entanglements, separations,
reunions must we go through together  ♫
♫  Uncover the vicious cycle of the past  ♫
♫  Fate has its uncertainties  ♫
♫  I've spent this life with brush and ink in hand  ♫
♫  Writing about what love is  ♫
♫  Borrow from the relentless of the night  ♫
♫  To exchange for the certainty of a promise  ♫
♫  There are too many bumpy roads along the way  ♫
♫  The more twists, the deeper it is  ♫
♫  Breaking up and making up is like an illusion  ♫
♫  Resembles a traveler traveling through this life  ♫
♫  Time ignores everything including obsession  ♫
♫  With the candlelight flickering indefinitely  ♫
♫  After the fire, there was only one thing left  ♫
♫  A bright moon that makes one's heart tingle  ♫