Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
[Weaving a Tale of Love]
[Episode 23]
[Hall of Sunset Pool]
Talented Lady Wu, your servant was wrong.
Please punish me severely, Talented Lady.
You can punish me however you wish, but just don't kick me out.
Talented Lady Wu, your servant knows wrong.
I should never have betrayed you.
Please, Talented Lady, spare this servant's life.
Song Tao, Talented Lady has treated us well.
How could you have betrayed your mistress?
Talented Lady, I was caught by Consort Yang when I did something wrong.
I was threatened and was forced to work for her.
Even so, if you were loyal,
you should have come to me to deal with the problem, instead of choosing to betray me.
What Talented Lady said is right.
We've stayed by Talented Lady for over ten years and have been her most trusted.
How could you work for Consort Yang and betray Talented Lady?
If Talented Lady weren't smart and noticed the clues,
she would have been trapped by Consort Yang this time because of you.
Sister, you're right to scold me. I was muddled and lost my conscience.
But I don't understand something.
I've been loyal to Talented Lady for over ten years.
How did Talented Lady discover my betrayal?
I originally didn't suspect you.
But lately, you've been paying extra attention to the gown for the Feasts for All Souls Festival and kept asking about it.
I thought it was strange.
Since you want to know, I will tell you.
I think this peony flower's design is the best.
Peony is the king of flowers and its bloom symbolizes fortune.
If Talented Lady chooses this one,
I think we can use the most precious golden silk thread to embroider the peony flower's petals,
and inlay Tian Mountain Jade as leaves
in order to highlight its graceful luxuriance.
I didn't expect that you couldn't wait to go to Consort Yang to report.
If Yu Liu hadn't followed you and seen you enter the Hall of Brilliant Joy, I wouldn't have believed it.
I was muddled.
I beg that Talented Lady will consider my service of over ten years.
Spare this servant one time.
I swear that I will be wholeheartedly loyal to Talented Lady from now on.
If I am disloyal again, I will be struck down by heavenly lightening.
Swearing an oath is the most useless thing in the world.
Since you chose to betray me,
then the Hall of Sunset Pool can't keep you.
Considering that you followed me for all these years, I won't be harsh to you.
It's just that our relationship as master and servant is now terminated.
Yu Liu, go to the Directorate of Eunuchs and find Pan Qinhai.
Just say that Song Tao made a mistake in the hall.
Let Pan Qinhai transfer her to somewhere else.
Yes.
Talented Lady wants to kick me out of the Hall of Sunset Pool.
It's the same as killing me.
Consort Yang will believe that I colluded with you to lure her into a trap
and suffered such punishment.
Consort Yang won't let me go easily.
Once I leave the Hall of Sunset Pool, without your protection,
I will only have death as my destination.
Whether Consort Yang will believe you, how you will explain it to her,
and whether you can stay alive, it's all up to your own abilities.
I am not going to keep anyone who is disloyal next to me.
Leave.
Talented Lady. Talented Lady!
Go then.
Yu Liu. Yu Liu, I beg you. Please help me plead to Talented Lady.
Considering the master-servant relationship,
save me! Give me a chance to live.
If you had known about today, why did you do what you did?
Talented Lady didn't beat you to death and is willing to let you go.
It's already very compassionate of Talented Lady.
After you leave the Hall of Sunset Pool, I wish you luck.
Yu Liu. Yu Liu!
Consort Yang, I've asked around.
The crown prince really favors Xiao Douzi all the time.
He frequently gives him rewards and has even summoned him to drink at the East Palace.
This Xiao Douzi originally came from the Courtyard of Misfortune.
His background is lowly. Soon after he arrived at the Bureau of Imperial Attire,
he already became popular with Crown Prince and Talented Lady Wu.
I heard that he can speak up to the crown prince even more than Wang Fusheng.
When I first saw Xiao Douzi at the Bureau of Imperial Attire,
I immediately thought that he looked fair-skinned, pretty, and full of schemes.
He is indeed a calculating person.
Who knows what magic potion he's given the crown prince?
Is there any talk in the palace that the crown prince is into males?
I've never heard that.
Talk comes from people telling each other.
I understand what to do then.
Master is still wounded and wanted this disciple to
embroider for Lady Wei in your stead. I dared not slack off
and spent two days to draw this West Market Scene.
Lady Wei...
Lady Wei likes the folk scene.
It will be most appropriate to use this scene to make a table screen.
This drawing is quite good.
What embroidery technique do you plan to use?
A table screen is a small scene that has enough details to see the big picture.
Therefore, it's most suitable to use the Wuxi's fine embroidery technique.
It's just that my skill is limited.
Please teach me how to sew in the fine embroidery technique.
Fine embroidery isn't only about your skill,
it's also about your talent. You can't learn it quickly.
When you try to cram at the last moment,
it'll just be useless. You'll waste your effort for nothing.
You may as well change to another scene when you can.
It'll be more practical.
She is back.
Yes.
I told you. She definitely wouldn't teach it.
Really? She really won't?
She looks pitiful.
What pitiful? She is not talented. Why teach her?
That's right.
Look at her.
Yan'er, come here.
I already said so. Attire Expert Zhuo would not teach her.
It's hard for Sister Qiniang.
You've actually condensed all the views in the West Market into a small scene.
Indeed, only the technique of fine embroidery can make it work.
There is an old proverb, "Teach the disciple, the master will starve."
Attire Expert Zhuo is willing to accept Qiniang as a disciple.
It is, first of all, because of pressure from Attire Chief Lin
to have people inherit the dressmaking skills.
Secondly, it's because Qiniang is a nice person and knows how to serve.
Yes, that's true.
Have you all heard of talk about Xiao Douzi?
- Yes, I've heard.
- How dare you talk about filthy rumors?
It involves the crown prince. Aren't you afraid of losing your heads?
Sister Qiniang.
Master won't teach me. I can't help it, either.
So people are laughing at me.
You respect her as Master, that's why you serve her well.
How can people laugh at you?
It's Attire Expert Zhuo who is narrow-minded.
She is afraid of disciples that will surpass her.
If anyone is laughing, they should laugh at her!
We can't totally blame Master as narrow-minded.
Probably I'm just lacking natural talents,
so Master won't teach me.
Don't cry anymore.
This is for you.
I previously promised to give you a gift.
I've been too busy at the Bureau of Imperial Attire for the Feasts for All Souls Festival, so I just finished it.
Thank you.
You didn't have to hurry so. I know that it's been busy at the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
Don't get so tired and hurt your eyes.
That's right. I rushed to complete it despite being busy.
You must praise me.
Sure, I praise you.
But you shouldn't make sleeping garments for other people anymore.
Why?
Because men and women are different.
Besides, men and women should stay apart.
The sleeping garment is something that touches the body.
Then I'm not giving this to you.
You just said that men and women are different. Men and women cannot touch. You are a man, so, of course, I can't give it to you.
- I am not a man...
- You are not a man?
I am a man, but...
You are not a man? Is my eyesight bad?
Fine.
Should I prove it then?
Let's prove whether I'm really a man.
No... No need.
If the target is you,
I'm quite happy to do it.
I'm wrong then. You are not a man.
You are a saint, a gentleman.
It seems that if I don't teach you a lesson,
you won't learn.
I'll let you know
how frightening men are.
I-I know I am wrong.
This is for you!
[Proclaiming Brightness Gate]
Why not hurry and greet Eunuch Wang yet?
Xiao Linzi greets Eunuch Wang.
- This one is...
- This is my foster son.
Since childhood, he has had white teeth and red lips.
He looks even more adorable than a little girl.
Just look at how cute he is.
Crown Prince will definitely like him.
I heard that the crown prince happens to
need a little eunuch in his study.
What about him...
Eunuch Jiang, this is not choosing a concubine for the crown prince.
What's the use of having a cute face?
We servants must have good character,
a quick mind, and diligence.
Besides, the Directorate of Eunuchs has already picked someone.
Eunuch Jiang, please go back.
- I...
- Please go back.
What's going on?
[Reserved Peace and Calm]
Yu Liu, wait outside.
- I need to discuss an urgent matter with the crown prince.
- Yes.
- Shulan, you can leave, too.
- Your Highness, I—
- You don't need to leave.
Yes.
I wonder what's so urgent with Talented Lady Wu?
Lately, there have been many rumors about Your Highness.
They are extremely ludicrous.
I originally just wanted to ignore them.
But these rumors have become more and more fierce.
That's why I disregarded being abrupt and came over to remind you.
Rumors about me?
Lately, there are many talks in the palace
that Your Highness is interested in males. The rumors are detailed,
and even say Your Highness protects that person
and often summons him to the East Palace to meet secretly.
I thought about it and realized it's probably hinting at Your Highness and Xiao Douzi.
This kind of baseless rumor should be ignored.
How can Your Highness laugh about it?
People's talk can melt gold. One should fear rumors.
Your Highness should be cautious and not be careless.
Talented Lady Wu is right.
Your Highness, the crown prince, please be cautious.
I've been wondering why there have been many young and cute eunuchs
volunteering themselves to work at the East Palace.
It must be because of the rumors. If I had known they came for this,
I would have slapped them for believing in this ridiculous rumor.
An upright person does not fear a slanted shadow.
If I am in a hurry to refute the rumors, then it would seem like there is something real to it.
A'Sheng, tell the Directorate of Eunuchs.
After the opening is filled in the study, we won't need any more help in the East Palace
to avoid people getting bad ideas.
Yes.
Even though some rumors will be reduced this way,
but the one Your Highness the Crown Prince should avoid to prevent suspicion is... Xiao Douzi.
I like Xiao Douzi because he is capable and very loyal.
If I keep him away because of these ridiculous rumors,
won't it disappoint people who are loyal to me?
Your Highness is the heir to the throne and you will do great things.
If you are hurt by these baseless rumors,
isn't it a waste?
If one wishes to make a false charge, there is no shortage of excuses.
If I try to deliberately avoid suspicions, they will probably say I'm hiding.
Besides, I happen to want to discuss something with Xiao Douzi these days.
I won't let the rumors stop me from what I need to do.
- But Your Highness—
- Talented Lady Wu, no need to keep dissuading me.
I know what to do.
What is this?
Your Majesty, this is ginseng soup that was personally brewed by Consort Yang.
Didn't I already say? I don't need her to get up every morning to brew the ginseng soup for me.
Your Majesty, I told her
but I couldn't convince her.
Your Majesty, Consort Yang also sends people here every day
to ask if Your Majesty is eating well and sleeping soundly.
Mother seems to be in better spirits and will come out for a relaxing stroll.
I'm very pleased.
I've been getting up early every morning
to brew herbal supplement soup for your imperial father for a month.
Your imperial father has finally allayed his anger.
The Feast for All Souls Festival's incident has finally subsided.
The talk that the crown prince is into males has already spread to your imperial father.
What does Imperial Father say? Is he angry?
Your imperial father came to the Hall of Briliant Joy yesterday,
looking very worried and absent-minded.
He even asked me by beating around the bush
whether I had heard of any rumors that were negative against the crown prince.
I just pretended that I didn't understand and even praised the crown prince some.
Ming'er, you must remember this.
Don't let any of the rumors regarding the crown prince
spread from our place to your imperial father
to prevent him from suspecting our intentions.
But rumors won't be enough to topple the crown prince.
If we want to substantiate the rumors, we must let Imperial Father see the crown prince in an embarrassing state.
At that time, let's see if he can still protect his seat as the crown prince?
Shouyue? Why are you still here?
You should go back to rest. I'm not going out today.
Yes.
A'Sheng, summon Xiao Douzi here.
Your Highness, you have been summoning Xiao Douzi a little too frequently in recent times.
I'm afraid there'll be more rumors and Your Highness will be hurt.
A'Sheng, can you do what Xiao Douzi does?
- I... I can't do it.
- Since you can't do it, why keep nagging?
If you could do it, then I wouldn't have asked him.
Hurry and go.
Yes.
[Esteemed Virtues Gate]
[Reserved Peace and Calm]
Don't make a mess. Just leave them.
Let Xiao Douzi take care of them.
Yes.
Your Highness, please forgive me.
I-I ate too many sticky rice balls at lunch, an-and I have the hiccups.
I'll drink some water to get some relief.
Once I get better, I'll come back to serve you.
- You may leave then.
- Yes.
[Esteemed Virtues Gate]
Where are you taking me exactly? Why are we taking the back door?
Wang Fuheng is going to summon you to meet the crown prince. You should avoid him.
The crown prince is looking for me?
A few days ago, you said you've taught everything that you were supposed to.
The crown prince shouldn't be looking for you these days, right?
Perhaps he has something else to ask me to do?
I'll have to see the crown prince to know what it's about.
Lately, there are a lot of rumors in the palace about the crown prince being interested in males.
You are the little good-looking physician that is favored by the crown prince in those rumors.
Me?
This is nonsense!
I am a girl.
Even if the crown prince is lecherous, he would be interested in females.
How can you still be joking at this time?
I've cautioned you a thousand times, but you've treated my words as wind passing by your ears.
I've remembered to heart everything that Young Master Pei has said.
The inner palace is full of danger. I must be cautious all the time.
I also have to keep my distance from the crown prince.
Even though the crown prince doesn't have evil intentions, but I carry too many secrets,
so I could attract fire to burn myself if I don't handle it well.
I really don't know what to do about you.
Imperial Guard Leader?
If I had known you were here too, I wouldn't have come here then.
Eunuch Wang, why did you decide to take this side path and come through the back door?
I took a shortcut to pass a message to the Directorate of Eunuchs.
I didn't expect that you two would be at the back door, too.
Let's go, Xiao Douzi. His Highness has summoned you.
Young Master Pei, I will remember all of your reminders.
Young Master Pei need not worry, I will definitely handle everything well.
Let's go.
I will do it now.
Your Highness.
Is Mother serving His Majesty at the Hall of Immortal Dew now?
Replying to Your Highness, Consort Yang is accompanying His Majesty now.
Heaven is helping us.
Your Highness, Xiao Douzi is here.
Greetings, Your Highness the Crown Prince.
Where did you go?
Why have you just come? I've been waiting a long time.
Your Highness, I have things to do.
Xiao Douzi, come here.
Your Highness summoned me. Is there anything you need?
Your Highness gave me a 10-day limit, but only two days have passed.
It's busy at the Bureau of Imperial Attire. I'm afraid that you'll be delayed, that's why I asked you to come.
If you draw here, it's quiet here.
- A'Quan.
- Present.
Have the rumors in the palace stopped?
Replying to Your Majesty.
I severely punished some gossiping palace maids and eunuchs
and stopped the rumors.
You can shut the mouths, but you can't stop the suspicious hearts.
I've been finding it strange, too.
Zhi'er has always been cautious in his words and behavior.
Why have these rumors come from nowhere?
Your Majesty, Prince of Cao is here to greet you.
This son and subordinate greets Your Majesty.
Greetings, Mother.
Ming'er, you may rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Mother, haven't you gone to the East Palace?
Beloved Consort, why are you going to the East Palace?
Replying to Your Majesty.
Mother said that the weather has been too hot and Your Majesty's appetite hasn't been good.
There is a wonderful lily pond in the East Palace.
Mother wanted to pick some lotus seeds herself
to make lotus cakes for Your Majesty in order to reduce the heat.
Beloved Consort, you are thoughtful.
Right now, it is the time when the lotus flowers are blooming and the lotus seeds are ripe.
I want to go take a walk outside, too.
It's better to be spontaneous when selecting a day.
I'll go with my beloved consort to the East Palace
to view the lotus flowers and pick the lotus seeds. How about it?
With Your Majesty by my side, it's my best wish fulfilled.
Ming'er, you can come with us.
Yes.
Your Highness, I suddenly feel uncomfortable and weakness in my limbs.
My face is hot and the heart is thumping. Why don't I take the drawing back,
and bring it back once I've finished it?
Should I summon the imperial physician for you?
I just feel discomfort. I'll be fine after I go back and lie down for a while.
Imperial Guard Leader.
I want to see His Highness. Please announce it.
His Highness is busy and shouldn't be disturbed.
Please come back later, Imperial Guard Leader.
Just rest here then.
Your Highness is joking.
How would I dare to take a rest here?
There's no outsider here.
I say you can rest here, then you can rest here.
I suddenly feel... feel better. It's fine now.
It's just that I feel really thirsty.
Will Your Highness bestow a cup of water to me?
Yuan Lang! Yuan Lang!
I have something urgent to report. It'll be delayed if not reported now. Please announce it now.
Your Highness has ordered that no one can disturb him. Please go back.
Talented Lady, didn't you go for a stroll in the garden to relax?
I couldn't find you after looking twice.
I see that the weather is good, so I walked more.
I didn't rest inside the garden.
Why are you looking for me?
Imperial Guard Leader just came by. He originally wanted to wait here for you,
but he was restless and wouldn't say what it was about.
Eventually, he left with a message asking that Talented Lady visit the East Palace.
East Palace? How long ago was this?
About an hour ago.
Eunuch Wang,
are His Highness and Xiao Douzi still inside?
- Yes.
- All right.
His Highness said not to disturb him. Eunuch Wang, just leave this here and I'll take it inside.
- Move aside.
- Yes.
Unruly.
Yuan Lang.
You don't need to serve here anymore. Leave now!
- But—
- Quit wasting time! Just go.
Go!
Yes.
Come back.
Do not tell anyone that His Highness and Xiao Douzi are in the Hall of Esteemed Virtues. Understand?
- Yes, I understand.
- Go!
[Proclaiming Brightness Gate]
I didn't know that Your Majesty and Consort Yang were coming to the East Palace.
I will go tell the crown prince now.
Wait.
His Majesty and Mother rarely come to the East Palace. The crown prince must not have expected them.
Why don't we just go on in and give the crown prince a pleasant surprise?
What do you think, Your Majesty?
I also want to see what the crown prince is busy doing.
No need to report to the crown prince then.
It's just... that it's not sufficient decorum.
No problem. What is the crown prince doing?
Crown Prince is reading... in the Hall of Esteemed Virtues.
- Why are you dawdling? Hurry and lead the way.
- Yes.
Talented Lady Wu.
You are?
I am Wu Kun, Deputy Imperial Guard Leader.
I was ordered to wait for Talented Lady Wu here. It's urgent.
Please follow me through the side door.
[Hall of Esteemed Virtues]
Why are you stopping?
Your Highness, I wasn't with the crown prince just now.
So I don't know for sure where the crown prince is now.
Why don't Your Majesty and Consort Yang rest in a side hall?
I'll go find the crown prince.
Your Majesty, Wang Fusheng is the closest personal eunuch to the crown prince.
How could he not know where the crown prince is?
This is clearly a lie.
Wang Fusheng, you seem to be hiding something.
It will make His Majesty think there is something unseemly with the crown prince.
It will actually hurt His Highness the Crown Prince.
Your Majesty, forgive me. Consort Yang, forgive me.
Speak. Where is the crown prince? What is he doing?
Why don't you lead me to him?
I dare not lie to Your Majesty.
It's just that the crown prince has repeatedly reminded me
not to let anyone know about this matter.
Especially, not to let Your Majesty know.
I am not hiding from you. Your Majesty, please judge wisely.
- Immediately take me to see the crown prince!
- Yes.
Please follow me, Your Majesty and Consort Yang. The crown prince is in the back garden.
Wang Fusheng, didn't you say the crown prince was inside the Hall of Esteemed Virtues?
No, no, no, the crown prince isn't inside the Hall of Esteemed Virtues.
- The crown prince is in the back garden.
- How dare you!
You dare to lie to His Majesty.
The crown prince is really in the back garden.
Your Majesty, what are they doing?
You live a pampered life, no wonder you don't know this.
They are reeling silk threads. Back then, Empress Zhangsun
personally led people to do it.
Is that Zhi'er?
Replying to Your Majesty. That person who is working there is indeed His Highness the Crown Prince.
Your Majesty personally arrived at the East Palace and I didn't get to welcome you. Please forgive me.
I came to your place to view the lotus flowers, and originally I wanted to give you a pleasant surprise.
I didn't expect to be the one to be pleasantly surprised.
Zhi'er, you are usually weak physically.
Why are you personally raising silkworms and reeling silk threads?
And deliberately did not let me know and were hiding it from me?
I am preparing a gift for Your Majesty's birthday this year.
- My birthday gift?
- I've prepared for several months.
I've told my subordinates not to say a word.
I didn't know that Your Majesty would still find out.
Royal Older Brother, where is the birthday gift?
Does Your Majesty remember, when Royal Mother was alive, she used to raise silkworms, reel silk threads,
and weave into silk fabrics in order to show the importance of sericulture?
After Royal Mother's death, Royal Father has missed mother greatly
and often visited the Hall of Establishing State to take a look at Mother's weaving frame.
That's true.
You were still a child at that time.
I was still young.
When your mother was raising silkworms and reeling silk threads,
we used to go help frequently.
I also often reminisce about that happy and joyful past.
That's why I have gathered the household to raise silkworms and reel silk threads.
Then let the princess consort weave into silk fabric,
then sew the fabric into clothes to present to Your Majesty.
This is a token of my filial piety to Your Majesty.
I hope that I can also comfort Your Majesty's yearning for Imperial Mother.
I have been worrying about you.
Too much kindness, not enough toughness.
I think I've worried too much.
As crown prince, my son knows the value of setting an example by doing,
and also knows to remember filial piety.
I am very gratified.
Your Majesty, I heard that the technique in weaving silk fabric is complicated.
I didn't know that Crown Princess Consort was so capable.
I would like to take a look myself.
Your Highness the Crown Prince!
Eunuch Yuan, why are you so careless? Are you all right?
It's nothing. But Imperial Guard Leader is a step late.
His Highness the Crown Prince has already left.
- Greetings, Your Majesty. Greetings, Consort Yang.
Meiniang, why are you here?
I came to the East Palace to learn how to weave silk fabric.
If I can weave and sew with my own hands, compared to putting on rouge and powder, teasing cats and dogs
in the palace, this is much more interesting.
Well said.
Your Majesty.
This silk fabric is woven with the silk threads made from the silkworms raised by Crown Prince.
Please look, Your Majesty.
This fabric is soft and smooth.
Very high quality.
Crown Princess Consort, where did you learn this weaving skill?
Replying to Your Majesty. I asked Xiao Douzi of the Bureau of Imperial Attire to teach them.
Xiao Douzi?
Your Majesty, this Xiao Douzi is the one
rumored to be favored by Crown Prince.
Is Xiao Douzi here?
[Enlighten]
Xiao Douzi kneels to greet Your Majesty.
Raise your head.
Does Your Majesty still remember the Feast for All Souls Festival?
The one who made the gown for the late empress is this Xiao Douzi.
Recently, the womenfolk in the East Palace and I have wanted to learn some dressmaking skills,
so we asked him to come here. Probably because we are too used to bing served,
we learn one thing today and we forget it tomorrow.
Xiao Douzi, however, is very patient.
He keeps coming to the East Palace. It's truly hard for him.
Replying to Your Majesty. Talented Lady Wu is humble.
The silk weaving technique is very complicated.
The ladies are naturally smart and are also diligent.
That's why they have learned in such a short time. It's really not easy.
A'Quan.
Present.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
♫  Watching the flowers bloom and fall in the courtyard  ♫
♫  How many loves, regrets, entanglements, separations, reunions must we go through together  ♫
♫  Uncover the vicious cycle of the past  ♫
♫  Fate has its uncertainties  ♫
♫  I've spent this life with brush and ink in hand  ♫
♫  Writing about what love is  ♫
♫  Borrow from the relentless of the night  ♫
♫  To exchange for the certainty of a promise  ♫
♫  There are too many bumpy roads along the way  ♫
♫  The more twists, the deeper it is  ♫
♫  Breaking up and making up is like an illusion  ♫
♫  Resembles a traveler traveling through this life  ♫
♫  Time ignores everything including obsession  ♫
♫  With the candlelight flickering indefinitely  ♫
♫  After the fire, there was only one thing left  ♫
♫  A bright moon that makes one's heart tingle  ♫