Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
[Weaving A Tale Of Love]
[Episode 11]
Do you really want to withdraw from the fair?
Yes. We don't have any samples of clothes now.
The sample dress of Ruyi Resist Dye Shop is here!
A'Ni!
- It's so great!
- We finally found the sample.
I thank Young Master Pei in the name of Ruyi Resist Dye Shop.
Shopkeeper A'Ni, quickly get ready!
All right!
That's really great!
The dress designed by Caoji Resist Dye Shop is gorgeous.
It has Great Tang's palace style.
It inspires people to widen their horizons.
However, it's still too early to declare victory.
Because the next contestant is
the famous Ruyi Resist Dye Shop!
Let's invite the shopkeeper of Ruyi Resist Dye Shop
to come up and present their work!
- Great!
About that...
How did you know that person was a liar?
Earlier with all the clothing shops,
that person single-mindedly only came to your stand.
It's proving that you are not that smart
and wanted to steal the clothes from you.
Thank you.
Don't admire me too much.
Don't forget! We are now...
still enemies.
Don't worry. It's you that owes me and I won't forget.
Let's say that what happened today repays a little bit of interest.
Dear colleagues. Dear customers of Ruyi Resist Dye Shop. Good morning, everyone!
Great!
This is the clothing designed by our Ruyi Resist Dye Shop.
This dress's design is based on the shape of a peony.
We used a gradual dying technique.
Its design is unique and original. The confection is complicated and meticulous.
It can set off the ethnic girl's
lively and cheerful nature of their foreign beauty.
Good!
Although the thought behind this dress is clever, it doesn't surpass our Caoji Resist Dye Shop's magnificence.
It probably can't appeal to refined taste.
It makes sense what she says. Right.
That's right.
Take a look.
Look! That piece looks better!
The color is really beautiful!
That's right.
Ruyi Resist Dye Shop cut the dress's skirt into a flower shape.
This shows great creativity!
But...
Wait a second!
The dresses and garments of Caoji are indeed magnificent.
But they are more suitable for the sweet-tempered and refined women of the Tang Dynasty.
Hu women are more lively and restless, and love dancing and singing.
Ruyi Resist Dye Shop's dresses
were designed for Hu women!
Clever talk in an ingratiating manner!
If we want to know whether the dress is beautiful or not,
we shall hear the verdict of the masses!
Shopkeeper Cao is right! In fact, I want to
make a deal with you!
Since these dresses and garments were designed for Hu women,
so, of course, they should be tried on by a Hu woman to judge whether they are ugly or beautiful.
I was born in Tang and I grew up in Tang.
However, there's Hu people blood flowing through my veins.
Today, I will offer my service, just like Mao Sui,
on behalf of the women in the western region that want to buy Great Tang's clothing,
I will try on this piece of fabric!
Good!
- Congratulations! Congratulations!
- Thank you!
- Thank you, everyone.
Congratulations, Shopkeeper A'Ni for winning the contest!
- Thank you! Thank you!
- Shopkeeper A'Ni,
you are getting so many Hu merchants' contracts, I think you may get too busy.
- Please share some work with us.
- Thank you.
We all do business in the West Market, and we are neighbors.
[Ruyi]
[An Residence]
A'Ni, you haven't fallen asleep, too. Right?
Whenever I think of the Hu Merchants Fair,
the angry look of Madam Cao and Shanhu,
I can't resist laughing.
The more I think about it, the better I feel. Let's see in the future whether they have the face to
keep cheating by using Attire Expert An's name.
Exactly.
Liuli, the dress you made shined so brilliantly today,
and our Ruyi Resist Dye Shop won. Why do you look so worried?
I am only thinking, did I mistake Pei Xingjian today?
I also think he doesn't seem like a bad person.
If he really is a good person,
then I have become the bad person that accused the good person.
I wonder if Foster Father and Xiao Shunzi are doing well.
Such a clever and obedient child,
Sun Decheng is willing to give up.
It really makes people's heart ache while watching.
Xiao Shunzi, I heard that your master
is in a hurry to cut relations from you to abandon you.
I originally didn't have to care about someone who was abandoned in jail,
someone who can only wait for death.
Water.
You have good luck. You still have a bit of worth.
Tell me!  Where is Xiao Douzi hiding?
What is his background? Why does he know how to do such good needlework?
I will go to Pan Qinhan now and plead for you,
ask him to release you. What do you think?
Xiao Shunzi,
this is your last chance.
If you don't grab it,
when you go to hell,
don't regret.
Water. Water.
Physician Dou is already gone.
What did you say?
Attire Expert Zhuo save me! Save me!
I don't want to die.
Water. Water.
Here.
What did you say? Physician Dou is already gone?
Physician Dou is already gone. He left the palace already.
Where did he go?
I don't know.
I don't know. I only know
that he left the palace.
Say it. Why did he leave the palace?
How did he leave?
I only know that he wanted to leave the palace.
You said that Physician Dou has disappeared. I guess that
he probably sneaked out of the palace.
I really don't know anything else.
Xiao Shunzi!
You have known him since you were young.
Who are his parents? How did he learn to make clothes?
You should know these best!
He is Master's...
He is an orphan from outside the palace.
He also doesn't know who his parents are.
How would I know?
As for dressmaking,
he taught himself.
He told me that he found a book of dressmaking secrets from the funerary items
belonging to a deceased concubine.
He burned it after reading it.
I only heard everything from him.
I didn't see any of this.
Everything you are speaking is the truth?
Yes. Yes. I really don't want to die.
Every word I said is the truth. Attire Expert Zhuo, please save me.
As long as you are speaking the truth, of course I will help,
and figure a way to get you out.
[West Gate]
Hurry up!
Lightly.
Hurry! Hurry!
Put it down lightly. Very Lightly.
- Hurry!
- Prince of Cao has eaten bear heart and leopard gall.
(Got emboldened)
He actually has dared to embed secret goods among the paper supplies.
What exactly are these secret items that Prince of Cao has to go through these maneuvers.
Prince of Cao is here.
This subordinate Xue Xu greets Prince of Cao.
Has it been successful?
We did encounter some problems,
but I have already solved them.
Prince of Cao, please rest assured.
This way.
Hurry.
Your Highness.
You can take a look.
[Seal]
How can Prince of Cao dare to secretly ship armor? Is he going to rebel?
Secretly transporting armor is the same as the major crime of rebellion.
Is Prince of Cao going to rebel?
The crown prince is pushing for reform, but the Prince of Cao is opposing it.
Not long ago, Crown Prince argued with reason
and submitted a proposal to reform the imperial examination system. He persuaded His Majesty.
His Majesty has decreed to let the crown prince implement the reform.
Unless he is not satisfied because of this?
So he is secretly transporting armor to plan for a rebellion?
This isn't right.
Even though reforming the imperial examination system is a major event, but it shouldn't lead Prince of Cao
to make this kind of move that disregards any consequences.
It doesn't help to overanalyze it. How do we know what he is thinking?
Anyway, secretly storing armor is the same as intending to rebel.
We saw it with our own eyes.
It's an absolute truth. The Prince of Cao is scheming
and good at allying factions. There are many of his cronies in court.
If he really intends to rebel, I worry for Great Tang.
It is only a week. What can he do?
No, it is not only these cars.
What?
Puzhou will continue to ship paper supplies for students to Chang'an.
It means, there could be more huge batches of armor that will continue to be sent to Prince of Cao's Manor.
Brother Pei, such a major event should be immediately reported to the Court of Judicial Review.
You must not be careless.
Crown Prince's reform must have affected the benefits of many aristocrats and nobles.
- These people mostly have sided with Prince of Cao and become his faction and spies.
- But...
You and I have low official ranks. Even if we risk our lives to submit a report to His Majesty,
the report will probably be intercepted even before it reaches His Majesty.
Everything Brother Pei has said is right. But knowing that there are people planning to rebel,
as His Majesty's subordinates, we shouldn't leave them alone either.
We have to report this.
But we have to do it through someone we can trust to send it.
Brother Pei, why not ask your teacher, Su Dingfang to do it?
My teacher is traveling and won't return for some days.
Besides, the risk is too big this time.
What if we can't knock down the Prince of Cao. I don't want to drag down Teacher.
Crown Prince.
Crown Prince?
Yes, Crown Prince.
Prince of Cao's plot is obviously to overtake the crown prince's seat as the heir to the throne.
We should tell him. This is the best way.
Why didn't I think of this?
But with our ranks,
it is hard to see Crown Prince.
Listen to me. Let's divide and conquer.
You continue to do your job at Puzhou.
Take your turn to transport the paper supplies and use the chance to find out Prince of Cao's movements.
As for how to report this matter to Crown Prince, let me work on that.
All right.
I haven't thought this Xiao Douzi would be so capable.
He even managed to sneak out from the palace.
Master, what do you plan to do next?
I will obviously report the whole incident to the Directorate of Eunuchs,
and make the Directorate of Eunuchs order his arrest.
Even though Xiao Douzi stayed in the Courtyard of Misfortune
as a medical officer of sanitation for many years,
ultimately, his physician title is undeserved.
If this is reported to the Imperial Academy of Medicine,
it will probably be turned into a trivial matter that is ignored.
Since Xiao Douzi's transfer order
was issued by the Directorate of Eunuchs,
and Deputy Director Pan Qinhai also accepted bribery from me,
I will
ask him to get to the bottom of this matter.
Strange.
This Xiao Douzi
would rather sneak out of the palace and not get a better position at the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
There has to be...
a reason for this.
I'm sure Sun Decheng knows where Xiao Douzi is hiding.
Qiniang, go to the Courtyard of Misfortune right now
to find Wei Lin. Tell him to monitor Sun Decheng's every move.
This time,
I have to know everything from top to bottom.
Yes.
[Ruyi]
[Ruyi Resist Dye Shop]
Small items!
You are my honored guests, please!
This way!
This! And this as well!
I have packed them all! Send them to my mansion!
That's the dress!
So pretty.
Beautiful.
I like this color.
You may look around! Take a look around!
There are also some of these inside! Inside as well!
Welcome.
Are you the shop's owner and elder brother to my elder brother's Madam An?
Madam, you are...
Kudi Yanzhong is my older brother. Speaking of it, you and I are relatives.
It's just that after Sister-in-Law passed away, the two families haven't stayed in touch.
I have come to your store sometimes, but have only seen shopkeeper A'Ni.
So you are Madam Kudi of the Commandant Manor.
I haven't been courteous.
I came today to see the new female artist in your store.
Our Miss Yu, Eighth Miss, and Madam Cui
can't praise enough of her skills.
Therefore, I also want her to custom make a few dresses.
Madam must be talking about the artist, Yu'er.
Yu'er definitely has good skills.
Too bad that she has already resigned and left.
I don't know where she went, either.
This new artist has just come. She was doing a good job.
Why did she resign and leave?
[Ruyi Resist Dye Shop]
Take a look!
Make way! Make way!
It's not expensive.
Good wine!
Good Wine!
[Ruyi Resist Dye Shop]
Fifth Madam, wait.
There was a reason that Shanhu couldn't marry into Commandant Pei's Manor.
You and I are still close relatives. How can Fifth Madam ignore us?
Instead of going to Caoji, you actually went to this shop.
Ruyi Resist Dye was always famous.
It also won at the Hu Merchants Fair. Why can't I go there?
To really discuss it, Madam An was my older brother's official wife.
Wouldn't Ruyi Resist Dye Shop be closer to me then?
I only wanted to help Fifth Madam make clothes and show my appreciation.
I spoke too fast and misspoke just now.
Fifth Madam, what dress do you want? Come to my shop and we can discuss it.
Your Caoji has been open for many years.
You still hang the banner of Number One Needle in the World.
But you lost to Ruyi Resist Dye's Shopkeeper A'Ni at the Hu Merchants' Fair.
Now, is there any renowned family that will still go to Caoji to make dresses?
That A'Ni is only a servant girl.
What skills does she have? It's all because that biitch helped her.
What? What you just said
was it about the new artist at Ruyi Resist Dye Shop?
Since Fifth Madam looks down on our Caoji shop,
I won't force you then.
Why is it that when A'Cao mentioned that female artist,
she seemed to hesitate?
When An Silang mentioned the female artist just now,
he also seemed flustered.
I heard that Ruyi Resist Dye Shop won over Caoji
because of a young female artist.
Yes, yes! I even saw her at the An family's old residence.
She was with shopkeeper A'Ni.
At that time, I even thought she was a member of the An family because she was a Hu woman.
Didn't An Silang say
that female artist had already left?
Why is she living in the An family's old residence?
Also, she is a Hu woman.
Could it be...
Impossible. It's absolutely not possible.
My niece, Liuli...
She died 11 years ago.
Madam, what's wrong?
I'm wondering who that female artist is.
So concealed and unpredictable.
I'm going to the An family's old residence to take a look.
Wait here for me.
Next.
Where is your waist badge?
I must have carelessly lost it. I come through frequently. Guard, you recognize me. Right?
Let me in first, and I'll go to the steward to get a replacement badge.
Without a badge, you're not allowed to enter or exit the palace. Go back. Next one.
Brother...
You need a waist badge to enter or exit the palace.
It's such an important item.
How can I get one?
Go. Next one.
[Arrest Bulletin]
It's him.
Yu'er's older cousin.
Didn't he already die?
Madam, wait please.
Please, does Ruyi Resist Dye Shop's shopkeeper A'Ni
live here?
Isn't that A'Ni?
Shopkeeper A'Ni.
Didn't you leave for the shop? Why are you back?
Hide immediately. Your paternal aunt is here.
My paternal aunt? Why is she here?
The house is only so big. Where can I hide?
I'd better hide outside.
No, no!  There's no time.
Shopkeeper A'Ni, hurry and open the door.
I saw you just now. I know that you're at home.
Shopkeeper A'Ni.
Shopkeeper A'Ni, hurry and open the door.
- It's not good if I don't open the door.
- Shopkeeper A'Ni.
Go hide inside. I'll persuade her to leave.
Shopkeeper A'Ni!
All right.
Open the door, Shopkeeper A'Ni.
Shopkeeper A'Ni, open the door.
Shopkeeper A'Ni.
Shopkeeper A'Ni...
Aren't you Madam Kudi? Why are you looking for me here?
We can talk at the store if you want anything.
Several womenfolk at the Commandant' Manor
have greatly complimented the female artist.
I also want her to custom make some new dresses for me.
Just now, I went to the shop but you weren't there.
I heard that you and the female artist live together at the An family's old residence.
So I came here instead.
Madam must be talking about Yu'er, right? I'm afraid to disappoint you.
You came a little late. Yu'er already resigned and left.
This female artist is so capable.
The customers like her, and she won at the Hu Merchants Fair.
How could she leave just like that?
How could you bear to let her leave Ruyi Resist Dye?
The artist originally came from out of town.
She is used to going around to different places and doesn't like to stay in any one place too long.
Even though we didn't want her to leave, but we can't force her.
Since you said it like this, I'd like to ask about something.
Is this female artist related to the An family?
Madam, why do you ask?
That artist is not related to the An family.
It's just by coincidence that our shop's owner hired her.
If you are just strangers,
why did the An family allow her to stay at the old family residence?
Could it be that this female artist has an unspeakable secret?
You hid her away and don't want people to see her.
I might even know this female artist.
Madam!
Shopkeeper A'Ni, no need to make it difficult.
Since this madam is so curious about me,
go ahead and let her see me. It's no problem.
Madam! Madam!
Shopkeeper A'Ni, I don't know who this Madam...
This is Madam Kudi from Commandant Pei's Manor. She is a customer at our Ruyi Resist Dye Shop.
And this is...
I am responsible for purchasing at the Bureau of Imperial Attire in the palace.
I heard about Ruyi Resist Dye Shop's fame, so I came here today
to discuss purchases.
Purchasing in the palace involves interests among different areas.
Before it's finalized, we must keep it low-profile.
Therefore, I especially reminded Shopkeeper A'Ni
not to talk about it to any outsiders to avoid unexpected conflicts.
There are too many people in the shop, and Caoji Resist Dye is always watching us.
This is why I invited our esteemed guest to come to our old residence.
Unexpectedly, as I was about to go to the shop to pick up some samples for the esteemed customer,
I saw Madam by accident. I didn't mean to avoid Madam.
It's just that... this involves Ruyi Resist Dye's business secrets.
Madam is also related to Caoji. That's why I had to be extra cautious.
It turns out that I made Madam misunderstand. Please excuse me, Madam.
What should we do then?
I almost disrupted Ruyi Resist Dye Shop's business.
Shopkeeper A'Ni, since you have an important guest here, I still have official business to do.
I'll bid my farewell today, and will return another day to discuss the purchasing matter.
I have slighted you today. Please leave safely, Official.
I was the rude one. Please don't be upset, Official.
Take a look! 10 copper coins for one! Very cheap!
[Wang Pancakes Shop]
Physician Dou!
Good!
Make way!
How about this horse?
Patron, do you want to buy a horse?
To buy a horse... this horse...
Look at these horses! They are all fine breeds from the Western Regions!
I don't know what kind of horse my patron would like to buy
so that he has to sit next to its feet and write out compositions.
Can this horse run?
Of course, I have to sit next to its feet. When buying a horse, one has to check its feet.
Checking its teeth, its eyes, its hair,
is nonsense. We're not choosing horses for their beauty!
Could you please step aside?
It's the first time I've seen someone buying a horse this way!
There is even more you have not seen yet!
That must be true!
This is also my first time seeing...
the physician who died but became alive again.
Where are you running to?
Let me go! Why do you want to catch me?
- Don’t move!
- Let go of me!
If you move again, I will hit you!
Go!
Customers, please come inside.
-  Shopkeeper, do you have a private room?
- Yes, yes.
There is a private room upstairs.
Attendant, hurry and take these two customers upstairs.
Customers, please go upstairs.
Behave.
Faster!
Take a look! Take a look!
Such frgrant and sweet desserts.
[Arrest Bulletin... reward available]
Customers, please enjoy.
Thank you.
I warn you.
I am not interested in Long Yang.
(I am not gay. From a story about King of Wei and Lord Long Yang who were lovers.)
Look at you.
You actually resemble your cousin who is the artist.
Not only do you look like her, but even your stinky temper is also similar.
Fortunately, I am alert and have sharp eyes.
I saw you and recognized you right away.
Otherwise, I don't know how much longer I'd be falsely accused.
Sharp eyes? I think you're blind.
What did you say?
Speak. Why did you pretend to be dead?
Does Yu'er know that her older cousin is still alive?
Even though I found your bundle,
to avoid arousing suspicion, I never even opened it.
But your cousin insists on saying that I exchanged the content in the bundle.
She won't quit until she gets her money back.
Right now, it seems that you two cousins colluded in a scam.
You looked for an easy target to blackmail a bundle of money.
I think this is a misunderstanding.
I'm just a little medical officer at the Courtyard of Misfortune. Because I yearned for freedom outside the palace,
I pretended to be dead and hid in the coffin so that I could escape out of the palace to reunite with my cousin.
Who was to know that as soon as I got out of the palace that day, the coffin was hit and overturned.
I hurried to run away and carelessly dropped the bundle.
That bundle really contained money, and it was my complete savings.
Yu'er saw that Sir Pei found the bundle, so she went to Simen College to ask for it back.
Who would have known that the bundle was switched?
The money never went through anyone else's hands, and now they are missing for no reason.
Naturally, Yu'er and I
thought that you did it. We just wanted to get it back.
- Except that—
- Except what?
Except that when you saw the victim, not only didn't you avoid me but actually kept chasing,
It really doesn't seem like what a thief would do.
So now I am feeling doubtful, too.
I'm concerned that we two cousins have blamed you by mistake.
In that case, you have a little conscience.
I won't randomly wrong a good person.
Since I can't be sure that Young Master Pei did it,
I will tell Yu'er to withdraw the lawsuit from Simen College.
We'll wait for the truth before we decide.
So, thank you for your hospitality. I'll bid you farewell now.
Wait!
Is this incident considered over and done with?
I've already explained everything, and I've also agreed to withdraw the lawsuit.
What else do you want?
Excuse me, but I've changed my mind.
It doesn't matter if you withdraw the lawsuit from Simen College. I don't care.
But you must do something to recompense for falsely accusing me.
As a eunuch that sneaked away, what can I do for you?
Loan me your waist badge.
Waist badge?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
''Moon Legend'' - Singer: Zhou Shen
♫  Watching the flowers bloom and fall in the courtyard  ♫
♫  How many loves, regrets, entanglements, separations,
reunions must we go through together  ♫
♫  Uncover the vicious cycle of the past  ♫
♫  Fate has its uncertainties  ♫
♫  I've spent this life with brush and ink in hand  ♫
♫  Writing about what love is  ♫
♫  Borrow from the relentless of the night  ♫
♫  To exchange for the certainty of a promise  ♫
♫  The more twists, the deeper it is  ♫
♫  Breaking up and making up is like an illusion  ♫
♫  Resembles a traveler traveling through this life
♫  Time ignores everything including obsession  ♫
♫  With the candlelight flickering indefinitely  ♫
♫  After the fire, there was only one thing left  ♫
♫  A bright moon that makes one's heart tingle  ♫