Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
[Weaving a Tale of Love]
[Episode 33]
[Hall of Shining Virtues]
Pu Banu, quite a few days have passed.
Is there any news on Pei Xingjian's side?
Your Highness, Pei Xingjian is picking up the drug more and more often.
Based on my experience,
the person who is taking the drug must be already addicted and can't break it anymore.
Since the fish has already taken the bait, let's reel it in then.
Pu Banu, from this moment,
cut off the drug.
Yes.
Are you also out of your drug?
May I ask Your Highness for more of the drug?
- Xiao Liuzi.
- Your Highness.
Bring some of the drug for Pu Banu.
Yes.
Thank you, Your Highness, for giving me the drug.
[Hall of Shining Virtues]
Just three pills.
Your Highness, this essay is full of wisdom.
It complements Minister Chu's advice from yesterday.
They are different in tune but serve the same theme.
You said that Xiao Douzi's injury is improving every day,
and he can come to the East Palace very soon.
But many days have passed, why hasn't he come yet?
Could it be that you've been fooling me in case I worried too much?
I've been telling the truth. I wouldn't dare to lie to Your Highness.
Xiao Douzi's injury has recovered very quickly.
At this speed, in another two days,
Xiao Douzi's medicine will be out.
I will find the time to leave the palace
to pick up the last medicine from the clinic.
Your Highness, someone is looking for Imperial Guard Leader and says it's an urgent matter.
[Esteemed Virtues Gate]
- Xiao Shunzi.
- Imperial Guard Leader.
What are you doing here?
Do you have more of the medicine?
The ones that I gave you last time have already been eaten?
That's right. Xiao Douzi seems to be eating them fast like she is addicted.
She is taking more and more of them.
Once she's eaten them, she is energetic and vivacious.
Once the medicine's effect is over, she loses energy and gets tired.
I didn't want her to eat more, but she hides away to eat more.
She said that she could recuperate faster if she ate them
and won't bother me anymore. But this morning, the medicine was out.
She started to go crazy. Imperial Guard Leader!
Xiao Douzi.
Xiao Douzi, what's wrong?
No, no!  What are you doing?
Where is the medicine?
What's wrong? Tell Foster Father!
Xiao Douzi, tell me!
Tell Foster Father what's wrong!
The medicine has already been eaten.
Hold it in. Xiao Shunzi is going to get more medicine.
- Foster Father, where is the medicine?
- Daughter.
- Liuli.
- Xiao Douzi.
- Are you all right?
- Go away.
Xiao Douzi.
Where did you get this medicine?
Liuli, what's wrong?
Liuli?
Many bugs are crawling on me!
Liuli...
What's wrong, my daughter?
Hurry and put her in bed.
Xiao Douzi!  Hurry!  Xiao Douzi.
Pei Xingjian, what is going on?
What is in that medicine? Tell me!
I don't know. Maybe there's something wrong with the medicine.
Pei Xingjian, if anything happens to Xiao Douzi,
I will fight with you to the death!
If anything happens to her, without you saying anything,
I will kill myself first.
Xiao Douzi.
Xiao Douzi...
Daughter...
- Why is Heng Tai Clinic closed today?
- I still need to pick up my medicine
I still need to get treated for my illness.
What's happened?
Why is it suddenly closed?
That's right!  Why is it closed?
My hand is not cured yet.
If she is recovering well,
just rest quietly.
There is no need to keep taking the medicine.
Just as the proverb says, 30% of the medicine is poison.
How many pills a day? How many days for each course? Please tell me, Physician Heng.
Unless it's urgent,
it's best to eat as little as possible.
Where is the medicine?
Daughter! Daughter!  Tell Foster Father what's wrong!
My head... My head wind illness has recurred.
Are you sure that the physician has left Chang'an?
Please rest assured, Your Highness.
I personally escorted that physician out of Chang'an. There's no mistake.
I would like to see
how Pei Xingjian will beg me to help his sweetheart.
At that time, I will exchange his sweetheart's life for the East Palace's military power.
Pu Banu,
is ther anything you still want to say?
I was just about to reply to Your Highness,
Pei Xingjian's sweetheart appears to be inside the palace.
A palace maid?
Why are you just telling me now this important news?
Your Highness, please allay your anger. I am only speculating and can't be sure.
Got beaten by planks...
Which young woman would get beaten by planks?
Then she is most likely to be a palace maid.
Xiao Liuzi, go to Hall of Brilliant Joy and tell my mother about this.
Ask her to check, which young palace maids
have been beaten by planks and have been injured?
Yes, I'll go right now.
[Hall of Gentle Breeze]
How is it? Have you found out?
Consort Yang, I investigated carefully.
During those days, there was no palace maid being punished.
However, a young physician
was beaten several dozens of times and almost got killed.
They say it's a young woman.
How could it be a physician?
Which physician in the Imperial Academy of Medicine would be punished so harshly?
I haven't heard anything about it.
It's not a physician from the Imperial Academy of Medicine.
It's Xiao Douzi, who was loaned from the Courtyard of Misfortune to the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
Xiao Douzi?
Xiao Douzi lost to Attire Expert Zhuo in the competition for Number One Needle in the World,
but he wouldn't concede his loss
and even accused in public that Attire Expert Zhuo stole the dragon robe that he had made.
Attire Expert Zhuo felt awkward and ordered him to be severely punished.
I heard that he was supposed to be beaten to death.
In the end, Pei Xingjian saved him and took him away.
Everything fits now.
The only difference is the last part.
That Physician Heng said the person Pei Xingjian was saving was a young woman.
But Xiao Douzi is a male.
What is going on?
Take a look! Take a look!
Best Sachets!
Come take a look!
Floral umbrellas!
It looks that the young lady you want to save is out of medicine now.
It is really you.
Speak... Where is the antidote?
I am looking for the antidote, too.
But this poison doesn't have an antidote.
To live, you must keep taking the pills.
Otherwise, death is the only way.
If you don't tell the truth, I will kill you now!
Go ahead and kill me. I am a useless person anyway now.
I would like to ask you something, Pei Xingjian.
How does it feel when you have ruined the person you wanted to save?
Who is she? Is she your sweetheart?
I understand very well the pain she is suffering now.
It's like a hundred bugs biting me, ten thousand needles piercing my bones.
Dying is better than staying alive. All of this
is thanks to you.
If you have to time to vent your anger upon me here,
why not think of a way to beg the person you should beg.
I don't need to remind you who that person is, do I?
Xiao Douzi!
Eunuch Sun.
- What's the matter with Xiao Douzi?
- Xiao Douzi is missing.
I'm afraid that she is getting desperate.
Reporting to Consort Yang. Xiao Douzi has been recuperating from injuries at the Courtyard of Misfortune.
When we picked him up, he was already tied up.
We don't know why.
Then this fits.
The drug addiction must be taking effect. That's why he's tied up,
so that he gets crazy and hurts himself.
Therefore, you are the person that Pei Xingjian is trying to save.
Xiao Douzi, you and I
are quite connected by fate.
You have a fair face with rosy cheeks.
The soft face...
is even prettier than a palace maid.
I was recuperating in the Courtyard of Misfortune. It's not against any palace rules.
I don't know why Consort Yang captured me here.
Recuperating?
It's good timing.
I have the best medicinal ingredients from the Imperial Academy of Medicine.
You only need to take off your clothes,
and soak your body with the steam from the medicine.
Your wound will recover very quickly.
Replying to Consort Yang.
I am a lowly person.
How can I overstep boundaries and use the imperial physician and ingredients from the Imperial Academy of Medicine?
Consort Yang brought me here.
If you want me to do anything, just order me.
I can't do that.
How can I be so coldhearted to order a sick person to work?
Come, disrobe Xiao Douzi.
Let go of me! Let go of me!
Let go of me!
You... are you crazy? I am being kind to help you recover from your injuries.
You actually hit me?
Speak.
Why are you disguising as a male to hide your true identity?
With your fantastic skills in dressmaking,
you can become a famous dressmaker anywhere you go.
Why are you being hard on yourself
by disguising as a male in the palace
and living under dangers?
I've already investigated your background.
You came into the palace at the age of seven, grew up in the Courtyard of Misfortune,
and taught yourself skills in dressmaking and embroidery.
That's why Zhuo Jinniang paid attention and transferred you to the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
Thereafter, you challenged Zhuo Jinniang for the seat of Number One Needle in the World.
Despite taking the risk of being beaten to death,
you still wouldn't give up.
There must be a real reason involved.
Speak. Who exactly are you?
Where did you learn your dressmaking skills from?
You want to kill me. Just do it.
Why do you ask so many questions?
I guessed it right.
You are indeed a female.
And even a pretty girl.
Dan Qing, take her away.
Change her into female attire to let me take a look.
- Yes.
What happened today, no one can spread it outside.
Otherwise, I will take your lives.
Did you feed her that half of a pill from the Prince of Cao?
She's already eaten it.
Consort Yang, why did you make Xiao Douzi wear female clothes?
I seem to have seen that face somewhere.
But I can't remember it right away.
I remember it now.
We met at the Hall of Sunset Pool.
In that case, Talented Lady Wu made you disguise as a male
and arranged for you to enter the Bureau of Imperial Attire?
Speak. Wu Meiniang
let you hide in the palace for many years. What is your scheme?
Wu Meiniang and Crown Prince are in collusion.
I have been needing a reason to knock them down.
This is perfect.
My disguise as a male has nothing to do with Talented Lady Wu.
Don't use it as an excuse
to drag down Crown Prince and Talented Lady Wu.
You say it's nothing, so it's not connected?
I am the daughter of
Attire Expert An, who was wrongly accused
and killed eleven years ago,
Kudi Liuli.
I disguised as a male to hide in the palace
because I couldn't help the circumstances.
No one ordered me to do it.
Indeed you resemble Madam An very much.
At such a young age, you overshadowed Zhuo Jinniang.
It's because you inherited Madam An's unique skills.
Now everything makes sense.
For several times, you helped the crown prince oppose me.
You also purposely entered the Bureau of Imperial Attire
to challenge Zhuo Jinniang for the seat of Number One Needle in the World.
It's for the incident of your mother secretly making the pheasant robe for the empress
and being punished to die by His Majesty.
That's right. I stayed in the palace
in order to avenge my mother
and exonerate her from the grievance.
Back then, Madam An secretly made the pheasant robe for the empress
and let Zhuo Jinniang offer it to me.
It attracted court ministers' criticism and dragged me into gossip and danger.
She deserved to die ten thousand times. What's the grievance?
My mother was framed!
My mother already received the late empress's kind permission
to let her resign her duty and leave the palace so that she could stay away from palace intrigue
and live a simple and quiet civilian life.
Why would she take the deathly risk
to appease you, a woman who wasn't conferred as the empress yet?
I was still young those years ago, but I remember it very clearly.
It was Zhuo Jinniang
who forced my mother
to fix the pheasant robe that she had made for you.
To protect the Kudi family, my mother
was forced to agree to it.
But who would have known that after the incident blew up, my mother
was falsely accused of the high crime of conspiracy of overstepping boundaries to make a dress to appease you.
Consort Yang,
I would like to ask you.
Is my mother's death connected with you?
Did you ask Zhuo Jinniang...
Didn't you order Zhuo Jinniang to make it?
Back then, His Majesty did want to confer me as empress.
But I was timid and didn't want to exceed my station.
Zhuo Jinniang and Attire Chief Lin took the initiative to offer the pheasant robe.
His Majesty happened to see it.
His Majesty was enraged and wanted to mete out punishment. Zhuo Jinniang got scared.
She confessed saying that the pheasant robe for the empress
was secretly made by your mother
and lied to her that it was just an ordinary dress,
and coaxed her to bring it into the palace to offer it to me.
It had nothing to do with her and the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
Consort Yang is saying all this so lightly.
If this is true,
you should hand this case to the Court of Judicial Review to investigate thoroughly.
Why didn't you listen to my mother's explanation,
and convict my mother to death row based on Zhuo Jinniang's version of what happened?
Clearly, you harbor ulterior motives and wanted to frame her
and shut her mouth by killing her.
It seems that, those years ago,
it was very likely that Zhuo Jinniang framed Madam An
in order to extricate herself from the crime.
Consort Yang, why are you so quiet?
Are you feeling guilty?
What happened those years ago,
it does seem to be full of suspicion when thinking about it now.
But even if your mother was framed,
the person who accused your mother was Zhuo Jinniang.
The person who convicted her was His Majesty. The investigation was handled by the Court of Judicial Review. I'm not involved.
Besides, the incident passed many years ago.
I hold your little life in my hand.
Why should I lie to you?
You only need to agree to work for me.
I will help you deal with Zhuo Jinniang
and revenge the grievance of her killing your mother. How about it?
You want me to help you?
What can I do?
You are a good chess piece that I've finally obtained.
Let me think it over nicely.
How can I use this little chess piece well
and win the big chess game from Pei Xingjian and Li Zhi?
I advise you to kill me quickly.
You want me to help you? Don't even dream about it.
When your drug addiction's withdrawal symptom occurs in a while,
we'll see if you can still talk tough.
Dan Qing, take her away and guard her well.
Yes.
[Regulations Bureau]
Imperial Guard Leader.
Have you seen Xiao Douzi?
Xiao Douzi? Isn't he recuperating in the Courtyard of Misfortune?
Xiao Douzi is missing. Did he return to the Bureau of Imperial Attire?
Why is he missing? What happened?
There's no time to explain.
I hope he is just hiding because he is feeling bad.
If he was captured by Prince of Cao or Consort Yang,
that would be terrible.
- Brother Pei.
- Please help me with a favor. Xiao Douzi is missing.
Take people to quietly search in the palace. Don't miss any place that you can think of or not think of.
Also, find a few most trusted ones to scout around the Prince of Cao's Manor.
It's also possible that Prince of Cao or Consort Yang has captured him.
- It's impossible to get inside Prince of Cao's Manor now.
- Why?
I was just about to report to Brother Pei.
You told me to pay attention to the armor stored inside Prince of Cao's Manor, and I have not dared to even slack.
Yesterday, two people who have been ordered to monitor Prince of Cao's Manor
finally saw that the armor has been secretly shipped out.
So they followed along the way to find where the armor was being sent.
Too bad that they were discovered.
One person was captured. The other one escaped and returned.
Are these two trustworthy?
These two are absolutely trustworthy. What I worry about is
that the one that has been captured will be seen through by the Prince of Cao
as one of our imperial guards.
Right now, the Prince of Cao Manor must be under heavy guard. If we try to get inside to investigate,
it would be practically impossible.
His Majesty's illness is getting worse and worse every day.
His Majesty also knows he doesn't have much time left.
That's why he has personally appointed Zhangsun Wuji and Chu Suiliang as ministers-regent to assist the crown prince.
His purpose is obvious. The crown prince will soon
inherit the throne.
For the Prince of Cao to secretly move the armor,
he is clearly prepared to rebel.
Don't do anything to alert the Prince of Cao Manor for now.
The most important task right now is to guard all the city gates.
What about the palace gates?
Don't do anything unusual at the palace gates.
Do you remember the Black Tortoise Gate's Coup years ago?
Thank you, Brother Pei, for the reminder, or I would have committed a great disaster.
Right now, the situation in court is beneficial to the crown prince.
But the more it's like this, the more we must exercise caution.
We must not get caught in any wrongdoing by the Prince of Cao.
He will use the chance to frame the crown prince.
We must also be wary of the Prince of Cao making a last strike with all he's got to revolt.
I shall keep it to heart.
The Prince of Cao is moving the armor, so something big will happen.
I'm going to report to the crown prince now to plan a countermeasure.
I didn't know that Imperial Brother and I are thinking the same way.
Pei Xingjian, why are you avoiding me when you see me?
Greetings, Your Highness the Crown Prince.
Greetings, Your Highness the Prince of Cao.
You came here looking so rushed.
There must be some secret news to report to the crown prince.
Imperial Brother is busy with state affairs. This younger brother won't bother you then.
I will arrange to meet Imperial Brother to reminisce brotherly bonds.
Sure, we brothers haven't had a heart-to-heart chat like today.
You must come more often to the East Palace to chat.
Thank you, Imperial Brother, for your kind gesture. I will take my leave then.
A'Sheng, help me walk the Prince of Cao out.
Yes.
Your Highness the Prince of Cao.
You dropped your sachet.
It's such a finely made sachet, you should put it away.
That's what I think, too.
I remember that this sachet
was given to me by a beauty some years ago.
I will walk the Prince of Cao out for the crown prince.
No need.
There are important things to rush, and unimportant things that can wait. Don't reverse the order.
That's Liuli's sachet.
The Prince of Cao deliberately came to remind me that he has Liuli.
The Prince of Cao used the word "beauty" to remind me
that he already knows Liuli is a female.
Prince of Cao's visit today is quite suspicious.
He only chatted a little but dashed away in a hurry after he saw you come.
With the Prince of Cao's scheming mind, I don't think he would do this for no reason.
The Prince of Cao's purpose is very clear.
He is using Liuli's life to threaten me
to stop me from reporting about the armor's movement.
You looked to be in a hurry just now. Is there anything urgent?
I heard that the Prince of Cao came here, and was concerned that he would take advantage of you.
That's why I rushed over here.
[Esteemed Virtues Gate]
Your Highness, is this Xiao Douzi so important
to make Pei Xingjian betray the crown prince?
Pei Xingjian is someone who regards friendship highly.
This kind of person, once he falls in love,
it's like there is a door to his life.
Xiao Douzi is Pei Xingjian's door to his life.
Not only will I use her to control Pei Xingjian
to mobilize the East Palace's troops,
I also want her to add an iron-clad proof
to frame the crown prince as plotting to usurp the throne.
Liuli, I've already thought of what you should do.
You only need to make a dress for me,
and I will let you live.
Could it be a funerary gown?
Unless you want me to overstep my boundaries
and make you a pheasant robe for an empress?
This time, I want you to make
a dragon robe.
It seems that the Prince of Cao can't wait to usurp the throne.
I am having this dragon robe made based on the crown prince's measurements.
The crown prince?
I heard that, in spite of all the embroidery maids in the Bureau of Imperial Attire,
the crown prince only wears the clothes that you make.
The crown prince has great affection for you and often summons you to the East Palace.
Everyone knows about this.
What I want you to do is not difficult to do.
You only need to make a dragon robe for the crown prince,
then find a chance to hide it in the East Palace.
Back then you framed my mother
and made me lose my family.
Now, you actually want me to help you to frame the crown prince as a traitor.
You are dreaming!
I will never help the evil commit wrongdoings against my conscience,
and become Great Tang's sinner for a thousand years.
Don't be so agitated.
With or without you, the crown prince will rebel.
I will let you make a dragon robe for the crown prince.
It's just to add an iron-clad proof to the crown prince's high crime of treason.
The real high crime of treason
still requires Pei Xingjian's help.
You have conjured the wrong idea.
Pei Xingjian is upstanding and honorable. He would never be disloyal
and do anything to betray the crown prince.
Pei Xingjian is upstanding, honorable, and strong with conviction.
We originally couldn't do anything about him.
But it's different now.
We have you as a chess piece.
Now we can make Pei Xingjian listen to us.
Liuli, Liuli...
Between you and the crown prince,
who do you want Pei Xingjian to choose?
You should enjoy how it feels without the medicine.
I'll see how long you can still resist.
Don't let her pass out.
I want her to feel deeply
what it is like to wish she were dead.
Yes.
[Prince of Cao Manor]
Imperial Guard Leader.
Hurry and report to the Prince of Cao that Imperial Guard Leader Pei Xingjian seeks to meet him.
Prince of Cao has been waiting for you for a long time.
Imperial Guard Leader, please enter.
Your Highness.
Greetings, Prince of Cao.
Pei Xingjian, are you here for this sachet?
I never realized that Xiao Douzi would be such a beauty.
No matter that you risked your life several times to save her,
it's because you were cherishing a precious jade, (refers to a beautiful woman)
and heroically saved a beauty.
What does Your Highness want? Go ahead and say it.
Good.
Very candid.
I want you to change your allegiance to be loyal to me.
What if I don't agree?
Then, I will stop her medicine
and expose her real identity publicly.
What did you say?
I don't have to pretend with you.
Xiao Douzi's real name is Kudi Liuli.
She is the daughter of Madam An, who was convicted of conspiracy.
She escaped death elevan years ago, and then
disguised as a male to pretend to be a sanitation medical officer at the Courtyard of Misfortune.
That's how she has survived till now.
If this matter is revealed publicly,
no matter by national law or by palace rules, she cannot escape from the death punishment.
Pei Xingjian,
as long as you change your allegiance,
not only will I not forgive and forget the past,
I will even help you come together
and become a fairy couple
that everyone admires.
I want to see Liuli, to make sure that she is all right.
Then I will accept Your Highness's suggestion.
Good. It's precisely what I wish.
Come here tonight at 9:00, by yourself.
All right.
I'll take my leave.
I really can't bear being mean.
Don't leave! Don't leave!
Don't blame me for being mean.
Consort Yang won't go back on her promise.
Even though I want to help you very much, but
you are the only one who can help you. I advise you to agree to Consort Yang's demand.
Why suffer so much?
This is the last pill.
If you don't agree, I really can't help you even if I want to.
You've decided to die.
Don't blame me after you die.
I agree!
Isn't this good if you said so earlier on?
It would have saved our effort.
[Hall of Gentle Breeze]
- Untie her.
- Yes.
I heard that you've thought it through.
It seems that you are not willing yet.
When you're like this, how can I be at ease to let you do the work?
You feed me the poison,
while you want me to do work for you.
How can I be willing then?
I have the poison, then naturally I also have the antidote.
As long as you do everything obediently,
I guarantee that you can eliminate the addiction and be well again.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to write a note and give it to Pei Xingjian.
If you can complete this task,
I will believe that you are truly loyal.
Say it. What do you want me to write?
Tomorrow at 11:00 a.m., the Prince of Cao will raise an army at the Black Tortoise Gate.
What are you worried about?
Are you worried that Pei Xingjian will believe you
and encourage the Crown Prince to mobilize his troops at the Black Tortoise Gate and fall into our trap
and get accused of treason and lose his title as the crown prince?
Such a woman in love!
At a time like this, you are still worried about pushing Pei Xingjian into disloyalty and dishonor.
You didn't know that those pills that have made you suffer and wish you were dead
were given to Xiao Shunzi by Pei Xingjian himself
to let Xiao Shunzi coax you to take them.
Your suffering today is all thanks to Pei Xingjian.
Therefore, you really should not feel guilty toward him.
[Tomorrow at 11:00 a.m., the Prince of Cao will raise an army at the Black Tortoise Gate]
Prince of Cao has caught a cold.
Consort Yang is going to his manor to visit him.
Consort Yang, why are you making the effort to go to the prince's manor?
Why not just let Pei Xingjing go directly to the Hall of Brilliant Joy?
What do you know?
The Hall of Brilliant Joy is not big. What if Pei Xingjian plays a trick
to destroy both sides? We would lose.
The prince's manor is our territory and it's outside the palace.
If he wants to play a trick,
at worst, we'll just destroy the body and erase all traces.
[Prince of Cao Manor]
Your Highness, Pei Xingjian is here.
Greetings, Your Highness the Prince of Cao.
Bring Liuli.
Yes.
Pei Xingjian, when you two see each other in a little while,
you don't mind if I stay here, do you?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
''Moon Legend'' - Singer: Zhou Shen
♫  Watching the flowers bloom and fall in the courtyard  ♫
♫  How many loves, regrets, entanglements, separations,
reunions must we go through together  ♫
♫  Uncover the vicious cycle of the past  ♫
♫  Fate has its uncertainties  ♫
♫  I've spent this life with brush and ink in hand  ♫
♫  Writing about what love is  ♫
♫  Borrow from the relenting of the night  ♫
♫  To exchange for the certainty of a promise  ♫
♫  There are too many bumpy roads along the way  ♫
♫  The more twists, the deeper it is  ♫
♫  Breaking up and making up is like an illusion  ♫
♫  Resembles a traveler traveling through this life  ♫
♫  Time ignores everything including obsession  ♫
♫  With the candlelight flickering indefinitely  ♫
♫  A bright moon that makes one's heart tingle  ♫
♫  After the fire, there was only one thing left  ♫