[Plot Love II]
[Episode 17]
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing behind my back?
I am just passing by.
Why are you so panicked?
I am not panicked at all.
Is it because of you
that Zheng Xiyue didn't come today?
How could this have anything to do with me?
Better not let me find out.
I didn't do anything.
What can you find out?
You better have done nothing.
Otherwise I should do something.
Mr. Lu, Chen Shaojie almost
failed to make the cut this time.
His performance
is really unstable.
As I expected.
We cannot
pin all our hopes
on Chen Shaojie.
It seems that you made a wise decision
to recruit Mrs. Lu into the company.
Whether Huanzhen can win the championship
depends on Su Bei.
I believe in her.
By the way,
did you find out
what happened
to Zheng Xiyue?
I contacted her today.
She said she fell from the upstairs,
so she didn't make it to the competition.
Congratulations on
getting the first place.
Thank you, Mr. Lu.
Your performance today was really good.
It was a wise choice for me
to hire you.
Mr. Lu has a good vision.
You were entrusted with a mission
at a critical moment
and you did a good job.
Thank you for your appreciation.
All right.
Let's go home
to celebrate.
But I made an appointment with Ye Ting.
It can be cancelled any time.
I will leave you alone.
I am leaving.
I don't want to be the third wheel.
Let's go.
Ye Ting!
Let's go home.
Just the two of us.
Grandma.
Sister-in-law, congratulations on winning
the first place in the preliminary round.
Thank you.
Grandma.
Why are you here?
You don't come to see me,
so I have to come to you.
How come?
Recently, Bei and I have been busy
with the preliminaries.
We were going to see you tomorrow.
Since Feier is also here,
let's eat something
to celebrate.
What is there to celebrate?
Just the first place
in the provincial preliminary round.
What if she won
the first place in the country?
Grandma, don't say that.
Sister-in-law cares much about the contest.
Dr. Li
brought Su Bei's medical examination report.
Su Bei is weak
and it is difficult for her to get pregnant.
If she wants to get pregnant,
she have to rest at home.
Bei.
The Lu family can give you
everything you want.
Why do you have to work so hard?
Grandma.
You know that
Huanzhen needs Su Bei.
Don't take the company as an excuse.
Even if Su Bei signed a contract
with the company,
she could resign.
What's your opinion?
Sorry,
grandma.
So
you don't want to resign.
Grandma.
We are young
and in no rush.
So
you don't have to
ask Su Bei to let go of her career.
Now I just
want a granddaughter-in-law
who focuses
on family.
That's all what I mean.
Today I am here
to give Su Bei
a chance to choose.
Either
give up the contest
and prepare for pregnancy at home,
or
leave the Lu family.
Grandma.
Shut up.
Su Bei.
Tell me your choice.
Grandma.
I won't give up the contest.
So
you want to leave Nan?
I will not leave Lu Nan either.
Grandma.
I know that the Lu family
can give me everything.
But I don't want to depend on you.
I want to realize my value.
Through my efforts,
I can help Lu Nan.
I didn't give you a third option.
Grandma.
We have our own plans for having a baby.
Don't worry.
And
even if
you drive out Su Bei today,
you can't stop the two of us
from being together.
Nan.
This is the first time
you have contradicted me.
Just for Su Bei?
You...
Aren't you going to
recognize me as grandma?
Grandma, I didn't mean that.
You did.
Grandma.
Our marriage is your decision.
So you think we have no feelings.
But now I have fallen in love with Su Bei.
We will have a baby sooner or later.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Could you think for me
just a little bit?
Lu Nan.
Do you have to protect her like this?
She's my only one in my life.
You!
What if
I insist that the two of you break up?
Grandma.
You got us married
and now you want us to break up.
Have you ever thought about my feelings?
I did this for the Lu family
and for your own good.
If so,
you shouldn't keep pushing me.
you shouldn't let me do
everything you want.
You shouldn't keep forcing me.
Don't arrange everything for me.
You!
- Grandma.
♪Another♪
♪Long talk all night♪
♪I haven't finished drinking the water
on the table♪
♪I stare at the windowsill♪
♪That fallen flower is no longer blooming♪
♪You always say♪
♪Like and love♪
♪Are similar but different♪
♪Finally this time I'm being depended on too♪
♪Listen and cover up, learn to sigh♪
♪How happy you are laughing♪
♪You are planning your future with her♪
♪I'm so numb, but I'm♪
♪Still listening♪
♪I don't have to guess your mind anymore♪
♪Is it funny, sad or helpless♪
♪Adults shouldn't lose their temper easily♪