Bloodstain.
You did this behind me?
What are you doing in my room?
Yang.
You should beware of this man.
I feel like this man is dangerous.
He's hiding something from us.
Maybe if he sleeps with a girl, he might like it.
But if we put the orchid dust in the cicada,
it will become cicada orchids with arousal property.
Doctor Qi leaving the house like this, they must have a plan.
But it's good for us.
It's the right time to make cicada orchids.
When the dust flies to catch the cicada,
it will make them breed like crazy.
In order to find the strong one that survived.
The weak cicadas will not be able to withstand the effects of the orchid dust
and eventually died.
After that, we wait for the mushroom to grow out of its body.
Why is the cicada making such a loud noise?
Burn them all.
Yes, Madam.
Li.
What's going on?
The cicadas are infected, so they all died.
But I ordered the workers to burn them.
Don't worry.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Mei.
Fu, why is Mei like this?
I don't know either.
She has been like this for a while now.
She stays in bed all day, and gets up and play with me once in a while.
But she didn't feel sick like before.
And how are you here?
We have food every meal
but we're not as happy as when we were at home.
When will we go back to our home?
Let me accomplish an important task first.
Wait a little longer.
Have you met Tian lately?
Why do you ask?
Well...
Do you see?
That I take care of your siblings and let them live comfortably.
I provide both food and medicine.
Don't worry about anything.
Just do your job.
Right?
From what you told me, Big Brother doesn't trust Li anymore.
He must have believed that Li had killed someone
to conceal Tian's secret.
I think that what it is.
Otherwise, Doctor Qi wouldn't be invited to investigate the strange herbs and mushroom.
Li is decisive.
But I didn't think that she could be this cruel.
If she can kill,
it means Tian's secret must be very important, very serious.
So have you seen anything suspicious about his secret?
Not yet.
But I came today because a strange thing happened last night.
Last night, the cicadas made loud noises throughout the house.
Why is that strange?
It's strange because its noises were louder than I've heard before.
And by the next morning, they were all dead.
Then Madam Li ordered the workers to tidy up and burn the remains.
Saying that it was because of an insect disease.
But from what I see, it’s not, so I collected its remain to let you check it.
Jiu. Jiu.
Fu, I'm going back now, what's up?
Yes, about Tian.
What's about Tian?
I heard Mr. Ma talking to someone.
He said that he sent a guy to Tian's house.
You must warn Tian.
Don't let those bad guy hurt him.
If I could, I would like to protect Tian from those evil bastards.
Please do it instead of me.
Get rid of those wicked bastards.
We have managed to burn all the weak cicadas already.
I'm going out to find the strong cicada
that survived from the power of orchid dust tonight.
Soon we will have the cicada orchid ready to be used.
This is the strongest cicada.
Who are you?
Tian.
Or is it Mr. Ma's subordinate?
Tian, Tian.
Tian.
Jiu.
Are you okay?
I'm really worried about you.
Hey.
I am fine.
Why did you come into my room?
I saw a stranger entering the house.
I'm afraid he will hurt you.
So you're alright?
Nobody hurt you, right?
And what is this?
Paint.
I dropped it when I was painting.
Paint?
If you're alright, I'll leave.
I'm glad…
that you are worried about me.
I thought you were still mad at me.
I'm not mad at you.
If you are not angry with me,
from today,
let's study as usual.
See you tomorrow.
It's me.
What's wrong with you, Jia? Who injured you?
It's Jiu.
But don't worry. He didn't know it was me.
Jiu?
The man that Tian accepted for work?
Yes, Madam.
I think this guy looks suspicious.
He's agile, good at fighting. He's not like an ordinary worker.
Keep an eye on him.
So did you get the cicada that survived?
Yes, Madam.
Soon.
We will get cicada orchid to make arousal drug.
Good.
When Tian has a wife and children and becomes the head of the association,
that day, I can die in peace.
You are nimble, not like other workers.
What did you do before staying here?
Why are you asking?
Mr. Tian is the heir of the Song Family.
Besides the people who come to seek benefits,
he's also a target of murder.
You.
I have to beware those who come close to Mr. Tian.
And you,
If you want to stay here for a long time, don't be so inquisitive.
They have been discussing for a long time.
Or do they not like my land?
Is it too expensive? Should I give them a discount?
No, if you offer discount, you won't get enough money to buy back the palace.
Do you like it?
Yes, but I think the price is too high.
I just took a look at the land nearby.
It's cheaper than yours for a hundred thousand.
But mine is right next to the river.
Most importantly, there will be a road running through the land.
You should probably heard the news as well.
But I don't quite like the land next to the river.
I'm not partial to water.
But if you give lower the price a bit more,
I will buy it right away.
Sorry for being late.
Madam, are you making an appointment with another customer as well?
Do you guys come to look at the land too?
Yes, and this is my boss.
He's very interested in this land.
Right, Sir?
Yes.
He's looking for a place in Bang Pa-in
to build a vacation home.
And most importantly, the land here is very beautiful.
The atmosphere is also good, next to the river.
She's selling very cheaply.
I thought my boss would have missed this place.
I hope that you haven't sold the land to other customers yet.
You can't, Madam.
I've been here first. You have to give me the chance first.
But my boss offers you four hundred thousand, Madam.
Four hundred twenty thousand.
I give you four hundred fifty thousand.
Four hundred thousand...
Come here. / What?
Yang, that's enough.
If they don't take it, we'll be in trouble.
Come on, I'll take care of it myself.
Madam.
My brother said it was too little.
Five hundred thousand is better.
If you want the land at five hundred thousand,
you can take it, sir.
Yang.
It's normal for new millionaires.
How can you compete with my boss?
Let's make a contract, Madam.
I give you six hundred thousand.
Wow.
Thanks a lot, Yang.
If it wasn't you and Tian, I still probably couldn't sell the land and wouldn't get this price.
Even if you couldn't sell, I will help you until you sell it anyway.
And your land is about to have a road running through. Many people want it.
But I'm a bit sad.
It's like I sold the lands of my ancestors for money.
I destroy the treasures.
Don't worry too much, your ancestors must be happy
that their wealth has helped the children.
Really?
You suddenly turned your face away from me and sighed. What does it mean?
Even though I and Tian break off the engagement,
what about you and me?
What is it between you and me?
I'm kidding.
Hey, don’t worry.
I know that we still have many problems ahead of us.
I know because I'm your ex-fiancé's brother.
But don't worry.
I believe that we can go through all these problems.
Believe me.
Let's eat cake.
Thanks.
Tian is back. The desserts are here.
Sit down, bro.
Wow, you bought a lot of books.
I want Jiu to practice reading a lot so that he can be fluent.
Jiu, the one you said that he seemed to be mad at you?
So how is it?
I am worried about myself and let you help me a lot.
We understand each other well now.
Let's eat.
My love.
I'd like two more plates, please.
What?
What do you mean that you will not marry Tian?
Right, Father.
After we get the money, we'll pay the debt to Aunt Li.
And it's done.
How can you do this all of a sudden?
If they find out, I'll lose credibility.
I already told you that I didn't want to get married.
I don't love Tian.
But he is a good man.
But I still don't love him anyway.
I don't want to be with someone I don't love, Father.
You'll love each other eventually.
No, I can't love anyone else.
Huh?
What do you mean? Do you already have someone you love?
Nangnoi.
Tell me now who is this man?
Where is he?
I won't tell you.
And if you still force me to do this,
I will run away.
It's here.
Five hundred sacks of rice.
Five hundred sacks.
Your handwriting has become more beautiful.
But the number five is not written like this.
It's written like this.
I'm sorry, I can't remember.
It's okay.
In the past, I wrote things in the wrong way as well.
My handwriting is a lot worse than yours right now.
Father.
I'm checking the accounts.
Do you want anything?
No.
I just came to check.
Go ahead.
Yes, Father.
Li.
Do you know anything about the new worker named Jiu?
Who is he? Where does he come from?
Why? What's the matter?
Why are you shocked?
What's the problem?
I just asked about a worker.
I wasn't shocked. I'm just surprised that you ask me.
So do you know or not?
I don't know who he is.
I only knew that he had saved Tian's life.
Usually you know everything about Tian.
Even his secret,
you also know that, right?
Despite your sarcastic remark,
it didn't make me know more than you.
Zhang, Zhang.
I wish you know the pain that I got.
Zhang.
Tian.
I'm sorry.
What happened?
I'm a homosexual.
No, it can't be true.
Tian.
I hope that someday you will experience the pain that I had suffered.
You will understand how I feel.
Zhang.
Tian, this is not true.
It shouldn't be you. Not you. Tian!
Tian.
(Blessing)
Amen.
Why did you wake up early today to offer food to the monks with me?
I'm a sinner.
I usually don’t go to the temple to make merit.
When I decided to make one,
it seems strange.
It's not what I mean, Sir.
I saw your face didn't look good, so I ask you this.
Are you not feeling well?
Maybe I'm really a sinner.
Why do you think that?
That time, I didn't protect Zhang.
So he decided to end his life.
I'm afraid that this sin will go to my children instead.
A bad premonition happened because you felt guilty for Mr. Zhang.
Mr. Tian and Mr. Yang both are boys.
Even though they are targeted, they'll be safe eventually.
But if you still feels uneasy,
let's find a day to make merit at the temple.
So you will be more at ease.
Since I let Jiu work for me, he can help me a lot.
Even though he can't write and read,
he is determined and is quick-witted.
I think he will be fluent soon.
Jiu is really talented.
What about his family?
His parents are dead.
He only has two younger siblings left. They are now living with a relative.
That's all.
And what about his wife?
He doesn't have one.
He's fine-looking.
Why doesn't he have a wife?
Why do you ask about Jiu?
I saw that he worked closely with you,
so I want to know his background.
Can you trust him?
Don't worry.
I can trust him, he saved my life once.
Keep working.
Bang Pa-in land, 30 rai, for sale.
30 Rai.
Jia, Mr. Song asked me about Jiu as if he suspected.
My heart almost stopped.
I thought he saw Tian and Jiu were close to each other like I saw.
Does your cicada orchid still not work?
Not yet. Last night, I sneaked in to check,
but it was still normal.
If we don't rush Tian to sleep with women,
I'm afraid that the secret will be exposed first.
Finally, Madam.
The mushroom is about to pierce through the cicadas.
It's almost ready.
Tian's wedding day is getting closer, Sir.
If we're late, we'll all be in trouble.
My son would have lost hope of inheriting.
You will also be oppressed by Tian.
I can't stay calm as well.
But my man is doing his job.
Did he send you news?
Who is he? Tell me please, so I can…
The cicada is not dead..
What cicada?
My man collected this for me the other day.
Is there something strange about cicadas at your house?
My subordinate is suspicious that the cicada
is related to the strange orchid.
The person sent to investigate about Jiu has already got some news for us.
He is a seller of sugar craft near the shrine.
He has two siblings.
His parents are all dead just like Mr. Tian said.
But there is still a doubt.
What's the matter?
The house that Jiu used to live in was in the area of Mr. Ma.
The locals have seen he went there as well.
This means...
Jiu is Ma's subordinate?
Did Ma send him to hurt Tian?
I'm not sure about it, Sir.
We can investigate until here.
Mr. Ma got eyes and ears everywhere.
If we probe into it too much, he will be aware.
There is another one that has eyes and ears everywhere like him.
What would you like me to do for you? Please tell me.
I know that you sell the secrets of Japanese soldiers.
Oh, Big Brother, don't say that.
I didn't sell anyone's secrets.
Those who visit my place like to tell stories to my girls.
And my girls like to talk.
They just talk to one another, that's all.
It's up to you. You can call what you like.
I come here to day.
Because I'd like you to help me check.
Who do you want me to check?
Jiu.
The new worker Tian has just accepted for work.
He once lived in Ma's area.
You suspect if he is Ma's man?
Don't ask too much.
Just do what I want you to do.
Don't let anyone know about this.
All right, big brother.
I will prove you
how honest I am to you.
But since you are here today,
do you want me to take care of you?
Don't do anything beyond my order.
I let you investigate.
Just do what I tell you, okay?
You can trust me.
I won't dare to do anything too much.
I'm scared.
Sir, Pin.
Are you coming to inquire about the progress of the wedding?
I'm about to let you know in the next two days.
But I'm busy recently, I'm really sorry.
Father.
I've looked at two venues,
but still can't decide which one.
We should let the bride and groom choose.
Aunt Li.
What's the matter?
I'd like to thank you a lot.
Uncle Song and Aunt Li have supported our family all these years.
You've been kind to me enough
to let me engaged to Tian.
But I really have to apologize.
Apologize?
Apologize for what?
We come here today to break off the engagement.
I would like to cancel the wedding of Tian and me.
What is this, Sir?
Madam.
Madam, Madam.
Madam Chan.
We got big issue.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry that I cause the damage.
But I really couldn't marry Tian.
It's okay, Pin. I understand.
But I don't understand.
What is this, sir?
Everything is already prepared.
How can you ask for a cancellation as easily as a child's play like this?
What about the debt and the mortgage for your palace you owe me?
Aunt Li.
Don't worry about that.
I'm getting a lot of money from selling land.
I'd like to repay the debt to buy back the palace with cash.
Selling land?
So it's like this.
My elders have already recognized the wedding.
I'll be embarrassed if you cancel the wedding like this.
How am I going to tell these famous people?
I won't accept this.
If you don't agree, what can you do?
Build a house, you have to please the dweller.
They don't love each other.
It's right to cancel the wedding.
The wedding is canceled, so does the assignment ceremony, right?
Sir.
Chan, it's not something that you're going to talk about now.
Mom, let's get out, it's not our business.
How is it not?
Yang.
Don't tell me that Pin asked to cancel the wedding today
because of you two.
It's not relevant, Madam.
Wait, calm down.
It's my fault.
See? I told you I wasn't involved in this.
The heaven would just want to punish you.
But you two are the ones who benefited.
This is definitely not accidental.
Nuan, take your master away.
Madam, don't give up.
I told you to leave.
You must accept the truth, Madam.
This is none of your business.
It's none of your business, then it's mine.
Enough!
All of you!
What's wrong with you?
In front of me, in front of the guests, you still dare to argue.
I'm sorry, Sir.
This is a big issue. Please go back first.
Let us consult and then we can talk later.
You know about Pin selling the land right?
I came across this notice in Tian's room.
I'm still confused at first, but I got it now when Pin told us a moment ago.
Yes.
I'm the one who helps her sell the land.
So she will have money to buy her palace back from Mother.
Why did you do this?
Tian.
The elders who worked with the Five Dragons Association
all know that you are going to get married.
Five Dragons Association is not a small one.
You can't just get married and end it like a child's play.
Your engagement and wedding is canceled.
It ruins our association's reputation.
I've already told you.
I don't want to get married.
but no one listens to me
Why don't you want to get married?
Is Pin not good?
Who do you love?
Who do you want to marry? Tell me!
Father.
Tian is not involved in this. I'm the one who helps Pin.
That's it, I knew it.
You are like your mother
seeking chance to destroy Tian.
You probably team up your mom to destroy his wedding, right?
Mother.
Yang.
It's you? Why did you do this?
What else?
He wants to inherit the position instead.
Destroying Tian's wedding is the only way to buy the time.
Mother, Yang is not such a person.
I just don't want him to be forced.
I feel sorry for him.
Yang.
Father. / Sir.
Father.
Let go of me.
Do you want me to get the doctor?
No.
I just felt dizzy.
I'm fine.
I'll be better after sitting for a while.
Li.
Prepare to cancel the wedding
and assignment of the new head of the association.
We have to visit the elders
to apologize to them in person.
Sir, this is a big deal.
Pin might hesitate like someone who has never been married.
Let me talk to her again.
I assure you that she'll change her mind.
Huh?
What? Cancel the engagement?
Does that mean that Mr. Tian won't have to marry Lady Pin?
They haven't concluded yet. Mr. Song let them go back first.
The woman breaks off the engagement like this, what can he do?
It must be cancelled.
What are they going to do?
The wedding will be held next month.
Right.
Mr. Tian is weird. He lost his fiancée,
and the assignment of association head may be canceled as well.
He's still cheerful and bright.
He doesn't have to get married?
How is it? Happy that much?
Huh?
Why would you be shocked?
I mean Mud.
Really weird.
What's wrong with Lady Pin? Mr. Tian is handsome and good.
Having a lot of money.
She can break off the engagement easily.
Right?
Didn't she regret it?
I doubt that the assignment ceremony of association head has to be canceled too.
Hey.
You shouldn't go in.
You've been scolded.
Hey, bro.
It's normal for me being scolded, I'm used to it.
And one more thing, I actually help Pin sell the land.
How can I let my dearest brother be scolded alone?
Actually,
canceling the wedding will cause you trouble
because the assignment of association head has to be postponed as well.
Do you believe me?
I never thought about that one bit.
In my life.
I never wanted that position.
No way.
What's wrong with you?
Even if you don't want to be one, you have to.
Can you replace me, Yang?
Hey.
I've taken your mischievous fiancée already.
You still want me to take the position of the association leader instead of you?
No, I won't.
I'm not like everyone else.
I'm not like you.
Do you remember when we were kids?
The Five Dragons Association had another member.
Mr. Zhang.
At that time, I never understood the adults why they scolded him harshly.
But now,
I understand it.
Because…
Mr. Zhang's lover is a man.
Tian.
I'm just like him.
I'm...
I know that.
What do you know, Yang?
When I was a kid,
I secretly saw Madam Li hit you.
Forbidding you from doing anything.
I didn't understand.
I didn't get it when I was young.
Why did she forbid you?
Until now I'm grown up,
I still don't understand.
What do you not understand?
Tian.
I don't get it
how loving a man will change who you are.
For me…
Tian.
Whether you love woman or man,
you're still my brother anyway.
It's okay.
Thanks a lot.
I'm really happy
that there is someone who understand and accept me the way I am today.
It's fine.
You'll be alright.
I love you, sis.
Hey, I'm telling the truth.
I really love you.
I love you too.
If you love me, turn around and smile at me.
Smile, smile.
Smile now.
I make an effort do make garlands for the monks at my best.
Tomorrow I will go to make merit.
Don't be happy too soon, Madam. They still didn't conclude yet.
If you didn't interfere, they would have canceled the wedding already.
It was you who called me.
But I think the wedding will be canceled for sure.
The woman have said this.
We can't be sure.
Because Madam Li and Jia are smart. They probably won't give up easily.
They aren't that smart.
But they are evil for sure.
I think they must be plan to do something.
Madam.
The cicada orchid is ready for producing the arousal drug.
Good, we shall use this with Tian and Pin.
Let's see if she sleeps with Tian already,
will she still refuse to marry?
A lot of mushrooms sprout,
the arousing effect will be even more intense.
Just like when cicadas are misted up with orchid dust and breed like crazy.
Wouldn't it be dangerous?
If we let him eat freshly-made one,
his body will become hot until the fire element in his burst.
But don't worry.
I mixed with herbs that have a cooling effect.
After Tian and Lady Pin consume the cicada orchids,
they will feel hot, dizzy and intoxicated.
They will be so fascinated that they want to possess each other.
This is the first time I see something like this.
What's this?
Right, Sir.
It's disgusting, just seeing it gives me goosebumps.
What mushrooms grow out of insects?
Or is it the weird orchid that Big Brother is searching
to catch Li?
The one that was used to kill Dong?
Gui, take this to a top doctor to see if anyone knows about it,
then hurry back and report me.
Yes, Sir.
If it can be used as evidence that this strange insect mushroom actually kills people.
Li and Tian won't get away.
Are you going with Mr. Song?
He goes to work. Why would you follow him?
I invite her.
There's a temple near the site I'm going to visit.
So I let Bua go with me to make merit together.
Hurry up, Sir. It will be sunny when it's late.
Bua, please take care of Mr. Song.
Yes, Madam.
Let's go. / Yes, Sir.
Madam Li order you to help mow the grass
and loosen the soil from here to the back.
Oh, it's so wide. How long does it take to finish all of them?
Why are you complaining?
It's an order, you have to do it anyway.
But what is Madam going to do with this area?
Why would you ask?
I have to ask so I'll do it right
whether to cut the grass or shovel the soil deep.
If it's for farming, we can manage only the top of the soil.
But if you want to plant a big tree, we'll dig deep.
Just clear the grass and prepare the top of the soil for farming.
Are you sure? Can you go back and ask Madam Li first? Then come back to us.
If you have a problem, I'll tell Madam to give order to you herself.
And if it isn't finished or there's not any necessary business,
don't go back to the main building, understand?
Yes.
Let's do it.
How is it? You got something?
Madam ordered the workers to clear the grass in the back.
She said if they don't finish it, don't enter the main building.
She must have planned something.
Otherwise, she wouldn't let the workers go elsewhere.
What else do you get?
That's all.
But before I came back, I saw Madam Li and Jia gossip about something,
then walking to the old barn behind the pier.
Or did she kill some one and hide the body there?
Let's go. / Yes, Madam.
I didn't see anyone here.
Are you sure Madam and Jia came here?
Yes, Madam.
They might be inside.
Would you like to have a look?
Nuan.
Madam, there's a room there.
Nuan, you've failed again.
Someone is here.
Mom, Nuan.
Yang, what are you doing here?
I should be the one who ask you. What are you doing here?
You're acting strangely, so I follow you here.
Nuan said Madam Li and Jia sneaked out here.
So I had to come here as well.
In case they plan to do something evil, we can I find a way to expose them.
They lured us to be locked up here.
I've managed to lock Madam Chan and Nuan up.
Mr. Yang is there also.
Good.
Then clean up and prepare this room.
This is where I will let Tian and Pin sleep together.
Father.
Can't I go today?
I don't want to get married and won't change my mind for sure.
Actually, it should have ended since that day.
Pin, even though I didn't force you,
but I don't want you to from your perspective only.
We are wrong
for letting things come to this point.
You've caused damage to them.
Go talk to them.
If you're not getting married, we can help figure out
how to tell the reason for the cancellation.
Please go talk by yourself.
If you let the prince talk to them by himself, we don't know what he'll say.
Perhaps instead of becoming better, things might get worse.
Why do you call Pin and Prince Pat to come here today?
Why didn't you let them come later?
You know that Father is not here.
How can we wait for something like this?
And if the news spread…
if the outsiders know about it, they'll talk to each other,
causing more damage.
Let's talk today. So we can conclude whether you're getting married or not.
Where are you going?
I'm seeing Yang. If they come, let someone call me.
Why are you going to him again?
What are you planning to do next?
The more I speak, the more it hurts.
If it wasn't because of Yang, things wouldn't be this messy.
Sit down and wait here.
We shouldn't be fooled by Madam and Jia.
It's you. You still dare to speak?
Sir.
Lady.
Please sit down.
I let you come here because I'd like to continue talking about the wedding.
But I forgot that Mr. Song is going out for work today.
Anyway, please stay here and wait until he comes back.
So we can finish this topic finally.
Alright.
I will put the color on the teacup.
Red one
will be coated with a drug that makes you feel exhausted.
Give this to Prince Pat.
So we can buy time to let Prince Pat and Pin stay here longer.
Sir.
Thanks.
The yellow one
will be coated with cicada orchid powder.
After drinking this tea,
The arousal drug will take full effect after two hours.
It would be the right time when Mr. Song comes back.
Pin.
For you.
Big Brother.
I got some news about the thing you let me do.
Let's see if Pin will refuse the marriage again now.
We can't plant anything on this kind of soil.
What exactly does Madam Li want to do?
We got big trouble.
Where is Tian now?