Did I tell you? If anyone knows this, you will be in trouble.
Madam, please. Mr. Tian will die.
What does homosexual mean?
It refers to a man who loves another man.
Or we call them gay.
A person of your kind can get married and have heirs.
A homosexual like me can have an heir.
But I don't want to, Mother.
Mr. Tian is homosexual. He's gay.
Aren't you going to tell Tian's secret? Tell me then.
If you don't have enough money, I won't dare to risk.
They will solve the problem for us.
Do we have to do this?
We have no other choice, Madam.
Dong.
Madam Chan.
Dong's voice.
I didn't see anyone,
and I didn't hear anyone either.
It is called beetle orchid.
It is a poisonous mushroom that grows in the insects.
It usually doesn't grow in human.
But I ground it and mixed it with special ingredients for you.
Its poison would make you numb, unable to move.
If you breathes in or consumed it,
it will accelerate its growth in your body.
Sucking your blood and flesh as its food.
After that,
the poisonous mushrooms will grow all over the body
and torture you to death.
But don't worry.
You won't suffer that much.
Jia.
If you aren't comfortable to stay here, you can go back. I'll see you later.
Be careful.
Guanyin, Goddess of Mercy.
I've made a mistake,
but I need to do it
for my son.
Done, Madam.
Li.
Where is she?
Mr. Song, something bad happened.
What happened?
Dong went missing.
Where will he be? Are you searching through the place?
Have you found him?
He can't go missing so easily.
Father.
How is it?
I didn't see him.
I think if Dong didn't run away,
He must have been drunk at the bar like he usually does.
I don't think so.
If you want to know where Dong is, ask Madam Li.
What are you talking about?
Right.
Aunt Chan talked like Mother knows about Dong's disappearance.
The other day, Dong came to me,
saying he got something important to talk about.
But Madam Li intervened and took him away.
Since then, when I asked him anything,
he never said again.
Last night I looked for him at his room.
But he's gone already.
I don't know what he's like now.
And most importantly,
the incident happened after Dong had a fight with Tian.
His disappearance must have something to do with it.
How is it relevant?
It is. Madam Li killed Dong to protect Tian.
What do you mean?
It's about… / Shut up.
I speak the truth, sir. It is …
I told you to shut up.
In front of so many people, how could you talk like this?
You guys.
Go talk to me in the hall.
Chan.
You must be careful with your words when you were in front of many workers.
You said that Dong disappeared last night?
Yes. Nuan and I went looking for him all night and couldn't find him.
I thought it might Madam who did this.
You can't accuse me without evidence like this.
Despite no evidence, it is a fact.
The other day, Dong was going to tell me a secret about Tian.
This secret that can put him out of the family leadership position.
Then later, Dong harassed and attacked a worker.
He also disrespected Tian.
But she gave in to Dong.
It was clear that
this must definitely be about Tian's secret.
Tian's secret?
What is this about?
Does Tian have a secret?
I doubt that.
What secret?
Dong must have seen that Chan was trying to push Yang
to become the clan leader instead of Tian.
So he made up a story to trick Chan for money.
Consider it carefully, sir.
When Dong said that he knew the secret,
he suddenly disappeared.
I couldn't help thinking that he has been killed already.
Madam.
You'd better confess what you did to Dong last night.
Stop accusing Madam Li, please.
Mr. Song is a wise and rational man. He won't listen to your nonsense.
Right.
I'm rational.
Li.
Where have you been last night?
I woke up in the middle of the night,
but I didn't see you there.
I had a bad dream, so I went to the Buddhist altar.
You never pray at the Buddhist altar.
Once a man went missing, you immediately did it.
Mr. Song.
Think carefully who benefits from this.
One missing worker.
But you make a fuss and blame Madam Li despite the lack of evidence.
Maybe it's you
who did it and blamed Madam Li.
Why did I do that?
Framing Madam to make your son replace Mr. Tian.
Alright.
If you think you're innocent…
Mr. Song.
I think we should report the police.
Let them investigate to find out the truth.
And if anyone is found guilty, put the person in jail.
Father.
We found Dong.
Dong.
Dong is really dead.
Madam.
You are so cruel and ruthless.
Do you have to kill him?
Does this mean Dong didn't drown?
Calm down.
No one killed Dong. He drowned in the river.
He may be drowned in the water.
What are you saying, Mom?
Dong sailed away and the boat capsized.
Bua was the one who found the body.
Bua, tell me what it is.
This morning when I took the boat back from the market.
I saw that there was a body floating in the lotuses over there.
Bua.
Why didn't you tell him
that last night we went looking for Dong.
We heard his voice in the back garden.
Last night when I came out to collect my clothes,
I did meet Chan and Nuan.
Dong.
Bua.
Did you see Dong pass by?
I don't see him.
But I'm not sure I heard Dong's voice.
What is this pouch?
That's the workers' wages that I prepared.
Did Dong steal everyone's wages and fled?
He was so evil.
That's why he bought Mud stuff and asked her to go out.
So he actually stole other's stuff.
In fact,
After Dong had a fight with Tian.
I called him to talk again.
But he became aggressive and disrespected me as well.
So I gave him final offer to get out of here.
But I didn't think that
he would steal the workers' wages and ran away and drowned like this.
This must be your plan.
Killing him, putting the wages at him and framed him for stealing money.
That's too much, Madam Chan.
Use your brain.
How could Madam and I fight Dong?
Look at his body size.
That's right. Dong was so strong.
Shut up.
Yang.
Check Dong again.
Is there something wrong?
Is there anything more?
No.
He must have really drowned
because there were no traces of fighting.
If you kept quiet about Tian,
you wouldn't probably meet an end like this.
Then it means Dong stole the workers' money
and ran away,
but the ship turned upside down and then drowned.
It's a mess.
Mr. Song.
Mom.
If you don't have evidence about the murder,
you shouldn't accuse Madam Li.
Hey, why are you siding with her?
Don't you want the position of the clan leader?
No.
I prefer to be a follower. I'm fine now, Mom.
Mother.
Stop looking for a way to make me take the position from Tian.
He is my brother and my benefactor.
He also saved my life.
If I take the position from him, that means I betray him.
So what you're doing now doesn't mean you betray me? Ungrateful son.
I really asked you.
You want to be inferior to him for the rest of your life?
Don't you see
what it's like to be second?
No matter what I say or do, no one listens and believes me.
But look at Madam Li,
everyone always follows her.
That's because her words are reasonable.
And look at you, you said everything loud like this, who would believe you?
I didn't yell for no reason.
Everything is reasonable,
but no one listens to me
because no one care about me.
You too. If you were the eldest child,
even if you were a rascal, everyone still respected you.
I must know
what Tian’s secret that will shake the position of the clan leader is?
Mother.
Tian.
Come in.
I made bamboo pith soup for you.
Thank you my son.
Mother.
About Dong's death…
Do you also think that I did it?
I said that I talked to him to fire him.
He must have been mad, so he stole the money and were drowned while running away.
He didn't die because he knew about me, did he?
Of course not.
How would he know?
When I, Jia and you didn't speak.
Yes, Mother.
I'm sorry for doubting you.
That's okay.
Remember that
I love you so much.
When you found Dong's body this morning,
did you see anything strange?
Not at all. It was normal.
Why?
Don't you think that Dong drowned?
I am just wondering.
I'm just not sure, so I ask you.
Not sure? What's that you're not sure?
Or …
Does Mr. Tian really have a secret?
So you suspected that Madam Li killed Dong.
There's no secret.
If you didn't see anything, that's fine.
Hey, how is it? Have you found the evidence of Dong's murder?
No, Madam.
I guess there's nothing here.
If I were Madam Li or Jia,
I would have destroyed all the evidence.
I'm really curious
who they both managed to attack a big guy like Dong?
Aunt Jia.
Where did you guys put Dong's body?
I heard the workers saying they would take the body to the temple.
But I don't know what temple.
Why do you ask about Dong's body all of a sudden?
What that has to do with you?
I'm just wondering. Usually, you don't care about him.
But when he died, you asked about him.
Ew, you talking about body and body again.
I can't eat anything.
I can still imagine Dong's bloated body.
Mud, at first I forgot about it already.
When you said that, I could see it too.
Madam Li asked me to take care of the workers.
Even if he was a bad guy,
But we have take care of his funeral ceremony.
Did he have any relatives?
He didn't have any relatives.
We've already carried his body to the temple.
Is that so?
And what temple did you take Dong's body to?
The workers said that Dong's body was taken to a Thai temple near the end of the market.
I think I should follow to destroy the body.
Otherwise there will be evidence that he died unnaturally.
Please take care of it, Jia.
It is called beetle orchid.
It is a poisonous mushroom that grows in the insects.
If you breathes in or consumed it,
it will accelerate its growth in your body.
Sucking your blood and flesh as its food.
After that,
the poisonous mushrooms will grow all over the body
You don't think that Dong drowned?
So you come to inspect the boat again.
I just wanted to make sure that no one really attacked Dong.
Since he died in our home like this.
The more I examined it, the more I found it strange.
But the crack is …
It got sharp edges like that when someone punched it.
Bua.
Didn't you see anything?
Mr. Yang.
When I found a dead body, there was nothing strange about it.
But the night before the body was found,
I looked out of my house and saw something.
A silhouette of someone.
She looks like …
Madam Li.
That night, Madam Li came out in the middle of the night too?
I think it probably was. But Mr. Yang,
she wasn't the only one who came out that night.
I was out there and met Madam Chan and Nuan as well.
I told you that I went out to find Dong
because I had something to talk to him.
Are you manipulating my son?
Bua didn't do anything, Mom.
Then why are you talking about it?
Or do you suspect about Dong's death as well?
Who is suspicious? Is it Madam Li?
Me too.
If we work together, we can find a way to expose her.
Bua.
Mr. Song and Madam Li want to see you.
Bua is here.
Yes, Madam.
Sit down.
What would you like me to do, Sir, Madam?
Tian, come in, come in. Bua is here now.
What is this, Madam, Sir?
Li discussed with me.
She wants to let you
become Tian's adoptive mother.
Madam.
I see that you love Tian like your real child
and always watch over him.
So today I want to make it formal.
Everyone will know that you are Tian's second mother.
But I don't want to…
Aunt Bua.
You don't want to be my mother?
Tian.
Please.
Tian has been kneeling down for a while now. His kneels hurt.
Hurry, Tian. Give her the tea.
Tian.
Madam Li must have a plan.
Bua, eat more.
Thank you, Madam.
Have some vegetables, Bua.
Thanks.
Here yours, sir.
Today we're having dinner together.
I really have good appetite.
Li, thank you
for being generous to Bua.
I'm the one who has to thank her
for taking care of Tian for more than ten years.
Today, I let Tian be your son as well.
Hope you love, care for and protect Tian
just like a mother should do for her child.
Yes, Madam.
So that's why!
You want Bua to protect Tian.
What did he do?
Why does he need two mothers to protect him?
Mom.
Chan.
Is it very painful for you to see Li and Bua getting along well?
Instead of being happy that our family lives peacefully,
you keep nitpicking.
When I say something,
it turns out that I'm slandering others, right?
You always cause trouble.
You'd better take your time to take care of Yang.
So he won't be ridiculous like this.
Father, please calm down.
Yang was not that ridiculous at all.
Don't pretend to help him!
Chan.
Is Yang my child alone?
Isn't he your son as well?
Why is it my fault to raise the kid alone?
Why don't you think that it's because you don't love your sons equally?
Mom, that's okay.
Don't say anything that is not auspicious.
There are good food here. Let's eat.
Because of you. You are like this.
Not serious about anything.
Listen carefully.
If I didn't think Yang is my son,
I would have drove you and him out earlier.
Please stop, Sir.
Right, I slander other people.
And my son is ridiculous.
There's nothing good about the two of us at all, right?
Mom.
Chan.
Sir, don't be mad at this nonsense.
Come on.
Let's eat.
Please excuse me.
You see it now?
He's never care about us.
No matter what I say or do,
It is annoying in his eyes.
I'm the daughter of a lord.
But your father listens to that low-class opera lead actress like Li rather than me.
It's okay.
It's alright.
In the past, I used to think
that if you behave well and do your job,
your father probably appreciates the two of us more.
But I know now. No matter how good we are,
we'll just stay in the same place.
You know why?
Because I'm just the second wife.
I always have to be under the first wife.
No one respects and listens to me.
Mom, listen to me.
No matter what Father or whoever says,
but for me,
you are the most valuable. No need to be praised by anyone.
If it were only me,
I got used to it.
But I couldn't bear to see you as his subordinate for the rest of your life.
So I struggle to do everything for you.
When I know that Tian has a big secret
to the extent that Madam Li struggled to cover it up, I can't let go of this.
But I don't want you to interfere.
Do you know it's dangerous?
Taking a risk it better than living under the wicked.
I will prove that she killed people to hide a secret for Tian.
Evil people shouldn't live a good life.
Noi.
The newspaper announced that a new mall has opened. There's a lot of stuff there.
Do you think they will accept more workers?
Oh my lady.
Do you really have to find jobs?
I've studied a lot. I should go out and earn money.
Or …
Should I work at this newspaper?
I'm an educated woman. I won't starve to death.
Come, come, come in
Please go wait over there.
Noi, take them to wait over there first.
Yes, please.
Who are they, Father?
Well …
I see that you look for jobs seriously.
I am not at ease as well.
I want to make money too.
Now, luck is on our side.
These people told me that the Japanese soldiers are selling out the oil .
They will sell it to us cheaply.
After receiving the oil, we'll sell it further.
It will be very profitable.
Did they secretly stole the oil from the Japanese?
Hey, even they stole it,
we know how much the Japanese soldiers
are taking advantage of our country,
so they deserve it.
If we get the oil, it must sell well.
We will be able become a millionaire like before.
This is the advantage of war.
Father.
Don't scold me.
Just this one time.
Later, if you are married to Tian,
we won't suffer anymore.
Okay?
Li
What's the matter.
About Dong…
I let people search for his relatives but they couldn't find them.
The body was taken out of the water.
It shouldn't be stored for a very long time.
I think we should hurry and cremate it.
That's true.
He died unnaturally and in the water.
But I think I think we shouldn't burn it yet.
Why?
When the body was found,
all the workers heard Chan said
that you may be involved in his death.
If we hurry to burn it now,
people will think that we are hiding something.
But the evidence is clear already
that Dong stole the money and ran away.
Don't you believe me and still doubt in me?
I believe in the evidence.
If you didn't do it,
you don't have to worry.
One more thing,
due to Zhang's death last time,
the association members haven't got along well like before.
Maybe someone will take this opportunity to frame you again.
Wait another seven days.
If relatives or someone else doesn't complain about Dong's death,
until that day, we can burn the body.
So that no one can accuse us.
Hurry up and look at Dong's body.
I'm sure there must be something.
Otherwise, Madam Li won't care about his body and hurry for the cremation.
There's probably nothing.
because I didn't see any wounds or bruises when he was brought out from the water.
No wounds and no injuries,
but he may not drown normally.
Have you forgotten that Jia is good at concocting pills?
She might use poison to kill Dong and threw him into the water.
Yes, Madam.
Dong, my master ordered me to do.
I didn't insult you at all.
Oh, Mr. Yang. I was so shocked. I thought it was Dong's ghost.
I'm scared.
If it was Dong's ghost, he would have killed you for sure.
Why are you messing with his body?
No, it's Madam Chan.
It's nothing. Madam Chan doesn't know about it.
I came here on my own. I just wanted to pay homage to Dong's body.
Because when he was alive, I often argued with him.
Don't lie.
I saw you sneaking out of the house.
So I followed you here.
What did she tell you to do?
Hmm?
Someone's coming.
Are you really going to sleep here?
You don't have to watch over him actually.
There's nothing valuable in the coffin.
No one would steal it.
It's an order of my boss.
Up to you, I'll go get you a pillow and a mat.
Madam let Aunt Jia sleep here and watch over Dong's body herself?
You ca go now.
If someone sees Dong's body in this condition, we'll be in trouble.
What?
Did Madam Li let Jia sleep there and watch over the body?
Yes, Madam.
It means we're on the right direction. There must be something with the body.
Actually I almost got the information
if Mr. Yang didn't interfere it.
Now it's hard to go back or find evidence from the body.
What's wrong with my son?
He's always in my way all the time?
I understand that he loves and wants to protect his brother.
But I don't get it why he intervenes and helps conceal the murderer.
It's because this has something to do with Mr. Tian.
If Madam Li and Jia really did this,
the person who would be in trouble is Mr. Tian.
So Mr. Yang wants to help them.
So what are we going to do next?
Since we can't handle this by ourselves,
we have to lend other's hands to help us.
Are you really going to sleep here?
You don't have to watch over him actually.
There's nothing valuable in the coffin.
No one would steal it.
It's an order of my boss.
Why did Aunt Jia have to guard Dong's body?
What is she afraid of?
Lady Pin.
Are you here to see Tian? He's not here.
He's gone to the warehouse.
No. I'd like to see Aunt Li.
Madam Li is not here. She went out with Aunt Jia.
What about Mr. Song?
Father is not here too.
Lady.
Do you have any business?
Too bad, I'd like to ask them to help stop my father.
What did your father do?
No, sir.
No, please.
Lady Pin orders me to stop you from buying it.
Nangnoi.
Will you believe my daughter or me?
I believe Lady Pin.
But I don't believe you and I will buy it.
Stop right now.
Who is this Japanese soldier?
We …
We have been informed that someone had stolen the oil for sale.
Sir, don't harm my father.
He was deceived. We didn't mean to do so. I'm really sorry, sir.
Father.
Quiet!
The offender must be punished.
He must be strapped to the board
and received waterboarding.
You have misunderstood.
We didn't steal your oil.
If you don't believe me, come and see here.
There is only one tank of oil bought from a gas station. Other twos are plain water.
Right! Only one tank of oil.
Yes.
What? What do you mean?
Are you guys deceiving me?
Father, Father.
Sir, don't punish Father. He was fooled.
Yes, I really don't know.
But …
If there is one tank of oil and the rest is water,
that means I didn't steal oil. I'm not guilty.
What not guilty?
This is considered cooperation with them.
Impersonate Japanese soldiers
Sir, please don't pour oil into Father's mouth.
Please.
No.
Fine.
For the sake of your daughter's gratitude,
I will not press charges.
But don't do this again in the future.
Be obedient to your daughter.
Do you understand?
Yes, I will listen to my daughter from now on.
Good.
Enjoy your meal, Mr. Yang.
I'll buy this meal for you.
It's alright, you don't have much money now, right?
I'm still okay for this. You helped me today.
Otherwise, my father would probably got scammed and lost more money.
Then I think the noodles are too cheap.
For a Japanese soldier like me, I'd rather eat something more expensive.
If I report the Japanese soldiers that someone was impersonating them,
how do you think he will be punished?
So the noodles are fine for me.
Let's eat.
Boy.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
I'm so sorry.
Let's go.
Thank you for today.
But no matter what,
the only way I can save my palace is to marry Tian.
Lady Pin.
Tian definitely doesn't love you.
Do you really love him?
Tian is handsome, polite and kind.
Whoever gets married to him will be happy.
I didn't ask if you are getting married.
I asked if you love him.
It doesn't change a thing.
I will have to marry Tian for my palace's survival.
Anyway, thanks again for today.
I got to go back.
Don’t accompany me.
It's getting worse each day.
I don't know who else to ask for help to sort this out.
I think of you
as the only one I can count on.
Do you think Li has something to do with the death of a worker?
And what about Big Brother?
He doesn't say anything.
Honestly, I still couldn't find any evidence that could clearly sue Madam Li.
If this leaks out,
The Five Dragons Association will definitely be damaged.
But are you sure
that you really came here for this reason?
Not because you want to borrow my hands to get rid of Li and Tian
to let your son Yang to take the position of Big Brother?
Right?
I am joking.
Everyone knows how much you loves
and are loyal to the Song Family and our Five Dragons Association.
Yes, sir.
I have brought you the news. How you'll handle it
is up to you.
And I was sure that
no matter what you do, you are also loyal to the association just like me.
It's definitely not for your own benefit.
Do you think Mr. Ma will help us?
If he really help us, the Song family's reputation would be damaged.
Will Mr. Song be in trouble?
He's a talented man. He can handle this matter.
Besides, now we need to find a way to get Madam Li and Tian as quickly as possible.
Are you sure it's worth it?
If we get caught, the two of us will be in real trouble.
Doing this is like bringing enemies to our home.
So is there any other way?
Besides, I've already said it.
We can't fix anything now.
A man like Mr. Ma,
he won't let this matter go silent without doing anything absolutely.
I'm really curious
what method Mr. Ma will use to deal with Madam Li and Dong's body.
But can we trust Madam Chan?
I'm afraid she will harm us later after we help her.
Because if this plan fails,
Song won't probably be pleased that we mess with this matter.
Just let him be.
He can't even handle the incident in his own home.
How can he be the leader of our association.
Everyone knows about Chan and Li.
They are competing for power to make their own children be the leader.
So why do you help her and side with Chan?
I didn't help her.
I helps people who give me benefits.
If we succeed, Song Family and Big Brother's reputation would be tarnished.
We will use this to destroy his credibility
and remove Big Brother from the head position of the Five Dragons Association.
If you buy it as a gift for girls, they will definitely like it.
Hey.
Don't cry, good boy.
Where is your parents? Hmm?
I'm lost.
No. No. Don't harm me.
Help me, Mei. Help me. Help.
You.
How did you get here?
I thought you've already throw it away.
I think if see you again, I will return it.
But I can't return it now. It's already stained.
It's okay. You keep it.
So are you living here with your two siblings?
Yes.
My parents died when I was a kid.
Have you been raising them since you were a child?
In the past, there was an aunt next door who helped take care of us.
But she moved a long time ago.
You are so good.
I'm not.
If I were really good, my siblings would be happier by now.
You are really good.
Your brother and sister look happy for me.
Come on, let me help.
You got a splinter in your finger.
I'll take it out. It will hurt bit.
Thanks.
Here.
This is a film tape.
What is it? It was left outside, so I picked it up.
It's the film used for showing movie on the screen
to tell stories.
I don't know it. I've never seen it. I want to see it.
Such a pity.
This is a war period. I can't take you two to watch it.
How about this?
I will find a movie for you to watch. I promise.
Really? Promise me.
That day, when Bai Suzhen decided to come down to the human world,
she found love with a handsome young man
and gave birth to a baby named Lin.
However, a priest intervene.
It's dark outside.
Let's go. I'll see you out.
Thank you very much for sending my brother home today.
Actually, I pass this area often
but never been in this this alley.
Otherwise,
The two of us must have known each other sooner.
Alright, it's the main road now.
Some day later,
shall we take the kids out for dessert? I have a favorite shop.
I think the kids will like it.
I don't think so.
Don't come here again.
Why?
My world is like this alley.
You just walk past and then leave.
You shouldn't associate with it.
The two of us just happened to meet.
My world and your world are different worlds.
But for me, we all live in the same world.
Whether you are rich or poor,
we can be friends.
You say this because you don't know my world.
Good luck.
Stop, don't move the body anywhere.
Open it.
What should we do?
Whoever got involved in Dong's death
and if it affects on the Five Dragons Association,
I will punish that person until the very end.
If you are in trouble, come to me. My father can help you.
Who is your father?
These orchids can help us protect Mr. Tian's secret.
Or is Mother with Aunt Jia?