♫ How much pain and sadness can be stuffed into one heart? ♫
♫ One sentence can change the ending forever ♫
♫ Tired of attacking and defending ♫
♫ I'd rather be that loser ♫
♫ You need not give in ♫
♫ Bruised black and blue, whoever's sincerity gets trampled on ♫
♫ I don't want to resist anymore ♫
♫ We just want to hear the answer we want in love ♫
♫ You need not give in ♫
♫ I surrender my pride, I miss the way I loved you originally ♫
♫ Slowly forgetting ♫
♫ You and I are the same ♫
(Before We Get Married)(Episode 3)
If I could press a button to delete everything that happened that night,
I would gladly press it.
Who are you? You want to sell my house?
I'm doing it for your own good.
What a coincidence, Weiwei.
So, the person who wants to buy the house is your boyfriend?
Do you want to consider becoming friends with me?
I will never be your friend!
- Kiss me.    - Are you crazy?!
Weiwei.
Be more natural. You look so nervous; people are going to be suspicious.
When can we stop sneaking around like this?
When can we announce that we've been dating for three years?
And that we're looking to buy a house and then getting married?
It’s not like you don’t know that the boss doesn’t like office relationships.
So when we get married, we don't have to invite any guests and go public?
Of course, we do. It's just...
We need to plan it out.
- I know you're good at planning.- Shh.
Then, when do you plan on going public?
Let's wait until we've bought a house and are preparing to get married.
If you tell the boss now, he'll turn against you right away.
I'm also scared that the boss is going to turn against us. That's why we need to plan ahead.
Okay. I know.
I already talked to the landlord. He will have someone take care of the floor problem.
You're really going to buy that tilted house?
You're so weird. You're the one who told me to ask the landlord to fix the problem with the floor.
Unless... you ask your classmate Gao Ziyuan about their house.
I don't want to. I'm going to a meeting.
Hey...
Boss, even if you're trying to punish me for my mistakes earlier,
you can't just delete all my messages with Kefei. That's really cruel.
I did it for your own good. You've put enough cost and effort into this investment.
It's clearly unable to be saved. If you continue on, I guarantee things will become too complicated.
How can love be an investment target?
I'm so serious about her. I'll give it my all.
Who taught you that love has no costs?
Did you know that in the end, it will be imbalanced? The ending will be tragic?
The point is, you want me to stop before I even start? I don't care. You have to make it up to me.
I need to make it up to you?
Just help me think of a way to chase Kefei.
If I go now, I'll get shot down for sure.
Fine.
If I go, you won't get a turn.
Boss, just help me think of a way. Just help me. You must help me.
I'm begging you.
(Are you working overtime?)
(It's raining heavily, did you bring an umbrella?)
(I brought an umbrella and I'm on my way home.)(I'll talk to you when I get home.)
Zhou Weiwei! Zhou Weiwei!
What are you doing?
Are you all right? I just saw you run in the rain to the corner store and I thought you would buy an umbrella or a raincoat.
You just took a piece of cardboard and ran out. Are you crazy?
You're the crazy one! I already have an umbrella at home. Why should I buy another one?
Also, one umbrella costs NT$105. That's enough for two meals!
All right. Then where's 321? (N.B. 321 or "San Er Yi" sounds like the last character of Li Haoyi's name)
His name is Li Haoyi. If he bikes here to pick me up, he will get rained on, too. Without him knowing, I'd rather just get rained on alone.
Does he know you have to work overtime? If he knew, why didn't he just stay and wait?
Why do you care so much?
Because if it were me, I wouldn't let you get soaked.
I've told you before, don't try to get close to me.
I've already deleted you.
Sorry.
That day when you came to look at my house, I was overboard.
That's why I wanted to wait for you here today so that I could properly apologize to you.
So, you've been waiting here since you got off work?
I wanted to gamble to see if I could run into you. Who would have thought...
I would have run into an idiot who used a cardboard box to run in the rain.
Is this your attitude for apologizing?
Sorry.
Whatever.
Let me take you home.
No need. I can go by myself.
Then I’ll give you an umbrella.
Won't Ziyuan look for you if you go home so late?
Zhou Weiwei, Ziyuan is only a family member.
Okay.
Do you have time later?
Since I bought you an umbrella, will you listen to a song with me?
♫ Turn on the radio ♫
♫ Don’t wanna care anymore ♫
♫ Perhaps not having to promise ♫
♫ is more carefree ♫
♫ And you won't be heavily shackled♫
♫ Turn off your favorite song ♫
♫ Just like there’s nothing wrong ♫
♫ Perhaps time will make this to be forgotten ♫
♫ And it will be taken as a misunderstanding ♫
♫ Oh, have you ever loved me? ♫
♫ Have you ever thought of me ♫
Who's the romantic guy?
Gifting flowers? How outdated.
- You don't want them? Then give them to me! - Hey!
Get your hands away. So rude. It's time for work.
Are you here to watch a drama or play? Get to work.
What time is it?
What?
Does receiving those flowers make you emotional?
Hello? Who am I? I'm Han Kefei.
I'm not that irrational, okay?
(I have a secret hidden in the flowers. Can you taste it?)
Sister Ziyuan, why did you send me another present?
Thank you, Sister Ziyuan.
Okay, I understand.
Okay. Bye-bye.
- When did this happen? - Just now.
What did she say to you?
She said it's all ready. It's all arranged for me to go with you to venture capital funds.
She even has to butt into your business?
She means well. Besides, wherever you go, that's where I should be.
I already wanted to go anyway. Just think of it as a shortcut.
(Chocola BB)
You’re back. Go rest for a bit. I’ll go pour a cup of water for you.
You bought stuff again?
Yup. I just bought some daily use stuff.
Drink some water first.
There were two people who came to see the house today.
But they seem to have a budget problem.
Today, I went to look at the house on the paper in your hands.
The inside is about 198 square meters. Plus, all the public facilities, it’s almost 330 square meters.
- That’s enough.- It’s just I—
You’re right 198 square meters is enough.
It's just, I wanted to find something bigger.
You know that I’m not talking about that.
Oh right. Within these are some presents to give to your new coworkers.
Later, I'll make a list of whose present is whose. That way you won't get them mixed up.
Are you done?
Can you not meddle in my life or my work?
Whether you want to swipe my no-limit credit card to buy presents, sell or buy a house,
or buy even more gifts for my coworkers, I'm fine if you do any of that.
But you even butt into Baiyang's business.
All these years, he's been with you and working so hard.
Is it wrong of me to want him to also find a better opportunity for advancement?
Kehuan, everything that I do
is all for your sake.
Stop saying that everything you do is for me.
And please stop saying that everything you do is for our future.
You know, that by doing this, you're creating a bigger distance between us.
That's why I'm trying to change.
The reason I want to sell this place and buy a new one is so that I can change our current situation.
It can't be changed.
Kehuan,
you promised my mom that
you would take good care of Ziting and me.
I can do what I promised your mom. But not with your methods!
Then, tell me what kind of method do you plan on using?
As long as I can always be with you,
I am willing to do whatever it takes as long as I can stay by your side to love you.
Just use your methods. I don't care.
Kehuan!
I said just use your methods!
♫ Love runs too deep ♫
♫ You need to not give in, tears ♫
♫ don’t lie. Emotions are being kidnapped ♫
- Have you noticed that within these few years, we've—  - I have noticed.
I've noticed that you've been able to do what you promised my mom before she passed away.
She told you to take care of me and Ziting,
and then buy a bigger apartment before we get married. You're doing that right now, aren't you?
Kehuan, everything I do is for you.
As long as I can always be with you,
I am willing to do whatever it takes as long as I can stay by your side to love you.
The number you are trying to call is currently unavailable.
Please try again later. Thank you.
Zhou Weiwei.
Wow.
Sorry. It's you?
How did I end up liking someone as rough and dresses as messy as you?
How else should I dress when taking out the trash? Formal attire?
Not bad. You can even talk back now.
Looks like our relationship has become closer.
Yeah, right. How did you know I lived here?
As long as I, Chu Kehuan, want to find someone, I will find them.
Are you a perverted stalker?
This pervert has something to tell you.
If it's too perverted, I don't want to hear it.
You can save NT$8,000,000 on this pervert's house.
But, of course, perverts have conditions, too.
If you want to save NT$8,000,000, you must spend a night with me.
You pervert! Are you crazy? Why should I spend the night with you?
Who do you think you are? Have you no shame? Who wants to sleep with you?
What are you saying? What do you take me for?
Do you agree?
Who said I agreed? Are you crazy?
You shouted it for the whole world to hear. See, even they heard.
Isn't that considered agreeing?
Chu Kehuan, I can pretend that what you just said was a joke.
But if you say
- anything related to—  -Do you want to consider
the NT$8,000,000 again? This way the NT$32,000,000 will become NT$24,000,000.
It's a big difference.
Chu Kehuan... get lost!
Zhou Weiwei.
You and Chu Kehuan are really...?
Yeah, right! You guys are all crazy!
Zhou Weiwei, I'll wait for your answer.
Go die! You pervert!
Not only are you rough, but you're violent.
Stop pretending.
Helping me wax? Two-faced.
Hypocrite.
Does Chu Kehuan want to go out with you?
No.
Look into my eyes and tell me the truth.
No. He’s just a crazy person.
I also want to believe you.
How can someone like Chu Kehuan want to be with someone...
...who dresses like you?
What’s wrong with me? Is there anyone who wears formal attire to take out the trash?
If he doesn’t want to go out with you and you don’t want to go out with him,
then can I have him then?
How many times have I told you already?
He is my university classmate’s boyfriend. You can't just eat him. You'll get diarrhea.
But...
But nothing. You can't have Chu Kehuan.
Why can’t I? With someone like Chu Kehuan,
I’d pay to spend the night with him.
You’d pay to be with him?
Yes.
If he would pay me, that would be better.
Is there a difference between this and prostitution?
Of course, there’s a difference.
Because I get to choose him, and it’s not him choosing me.
Let me make this clear, I get to choose him.
It's not him picking me, and he'll also be willing to pay me.
Everyone gets what they want. What’s wrong with that?
You can save NT$8,000,000 on this pervert's house.
But, of course, perverts have conditions, too.
If you want to save NT$8,000,000, you must spend a night with me.
To be honest.
If he did choose me, that means he has the need.
I’m happy and he’s satisfied. No one died and there’s no fire, so what’s wrong with that?
Zhou Weiwei, do you have fantasies about Chu Kehuan? Or have you guys already—
We haven’t. How many times did I tell you? I really haven’t.
I was just asking. Why are you getting all worked up?
But don’t forget. You have to share good things with good friends.
Do these things need to be shared?
Why not?
Do you expect me to look for Yan Baiyang every time and spoil the fun?
Kefei, are you happy?
Not bad.
So can I?
Yeah, you can.
Can you what?
You accepted my flowers and asked me to come out.
So, you’re willing to go out with me?
- What are you saying? - What did I say wrong?
You always ruin the mood.
I just finished.
We just finished and he said, "Be my girlfriend."
Who am I? I’m Han Kefei.
How could I give up a whole forest for just one tree? I’m not an idiot.
Next time, could you buy a better one? This one hurts so much.
Everyone uses beeswax nowadays.
Remember, good things need to be shared with good friends.
♫ The sky turns dark, the lights turn on, the day is over ♫
♫ Quickly shuttling on the way home ♫
Am I crazy?
♫ Living in a routine, quietly listening to songs ♫
I must be crazy.
♫ Where is the heart floating? ♫
♫ You need to not give in, tears ♫
♫ don’t lie. Emotions are being kidnapped ♫
Kehuan, Ziting is back.
- Long time no see, Brother Kehuan.- Long time no see.
Why are you back already? Didn’t you say you were coming back next week?
Right? She didn’t tell me until she landed in Taiwan. I almost didn’t make it to pick her up.
I didn’t ask for you to pick me up. I wanted to take the airplane subway but you didn’t allow me.
- How are you? - I’m pretty good.
So you’re staying here for good now?
Yup. But I already arranged everything before I left New York.
They will send me my recommendation letter in the next two days.
Don’t worry. I’m just living here for a little while.
I’ll move out once I find a place. I won’t be a bother to you guys for too long.
You better hurry. We’re selling the apartment soon.
You’re selling the apartment?
You guys are going to move to a new house when you guys get married?
You must be tired. Go rest and I’ll treat you to a meal later.
Ziting, you stayed in America for so long and you only have these two suitcases?
There’s more. The rest are being shipped here.
Kehuan, since Ziting is back,
do you want to come back to our bedroom and not sleep in the guest room?
Gao Ziyuan, I want to drink coffee.
Okay.
Are you and Brother Kehuan okay?
Yeah. We’re okay.
You haven't had my coffee in a long time. Do you miss it a lot?
What are you boasting about. It’s not even super good.
You can't buy it anywhere else. It's a Gao Ziyuan special.
Keep the change.
Weiwei!
- Dad! Over here.  - Uncle.
Long time no see. Why do you look skinnier since the last time?
No, I haven’t. I’m still the same.
Sorry for troubling you to come all the way from Kaohsiung to look at houses here.
It's no problem at all. Buying a house is a big deal.
Once you guys are settled and married, I’ll be happy, too.
Where's the house?
- It’s in that alley. - In there?
Let’s go. I’ll show you.
How come you’re looking at a house in an alleyway?
- It’s quiet in there. - Quiet?
Right. It’s so loud on the main street.
Are you sure this is right? From the first floor all the way up, the walls are filled with mold.
The dampness is so strong. Right now is not a problem, but if you live here for a long time, who knows what kind of problems will happen.
Dad, we can’t do anything about it either.
What do you mean?
Let’s say you guys do move in here. It’s going to be so much trouble to have to patch the holes and make things waterproof.
NT$18,000,000 for this place? Are you kidding me?
The market price is going to be like this in Taipei. This apartment is within our budget.
It looks like you don’t even know how to make the calculations.
In the south, NT$18,000,000 can buy a terraced house.
You’re spending so much money and it doesn’t even have an elevator?
In the future, if Weiwei gets pregnant, you want her to climb the stairs with her big belly?
You’re willing to, but I’m not.
I’m not satisfied with this apartment.
No wonder I felt dizzy when I was taking the stairs up here.
This house is very special. It's tilted, huh?
Weiwei, don’t marry this kind of man. Don’t marry him.
Dad, how could you say that?
Did I say something wrong? A man should take care of his wife and child.
Don’t let your wife have worries. When your mom was still here, I treated her like a queen.
And you? You even dare to buy a tilted house?
But you can’t attack me like this. According to our budget,
this is the best apartment we could find.
Who are you trying to lie to? How could there be no decent apartment in all of Taipei?
It’s not like there isn’t. It’s just the one we like is NT$32,000,000.
I’ll show you.
Here.
Is there no room for negotiation?
The owner is Weiwei’s classmate’s boyfriend.
Weiwei, why don’t you personally talk to her?
- I... - Actually, they are willing to reduce the price.
But Weiwei didn’t want to owe them anything.
So, in the end, we didn’t discuss it.
Weiwei was right to think that way.
How about this? If you guys really like it, I can take out my savings to help you guys with the down payment.
You can’t. Uncle, you worked hard your whole life to make that money.
It’s bad enough Haoyi doesn’t give you an allowance.
It’s okay. If I’m full, the whole family is full. As long as you guys are happy, I’m happy.
Weiwei, don’t forget to leave a room for me in the new apartment.
Uncle, don’t say that.
Actually, I've thought about this already. We can rent a place first.
We can slowly look for a house to buy.
Weiwei, Haoyi doesn’t have many achievements and has troubled you.
But I can understand why he wants to buy an apartment so badly.
Haoyi's mom passed away when he was in the fourth grade.
As a single man, I wasn’t able to take good care of him.
Plus, my work made it so that we had to transfer everywhere.
We would have to move at least every two years.
We never had a safe and comforting place to live. So he was unable to make intimate friends.
Although Haoyi never complained,
I was sad to see his disappointed face every time we moved.
Moving schools and saying goodbye to friends.
Then getting used to a new environment is very hard.
Dad.
Weiwei, Haoyi just wants a place that’s his own.
He doesn’t want to have to keep moving and wants to feel a sense of security. I can understand this.
I hope you can understand his persistence to want to buy an apartment.
- Sorry.  - Uncle, don’t say that.
Okay, Dad, it’s okay.
We can keep discussing this; we’re not in a rush to buy.
What is there to discuss? Let’s up our budget by NT$2,000,000.
There’s no more need for discussion. You just need to find a place that Weiwei is satisfied with.
Okay.
I didn’t know the reason you wanted to buy an apartment was so complicated.
My dad was being too dramatic.
Besides, I’m not overly sensitive.
Saying these things in front of you is like looking for sympathy. It’s so girly.
But if you don’t say it, how can I help take some of your burden?
I don’t want you to take some of the burden.
These past three years you’ve been willing to buy a place with me.
I made you scrimp and save, and sacrifice your quality of life.
It's been hard on you.
I've thought about it for the last couple of days.
Actually, you are my home.
So I'm okay with renting a house.
♫ Love runs too deep ♫
♫ You need to not give in, tears don’t lie ♫
♫ Emotions are being kidnapped ♫
I thought you guys were going to take me to a night market or a Chinese restaurant.
I've been craving soup dumplings and sour and spicy soup.
Gao Ziting, you're so difficult.
You want soup instead of this high-grade steak?
No wonder you gave up such a well paying job in the US. I don't know what you're thinking.
I missed you.
Besides, I never intended to stay in the US forever.
After finishing graduate school,
I only worked the extra two years to save money to repay Brother Kehuan.
Kehuan, thank you.
I calculated I probably spent NT$2,000,000 the last couple of years. I'm now repaying you.
Do you still have money if you're giving this back?
Relax, I can take care of myelf.
I'm not like you, so lucky to have someone pampering you.
Hey. What do you mean by that?
Nothing.
This is the way you guys live. I don't have an opinion, but I have my own principles.
Brother Kehuan, if you don't take this Bank of America check,
I'll get upset.
Okay, I'll accept it.
I wish you success in your future.
Thanks. That really lessens my burdens.
Even though Mom told you to look after us before she died,
you don't have to worry about me. I can be independent.
But Mom said...
That's her wishful thinking.
Kehuan, I've already organized your evening plans for your first day on the job.
I organized some bankers and investors to have dinner together.
You can network and ask them for help in the future.
You're even controlling Kehuan's networking obligations. Isn't that crossing a line?
I'm helping him share the load.
This way he doesn't have to worry about anything and just focus on work.
Am I wrong?
Haoyi just wants a house of his own.
So, he doesn't have to keep moving house without a sense of security. I get it.
And I hope you can understand why he wants to buy a house so desperately.
Actually, you are my home.
NT$8,000,000. There's a big difference between NT$32,000,000 and NT$24,000,000.
If you want to save NT$8,000,000, you must spend a night with me.
If one day, we're faced with some difficulty,
and one of us had to sacrifice something...
Of course, I should be the one to sacrifice. How could I let you go?
As long as it's not murder or arson and doesn't harm another person,
I'm willing to do anything.
Good morning.
Zhou Weiwei.
Do you need anything?
Of course, that's why I came looking for you.
What do you need?
I accept.
Accept what?
Your conditions for the NT$8,000,000 discount.
Okay. I'll pick the location. You pick the time.
Let's do Saturday.
(Did you leave yet? Do you need me to take you to the bus stop?)
(Recording)
(Voice recording cancelled)
(I'm almost at the bus stop already.)
(Pervert)
Hello?
Hold on. I’ll be down once I change my clothes.
No need to rush. Take your time.
I’ll give you 30 more mins. Take your time to fix yourself up.
Wear something pretty. Don’t wear what you wore when you were throwing away trash.
Considering I’m paying NT$8,000,000.
I only have those kinds of clothes.
From what I understand, every girl has at least one set of pretty clothes in their closet
but doesn’t usually wear them. Just wear that one.
What are you doing?
I’m not doing anything.
You’re not doing anything, yet you’re dressed so pretty. Did you get a boyfriend?
No, I didn’t.
No? I’m a lie detector. Don’t lie to me.
I want to go back to Yilan to visit my mother.
I haven’t seen Auntie in a long time. I miss her, I’ll go with you!
Hey. Why would you go?
Fine, I'm going back home to go on a blind date.
That makes more sense.
Zhou Weiwei, you’re going on a blind date.
You didn't even wear false eyelashes or apply any blush. Which shoes are you planning to wear?
I've matched it (with my outfit).
I wish you happiness.
Good luck.
Can you stop looking at me like that? It’s making me uncomfortable.
You’re really beautiful.
Someone said that eight million dollar merchandise must be packaged to be valuable. This is my most valuable outfit.
Even if you’re not satisfied, I can’t do anything about it.
I’m satisfied.
Please get in.
Can you concentrate on driving?
I’m very concentrated.
Where are you?
I’m on my way. There’s still some time before I arrive.
Mwah.
You’re about to spend the night with another man.
You are still sending a "kissing" sticker to your boyfriend. Like this, it isn't really good? Right?
Are you lying to me, him or yourself?
You’re not going to say anything? Are you embarrassed or shy?
Where exactly are we going?
It's the countryside. Can't you make it out? I like nature.
Oh, that's right! That "321" is your colleague.
I heard your boss doesn’t like office relationships.
And since you guys are still working there, that means no one has discovered you two.
You’re very good at keeping a secret.
Do you like it?
I reserved the whole place.
So today, we’re here for a BBQ?
What? You’re not satisfied with my arrangements?
In that case, we can also immediately go and find a hotel to stay in.
That’s not what I meant. I just think it’s kind of weird.
There’s someone to help us cook the meat, the tent is already set up, there are plenty to serve us food and drinks. Is this good?
That’s why I think it’s weird.
I want to buy cola.
I need to buy cola.
I really want to buy cola.
I. want. to. buy...
Cola.
(I want to buy cola.)
This is embarrassing.
(Are you sure you want to delete this post?) (delete)
(You have a new friend notification)
"One single root."
"I also want to buy cola."
- You are "a single root"?  - Yes
I also have another nickname.
You’re amazing.
It’s nothing. I’m just cooking skewers.
It’s almost done.
I’m not in a rush.
Thank you.
Take your time.
♫ Love runs too deep ♫
♫ You need to not give in, tears ♫
♫ don’t lie. Emotions are being kidnapped ♫
I really don't understand you rich people.
Camping is only fun when you do things yourself.
Who camps with help?
Why wouldn't you just go stay at a hotel and eat at a restaurant?
You look so serious grilling the meat.
And now you're eating so happily.
You seem to have forgotten the reason you're here.
I haven't. I was just looking for something to do. To take my mind off it.
I almost forgot. Today is just a transaction.
It's a bit awkward.
Have some wine. It'll dissolve the tension.
How are you?
Honestly. Really good.
You are the first one to understand what "Buy cola" means.
It's not difficult. "Make love"  (N.B. To buy cola in Chinese "Mai Ke Le" phonetically sounds like "make love.")
Kefei, even though I keep telling myself not to make any more mistakes.
- But I have to honestly face my...  - No.
Don't say anything.
Kefei. Kefei, don't ignore me.
Kefei, listen to me.
You listen to me.
You've already released all your tension.
Your lust has come to an end. None of your feelings were real.
Now walk out the door. Once you're out, you'll forget.
Or you can go have a shower.
When the cold water rains over you, you'll forget everything.
Yan Baiyang, don't say things that make me angry anymore.
Kefei,
I want to take you home.
Say goodnight to you downstairs.
And watch as you head inside.
Kefei, let's date.
Hello? Please get me an ambulance.
Because there's a psycho kneeling in front of me saying he wants to date.
Please send a few people
to capture him, shackle him, lock him up.
Don't let this psycho appear in front of me. Understand?
Here.
Take it.
What about it?
Cherish this apple.
What do you mean?
This is a Japanese import. Sun Fuji apple.
Sun Fuji apple?
I've seen this online. It costs more than NT$10,000 per apple.
That's enough to feed me for 3 months. You're going to eat this?
Of course. That's why I said cherish it.
Here. I'll go wash it.
Wait.
It's very expensive.
Why? I bought it to eat it.
No.
- I'm going to wash it  - That's such a waste!
- What do you mean "a waste"? Let me wash it.  - No! Don't waste it.
- No it's fine.  - No!
Zhou Weiwei!
Zhou Weiwei, what are you doing? Zhou Weiwei!
I found it.
I've got it.
Zhou Weiwei, you are the dumbest and most serious girl I've ever seen.
You shouldn't waste it.
No. Let me go!
I won't let go.
If I can be your man,
I will cherish you forever.
Can you turn the light off?
Are you nervous?
Tell me.
Why did you agree to spend the night with me?
I just wanted to make Haoyi happy.
Then, does 321 know you were coming? (N.B. He's talking about Li Haoyi)
Of course, he doesn't know.
I just thought that if we could save NT$8,000,000 on the house,
we would be able to fulfill our dreams.
So, that's why I'm here.
Is it your dream? Or his dream?
You made such a huge decision. You're here to spend the night with me behind his back.
You say you're trying to realize your dream.
What are you thinking?
Do you think he'll love you more?
Or do you think you'll love him more?
Do you think you're really great?
I'm not that great. I'm just...
I'm just doing this for our future.
I'm willing to sacrifice myself. Isn't that okay?
Sacrifice?
Do you think 321 will be grateful to you?
Do you even think he'll love you once he finds out you spent the night with me?
Idiot! You women are all the same.
You think your sacrifices are so great. It's actually abduction and blackmail.
Do you know how much pressure your sacrifices put on us?
You're like this. Gao Ziyuan is like this, too.
Don't you know your sacrifices drain the love between two people until nothing is left?
How dare you?
How dare you use your sacrifices to control someone else's future.
The deal is off. I'm not selling the house anymore.
♫ Love runs too deep ♫
♫ You need to not give in, tears don’t lie ♫
♫ Emotions are being kidnapped ♫
You must be so busy buying all this stuff, huh?
You didn't have any time to answer my call. I'm super hungry.
I'm sorry.
I was thinking that Kehuan is taking office as the CEO soon,
so I'd better make use of this time and buy some stuff to get everything in order for him.
That way, he can live up to his reputation.
It looks like you've bought a lot in just the few days that I've been back.
Brother Kehuan doesn't have a problem with it?
He spoils me. He knows I'm doing it for his own good.
He loves me.
In the few days I've been back, I'm getting a vibe that you and Brother Kehuan have become
very polite. It feels like there's a distance between you two.
He's just busy.
We've been together for ten years already. Even the most passionate of romances will fizzle out into familial affection.
It's like being family, so I'm able to accept that distance you speak of.
I can understand everything Kehuan does.
In the future, don't call him Brother Kehuan. Call him your brother-in-law.
You guys aren't even married yet.
We will get married.
It's so late now. Brother Kehuan isn't home yet.
Don't you need to call him and ask what he's up to?
He'll come home when it's time.
(Baiyang)
Weiwei, you're home?
I'm home.
You look terrible. Did your blind date go badly?
Hello, is anyone home?
Did you fall into the water? Why aren't you talking?
Boss, I really don't understand.
Are these living things called women that difficult to understand? I feel like I'm giving her my heart and soul,
yet she hits me, yells at me, and tells me not to meet with her again. Why is that?
Just because I told you not to confess to her before the act doesn't mean you can confess right after.
I know, but I couldn't resist. I couldn't do it.
So what now? You failed, so you're trying to save the relationship?
That's right. I'm thinking about giving her one pearl every month.
After some time, it can be strung into a necklace. If she doesn't accept it, I'll just consider it a regular investment.
Okay, then go take a look. If you need help, just call me.
You're not going to look with me?
Are you dating her or am I?
Okay.
I want to buy an engagement ring.
No problem. Do you want to prefer to see our .50-carat or 1-carat rings?
Let me think.
I prepared these for you. Please take a look.
I really don't know too much about this. May I ask which kind you girls prefer?
Of course, the larger the better.
The larger the better.
If it were me, I wouldn't pick these.
Mr. Chu, what a coincidence!
Diamonds increase in value as they increase in size.
It's not based on how much area is covered by all the melee diamonds.
It looks like you have a lot of experience in this field.
Are you saying that I'm a womanizer?
No, I didn't mean that, Mr. Chu. I meant, uh—
Don't get anxious. I'm just kidding.
So, you're getting ready to propose to Weiwei?
That's right.
I thought it over. We keep having issues buying a house, but I can't keep delaying this with Weiwei.
We'll talk about buying a house later.
I set aside some of the budget for our house to buy a ring and propose to her.
But in order to keep it a secret, I can't discuss it with Weiwei either.
I had to do my own research online.
And then you showed up here with such useful advice!
So, you need me to give you recommendations?
I need it badly.
- Weiwei is probably a very earnest person, right?- Yes.
So, she wouldn't like anything too flamboyant, right?
No, she wouldn't.
Then, we can choose a few that are simple and natural.
Miss, can you help us pick out a few that have a simple design?
- We want a single diamond without any melee diamonds.- Okay.
- Thank you.- Thank you.
I can only help you up to this point. The rest is up to you.
Thank you, Mr. Chu.
Good luck.
♫ Clarity ♫
♫ I can only rely on my dreamland ♫
♫ You must have heard ♫
♫ them say that I speak of you ♫
♫ It's just like how you look for them to vent about the past ♫
♫ It's difficult to resist ♫
♫ Memories ♫
♫ I reply, yearning is like a song ♫
♫ Playing in a loop ♫
♫ The prelude is just meant to set off the chorus ♫
♫ When memories boil out ♫
♫ Paired with a husky timbre ♫
♫ It covers up all the yearning and reluctance to part ♫
♫ Listening to this song ♫
♫ Hearing the bitterness between the lines ♫
♫ Choosing to let go because it was so happy before ♫
♫ Both of us have new choices ♫
(Next)
Marry me.
Do you know why I want to sell the house to you?
It's because we share a memory there.
I hope you can clearly listen to what I'm saying.
- We're already—- I know. Temporarily separated, right?
I really miss you.
Leave with me, right now.
♫ Closing the door, returning to real life ♫
♫ Shedding this skin, lazing around ♫
♫ Living freely ♫
♫ Neither bad nor good, it's just one person hanging on ♫
♫ Love runs too deep♫
♫ I miss you more than before ♫
♫ I've been forcing a smile all these years ♫
♫ Trying hard to live and be a better person ♫
♫ Believing that time will always take something away ♫
♫ Love is hard to give up ♫
♫ I love you more than before ♫
♫ Never having any talent for love ♫
♫ Being too earnest teaches you after getting hurt once ♫
♫ Some passersby in life ♫
♫ Can't be forgotten ♫