I'm really sorry about yesterday
I'm not usually the type who
makes mistakes when drinking
but yesterday I drank too much
Forty-five thousand won
Excuse me?
The bill from that bar yesterday
I was completely out of it
so I paid and left
Oh, yes!
I'll transfer it right away
Oh, by any chance yesterday...
nothing else special happened, right?
What kind of thing?
Well, yesterday
I don't remember very well
I clearly remember calling you
after drinking yesterday
but when I woke up in the morning
I was undressed
and you were hugging me tightly
So maybe...
Do I look desperate?
Excuse me?
In your eyes
do I look so desperate that I'd
sleep with just anyone?
No
Phew
Hold me...
Hold me
I just wanted to sleep
What?
But you kept bothering me
so I had no choice but to tie you up and sleep
I'm really sorry about everything
How long has it been since you broke up?
About a month
Well, it's not like I don't understand how hard it is
but still, you shouldn't say
you want to die so easily
I'm going to drop the formalities
since you seem younger than me
Ah, okay hyung
Sit comfortably
Yes
If you really thought about dying, you should do it quietly
without anyone knowing, planning it thoroughly
and executing it
If you threaten others saying you'll die
you just become an easy person
Even when you go, you should
remain as a cool person, shouldn't you?
I'm kidding
If you want to die
stay busy enough to die
Then this emotion will become dull
and memories will become hazy
Hazy memories don't have much power
They just naturally get forgotten
without trying
Why?
Hyung, my stomach...
What?
Oh wait, wait!
The bathroom is over there! Over there!
Go
Hey hyung
Um...
Can I call you?
No
Don't do it
If you do, you die
Okay
Maybe at least your name?
Yes, are you coming?
What?
If you say that now
Yes
Someone else is coming as a replacement?
I understand
Yes
Writer Choi Iseop?
I came as a replacement model...
I'm Kim Wootae
This is the concept for this shoot
Rather than poses or actions
emotional expression is important, so close-up...
Oh, you're a photographer
Hyung, but
is this studio rented?
It's not personally owned, right?
I originally started this
as a part-time job
but somehow work kept coming in
so I'm doing it now
But
Oh, but how do we meet like this?
Isn't it really amazing?
I originally today
when I got the replacement offer
I was planning to rest today
But
you said
to stay busy enough to die
And we meet like this
Oh, right hyung
speak comfortably to me
Please take care of me today
Going to drink again?
No
I
will drink water
Since we met again like this, it's fate
it would be a shame to just part ways
Come on, cheers
Cheers
How did the photos turn out?
Since I don't have much experience yet
I've always been curious
Do I look too...
amateur?
Yeah
I like that you're honest, hyung
Ah
Can I call you hyung?
Or should I say photographer?
Whatever you want
Okay, hyung
But hyung, don't you date?
You look like you'd be really popular
Right?
You're popular, right?
Well, it's not like there's nothing
I knew it
Then what about now? Are you single?
Why?
Going to introduce me to a girl?
Oh, but I don't know many girls either
What type do you like, hyung?
I...
like men
Ah
I see
I'm leaving
I don't mind
Actually, there aren't people like that around me
so I never really thought about it
But people liking people, what's wrong with that?
There's no reason why we can't
be friends, right?
You...
weren't really thinking of dying, were you?
You were just being reckless, right?
You're right
Why did I do that then?
Good thing you answered
If Jiyoung had really answered...
I would be really embarrassed to death right now
I understand
I understand one hundred percent
How can you understand me, hyung?
Have you ever loved someone to death too?
A cool guy like you, hyung?
You probably would have just
said bye coolly
I've had that experience too
Loving someone to death
I also screamed that I'd die, threatened
cried and acted pathetically
I really thought the world was ending
Don't go
I miss you
Why am I being like this again?
Hyung...
Are you okay?
I should go sober up a bit
Hyung
Are you okay, hyung?
Are you okay?
I missed you
No, hyung
This right now...
Whoever you are
I don't care