The pregnancy is fake but the relationship is real
I have liked Tang Weiwei for a long, long time
I really want to be your boyfriend
I think
Be with you openly
You have been with me for one day
If you want to be so free, you can go to Weiwei
I am not familiar with Wei Wei
Dessert Shop Inspection
Do you know that there is a word called "No silver three hundred taels here"
original
I am your brother
now
I am your boyfriend
Come on, see for yourself
This is what I gave you on the opening day
You have to hide it when you go back
Don't be discovered by Uncle Tang
thanks
you are welcome
Let's go back
OK, good night
Bye-Bye
A new store opened
Take a look
congratulations
Auspicious opening
Congratulations
All right
What's wrong
I take you to the hospital
No
So busy
You go
There are so many of us, let's go
That Weiwei
Hurry up and take Lin Ran to the hospital
Brother is watching that store
It's okay to go
go
Everyone, let's work
It's all gone
Hey boss
Is such that
I heard
When a store opened here
Firecracker bombed
Our security issue must be dealt with
Yes Yes Yes
Good job
Good bye like this
Doctor
Is he seriously injured
He paints
Will it affect in the future?
Not less than
Bandages can be removed in three days
But you parents
Pay attention to later
How dangerous are fireworks
She is not a parent
Is my girlfriend
It's not like okay
Pay for medicine
Remember not to touch the water
Thank you doctor
Walk around
Xu Jian
You are really good
Weiwei has a brother like you
Really hell
You still have the mind to play games here
Let's work
Annoying
Straightforward
Add ten
Mr. Jin
The information you want
You sit down
good
You said
Do I care too much about the value
This B
Obviously not as good as A
Under what circumstances did you say
People would choose B
Lard blindfolded
B's data is really bad
There are also more deductions
It is really
Not suitable for marriage and love
But I think Editor Li is very cute
very good
You're happy
Mr. Jin
Time is almost up
I'll wait for you in the car
What made it so fragrant
Trotters soup
Complement shape
I'm not a pig
And me
But sister's
Sweetheart
It looks so fragrant, so good
Drink it
So delicious
Still thinking about the dessert shop
Forget it
Smile
How can I not want to
So many things happened right after opening
I think I might be cursed
You are really cursed
Cursed by Eros
Drink, drink, drink
really not bad
Isn't this the shop that hurt people?
Why are you still shopping here
Know i just forgot for a while
thanks for coming
thanks
welcome
How did you come
You don't find me
I'm not happy yet, I'm looking for you
I tell you
Lick the dog to the end
Everything
What are you talking about
No one compares himself as a dog
Don't make trouble
Let people see
where
Let me tell you Wei Wei
Think about it yourself
Our day before
How much time is together
now
How many days and how long have you left me in the cold
Sure enough, women are like this
Throw it away
Ruthless
Let you heal at home
How can you raise a bitter woman in a boudoir?
I can't leave the shop alone
Stay with you every day
alright, alright
I close early today
Go back with you
No need to go home
You will get off work later
I'll pick you up
Take you to a place
Then you go back first
Someone watching
Where is anyone here
Just the two of us
No one
Just someone
Go fast
Do you think this looks good
nice
can you hear me
Can hear
Tang Weiwei
share happiness
Happiness becomes double
Sharing sad
Sadness will be halved
What make you feel unhappy
you can tell me
Because a heart is small
And i'm big
If you mess up
Stuff all inside
That would feel very crowded
Classmate Lin Ran
Where did you learn these
What kind of chicken soup
I am coaxing you very seriously
Have been coaxed
Tang Weiwei
Can you learn to be a lover
Instead of being my sister
Can you respect me
I will work hard
slight
Let's get married
Didn't we get married long ago?
The kids are there
It turned out to be a dream
Although it's a dream
But progress is gratifying
victory is in sight
What's wrong
I asked you what's wrong
Burning brother
Ji Han memorized you
The exchange student quota has been cancelled
This matter
You have to ask the teacher
Go back to get a good understanding
Thank you director
do you understand
Goodbye director
director
Do you want to ask this
About the contract of the art exhibition
Already going through the process
no
It's about Ji Han
what are you thinking
I warn you
You have a great future now
Don't do stupid things
Are you listening?
I know your kindness
But that day
Things started because of me
You are so unclear
I remembered it to Ji Han
Inappropriate
One person to do things one person to do
Things start from me
The punishment should also be memorized
What do you know
Do you know that in such an exhibition
Fights
What a terrible thing
I tell you
All the media saw it
Over Europe
Very dissatisfied
Take it seriously
If it wasn't for me to suppress it for you
You think you can stay out
what are you thinking
director
For whatever reason, Lin Ran
She really did it first
Even if you lifted my office
I can't get my exchange student quota
What do you think school rules and disciplines are
Play house?
Why are you so depressed here
Hey
What do you think
You are very free
What's wrong with you
What's unhappy
Say it makes me happy
Not Gu Zhen
Are you interested
We had a fight here two days ago
Now we two elders
Nothing at all
On the contrary, it is Ji Han
Memorized punishment
She also lost her exchange student quota
Are you happy
What exchange student
no
How is she now
Did you comfort her
I have a family
Why don't you go
I can't go
If i don't go
No one wants her back
just you
I can't do it, but my brother can do it
My brother is a shareholder of your school
real or fake
correct
Don't you forget
First put that depot
I signed the contract
Give your brother a call with your cell phone
I told him fast
Remember the contract
Beauty
What are you doing
Didn't I say everything
Lin Ran let me come
Help take care of you
you go
Why
You go
You went out to buy groceries at six o'clock in the morning
Aren't you just to give Weiwei food?
I don't dare to be greedy
Send it in by yourself
I'm your uncle
I let you go, you go
Why are you old
Still awkward
If you care, be upright and care
I won't go i won't go
you go
It'll be cold in a while, go go go
Getting older and more hypocritical
My dad did it
Also put more onions
Uncle him
I won't give it to you by myself
I'm afraid I can't help nagging
You don't like to listen
slight
It's okay
We will get better in the future
Opening day
Brother is confused, brother is wrong
Sorry
I will not do it again
Brother will stay with you from now on
Make this dessert shop well
elder brother
Try my newest researched dessert
How about it
it is tasty
Weiwei, don't be discouraged
All beginnings are hard
Business will get better
correct
this
I brought more
You help me show it to my dad
He hasn't eaten my dessert for a long time
Row
What are you looking for
I want an exchange student quota
You make a price
Do i seem to be short of money
Don't you want my parking lot
We can develop together
Flying in the sky and running on the ground
I can give you whatever you want
but
Except Tang Weiwei
I think you misunderstood
Although I am a businessman
But not all business
Education is the foundation of the country
I won't let one
People who don't have any cultivation value
To waste national resources
I think you also misunderstood
She is qualified enough for this classmate
Just to help the classmates
Lost place
I'm just
Want to help her get back what belongs to her
Is that classmate you
Except Tang Weiwei
I don't want to owe any woman favors
I don't want to have anything to do with them
If she is really talented in learning
It's okay to have one more place
but
I don't want to make this deal with you
I can pay for the parking lot
But you have to do me a favor
I want a woman's information
no
Tang Weiwei is my girlfriend
You think too much
What i want is
Li Xiang's Information
Li Xiang
classmate
Almost done
I'm closed
You in the end
How long will it take to see
Do you think I want to see you
Lin Ran asked me to come and help
Burning forest burning forest burning forest burning let you help
What help
Help
help
The school committee temporarily added a place
Recorded you back
you want
Thank you Lin Ran
If not this time
He begged the school committee
Your quota is not guaranteed
Director, I see
Go go go go
Ji Han
How about it
Have you said it?
All agreed
Lin Ran
thank you
Thank me why
We are good brothers
Good brother what do you say thank you
Good brothers to us
Don't think too much
Tell you
When you go abroad,
Don't shame me
do not worry
After i go abroad
I'm sure I don't know you
Just do
What's wrong
Where does it hurt
Neck is itchy
or
I will give you a psychological test recently
How do you feel that your illness is getting worse
Doesn't you smell sweet and allergic?
Will not
Don't make a fuss
Maybe it's just eczema
Mr. Jin, please wait a moment
thanks
Wei Wei is looking for someone
Okay
Mr. Jin
Take a look
This new product planning
Let's not talk about it
I came today to suggest you
Since your store opened to the present
I hope you change hands as soon as possible
Stop loss in time
Is it so bad?
Assistant Wang did market research
And the future prospect analysis of your store
condition
May be worse than you think
Do you want to listen
Mr. Jin
Let's go out and talk
I don't want him to know
good
Lin Ran
Help me take a look at the store
good
When it opened
It really affects us a lot
But I have been developing
Healing desserts
As long as the gimmick can be started
There should be a chance
Mr. Jin, I want to hold on
Isn't this Xiaotang?
Came out with boyfriend
Not aunt
What's so shy about this
It's really not that he is my boss
Pity
You two
Looks good
big boss
You consider considering our Xiaotang
Auntie, you misunderstood
Auntie, eat slowly
I'll take you to the surrounding environment
Our main audience distribution
Is the nearby university town and food street
Aunt
How do they match well?
I think it's a good match
Do not you think so
Dafei
What do you mean by a person on the road
Just like-minded people
Then why some people
It's not all the way
I'll check it for you
With
Brother, listen
There are several standards
First
Inconsistent thoughts
Tang Weiwei is a science
I am a liberal arts
Article 2
Inconsistent interests
Tang slightly likes desserts
But I like motorcycles
Article 3
Inconsistent living habits
That person
Can't eat sugar
Can't drink alone
Does this count as a different lifestyle?
Where is such a hapless couple?
Are you sick?
Hello what's wrong
Have you finished talking with Jin Zichuan?
We're done today
Let's go to a movie together
I think our feelings
It is necessary to train
The same lifestyle
I still have something
You go home first
Bye-Bye
Hey
Where is such a hapless couple?
Sick
I'm back
What's wrong with you
Are you uncomfortable again?
No fever
Did you eat candy?
Also said that I didn't eat sugar
are you feeling better
I'll get you something to eat
What's wrong
I can eat candy now
Can still eat sweet
We are a pair right
Stop awkward
Shop just opened
Everything is not on track
Of course I have to take care of it
Like I took care of you before
Understand
sister
Take me home
what
it is me
I'm sick again at home alone
There is no hot water at home
I don't know how to cook
You have the heart to leave me here alone
I knew why today
Who was arguing at the beginning
To move out of my house
I'm afraid you will look down on me
If i always live in your house
Then you will always treat me as your younger brother
I don't want to be your brother
We are all together
I want to leave you
Want to be closer to you
Save your red apricot out of the wall
Go away
do not want
stand up
Stop messing around
Eating sugar is too dangerous for you
About the opening of the new store
My dad keeps arguing with me
If you move back now
Just blatantly touching the bad
not to mention
My cousin returned to China till now
Have been living in my house
You go back now
It must be messy
slight
You believe me
I will be able to handle it
good
very hungry
I really want to eat noodles
Actually today is my birthday
I want to say
I like you
This should be our school
Accepted as the sweetest
If this is not true love
Then I don't believe in love anymore