Shut up
Lin Ran
Forget it before
My sister is married now
You still got involved
Do you want to ruin her happiness
First thing
It's me and Tang Weiwei
already married
Bastard
pardon
slight
That schedule is really a misunderstanding
And am I in a hurry?
Take the initiative
Otherwise, I really won't have a chance
That Miss Tang is really young and promising
It took half a year
Just manage the shop so well
Is someone supporting me?
I think she is wearing a ring on her hand
No more
It's all my family's own efforts
Her family is really relieved
Let her be here alone
Care about her
Maybe
Feeling broken
What are you two talking nonsense
Freeze said
Why are you here
how
You're still mad at me
Don't be angry with me
The psychological journey of anger
Need to include serious thinking
mood
External behavior
The correctness of the object
I'm done
in other words
I'm not angry anymore
Not angry anymore
I just think
It's useless to vent pure anger
so
I put anger
As
Feedback control
Row
You don't have to be angry
It's pretty good to listen to your studies
Xiaoyi
here I am
What does feedback control mean
Anger expression of feedback control
Can promote a positive change
For example
Parents are disciplining their children
Still throwing stones
Like a child
Tang Weiwei
Why grew up
No matter what i do
I look like a child in front of you
Still remember
When my parents threw me to Uncle Tang
You have been taking care of me
It might be an instinctive reaction
Until the first year of high school
I insist on going out
Go live on campus
Lin Ran
Take care of yourself after moving out
There is
Don't eat sugar
good
Then I found
Actually at that time
I like you
Maybe you don't remember
Was a
stop
go
Then you hug me
Ran home from the school gate
I didn't scold me
From that time
I realized
I can't take you anymore
I saw it as my childhood sweetheart
And me
Want to follow in your footsteps
Want to stand with you
want to
Marry you home
original
Your plan
Earlier than your watch
Don't confess
What can i do
You are good with everything
There are a lot of reasons to prevaricate me
I can't hold you back
What can i do
I'm too hard
I
Seems hungry
Come on me to carry you
Jump up
simply put
Although the effect of anger is small
but
If you meet a good tolerant
Accept negative emotions
Allow it to exist
And express
We will all grow up
Learn the harmony of life
So as to harmonize the essence of contradiction
coordination
Mutual love
Drink tea
Biluochun
Fresh today
Drink without eating
eat
waiter
Hello
Want a green
Bean cake
OK
Chief Executive
Your sentence is so cute
Thank you baby
Think about
I think you now
Should we focus on
Put it on our date
I'm here
What do you mean
Let me delete my friend
I divided you into a fish pond
Your free and happy single room
How many people squeeze a pool next door
Why are you talking weirdly today
Good
Let's go to the opera
Someone just gave me two opera tickets
I pushed
I'll see you on the weekend
High unhappy
Come hurry up
Wait for me, slow down
You didn't take anything
Fast in front
You see they are putting on Kongming lanterns
Want to play
I'll get you one
want to
wait for me a while
brother
Do you have more
Give you one
thank you
You are welcome
What the hell are you doing
look
Tang Weiwei
Lin Ran
grow old together
I'm going to sleep
stand up
Choose one of the floor corridors
I choose
bed
I helped you choose
floor
What are you doing
Good night
I didn't expect the school flower to be a dog licking
is this real
House collapsed
Heartbroken
This is my goddess
That's right, how can a school flower
seriously
I do not believe
I didn't expect her to be like this
Still doing such a thing
Isn't this the school flower?
Shameful
It turns out that they are both fake
Is it Lin Ran
it's okay no problem
It seems to be
I just said she posted upside down
You still write
How does it feel to see a goddess licking a dog?
fine
You ignore them
Ji Han
Burning brother
Hundred Thousand Hurry
Something happened to Ji Han
I'll go back right away
Ji Han
It's okay
do not be upset
Burning brother
How about it
Did you find out who did it?
It's a new trumpet
Did not leave any information
I asked the forum management
Check registered mobile phone
Calling past is also an empty number
I checked
I can find
Ji Han
Don't be sad
Yes indeed
Why didn't I think of it, you can check it
so
Me and Dafei
Check the IP of the post first
Ji Han
Du Ruyue
You just accompany her for a while
Let's try our best to keep this matter to a minimum
and
Tens of thousands
I can't let Tang Weiwei know
Burning brother
Do not worry
Everyone is not talkative
Can you really find it
can
Surely
Then let's go together too
No need no more
You are waiting here
Gu Zhen
Big fly
Walk around
How is the situation
I have checked the IP data
But want to determine who it is
It's really troublesome
what does it mean
simply put
I found
Is the IP address of the last two digits hidden
Theoretically
There may be two digits in it
Or three digits
In other words
Computer with the same IP data in front
There may be dozens or hundreds of
but
Just confirm the posting time
And then put the computers that have been active during this time period
List all
Check one by one
Should be able to find out who posted it
Okay you kid
My brother Gu, break off
nice
Come here, let me check for you
Why the post is gone
What's the situation
I do not know
Why is it gone
Get it out
I try i try
How did you come
Ji Han asked me to bring you some water
How is the investigation?
Don't mention it
It was fine just now
Sudden
Nothing nothing
It's a coincidence
Did I bother you
I'll go now
Bye-Bye
Check it slowly
You say
Most likely to get the diary
Could it be Du Ruyue?
You are here
Du Ruyue
What's wrong
It's okay
Just want to tell you
We just found the address
Yes
That's great
I'll go back and tell Ji Han now
Du Ruyue
I remember
You have an exam next week, right
Part-time job is very delayed for review
You next week
Resign from the dessert shop
It's okay
I don't miss the exam part-time
And Wei Wei is also very kind to me
I mean
you
Resign
Hello everyone
Otherwise, everyone won't be able to get off the stage
You go back
Kisaragi
Hurry up
Come try my new sugar-free cake
How about it
good to eat
I'll also have a taste
Ji Han
actually
I always wanted to thank you in person
thank you
no thanks
I want to ask you
You think
Who is most likely
Get your diary
What do you want to say
What do you think of Du Ruyue
Did you find something?
good
Lin Ran
I see what you mean
You can know it in your heart
Gone
Lin Ran
What's wrong
actually
I should apologize to you in person
Because of my personal reasons
Trouble you
and
Liking you is actually my business alone
Can be friends with you
I'm already happy
I know that after you and Weiwei are together
I already put it down
So that diary
I didn't take a good look
It's okay
Can be liked by a good girl like you
I should thank you
It's a pity
Our revolutionary friendship cannot be kept
Let's go
How did you find this store
Hello
Your dessert
thanks
Tell me
This
Why is it so hot today
It must be hot in August now
You say this August
Is there an important day?
Do you remember
No
Why not
Think about it for me
Really not
The last time I confessed to you
When
some days ago
last week
last month
no
I'm talking about the kind of formal
Once a year
Ritual
Your birthday
Then what
At once
Birthday
My birthday is past
I didn't mean your birthday
I mean
A guest is coming
I'm going to work first
You should go back to school and prepare
hurry up
boss
I want this
good
Hello
Is my cake ready
All right
You can come and get it now
OK
I'll get it right away
Hey Juyue
Wei Weijie
A customer in the shop ate something
Seems to be poisoned
I took him to the hospital
Do you want to come over
Ok ok
I will be right over
Who are you
Hello
I'm the owner of Tanyun Dessert Shop
As soon as it happened
I rushed over immediately
How is the patient
Is it convenient for me to go in and have a look
correct
this is
Supplements I bought for patients
So you are the owner of the dessert shop
Today, you almost ate people to death
do you know
This year
You can open a shop even with such a black heart
You guys
Imported ingredients
Won't you check it in advance?
Really sorry
But you can rest assured
Our ingredients are purchased uniformly
Also undergoes strict inspections
So there will never be a safe situation
Did the doctor say the reason?
What do you mean by that?
You don't want to be responsible
My daughter
She is in your shop
Eat the problem
Now you say you are not responsible
Do you still have a conscience
No no no
That was not what I meant
Then what do you mean
I tell you
My daughter
If she has any shortcomings
I will never let your store go
Wei Weijie
It happened suddenly
It's normal for them to be emotional
Don't worry
fine
You go back first
I stay to see
What else can i help
Wei Weijie
People from the Food Safety Bureau came here this afternoon
Say sampling
Wei Weijie
You go back first
let me tell you
Xiao Yin's husband
Is the deputy director of the Food Safety Agency
Where is my husband
Is the general manager of Hongtu
Deputy Director of the Security Bureau
Xiao Yin
Do you have time
I am coming now
Coming
long time no see
Drank it
Come in quickly
Come everyone
Let me introduce to everyone
this
Is my old classmate
People but
Top students
University bully
You talk for a while
You have to converge
Come
Sit sit sit
Just waiting for you
Sit down
Wei Wei
Have a drink with everyone
I
Don't know how to drink
The little girl can't drink
Don't drink
What's wrong
Isn't it enough to learn?
People always have the first time
Moreover
So many people are here
Wei Wei
Isn't this not giving me face?
Yes yes
Come come
Have a drink
That
so I
To everyone
well
Good drink
Weiwei hasn't come yet
Not allowed to eat
Did you hear
When is she coming
This dish is cold
I'm almost starving to death
Wait a while
Wait a while and won't die
Coming soon
Weiwei builds such a big shop on her own
There must be more guests today
Closed late
or
I call her
Good to make a call
Deputy Bureau
I come today
I want to ask you for news
After your bureau goes to the commercial store to sample
How long will it take to know the result?
if
Really detected something
What will happen
Miss Tang
Your shop is
It's a dessert shop
Call
Miss Tang
What about us today
It's a private party
So about the shop
Just follow the process
You misunderstood
I didn't want you to help
It's just something happened in the store
I
I don't know what the process is inside
So I don't have any points in my heart
Just want
Consult with you
husband
You say our old classmates
Rare to see once
This hasn't been renewed yet
Good for you
Talking about official business again
Wei Wei
Let's ignore him
Come
Let's do one
I really can't drink
Xiao Yin
I really have a business deal today
I don't care about your business and crooked things
I only know
I want to accompany my old classmate
You two drink first
Don't let him drink if you can't drink it
Miss Tang
From sampling to results in our bureau
It takes about three working days
If there is a problem
That
husband
Didn't you say it yourself
Let's not talk about official business at private gatherings
Don't slap yourself in the face
Lai Weiwei
Let's drink one
Come come come come come
Call us back when you heard
Pico phone keeps not answering
Will something happen to her
I gonna go see
What's that birthday
Then let's eat or not
Yes
I think this is also good
Hey brother
People found
At Wangjiang Road Clubhouse
good
Look how good you sing
right
that
I'll leave first
Why are you leaving so soon?
I still have something
Then I won't send you off
Slow down
Bye-Bye
be careful
Miss Tang
thanks
slight
Miss Tang
you
do you know it
I am her husband
thanks
pain
What happened to you
What's wrong with me
What did you do tonight
you
Would rather go and drink with those people
Don't want to come to me
I'm afraid what day is today
You forgot all about it
I know today is your birthday
Then you know that I am for my birthday
How many days have been set up
You know how many times i got the process right
I called everyone
Just to be fair and honest
Stand in front of you
Fend off all the rumors for you
But the result
Six o'clock
Seven o'clock
Eight o'clock
Nine o'clock
It's twelve o'clock, Tang Weiwei
No answer to the phone, no reply
I almost thought you had an accident
I almost called the police, you know
I really have business
Your business is for
Drink with those people
Lin Ran, can you tell me something
I don't make sense
Should make you drunk to death outside
do you know
You are not calm at all now
I don't want to talk to you
We will talk tomorrow
Your birthday present
today
Food poisoning among customers of dessert shop
I'll go to Xiao Yin's husband for help
Phone muted
I didn't hear
Sorry
Is it okay?
Then why didn't you say it earlier
Did you let me talk
Are you satisfied with the trouble now?
Let's calm down
whats the matter
Talk tomorrow
I'm tired
I'm going back
I painted it with the paint you gave
What you said
Can it be recovered?
I don't want to calm each other down
I just want to be passionate
All boiling for you
Sorry
I misunderstood
Hello students
In this international exchange learning activity
Before coming
I have something to tell everyone
Everyone here
Are all outstanding students in our school
Advanced cadre
Represents the academic spirit of our school
Have friendly exchanges with international schools
This is the end of my speech
Thanks classmates
You just said so well
Your manuscript is well written
Just use it for me
How does your brother explain
Little things
that
Lin Ran let me take care of you
real
Of course
You don't think
I did it for you
In short
This time
I owe you a favor
that
night
Wei Wei is going to make up Lin Ran's birthday
you
You be my female companion
Just pay me back
You just said by yourself
thanks for coming
today
Closed so early
Is it because there is a date
Need to prepare in advance
Mr. Lin
Please sit down
Wait
okay
Well done
Nice to have you
I used to make her angry
Make me a cake
such a pity
I can't eat
real
rest assured
This is not punishment
I'm not angry either
How about it
Feel
Feel okay
This is a special sugar-free cake
It's a gift from me
make up
I missed your birthday for the first time
starting today
I won't treat you like a kid anymore
Will face up to the relationship between the two of us
after
I'm wrong
You can correct me too
You are wrong
I will correct you too
What about this cake
Is my sincerity