[English subtitles are available]
[The Sweetest Secret]
Let go of my girlfriend.
Your girlfriend?
Not girlfriend.
You lied to me.
You bullied Wei Wei.
I don't like you since the beginning.
Hey.
You should stop going for a blind date.
You can't find a good man
with your current condition.
Mind your own business.
Why?
Does women's temper get worse
as they age?
I'll kill you.
[Episode 2]
Sorry, I'm late.
You're here.
Wei Wei.
Welcome.
How dare you come?
You just left me behind yesterday.
Forgive me.
Wei Wei.
You are so arrogant.
Everyone waited for you.
You didn't greet us.
Instead, you and Li Xiang
whispering to each other.
I'm really sorry.
Something held me up.
You need to drink three glasses
of wine as a punishment then.
Yes.
She is right.
Ignore her.
She means no good.
Everyone knows you'll change
as soon as you drink.
Let's drink.
We haven't seen
one another for a long while.
Cheers.
Where is Lin Ran?
He made such a trouble,
but he just escaped?
What else do you want?
Are you tired of living?
Yes.
Are you still a vegetarian?
[Evil]
Wei Wei.
I see that you're so busy.
Is your boyfriend checking on you?
It's a spam call from a property agent.
Who will believe it,
right?
I heard this not long ago.
Mr. Tang went around the neighbourhood
to seek a boyfriend for Wei Wei.
Really?
Wei Wei.
You're turning 30 years old soon.
You should grab
the opportunity when it comes.
It's 2020.
Women don't spend their time and value
on men anymore.
Moreover,
Wei Wei already has a boyfriend.
She doesn't need a blind date.
Boyfriend?
Does she have a boyfriend?
Why don't you bring him along
and introduce him to us?
Exactly.
Bring him over.
Anyway, she is in a relationship.
Enough.
Let's not talk about this.
Let's drink.
All right.
Cheers.
Fill your glass.
Tang Wei Wei.
Where on earth are you?
Reply me. Do you hear me?
I have to pick up this call.
You guys continue chatting.
Wei Wei.
Look at you.
You didn't talk much during the meal.
Is it because
we are incomparable
with you?
Don't say that.
Wei Wei is doing great.
She has just completed
her bachelor degree.
I heard you're doing a PhD.
She is
her lecturer's favourite student.
Doctor-to-be.
Tell us about your boyfriend.
We're curious.
Who has the courage
to woo an elite like you?
Yes, Wei Wei.
Tell us.
Who is that brave guy?
Xiao Yin's husband is
the deputy director of
the Food Administration Bureau.
My husband is
the general manager of Hongtu.
Perhaps
they know your boyfriend.
I have no boyfriend.
Then you should tell us earlier.
You've been keeping us curious.
Aren't you
being very proud of yourself?
Who says she has no boyfriend?
Isn't that Lin Ran?
He has grown up.
Why?
Are you still following around Wei Wei?
That's right, Wei Wei.
Even if you want to save your face,
you shouldn't ask Lin Ran to come.
We know one another so well,
don't we?
Besides,
Lin Ran was
popular among girls.
Yes.
Look at your age gap.
Your age gap is probably six to seven years.
Do you really think
you deserve a young boy?
That's very funny.
Why doesn't she deserve me?
If she doesn't deserve me,
how about you?
We're just saying.
Don't take it to heart.
I need to go to the washroom.
Wei Wei.
[If she doesn't deserve me,]
[how about you?]
No way.
Not Lin Ran.
Why not?
How dare you ask?
I came to save you.
Is this how you repay my kindness?
You know what?
Bai Lu kept crying when she couldn't
beat you in the study.
Xiao Yin is her lackey.
If I didn't come today,
you'll be the victim of bullying.
You don't know anything
about the adult world.
Do you think
this gathering is necessary?
It happens once a year.
We were classmates after all.
You concern about the social norms.
That means you're old.
Yes, I'm old.
Tang Wei Wei, let's flee.
Pardon?
Let's flee.
Leave this
displeasing place.
My bag is inside.
I'm your boyfriend.
I know what to do.
Let's go.
Tang Wei Wei.
How much did you drink?
You look tipsy.
I'm fine.
Are you happy today?
Hold still.
There's a big dog.
It's fine.
I'll protect you.
Lin Ran.
Come here.
There is another big dog behind you.
Woof!
[Don't come near me!]
Why are you still scared of dog?
Let's go.
Be careful.
This house
is well located.
However, it's too small.
[Happiness]
Listen.
After you get married,
sell this house.
You can pay the down payment
of a big house with the money.
Yes, buy a bigger house.
Are you eating sweets?
Listen.
I have diabetes.
I can't eat sweets.
You should learn to cook from now on.
Cook me some local dishes.
They are my favourite.
Look at this.
Your dirty clothes.
Why do you put them everywhere?
Exactly.
Wei Wei.
What is all this?
Do you want your mother-in-law
to do the laundry for you?
Take it easy, mother.
Tang Wei Wei.
Apologise to her now.
Are you drunk?
As a woman,
how dare you drink
in the middle of the night
and bring a boy home?
You're being ridiculous!
Where is Uncle Tang? Uncle Tang.
He has gone outside.
What brings
you two here?
We came to discuss with Uncle Tang
about our wedding.
Son.
Step aside.
So, you're the third party
who is ruining my son's relationship?
You act like a rogue.
I can tell that you aren't a good person.
Listen.
Get out now.
It's immoral to destroy
other's marriage.
Immoral!
Wei Wei.
What marriage?
Since when you two enter this stage?
You ought to
make it clear to me,
or else
I won't agree to this marriage.
Aunt.
I'll be frank then.
Go ahead.
Put it down!
This is my house.
So what if my house is a mess?
I can do whatever I want.
Do you have a problem with that?
I can drink coffee
or coke whenever I want.
It's not your business.
Lin Ran,
my brother.
I have a relationship with him. So what?
Lucky me.
You should drink more in the future.
You don't have a sea-view house.
It's none of your business.
You...
I'll drive you crazy.
Is this how you talk to an elder?
Where is your manner?
I can't handle this.
If something bad happens to my mother,
I won't forgive you, Tang Wei Wei!
Quick.
Dial 110 now.
I'm not scared of you!
I can do that too.
120.
My brother
can't eat sweets since he was little.
He'll die after eating one.
No.
No!
Stop.
Brother.
Who is trying to kill you?
Listen.
This has nothing to do with us.
You forced him.
Let's leave.
Rest in peace.
Get up. They've left.
Lin Ran.
Are you all right?
[Emergency Centre]
[Tang Wei Wei]
Yes, Wei Wei.
You drank wine?
You've sent Lin Ran to a hospital?
Where are you now?
[Baby.]
[I'll be right there.]
[I've changed a new car today.]
[A black commercial car.]
[So don't take the wrong car.]
Be quick. It's urgent.
All right.
We'll talk when I get there.
Mr. Jin.
What happened to Mr. Gu?
He called me first.
So, he isn't heavily drunk.
Let's go
to the hospital.
We have an appointment with Mr. Wang.
Postpone it.
What took you so long?
This is urgent.
Quick.
This is a matter of life and death.
Head straight to the hospital.
What are you waiting for?
Do you expect me to...
kiss you?
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
I get in the wrong car.
Hello. Where are you?
[Sorry, baby.]
[I have an accident.]
[I can't fetch you.]
What about me?
Hello?
Well...
I will do anything for you.
So can you do me a favour
and give me a lift?
Wipe off the mask on your face.
Mask?
Let's go.
All right.
I was in a rush.
[What have I done?]
[Gastric lavage?]
[Hospitalisation?]
[It's not a sweet,]
[but poisonous drug.]
[Alcohol will only lead to troubles.]
Lin Ran at Bed 24 is awake.
Miao Miao.
Hey.
Who are you?
You made my shirt dirty.
Are you trying to fool me?
Your shirt is already dirty
before you bumped into me.
The floor is cold.
Get up now.
Miao Miao.
Don't leave.
You fed me sweet
in the middle of the night
just for a lovely encounter
at the hospital?
Stop being sarcastic.
Do something about this.
Call me darling.
Darling.
Miao Miao.
I can't hear you.
Quick.
Miao Miao.
Darling!
Get lost!
Are you all right?
I want to bring you
to meet my cousin, Miao Miao.
Give me a hug.
What are you doing?
Miao Miao.
Let go.
Why are you following me?
I haven't paid you the travel fee, right?
Miss.
This is a public place.
I'm going to the hospital.
Hospital?
Still, you don't have to
follow me.
I'm going to the third floor.
Brother.
It's 2020.
This isn't how you
strike up a conversation.
There is no such a coincidence.
Let go.
No.
I said let go.
Mr. Gu.
Is he your family?
Tell him to let go of me now.
Gu Zhen.
Zi Chuan.
Are you all right?
Let me introduce.
This is my wife.
We will
register our marriage tomorrow.
Who is your wife?
I'll kill you.
I like a sassy girl.
Get lost!
By the way,
why do you look like
that person at the circuit
where Miao Miao always visit?
What are you talking about?
Circuit?
Why do you touch me?
Don't yell at me.
Go away.
Gu Zhen!
Go away!
Zi...
Zi Chuan.
[Nurse Station]
Here you go.
Let's go.
Look at you.
You put love before friendship.
You left me in the morning.
At night,
I need to clean up your mess.
Thank you
for coming at this hour.
Exactly.
By now,
I would have a date with a handsome man.
Remember to treat me a meal.
Your eyes move to the right.
You're lying, aren't you?
You're at home the whole time.
Is that guy
your new boyfriend?
I can't keep a secret from you.
Fine. I'll confess.
I met him on my way here.
However, there're certainly a dozen of men
waiting for me
to call them.
Li Xiang.
Don't get too far.
Marriage isn't a child's play.
You don't understand.
Handsome man is poor.
Rich man is old.
Handsome and rich man is a lecher.
Of course I need to be extra careful when
I'm choosing the partner of my life.
"Evolutionary Psychology",
"Sexual Relativity"
and "The Selfish Gene" suggest
that human is naturally egocentric.
When it comes to offspring,
people will never stop
looking for a better gene.
So we can hardly
be faithful to one person.
Fine.
I'm a vulgar person.
Relationship is about give and take.
No one can force me
as long as I stay true to myself.
Hi.
I come to apologise for my cousin.
I'm sorry.
Apologise?
[He is outspoken.
I'm sure he is a resolute man.]
Yes.
No worries.
Can I visit your friend?
He has fallen asleep.
I can
pass your message to him.
It's nothing.
I just want to apologise to him.
Since he has fallen asleep,
I won't disturb.
By the way,
my surname is Jin.
This is my name card.
[Jin Zi Chuan]
All right.
We'll call you.
Sure.
Call me
if there is any problem in the future.
All right.
Let's go.
[Emergency]
My goodness!
The reek of alcohol
and the smell of perfume...
My goodness.
It's choking me.
Really? Let me smell it.
What are you doing?
I...
I'll wash it for you.
No, thanks.
Go back and bring me a shirt.
What with that attitude?
Please.
Go back and bring me a shirt.
All right.
[Bad brother.]
This one then.
[Right.]
[Graduation certificate.]
What are you looking for,
Wei Wei?
Graduation certificate.
Zi Chuan.
I heard that
you drove me home last night.
I didn't bring any trouble to you, did I?
What are you doing?
Watch this.
What is it?
Just watch it!
[Why do you touch me?]
[Miao Miao.]
[Stay away.]
[Hey.]
[Look at me. I'm a man.]
[We can't be together.]
[Miao Miao.]
Sit properly.
Zi Chuan.
[Give me a kiss.]
I know my mistake.
I can't watch this anymore.
[Go away!]
[Miao Miao.]
[Tang Wei Wei, help me.]
I was mistaken as a driver
when I went to the hospital for you.
I can turn a blind eye if you're lazy,
but you've put me to shame.
From now on,
I'll terminate all your bank cards.
Then I...
I'll reactivate them
when I feel like I want to forgive you.
Don't do that, Zi Chuan.
Watch the video.
Morning, Bobo.
[Jin Zi Chuan]
That was definitely the worst event
in my love history.
[That man could be
the perfect partner for Wei Wei.]
[Let's give him a call.]
[Jin Zi Chuan]
[Thanks for helping me last night.]
[RMB 13 for the fare.]
[RMB 2 for the tip.]
Wei Wei.
The school has never
made an exception
if students fail to submit
their graduation certificate.
Sorry.
I can't accept your request.
Professor.
You know I've been busy
preparing for the exam.
I just can't find
my graduation certificate.
So, can you please at least
reissue a proof for me?
It's not that I don't want to help.
It's just that
the competition of
the science project is fierce.
Many people eyeing for the slot.
I can't help you
without a proper procedure.
How about this?
Go home and find it again.
I'll urge the school
for you.
All right.
Thank you, professor.
[What should I do]
[if I don't get to register myself?]
[Other than studying,]
[I don't seem to be good]
[at anything else.]
[Evil]
Hello. What's up?
[Listen to you.]
You didn't send my shirt by yourself.
Instead, you used a delivery service.
Look at what you have brought me.
Just make do with it.
I really have an urgent matter today.
[You know what, Tang Wei Wei?]
You should change your name to Tang Ge Ge.
You've stood me up for many times.
Does this make any sense to you?
I can't take a doctoral degree
unless I found my graduation certificate.
Where are you now?
I came to meet my lecturer at school.
[All right, stop wandering.]
[Go home now.]
I have three more examination.
After that,
I'll figure a way out with you.
[Tieguanyin]
Wei Wei.
What are you doing here?
[Evil Lin's first aid kit]
Tang Wei Wei.
I wanted to say this
when I came yesterday.
I want you to get rid of
all these irrelevant stuffs.
Once we've gotten married,
I will never allow you
to hang out with shady people.
Wait.
What did you say?
Marry?
Do you see this?
When two people get together,
the man should send betrothal gifts.
So, I browsed the internet.
It's nothing but some tobacco,
alcohol, sweets and tea.
So, I've bought it early in the morning
from the market for you.
Betrothal gifts?
Yes.
For me?
Who else?
Don't feel burdened.
I brought them at a wholesale price.
As for your dowry,
you can just prepare
hundreds of thousands.
I feel like
we are engaged.
That means...
[He takes it seriously.]
A man should get married on
coming of age, and so should a girl.
What else can you do at your age?
Mr. Dong.
I think I've made it very clear.
We don't suit each other
and we won't get married.
Anyway,
please take your stuff
and leave.
[To Lin Ran]
Tang Wei Wei.
[I can't believe
she prepared a gift for me.]
[Did she finally realise the good in me?]
[It's such a big box.]
[It must be hard to carry this alone.]
[Tang Wei Wei does have feelings for me.]
[I've actually thought of an idea.]
[Really?]
[Yes.]
[However,]
[before that,]
[should I claim for something in return?]
[I like rabbit the most.]