(Park Jin Young, Roh Jeong Eui)
(Lim Jae Hyuk, Jang Hee Ryung)
(The Witch)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were filmed under production guidelines.)
Like Murphy's law...
or Sally's law?
Right. A law.
There are...
strange laws in the world.
There's no law.
It's all coincidence.
What if there's actually...
a law like that?
What if there's someone haunted by that dreadful curse...
for their entire life?
Their life must be so hard.
What on earth are you talking about?
Someone is haunted by the law of death like a curse.
If I can understand that law, couldn't I break the curse?
Doesn't it mean I could save the person from the curse?
Joong Hyuk.
Do you think...
there's a witch?
Such a beautiful monastery...
This towering castle...
Also known as a background...
It's also known as a background...
of the fairy tale written by the Brothers Grimm,
- "Rapunzel." - Rapunzel was trapped alone...
in a high castle because of the witches.
Because of the witch's curse.
(Because of the witch's curse.)
I rarely go out.
I've been isolating myself from the world...
and living here.
The minimal space of freedom granted to me,
where I can be alone...
and no one can reach me.
Sometimes I feel like this space I've confined myself to...
is actually confining me.
Whenever I feel that way, I remind myself again.
"It's okay."
"I'm fine."
(Episode 2: Witch Park Mi Jung)
How about tteokbokki?
Sounds amazing!
Strange things have often happened around me since I was little.
- One, two, three, four. - One, two, three, four.
- Cinderella's parents died - Cinderella's parents died
- When she was little - When she was little
- Her stepmother and stepsisters - Her stepmother and stepsisters
- Made fun of her - Made fun of her
- Shabashaba ai shaba - Shabashaba ai shaba
- She must've cried so much - She must've cried so much
- The 1980s - The 1980s
- Shabashaba ai shaba - Shabashaba ai shaba
- What did you just do? - What on earth?
Hey, Park Mi Jung. Tease you.
- Hey! - What are you doing?
(Danger)
That boy fell into a manhole and was seriously injured.
Well... Mi Jung.
You know tomorrow is White Day, right?
Here. This is for you. These are candies.
I thought...
it was just a coincidence.
Are you okay?
Can you get up?
- The Lord's love - The Lord's love
- Blossoms - Blossoms
- He embraces me - He embraces me
- With mercy - With mercy
- Every day - Every day
- Every moment I breathe - Every moment I breathe
- He comforts my heart - He comforts my heart
- The Lord's - The Lord's
- Merciful touch - Merciful touch
- He always gives me good things - He always gives me good things
Mi Jung.
He called my name.
Can we talk for a moment?
Sure.
I wrote this. It'll be useful.
Take it. This is nothing.
Just take a look.
Thank you.
I'm moving to Seoul.
I was accepted to Hankuk University.
Congratulations.
Well...
Didn't you come first in class this time?
Yes.
I did.
Study harder. Don't let your guard down.
It'd be nice...
if we could go to the same university later.
It's quite impossible, considering my grades.
But you'll go to a university in Seoul anyway.
Then...
- Hey. - Hey!
Ik Jong.
Wake up!
What's the matter?
- What's wrong? - I don't know.
I think he was stung by a wasp.
A wasp?
Why is there a wasp in the middle of winter?
- What on earth is going on? - Hold on.
Oh, gosh.
He was immediately taken to a hospital for treatment.
(Congratulations on your acceptance to Hanguk University!)
(Year 3, Im Ik Jong)
When the new semester started, he left the town.
I haven't seen him since then.
Didn't you pay to learn it?
- No. - It's so nice.
Oh, my.
It seems Park Mi Jung is our classmate.
I have a reason not to be absent now.
- Hey, Min Ho. - Yes?
- Do you have a death wish? - That's so random.
What's up with the loving gaze?
- Me? - Yes, you.
My goodness. It hurts so much.
She only does this to me.
Are you okay?
- It was so loud. - It hurts so much.
You were there when Ik Jong was hurt, weren't you?
What?
Yes. In front of the church.
What did you talk about with him at that time?
Well...
Ik Jong...
was hurt because of you, right?
Right?
What?
Can you stop talking about that? Aren't you tired of it?
Mi Jung did nothing. Why do you keep asking?
He completely recovered and went to Seoul ages ago.
(Seoul Milk)
Jung Hwan.
- You're a man. - That was cool.
Is it good?
Yes. It's delicious.
How's school going?
Have you made any friends since the new school year began?
Well, I just...
I haven't even spoken to some of my classmates.
Isn't Da Eun who used to go to church with you in the same class?
The postmaster's daughter.
She is in the same class as me,
but we're not that close.
Friendships don't always thrive.
You argue, make up, and argue again.
That's what friends do.
And the friendship grows as time passes by.
Right.
Don't focus on study only. People don't like it.
You need friends too.
Daughter.
Happy birthday.
I prepared cash instead of a gift.
Is that okay with you?
Yes, but...
Thank you, Dad.
Treat your friends to good food. Okay?
You'll be able to get along with everyone then.
Yes.
Dad.
You can't even have a memorial service for Mom...
because of me.
I'm sorry.
Who holds a memorial service on their daughter's birthday?
To me,
you're more important.
Mom would be upset if she heard it.
Mom passed away giving birth to me.
It means my birthday is the anniversary of her death.
Why would she be upset?
No one told her to leave us in such a rush.
I...
will make sure she isn't upset.
So don't worry about that.
It seems like there's a food poisoning outbreak at school.
Apparently, 12 boys from our class have been affected.
The headteacher is trying to identify the cause.
So don't worry too much.
Everyone, be careful with what you eat during the summer.
Many students have been absent, but don't get too relaxed.
- Yes, ma'am. - Yes, ma'am.
Good. Class dismissed.
- That's what I'm saying. - It's possible.
Food poisoning?
So many people got it.
Does it make sense?
And all of them are boys.
What's going on?
There were unusually frequent accidents at school.
And most of the injured were boys.
Mi Jung.
What are you doing here?
Jung Hwan.
I don't have an umbrella.
So I've been waiting for the rain to stop.
Do you think it will stop?
Let's share an umbrella.
No. I don't mind getting rained on.
You'll catch a cold.
You always walk home instead of taking a bus, don't you?
I actually walk home too.
My house is in the same direction as yours.
Is that so?
Let's go.
By the way, why do you always walk home? It's really far.
I bet it's not to save money on bus fares.
No. I just like walking.
You like walking?
Sorry.
- For what? - Nothing.
My house is just a little further down.
How far is your house?
My house isn't in this direction.
What?
It's in the opposite direction from the school.
Why did you come all the way here then?
Do you remember when our classmates got food poisoning?
They actually talked about you.
About me?
Yes. All the boys said...
your English is amazing, and you're pretty.
When you stood up to give your presentation in English class,
the boys in our class had heart eyes.
What do you mean by that?
I'm saying many boys like you.
(Intra-city Bus)
Are you okay?
I like you.
Jung Hwan.
Take the umbrella with you.
I'll get going.
(Midong High School)
If Jung Hwan hadn't bumped into me that day,
would he have lived?
A riddling sense of guilt tortured me...
after Jung Hwan's death.
(Midong High School)
I began to talk less and less.
I was afraid of meeting people.
Hey, what is that? That's crazy.
Hey. Right here.
Mi Jung.
Why are you eating alone?
Well...
No.
I don't want to hear it.
I'll get going now.
On my count of three.
All right. One...
Hey, what are you doing?
- My legs hurt. - Okay.
Okay. One, two, three.
- Move out of my way. Move! - Did it come out well?
Hey, Hae In just farted.
- Move! - No, I didn't fart. Seriously.
Hey, isn't that Bang Ju Song?
There was never a shortage of both small and big accidents at school.
Hey, are you all right?
Hey!
- It's his shoulder. - He hurt his shoulder.
What?
As time went by, more students got hurt.
Hey, there she is.
Hey, let's go.
Boys who got injured...
didn't want to be around me and avoided me for some reason.
A boy who liked her got hurt.
Gossips about me...
Boys who like her get hurt.
Started to spread like an infectious disease.
Her? Anyone who likes her will end up dead.
Then did Jung Hwan die because of Park Mi Jung?
Even her mother died when she was giving birth.
See? Park Mi Jung is really a witch.
Someone had sparked...
the rumour that I was a witch.
Sweetie, can I come in for a second?
Yes.
Strawberries.
Here.
Thank you.
Sweetie.
I can send you to an academy.
I'm fine.
I have enough money to send you to an academy.
I get good grades even when I don't go to an academy.
Sweetie, what was that?
Did you just brag?
Yes. I did.
You're my daughter and all, but you can be a bit snobbish.
But tell me when you need to get more books and so on.
Okay.
Mi Jung.
How's school?
It's good.
What about your friends? How are you getting along?
They're all nice.
Think of me as your mother.
You can talk to me about your boyfriend...
or gossip about your friends with me.
Okay.
Aren't children supposed to make their parents worry?
So don't grow up so fast. Okay?
If something's wrong, tell me right away. Understood?
Okay.
Well,
everything is fine. I'm serious.
Okay.
Have the strawberries.
A new year began, and I began my third year.
I went to school quietly as if I was trying to hide.
Park Mi Jung.
Why are you always hiding as if you did something wrong?
Do I know you?
I'm a science major, so we barely ran into each other.
I'm Park Sang Ho, a 3rd year from Class 7.
I have nothing to say to you. Bye.
Jung Hwan's death isn't your fault.
What?
The truth is,
I saw you and Jung Hwan...
sharing an umbrella on your way home that day.
Do you think he might not have died if he didn't walk...
with you that day?
Is that why you haven't been talking to anyone after that way?
Is that why you've been alone and you won't eat in the cafeteria?
You...
What are you talking about?
Why is it your fault that he died?
Maybe, he was fated to die there that day.
Why must you suffer?
Stop it.
Just blame it on the weather that day.
Since Taebaek has a mountain climate,
blame it on the monsoon front.
It would be more scientific if you blamed it on the weather.
- Isn't that Park Mi Jung? - I think so.
Who's that next to her?
Blame it on the rain.
- Blame it on the lightning... - Is something wrong?
- that hit exactly in that spot. - I don't know.
I told you to stop.
You don't know anything.
Why are you getting worked up about it?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to...
Mi Jung.
I actually like you.
I thought I would regret it...
if I didn't tell you that.
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
Mi Jung.
Please remember that I like you.
What was it this time?
You didn't hear?
You know the pharmacy around the downtown area?
There was an accident.
But did you know that Park Mi Jung was with him?
Gosh, that's so creepy.
Is it true that Park Mi Jung is a witch?
Hey, don't even go near her.
You might die too.
Let's all have a moment of silence.
I was utterly sad and heartbroken.
But I couldn't even mourn.
(Midong High School)
(Park Mi Jung, the Witch from Year 3 Class 3)
(Witch)
There wasn't...
a single place for me in school.
Just like that, I left my school.
No.
I left the people.
People didn't call my name anymore.
Just like that,
I became a witch.
(Park Mi Jung, the Witch from Year 3 Class 3)
Why do you want to withdraw from school?
There must be a reason.
Why do you suddenly want to drop out of school?
You won't even pretend to listen to me?
Are you not even listening to me?
Your backpack.
Where did you leave your backpack?
Da Eun.
Can we talk for a moment?
That's nonsense.
Who started this?
Someone must have started the rumour.
Someone who bullied or ostracized her.
Who was it?
It just happened.
Well,
everyone just did it.
(Park Mi Jung)
Kid.
Yes?
What are you doing there?
Some kids scribbled some stupid stuff.
I heard there was a strange rumour at school.
A witch? How could that be?
It's just a stupid rumour.
All done.
But everyone seemed to believe it.
No.
Never. She can never be a witch.
How can you prove that?
I don't know yet.
But I'm sure I can find a way pretty soon.
How?
I should find a way no matter what.
Everyone thinks she's a witch.
But how can you believe that she's not one?
Just because.
She can't be.
You have neither a plan nor a solution.
You're just claiming that she's not.
But I like that answer.
But who are you?
I truly hope you will find a way...
like you said.
Thank you.
I didn't leave my house at all.
Make sure to eat.
I lived in hiding.
I just hoped that people would forget about me.
I thought time would make it disappear.
Instead,
the rumours spread like mold, spreading into...
every corner of the village.
There's not a single card I can take.
Oh, my. It's a Godori.
Goodness.
Here you go.
- Goodness. - Gosh.
- Jong Soo. - Come here.
- What... - Where are you going?
- My gosh. - What's going on?
- What is it? - Let go of me, Jong Soo.
You jerk.
Is it my daughter's fault that your son fell from the cultivator?
Stop it, Jong Soo. Talk to him after you let go.
You people are no different.
Why didn't you stop him from spouting such nonsense?
How can you when we live in the same neighbourhood?
I'm sorry.
Because it was my son who got hurt,
I wasn't thinking straight.
You son of a gun.
Your son isn't the only precious one!
Oh, no.
Whenever I think about my dear Mi Jung,
my heart...
breaks.
You lot.
Don't bring up Mi Jung's pretty and upright name with that filthy mouth.
Or else, I'll cause trouble for real.
(Jeongun-ri Village Hall)
Are you all right?
Good grief. What a hot temper. He scared me there.
- Really, that man is... - What happened?
Hey, Mi Sook.
Rumour has it that Park's daughter...
is bewitching all the young men.
That's ridiculous.
Even the Midong High School students know about it.
So many male students got hurt.
Doesn't your son also attend Midong High School?
Yes, he does. He's a senior.
Gosh.
Your son should also be careful.
You're right. Let's go.
- See you around, Mi Sook. - Bye.
Gosh, not a day goes by quietly.
Why do you keep feeding the cats?
That's why they come by every day.
Dad. Can't you buy me some cat food?
Cat food, my foot.
Kick those ominous things out.
Ominous?
But then, I'm the same.
(All Kill Solidifying Agent)
Gosh, you scared me.
I'd like some cat food.
I'm afraid...
we don't sell any cat food.
Wait.
It's not for sale.
But my son brought some.
Hold on.
But it's not even for sale.
Just take it.
Do you pity me, ma'am?
Sorry?
Welcome back.
Did you eat?
Yes.
How can the first thing you ask from me...
be cat food?
Here.
Thank you, Dad.
Mi Jung.
It's been a while since I saw you smile.
Smile more often.
I will.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
I can finally get a boyfriend.
Just you wait, my future boyfriend!
My Dong Jin...
My son...
You've graduated high school.
Really, stop overreacting at a high school graduation.
And where did you get this coat?
Did you buy one? Or did you borrow it?
You bought it?
- You've got terrible taste. - Hi.
- And what's with that ring? - Hey, Dong Jin. Congratulations!
- My gosh. - Gosh.
- Are you okay? - Did it get on my coat?
- A little bit. - Min Jae.
- That little... - Come here.
- Oh, no. - Come here, Min Jae!
- Come here. - No!
Goodness. What the...
Is it Da Eun?
(Midong High School)
Who is it?
So everyone graduated.
(Year 3 Class 3)
(Seo Ha Ram, Cho Ye Jin)
Mi Jung.
Are you studying these days?
Make a promise with me.
Start studying again.
What?
If you take that GED or something,
you can get a high school diploma...
and even go to college.
You can do it. You're smart.
Let's go to Seoul.
But this is where you and Mom lived...
From now on, I will take the subway instead of the truck...
and see the N Seoul Tower instead of the potato fields.
And with a first-class cable car ticket.
Dad...
The medicine...
It's okay.
It'll get better in no time.
This gum disease is killing me.
Get it treated at a dental clinic, Dad.
Okay, I will.
If this year's potato harvest goes well,
we can save some money.
Let's sell the farm and the house and move to Seoul.
When we get there,
I'll get my teeth treated.
Good grief.
Even if houses are expensive in Seoul,
I'm sure we can find a place for us two.
I've got your back, okay?
When we move to Seoul,
let's keep a little garden on the rooftop.
How about I make it into a potato field?
It felt like Dad was telling me with all his heart.
And so, I started studying again.
(English Key Points)
(Potato)
Dad.
I'm tagging along today.
Mi Jung?
Isn't today seed potato planting day?
Since you keep getting into fights, the others don't help you.
And you refuse to hire people. The only option is for me to help.
If the potato farming goes well, it'll do us good.
All right.
Like a date, shall we go together...
just this once?
I'm in.
Okay. Here.
Up you go. Now then.
Mi Jung.
If you're tired, take some rest in between.
I will.
Dad...
What is it?
Mi Jung!
What happened? Mi Jung?
Mi Jung. Wake up.
Mi Jung! Wake up!
Mi Jung! Wake up! Please!
Mi Jung!
Wake up!
Dad?
Dad...
Dad!
Mi Jung...
Mi Jung. Don't wait around.
Go to the hospital.
Dad... Don't tell me...
Dad had suffered from a severe gum disease for years.
Dad. Hang in there just a bit.
Just a bit, okay?
Excuse me! Please help us!
- Mi Jung... - Over here!
Please help us!
- Someone, please help us! - Mi Jung...
Stop shouting.
Don't call the people over.
If they see us, they will...
No.
Mi Jung.
Leave me here,
and go home.
No.
I won't go.
Answer me, Mi Jung.
Isn't my daughter a good girl?
You're obedient, aren't you?
Mi Jung.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Mi Jung.
I'm a foolish dad...
who doesn't know if not told.
I'm sorry.
Stop crying.
Nobody must know about this, okay?
My good-hearted, pretty daughter.
Mi Jung...
Nobody knows, right?
Oh, no.
- See that? - What's going on?
- My goodness. - No.
Nobody knows.
- What happened? - Good grief.
I became all alone...
and was called a witch...
who even killed her father.
(Jeongun Store)
(Ticket Office)
As if making a run for it,
I left the village.
(Statistics)
Why did you choose statistics?
Through statistics,
I have a life problem to solve.
Isn't he in our department?
There's a reason the guys call him a psychopath.
You're wrong.
Your report was useless from the start.
It was full of errors.
(2017 Traffic Accident Fatality Statistics)
The one who kicked her out...
was me.
I'll leave.
The only common factor between the incidents and accidents...
(Park Mi Jung)
was Park Mi Jung.
Is Park Mi Jung...
a real witch?