(Park Jin Young, Roh Jeong Eui)
(Lim Jae Hyuk, Jang Hee Ryung)
(The Witch)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were filmed under production guidelines.)
(Episode 1: The Female Student)
(Integrated Control Center)
Female in her 50s.
Runs a beauty business.
A yearly income of 150,000 dollars.
Visits the casino at least once a month.
- Wait. What? - Nice.
For real?
- Gosh. - Yes.
- One more time. - One more time.
A university student in her 20s.
A yearly income of under 8,000 dollars.
First time visiting the casino.
An office worker in his 20s.
A yearly income of 28,000 dollars.
Second time visiting the casino.
Hold on.
Three thousand dollars!
- Yes! - Yes!
All right.
How is this possible?
I want to check the CCTV.
Let go of me.
A Chinese businessman in his 40s.
A yearly income of 4.2 million dollars.
Over 50 visits to the casino in total.
- Please mind your manners. - Let go.
Any more bets?
Banker, natural eight. Banker wins.
Player wins.
Banker.
Players.
Bankers.
No more bets, please.
Early in his 30s. An office worker in his 3rd year.
Mid-low-priced shirt and shoes.
It's either his 1st or 2nd visit...
to the casino.
A rented studio in a small city in Gyeonggi Province.
Owns a domestic sedan.
His salary is around 42,000 dollars.
Besides having occasional drinks...
- Excuse me. - with close friends,
he doesn't do much in his free time.
(Grand Palace Building)
Card for player.
Card for banker. Players.
- Bankers. - Please.
One more player.
One more banker.
- Player, six. - Just one more.
Banker, eight. Banker wins.
Pain point. The psychological Maginot Line.
The amount of loss...
shocking enough to never return to a casino again.
We, Shine Solution,
analyse big data from various customers...
with similar conditions,
including gender, age,
living standards, casino adaptability, and more,
to estimate each individual's specific pain points.
Sir.
What?
You see...
What do you want?
Our hotel has prepared a meal especially for you.
How about getting some fresh air?
Sorry?
Taking a break at a time like this is a good idea.
Allow me to escort you.
When a guest's losses approach their pain point,
we help them reset by offering complimentary meals or drinks.
Sir.
This is a hotel voucher given to our VIP guests.
(VIP Guest Room Certificate)
Why are you being so nice to me?
Please use it the next time you visit us.
We'll provide the best service.
Enjoy your meal.
(VIP Guest Room Certificate)
This concludes the data we've prepared.
What do you think is the goal of a casino?
Isn't it making the most profit?
Our casino's goal is...
to collect as much of the guests' money as possible.
Frankly, it's not our concern if they sell their car or house.
It's not like our casino is a social enterprise.
Rather than leaving guests...
lose everything and never return,
wouldn't managing them in a way that encourages continuous visits...
be more profitable? More money will flow into the casino.
The atmosphere of today's meeting was great.
And Seohan Bank will renew the consulting contract.
Beef is on me today. It'll be boneless short ribs.
Boneless short ribs?
But I'll just go home.
Why? Why are you playing hard to get again?
We're always missing our ace in our team dinners.
I've got a long-awaited plan with a friend.
But you don't have a...
Is it Kim Joong Hyuk from our major?
Yes.
Right. After all, Kim Joong Hyuk is your only friend.
Is he doing well?
He's busy with all the cases.
Why don't we all get together sometime?
Okay.
Here comes the chairman.
Today's proposal was interesting.
Thank you.
Most people delude gamblers by talking about...
odds and statistics, claiming they can win money at the casino.
Your idea of making them lose less money was quite intriguing.
That is Shine Solution's distinctive competitive edge, Chairman.
I see.
- Director Kang. - Yes?
Consulting contracts are indeed needed,
but how about investing in Shine?
If Shine gives us the approval, I'll bring it up at the table.
Good.
Do you play golf?
No, Chairman.
What about tennis?
I'm afraid I'm not the athletic type.
Do you have hobbies like playing pool or riding a bicycle?
Reading books and analysing data in my room.
I guess those are my hobbies.
What a boring guy.
You're right.
Here.
- My years have taught me... - That should do.
- life is full of variables. - Thank you.
- Good luck. - Desire is even harder to measure.
How's the car? Is it all right?
Like you said,
it'd be great if world affairs were answered in numbers.
Spare me some time, will you?
I'll treat you to a meal.
I'll do so.
Get back safely, Chairman.
What...
My car...
You jerk!
Scum of a bag!
See that?
He's checking the phone number.
The man did it clearly knowing who owned the car.
A clear target means...
he has a grudge against you.
"A grudge?"
Or it's a crime of passion.
I'm not involved in any of that.
Look carefully. Does he not look familiar?
I've never seen him before.
Really?
Yes.
All right. Then...
Let's write a damage report first.
Your name, Lee Dong Jin.
The address is Gangwon Province...
Do you live in Taebaek?
- Please tell me again. - That's my hometown.
My primary residence is...
- here, the address on the bottom. - I see.
(Change of Address)
- "Seoul, Seocho-gu," - Go ahead.
- Your name. - "Seoun-ro 4-gil, 14."
Fine. May I get your name first?
"Unit 504."
- What do you do for a living? - Min Park.
- Sorry? - "Min Park?"
Your job. I'm asking what your job is.
I'm a data miner.
"Data min..."
(Occupation: Data min...)
Is the spelling of "minor" like in "minor league?"
No, it's not that "minor."
What I do is data mining.
It's inferring information from vast amounts of data.
I'm just an office worker.
Right, an office worker.
- Yes. - "Office worker."
Isn't this the so-called big data?
Big data, as in what I search on the internet pops up...
as advertisements...
- Yes. - on my social media...
and websites I visit.
Yes, that's one kind of data mining.
I see.
I'm guessing data miners earn big bucks.
- What? - Well...
A young man like yourself owns an expensive car.
It's strange these days.
I don't know what people do, but they're all making money.
And I mean a lot. Don't you think so too?
Give me your ID cards.
- Give him your ID card! - Stop it.
- Enough! - Darn it!
- Goodness. - Guys, please.
- You little... - This is a police station!
- Stop it! - That scumbag!
- Really, you... - Seriously.
Get off of me!
Drink some water.
And calm down, okay?
- Where did the report come from? - Sorry?
The owner of Milal Bar from across the street called.
You two are wasting time pleading the Fifth.
Take out your ID cards, will you?
What a total loser.
That scumbag.
Or else, both of you will be charged with mutual assault...
and fraud for dining and dashing on top of it.
I'll make a convincing warrant request and...
You get it, right?
Sir...
I don't think the two would want to get charged.
What do you mean?
I think they're a family.
You mean those two?
His shoulder.
And see his stained socks?
Identical staining due to a chemical reaction.
It's caused by the same laundry detergent.
Watch how they touch the water bottles.
A family living together is seven times more likely...
to pick up the same habits than the general population.
And they're probably keeping...
a white dog or a cat.
That man's shoulder.
Do you know each other?
Are you brothers?
- You think I'm... - Good grief.
Aren't you two too old enough to fight now?
Did you call Mom?
I so did. What? Are you scared, jerk?
- You idiot... - You're dead meat.
I'll see you at home, scumbag.
I am...
too humiliated to live in this neighbourhood. Seriously.
Goodness.
Good evening.
My apologies, Detective.
They say one with a cursed husband has cursed children.
And I'm the prime example of such a saying.
Mom. He ate all the snacks but wanted me to pay for the drinks.
Good evening, Mom.
"Mom?"
Did you invite me here thinking I might not know...
what a police station looks like?
You hopeless son!
You hopeless son! Get on your knees!
(Reliable Police, A Safe Country)
- Bye. - Bye.
- Behave yourself. - Yes, Mom.
Goodness, a data miner is impressive.
You're worth driving a nice car.
Anyway, vehicle damage falls under...
special property destruction, making it a serious offence.
Since you mentioned no one would hold a grudge against you,
we will investigate from multiple angles...
and get back to you.
- Okay. Thank you. - No problem.
- Hyun Woo. - Joong Hyuk.
Goodness. I'm beat.
Seriously.
Are you all right?
These men sure can run.
Great work, Joong Hyuk.
Good grief.
(To Joong Hyuk)
(Joong Hyuk)
Hey, Detective Kim.
Dong Jin.
I'm afraid something came up.
Is that so?
I'm sorry. I'll wrap it up quickly.
Actually, why don't we meet up next time, Joong Hyuk?
No, it's okay. I only need to make the handover.
Joong Hyuk! Hurry!
I've been dragged to a team dinner.
Are you being honest?
Of course, I am.
Jeong Woo is treating us to Korean boneless short ribs.
It'd be disrespectful of me to leave early.
Well, that's a relief.
How are you these days? Are you doing well?
Yes, nothing has changed.
Did anything happen?
No, I'm fine.
All right.
I'll see you next time, Dong Jin.
Okay.
(Ramyeon, Coffee, Beverages)
Why are you alone today? What about your friend?
He's busy and can't make it.
Well, that's new.
The train for Hanam Mount Geomdan Station is approaching.
Please be careful of the gap...
between the train and the platform.
The door is closing.
Please stand behind the safety line.
Come on, Mi Jung.
Turn me down with a reasonable explanation.
Only then will I not get upset.
Hey. Look at them.
What do you mean it's dangerous...
if I get to know you more?
Park Mi Jung.
Mi Jung.
Are you listening?
You can't take a hint, can you?
I told you to stop. So stop.
You see,
I can't do that.
Hey, be quiet.
That's because...
I like you...
a lot.
Please?
What do you even know about me?
You're selfishly imposing...
your one-sided feelings on me without considering my feelings.
But you want me to accept you?
It is her.
It's the Park Mi Jung I know.
I'm truly...
sick of it.
My mom told me if we were fated to meet,
we would meet one day.
I couldn't believe her then.
But today,
I ran into her like a dream.
(Midong High School)
Hae In, we're getting snacks. Do you want to come with us?
No. I'm good.
Okay. Do you need anything then?
- No, I'm good. See you later. - Okay.
- Rest up then. - Okay.
- Lee Dong Jin. - Yes?
How can you study right now?
It's white noise.
It helps me focus better.
I see.
Hey, Lee Dong Jin.
Are you planning to go to college alone?
This is a good example of white noise.
- Is math that fun? - Hey, get up.
- Let's play soccer. Come on. - Gosh.
- Hey, he wants to study. - Hurry up.
- Hey, get him. - Hurry.
Come on. Hey.
- Over here. - Hey.
- Block him. - Over here.
- Hey, block him. - Hold on.
- Nice. - Dong Jin.
- Hey. - It's mine.
- Dong Jin. - Hey, it's open.
- Dong Jin. - Dong Jin!
- Over here! - Hey, keep running.
- Pass it to me. - Pass it.
- Nice. Go for it. - Hey.
- Dong Jin! - Hey.
- Hurry up. - Get it.
- What was that? - Come on.
- He... - I gave you a nice pass.
- Seriously. - He's like a robot.
- Come on. - Let's go.
Hey!
- You should've scored it there. - Hey, let's try again.
- My gosh. - Come on.
With her neat bob haircut...
and no effort to enhance her looks...
Come on, go for it.
- Over here. - she was still pretty.
What are you doing? Come on! You're not going to play?
- Hey, pass it. - Hey.
- Hey. Okay. Keep going. - Hey.
- I got it. - Pass it.
Hey, keep going!
She was the type of girl...
who caught my attention...
and sparked my interest without even trying.
Finish it!
- What a surprise. - I told you that.
Back then, strange things kept happening in our school.
There was a rumour that it was all because of her.
That must have been why...
she was always alone.
Park Mi Jung.
Then one day...
What are you doing here?
Hey, Jung Hwan.
I don't have an umbrella.
I was waiting until the rain would stop.
You think it will stop anytime soon?
Tell you what. I'll share my umbrella with you.
No. I can just go home in the rain.
You might catch a cold.
You don't take the bus. You always walk home, don't you?
I actually do the same.
My house is in the same direction as yours.
Is that so?
Let's go.
My house is pretty close from here.
How far do you have to walk?
Are you okay?
Take this with you. Bye.
(Midong High School)
Oh, no.
A male student died in an accident on a rainy day.
Let's have a moment of silence.
(Midong High School)
Why did the hearse take a lap around the yard before it left?
I'm not sure.
Maybe, it's a way of praying for the departed.
A student from our school died.
Why are there so many accidents from our school?
Right.
Hey, how many accidents did we have so far?
A student broke his bone, and another got hit by a car.
Now, someone died.
Get back inside. Let's go.
- Let's go. - Hey, we should go.
Let's go.
But how did he die?
You didn't hear?
He got struck by lightning.
- Lightning? - Yes.
It rained a lot two days ago.
He was walking home and then got struck by lightning.
How could he die from a stroke of lightning?
I know, right?
The chances of that happening are lower than winning the lottery.
Anyway...
That day, she was definitely crying.
Hey, I heard it happened...
because of Park Mi Jung.
What?
You know the accident.
Oh, I didn't come up with it.
That's what my friends said. That it was because of Park Mi Jung.
You guys know Ik Jong, right?
The one who got into Hankuk University?
- Yes. - Of course, we do.
The banners about him are hanging in every alley.
My mom has been on my back because of him.
But what about him?
There was an accident at church.
He got stung by a wasp.
Da Eun told me that...
Park Mi Jung was there when it happened.
Bad things keep happening...
whenever she's around as if she's cursed.
Do you know how Class Three calls her?
How do they call her?
The Witch.
Jung Hwan was struck by lightning...
around Park Mi Jung's house.
- Is that true? - Yes.
Yes, I heard about that too.
That's so creepy.
Why is that creepy?
The fallacy of hasty generalization.
Lazy induction.
What? What's he saying?
Judging someone in her entirety based on a partial observation.
Here's an example.
Yes. Let's say there was an ice cream thief in the cafeteria.
Ho Young, the ice cream lover,
practically lives there during breaks.
Then...
does it mean he's the ice cream thief?
Hey. I...
I'm not a thief.
I pay for my food.
What? That doesn't make sense.
Right, it doesn't make sense.
It's the same logic.
Whether she was there when it happened...
or the lightning happened around her house,
it has nothing to do with Park Mi Jung.
Be quiet. Silence.
You can chat when you get home.
You can start dating when you go off to college. Got it?
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Study hard.
Yes, sir.
Be quiet, guys.
You be quiet.
- Mom. - Yes.
Are the camera batteries dead?
I don't know. I didn't even touch that.
Do we have any spare batteries at home?
Who uses that kind of camera these days?
Just take the digital camera.
Don't pester me later to get the photos developed later.
I told my friends that I would bring a film camera...
to take pictures of them.
Come on. Do we have any spare batteries?
Check the drawer under the TV.
My gosh.
They aren't here.
Yes, they are.
Come on.
I'm serious. They aren't here.
Unbelievable.
Where are the batteries?
Here. See?
- They were really here. - Good grief.
You can't see what's in front of you just like your father.
Gosh, don't laugh.
Thank you, my dear mother.
Our second semester began.
And we went on a school field trip.
All right. One, two, three.
Another pose.
- One, two, three. - Hey.
I don't have a lot of takes left. One, two, three.
Gosh, those fools.
One, two, three.
All right. This is the last take. Let's make it fun.
- When you jump, I'll take it then. - Okay.
On my count of three.
One, two, three.
Hey, what are you doing? My legs hurt.
- Hey, what are you doing? - Come on.
- Hurry up. Take it already. - Come on.
Okay. Let's do it.
One, two, three.
Hey, Hae In just farted.
- No, I didn't fart. Seriously. - Oh, no.
- I really didn't. - Move out of my way.
Move!
Hey, isn't that Bang Ju Song?
Yes, it is. Bang Ju Song from Class Three.
That must hurt a lot. Why are there so many accidents?
Did you see the blood? He was bleeding a lot.
That looks like a serious injury.
She was...
trembling as if she was overwhelmed by fear.
(Digital Photo Development Studio)
- Hello. - Hey.
You're here, Dong Jin. Hold on.
Here you go.
Dong Jin.
Nowadays, you can still get your photos developed...
with a memory card.
With the film rolls, it costs more to get them developed.
I have to wait for the pictures to be developed.
I like that.
All right. Check the photos then.
Thank you.
My gosh. These fools.
Will she be offended if she finds out?
What's the lunch menu today?
Spicy pork?
Then you do it.
- All right. - Hey, are you serious?
- You're ridiculous. - Seriously.
Hey, are you all right?
I don't know.
Hey, how did this happen?
Guys, you should be careful around her too.
What do you mean?
As more time went by,
she spent a lot more time on her own.
Dong Jin, are you coming?
I'm coming.
(Midong High School)
- We must try it. And that too. - Nice and sweet.
You're not even my friend.
She was having lunch...
in a quiet corner of the school as the sun beat down on her.
- I'm back, Mom. - You're back.
What is it? Why didn't you go home right away?
What?
Do you need money again?
Mom, you're the best.
What is it for?
The school bench in front of the storage...
doesn't have a sunshade.
- Like an awning screen? - Yes.
I was sitting on the bench after soccer.
It was way too sunny on the bench.
There's no coming back once you get sunburned in autumn.
I heard it could cause skin cancer.
Good grief! How could you say such a thing?
Or could you lend me money?
I'll pay you back when I grow up.
And how long is that going to take?
Darn it. Whatever.
Tell them the president of the PTA will donate it.
Really? Are you really going to set it up?
My only son is worried...
about getting skin cancer. What choice do I have?
My goodness. If I serve another term...
on the PTA, it might drive our finances into the ground.
Thank you, Mom.
- It tickles. Stop it. - Okay?
Stop it. Hey!
My goodness.
That brat. My gosh.
Good grief. That money-consuming thing.
- Okay. - Pass it.
- Hey. - Here.
- Hey. - Go!
- Hey, he got the ball. - Is it Dong Jin?
I can block your shot even without looking.
- Just kick it already. - Gosh, that little...
I'll block it without using my hands. Come at it.
Shoot!
Darn it, it smells.
Hey, don't throw it.
- Hey, we won. - Come on.
Hey, kick it. Come on.
No!
There's an awning screen.
- Hey, pass it to me. - Hey.
- Over here. - Hey, hurry up.
Hey, take it. Come on.
Hey, let's go.
- Hey, keep going. - No, kick it high.
I want to try too.
Another male student died...
in March of the new school year, just as we began our third year.
The dead student was in our class.
The students whispered to each other.
What was it this time?
You didn't hear?
You know the pharmacy around the downtown area?
There was an accident.
It would be more scientific if you blamed it on the weather.
- Isn't that Park Mi Jung? - I think so.
Who's that next to her?
- Is something wrong? - I don't know.
Blame it on the rain.
Blame it on the lightning that hit exactly in that spot.
I told you to stop.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to...
Mi Jung.
But did you know that Park Mi Jung was with him?
Is it true that Park Mi Jung is a witch?
Hey, don't even go near her.
You might die too.
Everyone, let's all have a moment of silence.
All the baseless rumours that floated around...
branded the girl as a witch.
(Park Mi Jung in Year 3 Class 3 is a witch.)
(Witch)
(Get lost.)
(No, Park Mi Jung is...)
(Don't come to school. That's enough. Witch.)
I thought I must talk to her this time.
I was just waiting for recess during class.
But she left school right away.
I...
couldn't say a single word to her in the end.
"Hi, I'm Lee Dong Jin."
I couldn't say it until the end.
This stop is Gangdong Station.
The doors are on the right.
Mi Jung.
Excuse me.
(Gangdong)
I just followed her before I knew it.
What do I even want to do?
She wouldn't even know me.
It's...
really hard for me...
sometimes.
Can I live without meeting people?
I really don't know...
how to live...
or how to disappear.
I know nothing.
I hoped she would be doing well.
I hoped she would be doing well wherever she is.
I've been wanting to meet her for a long time.
I didn't know she would be living like this.
Maybe...
I might've hurt someone today...
as I always have.
There must be a reason why you and I have met again...
after all this time.
Because people who are meant to meet...
will inevitably do so one day.
(The man who caused a nuisance on the subway)
(A man who looked obviously drunk...)
(confessed his feelings to a woman and was rejected.)
(Then he collapsed. It was a mess.)
I...
like you a lot,
Mi Jung.
Do you know that?
I really...
(Emergency on the subway)
Mi Jung.
Hey, are you okay?
- Hey. - He collapsed.
Please report to 911.
- Hey. Come on. - What's the matter?
He fainted.
He's unconscious.
What's going on?
Oh, no.
What's the matter?
Someone collapsed here.
Please report to 911 right now.
Right in front of the door.
It's number 5050.
Hurry up.
Someone collapsed here.
Mi Jung.
Hey, are you okay?
Hey.
Please report to 911 right now.
Are you okay?
Someone collapsed here.
Please report to 911.
Hi.
- You're here. - Yes.
Do you want to drink?
Here.
Is something wrong?
Joong Hyuk.
Some people are a little weird,
aren't they?
You?
No, not me.
What's weird about me?
You're totally weird right now.
What I'm saying is...
For example...
Will he show that side again?
He hit it!
- It's flying over! - It's going far.
It's like whenever you go to watch a game in person,
the team you support always loses.
Do you get it?
I think I do.
Whenever you look at a clock, it's always 4:44.
(4:44pm)
We have a table for two people. Please come inside.
Whenever you line up outside a restaurant,
they run out of ingredients right before your turn.
The machine that worked just fine when other people used...
is always broken when you use it.
Like Murphy's law...
or Sally's law?
Right. A law.
There are strange laws in the world.
There's no law. It's all coincidence.
What if there's actually...
a law like that?
What if there's someone haunted by that dreadful curse...
for their entire life?
Their life must be so hard.
What on earth are you talking about?
Someone is haunted by the law of death like a curse.
If I can understand that law, couldn't I break the curse?
Doesn't it mean I could save the person from the curse?
Joong Hyuk.
Do you think...
there's a witch?
(Special thanks to Kim Hye Ok, Ju Ji Hoon, )
(Yoon Bak, and Hyun Bong Sik for their cameo appearance)
(The original soundtracks "It's Still Love" by Choi In Gyeong...)
(and "Don't Go Away" by Park Jang Hyun...)
(are available on all platforms.)
Strange things have often happened around me since I was little.
How about tteokbokki?
Sounds amazing!
(Danger)
- It's all coincidence. - What if there's actually...
a law like that?
It seems like there's a food poisoning outbreak at school.
Apparently, 12 boys from our class have been affected.
Their life must be so hard.
I like you.
Why is it your fault that he died?
It was probably just his fate to die at that moment.
Oh, my gosh.
Is it my daughter's fault...
that your son fell from the cultivator? Is it?
Her mother died giving birth to her.
I told you.
Mi Jung is really a witch.
Mi Jung!
Wake up!