(Lee Sun Bin)
(Han Seon Hwa)
(Jung Eun Ji)
(Choi Si Won)
(Work Later, Drink Now 2)
By the way,
what can we do about this?
Well...
What Hyun Ju can't do, but we can.
Right.
Let's go.
(Gone Drinkers, Part 2)
Done.
Have we ever been this dedicated to something before?
Thank you.
Thanks.
We poured in all of the money we had saved up,
our talent,
and the stamina that let us drink like horses.
The first order of business...
was to see what we could do and what we couldn't do.
(What we can't do)
(What about drinking water? We need a hose.)
(Electricity: Can we borrow some from the neighbouring village?)
(What we can do)
(Staying positive, No drinking, Meditation, No arguments)
Tug on it and it'll unravel easily.
I studied this knot, and it can be easily untied.
- What the... - It won't unravel.
- Seriously. - I can't...
Why won't it unravel? Is it this end?
Here.
There. You won't be able to untie it.
Sweet, right?
I untied it!
No way.
Why did it unravel? Take it as a gift.
- Thank you. - Darn it.
But then again, who are we?
We'll take what we can't do and make sure it's done.
Gosh.
- Gosh. - Darn, I'm exhausted.
- Here. - My arm.
- My legs are like jelly. - Are you all right?
Sorry about that. Here.
It hurts.
- Get over here already! - She must be stiff all over.
- Come on. Let's go. - It hurts.
(Collecting firewood)
(Mud mixture)
(Refrigerator, Campfire)
And then came the day...
when what we could do surpassed what we couldn't do by far.
Shall we get going, then?
- Is it finally time? - Yes.
- Let's do this, then. - All right!
Let's go.
Doesn't it feel like there will be ghosts around here?
- What? - What is it?
There's a bug!
What did you expect in the woods? Get a grip on yourself.
But I hate bugs and insects.
Should we come back some other time?
We're too far away from the city.
Do you remember where we parked the car?
I do.
There's no cell reception.
No cell reception means we're on the right track. Come on.
- Really? - Yes.
But I don't want to.
This way.
Are you sure there aren't more bugs?
Please. What if there are snakes?
There aren't any.
It's a spider web! Hey, check out the flowers.
- What now? - Okay, let's see.
The mountain is higher to the Northwest,
and there's a slope to the Southeast.
Look. This is where we are.
Behind us is a tall mountain,
- and a stream is ahead of us. - Right.
- Can I have a tissue? - A tissue?
- Yes. - Got it.
All right.
It's been windy all day, but the air is now still.
There isn't any crosswind, and nothing's blocking the sun.
- In other words... - Is this the ideal spot?
That's it.
- Let's check the energy here. - Sure thing.
- Like this. Here we go. - Sure.
- What on earth? - Gosh.
Here. This is the spot.
You guys were like detectives just now.
- I can't believe it worked. - We're good.
Guys, there's poop here. Isn't that a good sign?
- Poop? - Yes, poop.
- Poop. - Gosh, that's a lot.
I wonder whose it is. Is there any more around here?
Hey, let's get digging. The shovel, please.
Nice.
The weeds have overgrown.
- I love the smell of soil. - This is a lot of work.
Okay, let me see.
Gosh, the soil here is fine.
This is the spot.
Girls, let's hold hands.
Hands.
I can feel it.
The ground's energy.
The warmth of the sun.
The texture of the wind.
It sure is relaxing.
I'm sure of it. This has to be a good spot.
- What on earth? - What is that?
- What was that? - What screeched?
(Reinforcements for windows)
Videos online...
make you think that anything can be done easily.
This is too heavy.
Push on two.
- One, two. - Two.
- One, two. - Two!
- One... - Then we get to realize...
that there's more to the work than what is seen on the videos.
A bee!
- But by then, it's too late. - It's gone.
Gosh.
Because we have already moved out of our homes.
Darn it.
For this day,
we trained in various fields.
The training we went under at the arcade...
finally proved its worth.
- One, two. - One, two.
There wasn't anyone...
who actually believed that this could work.
But what I can say for sure...
is that it can be done when push comes to shove.
- Are we good? - It's good enough.
No matter the circumstances,
there was always a way to eat, sleep, and excrete.
- Gosh, that feels good. - We were able to spend...
more and more time out in the wild...
which felt impossible at first.
We overcame the fear by believing in one another.
We did it!
We couldn't have done it alone. But as a group, we prevailed.
- Ji Yeon. - Yes?
Tomorrow,
we'll build a fireplace inside and light it up for warmth.
A chimney will also go up.
Starting tomorrow, we'll have heat therapy.
- Okay. - Got it.
- Hello, ladies. - Hello.
Sorry to bother you,
We're from the mountain over there.
We came to ask if we could use your electricity.
Can we?
We promise to pay for it.
Please.
How long will you be there for?
Do you want some chilli peppers?
We have dried radish strips too.
- We'll be back again! - See you again!
- Look at all this. - I know.
Someone must be sick.
We got electricity from a home down the mountain,
and clean water from a stream up the mountain.
Hey, we have water!
This is amazing.
Our chickens didn't run away today.
Hello.
Hi. Gosh, I'm exhausted.
The sweeties.
It looks like you gathered a lot.
They're just greens, but still.
"Just greens, but still?"
You can't get these anywhere in Seoul.
Then dinner is bibimbap with seasoned greens and...
fried eggs!
- They laid eggs? - Yes, two.
Our dear chickens.
Well done. Good for you. Come here.
There are three of us.
One more scoop.
- Mix it up! - Mix it up!
Mix it up!
It looks so good.
How is it?
The egg makes all the difference.
Doesn't it?
- Shall we wet our throats? - We must.
Yes.
- Let's drink. - Cheers.
We'd quit drinking alcohol.
It's detox tea.
Dried radish greens,
carrots,
dried radish, burdock,
oh, and some shiitake mushrooms.
I can tell it's made with love and care.
Right.
We quit drinking.
It's as rare as the sight of a chicken flying.
Hey.
The nights are seriously long up here in the mountain.
What time is it?
Right now?
It's 6:40pm.
- It's that early? - No way.
The old us would slowly be getting ready to leave home...
"Hello, it's us again."
Can I have some chicken feet with lots of Cheongyang chillies?
And a bottle of soju. Cold.
Do you want a beer too?
The first shot must be a mixer.
- Two-to-one, deal? - Deal.
Here comes the beer.
Pop.
Pow.
Hold out your glasses.
- Here comes the soju. - Nice.
And then I pour.
The clear sound you only hear the first time.
- What a lovely sight. - Here comes the beer.
A smooth pour.
How about I use my wrist this time?
At an orchard on the outskirts of the village, bottom's up.
Take your own.
Let's drink!
- Let's drink! - Let's drink.
The chicken feet is here.
It's hot, so take your time.
- Chicken feet! - Chicken feet!
- Gloves, gloves. - Right.
It's hot.
Shall we stop?
Shall we?
I was ready for one more shot.
Aren't you getting the signal?
- I am. - Yes.
Let's go. It's about time.
Right now?
Running will only make it worse.
We must gather our energy for this.
- Oh, dear. - Watch your step.
(Pretty Girls' Toilet)
- Hey, guess what. - What?
We pooped together every day since we moved here.
I got it. There's this rhythm thing.
- What's that? - What's it called?
Yes.
"Biorhythm?"
- Yes. - Yes, that.
- That's it. - Yes, biorhythm.
We must be synced.
- Yes. - In rhythm.
Biorhythm.
This is nice.
What's this smell?
You guys need to wait for me.
Gosh, you're so rude.
I feel so much better.
- Me too. - Gosh.
Should we have built it closer?
- Yes, it's far, isn't it? - A bit?
Is it?
- Hey. - What?
Why do you keep putting the teddy bear up there?
Goodness. What's that doing up there?
You left it there.
I did not. Why would I do that with something I hug in bed?
I bet it was you.
It wasn't me.
Don't you lie.
It wasn't me. Why'd I put it up there?
I have so much else to do.
Then who did it?
Darn it.
What was that?
I don't know.
Shoot.
Did you... see something?
I'm not sure,
but it bothers me.
Could you tell me if there is something?
Knowing won't do you any good.
You won't stay for long, right?
We're here to heal in nature.
My friend's sick.
We have to get better.
All mountains are haunted.
There are lots of graves.
This village has an extra lot of vengeful women.
Don't you scare her.
All graves are in good spots.
Actually,
I saw something like bones.
I don't believe in ghosts.
If you scare us and keep us up,
I will really kill you.
Are you already dead? Anyway, I have a nasty temper.
If you so much as touch a hair on us,
then I swear I'll follow you to the end of the earth to end you.
I tend to speak harshly.
Don't take it all to heart.
I heard a little about you.
I don't get you, to be honest.
Why would you die for a man?
Even if life was horrid back then,
didn't you have pride? Were men your everything?
Darn it. I went and upset her again.
Sorry.
I'm off. Isn't this pretty?
(3 months later)
They must be mating.
It's high time.
There's a bug on your side.
We're friends now.
We got accustomed to life in the mountains.
I'm heading to the stream to do laundry.
Do you have anything?
- No. - Ji Yeon?
Why bother washing clothes when there's no one to see?
Ji Yeon stopped looking into the mirror she couldn't do without.
Ji Goo quit smoking cigarettes which she couldn't do without.
Workaholic me even stopped using my phone all the time.
We actually became one with nature.
It's done.
Wow, it looks good.
- Do you like it? - It's comforting.
Why don't we call the protective spirit "Yang Ki Nam?"
- Yang Ki Nam? - Yes.
Three women living together is way too much female energy.
Well, yes, you have a point.
I like it. "Man of Energy."
But it looks like it's missing something.
What?
I'm off to do the washing.
Okay.
No, don't you dare.
- Hey! Get out! - What is it?
- The wild boars. - Are they back?
- Yes. - Again? Darn it!
- That's just wrong. - Right.
Is that so?
Those little pigs come during the day now.
Who do you think you're messing with?
Let's get guns in Seoul and shoot them with it.
You darn little pigs. Move!
What on earth?
She has lost it.
(Makgeolli)
Hold that for me.
Okay.
My dad told me that wild boars go crazy over makgeolli.
Once they tumble into this,
they won't be able to crawl back out.
I see we have something in common.
Darn it.
Gosh.
Got it.
- No, don't. - Wait.
- Don't. - Why not?
- No! - Don't open it!
(Makgeolli)
Guys.
What was that just now?
Tell me about it. I was completely out of it.
Why don't we have a drink?
No.
We'll meditate. I've been wanting to do it anyway.
- Namaste. - Sure.
(Kim Hyun Ju)
It didn't get any worse.
But the change isn't all that dramatic.
We'll see how you are in three months.
Sure.
Did we choose the best option?
Was chemotherapy the right way to go?
Would it have been better to do both?
Like every other patient and doctor,
we take a gamble...
while not knowing the right answer.
Ji Yeon...
She's asleep.
Right. She must be exhausted.
Are we...
doing the right thing?
I was about to ask you that.
What if...
What if this was the wrong choice?
That is a possibility. I could've been wrong.
Why would you blame yourself...
when it was a group decision?
If only I had let her...
receive chemotherapy.
You would've been wrong!
You almost gave me a heart attack!
Weren't you asleep?
I would've had to do it alone, and you know I lack tenacity.
After a few sessions, I would've bolted.
All those bars used to be ours to drink at.
I'll get better soon so that we can grab a few.
It's a green light. Go on.
It was the twist I hoped for,
but Ji Yeon kept pretending to be asleep.
Ji Yeon, we know you're not asleep.
Don't keep anything bottled up inside.
It'll only stress you out.
We won't pretend to be fine with everything,
so cry if you want to...
and be angry at the world.
Ji Yeon was truly the mother of all twists.
She was actually asleep.
She fools us every time, but we fell for it once again.
Whenever she seemed cheerier than usual...
- Ji Yeon. - Yes?
You don't have to fake it.
Just say it's taking a toll on you.
How can you not find this funny?
Fine.
The fact that she's one-dimensional is the greatest twist of all.
- This doesn't seem right. - It isn't.
- She laughs at what's funny. - Come on.
What is it? Does it hurt?
My mom visited me in my dream.
She cries when she's sad.
- Your mom? - Yes.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
- She goes when nature calls. - One, two,
three, four.
(Pretty Girls' Toilet)
She jumps up and down when she's happy.
Guys, come on out. The cloud is in a shape of a heart!
She sleeps when she's tired.
Gosh.
She does what she's told to do.
Ji Yeon, get up. It's your turn to start the fire.
Okay.
You'll be going into the water too.
We're taking a bath today.
Okay.
You have to write your name with your butt today.
With your pants down.
Okay.
- What? - She was willing to do it all.
Those sick...
- question everything. - You agreed to do it.
They wonder if a certain method can help them get better...
or if it's the right course of treatment.
However, Ji Yeon questioned nothing.
She blindly put her faith in us.
No way. It worked.
Guys, come quick. We got one!
You're all dead meat. Let's see how big it is.
- Hey. - What?
It's only a boarlet.
- What? - It's a baby.
Is a young boar allowed to drink? When it's that young?
There it goes.
Were we right to release it?
It's only a boarlet.
A darn boarlet.
Wild boars must have been walking down this path...
before we ever settled down here.
Since we are the intruders,
we had to find a way to share the land.
What are you doing over there?
This much is fine.
Once again, we predicted correctly.
Guys, check it out. They cleaned it out.
- Really? - Yes.
The wild boars...
had their makgeolli and left quietly.
What startled us more than the wild boars...
- Tell me about it. - were the people.
- What is it? - What's wrong?
- Where? - What's going on?
It's a human being!
Why don't you dig in first?
- I'll enjoy this, Ms. Han. - Sure.
It's good.
You look like a foreigner getting a taste of Korean cuisine.
It's delicious.
- He looks like Robinson Crusoe. - Right.
What is it?
- Is it a wild boar? - What's wrong?
A wild boar?
No, it's nothing. Please dig in.
- Are these organic? - We harvested these ourselves.
Of course, it has to be good.
You're all grown up.
Go on and eat.
Thanks.
Wow, this is crazy.
I should go now.
I'm not sure if I should leave you here.
It gets so dark at night.
I feel the chills too.
This is a good spot so you needn't worry.
- You watch out for yourself. - Yes.
Do you know the way?
I do.
What?
- What? - You don't know.
It's not that way, it's this way.
- You're right. - Goodness.
Bye, then. See you in Seoul.
Take care.
- Goodbye. - Bye.
- Take care. - I will.
Oh, dear.
Don't worry.
What a weird taste.
Goodness. What's that about?
Director Kang came and went,
and the severely cold winter came upon us.
It's the season when all things huddle and hide.
We were told we'd be lucky if Ji Yeon stayed stable at all.
Even she couldn't escape the clutches of winter.
You didn't sleep last night, did you?
No. I dreamed of...
a woman in white who asked me...
to come with her.
Am I dying?
You'd see a Grim Reaper if you were dying.
Not a woman in white.
Right?
I'd prefer a Grim Reaper over a woman any day.
Stop talking. You have a fever.
Have I ever not been with a man for this long in my life?
Darn it.
I quit smoking for you.
Quitting men is nothing like quitting smoking.
Cigarettes have no use but men do.
When did you ever date a guy with any use?
You of all people shouldn't say that.
I'm just saying men are better than cigarettes.
Darn you.
That's enough.
She's running a fever.
I'm burning up inside.
Whatever.
Did you have to upset her when you're sick?
Hearing her tell me off when I'm sick...
makes it a little more bearable.
What a joke.
That wasn't good enough?
Why are you digging?
I have something to do.
- Are you going somewhere? - Up the mountain.
To dig something up to feed her.
Is there anything to dig in this cold?
If there is something out there, it'll be the real deal.
Don't dig too much or you'll hurt your back.
Watch your step and don't slip.
- I won't. - See you.
When we first came here,
we were so sure.
That we could do anything.
Girls. Whenever Ji Yeon's condition worsens,
bring her right over.
There are benefits to relying on nature,
but if stubbornness becomes a belief,
it's worse than nothing at all.
It's possible...
there's not much left that we can do.
Let's see.
There has to be some mistletoe here.
All I see are mushrooms.
What the...
Stay there. What on earth?
Shoot. Why?
Don't come closer!
Come at me.
Fight me, you punk!
It's a baby.
Is a young boar allowed to drink?
Darn it, I was scared pantless.
What was that?
Darn it.
Did I wet myself?
Oh, shoot.
Is this poop? Darn it.
Darn it.
What?
I've never put so much care...
into something I couldn't care less about.
Help us out.
Help us.
Does Ki Nam...
have it at last? How interesting.
Don't touch it. It hasn't hardened yet.
I see.
It hasn't hardened yet, has it?
Guys!
- What? - I got lucky!
This is...
I found wild ginseng!
Here.
Eat it slowly, over a long time.
Chew on it.
There you go.
Good girl.
It's bitter.
No, don't swallow it yet. Chew a bit longer.
Chew it for ages, until you sucked out all the juices.
What have you done?
Wait. Let's see.
You swallowed it already?
You swallowed everything?
- Yes. - But...
Yes. Swallow every little bit stuck between your teeth.
- Okay. - That's it.
I ate it all.
Then rinse your palate with detox tea.
Won't that detox the wild ginseng's properties?
She's right.
- Don't drink this. - Okay.
Don't eat or drink even water until you poop.
I won't ever do that.
I'll keep it inside me for as long as possible.
That's a bit gross.
- Is it? - Let's go.
Was it the wild ginseng?
Or was it Yang Ki Nam sporting lots of male energy?
Doesn't Yang Ki Nam look like Director Toe?
It's not this big.
Ji Yeon recovered...
as if she'd never been sick.
Twenty-eight.
Forty-eight.
Forty-nine.
One more. Let's do one more.
One more?
- Well done. - Yes!
- What's next? - Well done.
- Slowly. - Okay.
Make sure you don't slip.
Left, left.
Like so, we overcame the harsh winter.
I'll see you again in six months.
Six months?
Six months and not three months?
You ultimately did it. Congratulations.
Thank you, Hyun Ju.
Ji Yeon.
The 3-month interval became a 6-month interval.
Come in again six months later.
Your cancer levels, neutrophils,
white blood cells, and liver index are all normal.
Another six months passed,
and it became autumn.
You can come in a year later now.
For real?
Hyun Ju. This isn't a dream, is it?
She can even participate in the triathlon with this result.
You're amazing, Ji Yeon.
I only did as these two told me to.
- Great job. - You had it tough until now.
There was a time we doubted our decision...
as we walked out of this hospital.
But when we were faced with the result...
that our decision was the best,
we became cheeky for a moment.
"Our decision was right."
"Our faith was something," is what we thought.
Hey. Are you still travelling?
You better come back now.
Two and half years ago, the owner of Obok House...
went on a backpacking trip the moment we disappeared.
And...
in the meantime, the world was...
said to have been calm and more peaceful than ever.
- What? - Oh, my gosh.
- What's this? - Is something happening?
- But everyone felt that day... - Oh, no.
was just around the corner.
What's going on?
(Obok House)
(Obok)
(Let's Drink)
Thank you.
Let's drink?
You did well.
Thanks.
It was one day when our 26-month-long abstinence ended.
(Mic Game)
When was the hardest after moving into the mountain?
Let's see.
The first day. No, scratch that.
It was the first month after we came here.
It was really hard that time.
I was scared and at a loss.
There were times when I wondered what I was doing here.
So a bit back then.
Nothing gave me a hard time.
I'd really appreciate it...
if you could answer the question with a little more sincerity.
But nothing was tough for me.
Would you have had a hard time when your friend was sick?
Well, I never had a friend who was sick.
There's at least one person like that in your life.
If not, you haven't met them yet.
I'm not sure. I'm not the type to get stressed over things.
But...
(Mic Game)
What was the question again?
(Work Later, Drink Now 2)