WHEN THE CAMELLIA BLOOMS
CAMELLIA
POLICE
Someone else was killed here
many years ago, you know.
Isn't it the prankster?
-Gosh, what are you talking about?
-Nothing happened for a while.
Is it starting again?
Keep out.
THE WOMAN WITH THE GERMANIUM BRACELET
What's going on?
-They're opening a flower shop.
-A flower shop?
Why open a flower shop in a food alley?
CAMELLIA
I wonder if they'll do well.
Ongsan is a tough place for newbies.
Have you seen the owner?
What? You think she's pretty?
-No, not at all.
-Pretty, my foot.
Close your mouth.
Oh, I'll do that.
Thank you.
She's a mom.
She must be a newlywed.
-What a pretty young mom.
-Yes, what a nice young lady.
-Are you going somewhere?
-Hello.
-She was swearing, wasn't she?
-Yes.
-Yong-sik must've caused trouble again.
-I'm sure he did.
I heard Yong-sik got stabbed.
-Is the kitchen this way?
-Yes, it's at the back.
-The water from the tap looks rusty.
-Okay.
I guess it didn't need windows
when it was a storage for dried seafood,
but it'd be nice to have a window
over there.
The place is 800,000 won a month
because there are no windows.
Still, I think it needs a window
because it's too dark in here.
When you rent this huge space for
such cheap rent, you're expected to pay
for any renovations out of your pocket.
You, as a tenant,
can take care of it yourself.
Let me tell you this about myself.
I love tenants who are self-reliant.
I see, self-reliant...
By the way,
where's your husband?
I need to talk to him about
the utility bills and the kitchen sink.
Does he work on weekends?
I'd prefer to speak to your husband
regarding the repairs--
I am self-reliant.
What?
You can speak to me regarding everything.
What's wrong?
Did Yong-sik get himself in trouble again?
-Did he beat someone up?
-Is he a thug or what?
Enough of that rice gimmick.
Make a talisman for me instead.
What do you want on it?
Help me quit this.
I've been taking it for the past 20 years,
which is a long time.
I can make a hundred talismans for you,
but even shamans can't change your fate.
Had Yong-sik been born in ancient times,
Joseon's entire system
would've been turned upside down.
You always seem to think
that my son would've been lowborn.
What I mean is,
I just think Yong-sik would've taught
all those useless aristocrats
a serious lesson.
Oh, dear.
Would his fate have changed
had I never asked him
to go to the bank that day
to pay the utility bills?
We need to check the accounts
for the third and fourth quarters.
This is Baekdu Marinated Crab.
Yes, where?
The police station?
Yong-sik is there now?
What? The bank?
You're such a troublemaker.
I heard it's on the news now.
When the armed robber
was threatening the bank employees,
a brave civilian started tussling with him
in an attempt to take him down.
The civilian pulled out
his insulated lunch container.
Despite the dangerous situation
where he could have been shot,
he fought the robber
without any hesitation.
The robber aimed the gun at him after...
Are you the hero of Ongsan or what?
I packed lunch
for your after-school studying hours,
not so you'd beat up
a bank robber with it.
Are you saying I have to pay
for that bank robber's dental treatment?
We call it excessive use of force, and
some might say it's a human rights issue.
Look, can't you see
that he's wearing his school uniform?
How could a bank robber
demand compensation
after getting beaten up
by a high school kid?
The thing is,
even though your son is only 17--
I get that he's a robber,
but look at this face.
I mean, just look at these eyes.
I'm sure he saw
the lunch container in my son's hands,
so he should've been careful.
Why let a high school kid break his teeth
when he had a gun?
And why must I pay for his treatment?
You moron, why are you eating this?
-I bet I'm the only woman...
-Jeez, Mom!
...in the entire country that has had to
pay for a bank robber's dental implants.
-Let go!
-Yong-sik's life itself
has been war against crime.
Mister,
did you lose your key or what?
Once, he caught a motorcycle thief
while peeing on the street.
Excuse me, sir. I just saw something.
I'm sorry.
What?
Gosh.
And why did he have to see a pickpocket
while driving his taxi?
Oh, someone was home.
I kept calling, but no one picked up.
-Unit 401, right?
-Yes.
This package is for you.
The dog is barking nonstop.
Why are you wearing gloves
in this heatwave?
-Are you sure it's for you?
-Yes.
Just a second. I forgot to check.
-Are you Kim--
-Yes.
-You're Kim A-reum?
-What?
What?
Jeez!
That young man beat him up...
Yong-sik, can you please call the police?
We're always here for you.
When I got up there, I saw
that little piece of shit walking out.
Gosh, talk about good timing.
I just got a bad feeling the moment I saw
that little piece of shit.
Well, he's not that "little."
We take live ammunition
when we're arresting pricks like him.
But you keep catching them
with your bare hands.
It makes us look like losers.
Are you messing with us?
Will I receive another award?
RECOGNITION AWARD
APPRECIATION AWARD
Yong-sik will become what?
But why would he?
THE 243RD POLICE OFFICERS
APPOINTMENT CEREMONY
I just...
I just caught him because I saw him.
What did you think the moment you saw
the escaped convict?
Well...
Nothing, really.
You see,
I'm not the type
that thinks a lot.
When I see
a criminal,
my body reacts automatically.
I see, when you see criminals?
That's right.
I mean, the second I spot them,
my body automatically...
Gosh, that fool. Why is he saying
the same thing over and over?
I feel something bubbling in my chest,
and my body automatically...
You're probably confused as to whether
you should be happy about this or not,
but what matters is
that he's now a civil servant.
If Yong-sik couldn't join
the police force, he'd end up doing
something ridiculously stupid.
So I knocked. When the door opened...
Aren't you busy?
-You must have a lot of time to kill.
-I took today off.
Why did you take the day off?
I wanted to be here
at this historic moment.
They say that you're bound to poop soon
if you keep farting.
-He was wearing a hat like this.
-You see,
I knew this day would come
when Yong-sik caught the bank robber
with his lunch container.
-I thought he must be...
-Well...
Don't get too close to my son, please.
With the frying pan...
He insisted on working in Seoul,
saying he must date a woman
who was born and raised in Seoul.
That's why he moved there,
but he's still not married.
And why did he get his arm stitched up?
Why jump at someone holding a knife
when he had nothing?
Don't worry.
That temper of his will be tamed
when he meets the right person.
A girl?
Do you think he'll get married?
A rabbit
will meet a dragon.
My gosh, it probably means
that Yong-sik will soar high.
I guess he'll meet a girl
who's like an adorable rabbit.
No. What I'm saying is,
Yong-sik will meet a dragon.
What? Come again?
Yong-sik is a rabbit.
Jeez, are you drunk?
Then where is this dragon?
In the east.
Darn it. You say that all the time.
I don't even know which direction is east.
That way. That's east.
I came by to say hello.
I brought rice cakes.
CAMELLIA
I'm with you.
You definitely need a window.
How could a flower shop
not have any windows?
I guess you'll mainly sell camellias.
Oh, camellias...
I wonder if a flower shop
would do well on this alley.
Gosh, of course.
I buy carnations once a year.
Goodness.
It's actually not a flower shop.
What?
-It's a bar.
-What?
It's a bar called Camellia.
I see.
Are you opening a pub with your husband?
No, I'm doing it alone.
Alone?
-What does your husband do?
-Respect her privacy.
I don't have a husband.
You don't have a husband?
Are you divorced? Or are you a widow?
No, I've never been married.
Oh, really?
Then who's this?
Is he your nephew?
No, he's my son.
You can have a child
without getting married, you know.
I mean, it happens.
Right, it happens.
-Feel free to come by anytime.
-Yes, of course.
I love beer.
I'm saying, how could
a single mother open a bar?
Is there a law that forbids single mothers
from opening bars?
Then widows shouldn't be allowed
to sell marinated crab either.
I sell soju along with marinated crab,
you know.
You probably can't stand me.
No, that's not what I meant.
Is having a husband
something to be that proud of?
I never said that.
Stay-at-home husbands
are useless here in Ongsan.
All they can do is help out
at the parking lot.
This way.
It's still better than not having one.
I only speak the truth.
Chan-suk.
I want my money back.
Pay me back soon.
As soon as you can, okay?
CABBAGE
CAMELLIA
Thank you.
By the way, would it be possible
to only buy half a box of the cabbage?
Sorry?
-Nothing, never mind.
-It's not a flower shop.
Men are practically useless
here in Ongsan.
All they do is break bumpers.
Seung-yeop, what are you doing?
Get ready to open the restaurant.
DAUGHTERS' MARINATED CRAB
Hurry.
Why did my mom even have me
if she was going to give everything
to her daughters?
How many pineapples did you sell?
Not that many. I sold a couple.
MARINATED CRAB
Whether it's the recipe or restaurant,
it's handed down
to either daughters or daughters-in-law.
Get fried chicken on your way home.
The spicy one, right?
-Half and half.
-Okay.
When your wife is your boss,
you basically have to work 24-7.
Coming!
Who'd want to have drinks
at the restaurant
where they've been working all day,
smelling the marinated crab?
We don't even have a place where we can go
and relax with a couple of drinks.
But apparently, it's not a flower shop.
CAMELLIA
Have you ever seen
a newbie surviving here in Ongsan?
I'll be impressed
if she lasts three months.
CAMELLIA
Thanks to the joys and sorrows
of the people of Ongsan,
Camellia survived for six years.
CAMELLIA
6 YEARS LATER
What are you talking about?
I told you I'm at a funeral now.
How did it go? Nice.
SO DELICIOUS
I LOVE SOJU BOMBS
SUPER BASIC ENGLISH VOCABULARY
BASIC ENGLISH
ONGSAN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL NEWSLETTER
Mom, have you decided
on your English name?
Do I have to attend
this counseling session?
All my classmates' moms are coming.
You're going to skip it again?
Is your teacher a foreigner?
Does your teacher only speak English?
What do you want your English name to be?
My English name?
Diana.
Let's go with Diana.
-Diana?
-Yes.
She was a queen of England.
Wait, was she a princess
or a queen consort?
Anyway, she was very stylish and smart.
-She looked very smart.
-Mom, do you want to look smart?
Dongbaek! Can we get more popcorn?
Of course!
You said you'd meet
Princess Diana in Seoul,
but you got demoted before you could
even meet the love of your life.
Why did you get demoted?
I got transferred here, okay?
Let's not call it a demotion, please.
Bullshit.
Why punch someone when you're a cop?
And why did you have to punch him
in front of cameras?
-Look over here.
-Over here!
-Is it true?
-Say a few words!
-Make a comment.
-Say something!
How do you feel right now?
Why did you kill your girlfriend?
She never behaved herself.
I hit her because she deserved it.
-What happened?
-Did he just smack him?
Just go, you prick.
Did you just hit me?
Why did you hit me?
Because you deserve it!
-Yong-sik! Stop.
-Calm down.
ABUSIVE MAN KILLS HIS GIRLFRIEND
WELL DONE,
I LIKE ABUSIVE COPS LIKE HIM
BUT THE RESULT WAS A DEMOTION
Do you think
you're an MMA fighter or what?
You see, I have no regrets whatsoever
regarding the knee strike.
Sure, whatever.
But I'm sad about moving back here
before meeting my Princess Diana in Seoul.
Why does he even like
Princess Diana so much?
My ideal woman
is someone who is smart,
graceful, and intelligent.
You know what I mean.
Simply put, someone
who looks like she always came in fifth
or higher on exams back in school.
That's the kind of woman
I'm talking about.
Are you hungry for intelligence?
Ideally, someone who lives in Seoul,
not in the countryside.
That vibe, you know?
Then why'd you get transferred here
before you could even date one?
The strange thing is,
women who are Seoul natives
aren't the only ones in the city.
-What?
-Strangely enough,
every woman I hit it off with
was from the countryside.
What's so strange about it?
Country bumpkins can recognize each other.
Gosh, come on.
I probably shouldn't say this
in front of the people from my hometown...
but in my case,
everyone thinks I'm from Seoul.
Okay, sure. Let's have a welcoming party.
There is a Diana in Ongsan too.
Gosh, I don't go to such bars
where the ladies are.
Goodness, that place isn't like that.
Are you really close to her?
Well, we are close...
like friends.
-Friends?
-Figures.
You're the biggest VIP here, Mr. No.
He's probably the only one
who drinks Chivas Regal in Ongsan.
Of course.
Hey, Dongbaek. I'll take another Chivas.
Oh, and you know...
Do you have any peanuts?
Do you want more peanuts?
Yes, I brought
prestigious assemblymen of our district,
so give me some peanuts on the house.
You must be close if you're asking
for something on the house.
Peanuts
are 8,000 won. I'll bring it to you.
Forget it. You can go.
I thought you two were friends.
I thought you were close to her.
Sir.
Yes?
Why do you call my mom "Dongbaek"?
Well, that's the name of this place.
Then do you call Jun-gi's mom "Crabs"
and Dae-seong's mom "Pork Belly"?
What? Wait a minute.
Then what should I call her?
She's the CEO here. Call her CEO.
What? Okay, fine.
And if you ever
speak casually to her again,
I won't give you free refills
on corn puffs.
I thought he might say he'll beat me up.
How did a softy like Dongbaek
give birth to a smarty pants like him?
He must have taken after his dad.
All right, Ji-seon.
You're eating so well.
Oh, yes. We...
We do it together. I help out a lot.
ABOUT YOUR BEAUTIFUL WIFE, MRS. KANG
I LOVE YOU, MY JESSICA
Come on, tell them.
Oh, yes. She's beautiful, really.
She always makes me say, "Do you
think looking pretty is everything?"
Do you want me to wash it?
Viewers have been complaining on the board
that you always pretend to eat
and never actually eat.
Do you have to film us eating this?
Let's cut it here.
UPLOADING
#BODYCHECK, #DIETER, #BUT_ATE_CAKE,
#I'M_MRS_KANG_JONG-RYEOL
How can you be so selfish?
If you're going to eat instant noodles,
eat it after I go to my mom's.
Do you have to eat it now?
And did you have to add the eggs?
I have to eat to go to train.
At least let me eat some instant noodles.
Gosh, you're so selfish.
Am I the one who's selfish, or is it you?
Your husband's an athlete.
How can you stop me from eating at home?
If you wanted a supportive wife,
why did you marry me?
I didn't ask you to be one.
Just let me be
when I try to cook for myself.
I never asked you to cook for me.
Do you think I married you
to cook for you?
No,
you married me to take pictures.
You're going from building 101 to 103.
You don't need a mask.
You aren't that famous.
Even the idol star who lives
in building 105 doesn't use one.
Tell me next time when there's a shooting.
If they come so suddenly, I won't do it.
Do you think they're stupid?
They already noticed that
we don't live together.
That's why you need to step up your game.
With what? My acting?
Jong-ryeol,
it's me, Jessica.
And what does that mean?
I'm a public figure.
Why are you a public figure?
Did you see that check mark
on my social media account?
I have 77,000 followers.
Right, you upload what you eat,
how you sleep, and how you wash up.
I'd follow you out of curiosity.
And...
will you please put on some clothes?
You must think those tights are sexy,
but it makes you look like
a black lollipop.
Why do you care if I get undressed?
I don't take off my clothes for you,
so mind your own business.
Or should I say, in your dreams?
Hey, all you are is pretty, aren't you?
That's all who you are.
Why does that kid cry so much?
"That kid"?
She's not someone else's child.
Is she?
Why is life so tough?
Why do I...
still feel like...
Daddy is the delinquent.
The delinquent.
What's wrong? Why are you sulky again?
What's wrong?
Really?
Ongsan Police Station
couldn't even catch Joker!
Wake up!
-Wake up!
-Good work.
Goodbye.
We cannot live like this!
What's with them?
Did Joker kill someone again?
-Wake up!
-Joker has been quiet for five years.
-Wake up.
But someone made a movie on it
that drew 10 million.
A movie?
It's titled Don't Be a Joke.
-Oh, that one.
-Wake up!
Ongsan was recently known
for marinated crabs,
but five to six years ago,
it was infamous for Joker.
Wake up!
Our land prices finally began to soar,
and we almost got a new image
with marinated crabs.
Why did he film a movie
-with the Ongsan serial murder?
-Wake up!
They're going to ruin the marinated crabs
if they filmed the movie.
Why do you suddenly bring the crabs up?
How can he be so selfish about his movie?
What about my marinated crabs?
The director of that movie is a jerk.
Does that idiot hold a grudge against us?
Come on, Mom. Stop swearing.
Exactly.
So why can't they catch Joker to this day?
You're right.
Why can't you catch that petty killer?
He may look like a joke,
but he's not petty.
I mean, his name itself is a joke.
He's named Joker.
That psycho left a message
whenever he killed someone.
It said, "Don't be a joke."
And what does he mean by that?
He just randomly said, "Don't be a joke."
Should I catch him?
Chief Byeon, you still have the case file.
You were demoted because of that.
I wasn't demoted. I was reappointed.
Why would you take a look
at the case file for Joker?
Mom, it's me.
I have a certain power
to end crimes no matter where--
Forget that.
Go to Yeong-sim's garlic field.
Yeong-sim's? Why?
Okay, fine.
-You'll get sick if you leave it out.
-I can do it. I'll do it.
-My gosh.
-My goodness.
Anyway, what did you find
in her field? Money?
A body?
Her dog might give birth to puppies
any day. Take a look at that.
Why should I care
if a dog is giving birth?
The poultry farm's dog
apparently impregnated her dog.
You need to be sharp and decide
if the puppies belong
to the poultry farm or to Yeong-sim.
My gosh, we have to be sharp for nothing.
What did you say?
Do you think
Yeong-sim's property rights are a joke?
Forget that.
Now that I got demoted...
No, reappointed,
I'm going to go after Joker.
Hey, will you keep saying that?
It's not the time for me
to go around finding out the truth
about the birth of some puppies.
Then what time is it?
To catch Joker,
we should be like CSI: Miami.
How can you become someone in CSI?
Not even in your next life.
There's a place I always visit
when I go to a new town.
Go to Yeong-sim's place.
I always go to the hall of knowledge of
that town, the bookstore. But where is it?
Why should you go to a bookstore?
Chief Byeon.
Henry Ward Beecher said,
"Where is human nature so weak
as in the bookstore?"
Hey, do you have any idea
what that Henry something did?
He's a higher being,
a guy who has quoted sayings.
You should stop using famous quotes
and lurking around bookstores, okay?
Why not?
You are
a type who looks much cooler
when you get physical
instead of trying to use your brains.
You know, an upright person.
An upright style.
My goodness.
Man, it gets a bit too awkward
to bring this up myself.
People think I studied humanities.
Go.
You can go to the bookstore.
I'm serious.
Darn it, how are Koreans
supposed to investigate?
Just like what Henry said,
did the bookstore weaken my nature?
If I had met her
at a marinated crab store,
what could have changed?
No,
to be honest...
I was smitten by her
only because she was pretty.
I can't believe
there's a pervert at a bookstore.
Her historic first words...
shot Cupid's arrows into my heart.
PREGNANCY, FIRST TIME BREASTFEEDING
Excuse me.
My first historic words were...
I'm a bachelor.
I'm a real bachelor. A real one.
Oh, my shirt.
That could happen.
Oh, that's not what...
Not in that sense.
-He must be insane.
-Excuse me.
I'll put these right here.
Yes.
Here's my philosophy, so listen up.
It's not "No money, no service."
It's "No manners, no service."
She's so fluent.
And no peanuts for No Gyu-tae.
No Gyu-tae will
never get peanuts in his life.
Don't take appointments from him, okay?
HONG JA-YEONG LAW OFFICE
Seung-yeop.
There's a law office downtown, right?
Why? Did you get in trouble again?
Is someone going to sue you?
If she can read English books,
she probably studied abroad, right?
Will someone who studied abroad sue you?
Kang Pil-gu! Keep your eyes on the ball!
I saw this lady today.
Is she pretty?
But she seemed like
she's way out of my league.
Is she pretty?
She's a lawyer.
A lawyer?
She's a lawyer, and she's pretty?
I think I met the real Princess Diana.
Princess Diana is going to sue you?
CAMELLIA, DONGBAEK
LAWYER HONG JA-YEONG
I didn't want to come all the way here,
but Mr. No won't pick up his phone,
and he won't give me what he owes.
You must be Dongbaek.
You don't have
any eye wrinkles.
Pardon?
THREE DAYS AGO
Don't you use tens of such products?
That's the most expensive one
with the least volume.
This is it?
-What?
-This is it?
Goodness.
Should I have bought you a handbag?
NOT FOR SALE
BUY 100ML, GET 20ML FREE!
For the first time,
my husband bought me eye cream.
But he gave the 100ml eye cream
to someone else
and gave me the 20ml free gift.
Team Doosan ended up
winning the first half of the game...
CAMELLIA, DONGBAEK
"Dongbaek."
I think I know
who got the 100ml eye cream.
Honey.
Do you know what I specialize in?
I'm a divorce attorney, you know.
So what? You want a divorce?
All I do at work is gather evidence
to prove that my client's spouse
holds liability.
Everything can act as evidence
starting from receipts
to navigation records.
Why are you telling me that?
Just in case you forgot what my job is.
I'm No Gyu-tae's wife.
Pardon?
Hello, ma'am.
This is my first time meeting you.
I rarely meet the tenants.
Right.
If I knew beforehand,
I would've brought some juice or...
By the way, don't you know
how to finish your sentence?
Pardon?
I noticed that you keep having trouble
finishing your sentences.
Did I do that?
I didn't realize--
See? You did it again.
Oh, I did it again.
I'm sorry.
You must think it's cute.
No, that's not what I think.
But...
My husband goes there often, right?
Seems like he goes there
five times a week.
Yes, well...
I keep telling him
that it's not good to drink too much.
So I told him not to come too often.
But he still shows up?
Why do you think so?
Should I tell him not to come?
No, be nice to him.
You should always smile
and be kind to him.
After all, that's your job.
I'm telling you to do your job.
Well...
It's not my job to smile.
What are you doing here?
Let's talk outside.
CONGRATULATIONS
-Hear me out here.
-My goodness.
-Thank you.
-Mr. No owns all the land
starting from the mill in the market
up until the mud flat.
I only own about five buildings.
And his cousin's sister's husband
and our superintendent are almost in-laws.
My goodness.
But what do you mean
they're almost in-laws?
Anyway, he's the most influential guy
in our neighborhood.
Your life will work out just fine
in this neighborhood
if you stay good friends with Mr. No.
-Thank you for this.
-No problem.
By the way, it sounds like
you run some kind of a business.
He and his wife
both have specialized jobs.
My gosh.
People call us the couple
who have specialized jobs.
My wife's an attorney.
She's an attorney?
Meanwhile, he runs--
You know how they say
the smartest doctors are eye doctors?
Studying the eyes of humans
is something that requires
a lot of education and intelligence.
Then you must be--
Yes, I'm an optician.
I see.
Then I'm guessing
all the attorneys in this neighborhood
or people who work in a similar field
would all be pretty close to each other.
They must all be colleagues.
Much closer than that.
People in Ongsan even ask my wife
to name their fourth-generation only son.
My goodness.
She's the most highly educated person
in our neighborhood.
This isn't something I say.
It's what other people say.
They say she's fit to be
the next first lady of Ongsan.
Oh, right.
He's going to become
the next governor of Ongsan.
He's practically a politician.
I'd love to hold a welcoming party
for our new neighbor.
-Goodness.
-That's not necessary.
But would it be low for a politician
to buy a cop drinks?
My goodness.
ONGSAN MARINATED CRABS
Why does she always go to the public bath
when she doesn't even have a husband?
-Hello.
-Hey.
Dongbaek, you must be happy
to earn so much money.
I heard the alumni
of Ongsan High School of Engineering
got together at your place.
They made a reservation last minute,
so it was really hectic.
Yes, I'm sure it was last minute.
They were supposed to come to my place.
But I guess I lost my customers to you.
I'm sorry.
I never intended on taking your customers.
I wonder why people always go to your bar.
Do you have a special business secret?
People always say they really enjoy
my stir-fried pork.
Then does that mean
my marinated crabs taste bad?
That's not what I meant.
Dongbaek, let's live ethically.
Let's not do anything
to embarrass our kids, okay?
NO GYU-TAE
Why won't she take reservations
when there's not a single customer here?
No manners, no service.
She doesn't want
to take Mr. Peanut's reservations.
What? "Mr. Peanut"?
You really need to stop
hitting on Dongbaek.
And stop obsessing over peanuts.
My gosh, she should be scared
of her landlord.
It doesn't matter
if you're the landlord or not.
You don't stand a chance against her.
She's a hippopotamus.
What would your kid learn from you?
You shouldn't do anything
to embarrass your kid.
-I...
-Yes?
I'm not ashamed.
What?
I didn't do anything to embarrass my son.
I'm not very well off,
and I raised him without a dad.
So I always feel sorry about that.
But I'm not ashamed.
I didn't do anything
to be ashamed of myself.
She's the only one who's still working.
Mr. No purposely created this gathering
to welcome you to the neighborhood.
Let her save her face.
Use this chance to introduce yourself.
Then why can't we just meet
at a barbecue restaurant?
I don't want to go to a hostess bar.
My gosh, it's not that kind of place.
You called her the Queen of Ongsan.
It's just a figure of speech.
To be honest,
it's because we have
no other place to go.
Did you just shit your pants?
Where can we go?
How about this place?
I wonder if my fate would've changed
if it weren't for this
peculiar neighborhood.
My gosh.
I thought the chief was joking
when he said there's nowhere to go
even though there are tons
of restaurants in Ongsan.
Let's just go here.
That's his sister-in-law's restaurant.
Can you pour drinks to your boss
in front of your sister-in-law?
I could understand that much,
so I let them off the hook.
But when I said we should go
to the whelk restaurant,
they said it's run by
the newbie's mother-in-law's friend.
He once got beaten up by his wife
for mentioning his first love there
after he got drunk.
It's always someone's
mother-in-law, sister-in-law,
or the best friend of someone's wife.
This place is filled with spies.
Would you drink at a place that
reports everything to your wife?
I really had nothing to say to that.
So I walked toward the eye of storm
thinking that this neighborhood
is still practically a clan.
We all have a good reason
for always coming here.
My gosh, what are you doing?
This is where our neutral nation stands.
CAMELLIA
-Come inside.
-My goodness.
My goodness, Mr. No. You're already here.
It's only right for the politician
to wait for the government officials.
This place is so tacky.
You're ready to be a politician.
-Sit down. Take your seats.
-Let's all sit down.
-Sit down.
-How's your business going?
-My gosh, it's all going well.
-Why won't this work?
My goodness.
-My gosh.
-Hyang-mi.
You could've killed us. You're practically
a terrorist for doing this.
Just leave her be.
She doesn't care about living a long life.
Guys who eat dog meat for nutrition,
smoke heated tobacco,
and cut down on alcohol
are always the ones
who end up dying in a car crash.
Plus, I don't think
I'll be living a long life anyway.
That's why I just live
in the present moment.
Is she supposed to be the Queen of Ongsan?
She's kind at heart.
Just make sure
you don't lose your lighter.
-What?
-She's a kleptomaniac.
A kleptomaniac?
She doesn't steal anything expensive.
But everything she sees
goes into her pocket.
But she's still kind at heart.
I want to go home.
Don't you have any hands?
I thought you were
going to pour me a drink.
That's not how it works here.
No, that's not what I meant.
It's just that she joined us.
She just likes to drink.
She does whatever she wants,
so don't mind her.
She'll leave after a few drinks.
Well, I guess that's why
she's called the Queen of Ongsan.
She does everything she wants.
It's not her.
I know this isn't the city,
but we have high standards too.
I'm younger and prettier than Dongbaek.
Show us your ID.
Hey, come on.
Dongbaek is the Diana of Ongsan.
"Dongbaek"?
Dongbaek, what's fresh today?
How about some small octopus?
No, but we have some fresh cabbages.
It's a thumbs up.
She's the Diana of Ongsan.
Isn't she beautiful?
The queen of my heart turned out the be
the Queen of Ongsan.
Hyang-mi, can we talk for a second?
Okay.
"A thumbs up."
Hyang-mi, your hourly pay is 8,500 won.
And that doesn't include the right
to sit with the customers
and pop their beer bottles
so you could have a sip.
I hired you as a waitress.
But you keep sitting down
with the customers.
This isn't that kind of bar.
Dongbaek.
If I don't even get
to drink alcohol for free,
why would I work here
and only get paid 8,500 won per hour?
Okay.
The woman I fell for isn't an attorney.
She isn't fluent in English either.
But I realized something.
Those weren't the reasons
why I fell for her.
I could only think of one thing
in my head.
She's pretty, and that's a fact.
Excuse me.
Have you ever lived in the city?
The academy just ended.
Buy some dumplings on your way home.
Okay, I'll be right there.
I should get going now.
Give me peanuts!
Peanuts.
Give me some peanuts for free
before you leave.
But the peanuts are--
What? They're 8,000 won?
Go ahead and say that one more time
if you have the guts to do so.
Gosh, he's so obsessed with peanuts.
Let me be frank here.
I'm the only person in this neighborhood
who buys hard liquor here.
I'm the only one.
I'm the only person who buys hard liquor,
and I'm also your landlord.
But you never once
gave me peanuts for free.
Mr. No, I'll get going now.
I need to get going.
Then have half a shot.
You never accept my drinks.
Mr. No, you're drunk.
Okay, fine. You know what?
If you drink this shot,
I won't raise the rent until next year.
You look down on me, don't you?
Why?
Because I'm not a governor?
Why? Why do you look down on me?
-Sir, I think you're drunk.
-No, I'm fine.
Don't raise the rent.
The cops here all heard what you said.
The alcohol tastes sweet.
I really wanted a shot today.
Thank you, sir.
You see?
It's so nice to see you smile.
Just think of me as a hometown friend.
You should sometimes
serve peanuts for free,
have some drinks with me,
and give me a smile every now and then.
I mean, how nice is that?
-Mr. No.
-Yes?
The whelks are 15,000 won,
the stir-fried pork is 12,000 won,
and the conches are 8,000 won.
But that price doesn't include
your right to touch me or my smile.
What?
I...
only sell alcohol.
The only thing you can buy here
is just alcohol.
That's it.
CAMELLIA
My gosh, let's go now.
Hey.
You only gave me 85,000 won.
You're supposed to pay 93,000 won.
I'm not going to pay for the peanuts.
What is it with you and peanuts?
I definitely asked her
to give me peanuts for free.
So why are you asking me to pay for that?
I'm not going to pay.
I can't pay for that.
-My gosh.
-Hyang-mi.
Hey, Dongbaek.
I tend to hold a big grudge.
That's all I can pay you.
Just take it or leave it.
Thank you, Mr. No.
Goodbye.
Mr. No, you drank a bit too much today.
I mean, come on.
The peanuts aren't the problem.
I always pay her with cash
for her own good.
I pay with cash, okay?
Don't be so harsh.
She's just trying to make a living.
The peanuts aren't the problem.
I have a problem with her sincerity.
-Excuse me.
-You see, I tend to be mean
to the people I like.
I never asked her to date me or anything.
I just asked her to be friends.
-Excuse me!
-But she's always so cold to me.
Give me 8,000 won.
You should pay Dongbaek 8,000 won.
Are you drunk?
What's with you?
Even the constable is causing a fuss
now that he sees Dongbaek
treat me with disrespect.
Stop nitpicking
and just give me 8,000 won.
No, I can't.
I won't give you that money.
If you give me 8,000 won,
I promise that nothing will happen.
My gosh, you're so scary.
What are you going to do
if I don't give it to you?
-Come on. Stop it.
-What will you do?
That's enough.
Hey, unclench your fist.
What's with that look in your eyes?
Not only did he clench his fist,
but he's even biting his lip.
It looks like you're about to hit me.
Well, go ahead.
Go ahead and hit me. Come on. Hit me.
Hit me!
You...
What...
Give that back to him.
That's stealing.
Did a police constable
just steal the future governor's wallet?
My gosh.
Hey, get over here!
You practically stole from me!
Hey! That guy stole from me!
I'm sorry for going home late.
Okay, I'll buy the dumplings and go home.
CAMELLIA
Dongbaek!
Wait!
-This is for the peanuts.
-What?
This money's from No Gyu-tae's wallet.
Why are you...
This money belongs to you.
You came back to give me this?
Yes.
Thank you.
But why did you...
My name is Hwang Yong-sik.
Oh, okay.
-I thought you were just pretty.
-What?
I thought you were just pretty.
But you're also really cool.
Me?
I became a fan
the moment you gave him a lecture
about the peanuts.
Did you drink a lot?
I don't know what to say right now but...
-Can I come back tomorrow?
-What?
Yes, sure.
I think I'll be here tomorrow
and the day after.
What a complete weirdo.
I think...
I think I'd want to come here every day.
Can I do that? Is that okay?
CAMELLIA
I LOVE ONLY YOU
POLICE
I feel like you always catch me
in my most embarrassing moments.
Please mind your own business.
I'm going to take legal action!
If I was her guardian,
you'd be dead already.
Are you starting to become curious
about your dad?
-Not really.
-Why are you paying for him to play games?
Dongbaek!
Do you even know what kind of mess
Hyang-mi's been getting herself into?
I sometimes feel like the neighbors
are a bit too mean to me.
Let's do "that."
Is it okay if I side with you and Pil-gu?
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi