[English subtitles are available]
[My Unicorn Girl]
[Episode 10]
[Fighting, my Unicorn guy (girl)]
-Coach.
Yan Wu Xu.
-Coach Ma.
-Did you see Meng Qi?
-He went out early in the morning.
I can't contact him.
Never mind, you guys handle this then.
The speed skating department has added
a friendly match today.
They will be using the skating rink.
The 3 on 3 match has been moved to 11 a.m.
It's 9 a.m. now.
Notify everyone, quick.
-Yes, Yes.
-Alright.
[Group chat.]
[Notify to everyone.]
[Da Qiang, Liu Xing Yun, Ling Bao,
Hong Tian, Huang Hao Ran, Li Fei, Li He.]
[Because the speed skating department
needs to use the skating rink,]
[Lu Yan, Sang Tian, Wen Bing,
Shen Wei Lian, Siao Siao, Sheng Yi Ming.]
[The match has been changed to 11 a.m.]
[All new students and seniors
must be here on time.]
Of all people, how dare you
provoke our captain.
Isn’t doing such a thing too much?
What's wrong with it?
We need to teach them a lesson.
Otherwise, they won't remember it.
And, who is Wen Bing?
He is the playboy who provokes
the younger sister of our captain.
And that Sang Tian,
he is so close to Senior Miao Miao.
He didn't ask about
the relationship...
between Senior Miao Miao
and our captain before he comes here.
And also that...
Shen Wei Lian.
I feel disturbed whenever I see him.
He is naive.
But, Coach Ma wants us to
notify everyone...
that the match has
been changed to 11 a.m.
If we didn't notify the 3 of them,
the coach will find out
and the blame will be on us.
If we say nothing, who would know,
right?
There are more than 30 persons,
so it's normal to miss one or two of them.
If they ask, just say that
we don't have their contact.
And I think that as  classmates,
they will notify each other.
So I know how to deal with the coach.
-There is no need to worry about this.
-Both of you are so mean.
I'm going to tell Coach Ma now.
-Don't.
-Let go of your hand.
No.
We were kidding just now.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
Let go of your hand.
Junior. This is our fault.
It's still early now.
You can still notify them.
At least you speak like a human.
Let go of my hand.
[3 on 3 match changed to 11 a.m.]
[Sent.]
-What are you doing?
-Get inside.
Close the door, close it.
Open the door. Open it.
Open the door.
I won't let you go.
[Shen Wei Lian: The match
has been changed to 11 a.m.]
A prank?
[Sorry, the number
you've dialled is unavailable.]
[Please call again later.]
Anyway, you are going to
complain about us sooner or later.
I will drag someone along with me
before I'm doomed.
You are shameless.
-Open the Door.
-I am shameless.
It's a weekend today. No one is using
the academic building now.
Open the door now.
Come back and open the door. Come back.
Come back.
Xiao Rou.
Is this shirt okay?
Will it tear later?
Tian Tian. Are you too used to
wearing men's clothing?
Why would you feel uncomfortable
in women's clothing?
Maybe you should try
to disguise as a man.
Actually, idol drama
is wrong to say that...
we can switch freely between
boy and girl.
Xiao Rou, actually...
I have an ominous hunch today.
Do you think that something will
be happen? I'm so uncomfortable.
Don't talk nonsense.
Today is your big day to start over.
Can you stay in Liuye or not?
Will you have a wonderful day tomorrow?,
It all depends on just today.
After the performance ends,
I will watch your match.
Let's go, it's showtime.
Did the match's schedule change?
Did you see Sang Tian?
No.
[Shi Mi Milk Tea Shop.
Closed every Saturday morning.]
[Roadshow at Civic Square.]
[Welcome, friends.
Support us if you're free. Love you.]
Nice.
Wonderful.
Nice, nice.
Fighting.
- Nice.
- Xiao Rou, I can't catch up.
You need to have more confidence
in yourself. You dance great.
Really?
Nice, nice, nice.
Nice, nice.
Good dance.
Nice.
-Tian Tian, what happened?
-What's going on?
What?
Nice.
-What is Wen Bing doing here?
-Wen Bing?
-Turn around.
-Nice.
Xiao Rou. I can't help you today.
I will leave now.
Hurry. I can handle this.
-Then I will go first.
-Go.
-Thank you, everyone.
-Why did you stop dancing?
What happened?
You're a girl.
I'm not a girl.
Don't take my photos.
I...
Excuse me, did you see this boy?
I'm looking for him for an urgent matter.
[This guy didn't recognise me.]
Well, I can help you
convey your message to him.
Help me to tell him that,
the 3 on 3 match today
has moved up to 11a.m.
It's 11a.m.?
Inform him quickly.
-Alright.
-Wait.
Your glasses.
Thank you.
-Here, Tian Tian.
-Did he recognise me?
How could it be possible?
Your dressing was so ugly.
And prosopagnosia can't recognise
facial features.
-It won't happen, don't worry.
-Alright, I will go first.
Hurry. Tian Tian, be sure
to do your best for the game.
I am at school now.
You need to hurry too,
see you at the match.
Want to take a ride?
Of course.
I thought you said that you have
went back. Why are you still here?
I haven't got a taxi yet.
Come on.
Hold tight.
Do you know how to ride?
Didn't I ask you hold tight?
Hands will get cold when riding.
Hurry, it's too late now.
Coach Ma.
Coach Ma,
don't go.
This is a small present, hope you like it.
Take your small present
and leave the ice rink.
Just take a look.
You may be surprised.
What complimentary gift are you
using to fool me again.
I use my life to guarantee that...
this present is authentic.
Not a complimentary gift.
It is real.
I'm so tired.
-Hurry up.
-Hold it. Faster, hold it.
Goodbye.
Hurry, go on.
-Coach.
-Hurry.
Coach.
Let's eat something first.
Why haven’t Brother Wen Bing
reached yet?
Brother, can the game time
be delayed a bit?
Wen Bing hasn’t reached yet.
We have notified everyone that
the time has changed.
You will be disqualified if
you are absent.
This is the rule.
The rule is fixed,
but people are flexible.
Aren't you the captain
of the school team?
Help me plead to Coach Ma, please.
Na Na, it's useless for anyone to plead.
Maybe, Wen Bing's delay is intentional.
-Maybe he's scared.
-You say it again.
What are you talking about?
I wonder who is the scared one.
The match has changed time.
But no one notified me, Wen Bing,
and Sang Tian on purpose.
And locked me in the toilet.
Luckily the cleaners helped me
open the door.
-Where is Wen Bing now?
-He hasn't reached yet?
I notified him before
my phone was taken away.
Where is my phone?
-What are you talking about?
-Where is my phone?
I will deal with you later.
Meng Qi, let me tell you.
If Brother Wen Bing is late
because of your trick,
I won't forgive you forever.
What? Na Na.
I don't even know about this.
I don't want to listen to your excuse.
You better pray that
Brother Wen Bing won't be late.
Na Na.
-Why are they not here yet?
-Yeah.
Why are they not here yet?
-Where are they?
-Well...
Coach.
Wen Bing and Sang Tian
haven't reached yet.
Can the game be delayed a bit?
-Coach, let's wait for them.
Just wait a while.
Begging me won't do any help.
What if this is the Winter Olympic Games?
Wei Lian.
You're finally here.
I thought I got stood up again.
No worries about that. Just get ready to
set off the firecrackers after the game.
Yours.
What.
What is this?
This is our unique mark, the iron trio.
Let's do our best.
We must win.
I repeat the rules of 3 on 3.
There is only 1 game.
20 minutes for the game.
Will the game be extended
if it is a draw?
If it is a draw,
you will win.
Great.
Seniors have showed
their kindness.
Do you have any objections?
Of course not.
Then, the game starts now.
[The players are,
Team Freshman, Wen Bing.]
[Team Senior, Meng Qi.]
[Team Freshmen, Shen Wei Lian.]
[Team Senior, Chong Kai Wen.]
[Team Freshman, Sang Tian.]
[Team Senior, Huang Zhi Lie.]
[Game starts, the referee is kicking off.]
[Wen Bing takes the lead
as he took the puck from Meng Qi.]
[He passed through the defense made
by Chong Kai Wen and Huang Zhi Lie.]
[He runs directly to the goal post.]
[Huang Zhi Lie chases him closely.]
[Wen Bing makes a turn and
leaves Huang Zhi Lie.]
Brother Wen Bing, fighting.
[Meng Qi suddenly makes
a fierce attack.]
[Like the Mars hit on the Earth,
he hits Wen Bing onto the boundary wall.]
Foul. How could he
hit people like this?
[Meng Qi catches up.]
[With his superior skills to control
the puck, he passed Shen Wei Lian.]
[Nice.]
[He passed by the agile Sang Tian.]
[Sang Tian tries to block the ball.]
[Interception failed.]
[Meng Qi runs to the goal.
Ready to shoot.]
[Goal scored. Meng Qi takes
the first point for Team Senior.]
[They are on the lead
with one to zero score.]
[The game continues.]
[Wen Bing of Team Freshman and
Meng Qi of Team Senior will kick off.]
[Wen Bing gets the puck and
passes it to Sang Tian.]
[Sang Tian passes it
to Shen Wei Lian.]
[Shen Wei Lian passes the ball
to Wen Bing.]
[It seems like Team Freshman
has great teamwork.]
[Meng Qi moves on.]
[He keeps watching Wen Bing.]
[Follow him closely.]
[Chong Kai Wen came out.]
[And hit the right side of Wen Bing.
Wen Bing has been hit.]
What kind of people does
my brother mingle with? Rogues?
[Meng Qi takes the puck and
passes through the midfield.]
[He enters the defense zone.]
[Sang Tian follows him closely.]
[Meng Qi tries to shake Sang Tian off.]
[Nice job, the puck has been
taken by Wen Bing.]
[Huang Zhi Lie and Chong
Kai Wen tries to intercept.]
[Shen Wei Lian escorts Wen Bing.]
[Meng Qi catches up.]
[Meng Qi catches up with Wen Bing.
They are sticking with each other.]
[Wen Bing leaves Meng Qi.]
[And he is ready to pass the ball to
his teammates.]
[Chong Kai Wen hits again.]
Look out.
[Wen Bing falls badly this time.]
[Shen Wei Lian gets the puck.]
[He shoots.]
[It slipped away from the intercept of
Yan Wu Xu. Goal scored.]
[Team Freshman brought up the score.]
Nice.
Wen Bing, how are you?
Is it serious?
Are you okay?
I'm fine, just get one more point.
We can win the game.
Let's go.
How is this fine?
Go and get some rest, hurry.
Wei Lian.
Let's go.
Coach Ma.
How is he?
Medicine chest.
Hold back.
They are too ruthless.
Brother Wen Bing.
No, let's send him to the school clinic.
Are you playing ice hockey
for the first time?
You're making such a big fuss.
-Are you really okay?
-I'm fine, really.
No, you have to go.
-You...
-If you're worried,
how about I take an X-ray after the game?
Don't push yourself too hard.
Avoid them when you are back at the match.
Do you hear me?
Wen Bing.
Are you all right?
You need to trust Wen Bing.
Wen Bing is fine.
[There are only 5 minutes
left in the game.]
[The two sides are still deadlocked.]
[Meng Qi tried to make a long shoot.]
[But it gets blocked
by the goalkeeper.]
[The puck fell into Shen Wei Lian's hand.]
[Shen Wei Lian passes the puck
to Sang Tian.]
Pass.
[Wen Bing is shouting to Sang Tian to
pass the puck to him.]
[But Sang Tian passes it
to Shen Wei Lian.]
[Is it because he wants to protect
Wen Bing who is injured?]
[Sang Tian made a mistake.]
[Meng Qi gets back the puck.]
[Wen Bing approaches him.
Does he want to intercept?]
[Awesome. He intercepted
the puck from behind.]
[Wen Bing turns around and attacks
the defense zone of Team Senior.]
[Meng Qi approaches.]
[He pushes Wen Bing
to the boundary wall.]
This is too over.
Fighting.
Coach Xue, can you talk to
Coach Ma?
Can she let Wen Bing rest?
He seems to be injured.
Please. Just a while.
-No.
-Coach Xue, please.
Do you know how important
this game is for him?
Can you watch the game quietly?
Who are you?
I'm talking to about Wen Bing.
Mind your own business.
What's the matter with you?
He is Wen Bing's uncle.
[Meng Qi passes through the midfield.]
[Sang Tian is like a cheetah,
he runs towards Meng Qi.]
[And falls like a kitten.]
[Meng Qi attacked towards the goal post.]
[Goal scored.]
[Team Senior leads with 2:1.]
Did you get hurt?
I'm fine.
Fighting.
Do you believe in a miracle?
But now...
Time is almost up.
Do you dare to make a bet with me?
I bet that you can stay in Liuye.
[There is only one minute
left for the game.]
[Can the Team Freshman
bring up the score?]
[Let's see.]
[Wen Bing passes the puck to Sang Tian.]
[Sang Tian passed by Huang Zhi Lie
and Chong Kai Wen with the puck.]
[Meng Qi intercepts the puck.]
[Shen Wei Lian hits Meng Qi.]
[Sorry, I was wrong.
It was Wen Bing who pushed Meng Qi away.]
[The speed of Wen Bing is too fast.]
[Sang Tian passes
the puck to Shen Wei Lian.]
[Shen Wei Lian passes to Wen Bing.]
[An awesome long pass.]
[Sang Tian gets the puck.]
[He directly attacks the goal.]
[He is ready to shoot.]
[Goal, it was awesome.]
[Team Freshman brings up the score,
it is 2:2.]
Well done.
Sang Tian, you're so awesome.
I knew we will win.
Sang Tian, good job.
-Coach.
We have won the seniors.
You need to keep your promise.
Wen Bing has shown his leadership
in the game today.
So I decided to let him replace Sang Tian
to become the monitor.
Wen Bing becomes the monitor?
I don't want to be the monitor.
Sang Tian is more suitable than me.
This is an order.
Coach, didn't you say that
if we win the competition,
we can make any request?
-Yeah.
Alright.
I don't want a Husky now.
I want Sang Tian to
continue to be the monitor.
Can you let me finish my word?
Starting from today,
Sang Tian will be the assistant monitor.
You shall assist in Wen Bing's job.
Coach Ma, does this mean...
Both of you, do your best.
Don't let me down.
Everyone performed well today.
Keep it up.
You are dismissed.
Monitor.
No, assistant monitor.
Why you don't make a deal with Coach Ma?
I'm happy enough
to be able to stay in Liuye.
I don't have any other requests.
What the hell.
You have no desires.
What about you?
Why didn't you make a deal?
I'm the same as him.
You should have let us win.
The deal allows for anything, but it
was wasted by both of you.
It's so boring, let's go.
Since there is no one around,
can you tell me...
what have you told Coach Ma secretly?
You were acting mysteriously.
I won't let you know.
-Tell me.
-No.
-Alright
-We are on the same team.
Wen Bing.
You're awake.
Are you okay?
You cried.
No, I didn't.
Then why are your eyes red?
Maybe it's conjunctivitis.
Brother Wen Bing.
You, are you okay?
Do you need an operation?
Will there be any consequences
after the operation?
Where is the school doctor?
Why is there no doctor
in such a large infirmary?
Who is responsible
if there is a delay?
The school doctor checked on him.
Nothing serious.
How is it?
Mild dislocation.
Dislocation.
Does he need to be hospitalised?
If needed, let me take care of him.
Excuse me, sorry.
Here.
Get up.
I will fix your arm for you.
Here.
Sang Tian, I will need your help
in the next few days.
Yeah, and this.
Apply it once each morning and night.
Remember, massage
at least ten minutes every day.
Let me do this.
Girls are more attentive.
Who said that a boy must be careless?
Oh my god.
Right?
No. Let me do this.
He hurt his arm.
He needs to take off his clothes
when he uses medicine.
It is inconvenient for a girl.
-I don't mind.
-I mind.
If the treatment delays,
it will get worse.
All right. Enough.
Sang Tian, I'll count on you.
Stop staring, let's go.
Let Sang Tian helps him to apply
the medicine. Go, go, go.
-Brother Wen Bing, have a good rest.
-Let's go
I will see you tomorrow.
Stop looking. He needs to apply medicine.
You better don't mess up.
Well,
I didn't know that
you're Wen Bing's uncle.
I was rude to you in the skating rink.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
After all, there are very few
young and promising uncles like me.
I forgive you.
Can I add your contact?
You can ask me anything about
Wen Bing in school at any time.
I'm sure no one in Liuye cares
more about him...
and understands him more than me.
There is no need for that.
I can understand him myself.
And, if you really care about him,
please look for your brother
immediately.
And talk with him.
Yes. All these happened
because of him.
I will find him now.
Nephew.
I can only help you until this far.
Help me remove my clothes.
Raise your hand.
I can't take it out.
You take it from the back first.
Excuse me.
You get up for a while.
Is your hand okay?
How, how is it?
What do you think?
Do you still need to apply medicine?
Of course.
Then we will continue.
Darling.
Let's go have lunch.
-Do you like it?
-It's really nice.
Public display of affection.
She got a boyfriend so fast.
Have you made a miscalculation?
Were you figuring out how to get back
the items that you've sent out before?
How is it possible?
I'm not this kind of person.
I don't care what kind of
people you are.
I will return those items to you.
I don't like owing favours.
If Brother Wen Bing has any after effects,
I will never forgive you.
You let me down.
No.
Na Na.
I didn't like you before.
But now, let me tell you clearly.
I hate you.
What you did makes me sick.
Miao Miao.
As a leader, you didn't think
about the unity in the team.
You bullied the others every day
and played tricks,
looking for a sense of presence
in front of the freshman.
Can't you just train properly?
I'm really disappointed with you.
I'm really disappointed with you guys.
-Captain, we were wrong.
-We know our fault.
Squat lower.
Let's see if you guys dare do it again.
[You haven't left yet?]
[Hurry, there's no time and
the task is urgent.]
I have something to do later.
You are here now.
You go up yourself.
Where are you going?
It's a secret.
Who promised that he will
take care of me just now?
In the next moment,
you're leaving me alone now.
Don't you have any conscience?
I accompanied you to the infirmary, right?
Besides, the doctor said that you need to rest.
I will disturb your rest
if I'm in the hostel.
-I'm leaving now, goodbye.
-Hold on.