Timing and Subtitles by the Reborn Team @ viki
Should I kill him now?
Three people went in... but two came out.
Kim Soo Hyeok... I knew a day like this would come.
Seong Ha, your brother is going to take revenge and bring back Ma Cheol.
You won't die. Don't die yet.
There are lots to do.
- Cardiac arrest!
- 120 joules!
Shock!
To 160 joules!
200 joules!
200 joules, ready.
Shock!
Hurry, hurry! Hurry!
"I know he's alive.
He will return in his own time.
From time to time, I come across those who have met Gong Ji Cheol.
Gong Ji Cheol's prison guard in charge
kept it a secret that Gong Ji Cheol had a pen in his possession."
Gong Ji Cheol, the devil artist, never regretted the murder.
He was blameless even on the execution grounds.
Since murder is... his work of art.
Let's go see your wife at the hospital together.
She will have a healthy delivery.
Yes, Sir. I hope so.
Excuse me, is this Lawyer Jang Hye Mi's home?
If you tell anyone that I'm alive... you...
and your family will die.
Do you believe that Gong Ji Cheol is alive somewhere?
I'm not sure. I wrote this book, but the Gong Ji Cheol in this book
is only a devil that the world has created.
I mean, this could all be true, but it might just be a work of fiction by someone who fabricates freely.
Since people prefer to settle for lies over uncomfortable truths.
Should I read the next paragraph?
The one who helped Gong Ji Cheol escape was a woman.
She tracked Gong Ji Cheol, who killed her sexually abusive stepfather.
"That woman was Gong Ji Cheol's woman."
"Inside her belly... lived Gong Ji Cheol's child."
There's cash inside the book. You're going to need it.
But must you go?
It would be better to hide for the time being.
You told me to find out Jeong Ha Eun's whereabouts.
Open the last page of the book.
You can just go to the place written there.
It's the address of a hospital in Samcheok.
"And he went off to fulfill his last wish during the time he had remaining.
That last wish was revenge.
The detective who harassed him and the detective's girlfriend who gave legal testimony,
Gong Ji Cheol believed they should pay for their sins."
It's me, Jang Hye Mi.
Still I'm your ex-lover, your words are too harsh.
Oh right... Today, I saw Gong Ji Cheol, whom you ordered executed.
You saw... Gong Ji Cheol?
April 7th, 1979, you remember the day he committed his first murder, don't you?
That day, Gong Ji Cheol fell and hurt his back while doing manual labor.
He was in critical condition for two days at Suncheon Hospital.
From what I remember, the yellow umbrella murder that day
occured near Cheongsin-dong in Seoul.
It's interesting.
How did Gong Ji Cheol, who was lying in a hospital in Suncheon, go all the way to Seoul to kill someone?
Didn't you check his hospital records?
What is it you want to say?
I'm saying make sure you kill him this time, don't make any mistakes.
If it's revealed that he's not the actual culprit, it'll put me in a very awkward position, too.
Like you.
There's a hospital near Samcheon harbor.
That hospital's name is Wonnam Hospital.
Go over there.
I will... forever... live with my mouth shut, Prosecutor.
You can leave.
- Hello?
-   You know,
about your drug smuggling case,
I'll take care of it. But there's something you have to do for me.
There's someone I need to get rid of.
What should I do?
He's a guy who's been executed. He's already...
He's already dead and you're asking me what you should do?
Come here and remove his hood.
We can't see his internal organs, but we need to see his eyes to grade them.
Hey, what are you going to do by living longer?
We need him alive to get the heart, so don't kill him.
I stabbed him in a vital point.
No one saw Gong Ji Cheol's last moment.
If Gong Ji Cheol is alive...
He will return in his own time.
Cardiac arrest!
120 joules.
Shock!
To 160 joules!
200 joules!
200 joules, ready.
Shock!
We got a pulse!
Prepare for surgery.
We have to go into surgery right away. Are you the guardian?
What is the patient's name?
His name... Oh, I called his parents, so they'll be here shortly.
Oh, hold on. Let's just do it, I'll sign.
I'm Cheon Jong Beom's mom.
Oh, it seems like he had cardiac arrest.
The side effects won't affect his brain or make him slow, will they?
He has a bullet in his head right now.
Before the bullet enters his brain, we need to go into surgery and remove it quickly.
Then are you saying his brain has already been ruined?
I can't tell you how much damage there is until we operate.
Without a guarantee that there won't be any brain damage, I won't consent to the surgery.
If you can't save him without surgery, I'll take him elsewhere.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
Me? I saved your son's life.
Since I saved him, I need to keep him alive.
What are you doing? Prepare for surgery.
If this bastard dies, all of you die, too.
The bullet is closer to the brain stem than the CT scan showed,
so we couldn't remove the bullet.
So until the bullet moves away from the brain stem,
we need to observe him.
And brain damage?
The bullet is lodged next to the temporal lobe,
an area called the hippocampus.
We'll know once he wakes up, but he may suffer from memory loss
where he doesn't recognize his friends or family;
or in the worst case, he could suffer from dementia or mental derangement.
What did you say? Mental derangement?
His hippocampus was damaged?
Excuse me! Just a moment.
I...
When Cheon Jong Beom wakes up, can you give this to him?
Please.
Your son is in no condition to go to the U.S.
We don't know if he'll live or die. Didn't you see he was shot in the head?
Not even gangsters do that to family.
Listen carefully, son. The herbal tonic your brother drank, starting tomorrow you drink it.
And you can't eat anything for snacks but dried fruit.
You know I gave birth to you on a plane on purpose, don't you?
You're an American citizen.
You don't need to compete with the losers in this tiny country.
You know that if you don't take after-school classes in the U.S. you become an outcast, don't you?
Let's have you take cello lessons.
Study for the TOEFL so you can make friends in the U.S.
Professor, I think Cheon Jong Beom's back from the U.S.
- What?
- I saw him in Insa-dong.
I don't think so. I've spoken to his parents. He's an exchange student in the U.S.
I'm sure it was him!
But... he seemed very different.
Something was off, like he was sick or something.
Cheon Jong...
Since I love you.
Do you want to be family?
Since I'm an ex-convict, too, I guess we are family.
♫   Your eyes looking at me   ♫
♫   somehow look sad   ♫
♫   When I look at you,   ♫
When you're flustered, you kick the ground with your foot.
♫   seems to have stopped while filled with you   ♫
♫   Even if someday a difficult time comes for us   ♫
You close your mouth and speak with your eyes. This is when you're worried.
♫   Even if the warm wind carries me away   ♫
♫   You are my one and only love   ♫
Are you busy or sick?
Who is this?
Dad, what's wrong?
Your pretty nurse didn't come by today?
I'll be right over. We should have some sweet rice drinks.
Over there.
Who do we have here? It's the Rambo prosecutor who got suspended for a year because of a firearm accident!
Brief me.
We found a hiker this morning.
Name Kim Yi Soo, age 33. In the ground under the tree where the remains were found,
this was discovered.
The forensics department thinks it fell off the body.
It's a heart transplant patient.
We'll have to do a detailed autopsy, but looking at the skull and thyroid cartilage fracture,
it seems that the victim was hit with a blunt object
and strangled with a nylon string.
Please carry out a detailed autopsy.
Yes, Sir.
Oh, let's see the umbrella.
Here.
It's too detailed to call it a copycat crime. He's back, isn't he?
The victim's name is Kim Yi Soo. Why does it say Jeong Sa Bin?
Wait. Not writing the date means he's going to kill Jeong Sa Bin sometime in the future!
Dad, why are you so listless today?
Who are you?
Hello. I'm Han Hee Joo. I've been in charge of his art therapy from a month ago.
You're his daughter?
Yes.
Your dad's yellow...
seems somewhat obsessive.
Other patients feel the active and positive energy from yellow,
but he feels fear and extreme anxiety.
He probably can't help it.
But he'll get better. Don't worry too much.
Let's end the lesson for today.
Let's have a meal together sometime.
I'm so thankful to you for giving him private sessions.
Let's do that.
Aren't you going to check? It could be an urgent text.
I'm at the NFS because of newly discovered remains.
Let's talk.
Excuse me.
You did well, Mister.
Your daughter will be able to live only if you keep obeying me well like you did today.
Got it?
How long are you going to ignore my calls?
You found remains?
Let's speak in person.
Okay. I think I'll be there around 7:00.
Cheon Jong Beom?
You... who are you?
You said Cheon Jong Beom died!
H-He did die, of course. After getting shot in the head.
B-Blood... he lost a lot of blood.
Then who's calling me? He's the only one who knows this number!
Then bring his dead body to me!
Right now!
Are you... still alive?
Estimated height is 167 cm, weight, 49 kg.
The depressed fracture on the right looks like a tiny fracture in a radial shape.
I think this person was hit by something like a baseball bat, but the cause of death wasn't the temporal fracture.
The cause of death was from thyroid cartilage fracture. The hyoid bone was fractured on both sides.
This is strangulation.
Jeong Sa Bin, what happened a year ago—
I don't want to talk about that.
It's a difficult memory for me, too.
But the yellow umbrella that was found with these remains had your name on it.
My name?
You need protection.
I'll call the police if I need protection.
♫   Because you were the first to come close   ♫
The yellow umbrella murder case, if Cheon Jong Beom is the culprit, why is this happening again?
♫   Even if it's a love I can't fulfill   ♫
Are you going to call it a copycat crime again?
♫   I can't give up my heart, I can't   ♫
I... don't dislike you for shooting Cheon Jong Beom.
It's because you insist that he's the culprit when you know it's not true
and because you don't regret shooting a person.
While I was suspended, I tracked Cheon Jong Beom.
He was known to have left to study in the U.S., but there were no records of him
leaving the country.
I have nothing more to say.
I told you once.
That I won't lose my people anymore.
Whether you dislike me or avoid me, it doesn't matter.
As long as you're alive, that's good enough for me.
Like you are now.
♫   even though it hurts, this is not goodbye   ♫
Could you turn up the light?
Yes, Sir.
Sorry, there are so many lights in this room, so—
Hold on. Please turn it off again.
Pardon?
Please turn it off again.
Yes, Sir.