Is this Jong Beom?
Yes, Mother...
Are you unwell?
You're breaking out in a cold sweat.
It's because I ran here.
Of course.
Our Jong Beom, since he was young, never got a cold...
My son was born with such great genes.
In wintertime, I caught a cold just from washing my hair with cold water.
And because of a nasal allergy, I always had a runny nose all the time.
Here.
You just adore him.
I'd be so happy if Jong Woo had even half of his brother's traits.
Honey, look at how our son's face is like a sculpture.
With skin like marble... And he's just like you when it comes to his good sense of style.
You designed all his facial features. I'm not surprised.
After this school semester is done,
go to your uncle's house in the U.S. And whatever happens, don't ever think about returning here.
Just endure over there.
And if he goes to America?
You must think he won't be your son anymore if you can't see him.
That's enough, Dad.
He's family, too.
Those eyes are not the eyes of someone looking at his brother.
Why don't you look at me, Father?
Are you scared of me?
What?
Jong Beom, go upstairs.
Now!
Let's talk.
Your biological father...
had an IQ that's in the top 10% of this country.
And I chose him from the top 1% professional jobs among them.
He could have been an outstanding doctor or a famous CEO,
and he might have been a great judicial officer like your father.
Mother... I've never thought of myself as unfortunate,
not someone who was thrown away,
but I was chosen with sperm donation.
I'm giving thanks to Father right now, too.
He was the one who raised me.
You had never learned art.
But you drew that picture of a landscape filled with snow when you were four years old.
You drew that painting as soon as you woke up one day.
For me,
I'm really happy to have you.
Even though you stay still, light beams out of you.
Since you were young, you've been the best at studying, drawing, exercise, and music.
I never brought you a tutor.
You even chose which medical school to attend.
Even though you liked drawing so much, you still went to medical school. Right?
You know how to become a person to be envied.
In this world, the 1% elite like you
leads the 99% thick-headed majority, Jong Beom.
Don't buy a car yet.
Even though it's my present to you?
I don't need a car,
but allow me to live near my school.
Is this house uncomfortable for you?
Do you want to leave this house?
If I stay in this house,
is it comfortable for you?
Listen to me carefully, Jong Beom.
The one and only reason for you to leave this house
is if I throw you out.
I won't throw you out even if you were to murder someone.
But...
Don't lag behind.
If you make a foolish mistake,
I'll have no choice but to throw you out.
Unbelievable incident! Today a young man's mummy was found in Gangwon Province.
I heard they put the body into formaldehyde!
It was discovered during an on-scene investigation for Byeon Seong Hoon.
I thought that guy only killed women.
But the bastard went around killing at random!
I heard that Byeon Seong Hoon might not have killed him!
That guy died holding a book called "Wuthering Heights!"
Is that by any chance a dying message?!!
Who would die holding a book?!
It's the murderer's marker, you dummy!
It seems your warmth still remains.
After living in the water for 30 years, isn't it great to see the world's light again?
Since we've cut the ropes off, you'll be able to rest comfortably today.
What was your name?
Your age is similar to mine, but you've shown me too much already even though we've just met!
I don't know what happened 30 years ago,
but you were murdered on the happiest day.
That's why you couldn't decay, right?
You bought a wedding ring to put onto your lover's finger,
and on your way to see her,
you died before you met her.
Is that right?
That's what happened...
Lee Bo So, will you trust me?
I'll find your identity for you.
And I'll find your bride.
If your bride is alive,
I'll find that woman and relay that ring to her.
You couldn't give that ring to her,
so you're still in this state.
But if your bride receives your ring,
then...
you can go in peace.
Hyeong Bin!
Did you have a nightmare again?
Get some more sleep.
I really don't like this.
- What?
- The fact that you got out of bed before me.
You're always like that...
Aren't we in a relationship where we will use the same bed together forever?
I don't like your tone either.  Even though we're already engaged, why does it seem you're not mine?
Didn't you like me in the first place because I wasn't yours?
I thought men obsessed with work were also obsessed with their women.
Those who fall deeply into something and go crazy are weak.
Why would you hand over their control keys to someone else?
Sorry, take everything in the refrigerator, they're all your favorite foods.
I bought you a necktie pin.
Why are you always carrying a fountain pen?
Don't let the Donggang investigation get leaked out.
Who was the person that was informed of the investigation? Please make sure she keeps it under wraps, too.
It's too late, Prosecutor. The remains became a skeleton overnight.
I don't know how the reporters found out,
but they're all stationed in front of the National Forensic Research Institute.
I'll be right there.
- Yes?
- Hello, Prosecutor.
- I'm Seong Hoon.
- Seong Hoon?
I guess you forgot my name. I'm Byeon Seong Hoon.
- Can you get the jerk on the phone who let you use the cell phone?
- Why?
I'm the one who wanted to talk to you.
- Really? Then I'll come to you.
- No, thanks.
- No, thanks?
- It's amazing. There's a reporter who believes me.
I heard it all during the on-scene investigation.
That the skeletal remains are 30 years old.
You know, that mummy.
Prosecutor, you're trying to lie by saying I killed that person. Right?
Ridiculous. Do you still think that I'm a serial killer?
Why? Because I was a juvenile delinquent?
I only killed one person!
Because you keep carrying out forced investigations on me,
it's making me give false confessions!
That I killed more than 10 people!
And your phone number...
This person next to me told me.
This person here knew your phone number and address.
I feel like you won't be able to live out your proper lifespan.
I'll see you at the court trial, Prosecutor.
Bye.
Warden Ahn, please check cell phone smuggling routes for your prisoners right away.
Focus on the punks who get medications prescribed from outside, not through the mail.
Whoever you find, send them over to me.
Playing?
Fine, I'll play along with you.
Is it possible for it to become skeletal? Or is there another reason?
Please move aside. Please.
Is it scientifically possible for a corpse to become a skeleton overnight?
Is there any possibility that the NFS made a mistake and switched the remains?
Has there ever been a similar case when remains become a skeleton?
Does that corpse belong to the victim that Byeon Seong Hoon killed?
Byeon Seong Hoon is...
We will give a statement after doing a detailed autopsy.
I think you can come in right now, Prosecutor.
Look!  That corpse isn't cold. That's not a living person,
What do you want for your snack?
Male, height of about 184 centimeters, and weight of about 75 kg.
He had a robust physique.
Looking at the condition of development, the bones' age is that of someone in his late-20s.
Time of death looks to be about 30 to 35 years ago.
Estimated to be between 1984 and 1989.
At the time of discovery, the wound in the chest was found in the shape of an upside-down cross.
And two unskilled cuts in the abdomen.
But the fatal injuries look to be from the wounds to the abdomen.
The knife wound in the chest looks to be symbolic. It could be the killer's signature.
The knife penetrated the ribs and went all the way to the spine.
How can you stab a knife into a person's body like this?
The left side of the face has been shattered with a heavy blunt object.
Everything from the cheekbones to the jaw has been completely shattered.
From that force, the skull has also been shattered.
Listen, Lee Bo So.
What on earth happened 30 years ago?
Tell me what happened.
Did you say hello to Prosecutor Kim Soo Hyeok?
He went into the observation room.
- He did?
- Did he leave?
What on earth happened 30 years ago?
This is really incredible!
Let's go.
The corpse which was found in Papyeong by the Royal Yoon family is called the Naju Donation Mummy.
It is said that the skin was elastic, as though it would rebound if pressed.
Like this, as long as the skeleton and the cartilaginous tissue exist,
we can fully determine the cause of death.
What was the cause of death?
When the remains were discovered, the noblewoman's stomach was protruding.
The CT scan and MRI results showed that the noblewoman's uterus had ruptured,
and the baby's head was at the vaginal opening.
She died while giving birth.
Why did her body not rot?
Lime was strewn outside the tomb.
The lime hardened like cement and prevented the body from decaying.
Then how long did it take for the Papyeong Yoon to become skeletal?
Even before it became skeletal, she became an uninvited guest in the anatomy room of a medical school.
There is no mummy conservation management law in our country yet.
Is it medically possible to explain how a corpse became a skeleton overnight after excavation like the one found in Donggang?
I guess you have a lot of interest in that case.
I'll invite those of you who are interested in the National Forensic Service practice to the autopsy room.
If you intern three times, you'll have an opportunity to be selected as an assistant.
But please be respectful toward the remains.
I reject any simple curiosity.
When can I come to the autopsy room?
Your face is like that of someone being set up to go on a date.
The NFS autopsy process differs from anatomical dissection.
They're mostly people who have died an untimely death. You need appropriate intent and condolence.
Okay. I will have that.
I don't believe in an afterlife, but I do believe in near-death experiences.
I've heard that people who are about to die, they see their whole life pass before their eyes.
And then after that, they see a world that's like a hallucination.
You said you don't believe in an afterlife.
People are organisms, so I'm sure one day there will be a medical explanation.
But... there's an X-file in my life which can't be explained medically either.
X-file?
I never learned to draw, but since the age of four, I've been able to draw pictures worthy of being shown in galleries.
And only certain types of pictures at that.
What kind of pictures are they?
A village where snow falls, a grove of birch trees, snowy landscape.
You're trying to tell me in a roundabout way that you're a genius, right?
When can I come to the autopsy for the Donggang mummy?
Is your dream really to become a forensic scientist?
Yes.
Fine. Then call me in front of the NFS at 2:00 tomorrow.
Sorry for your loss.
Thank you for coming.
Please head over that way.
Jong Beom, you're so brave.
Grandpa loved you so much.
Aren't you sad at all?
He's in shock. Why are you saying that?
Jong Beom, let's go outside.
Let's go.
- That kid isn't even crying.
- I know!
Maybe it's because he's young.
Tell me, Jong Beom, the thoughts you're having right now.
The dog that died in front of our house before,
you didn't say you felt bad for it.
Your first words were that you wanted to try and dissect it.
You want to know more about your grandpa's body, too, don't you?
I'm your mom, so you can tell me the truth.
You're curious about the inside of a body, right?
No.
Wanting to dissect isn't a bad impulse.
It's because you're a genius.
Do you know what a genius is?
You've received the DNA of the top 1%.
My son is different as expected.
Other kids at your age can't do anything but sob at funerals.
I'm curious.
Right. Right. It's fine.
Grandpa was a pastor.
If there is such a thing as a soul,
if he will come back to life,
and if he does, what he will look like.
What?
A book where a mummy bound with red ropes came back to life.
Hello?
I'm on my way. I think I'll be there at NFS in 10 minutes.
Okay, I'm coming out now.
What's going on?
What?
Everyone has their own fated time.
When that time comes, someone will discover me,
and I will discover that someone.
♫   Will a leaf fall from exhaustion   ♫
♫   At the endless chirping of birds through the night?   ♫
♫   It will still bloom even if you're far away?   ♫
Haven't we seen each other somewhere before?
Even if we live in another time, we can communicate with each other.
A copycat has appeared. It's Gong Ji Cheol's marker.
Director Cheon Seok Tae will gnash his teeth over anything to do with Gong Ji Cheol.
The person you hate the most.
I heard a medical school student has been coming by.
- There's a witness.
- So you're digging into my background now?
I got something conclusive.
Do you want to hurt someone who's alive because of a dead person?