At that time, I already
sensed my fate.
In my insignificant and worthless life,
the one who became a ray of light,
Jeong Ha Eun.
For her, whatever I can do,
I will do. Even death.
- What's this?
- I realized that I'm not qualified to be a prosecutor.
Also, I would like to fix all the mistakes I've made due to my beliefs.
And for not following your orders, I will take responsibility as well.
After splattering all the sewage water on me,
you want to take responsibility?
Let me ask since we're on the topic.
Why were you so desperate to put Gong In Woo and Baek Sang Ah behind bars?
You must already know how many people they both killed.
Also, Baek Sang Ah tried to kill someone I love.
And about Gong In Woo.
Think of him as the atonement of a detective who had a part in framing Gong Ji Cheol as a serial murderer.
Which detective?
Never mind.
Hearing the word atonement from your mouth, I guess it really is time for you to resign.
I'll assign you to a position in the provinces, so stay quiet.
Don't make things messier.
Let me ask you something, too.
Why did you try to cover up the Gong In Woo case
even by trying to kill me?
You...
What are you talking about? Kill whom?
Is it because you were in charge of that case,
or is it because there are more secrets that need to be kept?
The resignation,
I'll take that as you've accepted it.
This is my last request as your colleague.
Please make sure you look at the retrial petitions I sent over.
I know best.
Since I was in charge of those cases.
So don't confess anything on the first night.
You won't be forgiven just because you confess.
Isn't confessing a sin courage?
To someone who's hurt, burdening them with the obligation to forgive just makes it harder.
I wouldn't confess if it was me.
Then you're telling me to live with that sin?
No. You can protect them.
While protecting the person beside you, you can just put your life on the line once.
Can we meet right now?
I have something I need to say.
I can't today.
I'm with my dad right now.
Okay. I'll call you tomorrow.
Why did you bring so much?
Try some. Isn't it good?
Yeah, it is.
This is the sushi rice you love so much.
Please chew it well.
It's good. It's really. Flounder is good in the spring.
Our uncles are the best.
Sa Bin, you try some, too.
We're taking good care of her, so don't worry.
Just eat your fill, Big Bro.
Dad, try the strawberries I brought. You like strawberries.
It's good. I have a present for you, too.
- You have it.
- It's your diary.
I won't write diaries anymore. I'm not scared of Gong Ji Cheol anymore.
He's not a serial murderer.
Right. He's not a serial murderer. He was falsely accused.
So now I don't need it anymore.
Then, can I read it?
I come to you with the spring flounder!
Big Bro, drink some water, too.
That's good.
There's something you need to see. I'll be right over, so wait there.
What do I need to see?
It's this. My dad's diary.
Look at this.
It says here...
The person who killed you.
Gong Ji Cheol was killed by the prosecutor in charge.
The person who Gong Ji Cheol contacted after coming back to life in the morgue...
was Attorney Jang Hye Mi.
But she only pretended to help Gong Ji Cheol,
while making another deal behind his back.
There's someone you need to take care of.
Why is she asking me what I'm going to do with a punk that's already dead?
Cheon Seok Tae... he killed Gong Ji Cheol.
Cheon Seok Tae must have ordered you killed.
Jang Hye Mi told me that the person who killed me
was Cheon Seok Tae.
I couldn't trust Jang Hye Mi, so I wasn't sure.
But the only lawyer who I trusted stabbed me in the back,
and in order to cover up her past,
she aided the prosecutor in a murder.
You know now that revenge isn't done by shedding blood
but by making the person carry the weight of their sin
and atone for it while alive.
My father in my prior life destroyed my mind,
and the father I met in the present
killed me physically.
Gong Ji Cheol...
could be watching you from nearby.
Even though the body has disappeared,
the wronged soul returns.
Come in.
What brings you here?
- I have a question to ask.
- What is it that you are coming at this hour?
I met a man by chance recently,
and he trembled when he saw me, saying that Gong Ji Cheol had come back to life.
- What?
- Since you've met him in person,
you must know well.
Do you think that
I look that similar to Gong Ji Cheol, too?
What are you doing?
What did he say?
He said that Prosecutor Cheon Seok Tae told him
if he didn't keep his mouth shut,
he'd hurt him and his daughter.
Who are you?
Did you kill me?
Tell me. Did you kill someone because you didn't want to admit your mistake?
And by destroying even the remains,
climb to your present position?
Gong... Gong Ji Cheol.
Are you really Gong Ji Cheol?
That's right.
Gong Ji Cheol whom you killed.
Get out. Get out! Get out of here right now!
What's the matter?
- What's going on?
- You...
what did you do?
Where the hell did you get this devil's spawn?
Devil's spawn?
His DNA is from among the country's top 1% best and brightest!
The DNA I received,
- belongs to someone you don't even know.
- What do you mean?
Jang Hye Mi... She told me.
She switched the expensive sperm that you bought
with sperm that was donated without any identification.
- What?
- Get out.
Stop talking nonsense
and get out of my sight immediately.
Get out! Both of you!
Cheon Seok Tae,
I know you'll never change.
So I'm going to just watch you.
Since you'll have to remember I'm alive for the rest of your life.
And all the atrocious things you've done in order to succeed,
making sure you never forget until the day you die
is my revenge.
You still have a chance.
Hurry up and run away.
Don't blame your parents later for ruining your life.
Okay...
Someone who has never received love...
A person who was raised with a father's curse
that he would become a murderer.
I feel so sorry for you.
Rest in peace now.
Gong Ji Cheol.
I want to see you.
Me too.
I want to see you, too.
- Can I come see you?
- Of course.
Jong Beom.
Oh, right!
I have something urgent to take care of. I forgot.
I'll call you later.
Okay. I'll be waiting.
Did you...
make my life a joke?
What?
Did you cause someone to be born as my child
who looked like Gong Ji Cheol?
What are you saying? Do you think I'm a god?
I just switched the sperm your wife selected with anonymous sperm.
Who knew he would be born as Gong Ji Cheol?
So... why on earth did you do that to me?
You're asking because you really don't know?
Now that you've accelerated your success,
you can't remember anything of the past?
You said you would love only me until the day you died,
begging me never to stab you in the back.
Have you forgotten all about that?
You said you'd be happy just sharing some noodles together.
And what did you do?
You got introduced to a woman from a reputable family
and never even answered my calls.
After doing that,
you ask me what I've done?
Back then,
instead of Gong Ji Cheol,
I should have killed you.
Hanging on pathetically until the end
is really nauseating.
I'm the one who regrets everything.
If I hadn't told you where Gong Ji Cheol was,
you would still be floundering at the bottom right now.
Why did you tell me?
Are you going to tell me again that it was because of love?
That's right. I loved you.
I did it because I didn't want the man I loved to be ruined.
So...
that's why as soon as you broke up with me, you slept with that disgusting Gong In Woo?
Filthy...
You...
really want to die, don't you?
Hey, put that down.
Watch your manners.
Prosecutor Kim Soo Hyeok, to what do I owe this honor?
You want to arrest me because I hit you more?
How much is the rent for a place like this? I guess you wouldn't know.
- Since Chairman Baek or whoever pays for it.
- Prosecutor Kim Soo Hyeok,
do you still have business left with me?
Starting today, I'm not a prosecutor. I'm here to repay my debt to you.
What kind of ridiculous crap is this about?
Seo Seong Ha. Let's request a new trial.
Even after the defendant's death, you can still appeal.
I know better than anyone that his sentencing was wrong.
Give me a chance to correct his unjust death.
Are you being sincere?
I'll start by apologizing.
I'm sorry... to your little brother,
and to you.
This bastard... is he jerking me around?
I was in charge of the case, so I can't defend.
I'll get you a capable lawyer and submit all the files needed.
You get your guys and gather materials
to prove that Seo Seong Ha loved that teacher.
If the retrial request is accepted, then...
This punk...
The bullet's position has changed.
At the last examination, the bullet was lodged in the left temporal region,
but now it's touching a blood vessel and the brain stem.
So you're saying...
it's gotten much worse, right?
Yes. At this rate,
it's only a matter of time before the bullet enters the blood vessel.
I can't even guarantee one month.
Then I'll have the operation right away.
You said I could survive if I have surgery.
Let's do it right now.
The situation now is different than before.
The chances of a successful surgery are not even 10 percent.
Doctor,
I have to live.
I...
have a reason to live now.
So why did you push back the surgery until so late?
I want to live, please... Please save me.
Right now... I can't recommend surgery.
The Donggang mummy remains that were discovered on March 5, 2020,
according to the racial classification test
and hematological analysis for paternal and maternal lines,
the person who died in 1988 and
was born in 1956 has been confirmed to be Cha Hyeon Bin.
Rest in peace.
- Detective Cha!
- But your presence
enabled us to identify him quickly. What should we do with the remains?
He just... told me to take care of it all.
- Is there a living relative?
- Detective Cha...
No, Detective Cha's distant relative told me to do that.
Okay then. Then let's close the Donggang mummy case as of now.
Mr. Lee Bo So found his name thanks to you.
Good work.
Can I... take it in your place?
Pardon?
If you find Hyeong Bin's body,
please bury him here with me.
Yes, In Do... I'm here waiting now.
What?
"Whether you're alive or dead, I will find you,
and you also must find me."
That's what I prayed for 30 years ago.
The reason I was reborn must have been
to find you again like this.
♫   and whose name I do not know   ♫
♫   My lover who grazes by my past dream   ♫
Thank you for finding me again, Ha Eun.
Thank you for letting me find you,
Hyeong Bin.
♫   You were that familiar image I may have seen somewhere   ♫
♫   The image of love I had forgotten   ♫
♫   My lover I'd seen some years ago   ♫
♫   Dearest, whom I've met some autumns ago   ♫
♫   I'm afraid if I open my eyes I will awake from this dream   ♫
♫   So I am unable to open my eyes as I watch you   ♫
♫   My dream that is broken like a bubble   ♫
♫   Please come tonight  ♫
In the end... the two of them were buried together.
Jeong Ha Eun... lucky you, your wish came true.
♫   My dearest who disappears when I open my eyes   ♫
With this, the 30-year-old story of Jeong Ha Eun and Cha Hyeong Bin
has ended.
Now... should we talk about the us of this lifetime?
♫   Come to my dream tonight, my dearest   ♫
Soo Hyeok, should we...
Wait.
Cha Hyeong Bin's story hasn't ended yet.
I feel like I may have come back into your life
because I wasn't able to tell you this.
You mean, what you wanted to tell me before?
Yes.
It's something I should have told you when I first came to see you.
Even if it's hard, will you hear me out?
Kim Jin Hyeok, you bastard, I'll catch you today no matter what.
I knew at least that the person who caused the accident was a wanted criminal being chased by the police.
But... you're saying... that person was you?
Yes... It was me.
You were only chasing the suspect.
You didn't cause my parents' death, he did.
Right?
Isn't that so, Hyeong Bin?
If I hadn't cornered him like that,
that accident
might not have happened.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Ha Eun.
I fell in love from the first moment I saw you... I was afraid I wouldn't get a chance even to begin that love.
That's why back then, and until now,
I couldn't tell you.
I'm sorry... I'm really sorry, Ha Eun.
I... I'm...
so... confused right now.
Sorry.
Why are you coming now? I thought I would die from missing you.
Jeong Sa Bin!
How long are you going to keep this up?
What's going on?
Shouldn't we just break the door open and go in?
She said she just wants to be alone to think.
A day or two is one thing, but she hasn't eaten or gone to work for a few days now.
This won't do. Get Jan Beom.
- Jan Beom?
- Jan Beom.
- Who's Jan Beom?
- You mean Jong Beom?
He calls him that because he feels bad for him whenever he sees him.
Jong Beom, Sa Bin hasn't come out of her room for three days. Can you come over?
What's going on?
I don't know, but Sa Bin is holed up in her room and won't come out.
Can you call her out?
Senior, is something wrong?
You've been like this after crying like that the other day?
You told me once.
"You can be sad, angry, and feel pain."
I didn't know it then, but now I do.
Since you taught me how to sympathize.
If I was like this, you'd do everything in your power to drag me out.
We're all worried about you, Senior.
Please come on out.
Senior.
♫   Meeting you   ♫
♫   I don't want it to become a sad destiny   ♫
Sa Bin.
What's wrong? Why are you crying?
What in the world happened?
I was going to come out when the tears stopped... but they won't stop.
I was going to come out smiling when I felt less pain.
But it's not getting better.
It... It hurts so much I could die.
♫   Pain rushes into the heart   ♫
♫   Even if I'm left alone again   ♫
Sa Bin!
Sa Bin! No!
There's always a scent of the earth on your back.
The scent of the earth after it's rained for awhile
and the sun has just come out. I know this scent.
But do you know something?
Another man was with Patient Jeong Ha Eun the whole time.
But it's not the first time.
Last time, too, he carried Patient Jeong Ha Eun here.
I remember now.
Your back... the back that always saves me.
It was you... Gong Ji Cheol.