When you ingest grapefruit while taking an immunosuppressant after an organ transplant,
don't you know it can cause abnormal heartbeat, abnormal respiration, and even death?
Because of a chemical compound, furanocoumarin, found in grapefruit, the effects of the immunosuppressant
can become five to ten times stronger and cause serious side effects.
How did you know I had a heart transplant?
Among the medical students, more of us know about it than those who don't.
I understand that your magazine interview was translated into five different languages.
The first person to get a heart transplant from a death-row inmate 18 years ago.
Oh, right. I have a present for you.
Present?
Since you like remains, I thought you might like old stones, too.
An old stone that's flown over from outer space.
It's a necklace made from a meteorite that fell in Argentina 5,000 years ago.
The astronomical observatory verified it, so it shouldn't be fake. Right?
It's a stone but it's glittery.
The way it changes colors should be amazing. Try it on.
They say he only dates girls with surgical scars.
There's something I want to ask, but... what do you think of women with surgical scars?
Surgical scars? If you're a medical student, there's no need to dislike them.
Are you done yet?
It's done.
Are you cold? Why are you shivering?
Obviously. I'm trusting my neck to someone else.
That's not it.
Not my neck, but I'm trusting my body to... That's not it either.
I'm leaving.
♫   Even if I'm carried away by the warm wind   ♫
♫   You are my one and only love   ♫
♫  Don't let go of my hand  ♫
♫  My dear, even if we say nothing  ♫
♫  and I am only looking at you    ♫
What are you doing?
♫  You are the one I miss  ♫
Fifyy centimeters long, assumed to be less than two months old.
We cannot distinguish its gender.
A child that ended up dying around the time it was able to see its mother.
Are you done?
This child didn't even have teeth yet.
The DNA results from the child's remains came back.
It is the child of Im Hwa Yeong from Pureun Studio Apartments.
And Cheon Jong Beom is the suspect in this murder case.
If you'd like, I can send you the case files.
Cheon Jong Beom?
Investigating while designating someone as a suspect
is the most dangerous, isn't it?
Why are you letting your guard down?
You can't give chances to someone like Cheon Jong Beom.
Sometimes an animal can appear like a human being while living among people, hiding its instincts.
Those bastards will rush in and chew people up anytime they're given a chance.
Murders don't happen in broad daylight,
but within those cracks.
The animals that come out of those cracks to hurt my people, I won't allow anymore.
That crack may not seem like much, but my father...
Why do you always get angry when you're with me?
I've never been angry.
I'll ask you again. Why do you always get angry when you worry?
- Worry?
- Right now, you're worried about me.
Let's stop.
You've separated the bones from flesh well, right?
You're the best in your field, Uncle.
What about the bones? Did you throw them away properly?
Cheon Jong Beom?
I'll be there soon. Okay.
I overheard your conversation unwittingly. Can I get in on those bones and flesh that were separated, too?
What brings you here?
My home is near here.
Really? Where is it?
This is your home?
No. This building's rooftop room.
Lady Sa Bin!
♪ Whenever you're lonely, come see me ♪
♪ Whenever you're down, come see me ♪
♪ Oh, when you're lonely, the best thing is Body Check Live ♪
♪ Come see me! ♪
So you're Sa Bin's student?
Did you say this kid's name is Jong Beom?
♫ When the time can be stopped ♫
Do you like freshwater fish or salmon?
Hey, hey. Put that knife down right now!
I raised our Sa Bin with this knife!
If you're holding a knife looking the way you do, who would ever think you filet fish?
You look like a defector or an ex-convict who is out to kill his cheating wife.
A defector? An ex-convict?
A defector... An ex-convict...
♫   Will I turn for the sake of your happiness   ♫
♫   without any regrets   ♫
I didn't kill anyone, only attempted murder.
♫   Even the blazing sun   ♫
You're a pseudo-ex-convict who lived off this girl. How dare you run your mouth? You want to die?
I'll just rearrange your ribs in a revolutionary way today.
A man who hates his brother... Ouch!
Will commit murder!
Sa Bin, listen. Between someone who attempts murder
and a bastard who commits fraud by selling out his friend, who's worse?
- Honestly?
- Honestly.
I think they're one and the same.
Both should be ripped up and quartered.
But... personally,  the one who plays around with people's emotions is a little more unlikeable.
Right?! Right?
You... Hah!
Jong Beom, what do you think?
Tell us! Who's worse?
I'm curious about something.
Tell me. Tell me.
Was it that you gave up the murder or that you failed?
I'm sure you planned out the murder. Didn't you feel dejected after giving up?
Amen! Well...
those who have ears to hear will hear.
Our Jong Beom, are you a forensic psychologist?
With your looks and how you talk, you're just my type!
Those who have ears to hear, let them hear!
- This bastard, acting like he knows when he knows nothing!
- Go ahead and eat.
That's right.
Hyung, aren't you going to ask me in? I came because I miss you.
Isn't it time to stop all this?
How can you live in a place like this?
Your blood really must be different from mine.
I don't think I could live here for even a day.
If Father finds out that you came here, he'll be really angry.
At me? It'd probably be at you.
You should hang things like these in your room. Don't you think so?
What? Did you leave them behind because you're coming back?
Drink it, Brother.
If you don't drink the juice,
Mom will be so disappointed in you.
His brother?
If I don't drink it, you'll be disappointed, not Mom.
Why don't you drink it? You should taste what you made at least once.
What? You drank it knowing?
We can never be family since you're this spiteful.
I feel sorry for you. Did you want to keep living in our house
while drinking detergent?
I don't need to drink it anymore. Take it all back.
I see. So you're saying we're not family anymore.
Who are you?
Hello. I'm his brother.
Brother, I'm leaving.
By the way,
Mom said to make sure you attend the fundraiser this weekend.
My uncle told me to give you this.
He said it'll be cold up here because they're fixing the boiler.
Don't touch it.
I said, don't touch it.
Are you stupid?
If you knew someone was messing with your juice, you shouldn't have drunk it.
If that won't do, you should have thrown it in that person's face.
When your brother was doing something like this to you,
you should have at least alerted your family! Why would you drink this?!
I'm warning you.
Don't get any closer.
Why did you do that?
Tell me. Why did you drink it knowing there was detergent in it?
- Because I had to stay there.
- There?
That was the only place I could go.
Leave now.
Why?
Because you're a juvenile delinquent? Because you're a psychopath?
If that why your family treats you this way?
Even if you can't feel my anger, sadness, and suffering,
you can analyze and predict them.
It's called cold empathy.
I can feel your anger, sadness, and suffering.
It's what you call hot empathy.
So there's no one in this world who isn't able to empathize with others.
Please leave.
I'm going to go find her even if it kills me.
You don't look well. Is something wrong?
I have some things on my mind.
Soo Hyeok, your mate in this lifetime is Sang Ah. She's your soulmate.
You have to make sure you protect her no matter what happens to her.
Did you two plan this?
I heard that a relationship so full of affection that it hurt in your past life comes back only to graze past you in the present.
But a bad relationship in your former life will come back to you in order to untie that knot.
So no matter what, you have to take care of each other and love each other.
Soo Hyeok, you heard Mom, right?
You have to be nice to me.
I guess you're okay with the bad relationship in our past life.
I started making these because a regular customer who's an archaeology professor requested them.
It's perfect as a side project.
If this was a ring, I'd engrave today's date on it.
Right, Mom?
Too bad.
The ring that he couldn't give up until the moment of his death, I'll make sure to put it on for him.
♫   In my dream... In my dream, I saw yesterday   ♫
Where are you right now?
I'm at the autopsy room, of course. Why?
I'll be right over.
♫   One I've never seen and whose name I do not know   ♫
Hello, Mister. What is it?
Why are you beating so fast again?
♫   My lover who grazes by my past dream   ♫
♫   I think thoroughly tonight   ♫
♫   You were that familiar image I may have seen somewhere   ♫
♫   The image of love I had forgotten   ♫
It's the weekend. You're interrupting my leisure time.
I'll leave once I give you this.
This is...
We discovered six bodies related to Byeon Seong Hoon's case, and there will soon be a hearing.
Give the ring back to the rightful owner.
I'll leave now.
Wait. Since you're here, let's go together.
You have to go return the ring with me.
Elder.
This stamp, is it used at this store?
Not now, but it was used a long time ago.
- Here.
- I see.
Then, how long have you been running this bookstore?
About 30 years?
The owner passed away, and after his daughter died,
- I took it over.
- Oh.
His daughter?
Then you must know the daughter well.
She's been dead for many years.
I even went to her funeral.
Thirty years ago.
- Oh, she died?
- Yeah.
I knew this would happen. Did you think you'd be able to meet her if you blindly came?
She looks... so much like her...
But it feels like time has stopped here.
It could feel that way.
For 30 years, no new books have come in.
I want to leave it as is until I die.
This book went out of print! Wow.
Look!  There are dissertation papers here, too. Amazing.
Prosecutor, pick out a book for yourself, too.
It's my treat today.
Weren't we here to find the owner of the ring?
I'll take this one.
Oh, it's raining.
You're going to get the book wet.
Do you like it when it rains?
Everything that comes down from the sky is beautiful.
It's beautiful, but all the cherry blossoms will be gone by tomorrow.
You know the big cherry blossom tree in front of the NFS?
I really wanted to take a picture in front of it this spring.
That tree fades away last.
- Pardon?
-  I said, that tree is the last one to fade away.
Do you like cherry blossoms?
I'll bring the car, so wait here.
I... got a heart transplant from an ex-convict.
I think his heart starts beating fast whenever I see you because he's scared of you.
But sometimes, I get confused about whether it's his heart or mine that's beating fast.
Can I try holding your hand once?
I just want to know whether it's my heart or his that's beating fast.
To be honest, my heart has been beating fast since the first time I met you.
What?
♫   I won't leave   ♫
♫   Even if I'm carried away by the warm wind   ♫
Why? Was it not enough?
If it isn't, can I take it further?
♫   My dear   ♫
♫   Even if I don't say anything, even if I'm just looking   ♫
♫   You're the one I want to see   ♫
You're a medical university professor. Don't you have experimental ethics?
I was a little... a little...
It is a little strange. I don't have an arrhythmia. Why does it beat fast whenever I see you?
My heart has never beaten fast because of a man.
I acknowledge that I have a strong experimental spirit,
but...
It was the first day I felt someone else's pain.
And...
Crazy...
This woman who has accepted my darkness,
I've developed feelings for her.
♫   When did you go and not come back   ♫
♫   You who left a single leaf and went away   ♫
♫   Soaking tears left on top of the branch   ♫
♫   The rising sound of the wind is left behind   ♫
♫   On top of the bare branch   ♫
I see it.
It seems like you notice other people's wounds but not your own.
I'm happy that I didn't make you regret it.
I like you, so don't ever get hurt.
Love? When someone doesn't return your love, it becomes an obsession.
In the end, Cain became mankind's first killer.
No. Prosecutor!
♫   The single leaf   ♫