♫  Sleigh bells ring, are ya listening?  ♫
♫  In the lane, snow is glistening  ♫
Is there such a thing as being fated to meet?
♫  Walking in a winter wonderland  ♫
♫  Gone away is the bluebird  ♫
Book?
♫  To sing a love song, while we stroll along  ♫
♫  Walking in a winter wonderland  ♫
Excuse me. The book...
It seems you're really interested in corpses.
This is the book that I ordered.
It's a limited edition with the author's real autograph.
I ordered this book for him to come and sign at 3:00 today.
It's 3:15.
Oh, please. This is a book I really need.
Timing and Subtitles by the Reborn Team @ viki
Well, do you want to buy mine?
You scribbled in it, just a minute ago.
I'll give it to you used.
Used?
If you don't want it, then give it up.
But... it looks like you have a habit of pressing down on that fountain pen.
The nib will wear out really quickly.
I think it's a better habit than spilling coffee on books.
I thought you weren't coming... I'm sorry.
Why would someone who's emigrating want that book?
Why do you think that person's departure date is exactly tomorrow morning?
Isn't it fate that this person wouldn't get this book?
I guess it's the sad fate of that person who values the author's own autograph more than a million dollars!
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, yes.
♫  Even though that person looks at me  ♫
♫  I do not know that person  ♫
♫  Though my beating heart is in pain  ♫
♫  Now I don't know them anymore  ♫
They say that fated lovers will never be apart.
Though we don't know when or where,
we will meet again,
even in the next life and again in the life after.
How I envy this. Jeong Ha Eun, who dreams of a fated love,
are you listening?
I will play the song you've requested. Lee Moon Sae's "If Love Passes."
♫  When I just pass by the face   ♫
♫  I wanted to see so much  ♫
♫  Your dejected look   ♫
♫  in it   ♫
♫  I no longer regret   ♫
Miss, you shouldn't carry that around. That yellow umbrella.
Don't you know there's a crazy bastard who only kills women with yellow umbrellas?
Haven't you heard?
Wo... men?
(T/N: North Korean word)
I'm not a spy.
I defected to South Korea.
There are so many bastards that kill women in South Korea!
Those kinds of bastards should all just be buried somewhere!
Don't you think so?
They'll all get caught. My boyfriend is a detective.
- Oh my goodness.
- What's going on!
Those eyes have seen hell.
Wow, this is the first time this has ever happened.
Look! Look here, Detective Cha.
Here. The chest. From this side, twice.
Then double. From here, once like this!
And then from the other side, once like this!
And from here, he just went crazy.
Hey, move!
The body is damaged but the face is clean.
What could this be, Detective Cha?
It's two guys.
One guy killed her.
One guy buried her.
Oh!
We found a clue!
The culprit has long hair!
There aren't many men in Korea with long hair.
Nine.
Nine?
He killed nine people and then did nothing for two years.
Why would he start killing again?
In Do, do you think there is such a thing as murder without a motive?
How could someone kill another person without a motive?
Hey! Get out of here! Hey!
- Hey! Hey! You can't!
- Ah, it's strange!
Come here! Hey!
Are you all right?
The one with a bad heart is your girlfriend. Why does this happen to you every so often?
With a heart of stone.
Let go. Let go! No!
Between people who love each other, could their hearts be connected?
"In the same moment I feel pain in my heart,
that person also feels pain.
It isn't my heart that hurts,
it's like a knife
is being stabbed in my heart."
Here. Right here.
♫  Was it only just a misunderstanding?  ♫
♫  With a bright smile you look at me   ♫
♫  You made me into a fool   ♫
♫  The day you left my side  ♫
You scared me!
I thought my heart was going to fall out of my chest.
Sorry, are you okay?
Are you okay? Try breathing. Can you breathe? Hurry up and take a breath in! Okay.
And let it out. Hurry!
This won't do. Let's go to the hospital. You're turning blue.
Are you a Smurf? Your face is bluer right now.
Do you always have to say that your heart is falling out of your chest?
A patient with a heart disease is saying her heart is falling out of her chest. It's sincere!
You can't use this.
Throw it away. Let's go.
Mine's not just any yellow umbrella. It's a baby dragon umbrella.
“If all else perished and he remained, I should still continue to be.
Whatever our souls are made of—"
"His and mine are the same.”
Emily Bronte.
Wuthering Heights. Page 123.
Hey! Really—
Should we throw away this ladder, too?
Hey-Hey!
It's page 73. I read it to you so often and you still forget.
Really?
Whatever the case, open it. To page 123.
Why page 123?
What is this? You already found 73 so easily, too.
Will you be my wife, Jeong Ha Eun?
I told you that customers won't buy it when you scribble in books.
I'm not sure if that's something a used bookstore owner should say.
You said that the scribbles in books are a part of their history. And that isn't a scribble. It's a proposal.
I waited a month for your answer.
Okay. Then I'll answer you through a scribble.
Look for my answer when I'm not here.
You're going to have to write a lot. I wrote them all down.
Every book in your bookstore.
What?
Then... I'll answer now.
I reject your proposal.
What?
I don't believe in love.
"Love Story" came out with a sequel. In the sequel, he loved a different girl...
Well, one more year.
If my heart beats for one more year, we can get married.
You've been rejecting me for four years now. This time it won't work.
Hey, Cha Hyeong Bin.
Don't say it. I know your next line.
We're... not fated to be a married couple.
Then, what are we?
Lovers.
A lover that you miss even if you're looking at them.
A relationship where we can always feel each other. A relationship where we will be together even in death.
That's you and me.
Then I don't want to be lovers.
I'm going to be lovers with you forever.
You can get married to a different girl.
I don't want to embrace your body but your soul.
I don't.
I've never looked at another girl like this before.
I want to touch your face and hold you as I fall asleep.
♫  Still you are   ♫
I want to see you when you fall asleep, when you open your eyes, when you feel pain,
when you cry, in my arms.
What if I die in your arms? Is that okay with you?
♫  feel so deeply   ♫
I'm happy even just looking at you like this.
♫  that is love   ♫
When you die, I'll be happy because I'm your husband;
and when you die,
I'll think about that moment for the rest of my life.
Please stop.
I really hate this kind of melodrama.
I told you I don't like these because it feels stuffy.
I could start a business with all the gloves you've bought me.
It's because I can't walk you home. I got an emergency call.
Why? Because of that yellow umbrella guy?
That bastard. He really evades Detective Cha Hyeong Bin so well.
He's going to die if he gets caught.
You know you can't run, right?
Stick to the wide roads. Don't go anywhere without street lamps.
I know your short cut very well.
You'll get in trouble. When you get home, check all the locks—
Oh my— Your nagging has started. I have to run.
When you were screaming earlier, you were imitating that girl's scream. Weren't you?
Yeah.
You heard that dead girl's scream, yesterday.
You saw the guy who left the yellow umbrella. That guy's face! Right?
This woman has the mind of a seven-year-old.
Come here, little kid.
Let's do something fun with this man.
This man who looks sharp as a razor blade.
If you really get to know him, he's really not such a bad man.
- It's okay, it's okay.
- You're the one who looks old.
Hey. Who would think you're 23?
I told you this face has passed down generation after generation in my family.
This kind of face doesn't age.
Look at me in 30 years. My face will be exactly the same.
Come here, come here.
Come here. Let's sit here.
What you saw yesterday on the mountain... can you draw it?
Let's just go eat.
It's fine. You should eat before you go.
Let's order fried rice for this woman. I want jjamppong  (spicy seafood soup) .
I said it's fine.
Timing and Subtitles by the Reborn Team @ viki.com
Wait!  What is that young man doing over there?
Why are you...
leaving umbrellas at my house?
I'm hurt. I don't think I can keep painting.
Was that it?
Because you can't paint anymore... is that why you started again?
You're suffering a lot because of me.
Don't worry. This time, I'll stop for a while.
It's all thanks to you.
Thanks to me?
Because you put socks on those white feet,
it seemed like... at her point of death,
that filthy wench looked like the Virgin Mary.
What?
This time, this wench...
She looks like your mom who abandoned you.
The wench before that... she looked just like your stepmother who did that to your eyes.
Why are you dragging me into this?
You killed them because you wanted to kill them.
Should we have dinner together, son?
You will certainly commit murder.
Once you start, you can't stop.
How...
How could you do this to me...
Don't fight it, just accept it.
Just bring the demon onto your side.
Draw inspiration from the demon and paint. Like me.
You got my blood but not my talent.
You have to murder in order to find freedom. I was the same way.
Do you think I enjoy murder? I do it because I can't help it.
But once you start,
you'll never be able to stop.
This time the girl I killed,
she was a wench that kept her sick father locked up and starved.
If that wench had lived, that wench's father would have died.
Didn't I save an innocent person by killing that wench?
I'm different from you.
You've never loved a woman before.
Love. You love a woman?
When other kids cut colored papers with scissors, you were stabbed in the eye with these by a woman.
But you think you love a woman?
Even if you don't kill her, she's going to die soon.
If you want, I can send her off comfortably.
Love.