[Final Episode]
I'll tell Shun
that I want to break up with him.
Why do you go to such a great extent?
You don't want to break up.
You know...
my relationship with my mom has never been great.
I felt unhappy at home.
I felt suffocated all the time.
So, maybe it's my ego...
that I don't want Shun to suffer.
I don't want him to go through
the same family issues as I did.
You're in pain too, aren't you?
Huh?
Previously...
You mentioned this.
That you stop feeling pain
once you get used to it.
I can't begin to understand
how much you must've suffered...
before arriving at this opinion.
You had a sibling to support you,
yet you couldn't be together.
Because if you had...
your life would've been less painful.
Why?
Why are you crying over us?
Because the reason you got separated...
wasn't your fault.
If things had gone the other way...
you could have relied on each other...
and lived together.
When I was having a hard time,
I often thought about how great it would be
to have a sibling to talk to at times.
So, I want to help you if you're in trouble.
Because we're family.
I often think that...
we can't change the past,
but time is all connected.
Right now,
it's just a continuation of that past.
So...
if you feel lonely...
like me...
it's in your hands to change it.
Do you think I can do it?
Of course, you can.
Honestly, I can't win against you.
Huh?
I've grown weary
of hating the people around me.
Hello?
Thank you.
I'm really happy to get the opportunity
to work with you all.
After coming here,
I realized that I love this job more than ever.
Aww, now you're saying that!
Don't leave us!
Thank you for everything.
Take care of yourself when you get back.
Sure.
President, could you check these documents?
How do I look today?
What do you mean?
You look as handsome as always.
Good.
Maika!
Shun.
Welcome back.
Glad to be back.
I got a message from Kato.
He's going to back out of my mother's plan.
That's great.
All because you changed his mind.
No. I did nothing.
As long as you're here,
I feel like I can overcome anything.
Will you stay by my side
for the rest of our lives?
Of course.
Good morning.
Do you have time this weekend?
I want to properly introduce you to my parents.
Okay.
Where's Dad?
He's not coming.
What?
I told him he didn't need to come.
Why did you decide on your own?
It's ridiculous to waste
his valuable time on this.
You should also act like a president.
If you think about what should be
prioritized for the company, you'll understand.
Marriage isn't about you alone.
You can go to any extent
for the company, right?
You asked Yugo to get close to Maika, right?
Oh, so you know it.
Did she tell you?
No, I investigated it myself.
You investigated it, huh?
It's because he was acting all sketchy.
He's been useless anyway.
Excuse me.
How can you say something like that?
Can't you see how much Kato was suffering
when he was trying to help with your plan?
Outsiders should not interfere.
Shun and Yugo are my children.
They should listen to me.
No matter what you do to stop us,
I'm going to spend my life with Maika.
I only love Maika.
I can't allow that.
I will make Shun happy.
Don't talk nonsense.
I'm telling you, you can't be a partner for Shun!
Mom! Are you okay?
I'm sorry for being late.
Dad.
What are you doing here?
I felt something would happen,
so I came to check myself.
Maika, I'm sorry for my wife's behavior.
Are you hurt?
No.
Please don't be intimidated by Mitsuko.
You are a good girl, and you are perfect for Shun.
Are you serious?
The future of the company is at stake.
After marrying me,
you've lost sight of something important.
- What?
- The fact is that you're worried
about your pride, not the company's future.
Before interfering in company matters,
try to be a mother to your sons for once.
I want to introduce
someone important to both of you.
Maika Hattori is the one I love.
How can you think of marriage
based on just a fleeting emotion?
A girl from such a non-privileged family is
not suitable to be a company president's wife!
Enough!
How much more will you hurt your sons?
You're the one who needs to leave!
Until you rethink and properly apologize to Shun,
don't show me your face.
Maika, you'll catch a cold like that.
Shun.
I'll prepare some clothes for you.
Wait a minute.
Do you know how much I've done for you?
You should thank me at least!
No matter how hard it was, I bit the bullet.
I have done everything for you.
All of you should care about my happiness!
Come in.
Excuse me.
Shun.
Any word from your mother?
No.
She hasn't returned home yet.
It's been a week.
President, we have found Ms. Mitsuko.
She's staying in one of our hotels.
I see, thank you.
I think she doesn't have anywhere else to go.
You should go and bring her home.
I always wanted to get revenge on her.
Shun.
No matter how badly she treated you,
you couldn't abandon her.
That's because she is truly irreplaceable to you.
What do you want?
We just want to talk to you.
We can't move forward like this.
See, I got Castella. You used to love it, right?
Shall we all have some?
Thank you.
Huh?
Thanks for coming here today.
If it were just me,
I think it would have ended in an argument.
I feel the same way.
Hattori told me that time is connected.
I was reminded of something obvious.
It's all up to me
to change the equation with my family.
I see.
It feels great that the three of us could meet.
Thank you.
Yeah.
I'm back.
Hi.
The three of us talked about various things
at leisure.
That's great.
Finally, we can plan our wedding.
About that...
Oh? Is it just you?
Where's the president?
Shun isn't here.
He said he'd come back here.
I assumed you'd come with him,
and announce your engagement.
About that...
I think we'll live without
the formality of marriage for a while.
- What?
- Of course, I'll be with Shun forever.
What are you saying?
What if you miss the timing
and delay your marriage?
A woman only truly understands happiness
after she's married.
For so long,
I've been bound by those words of yours.
But now I've realized.
Life doesn't just revolve around marriage.
What do you mean?
We might choose
to get married eventually.
But...
we will come to that decision on our own.
What nonsense.
What about the president's attitude?
Mom, I didn't choose the president.
I chose a person named Shun Satori.
Do you remember?
I was close with a boy during my student days.
His name was Kagaya.
Huh?
You threw away Kagaya's book,
and said such hurtful things about him
that I don't even want to repeat.
He was my first love.
Why bring up something unrelated now?
Satori Shun.
He is Kagaya.
What?
I'm glad to reunite with Shun.
I truly feel happy about it.
That's all I wanted to convey.
If you listen to my words, you can be happy.
Mom.
I am very happy right now.
Miss, it's going to get dark soon.
Shun, what are you doing here?
I got a call from your mother.
Please, take care of Maika.
Of course.
She's sensitive just like me, so, I'm worried.
My mom...
Did she say I resemble her?
Yes.
What? We don't resemble each other at all.
Maybe it's the habit of deeply caring
about people important to you, no matter what.
Your mother got married early and she was happy.
So, she probably wanted you to live the same way.
But she realized that it is a burden for you.
That's why she called me,
and asked me to take care of you.
It's painful when people you care about
don't understand you.
But if you try to understand each other,
the gap might become smaller.
That's true.
Shun.
Yes?
Thank you for being so understanding.
I really appreciate it.
Marriage isn't something to rush into.
Let's take our time to prepare it.
After all, we have plenty of time.
That's right.
It's been 12 years since that day.
I ended up relying on you again.
Even 12 years from now,
I'm going to be there for you.
Thank you.
Me too.
I want to be there for you forever.
Yeah.
Shun.
Yes?
I love you more than before.
Me too.